Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[♪♪♪]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
♪ It's Christmas again
♪ Finally
How are you doing today,
Maggie?
Looking pretty good.
Let me see those paws.
Why so grumpy?
It was just one little needle.
[cat meows]
♪ Reindeer and lollipops
♪ Sleigh bells and snow
♪ Life is so magical
♪ We give and we grow
Don't wiggle that nose at me,
Floppy.
You know these ears are dirty.
♪ It's a time to share
my happiness ♪
♪ It's a love I feel
♪ And hold so dear
♪ When you are near
All right, Puggles.
I'm going
to take your bandage off.
[Puggles coughs]
Is it going to hurt?
No, of course not.
You might be stiff
for a little while,
but that's normal.
How is it
when you talk to them
it seems like
they're really listening?
I... I'm not talking to them.
I mean,
am talking to them,
but it's just
to make them feel better.
How was your day?
Productive.
So...
Did you come up
with any new toys?
Well, I'm
working on it.
But what I did
come up with
is a surprise for you.
A surprise?
Before Christmas?
Don't worry,
there's no obstacles.
Okay.
It's all good.
Oh, my gosh,
what are you doing?
Oh, nothing.
We're just out walking.
-No peeking.
-Okay.
-One more step.
Here you go.
All right. Still not looking?
-No.
-No? I've got a spot.
-All right.
-All right. Yeah? Yeah, yeah?
All right.
And... look.
[gasps]
What do you think?
I love it.
[electricity zapping]
Oh! Classic.
Probably a loose bulb
just needs to be tightened.
So, listen,
I was, you know, thinking
now that your apartment
is all decked out
for the holidays,
maybe you'd want to invite
your parents over for Christmas?
You know, we've been together
for a while now,
and I'd just really
love to meet them.
Oh... Um...
[electricity zapping]
Please hold.
I have an extra
set of lights.
[both chuckle]
You know, the holidays
are a really busy time
for my parents,
and Christmas is only
a couple of weeks
away.
So, um...
But maybe next year,
you know?
Got it!
Whoa.
I guess it fixed itself.
Yeah.
You were right...
Just a loose bulb.
You understand
about my parents, right?
Um...
I do...
Look, there's
something really special
that I want to do
this Christmas,
something that
I want to ask you.
But before I do that,
I need to ask
your parents,
your father, in particular.
Oh.
Oh! Oh, oh!
Oh, oh! [coughs]
Are you... Are you saying
what I think you're saying?
Look, Holly.
Holly, I love you.
Okay? I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
I just want
to do it right.
I want to ask your dad
if it's okay.
Oh, wow.
Oh, boy, um...
Hey...
I've got a great idea.
You were saying your parents
are always too busy,
they can't come here.
Why don't we go there?
Oh, no, Connor,
they live way, way up north.
But you know
what we can do?
We can screentime them.
Huh? Wouldn't that
be great?
No, I kind of want
to do it in person.
You know, I mean,
besides,
if we're really ready
to take this next step,
don't you think it's time
I met your parents?
[ringing]
Hello-ho-ho.
How can I help you?
Hey, Uncle Mario.
It's Holly.
[stammers excitedly]
How are you doing, Jingles?
I'm great.
I'm coming home for Christmas...
with my boyfriend, Connor.
Hey, Uncle Mario.
It's Connor.
Well, well, well,
won't your parents be tickled!
I'd get them on the line,
but they're off
making sure
that the sleigh's flying right.
Right, because
it's so fast,
it's like
it's practically flying.
Um, speaking of which,
can you get Mom and Dad
prepared for our arrival
and make sure that everything
is running... smoothly?
[Mario]:
You got it, Chestnut.
I'll pick you up
at the airport.
Oh, I've got to go...
It's time for the elves'
cocoa break.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Uncle Mario,
he's such a kidder.
Yeah.
Morning, boys and girls.
[electronic games beeping]
Can you guess
what I have in here?
Any takers? No?
All right, this is Fido,
all right?
And he wants to be
your best friend.
[electronic games beeping]
Yes.
Does it make any sound effects?
No, but you can absolutely
make your own sound effects.
Does it come with an app?
Uh, no,
but the great thing about Fido
is that doesn't need
to be synced up.
Put those back on...
Uh, he's compatible
just the way that he is.
Does anybody
want to play with him?
Anybody?
You want to... give it a try?
Okay! [laughs]
Well, that's all we're going
to need from you today,
boys and girls.
Now, there is a docking bay
right over there
where you can plug in
your electronics,
and there's
some snacks
over there
in the staff room.
Go get 'em!
[chuckles]
Little rascals.
That toy was lame.
Stuart, Wesley, Kelly!
Well,
thanks to Connor here,
you can kiss your little
Christmas party goodbye
because you're all
going to be too busy
coming up
with a better idea
than a wooden dog
with wheels.
I... I got something.
Hit me.
Um, what about
a hunky Santa doll?
You know,
for the teen market.
Um, I think
that was my idea.
Since when?
Yesterday,
by the water coolers?
Oh, I thought you were
talking about your date.
Yeah, I was.
A hunky Santa doll.
Yeah.
You might have something there.
Hmm? Huh?
Huh?
That's more
like it.
So get busy!
[♪♪♪]
So we'll have two stopovers
before we fly into Nunavut,
and then after that,
Uncle Mario is going
to pick us up
and drive us
the rest of the way up north.
It's a bit of a trek,
but we should make
good time in Dad's car.
Connor? Your lunch?
Right, yeah. Yeah, thank you.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah,
everything's fine.
Okay.
Ahem.
Way to go, Connor.
Yeah,
thanks a lot.
The Christmas party
was my only chance
with Deb
from accounting.
Yeah, in your dreams, Wesley.
Dreams can
become reality.
What's going on?
Ah, Wegman canceled
the Christmas party
thanks to me
and my toy.
Oh, Connor.
Yeah, I don't know what it is,
but I just can't
get the kids interested
these days.
And all Wegman wants
is, like, some
flash-pan toy
like
a hulky Christmas Santa doll,
and that's popular,
you know, in the moment,
but it doesn't stand
the test of time,
not like the toys
that I make.
Well,
maybe you'll get inspired
at my parents' place.
[♪♪♪]
That him?
Yeah! I think
that's him.
-Can you grab the...
-Okay.
Uncle Mario!
Chestnut!
How ya doin'?
I couldn't be better.
Well, you still look
pretty as a snowflake.
Although, you know,
you could put a little sugar
on your bones.
Aw...
Well, Mario,
this is my boyfriend, Connor.
Nice to meet you, Mario.
Yeah, well,
he's, uh, skinny, too.
[laughs]
Oh, well,
no worries...
We got lots of goodies at home
to fatten you both up
for Christmas.
Well, away we go!
[♪♪♪]
Geez, you weren't kidding, eh,
when you said your parents
live up north.
[chuckles awkwardly]
So, uh,
how long
till we get there?
Oh, it, uh...
shouldn't be
that much longer.
Uh, here, try some of my
special hot cocoa.
Oh, yes, please.
Yeah,
it's a home brew.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
It's very hot.
Oh, thank you.
Mm, smells delicious.
Bottoms up.
Wow.
Mario,
seriously.
That's, like, some good hock.
All right, Jingles.
Are you ready to go home?
Ready.
Wow, Mario,
you've sure souped up this ride.
You have no idea.
[rocket-like acceleration]
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoa.
[dog barks]
Snowball! Oh, Snowball!
Whoa, whoa!
I'm sorry,
we don't get a lot
of visitors up here,
so he gets
a bit excited.
Nick. You must be Connor.
Yeah. Nice to meet you,
Mr. Klaus.
Actually, it's "Claus".
Oh. I could have sworn
it was "Klaus".
Oh, Klaus, Claus,
potato, patato...
same name, really.
Honey, you must be
so hungry
from that nap.
Yeah, wow. Talk about
hitting the snooze button.
Don't make the poor guy
just freeze out here.
I am the mother.
Come in, come in.
-Come on.
-All right.
There we go. Come on.
Get in there,
get the chill off your bones.
[chuckling]
Welcome, welcome.
Watch your step here.
Come on in.
Make yourself
comfortable.
Wow, this place is amazing.
Oh, this is all
my wife's doing.
Wow.
You must have the best
decorations in town.
Well, I should hope so.
[chuckles]
Would you care
for a tour?
Are you sure, Dad?
There's not much to see,
is there?
Well, don't worry,
I'll give Connor the short tour.
Come on, come on.
Yeah, yeah, do that one,
because dinner's almost ready.
Oh, can't keep
the ladies waiting.
Come on, come on.
Lordie, that boy's gonna
need some fattening up.
Let's go make the beds.
I have to admit
I was a little
surprised to hear
that you were
bringing Connor up with you.
Uh, is this serious?
Well, yes, it is.
Um...
I think he's
planning to propose.
Propose?
Oh, Holly...
Well, are you sure?
I mean, Connor's lovely
and everything,
but, um... Jack?
What about Jack?
Well, you always seemed
like such a good fit.
Plus he knows your family
and the business,
not to mention
he's already prepared.
Are you sure
that Connor's the one?
Oh, yes, Mom.
He's everything that
I could have wished for.
He's kind, and he's generous,
and he adores kids.
He even makes toys
for a living.
I've never met anybody
who loves Christmas
more than he does...
besides us.
Well... I guess
he'll do fine.
[Nick]:
Hey, come on, Connor,
I'll show you the barn.
Oh... [stammers]
Hey...
[♪♪♪]
[animal snorting]
What do you keep
in here?
Horses?
Something even better.
What are those?
Those, my boy,
are reindeer.
For real?
You bet.
[chuckling] All of them!
Whoa.
I've never seen reindeer
in real life.
What do you use them for?
Well...
We use them for the sleigh!
Rides!
My parents own
a lot of property up here,
and they like to give
authentic sleigh rides
to the visitors.
Right, Dad?
Something like that.
What?
I thought you said
you didn't get many visitors.
Gosh, guys, we are going
to get in trouble
if we make dinner
cold.
Chop, chop.
Come on.
[chuckles]
Oh, will you look at that.
Wow.
[chuckling]
So, what we have here now
is beef tenderloin
with chocolate sauce,
sugared carrots,
and Holly's favorite dessert,
a holiday trifle.
Welcome home, darling.
Thank you, Mom.
[chuckles]
Should we wait
for your uncle Mario?
Oh, no, don't worry about him.
He's probably
just tinkering away
on something
down in the factory...
[coughs loudly, clears throat]
So I have some good news.
I am officially
a part of the veterinary team
at Secord clinic.
[Mom gasps]
Ho, ho, ho,
that is something!
It is.
She's incredible,
actually.
She just has such a way
with animals.
That's my girl.
And so, Connor,
what do you do
to keep yourself busy?
Oh, I work
for a toy manufacturer.
Wegman's.
You guys ever
heard of it?
[Nick]: Wegman's...
I may have.
Oh, the elves would know...
Connor is an amazing
toy creator.
Aren't you, Connor?
Oh, well, I mean,
I'd hardly say that.
My last idea
actually tanked so bad
that Mr. Wegman
canceled the Christmas party.
Well, bah humbug to that!
You give me
his whole name
and I will put him
on the naughty list.
[exaggerated laugh]
More carrots?
I've got to say,
I've never thought to put beef
and chocolate together,
but that was delicious.
You can't go wrong
with chocolate.
[Snowball barks]
No, apparently not.
What is it, Snowball?
Oh, he wants you
to go outside
and throw the ball
to him.
It's his
favorite game.
Oh.
Well, in that case, huh,
let's go chuck some ball.
Whoa, whoa.
[Snowball barks]
I need a jacket.
Where's Snowball?
I need my slippers.
Oh, Connor took him outside
to throw the ball.
Oh, did you tell him
not to throw it
to the back of the house
where all the lights
are hooked up?
[gasps]
[Holly]: Connor!
[knocking on door]
Connor?
I brought you
some trifle.
Oh, thank you.
What are you
doing?
I was seeing
if I had any messages from work,
but I can't seem
to get a signal up here.
Oh, well.
Hey, did your parents
get those lights
back up and running?
Mario's
working on it.
I'm sure they'll be
back up and running
by the morning.
I feel like
I should go help him.
No, no, no, no.
Mario likes doing
that kind of thing.
So I made a great
first impression, huh?
Of course you did.
You didn't know
that Snowball
was going to go running
through those cords.
[sighs]
No.
[chuckles]
Come on.
I've got something
that I think
will cheer you up.
[Connor]:
Where are you going?
Just follow me.
[panting]
Are you sure this
is structurally sound?
[chuckles]
Look.
Whoa...
What is that?
The Northern Lights.
The North Pole
is one of the best places
to see them.
The North Pole?
This is the North Pole?
I told you that,
right?
I... I could have sworn
I told you at lunch...
No.
No, no, no, you said
that your parents lived,
like, way, way, way
up north.
You didn't say
they lived this far.
Well...
Here we are.
I hope that's okay?
It's okay.
No, I love it.
It's like
there's something magical
about it all, don't you think?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's magical.
Yeah.
I love you, Connor.
[elves giggling nearby]
What was that?
What was what?
It kind of sounded
like a kid.
[nervous chuckle]
-Connor, look! A shooting star!
-What? Where?
-[Connor]: Whoa!
-[elf]: Ow!
Look at that.
That's crazy!
I've never seen anything
like that before.
That was, like, pfff!
Well, it's like
you said,
it's, uh,
pretty magical up here.
Yeah.
Maybe we should go
back inside.
It's... brrr!
Okay.
-[thump, thump!]
-Whoa... Whoa!
I'm okay!
[cranky grunt]
These lights, Snowball...
Yeah, it's not like
I had enough to do, no, no.
I...
I needed to fix the lights,
so I really appreciate it.
Good dog.
[not pleased] Good dog.
[grumbling angrily]
[Nick]:
I tell you, every year
it seems the kids wish
for more electronic gadgets.
Some toys.
Listen to this...
Dear Santa, I think I've been
a very good boy,
so I'm wishing
for an RX-48 Gaming System,
a cellphone,
and a tablet.
Love, David.
Oh, wow.
Well, David's got
a tall order.
Is he on the nice list?
Why, yes, he is.
-Good morning.
-Hi.
Oh, well,
good morning, sleepyhead.
[Nick chuckles]
Yeah. Yeah, so sorry.
I... I slept late.
Oh, it must be that
fresh arctic air.
Pancakes?
Uh, yes, please.
[Man]: Don't mind if I do.
Oh, Frost, my boy!
Hello.
Nick.
Hey-hey-hey!
Well, ho-ho-ho!
[guys chuckling]
[Mom]: Nice
to see you, Jack.
Jessica, you are looking
as rosy as ever.
Very charming.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Hello, Jack.
"Hello, Jack"?
That's it?
I haven't seen you
in forever, it seems,
and that's all I get?
Uh, Jack, this is
my boyfriend, Connor.
Connor, Jack.
Boyfriend.
Hey. Connor.
Nice to meet you.
-Yeah.
-Wow, chilly hands.
You should get some gloves.
Ah, well,
they don't call me Frost
for nothing...
[laughing]
Oh, do you hear that?
Which reminds me,
I brought you
a welcome home present.
Oh...
-Oh.
-Oh!
One of
your ice sculptures!
Yeah,
it's a replica
of the life-size one
I made for Holly
on her 16th birthday.
Remember, Holly?
Beautiful.
That was the day
you agreed to be my girl
forever and ever.
[awkward chuckle] Ah,
that was a long time ago.
It wasn't that long.
Why don't I just go
put this on ice?
Yes.
So is that your thing,
like, ice sculpting?
Ah, well, not just ice.
Snow too.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Wow.
-Think fast.
-Oh!
-Oh, come...
-Jack!
Uh, uh...
Really?
Oh, come on,
it's all in good fun,
right, Connor?
Yeah, that came
out of nowhere.
[Jack, laughing]: Well, I can't
imagine Holly dating someone
that hasn't got
a sense of humor.
Yeah, you're right.
Look at her father.
It doesn't get
jollier than this guy.
[laughs] I guess not.
Jack...
Oh, it's good to see you.
Let me help you out.
Okay, see
you guys later.
[Nick, laughing]:
Oh, he slays me.
Holly Claus,
I'm surprised at you...
Dating someone
who can't even
catch a snowball.
Oh, we live down south.
He hasn't had
a lot of practice.
So, what,
are you actually serious
about this guy?
Yes. Yes, I am.
I think he's going to propose.
You're kidding, right?
You actually
think Conrad...
Connor.
...Connor will fit in
to your family?
Because, you know, with me,
I never had that problem.
I mean, in fact,
it's what made us
a great match...
It's what makes us
a great match.
It's not going to happen, Jack.
I'm with Connor now.
Okay.
We'll see.
But I'll be by
again soon, Holly.
It's good to see you.
Everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Yeah.
So that was
the ex-boyfriend, huh?
Yes. That was
a long time ago.
Yeah, well...
So he lives here?
At the North Pole?
Yeah, he's our neighbor.
He's probably
the closest one...
In... In... Not that
he's the closest,
but in proximity.
Yeah.
Come on,
let's get some pancakes
before they get cold.
Actually, you know what?
There's a little something
that I need to work on.
Okay.
All right.
[footsteps recede]
[sighs]
Dear sir...
No.
Dear Mr. Claus...
Mom...
Hmm?
Why did you have to
tell Jack I was home?
Well, I didn't, honey.
The little birds told him.
You know how
those doves do chatter.
Well, just
so you know,
it's over
with me and Jack.
It was the moment
that I left.
Well, that
doesn't surprise me.
That boy would have melted
if he'd left the Pole.
Well, I mean,
that's not why it ended.
It didn't work.
You understand, right?
Yeah, of course I do.
Honey, you have not yet
told Connor
who you really are.
I will.
And when I do,
I think he is going
to fit in perfectly.
Yeah.
Right, Donner?
See, Donner agrees.
Well, there's a truth.
That's settled.
Dear Mr. Claus.
Mr. Claus,
uh, may I have a moment?
Just a moment of your time?
A word?
Your daughter, she's...
She's a wonderful person.
You know what,
she has made me so happy.
What I'd like to do
is ask
for her hand in marriage.
[footsteps approach]
Hey, hey, Connor!
Hey, Snowball.
Nick. Mr. Claus. Hey.
Do you have a minute?
I will, after I get back
from my fitting.
Seems I've lost a wee pound
or two this year.
I'll be back.
Milk and cookies
in the kitchen.
Something special...
in the corner.
[chuckles]
Oh.
Something special in the corner.
[chuckles]
Now, ladies,
you have got to stop gossiping
to Jack
about me and Connor.
You got it?
I know we're friends,
but you can't betray my trust
here.
Jack doesn't get
to know everything anymore.
There you go.
Those birds can't keep
their dang beaks shut.
Yeah, I'm talking about you.
So how are you holding up?
Oh, you know...
It's kind of strange
to be here,
especially with Connor.
Have you talked to him
about...
No, not yet,
but I will.
I'm just kind of
scared that he...
It might freak him out,
and then...
Maybe just talk to him,
and then you'll know.
You're right, Mario,
I just need to talk to him.
Going to tell him right now.
Attagirl!
[cuckoo clock chimes]
Huh...
Don't mind if I do.
Ah, perhaps I'll try
a thimble of the sherry.
[beeping]
What?
[slam!]
Connor?
Aah! Aah!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Wha... Whoa! Oh!
[gasps]
-[alarm blares]
-Intruder!
[all shrieking]
What? Wha... Whoa!
[alarm blaring]
Oh, no!
Oh!
[alarm blaring]
Huckleberries and mistletoe!
Don't move.
[elves shouting]
There's got to be some kind
of misunderstanding here, okay?
What's going on
here?
Intruder, sir.
No, I'm not an intruder.
Oh!
Guys, he's not an intruder.
He's my boyfriend.
Yeah.
Come on,
you merry munchkins,
untie him.
Yeah. Thank you.
Thank you.
[Mario]: Yeah...
You guys are animals.
Thank you.
Yeah. All right.
Are you okay?
I... I mean, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
What is this place?
Uh, it's a factory.
Oh!
So, like, when
you were talking about
how your parents
are busy all the time,
it's 'cause they run
a factory.
Exactly.
What do they make here?
Toys.
We make toys.
[Nick]: Jumpin'
juniper berries!
What's all the ruckus?
At least let me get
the last of the pins out, sir.
Oh...
You have to tell him,
sweetheart,
before his head
explodes.
[sighs]
Connor... Oh.
Um, there's something
that I've been meaning
to tell you.
My parents,
they have
a very special job.
Oh...
Oh... [stammers]
Oh, my gosh...
Here? North Pole.
The toys...
Uh-huh.
Your guys' name?
Uh-huh, yeah.
Um, I'm Holly Claus,
and I am Santa Claus'
daughter.
Oh! Daughter.
Father.
Mm.
Mother.
Hah! Oh, boy.
I'm... I'm so sorry,
Connor.
I meant to tell you
before we left,
and I got nervous,
and then I was on my way
to tell you now,
and it's, um...
Well, now it's too late, so...
[takes deep breaths]
Connor, are you okay?
I...
I need that sherry.
Okay, so let me
get this straight.
These reindeer...
are "the" reindeer.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Oh.
Donner in there.
Vixen.
Blitzen, Prancer, Dasher.
Dancer, Comet, and Cupid
are out to pasture.
Rudolph,
he takes off right
after Christmas,
and he doesn't come back again
till the next year,
like, the night of.
It makes my mom
so crazy with worry.
Okay, so let me
get this straight.
If you and I get married,
my in-laws
will be "the"
Mr. and Mrs. Santa Claus?
Yes.
But you can call them
Nick and Jessica, of course.
Connor, if you're not
okay with this,
I totally understand.
Okay?
I'm better than okay.
I'm so good!
[both laugh]
I mean, you...
you and your family
are incredible.
Oh, I mean...
We're just, you know,
we've got issues
like every family.
No, this is exciting.
Okay, what are the
chances? Seriously.
Me, my absolute favorite
time of the year
is Christmas.
Now this. Huh?
Fate? No, destiny.
Speaking of destiny,
I actually...
I'm going to marry you,
Holly Klaus. Claus.
Santa Claus' daughter!
[both giggle]
I'm going to marry
Santa Claus' daughter!
I'm going to ask Santa
to marry his daughter.
I...
I've got to ask Santa
to marry his daughter!
What?!
That's insane!
That's like
asking the president
or, like, the Easter Bunny.
Is the Easter Bunny here?
No. No.
Okay, good.
I need to focus.
What am I going to say?
What do you mean,
what are you going to say?
Well, I mean, I've got
to convince Santa
that I'm worthy
to marry his daughter,
or else why would Santa
let me marry his daughter?
Why wouldn't he?
He will because I love you.
I love you.
Okay. Okay.
Let's do this.
Hand?
Let's go.
[giggles]
[♪♪♪]
[softly] Uh, Nick?
-Oh. Hello.
-Sorry.
Uh, yeah. Uh, Santa Claus.
Mr. Claus.
Yes.
May I have a word?
Oh, of course.
Come, come, come.
Yeah. Thank you.
Oh, my gosh.
Is that the book?
Oh, it sure is.
Have a look.
Don't worry, you're
on the "nice" list.
[Connor]: Wow.
What's going on?
[whispering] Shh.
He's going to ask Dad.
[laughs] Donny Bartlet?
Wow.
He comes to our focus groups
all the time.
He's got a bit
of a mouth on him.
You sure he should be
on the nice list?
You learn, in my business,
everyone gets another chance.
Oh.
I wonder if Stuart Cuthbert
is on there.
[Nick]: Uh, yeah...
Well, it's taking forever.
Look, Connor.
You wanted to speak
with me?
Yes. Yes, of course.
Okay. Here it is.
Okay.
Yeah, I, uh...
Mr. Claus...
I want you to know
that I love your daughter
very much.
She inspires me.
You know, she motivates me.
I just can't imagine my world
without her.
So I wanted to know...
would you allow me
to marry your daughter?
Connor...
Welcome to the family.
[chuckles]
[squeals]
[Nick]: Oh, my boy...
Holly, Holly, Holly...
Yes, yes, yes.
[Nick, chuckling]:
Oh, Mother...
[Holly]: Oh...
Holly Claus...
Will you marry me?
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
Oh!
[chuckling]
Oh, you two!
[♪♪♪]
[doves coo]
[humming]
So it's official.
It is.
And you've told him, right?
I will.
Honey...
Look, you cannot forget
the task at hand.
It has been our job
as the women in this family
to prepare the men
for their job
as the next Santa.
I know.
I do.
I will.
But I would just like
to give him
a couple of extra days
to get used to the idea
of all of this first.
Fine.
But it doesn't mean
we can't start working,
though.
Time is ticking.
Absolutely.
Tick-tock.
So, what are we doing?
I think we should see
if he could hold his cookies.
I mean, after all,
on Christmas Eve,
he's going to be eating
about five billion of them.
And a Santa on Christmas Eve
with an upset tummy...
ooh, is a cranky Santa.
So over here
is our test area.
It's kind of our, uh,
quality control.
And here's
our newest creations.
Every year we like to create
about a dozen new toys.
I mean,
you know how it is...
Kids,
they get tired of their toys,
so we like
to change it up.
What is this?
Oh, oh, actually,
that's not a toy.
It's a contraption
I'm working on
that warps time and space
so when the elves
have to go back
and do damage control,
they can leave the North Pole
at warp speed.
So how does it work?
Oh. Well, you just
write your address here,
and then... but...
[stammers]
Uh, actually, it really
hasn't been tested...
No, don't break it!
[zapping]
[shrieks]
-Connor?
-Yeah?
Mom and I
were wondering
if you could assist us
in the kitchen
with something.
That's a great
idea.
Yeah. Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
Mario, hey.
Thanks for the tour, bud.
And, uh, sorry
about the... the thing.
Ah, no biggie.
[chuckles]
I'll fix it.
Nice.
Yeah.
Okay, Connor.
Here you go.
Those look delicious.
Well, we hope so,
'cause, you see,
Mom is trying out
a bunch of new recipes,
and she needs your help
testing them for her,
right, Mom?
That's right.
Well, now, there's a job
I'll have no problem with.
All right,
let's get started.
Wow.
[slow munching]
How are you doing,
sweetie?
Yeah, yeah....
Um, I think I'm full.
Oh.
[door opens, closes]
[someone whistles]
Hello?
A little white dove told me
Mamma was baking
some of her famous cookies.
Darn doves.
You always had
a real hankering
for my cooking.
Pff, yeah, only because
they're the best cookies
this side of the Pole.
Okay.
Hey, Connor.
You're looking
a little green, man.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Yeah, I was just
taste-testing
some of Jessica's
cookies, yeah.
Unfortunately
I don't think we'll be
getting through these.
Oh, no, no,
he'll be fine.
He just needs
a little bit of a break.
Right, Connor?
[quietly]
Do you have any antacids?
I have a little heartburn.
Oh...
Is this all that's left?
Because... No problem.
I am Jack Frost,
after all.
I'll test them for you.
Jack Frost?
[rapid chomping]
Mm...
What?!
[Jack lets out a breath]
That was tasty.
Okay, Jack.
These are for you.
Try not to eat them
all at once.
I'll do my best,
but no guarantees.
[laughs] Thanks, Jess.
Hey, Holly, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Yeah.
Oh, thanks.
So, what was that
in there?
What was what?
I see the ring on your finger.
You were testing him.
Oh...
You don't know
what you're talking about, Jack.
Does he even know
what he's in for?
Wow.
Well, all I have to say
is good luck.
I mean, by the way
he failed miserably
with those cookies,
looks like you've got
your work cut out for you.
Always nice
to see you, Jack.
Just remember, Holly...
Christmas is the
most special day
of the year.
You don't want to ruin it
by giving the job
to someone who can't handle it.
Right?
I'm just saying.
[sighs]
I brought you
some antacids.
Oh, thank you.
Jack still here?
No. He left.
Nice.
He's got quite the appetite.
I've never seen
anything like that.
Oh, he was just showing off.
Yeah?
For you or your mom?
Connor, you don't have
to be jealous of him.
I know. I know.
It just...
kind of seems like he fits in,
and...
I, uh...
You have nothing
to worry about, okay?
You're going
to fit in.
I'll make sure of it.
Okay.
Could you please tell your mom
that I might skip dinner
tonight?
Sure.
Thanks again.
[♪♪♪]
Only two
marshmallows.
I need the rest
for the smores.
Okay.
So where's
this Connor fellow?
I think he's down
in the factory.
He seems very interested
in what the elves are doing.
Mm.
Sounds like he might
be better served
making toys
than being Santa.
What?
Oh, come on,
Jessica.
Don't tell me you don't
have your doubts.
I mean, he's from the south,
for goodness sakes.
It never gets colder
than 30 degrees down there.
Now, Jack, we have to
give the boy a chance.
And I think Holly
is going to do
a really good job
at training him.
Yeah, but what if he fails?
[Jack, to Holly]: So I guess
congratulations are in order.
Yes, thank you.
Must be lots to do
before the big day, huh?
Geez...
Speaking of which...
Uh, Connor, you ever
slide down a chimney before?
Excuse me?
Uh, Hol and I used to do it
when we were kids,
all the time.
We had so much fun,
remember, Hol?
Yeah, I've slid down
a few banisters in my day.
Ah.
Well, then,
you shouldn't have
any problem at all
with a chimney.
What do you say
we give it a go?
[whistling innocently]
[wind howling]
Is it always
this windy?
Yeah. It's
the North Pole.
[footsteps approaching]
Oh-ho, how are you, my girl?
I thought I'd have myself
a quick read.
[grunts]
What?
Nothing.
Don't tell me "nothing".
I know you.
Tell me.
What, what?
It's all good.
You'll see.
Oh, good news, though...
it's really hot
in the chimney.
Think you can
handle the heat?
Yeah. I can
handle the heat.
We'll see about that.
Here goes nothin'.
-[light thump]
-Ooh!
[guys chuckle]
Oh, Jack!
Just doing a little
chimney sliding, Nick.
Jack...
[Jack]: Such fun.
All right, buddy,
you're up!
Yeah, yeah,
I'll be right down.
Wow.
Connor, you don't
have to do this!
[Connor]: Don't worry,
I got this, babe!
What are you kids
up to?
Uh...
[wind howling]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
Yeah. Yeah...
[Connor]: Whoa! Aah!
Connor?
[Connor]: Hello!
Are you
all right?
[Connor]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
Just a little stuck, I think.
Well,
pull your shoulders together
and suck it in.
[Connor]:
Yeah, still not working.
[Jack]: I got you, buddy...
use the ol' poker trick.
[poking, grunting]
-Jack, Jack!
-What?
Not helping.
Relax, everyone.
I'll...
I'll melt the butter.
[sighs]
Oh, my.
Are you sure
you're okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just, uh, you know,
came down on a wrong angle...
or something.
Okay.
It was a solid
effort, Connor.
You're a good sport.
[clears throat]
Yeah.
[♪♪♪]
How's it going?
Hey.
[chuckles]
Uh, it's okay.
Um, listen,
about today...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that went well.
Yeah...
Listen, that
was my own stupidity,
like, thinking I could
actually slide down a chimney.
It's not like I'm your dad
or anything.
What I should
be able to do
is make a toy
that kids actually
want to play with.
But for whatever reason,
I don't know what to do
to make it better
or more fun
or whatever it is
I've got to do to this thing
to make it
more interesting to kids.
I guess
I could make an app
or add some lights
or something,
but that's kind of
like, plffft!
You know, once my dad
gave me a doll,
and it was kind of
an ugly doll,
to be honest.
It was one of
the elves' prototypes,
and it didn't
quite work out.
And I didn't want
to play with it,
and so it just sat
on my bedroom shelf
for months and months.
And then one day
I spilled hot cocoa
and I got the
doll's dress dirty,
and so I picked her up
and I started cleaning her.
And the moment that doll
was in my hands,
it was like magic.
I cleaned her,
I dressed her,
and for the first time,
I played with her,
and from that moment on,
she was my
most favorite doll.
So, you see,
sometimes you just
have to get the toy
into the child's hands
for them to realize
how wonderful it is.
You'll get it.
Thanks.
Hmm.
Oh, my, Mr. Claus
smells something yummy
from Mrs. Claus' kitchen.
Ho-ho, good morning, dumpling.
Where are the children?
Holly is out
feeding the animals,
and I have Connor
chopping firewood.
Ooh.
Nicholas,
do you have any,
you know, concerns
about Connor's
abilities?
I mean, when I first met you,
you at least could polish off
a couple dozen of my cookies.
Ah, well, I always had
a good appetite.
But we still had our doubts
about me.
Like when you forgot
to harness the reindeer
and they took off
without you.
You sure whipped me
into shape.
And Holly will do
the same for him.
Besides, the boy has
plenty of Christmas spirit.
That will get him through.
[sighing] I don't know.
Look.
I tell you what.
I'll think of a task
I'm sure he can do.
Hmm?
Okay.
Don't touch that...
Oh, boy.
Oh, Connor, my boy.
Just stacking some wood.
Oh, don't worry
about that.
I've got another job
for you.
Job? What kind of job?
Well, the elves are having
their siesta,
but I need some toys.
I was going to get Connor
to go down to the factory
and fill this up
while I get
some work done
in the office.
I could do that.
Um, actually,
I need your help
in the office,
you know what I mean?
-Mm-hmm.
Just get
what's on the list,
and make sure
to be very, very quiet
so you don't wake up
the elves...
Or else they'll get
real cranky.
Got it.
Don't wake up the elves.
[chuckling] Good man.
There we go.
[elves snoring]
Oh yeah!
[snoring]
I think he's got this
in the bag!
[smash!]
[Elf]: Hey!
Aw!
[elves chattering angrily]
[sighs]
[♪♪♪]
Heave, ho-ho-ho!
Heave! Good.
[♪♪♪]
Pull, Santa, Pull.
You sure these
are the right size?
Yes.
[grunts]
Whoo. Whoo.
[♪♪♪]
Robin,
you're the best.
I know.
[laughs heartily]
You're looking very sharp
for the big day, Snowball.
[Snowball grunts]
What? Oh. No.
I haven't told him yet,
but I will.
I mean, there's no rush.
We haven't even set
a date yet.
Rush what?
Um...
I was... I was just
telling Snowball
that, now that we're engaged,
that we don't have to
rush getting married.
We can take our time
and set a date
and plan, and...
You know, actually,
I was thinking
maybe we could...
we could do that sooner
rather than later.
Uh, sooner...
Okay, uh, well,
the summer is always nice.
And the... Oh, the fall
would be beautiful,
with all the leaves...
I was actually thinking
this Christmas.
This Christmas?
Yeah. Why not?
We're already here,
your family's here,
Mario, the elves...
Oh, plus your dad
will be done
delivering all
the presents.
He can kick back,
have an extra egg nog
or two...
But what about
your parents?
Well, first of all,
my parents are in
Florida vacationing,
like they do
every Christmas.
Second of all,
they eloped themselves,
I already talked
to them on the phone,
and they're great with it.
[♪♪♪]
[bouquet freezes, cracks]
Mm!
Is that
your holiday stew?
Mm, yes, it is.
A couple bowls of this
has kept your father going
all Christmas
for almost 30 years.
I thought a bowl or two
might help Connor along.
Yeah.
Um, speaking of Connor,
we have set a wedding date.
You did? When?
Christmas Day.
Oh, honey, that
gives us plenty of time...
Christmas Day this year.
Good golly gumdrops,
Holly Claus!
That's in less
than a week!
I know, but he was
just so excited
about being here,
and us being here, and...
So he already knows?
Actually, I wanted to give him a
little bit more time to...
Oh, Holly, really...
Mom, please.
I just think
that if can complete one task,
he's going to feel
a lot better about this.
Well, let's see
if he could handle...
the sleigh.
Perfect!
Except, for now,
let's keep the reindeer
out of it.
Right.
All right,
these new hydraulics
should take some of the load
off the reindeer
so you can get
to where you need to go
faster.
Ooh!
You guys needed me?
Oh, yeah,
um, sweetie,
Mario just added
hydraulics
to the sleigh.
To ease the load.
And we were hoping
that you might
test-drive it for us,
considering
you probably know
a little more about this
than Dad.
[Nick]: Oh, yeah,
I'm used to
using reindeer dust.
[Connor]: Absolutely.
Yeah, I used to build
go-karts when I was a kid.
I got this.
-Oh!
-Climb aboard, captain.
Okay, so, what have we got?
These ones start it up.
This one gives it the lift.
But right now,
you just want to ease it
out of the barn
in a hover.
You got it?
Got it.
All right!
Good man, good man.
Here we go.
[starts engine,
Jingle Bells plays]
[chuckling]
[Connor]:
That was festive. Good tune!
[Nick chuckles] Yeah!
[controls beeping,
engine humming]
[Nick]: Attaboy, attaboy.
[RPMs increase smoothly]
Sounds good.
-Yeah.
-Yeah!
It sounds
like it's warmed up.
So now,
just go up into a hover.
-Here I go.
-Here you go, here you go.
Nice and easy.
[RPMs increase smoothly]
[alert beeping]
[electronics zapping]
I... I don't know
what happened.
[Connor stammers, bewildered]
Everything was good...
Mario?
Uh... duct tape.
[Mario chuckles awkwardly]
[♪♪♪]
Here you go, Donner.
That's enough, Thistle.
Good night, now.
Hey.
Can Mario fix the sleigh?
Oh, he'll set it right.
Dad, do you think
Connor can do it?
Now, now, now,
let's have none of that talk.
But he hasn't been able
to finish a single task.
Holly...
I flunked
rooftop parallel parking
seven times.
My first chimney slide,
I landed
smack in the fire,
singed my "South Pole",
couldn't sit down
for a week.
Darlin', if I can do this,
have faith he can.
Hey, Holly?
I think I might need
some aspirin.
What about you?
You know
where the aspirin is?
[barking]
[Jack]:
Hey there, partner.
Looking for these?
Nice catch.
Yeah. Thanks.
So, from what I hear,
the big day
is right around the corner.
Yup.
Bet you never thought
you'd be in the shoes you're in.
No. Some pretty big shoes.
Wow, that's an understatement.
I mean, how many
people can say
they're marrying
Santa's daughter?
Just me.
That's right.
Just you. You're the one.
And it's just you
taking on that big, red,
jolly responsibility too.
That's right.
Mm.
Gee, I'm sorry,
I don't really know
what you're talking about.
Oh, just the whole
Santa legacy thing.
I mean, you
can't tell me
you're not just
a little bit freaked out
about the idea
of becoming Santa, right?
[both chuckle]
Oh...
Oh, wow. Mm...
She hasn't told you, has she?
What?!
Ugh. Well, this is awkward...
for me.
Okay, so,
what you're saying
is that,
because I'm marrying Holly,
I'm actually
next in line
to be Santa?
That's about right.
Hit the nail
on the head.
Why wouldn't
she tell you?
You know?
Yeah, of course,
I guess
she could have her reasons,
like... maybe in her heart
she knows
you're not cut out for the job?
Look, I'm...
I'm sorry.
Forget I said anything,
all right?
You're a good man,
Connor, okay.
And I'm sure
you understand
that Christmas
is the most magical day
of the year...
which is why I know
you wouldn't want to spoil it
for generations to come.
Right, buddy?
Feel better, bud.
Ooh!
[door closes]
Oh, hey, Snowball.
Okay, I'll take care
of that.
We need some aspirin...
Actually, I already
took care of it.
-Oh, you did?
-Mm-hmm.
I think I should just
go check on him anyway.
It's okay.
He was almost asleep.
Poor guy.
Really?
That arctic air
is really knocking him out.
Yeah.
So why don't you
just let him rest?
Let's say we have
a cup of cider, huh?
Oh, I really should...
Oh, I'd love
some cider.
After a day like this,
I'll take two cups.
All right.
Then we'll all
raise a glass, huh?
Oh, I...
I really should, um...
-Come on. Yeah!
-Okay.
All right.
[♪♪♪]
[group laughter]
So we snuck out
around midnight,
without waking
any of the elves,
and then
we pushed the sleigh
out of the barn.
Holly bribed the reindeer
so they'd help us out
and keep quiet.
With candy apples.
[laughing] That's right,
with candy apples!
So we pushed the sleigh
far enough away
that when we took off,
you guys wouldn't hear us.
Oh, you're such rascals!
Well, it didn't hurt
that we gave you hot cocoa!
[group laughter]
That's right.
Where did you two fly to?
We went all the way
to the top of Snowy Ridge.
Oh.
It was beautiful.
Oh, you always could
handle the sleigh, Jack.
Well, I had
a great co-pilot.
-Ooh.
-Aw.
[Nick]:
I'm about ready for a top-off.
Oh!
How about we do
some Christmas caroling?
You guys used to do
some caroling.
What was one of the songs
you used to sing?
[Jack]: Oh,
you mean this one?
♪ It came upon
the midnight clear ♪
♪ That glorious song of old
That's the one.
-Come on, Holly.
-Oh...
-Join me up here.
-Oh, no.
[Jack]: Join in.
-No, I don't want to.
-Come on!
Honey, we haven't heard
you sing in so long.
[Nick]: This is true.
Come on.
[Holly]: All right.
[in perfect harmony]
♪ From angels
♪ Bending near the earth
♪ To touch their harps of gold
[Nick]: Oh, this
is wonderful!
[chuckles]
♪ It came upon
the midnight clear ♪
♪ That glorious song of old
♪ From angels
bending near the earth ♪
♪ To touch their harps
of gold ♪
This is nice.
Oh, yeah.
♪ Peace on the earth
♪ Goodwill to men
♪ From Heaven's
all-gracious king ♪
♪ It came upon
the midnight clear ♪
♪ That glorious song of old
♪ And all the world
♪ Give back the song
♪ Which now the angels sing
[group chuckling]
What a lovely
evening.
Thank you, Jack.
[Jack]: Aw. You know...
There's no place
that I'd rather be.
I'm going to
go check on Connor.
[Jessica]:
All right.
Good night, Jack.
Yeah. Good night.
Night.
Good night, Jack.
Thanks for the memories,
old friend.
Thank you guys.
Safe home.
[humming Silent Night]
[together] ♪ Holy night
♪ All is calm
♪ All is bright
[♪♪♪]
Connor, sweetie?
Are you okay?
Hmm.
Dear Holly,
The first day
I laid eyes on you,
I knew I'd be a lucky man
if you ever gave me
a second glance...
because not only
were you the most beautiful girl
in the room,
but you were the most radiant.
But I took a chance,
and when I did,
not only did you give me
a second glance,
but one
of the most magical nights
of my life.
I know I've told you before,
Holly,
but I fell in love with you
that night,
and nothing has come close
to that moment
until the day you said yes.
I love you, Holly...
and I'd do anything
for you,
which is why
I'm saying goodbye...
because you deserve someone
who will take the reins
and fill your father's boots
in a way
that I'll never be able to,
and I cherish Christmas too much
for that.
And I love you even more.
Merry Christmas, Holly.
Love always, Connor.
[sniffles]
[voice breaking] Oh...
[muttering]
Craftsmanship nowadays...
[reindeer snorts]
Oh, you think
this is real funny, do you?
[sobbing nearby]
What is it,
Jingles?
I was...
I was going to tell him,
you know...
prepare him.
But I guess he found out
and panicked.
But that's not
the worst of it.
The worst of it
is that I doubted him...
I doubted if
he was up for the job
of being Santa...
which is terrible,
because... I love him.
I guess if I had
kept the faith
and not fallen
into doubt,
he would still be here.
Chestnut, there was
nothing you did.
This is on him.
And destiny.
And if it was meant to be,
the stars will align,
and believe me...
he'll be back.
What if that
doesn't happen?
Well...
you'll still
be all right.
[both chuckle]
[sighs]
[♪♪♪]
[gasps]
I just got a huge order
for hunky Santa dolls.
Yes!
Merry Christmas!
Hey. Uh...
Yeah.
[Jack]: I heard
what happened,
and that's lousy.
I mean,
a Dear John letter?
I mean, at least
be man enough
to tell you
to your face, right?
I guess that's why
he's not cut out
for the job.
What do you want, Jack?
What I've always wanted.
You.
Really, Jack? Now?
Now is a better time
than never.
I can't lose you
again, Holly.
You've got to know it...
We're meant for each other.
Your dad knows it,
your mom knows it.
You've got to know it.
I mean,
think about how much fun
we all had together
the other night.
Right?
And there's no doubt that
I'm the man for the job.
I...
Just think about it.
That's all I'm asking.
[♪♪♪]
Wow.
That's quite the piece of ice
you got there.
Jack gave it to me.
He asked me to marry him,
in so many words.
Well, can't say
I'm surprised.
I guess you think
that's a good idea?
He would make
a great Santa.
I don't think
anything other than
wanting my little girl
to be happy.
And does he?
Does Jack make you happy?
I don't think
it matters, does it?
You know what I love best
about being Santa?
The look on
those kids' faces
when they open up
a present
they've been wishing for
all year.
The twinkle
they get in their eyes...
The flush of pink
to their cheeks...
The feeling of pure joy.
Now, you tell me,
does it matter
if he makes you happy?
Connor!
Surprised to
see you here, buddy.
I thought you would have
taken off for the holidays.
Yeah, I decided to come back,
you know, get some work done.
Ah.
Yeah, well,
thanks to my new
hunky Santa doll,
Wegman's throwing us
another party.
Yeah, but don't worry,
you don't need
to stick around.
Don't do us
any favors, okay?
So I was thinking
of a sexy Santa doll
to go with the hulky Santa
doll...
-I need a focus group!
-What?
Focus group. I need one.
No, no, no, no,
Connor, not now.
Can't you see?
You know...
-Ah!
Besides, all you've got
is that weird dog thing,
and it was a flop.
Oh, that's right,
Connor,
the dog with wheels.
Yeah. Wheels are turnin'.
Mr. Wegman, trust me.
I got something.
Holly?
Hey!
It's me, Jack.
You wanted to see me?
[footsteps approach]
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Ah, you're the man, Jack.
That's right.
All you've got
to say now is "I do,"
and this
will all be yours.
Ho, ho, ho!
All of you are naughty.
Oh.
So that's what this
has always been about?
Wh... Holly, baby.
I was just
trying it on.
And guess what?
Fits like a glove.
Just as I said...
we're the perfect match.
Don't try to get yourself
out of this one, Jack,
'cause I get it now.
I mean, I can't believe
it took me this long to see it.
This...
This is what
you've always wanted.
Not me.
Holly, please.
How can you say that?
It's only ever
been about you.
I mean, look at us.
We've been a team
since we were kids.
I love you.
You know what,
if actually cared,
I might try to believe you.
But I don't.
Holly.
Come on,
of course you care.
You're Holly Claus.
The most important thing
in the world to you
is Christmas.
So, really,
if you care about Christmas,
you care about us.
You're right.
I do care about Christmas.
I knew it.
So, what do you say?
Shall we make this
official? Hmm?
All right.
I'm officially taking over
the role of Santa.
What did you say?
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do the job.
[laughs]
That's... That's golden.
Oh, man...
You, as Santa,
with the belly...
and the beard!
I'm serious, Jack.
Why not?
As long as the job
gets done.
And I know I can do it.
Don't be
ridiculous, Holly.
I should be Santa.
Not you.
I mean, come on.
Do you know how many years
I've been working towards this,
with you
and your family?
Do you know how many
of your mom's cookies
I've had to choke down
over the years
to get here?
Oh, I thought you loved
my cookies.
Uh... Of course
I love your cookies, Momma.
I was just
saying that...
Oh, save it, Jack.
And do me a favor.
Take off the jacket.
And don't call me "Momma".
[wind howling]
You're making
the biggest mistake
of your life.
I'll take that chance.
[door closes]
So...
You are going to follow
in your father's footsteps?
Oh, I'm going to try.
Oh!
You think Dad
will be okay with it?
Given that
you're your father's daughter,
I think he'll be just fine.
[electronic games beeping]
This is going
to be weak.
[chuckles]
Hey, boys and girls.
Listen, have I got a toy
for you, okay.
Now, this toy...
the batteries
will never, ever, ever run out.
You'll never
have to charge them.
Okay, this toy will stand
the test of time, okay,
and it will be with you
for as long
as you're willing
to take care of it.
This toy...
[sighs]
...is Fido.
This is
ridiculous!
Come on,
give the kid one of
my hunky Santa dolls.
Or try one of my
hunky Santa dolls.
Okay, for the last time,
it was my idea, okay?
So drop it.
Not even.
Look,
yes, it was.
[Connor]: Meet Fido.
[Wesley]: By the way,
a winky face means nothing.
It just makes you look
like a stalker.
Hey, can I
have a turn?
Hey, this is cool.
-What is it?
-It's a toy dog!
[kids chatter excitedly]
[kids laugh]
I like its ears.
Yeah, he looks
really cool.
-Wow!
-Wow, I love it.
[excited chatter continues]
Brilliant, Connor,
just brilliant.
Work with me.
That was one heck
of a presentation.
Holy Dinah.
And I've got to say, Connor,
this whole time,
I knew you had it in you.
Wesley!
-I'm right here, Mr....
-Geez!
Wesley, let's
get this toy ready
to roll out
into production,
ASAP!
Got it.
And let's cut the order
of hunky Santa dolls
in half.
I want to double up
on Fido.
[Kelly]: Oh, no. Really?
I am so sorry your idea
didn't pan out, Wesley.
[Wegman]: Okay,
so much bickering.
Let's go.
Back to work.
The classic toys
are back!
[chuckling]
Whoa, Connor...
A little success
has given you
quite the appetite.
That's a lot
of donuts.
Ha! I can do it!
You can do it?
Look, I can do it!
You can do it.
Do it!
I can do it.
I did that!
[ringing]
Cookie break is over.
Back to work.
[elves]: Aww!
Ho, ho, ho!
How can I help you?
Mario?
Hey, it's Connor.
How you doing, Sasquatch?
Listen...
Merry Christmas, Stuart.
Hey, can you pick me up
at the airport?
Hey, you bet your tinsel
I can.
Awesome. Yes!
Listen... Um...
I'll see you
after the next flight.
You got it!
Yeah.
Oh...
The stars have aligned.
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas, everyone!
Ho, ho, ho, ho!
Merry Christmas.
Whoo!
Merry Christmas, sir.
[sighs]
All right, Donner,
seeing as I'm going to be
the one holding the reins
one day,
I should probably
get some practice in, huh?
[Donner vocalizes]
Well, thank you.
I appreciate
the vote of confidence.
I think I can do it too.
I just wish I didn't
have to do it alone.
[Connor]: You don't.
Connor!
Holly, I am so sorry.
It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
I should never
have left you like I did.
I should have
talked to you first,
'cause that's what
couples do, right?
They talk it out.
And if I would have
done that,
then maybe
I would have realized
that the reason
I wasn't succeeding
was because of my confidence,
my lack of it.
Oh, Connor,
I never wanted
to put that kind
of pressure on you...
which is why I waited
to tell you,
because I was...
I was afraid.
And I totally understand
if you don't want to...
No, no, I do.
I want to do it.
I can, Holly.
You watch me.
[♪♪♪]
Here I come!
-Whoa!
Oh, my, my, my!
[♪♪♪]
[cheering]
And remember,
a busy elf
is a happy elf.
Ha, ha, ha!
All right, Ewing,
loading it up.
Yeah!
With the legs... Yeah.
Ho, ho, how do I look?
Oh, honey, well,
you're a little skinnier
than last year,
but otherwise
pretty perfect.
Rudolph
just rolled in.
Oh!
Oh, thank goodness.
He always gets here
at the last minute.
[Nick]: All right.
Now we're all here,
I guess it's time
to get this show on the road.
Connor...
You'd best get a jacket
or something.
It gets a bit chilly
up there.
I'm sorry, where?
In the sleigh.
You're coming with me,
aren't you?
I mean, you need
at least a few practice runs.
Yes, sir.
I mean, Santa.
Yeah, absolutely
I'll go up there with you.
Then let's do this.
Ha, ha, ha!
Whoo!
[chuckling]
Come on, everyone!
My favorite night
of the year!
Now, I packed
some extra socks...
Oh, I've got extra socks.
And some
little snacks,
and I've got
a lunch for you...
I don't need lunch.
I'll be eating
cookies all night.
Okay, okay.
Bye-bye, bye-bye.
Good night.
-Have a good time.
-Yeah.
-One more.
-Aw.
Are you
all right?
Yeah.
No, I'm better
than all right.
I'm great.
Hop in, Connor.
There's plenty of room.
Room for two?
Because this generation
of Clauses
is going to do it
together.
Really?
Yeah.
That's my girl.
Come on, come on.
Oh, there's my girl.
Oh, you look
right at home there, Connor.
Now, will you both
do the honors?
On...
[together] Dasher and Dancer
and Prancer and Vixen!
On Comet and Cupid
and Donner and Blitzen!
And you too, Rudolph!
Yeah!
To the top of the porch,
to the top of the wall!
Now dash away! Dash away!
Dash away all!
[excited laughter]
Bye!
Merry Christmas!
[laughter]
Oh, oh, here.
Whoo!
[jolly laugh]
Oh, whoo!
And... Merry Christmas!
[♪♪♪]