Subtitles by explosiveskull
Hey, Mom.
Hey! Where did you find
this stranger?
Found him on the road.
Is it okay if I use your car?
I really need to get to work.
- Sure.
- Yeah?
You don't wanna stay and help us finish
off the last of Bambi with this stew?
I'd love to, I have to go.
Dad, thank you.
Have a good one.
How was it?
Yeah, wasn't too bad.
Hey...
you're gonna have to
say a few words tonight.
How many?
Well...
Lincoln did, what,
282 for the Gettysburg Address.
So, 100?
Come on, they're just
trying to thank you.
It's not gonna be
a firing squad.
That would be
over quick, though.
Is that new?
No.
Just tuck it there.
Um...
Um, I'm... I'm no speech giver.
But I sure as heck am very honored to
be named Kehoe's Citizen of the Year.
However, if... if
it were up to me...
I'd give it to
somebody more important.
Uh... I'm a...
I'm just a guy who keeps a strip
of civilization open through
the wilderness for people.
Hmm...
When you...
when you drive the same road
day after day,
it's... easy to start thinking
about the road not taken.
I try not to do that.
You see...
I was lucky.
I picked a good road early...
and I stayed on it.
Hey, kid. How was your day?
Easy!
Kyle. Kyle!
Shut up!
- Help!
- Shut up!
Get his arms!
- Get his belt!
- I got it.
Pull it down.
Help!
Shit.
- What's going on?
- I don't wanna go.
Hey, I know you're smart
but you're not that smart.
Uh, hey.
- Doesn't wanna go.
- Ah, shit.
Let me guess,
this is about Tim, right?
Ryan's got a bully in his class.
Tim rubbed his face
in the dirt yesterday.
Do you know what a bully is?
It's a chance
to prove your mettle.
Now, you don't wanna
waste those chances in life.
- He's a lot bigger than I am.
- Yeah, even better.
Are you saying
I should hit him?
Yeah, for a start.
- That's not a very good idea.
- Oh yeah, why not?
Because then I'll be
as stupid as he is.
Listen... come here, come here.
I gave you Lord of the Flies
for your birthday.
I'll bet you haven't
even started it yet.
Well, then that's too bad.
All the answers you'll ever need
are in that book.
Come on, time to go.
You were a real wild man last night.
- There's no one crazier than you, buddy.
- Who knew you could dance.
- Ah, good times, huh?
- Tell you what, we'll do this again, huh.
Yeah!
You look good.
Get you some breakfast.
Jesus, Grace.
Your son?
He died of a heroin overdose.
Um, excuse me.
Kyle wasn't a druggie.
Sorry,
but all the parents say that.
But he... he wasn't a druggie.
What... what are you gonna do?
I'll be turning it
over to Vice and Narcotics.
We didn't know our own son.
Kyle wasn't a druggie.
You're not listening!
He leadeth me to the paths
of righteousness for His name's sake.
Yea, though I walk through the
valley of the shadow of death,
I shall fear no evil
for thou art with me...
Thou anointest
my head with oil.
My cup runneth over.
Surely goodness and mercy
shall follow me
all the days of my life.
And I shall dwell in the house
of the Lord forever.
Hmm?
Nels?
Dante?
I'm sorry, Nels.
I'm really sorry.
It wasn't supposed
to end like this.
I know where and when
the cocaine arrives.
Kyle didn't know about any of this.
That's the truth.
It was just one bag.
Just one bag!
But people like that,
they always find out.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
What people?
What people do you mean?
Um...
Do you have...
do you have any cash?
- If they find me, they'll hurt me!
- What people!
- Please! Please!
- What people do you mean?
Speedo,
there's a guy named Speedo.
- Speedo?
- He's the only one I know!
Just tell me
where I can find this guy
and then you get the hell out of here!
Where is he?
So, you're Speedo?
Bingo, gold star.
Dante says hello.
I don't know any Dantes.
Yes, you do.
He worked at the Kehoe airport
with my son... Kyle.
You know him too.
Kyle?
Oh, yeah.
Kyle, that's your kid?
Yeah, yeah, I, uh...
No, I don't know him. Sorry.
I know a lot of people,
I know a lot of... Kyles.
Tell me what happened.
Tell me.
All right, Pops.
There's the door, all right?
I don't know what igloo you crawled out of
but I think it's time you crawled back in.
And trust me,
that's your, uh, best move.
Okay?
You have my phone?
Tell me what happened.
I was...
I was just taking orders.
Taking orders from who?
Who!
- Limbo.
- Huh?
- Limbo?
Limbo.
Limbo...
Is that him? That Limbo?
No doubt about it, Dan Reeves
was at least in the top three best coaches.
And since we're strolling down
memory lane at the Mile High Stadium,
here's a late night question
for you, Denver.
Greatest quarterback ever,
Elway or Manning?
Give me a call on 555-2395.
Elway.
Aren't you gonna ask
where I've been?
Uh, Speedo's missing.
Who's Speedo?
One of my employees.
But you wouldn't know about him,
because we don't talk about business
on the way to school, do we?
Who packed these?
- Didn't think a treat would kill him.
- High fructose corn syrup.
Lecithin.
Baking soda?
The only thing not in those
is rat poison.
I want you to know...
I had no hand in this.
I say make them all legal.
Meth, ex, opium.
An opium den in every mall,
that's my platform.
Give the people what they want. Tax the
shit out of it, then double our pay.
- What do you think about that?
- No thanks.
I wanna be able to tell the good guys from the
bad guys. That way I'll know who to shoot.
Nels Coxman.
Citizen of the Year.
Good for him.
It's a real word, you know,
cocksman.
It means "a man adept
at the art of fornication."
Nice.
You see these guys?
Whoa. Whoa, hey...
It's just weed.
Yeah, it's legal to purchase,
legal to smoke at home.
Take a breath.
Come on, breathe.
There's a principle
you need to get on board with
if you intend to survive and
advance in Kehoe law enforcement.
It's called community policing.
Wherein we embrace and enforce
the values of our community.
The values of them
giving us the finger?
We're a ski town. Folks come here to
ski, have sex and get high.
So lighten up.
Here, you wanna get your Dirty Harry on?
The meter just hit zero.
Get rid of the gum.
So, what can I do for you, boss?
Uh, I'm...
I'll be right with you.
- Just can't believe this is happening.
- Give me one second.
What's the verdict back here?
Wow.
It's absolutely stunning.
Hmm. Yeah,
I can't believe this.
I love the detail
in the lace. The shape.
- It's so elegant, right?
- Yes.
No, I absolutely
love it. I think this is it.
- I think I'm gonna cry.
- It's so stupid.
You look absolutely...
I'll throw in the veil
at no extra charge.
Wow!
- Congratulations.
- Thanks for everything.
It feels surreal.
All right.
How can I help you, boss?
Uh, I'm, uh,
I'm looking for a tux.
You got it. When is the wedding?
It's not a wedding. My...
my wife and I,
we're renewing our vows.
Still going strong, huh?
That's what I like to hear.
- How's about we get you measured, huh?
- Sure.
You killed my boy.
Who told you to do it?
Who?
Santa. Santa.
- "Santa"?
- That's what he goes by.
Where can I find this "Santa"?
There's a little airport
in Kehoe.
He flies in with the coke
and out with the money.
What does he look like?
He looks like a Santa.
No! Come on, please. You don't
have to do that. Come on, please.
Elway or Manning?
What?
Greatest quarterback ever.
Elway or Manning?
Elway.
Did you know Kyle
had a Facebook?
Do you know his favorite band?
He posted his favorite movies,
do you know those?
What'd the two of you talk about
on your damn hunting trips?
Hunting.
Damn it.
Goddamn.
Damn it!
That's the fourth gym bag
you've lost.
Yeah,
but who's counting, right?
You might find this
hard to believe
but I've got more important things
to do than keep track of gym bags.
Like earning the money
to pay for them.
Tell you what...
why don't you take this
and buy him every single
goddamn gym bag he'll ever need.
Does that work for you?
All right.
Well, that's for you.
- Tell me this is a joke.
- No.
That's Ryan's new diet.
And you're gonna follow it to the letter.
Breakfast: grass-fed beef,
asparagus, cashews.
Lunch, the same.
Dinner, the same.
Yeah, that's on Mondays. Tuesday it
rotates. Chicken, broccoli and almonds.
For breakfast, lunch and dinner?
You want our son to eat the
same thing three times a day?
Eighty percent of our immune
system starts in the gut.
Keep it simple in the gut,
you get to live a long life.
A week on this diet
and he'll wanna kill himself.
And I'll help him do it.
You know what,
you should be grateful.
My dad started my day with half a
grapefruit and three lines of primo coke.
"Breakfast of champions,"
he called it.
And now your son can't look at a
candy bar without breaking into hives.
Congratulations,
you've broken the cycle.
And to think...
I used to love the mouth on you.
I've spoken to my lawyer.
We want a new arrangement.
Ten days with me, four with you.
Huh.
Here's my counter offer.
Fourteen days with me and none with you.
Let's see what your lawyer
thinks about that.
- Morning, Aya.
- Hey, Mustang.
They say Limbo's disappeared.
Don't worry about it,
he'll get over it.
Is that Mozart?
Bach. You can always tell Bach
because he's really mathematical.
- Is he the one with all the kids?
- Yeah, 20.
It's a wonder he found
any time to compose.
I need your help
with my fantasy football.
I can't... I can't win a game.
Playing for money?
Yeah, of course
I'm playing for money.
You got four Cleveland Browns
on your team.
Well, they're my home team.
What's a man without loyalty?
I can't help you.
Hey, there's not enough
room to pass,
I was wondering if you'd
back down to the turnoff?
Any chance you could back up?
Um, just between you and me,
right?
Me, you and frosty.
Sure.
You have no clue
who you're messing with, man.
Who am I messing with?
You're dust, pal.
Tell me.
You're wasting your time.
Are you tired, old man?
Yeah.
Grace?
What are you doing here?
Kyle's dead.
Somebody killed him.
What's that got to do with me?
Can I come in?
Better take your shoes off. She'll
skin you alive.
I'm going to make
some phone calls.
Find out what happened to Kyle.
She thinks you're one
of the guys from the old days.
Don't worry about her.
Kyle. He got mixed up with some
clown by the name of Dante.
And they stole
a kilo of coke from Viking.
- Who's Viking?
- Drug dealer. A big one.
- You know him?
- Yeah, when he was a snot-nosed kid.
- I knew his old man, Bullitt.
- Dad knew him, too?
Whenever Bullitt had rough stuff to be done,
that was his go-to guy. After Dad, me.
And then Viking took over.
Viking's a whole
different breed.
He likes hurting people.
I'm gonna kill him, Brock.
Sure you are.
What makes you think
you can kill a man?
I've...
I've killed three of his guys.
What did you do with the bodies?
Wrapped them in chicken wire,
threw them on the gorge.
- Chicken wire?
- Yeah, to let the fish get at them.
They'll eat the flesh
off the bones.
So the bodies don't fill
with gas and rise.
They stay at the bottom.
- Where did you learn that?
- I read it in a crime novel.
- He is my brother.
- Brother?
My ass.
I know.
- Maybe I should...
- Shut up.
You stay out of trouble.
The things we do for love, huh?
She was skimming the till
at a massage parlor.
They sent me to beat the shit
out of her. Instead...
How's Grace?
She left.
The lady's got good timing,
I'll give her that.
How do I find this Viking?
You don't.
- You've gone as far up the ladder as you're gonna go.
- We'll see.
One guy can disappear.
Two? I don't think so.
Three? With ten keys of coke?
Maybe they were
all in it together.
You think three of my dealers
ran out on me?
That would make me the worst judge of
character in the Rockies, that's your theory?
- No.
It was those goddamn Indians.
This is all my father's fault
for getting into bed with them.
I'm sorry, the Indians?
When Viking's father
was first getting started,
he made a deal with an
Indian named White Bull.
He supplied him,
White Bull dealt on the reservation.
Until White Bull
wanted more turf.
- So he tossed White Bull a few piece of crap towns.
- Like Kehoe.
And Kehoe builds a ski resort.
Turns it into a gold mine.
What's the one thing
history's taught us?
You keep those Indians
on the reservation.
Those Indians,
they're always wanting more.
Because they think the turf
was theirs all along.
Might kinda have
a point there, right.
White Bull gave this
to my father...
the day they shook
on their deal.
Yeah.
It's time we give it
back to him.
- What can I do for you two?
- You could sit down with us. Tell us your story.
- I got other customers.
- Yeah, that's funny. All I can see in here is you.
Please tell me you work nights.
Thursdays. Why?
You look this good in sunlight,
I gotta see you after dark.
Eggs, bacon, pancakes.
And for you?
Surprise me.
Okay.
I was 13 when my dad kicked it.
You know his last words to me?
"Try to bang every waitress
who ever serves you."
This Indian is
taking forever to show up.
So, tell me
about this motel trick of yours.
Twenty bucks.
It's not a trick, all right.
It's a beautiful invention. It's an invention
Steve Jobs would have been proud of.
- Steve Jobs, huh?
- That's right.
You know what made that guy
such a genius? Simplicity.
- Let's hear it already.
- All right.
I stay in motels
100 nights a year, right.
First thing, every morning, I hang a
"clean the room" sign on the doorknob.
Maid sees the sign,
she opens the door.
Now, pay attention
to the details here.
All the hard thought
behind them.
I'm lying on top of the covers,
stone naked.
First crucial part,
I look into the maid's eyes, all right?
If I don't, she backs right outta that
door. It's over before it even starts.
I take the twenty,
I lay it right on my Jimmy.
- Boom.
- Just a twenty?
Maids make $8.35 an hour,
and they've got miserable lives too.
That's the totally
underrated part of this.
The ball is completely
in her court.
She could back out of that door
no harm, no foul.
Or... she could come and get it.
- What's your success rate?
- Thirty-one percent.
Hundred motels a year,
you do the math.
He's got the same little
yellow gloves White Bull wears.
- Is that an Indian thing?
- I guess.
It's good.
That's Steve fucking Jobs good.
I see one flaw. Quality control.
I'm paying her 20 bucks,
I'm not asking for Miss America.
Still, there's no way there's 31 maids
in the whole country worth banging.
You'd be surprised.
Oh dear.
Been at it all night,
haven't gotten a thing out of him.
And you won't.
You know, pain...
it's like a religion
to these guys.
You know, the Apaches used to consider
getting tortured a mark of honor.
How's that for a value system?
He's a Ute.
- What now?
- Local Indians are Utes. Not Apache.
You know I married an Indian.
Don't you think I know the difference?
This doesn't happen
in Kehoe.
It just did.
It was his first run.
"Just one run, Papa,"
he says to me.
"I can do it."
"I'm your son."
What are we going to do?
Okay, let's go home to Denver.
Mr. Coxman.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
Thanks.
Hey.
So...
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Ex-boyfriend of mine works Vice in Denver.
So I gave him a call today.
Because you missed him and
wanted to see how he was doing.
Well, he still thinks
there's a chance for us.
What's his name?
Kurt.
- How long were you two lovers?
- Oh, Jesus. Two months, okay.
I had him look up the forensics on our sign
hanger. The guy's name is Simon LeGrew.
Now, his father is White Bull.
He's a Native American
drug dealer from Denver
who's been dealing coke
around here for 30 years.
So now, White Bull
shares territory with Viking.
He's a Denver drug dealer whose
real name is Trevor Calcote.
So...
I'm thinking...
what we have here is a turf war.
A drug turf war.
Right here in Kehoe.
So what are we gonna
do about it?
Well, my 30 years' experience tells
me that this is a job for Denver Vice.
It doesn't bother you that I just
learned more about a local drug lord
in five minutes on the phone
than you've learned in 30 years?
What bothers me is that Kurt's lying in bed
tonight convinced that he's back in your heart.
Kurt's a big boy.
I knew you'd be back.
All right, Viking's real name
is Trevor Calcote.
If you want him dead,
you're gonna have to hire a hit man.
- A hit man?
- Yeah. An assassin.
Do you know one?
The Eskimo.
So, how does this work?
You buy The Eskimo a train ticket.
He's afraid to fly.
You pick him up at the train
station, you drive him to a motel
where you give him
half the money upfront.
And then you go home.
- How do I know when it's done?
- Keep checking The Denver Post.
They can't resist
a good rub out.
What is it with all these nicknames?
Speedo, Viking, Eskimo.
The Eskimo.
It's a gangster thing.
Did you have a nickname?
Yeah. Wingman.
Wingman?
Yeah, from Top Gun.
As in "you can be my Wingman."
Wingman.
Come on.
I tried, buddy.
Some real music, please.
- What do you want to hear?
- Anything else. Just no Kanye.
Take it out of his tip.
There's a convention in town.
This is all I could get.
- This is only half.
- That's right.
Are you a cop?
No.
The reason I ask is cops are
always a year behind the street.
But the street knows it's two-thirds
upfront, one-third when the deal is done.
But cops... they still think
it's half and half.
Okay. We can do two-thirds.
We're gonna get along
just fine.
Yes!
Yes! Ten grand! Ten grand, baby!
Ten grand!
That Jet touchdown just beat your Browns.
Whatever happened to loyalty?
Sometimes loyalty
comes at a price.
And besides,
my grandmother's from Brooklyn.
So? Why don't you
give her a cut?
Yeah?
Says he's The Eskimo.
Says he has information you wanna buy.
Let's hear him out.
I've been offered
ninety grand to ice you.
To ice me?
You wanna ice a guy, you go to The Eskimo.
Well, that works for me.
Who knew White Bull
had that kind of coin?
White Bull's an Indian.
Indians don't farm out their kills.
- So, if it wasn't White Bull, then who the hell was it?
- That's what I'm selling.
- Well, how much?
- Ninety grand.
You gotta love
the symmetry, there.
You are one hell
of a businessman.
I tries.
Try. It's a singular.
- Do we have a deal?
- 'Course we got a deal.
Deposit the money into
this Cayman Islands account.
When it hits, you get the name.
Goody.
I like working with pros.
Cuts way down
on the bullshit factor.
Yeah. So...
who wants me dead?
Guy's name is Coxman.
Coxman.
There was a Coxman
on Dad's payroll, right?
What was his name? He called
himself, uh, Wing... Ding...
Ringworm... Wing... Ding...
- Wingman.
- Wingman!
Wingman!
Wingman wants me dead? Why?
The why of it ain't my
business so I don't aks.
- Ask.
- I think our business here is done.
So it is.
Hey, can I ask two questions?
If I may.
One pro to another.
Shoot.
Why do they call you The Eskimo?
Comes from the brothers
in the hood.
Any nigga crazy enough to move up to snow
country has gotta be a fucking Eskimo.
That's... you're funny.
- Second question.
- All right, it's...
Who taught you your ethics?
Come again?
You made a deal to kill me for 90
grand and you didn't honor that deal.
It's because
I'm honoring this one.
Yeah.
Guess a man's word doesn't
matter in the hood, right?
Guess it's just every man
for himself in there.
You see, out here,
character counts.
Without character there can be
no business and...
without business...
well...
what the hell
would we do all day?
Would you mind
stepping off the rug?
Is this what you call
an Eskimo Roll?
I'm thinking Ireland.
Maybe Germany.
Yeah? For what?
- My ten grand vacation.
- Oh.
Yeah, well,
Guinness over Becks any day.
Then Dublin it is.
You're gonna take me to Dublin?
Yeah.
Hey.
Mustang, if we get caught out.
Wingman.
How the hell you been?
We'd like you to come
for a little ride.
Okay, Wingman,
tell me about The Eskimo.
I guess you just don't get
what you pay for anymore.
- Some of us do.
- Oh yeah?
Well, what about Speedo
and Limbo and Santa?
How did those guys
work out for you, huh?
Okay. Now before you die, you're
gonna tell me what this is all about.
The only question is,
how much pain do you wanna endure?
I got cancer of the ass, dickweed.
So screw you, and screw your pain.
You wanna know
what this is all about?
- It's about Bullitt.
- My father?
Lying piece of shit
stole my woman.
Dad banged anything
with a hole.
Hey Bone, what is it
you used to say about him?
He'd bang a rattlesnake
if someone held its head.
- No offense.
- No, none taken.
- Dad had thousands of women.
- Yeah, well, one of them was mine.
- What's that got to do with me?
- His rancid blood runs through your veins.
And that stupid grin of his is
plastered all over your arrogant face.
Where's my cocaine?
I flushed it down the toilet.
- That was ten kilos.
- At least.
Honestly, I thought it was more.
So, you kill my men,
you steal my coke,
over a goddamn woman?
It's called love, sweetheart.
You should try it sometime.
Now, are we done?
Or do you want
to keep on chatting, skippy?
Nah.
Okay, Wingman.
See, that's
how you do it, fellas.
That's how you go out strong.
Kehoe Precinct.
- Yeah, just a sec. Kim.
- Yeah?
Denver Vice.
Kurt, hi.
So, that deep dive into Viking
and White Bull that you asked for...
I got all the files here.
You're the best.
Wasn't easy.
Thank you.
Can you email them over?
I could. Or I could drive them up and
put them right into your warm hands.
'Course, it's a three-hour drive,
so I need a place to stay the night.
Well, there's always my place.
But, here's the thing.
I really need to spend
all night with those files.
Now, if you were to shoot them
right over to me,
I could probably be done
with them by tonight.
And then I could put all my pent
up energy into something else.
Hmm. Okay, well, you got them, baby. Bang.
Right in your inbox.
Oh, they're right in there.
So, how do we wanna do this?
I'm thinking you leave the
door open and your lights off.
Trust me to find...
Hold on a second. What was that?
- I said...
- Oh God, we got an avalanche.
I gotta call you back.
Oh, hey, Gip?
Yes!
Do I look like
a homeless guy to you?
Thirty years ago...
I lived in a hole in the ground below
the house of the guy that dealt me drugs.
One day, he came to me,
stuck out his hand.
I took it.
And we made a deal.
It was a good deal.
Not a great deal.
I should have bought a casino
like my brother.
But a deal is a deal.
And I honored it.
That honor...
was repaid with butchery.
They took my only son.
Today...
my boy will make
his final journey home.
We will stay.
Take our revenge.
I will have blood for blood.
A son for a son.
Hi.
- Goddamn it.
- You forgot.
What?
- What?
- The bullying seminar.
Oh, God.
- Every other parent was there.
- You're right, I forgot about the bullying seminar.
But I'm allowed to forget,
you know why?
Because I wrote a check
for a new computer center.
You write a check, you get to skip on
150 bullying seminars. That's the math.
That's one of the perks
of my business.
You're not a businessman,
Trevor. You're a criminal.
My powder's not good enough for you anymore?
I remember when it was plenty good enough.
When you used
to roll around in it.
Ah.
See, I remember when just
a little bit of my powder...
made you buck like a bronco.
Goddamn.
Close those beautiful
brown eyes of yours.
See if it all
comes back to you.
They needed a host for next week's
fundraiser. I signed you up.
Here.
Three of Viking's drug dealers
have disappeared in the last week.
Tell me who Viking is again?
The Denver drug lord.
White Bull's rival.
Let me ask you a question.
What is it you think we might
do to Viking or to White Bull?
Take them out. Save our town.
We got a little problem
to solve.
We...
we hung an innocent Indian
from a road sign.
And my guess is White Bull's
not gonna like that.
So, has anyone got any ideas on
how we might set things right?
Yeah, maybe we should apologize.
Yeah?
One little screw up shouldn't make us their
bitches. So we send them a short note.
Hey, and what does
this, uh, short note say?
I don't know. How about,
"Sorry about Tonto, won't happen again"?
No.
I'm thinking we need something with a
bit more oomph. Something from our heart.
Yeah, cut off his head.
Stick it in a box and send it to them.
Tell them he's the culprit.
Tell them our old arrangement's
back in effect and good to go.
Get that shit away from me, man.
What the hell's wrong with you?
We've got some of the best pot
stores in the world, man. All legal.
But no, instead you choose to
smoke that dang reservation weed.
Maybe I like it better.
- White people, man.
- Yeah.
You know I had a rat
that was bigger than that thing.
You should try smoking
that shit instead.
That's gross.
Mom!
She gets him this week,
father gets him next week.
Can you imagine
sharing your own son?
Damn.
- Kehoe.
- Hey, it's Kurt.
Hi, Kurt.
You don't deserve this intel.
- Intel?
- First tell me you don't deserve it.
I don't deserve it.
What you got?
A body. Dante Ferstel. Kehoe kid.
Found dead in a Denver alley.
Smack overdose.
So, what's new, right?
Just another
Saturday night sleeper.
And here's the kicker.
Dante was a baggage monkey at the airport.
The Kehoe airport?
Mr. Coxman.
What can I do for you?
It's about your son.
- I didn't know if you'd heard about Dante Ferstel.
- Yeah. He died of an overdose.
Dante worked with your son
at the airport, right?
- Yeah.
- Did you know him?
No.
Kyle never mention him to you?
Is that it?
I guess it is.
I don't understand
why you're here.
Truth?
I don't think
your son was a junkie.
And I don't think
Dante Ferstel was either.
So, what do you think
happened to them?
I don't know.
I was hoping you might be able to
tell me something that could help.
Sorry...
I can't help you.
You can't help me.
I got work to do.
I understand.
Tape.
Taser.
Antibiotics.
Antibiotics?
Yeah, you ever been bitten
by a kid?
Little bastards are nasty.
You almost wish you were bitten by a dog.
Yes?
Okay.
We can't grab him yet.
- Why not?
- They're sending a messenger.
I am the messenger.
Thank you for seeing me.
He's been punished for his deed.
We want peace with you again.
Okay.
I appreciate the gift.
It was thoughtful.
You showed a lot of guts
coming here alone.
But I need a son for a son.
Careful, man!
You might hit a kid.
If you do it again,
I'll kill you.
Yes?
- See you guys tomorrow.
- Hey, Ryan.
Um, I'm taking you home today.
But this is my mom's week
to pick me up.
Yeah, I know, but she got stuck at the
dentist. Asked me to come and get you.
What?
We take him.
- What about the messenger?
- We shot the messenger.
I don't remember her telling me
about a trip to the dentist.
Yeah, she had a root canal
develop some problems.
And your dad said could I pick you up.
So, here I am.
- This is us here.
- What happened to the Tesla?
Shit!
Seatbelt.
- Where's the kid?
- He got away in a van.
What kind of a van?
Said "Kehoe" on it.
We'll find the kid. We'll find the van.
It won't take us long.
Get rid of these two
before they start to stink.
Answer the phone.
Hello?
No, he can't talk right now.
Because he's dead.
Let's go. Three cars.
What about the body?
Minya, take care of this.
I'm busy.
Let the fucking Indian do it.
You don't work for my father,
do you?
Who were those guys anyways?
I don't know.
You don't have to worry
about them.
Right.
They can't take my son
and not call.
That's not how it's done.
Those tepee asswipes.
Those goddamn alkies.
I'm gonna take one of them, I'm gonna hang
them from every road sign from here to Utah.
You take a man's son, you call!
Everybody knows that!
I mean, they took my boy.
My little boy.
Are you insane!
This is my week.
You pick him up without asking? Are you
so damn stupid you'd kidnap your own son?
I can't wait to watch my lawyer write
up the new arrangement. Full custody.
You'll be lucky to get him two
hours a month. Two supervised hours.
A cop in the room with you,
watching you play.
You won't get him alone until
he graduates from high school.
A public high school! With normal kids.
And no stupid diets!
I guess you won't be doing that again.
Right? Uh-huh.
He's not here.
- What?
- Ah...
Turn that song off.
It's a text.
From a different number.
"Sequoia Motel. Room twelve."
"Steve Jobs, baby."
Hello.
A little peepee tepee.
Oh, shit.
I know how this world works. They call with
their demands. I give them what they want.
We get Ryan back.
In 24 hours, I call the police.
In 24 hours, he'll be home.
- You'll burn in hell for this.
- Yeah.
I'll see you there.
Welcome to Kehoe Chateau Montclair.
- We need rooms tonight.
- I'm sorry, you need a reservation.
Excuse me.
A reservation.
Really?
A reser... Oh! No,
I didn't mean it like that.
I meant you need to reserve...
book before you get here
because we're all full.
That's all I meant.
You know what I heard?
You told me and my friends that we
need to go back to the reservation.
Oh, no.
Do you have any idea
what I can do to you...
on Yelp?
You might wanna get
your boss out here.
Or you could take another look.
I will take another look.
- You hungry?
- Sure.
Eggs?
Okay.
- You live here?
- Yeah.
All alone?
Yeah.
You don't have any kids?
No.
You like rock?
I like classical.
It wasn't very smart
bringing me to your house.
Why?
I want to talk to your dad.
Tonight?
In the morning.
They're a bit greasy.
You said you didn't
have any kids.
He went away.
Go on, get in bed.
Where are you gonna sleep?
In my room, down the hall.
- What if I run away?
- There's nowhere for you to go, kid.
You'd freeze to death
out there. Goodnight.
I always get read
a story before bed.
- I don't know any stories.
- You can read me anything. I don't care what it is.
The new C-130 is the crème
de la crme of snow-pushers.
Built to humble Mother Nature,
she has a rated load of three tons.
The Overhausen UTV attachment snow
blowers are made for universal use,
equipped with powerful
modern engines.
They're extremely effective
and flexible.
A capacity of four thousand
tons of snow per hour.
Throwing distance
of a hundred feet.
Yeah.
She is a great machine,
all right.
I've got one of these.
I thought you were a kidnapper.
Not all the time.
Well, can I get a ride in it?
You are going to sleep.
Have you heard
of the Stockholm Syndrome?
Morning, boss.
Did you find him?
Not yet. We will.
Mr. White Bull.
These are some complimentary ski passes.
Good for the whole weekend.
For you and all of your...
friends.
And I just wanna thank you again
for choosing to stay with us.
We know that you do have
other entertainment options.
Thank you.
- Janitor from Ryan's school.
- Janitor, why not?
It's an honor to be here.
You hear the whispers but...
- You have something for me?
- I might.
The van your boy got into.
I've seen it before.
And the guy that was driving
that van, I've seen him too.
Me and my family go up
to the resort in Kehoe.
- You know, the fancy one? Chateau Montclair.
- Oh, yeah.
Well, we're driving up and, you
know, she scoots over and she's...
showing a little appreciation
on the way up, you get my drift?
- I do.
- Yeah.
You ever tried to keep the wheel
straight when someone's...
The van.
Well, like I was saying.
The van that stopped to help me...
that's the same van
that your boy got into.
And the guy who pulled me
out of the ditch that night...
he's the same guy
that picked up your boy.
He's got one of those names
that you never ever forget.
Coxman.
Yeah. We laughed about it
all night long.
- Because what she was doing...
- Oh my God.
- Coxman had a relative.
- And he hasn't spoken with the cops.
Well... how much
did my guy offer you?
Ten grand.
Ten grand it is.
Hey! Hey, check him out.
You're crazy, Avalanche!
You sure you've
done this before?
I was born to fly, white boy.
I have your son.
If you wanna see him alive, come alone.
Yeah, yeah.
I know how it's done.
So, how much
do you want for him?
We'll talk about that when you get here.
2210 Quarry Road. Kehoe.
I'm just leaving Denver.
It's gonna take me about three hours.
Jesus Christ.
Son of a...
- Hey.
- Hey. Taking a day off?
- Main road could use a plow.
- I'll get to it soon.
My nephew. Visiting.
Must be a comfort
to have family in town.
We saw all the cars
at your place.
Yeah.
Look at this.
- So now we know he's banging a hippie.
- No.
On the truck. The company name.
- Open Road.
- It's four miles away.
- Get the men.
- Let's go.
- That was so much fun!
- I need you...
to sit here...
and wait till someone comes
to get you.
- They're headed to Open Road Garage.
- Again. Say what?
Open Road Garage.
On Old Bend Road.
Ryan!
Come on. Inside. Come on, move.
- Why do you have a rifle?
- Just do what I say. Up the stairs, move.
Get in the cabinet.
Why are you mad at me?
I'm not mad at you. It's just...
It's just really important
you do what I say.
You're a good kid.
- What?
- I said don't move.
The last Coxman.
Where is my son?
My business can get very creative,
but I'm an old fashioned kind of guy.
I like to keep things simple.
So if I have to ask you again,
I'm gonna pull out your fingernails...
cut off your fingers,
chop off your hands...
and hack off your nose.
Oh, and that part
about the nose,
you are really not gonna
like that part.
You don't deserve your son.
Take him to the garage.
Bastard!
Got a kid driving
a snow blower headed towards Kehoe.
Get a message...
to Aya.
Tell my wife...
tell her she's a...
What are you doing?
My job.
Subtitles by explosiveskull