The film based on a true event
Name Roles and theatrical events after treatment
Please
You ought to slow down
We have crashed
Are you OK
nothing and you
All right
How do you drive so fast in the evening
Photo looks good thing
what
No need to take pictures
what are you saying
Insurance is very important to go photo
Do not admit a while
Car scratched
Title: wicked pass
August 2005
Near Cheonan took place early this morning murder
Since last year more than murders and disappearances have taken place
But police have not yet solve the case
We also want to solve the case
Solve a case
Holiday promotion
Turn off the siren
This city no one cares
No one there
It's a dirty world
You're right
Look at those hooligans
Those guys have severely pack
Where are you going our investigators
This looks like hell, like hell it
Tai Situ Rinpoche
See site
I'm sorry that you can not do it
Really
Please go past
I am a police officer go
I said do not let me see you
Blocked the entrance
Aside
So hot here today how you go again
The police here do need permission from rogue
police officer
Please return it today was not a good day
What happened today yet
Blocking the road you have to mess mess
Ok
Please return it to you
Bastard you take me for anything
Hello great courage dare to buy me
Well darn thing
The more careful you are
Why go to a police gang obstruct it
carry on
I hope you win
Boss
The police came
Cut him down
He put together a good package good boss
I received a $ 200 gift certificate
Remove ten percent rake
Your bonus is $ 18
Which bastard
turn on
loyalty
Scoundrel
You have been accused of illegally trading Gift Certificates
You have the right to remain silent
The right to a lawyer
let's go
police officer
Come into the room sit it
Brothers out of it
Obediently put it on
Good morning boss
it's me
Your muddy kid is back
what
I sent him to the crime scene to him what you do there
Ask yourself that bastard right
I want to tell Xu Shandong passed
You can not do this to me every month also took the money
Because you have pocketed
Your men have come to disturb my work
I told you not to deal in the store is not it
Opened in the name of someone else's home exchange
Or share the risks you know the rules of the game
I do not do small business
You can not stop him before he came it
I was busy making machines and to open new stores
I want to raise a family of brothers
Ok I'll deal with him
what's up
What do you say
We work it
Where are you
I hung up on the way to the crime scene
I do not want a friend like you
Let me shut the
Fan over
Parked in front of it
Good to listen to you
Come police officer
Thank you for sending me thank you
I gave you a ride each other halfway
Fare here
Damn traffic jam
He knelt on the ground
I want to call the police arrest you
Where did you go to hell in the end
It has been onlookers yet
Let them go away
Reporters and gentlemen, please wait
Then we will take pictures really sorry
You satisfying way to get out of it
Properly cordoned off the area, what did you just
Go away
You're too late
More and more people
All gathered around the
Hello there
You checked his identity yet
We are checked his license plate number and soon there will be news
He died just a few hours ago
Between 3:00 to 5:00
The cause of death was loss of blood
Or a heart attack
This is my preliminary judgment
Young people to take some photos
Car Xiuzhen come
Also look at this
I told you not to address him my name at the crime scene
Sorry car police officer loyal please have a look
what is this
Rear-end it
It seems true
I hope he is not died because
I tend to believe this is from the random murder
A few days ago Thank you very much
Let my men become disabled
Due to the presence of its own rules
anyway
While we each do business but the machine is shared and engineers
Ok
But we have to solve the problem is not it turf
Flexible point
Shan-dong
How the book East
If you can only eat sweets toothache
Do not stir up trouble
I was assigned to the good management of your store
Everyone has their own bottom line
If you crossed that line will die
But I could not even have road
Steve Jobs said
To hunger for knowledge
I did not have capital investors
So I'm still hungry
Mr
That's why he provides technical and engineers for you
My boss magnanimous because you two are friends
Slot machine business
To compete with the bars and clubs are not the same
What are you yelling at the big boys in front of it
Tell us what you have to let us comfortable bastards
I've had enough
Scoundrel
You're so fine you people do
I still see him stare
East book
You just gave me some bread crumbs how also installed played a great
Us how peaceful coexistence
come
It is the boss
Can not you see we speak to
come
Look at this idiot
Now we can the peaceful coexistence
Continued Cup
well
46-year-old Cui Zheng Liu
No bad record enemies debt litigation
Obviously autopsy report
He died of a dozen stab wounds
It appears to be an amateur killer
He just crazy
But if the killer was an amateur and a bit strange
Because without leaving any evidence
Fingerprint what no footprints and no blood hair
Wallet may be gone robbery
But maybe not so much of money
People will be a little small thing killings
Briefing the end of a captain called
it is good
Good Secretary
This case is likely to be robbery and murder
Find people with similar criminal records
Immediately went Executive
Do you support a team work
Three cases is the same as a suspect
What case
July 15 Western Hills reservoir
July 23 Boryeong Sunny Beach Motel
As well as last night's case
In these three cases are the tools of crime knife
From the point of view of the length and width of the knife
It may be the same knife is not the same knife
This is the serial killings
This is not the United States
Korean unable to obtain firearms every murderer is committing the crime with a knife
I was shocked
There are more than 1,000 murders a year
By your logic is half of a person for murder
Are you crazy
You think you are going blending case of other jurisdictions
The murderer cares districts do
If we do not catch him soon there will be more people killed
He was too careful indiscriminate killing white
He could attack again any
You do this job too easy
The case is not what homemade salad
You can not just throw them together
No
I'm not at liberty to mix them in a
These cases occurred in the Chungnam area a week ago
Our informant nothing
This is the intuition
Go to your intuition
Your intuition for you to do gang game room
You are very right time
Is it that they are not criminals
Gangster and murderer not a good thing
Zheng Taixi this and what is your relationship
Do you too want a promotion
My God
I is for promotion
Then promoted to arrest murderers
End of presentation out of it
We caught the murderer go
I did not drive drunk myself
But Mr.
With brothers back
It is the boss
Yes, Mr. President
Xu Shandong is a bit reckless but he is a smart man
He will not be in trouble
Yes, do not worry
good night
I am sorry
Slippery road
It looks okay you go
what
But after all, I hit you
I'm okay you can go
Do you really all right
Yes, all right
Asshole
hateful
what happened
who are you
come
Who Where
The man is not Xu Shandong
Never seen him
Is the boss Xu Shandong
He is not a gang of people
His attack but not without feeling cold
Feel the difference
We're in there who want to kill you
Give me that
It was too dark to see clearly
Out
To find it anyway
Be careful
We are friends
excuse me
Patients look really comfortable ah
what happened again
I brought you a box of Red Bull
I heard that you were stabbed
I received a hospital phone
You must have felt very ashamed of it
After all, you've got a gangster
From each other after all, you're a cop
The police too incompetent
So model citizen ever accident
My God
Model citizen Zhang Dong book
To what happened last night told me
I'll help you catch him
Maybe I can catch him faster
is it
To bet on it
Well bastard
I'll help you catch him
Well I do not mind close to the point
Last night, I stumbled injured
Well last night
You have to go where you walk in and see
Where unlucky bastard stumbled fell out so many stab wounds
Zhang Dong book is black Mercedes car license plate 3849 pairs it
Received a call you later
Scoundrel
Rear-end
White car
I was right bad thing
Oh my God look at you
Are you ok
Sit down
no need
Too hard to endure I can not see you
What happens next
The ink is not dry on the contract you suddenly attacked
what do you want me to do
I now have a lot of brothers crippled
The hospital bills to pay some compensation
And then hand over those that shop and flagship store of the provincial security
I'll compensate you brothers
Those who do shop
That is what you plan to do
East book
If I really dry
Do you still alive.
Think about it
I am also very curious
Who would do this to you
I am leaving
Really embarrassed
A gangster was stabbed me if I would rather commit suicide
I believe I gave two people deal with this case
I will break the breath of these cases
How do not you just leave request
Manpower in this sector is not very enough
Why are you going to clean up someone else's mess
Secretary This is a big case
The other on a broken are broken
Like long tail train column
I'm furious
A witness has survived in the attack
Witnesses take the initiative to come to us yet
Zhang Dong book
What books do Zhang Dong
A few days ago he was stabbed
Do two hours of surgery barely survive
Listen to what you're saying
Think
What kind of fool would promote a gangster attack it
The killer is not a gang of people
I'm sure he's a serial killer
To shut up
It was a gang case I will be assigned to deal with two teams
I warn you not to get involved
Out
Save it, do not cover him
Now is not the time
What you defend him
What else is
You are a bastard
Even if you are right
But the book is Zhang Dong victims
You can apply for an arrest warrant to do
Or go directly to arrest him right
How many crimes he committed
We want to catch him he toppled
He is about to explode
If we do nothing he would kill the murderer
There are three cases we did not catch the murderer
Zhang Dong how can he find books
He is not a gangster police
Let his men go is not a personal thing
And the book saw Zhang Dong
The murderer's face
Out
Your words unjustified
Why do not you tell the landlord
What do birthday
Then how should I do
I have to work hard to make money
Why is so important to the baby's birthday
I'm exhausted
I have two days without sleep Do not tell me what nagging birthday
Your baby birthday do
what
You mentioned that the children
Give me that
Face is sharp
Cheeks thin angular chin
Narrow nose
Big mouth than the nose
Very close
You should not have children.
It's not his fault
Find him before the police
Good Boss
Brothers Where are we
who are you
Thank you for your cooperation
We seized illegal slot machine game room
Everyone should stay
Where is the boss
Let him down
Really wait
Good Continue
Zhang Dong book is respectable he is a crafty bastard
97 machines, 63 table has been tampered with
I go to get hold of an arrest warrant today it
I asked him to wait at
So apply for a warrant of arrest
what do you want
That hurt your people
Tell me everything I would look at another way
If I do not do
Since you bought my boss I'm no threat to you, right
Listen Zhang Dong books
That hurt your people
An ax murderer
He bit strange
And other psychiatric patients with different
You are witnesses
What are you talking about
Why else do you think he wants to provoke you
Most psychiatric patients murdered girl
Or weaker than their people
But there is no law to kill this fool indiscriminate white
If we do not find him soon there will be more people killed
You people in the end what is the problem
Give me the information and continue to do your gangster
This is a win-win thing
I will take him to let him stand trial
and then
Without an end
that's all
Let him sit in a hole
The country's largest luxury casino built in
This skyscraper penthouse
The entire area around the building we Zeus
Will become the most popular place in town
Enough of this nonsense I hear this place has been abolished
hateful
Those who lined up to buy pre-construction are gone
Investors naturally delay does not give money
You happen that afterwards was full of strange rumors
Chungju area is another problem
Xu Shandong men are entering our site
I have not found him yet
We found his car in a country lane
His car it
Car at the rest stop a few days
My men found
Where is the car now
We brought back
A few days ago there was a murder in Sintanjin
and this
Discarded or lost
They found that at three kilometers outside the car
Save it
It is the boss
Hello there
My book is Zhang Dong
What a surprise
You know murder Sintanjin do
what happened
That bastard is dry
what
How did you know
We found his car in there
My game I call the shots
I came here risking their lives
Then someone came and grabbed my ankle
What I can do I can only put his arm cut off
I can not cut off his ankle
But after a gang of guys destroy the reputation
Disappeared
brothers
Whoever provoke me share the responsibility
Reputation is everything a gang
I'll chop him
Made public
You are telling a cop you want to kill it
We do it is legal not allowed
A bad person will catch the bad guys do another
No
Two bad guys will catch the worst person
This is his car keys
You do not treat me as a cop it
I can arrest you immediately
Why can not
You caught him more than I would like
I will provide manpower to pay
Share Information
help each other
That in the end it
He put it into two halves
Who grabbed his disposal who would
So if I left him to catch the proceedings
If you catch him you buried him yet
Deal if you have so much confidence, then
Well, it's a deal
You will regret this
how old is he
35-year-old
This guy is pretty handsome
I can not see dark rain
Use this to keep in touch
Gangs and police join forces arrested devil
This is so exciting
Scoundrel
I'm in the same boat with you I have to be safeguarded
We can not draw up a contract
I give you with high-tech recording it
hateful
This villain to use his brains
That's why I do not believe sliver
I was too tolerant of you.
Listen bastard
Once this is something I'll beat you up first scoundrel
He also stabbed Zhang Dong book
He is Sintanjin case behind what this means
If we act according to my way
Kexin fell swoop we detected five cases
35-year-old male of average height
He only during the night of his murder from the point of view of the perpetrators mode
Not affect the position and only with a knife
This is the two knives in a
Preparation of a knife or stick a knife ready to commit crimes
So far no other clues
We will catch him
I made a deal and police
Of course, we will not tell Secretary
How can we trust the police do
How can we believe that gangs do
Who believe
We need manpower to catch the murderer
This is not the case that we can handle their own
We told the director it
and then
Crime Unit will be involved
Media involved to take away all the glory
Not only that Secretary Zhang Dong book protection
This is the only way to solve the case
The Secretary is a mess
Zhang Dong books have seen his face in his car
Only his portrait painting is not enough
We need to fingerprint and DNA
We find the use of gang murderer
Then we took him to intervene
I will use them and then they finished behind
We are also citizens pay taxes
Let us for once police support
From the outside it like a disused warehouse
But tens of thousands of gaming machines are manufactured here
And then sent around the country
Scoundrel
We'll find some clues
His hair may be even his fingerprints gas row
We must not be found
We'll search every inch of the place
let us start
Put all the dirty work left to Zhang Dong simple book
We all current cases are combing again
This is Sintanjin murder monitor screen
His unique mode
So far he has used a vehicle in all murder
He elusive elusive
We know that everywhere yet solved crimes but certainly there are other cases
Do not forget that from the perspective of the serial killer case
If you find any information to report to me
He is a ticking time bomb
Look at the case in other regions could explode at any place
Do not swagger
Okay
Good good sir
We will solve the case after locking gang
Cleanly
Ultimately up to us to seize this murderer
In that we get rid of it before it Xu Shandong
Scoundrel
Are you crazy
What are you doing here
In the end what you want
I'm waiting for you
I think you hurt my back
You should not scare me
I was shocked
I want to drink too
So comfortable
Can you look at this it
very urgent
what is this
It is nothing special
I found some hair and blood
Tell me who is
Zheng Taixi
It's not like you how you
what happened
It's a dirty world
I'd like to hands
On the dirty world
This is very strange murderer
He left the weapon to us
Murder and disappearance maritime police
Cry over spilled milk
Now dead gangster
What would you do
What should we do
Do you have a mouth words to speak ah
Xu Shandong's case to the Second Team
They will investigate
What are you doing
Do not stare at the display
Out
Immediately went out
Look for evidence to solve the case
At least pretend to care
Hurry
Well yes
brothers
You want to die
what happened
This stuff is nothing special about it
I just got the results
I do not believe in that
Come tell me what
There are other people do
DNA testing to the most recent murder victim's Chungnam
is it
In addition to other people known to the victim in
No
This should not be ah
You have to correctly detect it
nobody else
But that is not a problem
Out of some bad things
Just a minute
go on
Detected on the weapon Xu Shandong
Truck drivers and factory owner of the dog DNA
what
That all this is just one person
This will be officially classified as a serial killer
I have to go
Zhang Dong book is it you did
It's you
Mr. I call you back later
Answer me bastard
Are you crazy
You idiot men back
hateful
Here is his home when he
Who else do you like that ah
We talk later
A policeman and a gangster This is what you are doing
You're not a cop it
Tell me bastard
Do you kill Xu Shandong
For me to kill him
I believe a gang is my fault
You believed in me
Fool would show Xiaopodupi
Nothing has changed
We'll catch him
do you understand
wait
It's all over
I'll investigate your
Brother does not matter
Since July this year, the region's murder
It has been confirmed as a serial killer
The transfer of these cases to the police Crime Unit with the Cheonan joint investigation
So that these cases are no longer stagnant
Murder cause of action in each district police station processing
But by focusing on the investigation
With new hope to solve the case
I hope this ordeal will end residents to restore calm life
Let's connect the reporters
You come early ah
Dong Zhe
Outside the hotel I was a leader of the murder in September 3
It is said that this murder victims want is Xu Shandong
This man Chungnam area of a violent gang leader
It is said that he was involved in a turf tray
If you start to put a case to us
Would not have come to this
Murder is not a children's game
You guys just destroyed investigation
In still others here say something nice bar
Do you have any question
am I wrong
Yes folks
I'm having trouble scoundrel
Come at me
Damn feed stop
In Xu Shandong murder scene found a knife
There are other victims of DNA
Ministry of Public Security set up a special task force investigating the case Xu Shandong
And all the killer might be the same person's murder
that's not me
The Task Force by the Regional Crime Unit and homicide team
As well as the country's best side write the serial killer who formed part
We will conduct a thorough investigation
As well as the help of forensic
The police are also expected to be attended by a large number of gangs Xu Shandong funeral
The heart they would remain vigilant
Here I'm surprised to see you
Of course I'll come he is my friend
Hey
Now come
Why should I past
Pack your own mess here
who are you
Someone used my knife to kill Xu Shandong
If you want to kill him yourself you'd better find something
If the Crime Squad caught him before you and I will be finished
Your whole life is so yet
I really sympathize with you poor police
Do not commit any crime you idiot
If you do not like me you ought to unemployed people
That is life there is prey predator
There was stabbed victim
He attacked me from behind me unprepared
But I'm still holding his knife stabbed him
stop
what happened
You stabbed him yet
Yes what's the matter
I seem to find something
what happened
Scoundrel
Zhang Dong how the book is going
Who are these guys
A group of bastard
Dodge
Go to hell bastard
Hey Brother
Scoundrel
The end of the stop bar
You'd better go I'll wrap him
it's OK
He just bled
It's just blood
Bastard out of here
The police claimed that there is sufficient evidence to arrest the perpetrators of the killing Xu Shandong
Seize suspect only a matter of time
Murder suspect fixed his way and is active in the area
Where are you dear
Apocalyptic nap thing
His face was how the
Wake up fool
What have you been doing
Go to hell
Where are you going
To hold
This is a case of abduction
Chun-ho already there to talk to him rendezvous
Why do with the kidnapping is now so important
We have to catch a serial killer
Do not mention this matter
Can not you see it in the office Crime Unit
They are a team with so cooperation deal with the kidnapping bar
From the beginning I told you this is a serial killer
Now a team of Crime Unit and it
They know what in the end
They have no clue as to the fucks
I've had enough
You just say what
shut up
You did say it was serial killer, but there is no evidence
You were with evidence or witnesses yet
If you are so powerful that he is not in prison now Why do
hateful
The victim was a venture capitalist
Tai Situ Rinpoche
The attackers should be very close with him quickly investigate
Zhang Dong books do you provoke
This is how the face
What must have happened
Enough talk
To his colleagues informed him of a woman
How many times have
Why do you always replace the meeting place
He still alive.
If you want the money Lord let him answer the phone
This is the last Woer Ming see Jill snack bar
immediately
What are you doing to go
This package is for you to pay it
give it to me
Why should she contracted the woman
Go to hell
This is your cooperation with the police to tell the world
Who is on the roof
He was on the roof
Dong-chul he went to the north
Where is he
Pei led him into the main street
Hey
What do you in the end
Chun-ho intercept him from the side
To stop
I do not see him
He was there on Main Street
Pei where are you children
Stop Hold
This bastard
I go down
Quickly
I do not see him here
I will kill you where he went
Keep up
Upstairs fast
stop
He had just turned the corner and blocked him from the front
Him which way to go
In the piece there
Go that way
Why are you holding the bag you do not know what was inside
Why do you roar me what I did wrong
I was asked to take it
Who
Tell us or you have to go to jail
I've never seen him
He was alone for dinner so I showed him the bag
He gave me $ 20
how does he look like
It looks very ordinary
He ate only what you
A bottle of soju
Jinro brand
Where in the bottle
Only different label
All bottles are the same
I wish you have fun
Hell's label
Dong-chul is the Executive
Only to find brand Jinro get it
Not only to find brand Jinro
I do not believe in that
The bottles are the same
Do not work hard
Are you serious
How about the steering wheel cover
The earliest results came out today
I charge $ 2000 per machine
Thank you
If you need I will provide you with technical support
It's not too expensive yet Zhang Dong book
If Zhang Dong book can achieve his goal
We would be very happy not it
I do not know whether I should have scored such a good business
Take a look at the fate of Xu Shandong
Be careful everyone
After the book was stabbed Zhang Dong Xu Shandong killed
His assistant disappeared
Continue to eat your dinner
What are you doing here
This person go first
We found a strange fingerprints
Part is complete
He could erase it
I found a trace he left behind
His whereabouts are unknown
Put the steering wheel is also found in his blood
He did not come back for about 3 months
Where is he going to say it
Then he went to work every month
This time he went for a long period of time
I reported the incident afraid of him what had happened
He has any questions for me
There is no problem at all
He never rent arrears
And never drink
He is a faithful Christian
Clean innocent life is a good man
We found a strange fingerprints
Part is complete
He could erase it
017-684-2784
Find all information on this number owner
Do you have kidnappers voice files you
Sent directly to me right away
I heard that you have paid for his funeral
You're a loyal friend
Also do this to me
I told you it is not good to eat
Damn it
Why did you ruin the Dayton delicious lunch
For your benefit I am careful everywhere
Eat your dinner
Please continue it
I sent you a photo to view the next immediately
Listen to this
This is the last Woer Ming see Jill snack bar
immediately
I am sorry
Slippery road
But after all, I hit you
35-year-old Xu Jing Jiang
He grew up in an orphanage by his father abused
No criminal record
Every day to his 70-year-old mother called
They are used in a disposable cell phone
Before August, he is calling from Chungcheong
But then he called from all over the country
We traced his phone calls from mainly Ansan City
But mostly from the region
Large Bunkyo it
Yes
There are several universities
So there are a lot cheaper rooms and apartments
There are thousands of old houses
so troublesome
This means that
He then stabbed Zhang Dong hid the book here
Scoundrel
Your upbringing which went
Zhang Dong book
He is a friend of yours bastard
Damn gang
All you note any different
Scoundrel
How dare you hands
Damn let me go
You want to die
come
brothers
If we do not catch him
We would have been ended Do not you know
If we are in the same boat
Whatever we have to tide over the crisis
Let's go
You have a picture yet
Have
You have only one task
At all costs to find this bastard
Yes
Low-key
See anyone like him
Immediately call these guys
5 pairs
The person in charge of each group report once every 8 hours 3 times a day
A large area as the center of Beijing
Search a designated area and then expand the search
Cheap motel and hotel rooms for single men
Never seen him
Short-term rental lease long-term hotel
Be sure to check these places
Afternoon city center
Market dock and other public areas.
Search bar game room Internet cafe
Search karaoke nights and other shops
do you understand
understand
Beijing large area in the middle of the river to the area
The place closed
Yes, I hurry out
Ok
When the bus to
Young people come here to feed
Took
I'm fine.
Ok
Thank you
What about you
Good to stay in school
Hey Zhang Dong book
No time for them to dinner
Let them work you have to let them eat ah
Woosung will soon come
Your umbrella too
Do not pretend saint
you
Call me
Do not take things from strangers
He was a gang
You look more like a gangster than he
what
Do not laugh
Goodbye careful
Thank you
We may have many different pairs of hands
But we only have a common heart
Until the end of life
We are a family
Thank you, boss
I would like to join you
My life is a mess
I can not believe you work together
When the police take it
We take your life to work so they do not need these salaried
You were a bastard gang me a drink
We say thank you to drink like Hello
I brought them wine to drink heartily
A variety of business you have mastered ah
You want to join it
Should I join you
You should join
You will see that looks meteoric rise in gang in
Shut up and drink a cup
Give me a glass of good
Do not
I did not turn back
My cup oil
Dash sing us a song mood is not very good
My brother used to be the man of the band trainee
I'll give you sing a song Awesome
1   2
1 2 3 4
Hello quiet
Put that in turn
High school girls were killed on the way home
She was killed when
Age is still small
Police ruled out revenge killings
And pointed out that the motive could be sexual assault or murder
Woosung
Give me up
It is the boss
Search every corner near the No. 32 bus route
What we missed
North West crossing the busy central square as well as fertile slope within 1 km
Hurry
He must remain vigilant here
We come from a large area from Beijing Chung-down
I searched in the central square
I think I found him crossing the busy motel here
Let our people also search the collection vehicle
It was seen crossing the busy motel
Do not just search the motel to see nearby bars and karaoke rooms
Excuse me I am the police
His room No. 304
What do you
Tell me where he is
He had just left the
I found him a police officer
We must remain vigilant to find him
Stay in the car to see if he will not come back
Do not act rashly
We have to let him in
Do your fair share of things scoundrel
Cancel Search sent three people to come here
Buddy children do not move
Down
Nice to meet you bastard
Idiot
He drove like a fool
Hey
Parking bastard
parking
Step aside
hateful
Hateful bastard
what are you doing
I caught him
over there
Scoundrel
Go to hell
Woosung not
Wake up
over there
Go
hateful
Where are you
This bastard is mine
Where are you children
Zhang Dong locked position book
He took his murderer found
fasten your seatbelt
Before I kill you give me a good living
In the rest stop parking
what
I am starving
really interesting
What do we have different
It is obvious that you do not see it yet
I'm stabbing you a bastard
It is not very interesting
Playing with the lives of others
He drove to the city of Cheonan
Monitoring toll station to take him
Scoundrel
You know the process of killing
When you feel the best
shut up
Do you like it Roumo
I want you to cut to pieces
Then thrown everywhere
Scoundrel
This is the best moment
Life and death hold in your hands when
Try it
carry on
kill me
You know what they're talking about it
After you kill so many people think you can continue alive.
So you should kill me
Shut up
If you speak blood squirt
Sorry folks
I was a policeman
Nice to meet you bastard
Jiang Jing Xu I arrest you on charges of murder
Even if you are like the devil
Also have the right to hire a lawyer
Right to remain silent
Anything you say may
Become evidence in court
If you can not afford a lawyer
We will use taxpayers' money to appoint a scoundrel for you
what's the situation
Is not it obvious
He is a serial killer
what are you doing
Come back home
tidy up
Come on baby
Wait a bit to get out
Let's get out of the past
In the investigation of the kidnapping in September
Cheonan City police obtained a key piece of evidence in order to find the Jiang Jing Xu
He is currently receiving treatment due to minor injuries
After which he will receive further police investigation
After the trial and then handed over to prosecutors
Next News
Slot machine game room recently become a social problem
The prosecution traced to the game room is operated by the gang
Zeus now wanted gang leader Zhang Dong book
Zhang Dong book operates dozens of slot machine game room
By illegal modifications
And made a bundle selling street cabinets
Currently unaccounted for Zhang Dong book
It's all you did it
No
You convince the world that he was the murderer but now it
There is no evidence yet
Our evidence is circumstantial evidence
There is no concrete evidence that he killed these people
Even if I was a judge
It would not sentence him to death
what is this
This is a knife
Is your knife crime
What is your outlook on life
No matter how I think I can not understand why you
Because you are not a person
What is your outlook on life
The police do a good or a model citizen
You can not answer me
Who would follow a life of it
We did so because we live
I first murder when wearing gloves
But they do not follow the slip has been moved as I think of
You have to stab one go
The kind of feeling into the thorn
You can feel from the fingertips
like this
There are these photos
what
Order completely wrong
There is evidence to prove that I did it
Even though I was sentenced to death
You know I will not die
Go to hell
I'm going to kill you
Let me kill him
If you accept the death penalty in the absence of evidence to the
That's murder
The real demons are those who look kind of criminals
Think about the creator and executor of the law as
You really do have this right
If, as innocent
Then I also
You said you've never seen it this knife
Yes
This knife between July 2005 and September killed five victims
Objection, Your Honor
The prosecution did not provide any evidence in this trial
Prove my client to have any contact with the knife
Not imply that the knife belonged to him
Yes, you are right
This knife has nothing to do with the defendant
At least up to now is
Your Honor, we ask a witness to appear in court next
He is evil Xu Jiang in Beijing by the sword the only survivor
Please witness to testify in court
You have courage in front of me
Damn you look a mess
We pay taxes so that you arrest and kill those bastards
This is the law
It arrests punish them
This is to protect us its meaning
Shut up you should let me kill him
You are my last resort
Let us use the law to kill him
what did you say
You go to surrender
Are you crazy
Do you kill Xu Shandong
I killed
I've had enough
Once you open and I had to die
Do not make me use this
Then surrender to testify
You're the only witness
Have you and I can put all of his murders linked to the witness stand
We go die together
I swear the evidence I shall by Almighty God that the truth should be
The truth is only truth
Your Honor
Prosecution witness was a gang leader wanted by
Accused of several serious crimes
He is a suspect in other cases
It does not affect him to testify
I agree
witness
How do you prove that the defendant stabbed the person you are
I like such people are often stabbed
Before they were buried, I will not forget what they look like the
Is that bastard stabbed me
After I was stabbed
Find someone immediately drew this sketch
Your Honor, the portrait just Zhangdong book personal portrait
It is not as substantive value and scientific value of the evidence
Your Honor
This is the ward record witness
Just after the attack
Witness a gang boss
He stabbed his normal
Because he could be treated for stab wounds others
He violated the rights of the accused blasphemy law authority
Damn that fool so many words
lawyer
witness
If your family was killed in the same way
You will say it
Rights of the accused do
How he deserves the right to do
That bastard to kill for pleasure
I am also a bad guy but he should not be alive
Evidence it
I show you
That night he hit my car forced me to get off the view
Then next to me nudged me twice
After a struggle he stabbed me in the chest
I tried to grab his knife to the finger
If I were an ordinary person I would have died on the spot
His clothes off
I stabbed him in the left chest
He should have a wound there
Then check his hand you will find a lot of scars
Those who use the tool will be minor cuts in the assassination of others
It will damage your fingernails
At last
That bastard wrote this
His handwriting analysis you will find a match
FYI Xu Shandong is my friend
Xu Shandong and his assistant died
I feel very sorry for Woosung
But if Jiang Jing Xu everything shake out
We can say is dry Woosung
The defendant had an extremely violent
Contempt for human life
As well as victims of suffering
Weigh the crimes he deserves to give judgment
Thank you sir
Therefore, the defendant Jiang Jing Xu
Sentenced to death
turn back
salute
Our boss came to greet him
Good afternoon Boss
I have one condition
What conditions
I put him in the same prison in
We played the game with three lives
We have to end it