[man on PA]
We have touchdown.
Donor is on site.
I repeat, donor is on site.
[indistinct shouting]
The donor signed the releases.
We're clear?
We are cleared.
[man on PA] Attention,
donor en route to main lab.
All techs and personnel,
please report
to the operating theater.
I repeat, all techs and personnel
please report
to the operating theater.
[man] Ready?
[clangs]
[William] Time since cardiac death?
Uh, seven hours, 15 minutes.
Proceed.
[man] Stand by for commencement.
[woman] Stand by for neural probe.
Uh, neural tissue intact.
Protoplasmic integrity looks good.
We have a viable cortex.
Do you concur?
I concur.
Ball's in your court, William.
This man is dead.
Yet his neurological data
is still accessible.
We are going to take his biological brain,
imprint it into that synthetic brain,
to replicate the human mind.
Ed, boot the mapping sequence.
- [woman] Positioning optimal.
- [computer] Target acquired.
[Ed] Lachrymal targeting complete.
Stand by to engage neural probe.
[woman] Stand by for neural probe.
- [man] Stand by.
- [electronics whirring]
[equipment clangs]
[woman] Initiating ocular transfer.
[man] Mem drive is online.
[beep]
Okay, mapping confirmed.
Remove the donor.
Stand by to initiate neural imprint.
[electronic pulsing]
Initiate.
[electronic humming]
Scott, try protocol Alpha 9,
please, in Parietal.
[electronic pulsing]
Thank you.
Temporal annex zone online,
looking good.
Frontal online looking good.
Okay.
New theta, connectome protocol 345.
Beta one, two-phase application.
[electronic chirping]
P1 site parameters.
AP insular. Primary action.
Stasis modality, exceptional.
And translate.
Finalize.
Confirm.
All states, go.
All functions, go.
[monitor chirping]
[electronics pulsing]
Imprint complete.
Margaret, energize the body.
- [Margaret keying]
- [electronics humming]
[circuitry chirping]
Sergeant Kelly.
[circuitry sparking softly]
[metallic clicking]
Do you hear me?
Sergeant.
[metallic joints clicking]
[distorted male voice]
Who am I?
[William] Sergeant.
You've transitioned to a synthetic body.
[Kelly gasps]
[breathing erratically]
[William] Try to relax.
You're coming online.
It'll take some time.
[Kelly] Huh?
Who am I?
[William] Sergeant. Try to relax.
[Kelly, furiously] Who am I?
Sergeant.
[Kelly gasping]
[William] Sergeant! Sergeant Kelly!
- [Kelly] Who am I?
- [William] Sergeant Kelly!
[Kelly groaning]
Turn it off. The imprint failed.
- [beeping]
- It severed the override!
- [man] No!
- [circuits sparking]
[Ed gasping]
[Kelly groaning]
[Kelly] Who am I?
[electronic humming fades]
[circuits sparking softly]
[indistinct announcements on PA]
- It spoke.
- They've done that before.
No, they've vocalized before,
made noises, this one spoke.
I can't tell you how amazing
that would have been eight months ago.
Today, it just annoys the shit out of me.
It's progress, undeniable progress.
In my world,
progress is measured in results,
which we don't have.
The truth is, I'm not sure
how much longer I can keep the lights on.
Turns out, colossal and repeated failure
tends to spook shareholders.
Who knew?
This is my life's work.
I moved my family here, made sacrifices.
I promise you, I am this close.
Well, it just isn't close enough,
is it, Bill?
But don't let it ruin your weekend
or anything.
[watch beeps]
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry I'm late.
- It's okay.
- How's it going, honey?
The kids aren't even packed yet.
They're wild. [giggles]
[pop music playing]
Daddy!
Zoe!
How's it going? How was your day?
Matt!
[Matt] Not in the house, I know.
The troll will not stop spying
on me with that thing.
- It is called a spy drone.
- Okay.
So, go pack now
and don't jump on the furniture.
[door opens]
- Hola, Foster family.
- [Zoe] Ed!
Hey, nugget.
Can you feed him once a day?
But don't overfeed him.
- I'll show you the food. Come on.
- Okay.
Hey, uh, you talked to Jones?
Something like that.
Okay, well, what did he say?
Did you get fired?
- What's "fired"?
- No, I didn't get fired.
- Who got fired?
- Daddy.
- What?
- Nobody got fired.
Well, I thought you were a goner, man.
Wait, what's going on?
Uh, our test subject ripped
itself apart earlier today.
- It was pretty brutal.
- What's "brutal"?
It spoke, Mona.
345, the test subject.
It actually spoke.
It spoke?
If it could speak, then it could feel.
We shut it down as soon as possible.
You can't keep bringing people
back from the dead
until you have this stuff worked out.
How many times have you had a patient
flatline in ER and you brought them back?
My patients don't rip themselves apart.
She's got a point there, William.
[chuckles]
I should probably, uh...
find Sophie for the fish situation.
William, honey, I believe in you.
But I don't like where this is headed.
People could suffer.
The first heart transplant
patient survived 18 days.
He suffered. Was that wrong?
No. No.
[William] I'm on the verge
of a breakthrough, Mona.
Soldiers, accident victims, Alzheimer's.
Lives that won't have to be cut short.
But something's preventing the synthetic
from achieving watershed consciousness.
Maybe there's more that
makes us human, like a soul.
We're the sum total of what has happened
to us and how we've processed it.
That's what makes us us.
It's all neurochemistry.
Do you really believe that?
That's all I am?
Your children?
Just pathways, electrical signals
and chemistry?
You have kids that love you
and a wife that adores you.
And we have a scientist.
Do you think I should quit?
- [Zoe] Hi.
- [both] Hi.
I'm just worried you're losing sight
of what's right and wrong.
I won't.
Trust me.
[Ed] Okay, have fun.
Oh, I'm gonna get you back.
What's the boat called again?
It's... [sighs]
It's called the Cheatin' Hussy.
- [Zoe] Daddy!
- [Ed] Uh...
Keys are in the bait box.
[chuckles] We don't do that.
- Daddy!
- [William] All right, thanks.
- We'll see you Sunday night.
- Yeah. Okay, man.
Everybody in?
[Mona] Seat belts.
The Foster family ferry to Funtown
is ready to sail.
- [Zoe] Yay!
- [Matt] Really, Dad?
- Actually...
- Hoist the mainsail, Ahab.
[thunder rumbles, cracks]
I spy, with my little eye,
something that is...
Bored, embarrassed?
Possibly adopted?
That would be me.
Hey, Dad, when we get there,
can we go fishing on the boat?
- Absolutely.
- Are we almost there?
Well, we could just wait
for the boat to float by.
You know what they say.
If you don't like the weather,
just wait five minutes.
[thunder rumbles]
I can't see anything.
Can you see anything?
I feel like we should pull over.
- [truck horn blaring]
- [Zoe and Mona scream]
Okay? Everybody okay?
- Holy shit! Holy shit!
- That was close.
- [thunder cracks]
- [hail pelting]
- Whoa!
- [Mona gasps]
- [glass shatters]
- [Zoe] Daddy!
- [William] Hold on!
- [Sophie] Oh, my God! Mom!
[Zoe] Mommy!
[children screaming]
- [Sophie] Zoe, hold on!
- [Zoe] Mommy!
[Zoe] Daddy! [shrieks]
[glass shatters]
[water sloshes]
Mona. Mona.
Kids?
Oh, God
Sophie! Matt!
Zoe! Zoe!
[William groans]
Oh, Zoe!
Oh, my baby girl!
[sobbing]
Mona! Mona!
[dialing]
[line ringing]
[sets brake]
[car alert chiming]
William?
What's up? What's going on?
[William] I told you, no questions.
Where is it?
It's all in the back.
Oh, shit.
William.
What the hell happened, man?
I need you to do something for me, Ed.
Oh, no. No way.
- I can't.
- They are not gone!
Not yet.
William, we need to call the police.
Or something, man. I mean...
William. What the hell?
Boot the mapping sequence.
[Ed] We cannot do this, man.
Boot the mapping sequence, Ed!
[device beeping]
[monitor hums]
[computer] Edward Whittle.
Access granted.
[Ed] Okay.
Just because I think I can do it,
doesn't necessarily mean I can, okay?
There is a reason
human cloning is banned.
And just because it's hard to do
is only half the issue here.
Just let me know what we need.
[sighs] God. Look, William,
I know you've been through hell,
but you need to understand
something here, okay?
The first few animals
I cloned came out blind.
Their skulls were deformed.
Their internal organs weren't
internal anymore, man.
That's what a mistake here means.
And if we make a mistake,
I need to know
if you're prepared to terminate.
We just won't make a mistake.
[sighs]
Okay, uh...
Those are pods.
Can I clone a human being in one?
Technically, yeah, it's possible.
But, look, William, if this works,
their brains are gonna
come out like infants,
okay, a total blank slate,
and not to rub salt
in the wound here tonight,
but you haven't exactly
worked out all the kinks
for transferring a mind.
Do I need to remind you of
what's happened every time you've tried?
We've transferred biological to biological
on cloned animals.
- Rats, monkeys.
- Not human beings, man.
You've seen it. We can do it.
What if something horrible goes wrong?
Something already has.
Ed, nobody can know what happened.
[whispering]
I need you to get rid of the bodies.
[nervously] William, I don't know if I...
I'm begging you. I can't do it.
[scoffs] Okay.
Okay, I'll, uh...
I'll meet you at the house.
[door clangs shut]
[truck beeping]
[beeping]
[truck engine stops]
[lock clangs]
What's in the barrels?
Uh...
Components, building blocks.
Amino acids, fructose, accelerants.
You know, just a ton of primordial ooze.
Everything you need to build a... "you,"
you know?
There's only three pods.
Three's not four. I need four pods.
Yeah, I know. Well, there weren't four.
I need four pods, Ed.
I can maybe get another one,
next quarter, maybe.
Do not tell me there aren't four!
What do you want me to do here?
Okay, these pods are $1.7 million each.
I'm not a freakin' genie here.
I can't sneeze out another pod.
Sorry, William.
[Ed] William?
You all right?
[William] Pick a name.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
There aren't enough pods.
Pick a name.
No way, man. You pick it.
Please? Please, goddamn it.
Please, pick a name!
William, no, no!
- Pick the name!
- No!
This one's on you.
You wanted this. You pick it.
You pick the damn name.
[sobbing]
[indistinct voices]
[Ed] You gotta watch the levels.
The levels are everything.
I've seeded the pods with their DNA.
But you got to keep an eye on them
all the time. Never leave them alone.
If the chemical balance isn't maintained,
the clones will die,
and we can't just start over,
so, you need to watch the levels.
Okay, and they'll all be done
at the same time, right?
[Ed] Okay.
Uh... Ah, shit.
This just got a lot more difficult.
Tell me you can do that.
Uh... yeah, yeah, I just gotta
compensate with something.
- Ed?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it can be done.
Oh, uh, where is your backup generator?
In case we lose power.
- I don't have a generator, Ed.
- Okay.
Is there something I should know?
Yeah. The pods can't lose power.
Ever. If there is a seven-second
power interruption,
well, then,
that will throw off the levels,
and I just told you
how important those things are.
- So, yeah, we need a generator.
- It's 2:00 a.m.
Nothing's open.
Well, shit, man, I don't know.
What do you want from me?
I can't think of everything. All right?
I am so far in over my head at this point.
And so are you, man. You know that?
Is there anything else?
Uh, no, I think that's it.
[motorbike revving]
[Ed] That is a lot of batteries.
In 17 days, they're coming out.
You got till then to figure out
how to give them watershed consciousness.
If, by some miracle,
we can pull this off...
what about Zoe?
Every memory they had is in here.
I'll delete her.
I'll delete the memory of her
on the drives.
[scoffs] You can do that?
[William]
Humans lose memories all the time.
Beta amyloid proteins.
Neurofibrillary tangles.
I'll corrupt the memory
on the mem drive.
Upload the new neural map.
They'll never remember her.
We are going straight to hell.
Thank you.
Good luck, man.
- [bicycle bell rings]
- [Zoe] Mommy, look!
- [indistinct talking]
- [Zoe] Daddy!
[William] Zoe!
[indistinct conversations,
family laughing]
[Zoe] Ready, Daddy?
Matty stole my unicorn.
[Mona] Oh! Zoe, honey...
[voices fade]
[all singing] Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Zoe...
[Zoe] Hi, Daddy. Hi, Mommy.
[singing] Happy birthday to you
[Zoe shrieks]
[straining]
- [banging continues]
- [William groaning]
[doorbell rings]
[rings]
[pounding on door]
- [doorbell rings]
- [pounding]
[monitor beeps]
- [man] Mr. Foster?
It's the police.
Good morning, officers.
Do you speak Spanish?
- No. Sorry.
- Well, pardon my English.
I'm Officer Perez. This is Rodriguez.
We're following up
on some recent car robberies.
Somebody stole the batteries
out of every car on the block.
How odd.
Perez: Did they get you, too?
No. No, they didn't.
Ah, you're the lucky guy.
Yeah.
Nothing out of the ordinary?
Well, if you see anything
or anybody suspicious, let us know.
Will do, Officer.
Have a good day.
[officers speaking indistinctly]
Okay. All right.
That happened.
[Jones] Edward.
I feel compelled to comment
on the noticeable lack
of Bill around here.
Wouldn't happen to know
anything about that, would you?
Uh, well, just that he has pneumonia.
Uh, the walking pneumonia.
- Walking?
- With pneumonia, yeah.
[Jones] Would you convey
a message for me?
I spoke to the board today.
Unless 345 works, we're getting shut down
at the end of the quarter.
Shut down?
Would you like a nice reference letter?
Uh... yes.
Uh, I'm sure he'll be in soon.
You know William.
He's got a really strong immune system.
[beeping]
- [William keying]
- [monkey chattering softly]
[computer] Test subject 221 updated.
Transfer of consciousness from
original subject to clone successful.
Animal consciousness can be transferred.
Why not human?
- What am I missing?
- [monitor chirping]
- [phone autodialing]
- [line ringing]
[cell phone buzzing]
- [Ed] William.
- Yeah.
Hey, I just, uh, talked to Jones,
and he said that
if we don't get 345 working,
- he's gonna shut us down.
- Oh, shit.
Yeah, there is $8. 7 million
worth of Bionyne equipment
in your basement, and, uh...
if he shuts us down,
they're gonna come looking for it,
and you wanna know
the scientific term for that?
Royally and utterly boned.
So, what are we gonna do?
- Okay, get over here.
- What?
- [stammers] Where? There?
- Yeah, here.
- Why?
- I gotta go to work.
- You have to watch the pods!
- Okay, man, you don't have to yell at me.
I'm not...
Okay, so I was yelling.
Look, just hurry up, man,
and, uh, you have pneumonia.
- What?
- [phone clicks]
- [beep]
- [computer] Dr. William Foster.
Access granted.
There he is. Hi, Bill.
Jeez, you look like hell.
[coughing]
Can I get you anything?
Maybe something herbal?
What do you have, exactly?
Pneumonia.
What a trouper!
Ah, you're here.
I need you to review the data links
before I can get to work
on 345's neural junction specs.
- Yeah, look, not now.
- Jones is all over us.
William, we're waiting on your okay
of the MF interface
for the server replacements.
Get in line.
Okay, okay.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Why?
No reason.
[house door opens]
- Hello.
- Oh, I'm so sorry about Matt.
You don't remember me.
Matt's teacher. Mrs. Barnes?
Oh, I can explain.
Your cousin told me.
Sorry to come by unannounced.
But Matt hadn't been to school
in a few days
and I couldn't get your wife
on her cell phone.
And I know we're not supposed
to have favorites, but...
Well, I hope that clears everything up.
Mm-hmm.
- Happy holidays.
- Hey, is she gone?
- What happened?
[Ed] She said she had
to use the bathroom.
She was banging on the door
like a psychopath.
I don't know. What was I supposed to do?
- What did you say?
- I said Matt had chicken pox
and that he went to stay
with his grandparents.
His grandparents are dead, Ed.
- How am I gonna explain that?
- I don't know, William.
Don't drag me into your
giant sucking hole of lies, okay?
You didn't call the school,
make something up?
No.
What about the clinic that Mona works at?
It's been five days.
You didn't think that anyone would notice
your entire family was missing?
I've had a lot of things on my mind, Ed.
Yeah. Sorry, man, I just...
You're gonna have to deal with that.
How are they?
They're a foot taller.
[phone chiming]
Wow.
[chiming continues]
Really?
[chiming stops]
[messages pinging]
[message pings]
Hello, Juan.
I don't think so.
[man] You think they're really
gonna shut us down?
[Margaret] All I know is we need this
robot ready before the next donor arrives.
- [man] Well, where's William?
- [sparks zapping]
[computer beeping]
- [electronic pulses]
- [alert beeping]
[pod bubbling softly]
[dull pounding on glass]
[indistinct conversation]
What am I missing?
[car approaches]
[car door opens and closes]
- [car door closes]
- [car alarm chirps]
[doorbell rings]
Ah, Jesus, man, you look like
you're up to nefarious shit.
And that is not a good look
for someone who's actually
up to nefarious shit, by the way.
- I'm not ready.
- No, I said 17 days.
It's been 17 days.
There is no "I'm not ready" here.
Ed!
Ed.
[Ed gasps]
Shit.
Ed.
Ed. Do you see that?
I still don't know why it happens.
If I don't know what causes it, how can I
be certain it won't happen to them?
Yeah, well, Christ, man,
you should have thought
about that 17 days ago.
The accelerants follow
the DNA profile precisely, okay?
You keep them in the tanks,
they keep aging.
Your wife, uh,
two weeks from now,
cancer maybe.
Your daughter, menopause.
Your son, I don't know,
male pattern baldness
and a droopy old man sack.
My point is, in a couple of days,
even if you do figure this out,
they will have aged years
beyond the age they were
when they died.
How are you gonna explain that?
[laughs] How are you not freaking out
right now, William?
- I'm trying to think.
- [Ed] Okay, good.
Yeah, sure, you think.
I'll think, too.
I'll think about what's it like in jail,
or when Bionyne sues us
for $30 billion, or...
What? What are you doing?
I'll sedate them, induce a coma.
It'll keep their minds in a blank state...
till I figure it out.
What if you don't figure it out?
You can't keep them sedated
for more than 72 hours, tops.
After that, you're gonna have
to make a very tough decision.
Drain the pod.
[alarm sounding]
[Mona gasps]
[breathes deeply]
[Ed] Got her?
Whoa! She's slippery, man.
[Mona groaning]
Hold her!
[Mona groans]
[Ed] Holy shit.
[chuckles]
I did it. We did it.
She's perfect, man.
It's better than successful.
I mean, this is perfect.
Holy shit.
Okay.
This should keep their bodies
fed for a while.
And, uh,
drop some more off tomorrow.
Thank you.
You got it.
You got three days, man.
Yeah. I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Hey, we made clones today.
You can add that to your resume.
[William] Margaret, energize the body.
Sergeant Kelly. Do you hear me?
[Kelly groans] Who am I?
[Kelly breathing erratically] Who am I?
[alert chimes]
Sergeant.
[Kelly breathing erratically]
- [Kelly screaming]
- [William] Turn it off.
The imprint failed.
[screaming continues]
[equipment crashing]
- [monitor beeping]
- [screaming continues]
[William] Turn it off.
[Zoe laughing]
[monitor beeping speeds up]
I thought I could do it.
Sorry.
[phone rings]
[rings]
- What?
- [Jones] Bill.
Have you been avoiding my call?
Bill? Bill?
What?
Do you realize how much money has been
invested in this project?
[monitor beeping]
People are counting on you.
I'm counting on you.
Holy shit.
- And we're almost out of time.
- Holy shit.
What did you say?
[monitor beeping]
Do you hear me?
- [line clicks]
- Bill, are you still there?
We've been looking
in the wrong place.
You're really close to me, man.
No, it's not the mind,
it's not the brain, Ed.
It's the body.
- The body?
- [William] It's so obvious. So elegant.
So simple!
Hey, man, let's pump the brakes
on the crazy train, all right?
- Follow me, Edward.
- What...
[footsteps climbing stairs]
Dead flat.
Watch this.
[electronic hum, monitor beeps]
[hum, monitor beeps]
Her mind is a blank slate.
Comatose.
She's never experienced
a moment of consciousness.
Yet she's breathing.
Her heart's pumping.
But that's not a sign of consciousness.
Those are involuntary functions.
All controlled in the brain.
Her brain knows it has a body.
This specific body.
That's what I was missing.
That's why 345 doesn't work.
It has electrodes and wires
connected to steel and titanium.
We're imprinting a biological brain
into a synthetic mind.
But it doesn't know that.
It's looking for its body,
its heart, its lungs.
But it can't find them.
So the lower reptilian brain
freaks out.
It thinks that it's dying,
reacts accordingly
and never has a chance to reach
watershed consciousness.
Oh, shit, yeah.
It's like transplant rejection.
We just have to trick the synthetic mind
into believing that it has its biological,
actual flesh-and-blood body.
That's the solution.
That may be 345's solution, but what does
this have to do with your family?
They're not robots, William.
It has everything to do with my family.
I'll be imprinting her mind
into her own body.
I know it's going to work.
But are you sure? I mean,
we're only gonna get one shot at this.
Stand by to initiate
the neural imprint, Ed.
Ready?
Has that ever mattered?
Initiate the neural imprint.
Commence bio-to-bio protocol.
[electronic pulsing]
Keep an eye on Mona's sensory cortex.
Good.
I'm going temporal.
Parietal.
Limbic.
Vitals?
Vitals are good.
Okay.
Pulse state's good.
All functions good.
Initiating neural imprint.
Incredible.
Imprint completed.
[Ed] What's going on, man?
Nothing's happening.
Can you hear me, Mona?
[monitor beeping]
[beeping accelerates]
Shit. Oh, shit. She's rejecting it.
Oh, shit, man,
what are we gonna do?
Wait!
[beeping decelerates]
William?
Baby.
Whoa, whoa.
William, what are you doing?
Putting her to sleep.
I can't have her and the kids
wake up to the house like this.
[Ed] Yeah. Yeah, good thinking.
You have any idea what we just did?
I mean, this is the single greatest thing
that I have ever done in my life,
you, anyone has ever done.
I mean, granted,
we can't tell anybody about it,
but, oh, my God!
I mean...
We're talking Nobel Prize, right?
Foster-Whittle?
Scratch that, Whittle-Foster.
[voice fading]
It doesn't have to be alphabetical.
Well, I, uh...
I hope they're gonna be okay.
- We did it.
- Yeah.
All right.
Well, I'll, uh... I'll see you at work.
[sobbing]
[kisses]
[groans]
Mona?
Kids?
Good morning, William.
[William] Good morning.
So, how is everybody?
- I'm hungry.
- Starving.
I feel great. I'm going for a run.
- Outside?
- You look tired.
Did you sleep okay?
Yeah.
Have a good run.
[Matt] Dad. Dad.
Can I have some pancakes?
Yes.
Yes, you can have
some pancakes, Matthew.
Sophie, you want
some pancakes, too?
- Yeah.
- [William] Great.
Great.
[William] Flapjacks up.
- Hey, can I have French toast?
- Oui.
French toast for the lady.
Coming up.
[labored breathing]
Gross.
Mom, this milk went sour.
Did you go shopping?
- I bought this the other day.
- [Sophie] It's curdled.
- They sold us expired milk.
- Yeah.
Somebody's gonna get a piece of my mind.
- I'll take care of it.
- [phone buzzing]
[William] Work.
I gotta... I got...
Okay.
[buzzing continues]
[phone chimes]
- Yeah.
- [Ed] Yeah, hey, it's me.
We got a donor inbound. 37 minutes.
You gotta meet me at the lab, ASAP.
[William] My familyjust woke up.
Congratulations, but it's gonna
be a pretty short reunion
unless we solve 345.
- If we get shut down, we get exposed.
- [dish clatters]
- [Mona] Matt, careful.
- [Ed] Are you listening to me?
William, you hearing me?
Hello?
Yeah, okay, I'll be there.
- [blade clangs]
- [Matt] Damn it!
Buddy, you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Are you all right?
You don't seem like yourself today.
I have to go into the lab.
You take off, baby. We're good.
[scoffs] I hate to leave you
on a Saturday.
We'll still be here when you get back.
Okay.
[indistinct announcements on PA]
Neural tissue intact.
Protoplasmic integrity approximately 60%.
I make it 55.
[Ed] Still, cortex is viable.
Do you concur?
William?
Negative.
It's too corrupt.
What's going on, man?
Donor was good.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't put
another person through that.
[scoffs] Well, you picked a hell of a time
to grow a conscience.
I hope you're ready to go to jail,
lose your family,
because that's what's gonna happen
if we don't get 345 to work.
So you better figure something out.
Soon.
[door opens]
[Jones] Are you in there, Bill?
Yeah, it's me.
[Jones] Everything okay in there?
All good.
Damn shame about
that donor today, huh?
We'll get the next one, sir.
[Jones] Hope there is a next one, Bill.
- [door closes]
- [William hyperventilating]
[electronic whirring]
- [hydraulic pulse]
- [device whirring]
[William groaning]
Oh, my gosh.
Mom, have you seen my cell phone?
No, I've been looking for mine, too.
Well, your whole social life
doesn't depend on it. Mine does.
- So where did you have it last?
- [Sophie] I have no idea.
Troll, did you take my cell phone?
- No.
- Oh, my God.
[William] Ed!
Hey!
Jesus, are you crying blood?
William, you didn't...
- I did.
- On yourself? Are you out of your mind?
Have you considered
the very real possibility
that you've gone
completely batshit insane?
- That could kill you.
- Ed, I had to.
Listen, I'm going to upload
my neural map into 345.
Ed, it's going to be me in there.
- Sure, that makes me feel...
- [man] Edward, William.
Hey, Phil.
We start with a scan of my body.
I take that data, create an algorithm
which will bridge with
my neural imprint in 345.
Okay, so you write an algorithm
that tricks the synthetic brain
into thinking that
its real, actual body is there.
Exactly.
And with my mind inside,
we'll be able to verify
that the synthetic has reached
watershed consciousness because
I'll be able to ask... myself.
I'm the baseline, Ed.
I'm the control.
It will be me.
I'll start writing the algorithm tonight.
[Ed] Okay, so are we still going
tree shopping tomorrow?
- [Mona] Something's wrong.
- What's wrong?
I don't know, William,
but something's not right with me.
I don't remember what I had
for dinner last night.
I don't remember leaving
the clinic for Christmas break.
And didn't we go on a boat trip?
I don't remember going on a boat trip.
Something's not right with me.
Oh, baby.
Where are the kids?
Asleep.
Sophie has a fever, but she's okay.
Maybe you have what Sophie has.
Maybe.
Why don't you go and lie down and...
see how you feel in the morning?
Yeah.
I'm exhausted.
Support directive 2.5.
Site OT-45, annex 1.7.
Suppress directive. Now you're talkin'.
[dings]
[sighs]
[breathing unsteadily]
[gasping]
Mom! Mom! [hyperventilating]
- Dad! Dad!
- Sophie? Sophie!
- Dad, is Mom dead?
- What?
I saw her die, Dad!
- No!
- Dad, are you sure?
No, it was just a bad dream.
Mommy's okay.
I saw her die!
No, no.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Go back to sleep.
But it felt so real.
- It's just a dream. Mommy's okay.
- You sure?
Yeah. It's okay.
It was just a bad dream.
- Okay.
- Yeah. It's over.
Shh.
[William's voice]
I spy with my little eye...
- [muffled voices of family]
- [Zoe] Are we almost there?
[Zoe screaming]
[muffled impact, screaming]
[Zoe] Daddy!
There now.
All better.
It'll be like it never happened.
[Mona] William.
What's going on?
- Mona, can we go upstairs?
- What have you done to Sophie?
I gave her a little sedative.
- You did what? What?
- She's okay.
Mona, please. Let's talk upstairs.
No, William. Tell me the truth.
There was a crash.
You and the kids died.
I brought you back.
You're replicas.
Get that thing... off her head.
I'm dead.
You're alive.
You're you.
Matt is alive upstairs.
Sophie, and...
and no one has to know.
How could you do this?
I watched our children die.
I held your lifeless body in my arms
and I thought...
I could bring you back.
What would you have done?
Hey, Ed!
Hey!
- How you doing?
- [Matt] Very good.
- What's up?
- Hey.
- Good.
- Morning.
Morning.
- Hi, Ed. How are you?
- Hey.
- I'm good, how are you?
- [Mona] Great.
Hey, Matty, come stay here with me.
- But I like this one.
- No, I hate those ones. They're fake.
I think they're... nice.
[scoffs] Come on. Let's look over here.
[Sophie] Mom, check this one out.
[Matt] Think this one's big enough?
So... you got 'em back.
[Mona] You like this one?
- Yeah.
- [Latin music in background]
All right, let's get you a tree.
Maybe... Maybe we should
move back home.
- What?
- We just settled here.
Are you serious, Dad?
- Matt, you missed your plate.
- Idiot.
What?
- Hey, Dad, who is Zoe?
- [glass shatters]
Who?
Someone scribbled "Zoe"
in my closet with a crayon.
There was a bunk bed
in that bedroom.
A bunk bed?
- Are you sure?
- [Mona] I'm not crazy.
I remember photos
in the upstairs hallway.
Honey, that thing that happened,
there might be some things...
And I remember
what you look like when you're lying.
[doorbell rings]
Feliz Navidad, Bill.
Mmm, is that lamb I smell?
I'm interrupting dinner, aren't I?
Mona!
- You look stunning.
- Mr. Jones.
Such a lucky man, Bill.
What an unexpected pleasure.
Do you care to join us?
Beautiful and generous.
I've heard about women like you.
Thanks, but I wouldn't dream of imposing.
William, can I have a quick word?
Promise I'll have him back
in five minutes.
We're not done.
What brings you by?
Let me ask you something.
Didn't you ever think
this was all a little too easy?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, let me help.
Subjects 346, 347, 348.
Bionyne property, Bill.
Desperation has driven many a great man
to accomplish the impossible.
Fate caused that car crash.
I just let things play out.
Color me impressed,
but now I have a problem.
Three, actually.
Do you know what would happen
if word of this ever got out?
Nobody has to know.
Nobody will ever know.
Mona knows.
How long until Sophie and Matt
start asking questions?
Maybe their friends will.
Lies are messy.
I'm not in the business of messy,
it's risky.
Simple is safe.
Those three subjects in the wild
is something I cannot tolerate.
I know how to make 345 work.
That's worth something.
Bionyne would be the most successful
biomedical company in the world.
William, ask yourself a question.
Who would spend this much money
saving mortally wounded soldiers?
My God, man, come on.
That's not how you win wars.
We're not a biomedical company.
My name isn't even Jones.
Now, you figured out how to transfer
human consciousness into a machine.
Imagine, the best pilot put into
a thousand individual drones,
the mind of a hacker
loaded into the virus.
Do you have any idea
how much that's worth?
Bill, isn't it exciting?
What about my family?
Your family died in a car accident, Bill.
The algorithm.
Get me the algorithm.
And then finish dinner.
Kiss the kids good night.
Hell, make love to your wife.
Have what you didn't have
the first time.
A chance to say... good-bye.
That's my gift to you.
I'll get the algorithm.
[phone chirps]
[cocks gun]
You see? Knew you were smart
enough to do the right thing.
[Jones groaning]
This is gonna piss me off, isn't it?
[Mona] William, you are scaring the kids.
- Where's Mr. Jones?
- [Matt] Mom, Dad.
Are you guys getting a divorce?
- [Mona] Maybe.
- [William] No.
Can you go to your rooms, please?
- [William] Where's the tin foil?
- In the top drawer by the dishwasher.
William, I need to know what's going on.
And who is Zoe?
Zoe is our daughter.
I couldn't bring you all back.
I couldn't save you all.
There weren't enough pods.
I deleted her from your memories.
You took the memory
of my child from me?
I'm sorry.
And I don't blame you
if you want to hate me
for the rest of my life,
but right now, we have to go.
Bionyne isn't a medical company.
I don't even know what they are.
But they're going to kill you and the kids
unless we go, right now.
And I didn't defy
every natural law there is
just to lose you again.
We have to go.
Kids, we're leaving!
[cell phone ringing]
[car starts]
[tires screech]
- [Mona screams]
- [car bangs curb]
[Mona shrieks]
[tires screech, engine revs]
[groans]
[Sophie] What is going on?
[Mona] Matt, Sophie.
There are some bad people
trying to hurt us.
Just hold on and everything
will be all right.
We'll go to Ed's boat,
get out of here.
[zapping]
[beep]
[sizzling]
I'm disappointed, Bill.
Very disappointed.
Sir, they're on the move.
Don't shoot him in the head.
- This is all your fault.
- I didn't do anything.
[thud]
- How did they find us?
- Don't you guys watch TV?
- They tracked Sophie's phone.
- They didn't. Shut up.
Shit, maybe it's in the car,
maybe it's the GPS.
It's not the car, it's not the phones.
Bionyne puts tracker markers
in all of the experimental animals.
The trackers are in you.
William!
[screaming]
- [horn blares]
- [tires screech]
We're okay!
It's all right. We're all right.
- You okay?
- [William] We're all right.
[both gasping]
How do we get the trackers out?
They're in the pods and they
attach to the spine in utero.
They're powered by
the central nervous system.
They don't come out.
- What are you talking about?
- Drive to the clinic.
That's back the way we came.
Drive to the clinic.
Okay.
- Sophie, I need you to lie down.
- What do you mean? Dad, why?
It's okay. Get on the table.
- It's all right.
- [Sophie] What?
The trackers are powered by
the nervous system so this will fry them.
Red, white, black.
- Trackers? What are you saying?
- [William] It's okay, Sophie. It's okay.
Mom, what's going on? I'm serious.
Somebody put something bad in us,
and I'm trying to kill it.
And I know you're afraid,
but you're just going to have to try
and relax and trust me. Okay?
It's going to be okay.
[beeping]
- Mona.
- If I get this wrong, I stop her heart.
What? Mom!
[man] This should be it.
Inside the hospital.
- Clear!
- [Sophie groans]
- [beeping]
- [man] Shit. Let's go.
[monitor beeping]
[indistinct chatter]
[panting]
It's okay, Matty.
It's not as bad as it seems, okay?
- [Mona] Clear!
- [defibrillator sparks]
- [erratic beeping]
- [man 1] There goes another one.
[man 2] They gotta be upstairs.
Hey! Hey!
What are you doing here?
[gunshot]
- [monitor beeping]
- [Matt] Dad, hurry up.
[rapid beeping]
Baby, try to calm down.
- Up ahead, on the left.
- Here.
Dad, someone's coming.
- [monitor beeping]
- Damn it!
- Now!
- [Mona groans]
[rapid beeping]
[beeping slows]
[man] They were right here.
[tires screech]
- [beeps]
- Targets are off the X.
They fried their trackers. We lost them.
[phone autodialing]
It's Jones.
I have a question for you.
[foghorn blowing]
[William] You and the kids
stay in the car, honey.
I want to make sure it's safe.
I'll see if I can get the boat.
[groans]
The bait box.
When is Dad coming back?
Shh! Honey, stay quiet.
Keys are in the bait box.
You said the keys were in the bait box.
- Mom!
- [Matt] Mom! Let go of me! Mom!
Oh, Ed.
- Mom! Let go of my brother!
- Mom! Mom!
- Get off me!
- Let go of my kids!
[screaming]
Get off my kids!
[Sophie] Dad, come back!
[Matt] Dad!
William!
- [Matt] Dad!
- [screaming]
Inside!
We got the wife and kids.
What about Foster?
He'll come to us.
Good call, Eddie.
Here are your boat keys.
You bastard.
Mona, look, everything's gonna be fine
if William just cooperates.
Fine? You idiot.
They're gonna kill us, Ed.
- Mom.
- What are you talking about?
I have snacks in my office.
Take the kids in there.
Mom!
Mom, come with us.
[man] Foster's here.
Yes, sir.
[hangs up receiver]
Look, Mona, we...
We stole millions of dollars' worth
of Bionyne equipment to make you.
- Make me?
- Yes, make you.
To bring you back.
You died, remember?
I was supposed to get rid
of the bodies.
Your bodies. But I couldn't do it.
And then Jones found out,
and, look...
If we just play ball,
we can make it out of this.
Get your hands off my wife!
- Where are the kids, honey?
- They're okay. They're over there.
William, man, I'm... I'm sorry.
This wasn't supposed to happen.
This got way out of hand.
It's all right, Ed. It's going to be okay.
I destroyed the algorithm.
I noticed that.
The only place that algorithm
exists is in my head.
You want it, we walk out of here.
You never see us again.
Me and my family disappear.
Bill, are you negotiating?
You need me.
[Jones] Maybe.
- But I don't need her.
- Jones, wait!
[Mona screams]
Or him.
Wait, no, I'll do it!
I'll do it, I'll do it!
I'll give you the algorithm.
I know.
If you trust him, he'll kill us.
I love you.
[electricity pulsing]
[equipment clangs]
[metallic clanging]
The algorithm.
- It's all there?
- It's all there.
Now, let my family go.
Why are you stuck on that?
This thing...
It's a copy.
I mean, you really don't get it?
The experiment's over, Bill.
No, it isn't.
[William's voice, distorted]
Jones.
I'm here for my family.
The kids! Let's get the kids!
[starts car]
Go.
Mom, what is he doing?
Where is he going?
He's gone to get something, honey.
He's gone to get something.
[gagging]
[William] William! William!
That's enough.
What's it feel like?
This is going to sound strange.
But it feels...
like me.
[Jones feebly] Bill.
You know they'll just send somebody else
after I'm gone.
Sooner or later, they'll find you.
Not if we work together.
Bill, are you negotiating?
What if I told you
there's another way, Jones?
Give us what we want
and you can live again,
as a very rich man.
What do you say? Do we have a deal?
See you soon, Bill.
I'll handle it from here, William.
Are you sure?
You'll have to stay behind.
There is no other way.
You take care of the family.
We'll be fine.
[William sighs] Ed.
[electronic pulsing]
[monitor beeping]
[laughing]
Mommy!
Zoe!
Mr. Quissam.
I am so glad you could make it.
[latches click open]
Trust me. You won't regret it.
Because I ask you,
what price can you put
on a second lifetime?
Please.
Oh, Bill, it's time to go to work.
[electronics pulsing]
Boot the mapping sequence.
[pop music playing]
[pop song ends]
[techno starts]
[music ends]