Mommy's coming.
What did I tell you about
dressing like a girl.
Get that dress off right now.
Right now.
Get it off.
It's for your own good.
No, my God.
I'm sorry.
This is for your own good.
Get dressed.
And get the hell outside.
What have you done?
What have you done to yourself?
Do you have a question?
I want to paint some clouds on it.
Sorry, I, I need to read your lips?
Oh, I want to paint some clouds on this,
but I'm not sure how.
Okay, get a small amount of
white on the end of your brush.
Yeah, and you use circular strokes.
Like that?
It's perfect.
Looks great.
Your sister Michelle's here?
Oh.
Hi.
They cancelled drama club.
So I thought I'd ride home with you.
Okay.
I still need to do the last speech,
probably another 15 minutes.
Alright,
I'll be outside working on my French.
Only 962 more days until we move to Paris.
Uh, uh, 965.
We're going to your graduation ceremony.
If we must.
Um huh.
Everybody, put down your brushes,
if you'd stop painting and look up here.
Good job.
Okay, before we start cleaning up.
I want to say a few more words
about overcoming adversity.
Okay?
Now when we came in this morning,
how many of you thought that your paintings
would turn out half as good as they did?
Anybody?
Okay, but they're really great.
They're beautiful.
That's because you all
believed in yourself.
You broke down the challenge
into manageable steps
and gave it your best effort.
You turned a problem into a masterpiece.
And these steps can really be
used to overcome any obstacle.
That's the most important message here guys
is you can achieve anything.
Please.
Oh God.
No, please.
962 more days till we move to Paris.
So, how are you doing?
How's school going?
I got an A minus on the first physics test,
but I'm not really worried
cause we get to drop a score.
Drop that one.
Yeah. It's very bad.
It is. Bad grade.
compared to last years.
You smarty pants.
Mrs. Pierson called me about the bullying.
She says a click of girls
have been calling you names
and tripping you in the halls?
Everyone at school calls me the fetus,
it's like they don't want
anything to do with me.
And I was so excited about
skipping seventh and eighth
and going straight to high school,
but now I think it was the biggest mistake
I've ever made.
I know how cruel high school girls can be,
okay?
But you can't let them get to you.
You are amazing.
So smart and funny and kind.
I'd trade all of that just to have boobs.
Baby, those girls aren't like you.
okay?
All they care about are their clicks
and their boyfriends and their popularity.
And pretty soon, you're gonna blossom
into the most beautiful girl in school.
I got you something.
Big sister promise: by
the time you graduate,
I will have saved enough money
to move us both to Paris.
Are you serious?
Yes, we will get an apartment
and you will go to school
and I'll wait tables
and while all those other girls
are reminiscing about
pep rallies and keggers,
you and I will be busy
exploring the city of light.
Oh my God, thank you so much Lily.
Okay, but there's one more thing.
Um huh.
If you ever find yourself in a situation
with those girls or a boy, or anyone,
and you feel like things are
spiraling out of control,
you do whatever it takes
to defend yourself.
You understand me?
Yes.
Okay.
I got you through foster care,
we'll get you through high school.
Okay. Just keep your nose in those books
and you learn as much French as you can.
Okay.
You promise me?
Yes, I promise.
Pinkie promise.
Mommy said that a lot.
I don't remember.
After losing Michelle I
spiraled deeper into the abyss
than I ever have been before.
At least after losing my hearing
I had my mom to comfort me
and baby Michelle to distract me.
Then after my mom passed,
Michelle and I had each other.
I was focused on guiding her
through foster care,
and getting ready to legally adopt her.
But when Michelle died,
I, I never felt so alone,
so utterly lacking direction.
When I ran out of savings
it was the best thing
that could have happened.
Forced me to face the world again
and to find a new path for my life.
Well, I so glad you've
chosen Cassadaga University
to be the compass for that new path.
We're all excited to have the daughter
of such a highly regarded alumni.
And if you're half as talented as your mom,
you'll make the university proud.
I just, I really want to thank you again,
and not just for the scholarship
and a place to live,
but I know you had to pull some strings
to get some admissions requirements waived
and I really appreciate it.
No, that's nonsense.
You're a first choice applicant.
And with what you've accomplished,
the obstacles you've overcome,
I have no doubt that you
are the ideal recipient
for the merit award.
Thank you for saying that.
Now, let's take a tour of the house,
and then I'll show you where
you're going to stay.
Okay, please.
We are a bit particular
when it comes to our privacy,
so I hope you'll use your discretion
when you invite guests over.
I will.
And I know you may have noticed
that there are a few areas that are locked.
And I did that for your convenience,
because I want you to have
total access to the house
without worrying about what
may or may not be off limits.
Okay, no problem.
I love the trees here.
They're live oaks.
Is that moss hanging off?
Yeah, beautiful.
That's my grandson, Thomas.
He keeps to himself on the upper floor.
You'll hardly know he's here.
So the old house is mostly unfurnished,
but your bedroom is cozy.
It gets wonderful light.
You have all the solitude you need
to concentrate on your painting.
Yeah, it's amazing.
Uh, I've never seen anything like it.
I know it's eccentric,
but I just couldn't bring
myself to tear it down
when we moved into the new house.
There's 100 years of history in that house
and four generations of my
family that called it home.
Well, here are the keys.
So go and get settled in.
If you need a hand, just let me know
and I'll send Thomas.
Okay, great, thank you.
Hey munch get off the ground.
Sorry I'm late,
I had a cardiac arrest
at the end of my shift.
It's okay, daddy.
Yeah?
Saving people's lives
is the most important job in the world.
No it's not.
Being your dad is the most
important job in the world.
Saving lives is a distant second,
remember that, alright.
What'd I just say?
Saving lives is a distant second.
Yes ma'am.
And when she was 14,
she got menintitus and went deaf.
Menintitus.
I never heard of Menintitus,
you sure it's not Meningitis?
Meningitis, yeah,
and she knows how to speak
French and English,
Sign Language. Wow.
And her mom was in the Symphony
and she taught her how to play the cello.
She's a pretty good art teacher too, huh?
Maybe we should think about
getting you some private lessons?
Really, can I please?
It's cool with me,
if it's cool with your mom.
There she is.
Hailey, watch for the cars.
Come on.
Guess what? What?
My dad said I can take painting lessons.
Did you see that car coming?
You gotta watch for cars girl.
Hi.
Hi. I'm Lily Murrow,
I taught the art seminar
for your daughter's class today.
I'm Mike.
Her dad.
Nice to meet you.
Your daughter's great in class,
very polite, very attentive.
Yeah, she really seems to enjoy it,
I've never seen her so excited
about anything, really.
Well, she's got the eye, great instincts.
Here, let me give you some information
and you and your wife can look it over.
I'm divorced actually.
Oh, well, do you want to set
something up right now then?
Yeah, you know,
I'm in the middle of a custody thing,
so I don't, I only get her sporadically,
but I do know that I have her on Saturday
if that's not too hard on your social life?
I just moved here a couple days ago
so I don't really have
a social life right now.
Uh, Saturday?
Saturday at two?
Yeah, two o'clock, yeah?
Two o'clock. Yeah.
Sounds good.
Um, great, I'll see you then.
Bye. Bye.
Let's go.
You like my teacher.
She's pretty.
Why did you let me die?
Hi.
Oh, I'm so sorry to bother you
so early on a Saturday morning.
No, it's okay.
I have a friend coming
over to pick up a book
and Thomas isn't answering his phone
so I thought you wouldn't mind
running upstairs for me and grabbing it?
Oh yeah, of course, no problem.
Get away from me now.
Touch me.
Ahhhh.
I love your use of color and composition.
I think the yellows are
blended really well.
We need to work on the depth.
Here, let me show you something.
When you're painting the vase,
if you make arching strokes like this,
It'll give it a more
three dimensional appearance.
Want to try?
Nice job, that's perfect.
Just like that.
You're my favorite teacher Ms. Murrow.
That's sweet.
I like you too.
Yeah.
Mom, me, Michelle.
Very pretty.
Thank you.
Um, this is the last picture of her
before she found out about the cancer.
We were celebrating her offer
to return to the orchestra to Paris.
You?
Dad?
Dad, father?
No, he's just a friend from the orchestra.
I don't have any pictures of my father.
I love this one.
This is Michelle in her
first dance in Middle School.
Great job today.
Next time we're gonna paint
something in the garden.
Okay?
Give me a hug.
Go wait in the car.
Go wait in the car, come on.
Um, a few of us EMTs we,
we get together on Sundays and we
Um, if you don't look at me,
I can't read your lips.
Right.
You want to go out with me tomorrow,
maybe get a drink and some food?
Make some friends?
Yeah, I'd like that.
Yeah?
Great.
Seven o'clock.
Yeah, that's fine.
Okay, so I'll see you then.
Okay.
Oh come on, don't be such a poor sport.
Just admit it already,
you chose a stupid internship
and it's a complete waste of your time.
The only waste of my time
is trying to have a conversation with you.
Ohhhh.
Pitcher of Miller Light please.
What are you guys fighting about this time.
These guys, they're always
Did you hear about this.
Okay?
She has taken a paranormal,
psychology internship, okay?
The whole night she's been
trying to convince me
that those crystal ball gazing crack pots
are actually the gate keepers of truth.
That is not at all what I've been saying.
Oh really?
The point I was making
is the phenomena exists.
Sure.
99.9 percent of so-called psychics
are easily exposed as frauds,
but the remaining one tenth of one percent,
those people have inexplicable
abilities that will astound you.
Where'd you get those statistics?
Don't let her fool you okay.
She butters up her bull shit
with ten dollar words.
It ain't gonna work.
Then why has every administration
since Eisenhower kept psychics on retainer,
spent hundreds of millions of dollars
trying to militarize their abilities.
Your boy Regan, spent more money
on psychic research than all
the other presidents combined.
Prove it.
Prove it, tonight.
Okay.
Break out your little psychic rolodex
and you find me the most inexplicable
of all your supposed psychics.
Huh?
Ya'll, ya'll want to do this.
Who wants to talk to Elvis?
Sorry, bingo ended 30 minutes ago.
Actually, we're looking for Susan Baker,
I was told she lived here.
Again, sorry.
Susan doesn't do public readings.
She knows me.
My name is Sharice Henderson.
I was a research assistant on a parapsy
Unless you have an appointment
I can't help you.
How is Emmanuel,
has he had any luck in finding
the genetic component yet?
He's got some leads.
What?
You know him?
Susan and I participated in the study.
Oh, so any chance we could get
a sitting with her tonight?
I'll tell you what?
I could make it happen
for a 500 dollar donation.
What?
Connecting as deeply as Susan does
requires days to recover from.
People come from all over the world paying
two, three thousand dollars
just to sit in a room with her.
Thanks anyway.
Um, I'll pay.
I mean, assuming that it will
work for someone who's deaf.
Oh, it will work Missy,
you don't need your ears to hear a spirit
any more than you need eyes to see one.
Place your fingers on the phonograph arm
as you would with a Ouija board planchette.
Your sister will communicate
to you through this device.
We will hear the recording,
but you will hear her voice.
What is her name?
Michelle Murrow.
And your parents?
Our mother's name was Collette.
I invite the spirit of Michelle Murrow,
sister of Lily, daughter of Collette.
Lily.
Was that her? Was that her voice?
Michelle is with us now.
You may speak to her directly.
Michelle, can you hear me?
I can hear and see you.
Where are you?
Who's with you?
I'm with mom now.
Michelle, I want to tell you..
Where's the tower necklace Lily,
you should wear it to remember me?
It's back at home, I can find it.
Michelle, can you hear me?
Lily.
A different presence is with us now.
You must go.
You are not welcome here.
Leave us ghost.
We intend to speak only to
the spirit of Michelle Murrow.
Leave us ghost, you are not welcome here.
Leave us.
Lily.
You okay?
What happened?
You fell out of your chair.
Will you take me home?
Yeah, of course.
Come on.
Please, wait a minute.
A ghost has manifested itself to her
and she's going to need guidance.
For what, 500 bucks more,
fuck you dude, I'm out of here.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Okay.
You sure?
Yep.
I'll see you later?
Yes ma'am.
Hello.
Mommy, I miss you.
Mommy misses you too.
Eww.
I'll be home soon and we can
watch cartoons okay?
Cartoons.
Okay mommy, see you soon.
Okay, put your daddy on the phone.
Daddy.
Gabby?
Listen, I was gonna stop by
the grocery store after my run,
do you need anything?
I'm good.
Okay, alright.
I'll be home in about an hour.
I'll be here. Okay, I love you.
Love you too. Bye.
Very pretty Gabriella.
I bet all the other girls are envious.
That's not me.
Hey, I'm over here,
I've been watching you for weeks now.
Not now.
In the tress.
Morning.
You don't mind do you?
It helps with my glaucoma.
It doesn't hurt my arthritis either.
Want some?
Sure.
Thank you.
Have you ever visited
the spiritualist community
on the edge of town?
Well, I've been there,
but I've never participated in a séance.
Is that because you've
never felt inclined to,
or because you don't believe in them?
I think there are places in the world
that amplify certain realities
like mountains and revelations
or Bermuda Triangle and chaos.
I think Cassadaga's one of those places.
So I wouldn't go there looking for answers.
I think I, I would try to
find clarity through my work.
Pain and suffering are tools
at an artist's disposal,
just as much as canvas and paint.
So, maybe it's time you start painting
what you feel instead
of painting not to feel.
And don't tell Thomas you saw me smoking,
okay?
Oh.
He's paranoid about those things.
It is said that art is man's way
of expressing himself by
showing us how he sees things.
Sometimes he shows us instead how he feels.
What's in his heart,
what may be in the darkest places,
which brings us to Caravaggio.
His theatrical use of contrast
had a profound influence
on the emerging Baroque style
of the time and in particular of this work,
titled sleeping cupid,
Caravaggio employs his signature
style of lighting,
of stark contrast between the light
and the dark with almost
no intermediate value.
Commissioned in 1608
for Frau Francesco Delata,
the Grand Master of the Knights of Malta,
the subject is a sleeping cupid
lying alongside his arrows.
Background shadows are profoundly
Yes, Lily.
Lily.
Lily, are you alright?
Hi.
Your professor called me,
told me what happened.
How you holding up?
I'm sorry about that.
He insisted I call somebody,
and I didn't have anybody else.
No problem. I got it.
I just finished my shift.
I was on my way home.
Hey,
you probably think I'm a huge nut job now.
Of course not.
But I did buy you something online.
Sort of a con man instruction manual.
You know, details all the things
needed to create the illusion
of contacting the dead,
you know, thumping tables, gusts of wind,
wayward spirits, cutting the séance short.
It's all in there.
There is more going
on there than you saw Mike.
I heard her.
I mean, not, not with my ears, in my mind.
I saw things too, I'm still seeing things.
Look, let me take you
to my doctor, alright?
I have,
I have Hailey for a couple hours today.
I promised her I'd get her a pumpkin.
There's an awesome
pumpkin patch down the road,
let's go have some fun.
Alright?
I don't want to intrude on your time.
You're not gonna intrude on us,
she loves you.
Come on.
Come on, you gotta get out of your head.
Come on, yeah?
Yeah. Yeah. To fun.
To fun.
We're having fun.
Yeah, that one.
It's my mom's place.
My, my lawyer suggested
that I move back here
for a little while, you know,
just to give Hailey some normal hours
while I'm working night shifts.
Yeah.
Makes sense to be surrounded by yourself
with female hair cuts as a child.
I'm gonna go upstairs,
grab some things real quick,
you want something to drink?
- I'm good.
- No. No.
Alright. Thank you.
It had bruises on the side,
but besides that, perfect.
It looks perfect and sometimes
that stuff makes it even better.
Yep.
I'm going to carve it
into a jack o lantern.
What kind of jack o lantern?
Well, he's gonna have two eyes,
triangular nose, and a mouth
and I think I'm gonna
add some teeth to his mouth.
Are you hungry after working?
So my dad taught me the game when I was,
I don't know, five, maybe six.
He was a tough guy.
He had a hard life, you know,
he worked two maybe three jobs, sometimes.
But it didn't matter.
Every time he was in those
stands watching me play ball.
He was nothing but smiles.
How did you get the nickname Locomotive?
It's actually Loco motive,
like crazy train, you know.
It was the high school state championships.
I was this really skinny
little sophomore kid, right?
Trying to stretch a triple into a homerun.
Ball gets to the catcher first.
He's this big old beefy
Southern Boy, right?
I'm like screw it, I'm gonna go for it.
I throw down my shoulder,
boom, plow right into him.
Knocks me out cold.
So, one of my teammates
starts calling me locomotive
and it just, you know, it stuck.
Stupid name.
That's kind of,
kind of who I am though, I guess.
Yeah.
I have, I have this tendency
to just throw on these blinders
and focus on achieving
one goal at all costs.
Doesn't fucking matter.
I'm gonna get it, you know.
That's what happened with my family.
I was so determined to make the majors,
you know, go all the way.
Be a big star.
I put everything else on hold.
I know, it's crazy, I,
I wake up one morning
and, I'm in my mid twenties,
I'm divorced,
my wife has custody of my daughter,
you know, that's when I,
that's when I realized it's time
to step off the crazy train, you know?
So I moved back here, got this EMT gig,
and jump started the process
of getting Hailey back in my life.
Hmmm.
I'm sorry.
What?
Here I am, I'm fucking going
on and on about Hailey again.
No.
I promise you,
that's not the only thing I talk about.
I like it.
It's endearing.
Shows you're, you're a really good father.
I can see that.
Trying.
Trying my hardest, you know.
God.
Oh my God.
What are you doing.
What are you doing?
Ow.
You're sick.
Shhhhh.
What have you done to yourself?
Good morning.
Morning.
Some tea?
How you feeling?
Better.
Safe.
Good.
All you needed was some rest,
and a little distraction.
Is that what you call that?
A little distraction.
Hey, I had an amazing time,
and you are, never mind.
What?
I gotta go.
I have my, my first custody hearing
with the judge today.
But, I do have a couple
hours before I go to work,
if you don't mind me coming back.
Hm uh.
Yeah. Yes.
Yes.
I'd like that.
Okay.
Alright.
Get some rest, yeah?
Get lots of rest.
Alright, I'll see you in a few hours.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, hey.
Sorry.
I didn't.
Oh.
I didn't mean to startle you,
well, I just, I honked when I drove up,
but I guess you didn't hear me.
Oh, I'm deaf.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I read lips.
Well, Christian Burton.
I'm the, I'm the contractor that built
the green house for Mrs. Andersen.
I was just,
just here checking her for storm damage.
So you, you a relative, or what?
I'm sorry.
I'm Lily.
I'm a student staying at the guest house.
So they're giving the promise award again,
huh?
Yeah, the merit award.
Yeah, it used to be
called the promise award,
but then, anyway, um,
can you tell Mrs. Andersen
that I, I inspected the green
house as best I could.
She wants me to come back
and check the locked areas,
just give me a call.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Oh my God.
Hey.
I saw the milk.
It was just milk.
No, no it wasn't.
It wasn't just milk.
Okay, so what?
You walked to the refrigerator,
and there she was.
Yeah.
Come on Lily, are you,
are you sure that you didn't
just fucking dream this,
that you fell off the counter.
You, you hurt yourself?
How could a fall from
the counter do this to me?
I don't know.
Hey.
You know that this mediation process
is part of the custody battle, right?
Right?
It's not a path,
it's not a means of reconciliation.
It's nothing like that.
You think that I'm making this up?
No.
You think that I'm just doing this to
I don't fucking know.
Look, I don't know.
Alright.
But if you rule out the supernatural,
it's kind of fucking hard to believe.
Mike, this is real. Okay?
This is the girl I have seen
getting inside of my head.
Okay?
She used to live in this house.
She used to sleep in that bed.
And now she's.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Here, here.
Oh my God.
I told you.
Yeah, the girl from the séance.
I know it seems self inflicted,
that's what I thought.
But you know what?
I just saw this girl hack up
a handful of bloody fucking maggots,
now if that's not real, what is?
So you gonna help me or what?
Thank you.
Alright.
It's set, Theresa's gonna cover my shift.
My buddy Todd said that you can
use his place in Daytona,
it's just temporary till we can figure out
some better arrangements,
but it's better than this shit, alright?
Uh huh.
We're gonna figure this out.
We're closed, come back tomorrow.
We need to talk to Susan.
Remember we had a séance
the other day alright,
it went sideways. I recall.
And I also recall offering you guidance,
guidance which you declined.
We're not declining it now.
Nevertheless,
Susan is retired for the evening
come back in the morning
and we'll discuss her availability.
Listen to me you mother fucker.
We need help.
Alright.
This girl's getting fucking attacked here,
and we're not gonna leave until somebody
undoes whatever the fuck
it is they did to her,
you got that?
Just step away from Mr. Banks,
huh,
or I'll use this blade and drag you away.
Heath, let him go.
I'm still in my chair.
I want to help.
Once a vengeful ghost connects to you,
it will not relent until you do
whatever it is it wants from you.
The attack in the car,
that was her way of
keeping you from leaving.
And if you tried it again,
you get the same result.
Whatever it is she wants you to do,
it is right here in Cassadaga.
Well, then we should contact her again
and ask her what she wants.
The only thing another séance will do
is bring about another attack.
Ghosts are not the beings of free will
the way spirits are.
The consequences of refusing to cross over
is entrapped in one tragic moment.
All other memory is lost.
Ghosts cannot read, they cannot write,
they cannot speak.
Those images are our
only means of communication.
They're carefully chosen fragments
of her final memories meant to lead you
to do whatever she wants you to do.
They don't mean anything.
These are just random unconnected images.
They mean something.
Somehow, some way,
those images tell you everything
that you need to know.
Gotta get low.
Get low.
They come under man.
If it isn't the loco Motive himself.
What's up man?
How you doing Mike?
Not too bad, how you doing?
Doing good man.
What's up man,
I see you not wearing your cleats.
So I'm assuming you're not
here to join the police team.
No sir.
Just got a couple questions for you man,
regarding that, that Eastman case.
Remember that girl that went
missing a couple years ago?
Yeah, what about it?
What are the chances I can
get my hands on that file?
Hi. Hi.
How's it coming?
It's getting there.
Are you finding anything?
A pattern or something?
No, not yet.
Tell you what.
You want that file,
see if you still got it, let's go.
See if I still got it, alright.
Here we go.
Let's do this.
Wooo.
You said that Thomas is taking Mrs.
Andersen
to a doctor's appointment tomorrow, right?
How long they usually gone for?
About an hour, sometimes less, why?
Doesn't give us much time, come here.
Officer Hall.
What's up man? How are you?
You come across some new information,
come to me first.
Her IM records indicate that
she finished a conversation
with her friend around 7:15
so she could go on this job
with the dog right?
She would do three trips
around the work out station
and she would job back home.
They ever suspect that family
she was living with?
Sure, I mean, standard procedure
makes them persons of interest.
But, as expected,
they pressured their connections
to expedite the investigation.
Connections, to who?
He watched her.
He watched her from those woods.
He trailed her once or twice,
and then he just waited
for that perfect opportunity.
Hey, Jennifer, how's it going?
Without a body, without a motive,
there's nothing to contradict
a voluntary disappearance classification.
Alright, it's what I'm saying.
So you give me a couple of days?
Yeah.
They say that lock picking takes time,
or skill, not both.
So we're gonna sit here
and we're gonna do it till we get it right.
Fuck.
Okay.
You want me to pick, that's what I picked.
Oh my God.
Am I in a mental institution or something?
Shit.
Let's just have bread and water.
What happened?
Must have thrown a breaker.
I'll take a look.
There they are.
What a fucking pervert.
There's more.
He has her doing everything.
Oh my.
Fuck me.
Hey, what's up?
No, I know. I'm on my way.
No, I got a last minute dementia patient
in my shift it took forever to wrap up.
I know that Janel.
I'm 15 minutes out. Alright.
I'll apologize to the teacher
when I get there.
I'm gonna be there. Alright.
Fucking Christ.
Hey. I gotta get out of here.
Um, I have a parent teacher meeting
that I completely fucking forgot about.
Okay. Alright.
You alright?
Yeah.
What's next?
What did I tell you about dressing up?
What did I tell you about dressing,
what did I tell you about dressing up?
What did I tell you about dressing up?
Please, kill me.
Please.
Please kill me.
You're the prettiest girl in town.
Watch your finger.
Always cut away from yourself.
This way?
Oh, watch my finger.
There you go.
Boom.
Yum.
That's gross.
Lily?
You want to see Bruce?
I have an idea,
why don't you go in and show Mamaw first?
She should really be the
first one to see it.
Don't you think?
Yeah.
Okay.
Sorry.
Look, it's been four years.
He's dropped his guard.
He has to have.
He's left himself exposed.
Someplace that he goes to,
somewhere in that house,
that's the next piece of information
we need to find this body.
Oh.
After all your hard work, are you okay?
Get her away, don't let her see this.
Aw, come on.
Don't move.
Lily, open the door.
Please go, please leave me alone.
Please.
Lily.
Come here.
Come in.
I just want to talk to you for a minute.
My ex-wife filed an emergency order
with the family court today.
She claims that my relationship with you
is detrimental to Hailey's safety.
She says that she has an expert witness
who's willing to testify that your episodes
were nothing but a violent
form of schizophrenia.
You know that's not true.
You know that's not true at all.
My lawyer thinks that
I shouldn't see you anymore.
Your lawyer, or you?
Yeah, me too.
Well, we can figure it out.
Hailey has to be my number one priority,
I'm so sorry.
I, I know.
I don't have a choice.
You, Mike.
Just, we can, we can work,
we can figure something out.
I need you.
Why?
Why me?
Why the fuck me.
Leave me the fuck alone.
Why are you doing this to me?
Come on.
No.
Oh no.
No, no, no, no.
I found you.
Good boy.
You have a beautiful figure.
Did you say something?
That's not me. I'm over here.
Hey, shhh.
What's a matter?
You are such a pretty girl.
Oh God, oh God, oh God.
God please help me, please help me.
Please help me.
God's not here.
God is not here.
What the fuck are you doing in here?
I know what you've done.
I've already called the police.
Why would you do something like that?
This is none of your concern, okay?
What I did, I did for my fucking grandma.
Okay?
Why don't you just,
just forget what you saw here,
and let me dispose of this
before the cops arrive.
Sorry, I can't let you do that.
Be reasonable.
Oh God.
You ungrateful bitch.
My family reached out to you
and took care of you,
and this is how you show your appreciation,
by violating our trust and betraying us.
Hands in the air.
Now get off the girl, nice and easy.
You okay?
Yeah.
The body's down there.
Here's some cash for clothing and food,
in a case like this it could be days,
maybe even weeks before you'll be approved
to get back at the house
to collect your things.
So I'm gonna pick you up tomorrow,
take you down to the station,
we'll get your full statement.
In the meantime, if you need anything,
I mean anything at all.
Don't hesitate to call.
Okay.
Get some sleep, you deserve it.
Thanks.
What do you want from me?
I have done everything.
Leave me alone.
Just a few yards from where I stand lie
the gory remains of Jennifer Eastman,
a Cassadaga resident who
went missing four years ago.
Her body was discovered in a hidden,
underground workshop where
her limbs had been dismembered
and then reattached to form
a gruesome human marionette.
The primary suspect,
a man now dubbed as Gepetto
by the national media
is none other than Thomas Andersen,
heir to the
The pulleys and the metal used
for the joints to hold them together
were widely available
in any local hardware store,
but the rope has an
industrial coating on it,
it makes it resistant to rotten mildew,
specifically designed for foresters.
So I'm guessing the stores
around here don't sell it.
Nope, only online.
Well check the stores around
their vacation properties.
Anything within 100 miles.
Now what's the status
of the Greenhouse blueprints?
I made a call to city planning this morning
just waiting to hear back.
Good work.
Let me know when you hear something.
Alright, will do.
Ready to go?
Yeah.
You okay?
You up for this?
What'd you find in the house?
Behind all the padlocked
closets and drawers?
Valuables, drug paraphernalia.
Some pornography in the upstairs trunks.
And what's Thomas saying?
Standard response,
denies everything but the marijuana corp.
Claims he didn't know about the dungeon.
Says that during the bulk
of the greenhouse construction
he and his grandmother were on vacation.
Yo, what do you got for me?
Huh.
Maybe he still has the original.
Can you give me his office address?
What about the other permits on file,
anything recent?
Yeah, give me that address.
I'll swing by and see
if he's still on the job.
We need to make a quick stop.
Okay.
You know what?
We're still at least 30 minutes out
if you wanted to crawl into
the back and catch some zs,
I got some blankets in the truck.
Yeah, that'd be nice.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Sleep tight sweetheart,
I'll wake you when we get to the station.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Aw, sorry, the Matteson's aren't here.
They should be back later this evening.
Actually I was hoping I could
have a moment with you?
Are you Christian Burton?
Yeah, is there, is there a problem?
Nah, nothing like that.
I just had a few questions
about the Andersen estate?
You built the greenhouse
for them a while back, right?
I did yeah.
I guess that was four years ago.
Did you hear the news at all today?
No, why?
Well, it turns out that Thomas
used the greenhouse you built for them
to store some remains
of a very unfortunate young lady.
Um, I'm sorry to hear that.
My sympathies to the family.
Yeah, but I just had a few questions
about the cellar built into the foundation.
What, the mushroom house.
Is that what that's for?
Growing mushrooms.
Well, it's not for everyone,
but, for some gardeners
mircroculture's part
of the experience yeah.
So I'm assuming this mushroom house
is on the blueprints you submitted
and Thomas signed off on them.
Of course.
Would you happen to have
a copy of the original.
The city seems to have lost their copy.
That would be an extremely
beneficial piece of evidence.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm sure I got them.
It might take me a couple
of days to get them.
I mean, that was four years ago
and I'll probably have
to dig them out of storage.
That's fine, do you have a card,
something with your info.
City doesn't have anything.
Here.
Thanks.
I'll be in touch.
Anything to help.
You said you built that greenhouse
four years ago, right?
What time of the year was that?
Early September, late October.
That's around the time
that girl went missing,
Jennifer Easton.
I don't recall seeing your name
on any police report.
Anyone ever ask you to give a statement?
No.
Do you mind coming down
to the station with me,
making a full report?
What have you done?
Go back to the car.
Wake up.
No, no, no, oh my God, no.
Oh my God.
No.
No, no, please.
Let me out.
Fucking shit, no.
Please.
No, no, no, no, no.
Let me.
Please.
Don't, don't touch me.
Don't.
Please, please don't.
Please don't.
don't, don't, don't.
Please.
Oh, no. No. Oh my God.
No. No.
No.
This is for your own good.
I can't hear you.
Stop.
Oh God.
Oh my God.
Fuck you.
Ahh.
Ahhh.
You have a beautiful figure.
That's not me.
I'm over here.
And your dog.
Everyone at school calls me the fetus,
it's like they don't want
anything to do with me.
And I was so excited about
skipping seventh and eighth
and going straight to high school,
but, now I think it was the
biggest mistake I've ever made.
Baby soon, you're gonna become
the most beautiful girl in school.
Really?
I got you something.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
By the time that you graduate,
I will have saved up enough
money to move us both to Paris.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Thank you Lily.
You're the best mom
a little sister could ever want.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry for what
happened to you that day.
It was my fault.
It was my stupid idea to move to Paris.
It's not your fault.
I was excited to go.
I wanted to go.
I cherished every moment
I ever spent with you Lily.
You made me happy every day of my life.
I love you.
And I'll always love you.
Don't go.
Please don't go.
♪ I will do my puppet show
any day or night for you. ♪
♪ I'll kick my heels and add some
frills and tap a toe or two. ♪
♪ You know just how to make
expressions on my face. ♪
Hey, I'm gonna leave here in a second.
Hello?
Hey, are, are you okay?
Hey. Where's your mom?