Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(ETHEREAL MUSIC ECHOES)
(WATER ECHOING)
(MUSIC CRESCENDO)
(SPLASH)
- (BELL RINGING)
- (LAUGHTER)
(SPLASHING)
(COUGHING)
(LAUGHTER)
(CHATTER)
Oh, really? Okay, okay.
Yeah, why not?
Hey, isn't that Mia?
CATHERINE: I'm so sorry,
I-I must have slipped.
- GIRL: Did you have a nice swim there?
- (LAUGHTER, SPLASHING)
Don't touch me.
- (LAUGHTER)
- GIRL: Oh, my God!
CATHERINE: It was an accident, I swear.
(GIGGLING)
Dude, your sister is so lame.
She's not my sister.
Come on.
ALEXA: Let's go.
(LAUGHTER)
Oh, my God!
CATHERINE: Such a loser!
(CHATTER)
Why is she all wet? I swear!
I'm sorry about that.
But we are going to
see you tomorrow, right?
Yeah. Tomorrow.
Okay. Bye.
It's going to be amazing! I promise!
Amazing! Bring your bikini!
Do you want to tell me what happened?
You should just drive.
(UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC)
Hey, Mrs. Riley.
Hey!
Whoa, did you go for
a swim in your clothes?
MIA: Shut up, Ben!
Hey, Mimi!
MIA: Don't call me that!
Why are you all wet?
Why is she all wet?
I have to talk to her, babe.
What happened? Hey! What happened?
Somebody pushed her in the pool at school.
No big deal.
It's not my fault that nobody likes her.
You know, that's a real nasty thing to say.
Sorry.
Sasha!
Look, I know it's tough moving here,
but you two got to look
out for each other, okay?
Okay.
Thanks.
You guys about done?
Yeah, you are all loaded up, boss.
Alright. Thanks, Ben.
See you tomorrow?
See you tomorrow, Carl. Get some rest.
Yeah. I will do.
Alright, thanks.
(BIRDS SINGING, TREES RUSTLING)
(KNOCK ON THE DOOR)
JENNIFER: Hey. Mind if I come in?
What's going on?
I hate it here.
Mia, you're so much stronger
than you think you are.
And if your Mom were here,
she'd be really proud of you.
Well, she's not here, is she?
Well, I'm proud to call you my daughter.
Look, I know you and Sasha have a
hard time sometimes, but we're family.
She's not my sister.
(WAVES LAPPING)
(GRANT MURMURS)
It's very good.
It's great.
(GRANT SIGHS)
Hey, I almost forgot to show you
guys what I found this morning.
Look at this.
(JENNIFER MURMURS)
MIA: That's a shark tooth.
Yeah.
MIA: Is it a great white?
GRANT: I think so.
Where did you find it?
We uncovered a passageway that
leads to a new part of the city.
JENNIFER: Nice.
MIA: But how did the shark get in there?
I don't know.
Maybe he swam in from
the sea, chasing a seal,
GRANT: got lost in the
tunnels hundreds of years ago.
That's so cool!
GRANT: You can keep it.
That kind of brings me
around to something else.
GRANT: Girls, I know I said I was
going to hang with you this weekend,
GRANT: but opening this new passageway,
GRANT: it means that there's
this team of archaeologists.
- GRANT: They fly in from Europe next week.
- MIA: It's fine, Dad.
So I got to finish mapping
the caves, laying the lights...
You don't have to explain.
But your father planned something
very special for the two of you.
What?
Well, the shark tooth is a clue.
(CHUCKLE)
Girls, come on. Here, show them.
JENNIFER: There you go.
A glass bottomed boat ride
SASHA: to see great white
sharks in their natural habitat?
Sounds fun to me.
No. This is for tourists.
Well, we're kind of tourists.
Girls, it's going to be awesome.
They take you out to where
the great whites feed.
You get to watch them through this
viewing gallery in the bottom of the ship.
GRANT: It's awesome.
No. I have plans for tomorrow.
Well, you'll just have
to rearrange your plans.
And besides, I think this is a
wonderful way for the two of you
- JENNIFER: to spend quality time together.
- GRANT: Yeah.
(SIGH)
JENNIFER: Where are you going?
To let Alexa and Nicole know
that I can't hang out tomorrow.
Is that okay?
Watch your tone.
Well, I am sorry about tomorrow, but
the sharks are going to be really cool.
And maybe next week you
and I can go scuba diving.
GRANT: Remember how much you
used to like diving with me?
Yeah, I was, like, ten years old, Dad.
Ten years old. The youngest
person I'd ever seen scuba dive.
Come on. Are you kidding me?
JENNIFER: And the cutest.
GRANT: Yeah, you were
like a little sea monkey.
(JENNIFER LAUGHS)
(MUSIC)
ANNOUNCER: Alright, guys. Who's
ready to see some sharks today?
- (BEN LAUGHS)
- (CROWD NOISE)
GRANT: I'll pick you up
on the way home. Okay?
GRANT: Alright.
GRANT: Hey, Mimi, don't
get eaten by a shark!
Stop!
Yeah, Mimi, don't get eaten by a shark!
(BEN LAUGHS)
(CARL HOLLERS)
Hey, if you start to drown,
we'll come and save you.
I'll save you!
- (LAUGHTER)
- (CAR HORN BEEPS)
(CARL AND BEN HOLLER)
(GASPS)
Look!
CATHERINE: I can't believe she's here.
Oh, my gosh!
- (CAR SCREECHES)
- (CAR HORN BEEPS)
(CAR SCREECHES)
(HORN BEEPS)
What the hell are you guys doing here?
NICOLE: Come on. We had plans.
I told you, I can't.
Dude, I am going to
take you to a place that
no tourists would ever
find in a million years.
Chance of a lifetime.
Or would you rather stay
on this stupid boat instead?
Yeah.
ALEXA: I mean stay. Stay if you want to.
Hey, maybe you can become
friends with Catherine.
(CATHERINE GIGGLES)
ALEXA: Talk about how beautiful she is!
She is beautiful though.
Dude, shut up!
It's up to you.
- NICOLE: Come on!
- SASHA: One second.
(TONGUE CLICKS)
SASHA: You really want to spend
all day on a boat with those girls?
SASHA: Come on.
CATHERINE: She's so scared.
- (ALEXA SIGHS)
- NICOLE: What do you think?
I don't know.
Don't let those girls get to you.
Catherine.
(GASPS)
SASHA: Come on.
(LAUGHTER)
Goodbye, Catherine.
(UPBEAT POP MUSIC)
Let's go. Come on.
(CHEERING)
(HOLLERING)
(GIGGLING)
(EXCITED CHATTER)
(LAUGHTER AND CHATTER)
(MUSIC ECHOES)
(JUNGLE WILDLIFE SOUNDS)
Okay, watch your step.
(ALEXA GASPS)
ALEXA: Guys, come on! We're almost there.
SASHA: You keep saying that.
ALEXA: This time I mean it.
(ALEXA SIGHS)
(GASPS)
Oh, my God!
(NICOLE CHUCKLES)
NICOLE: Whoa!
SASHA: I mean, how did you
even find out about this place?
ALEXA: Ben took me here.
SASHA: Ben? Like my
stepdad's assistant Ben?
Oh, she... stop with that. Oh, my God!
(GIGGLING)
Okay, so how do we get down there?
So there's a path that'll
take us around and down.
(NICOLE SCREAMS)
- (NICOLE CHEERS)
- (SPLASH)
Or you could go that way.
- (NICOLE GASPS)
What are you waiting for?
It's amazing!
SASHA: I don't know, I...
(ALEXA SCREAMS)
- (SPLASH)
- (ALEXA CHEERS)
We should take the path.
(ALEXA AND NICOLE LAUGH AND SHRIEK)
That was amazing!
Screw the path.
(MIA AND SASHA SCREAM)
(UPBEAT POP MUSIC)
(SPLASH)
(LAUGHTER)
(MIA AND NICOLE CHEER)
(HAPPY CHATTER)
- (SHRIEKS)
- (SPLASH)
- (CHEERING)
- (SHRIEKS)
- (SPLASH)
(LAUGHTER)
(MUSIC FADES)
That's so cool.
NICOLE: Look at all this stuff.
Whoa.
(SASHA GASPS)
SASHA: That's a lot of scuba gear.
This is all the equipment that your
stepdad and Ben have been storing
for the archaeologist team
that's coming next week.
Is this the entrance to the City?
MIA: Guys, if my Dad finds
us, he's going to kill us.
ALEXA: Chill. I talked to Ben.
ALEXA: Your Dad is on the other side,
mapping out the new tunnel they found.
ALEXA: They will never know we were here.
Doesn't look like much of a city to me.
It's Mayan.
It was built underground,
out of their burial sites,
to hide from the Conquistadors
when they invaded.
Rising sea levels put
most of it underwater.
NICOLE: Thank you, Professor.
NICOLE: Did Ben ever take
you diving into the city?
Yeah, once.
MIA: What's it like?
It's pretty insane down there.
I mean, we only went as
far as the first cave.
It was built as an entrance to
- ALEXA: ...is it Xibalba? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- MIA: Xibalba! Yeah!
- MIA: Place of fear.
- ALEXA: Yeah.
Like I was saying, the Mayan underworld.
Burial caves.
Yeah, it's pretty scary,
but it's really cool.
They have all these old
statues, and altars, and stuff.
So what are we waiting for?
Come on. Just the first cave.
- MIA: But my Dad...
- NICOLE: Is miles away!
Yeah, they have a different way in.
Here, look. Everything we need.
I mean, there's no fins, so...
Come on! It's the first cave.
We're not swimming the whole city.
Guys, cave diving is dangerous.
NICOLE MOCKING MIA:
Cave diving is dangerous!
SASHA: No. Mia is right, Nicole.
I don't really know about this.
Look, we've come all this way and
we don't even see the temple? Really?
- It's unlike anything you ever seen before.
- NICOLE: Yeah.
ALEXA: We should just go in, go once
around the first cave, and then out.
NICOLE: Yeah. Come on.
When was the last time you went diving?
Years ago.
- MIA: I used to go all the time with Dad,
- ALEXA: Perfect.
but I've never been in caves before.
It's like riding a bike, right? I mean...
NICOLE: Come on, Mia!
Mimi!
NICOLE: Yeah, she's going to do it!
Let's go! Let's go, that's great!
- ALEXA AND SASHA: Let's go, Mia! Yes!
- NICOLE: Come on! We're doing it, let's go!
Hey, it's going to be fun, okay?
Just remember, keep your
movements nice and small.
Last thing you want to do
is kick up silt down there.
You won't be able to see your own hands.
ALEXA: Okay. You guys ready?
I'm going to lead. Keep
behind me at all times.
One circuit around the
first cave, and back.
NICOLE: Yes, teacher.
ALEXA: Nicole, I'm serious.
Either you do as I say, or...
- Yeah, I hear you.
- (SPLASH)
we don't do it at all.
(NICOLE GIGGLES)
- (UNDERWATER ECHO)
- (SPLASH)
(NICOLE SHRIEKS AND LAUGHS)
NICOLE: Let's go, ladies. Get a move on.
Everyone okay? Sasha, are you good?
Yeah.
ALEXA: Mia?
Yeah, I'm good.
Everybody check your air gauges.
You should all have a full tank.
MIA: Mine's on 100 percent.
SASHA: Me too.
NICOLE: Come on, I'm getting old already!
Okay. Turn your lights on.
Follow me. The entrance is
just at the bottom of the steps.
Let's go.
- (WATER MOVEMENT)
- (BREATHING)
ALEXA: You guys are going to
freak out. It's insane down there.
ALEXA: Come on!
SASHA: Oh, my God. Are you sure about this?
ALEXA: Yeah, trust me.
NICOLE: Oh, my God! This is so crazy!
ALEXA: I can't believe we're
doing this. (ALEXA LAUGHS)
Look at that.
(BUBBLING SOUND)
ALEXA: Run out of air in a cave, and your
last chance is sucking the air from those.
Seriously?
ALEXA: For sure. You want to try it?
The corridor gets narrow
up here, so single file.
Just through here.
ALEXA: You all okay?
- NICOLE: Yup.
- SASHA: Yeah.
MIA: Yeah, I'm good.
NICOLE: Sasha, you could barely
get your ass through there.
(SASHA LAUGHS)
Shut up, Nicole. At least I have an ass.
ALEXA: All okay? Mia?
- MIA: Yeah.
- ALEXA: Sasha?
- (SASHA MURMURS)
- ALEXA: Nicole?
NICOLE: Yes, teacher!
You guys ready for this?
(GENERATOR SOUND)
(GASPS) NICOLE: Holy...
SASHA: ...crap!
- MIA: That's so cool!
- (SASHA LAUGHS)
ALEXA: I told you guys.
Xibalba.
This place is insane, right?
Hey. Nicole! No!
Keep behind me and keep together.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
One lap around the altar,
and then we head back, right?
SASHA: Right.
Let's go.
(NICOLE GIGGLES)
(GIGGLES) (GASPS)
Oh, my God!
MIA: They made human sacrifices here.
Creepy.
NICOLE: Guys, did you see that?
I think I saw something move.
ALEXA: There's nothing down here, Nicole.
NICOLE: There was something there.
- ALEXA: Oh, come on, Nicole.
- (SASHA LAUGHS)
Maybe it was a mermaid.
NICOLE: Shut up, Sasha. I'm serious.
ALEXA: Come on, Nicole.
Stop messing around.
MIA: Maybe it was my Dad.
ALEXA: Your Dad's on the
other side of the city.
ALEXA: There's nothing there.
Nicole's just being an idiot.
NICOLE: I heard that, Alexa.
Come on, let's just go back.
We said we would come in, and
then head straight back out, right?
ALEXA: Nicole!
Nicole?
SASHA: Nicole, stop being an idiot.
(SIGH)
NICOLE: Come, look, look!
NICOLE: Look!
ALEXA: Oh, my God!
NICOLE: Where are its eyes?
MIA: It doesn't have any.
MIA: It's a Mexican
tetra... a blind cave fish.
ALEXA: Wait, I heard about these.
No light down here, so they
don't need color or eyes.
They evolved without.
SASHA: How does it know where it's going?
MIA: Heightened senses.
I didn't know they got this big.
It's probably never known a human.
It's hiding from us.
Well, who says it's us it's hiding from?
Stop! (LAUGHTER)
- NICOLE: Here, fishy fishy! Nice to meet...
- ALEXA: No, Nicole. I wouldn't.
- (SCREECHING)
- (NICOLE SCREAMS)
- ALEXA: No!
(NICOLE SCREAMS)
No, stop it from falling!
No!
(PILLAR CRUMBLING SOUND)
(MIA'S MUFFLED SCREAMS)
MIA: Guys? Guys?
(DISTORTED RADIO VOICE)
MIA: I can't hear you!
ALEXA'S VOICE DISTORTED: Nobody move!
MIA: Anyone? Nicole? Sasha, where are you?
(ALEXA'S VOICE DISTORTED)
MIA: Guys? I can't see
you guys, where are you?
(MIA BREATHING FRANTICALLY)
MIA: Sasha... I can't hear
you, guys, where are you?
MIA: Sasha!
MIA: I can't see anyone.
(ALEXA'S VOICE DISTORTED)
MIA CRYING: Sasha!
(MIA BREATHING FRANTICALLY)
Sasha!
Alexa, I can't see!
ALEXA'S VOICE DISTORTED: Mia!
BEN: Mia! What are you doing here?
Oh, my God! I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- MIA: We were at the lake and...
- BEN: Whoa, whoa. Whoa, whoa.
- BEN: Calm down, alright? It's okay.
- MIA: It was really stupid, I'm sorry.
Let me guess. Alexa persuaded
you to come down here, huh?
And then we knocked over a stone column,
and I got totally lost in the silt.
You didn't think to come
down here with a guideline?
ALEXA: Mia! Mia! Thank God!
BEN: Oh, man, I should've known.
So you thought you'd try a
little bit of cave diving, huh?
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Honestly, we were supposed to just go
in and then straight back out again.
BEN: That's the last time I'm
showing you any of my secret spots.
BEN: I take it Sasha
and Nicole are close by?
ALEXA: They're waiting by the exit.
BEN: Yeah? What a surprise.
BEN: Let's just get you guys the hell
out of here before your Dad finds out.
MIA: You're not going to tell him, are you?
BEN: Are you kidding me?
- (CRASHING WATER SOUNDS)
- (MIA AND ALEXA SCREAM)
- (WATER SPLASHING AS BEN STRUGGLES)
- (BEN SCREAMS)
MIA: Alexa, where are the others?
MIA, FRANTICALLY: Where are
they? Sasha? Nicole? Sasha?
SASHA'S VOICE ON RADIO: Mia! Where are you?
NICOLE: Sasha! Look
they're here, they're here!
MIA: Guys, there's a shark.
SASHA: Mia, what is it?
MIA: There's a shark. I'm serious.
MIA: It killed Ben.
SASHA: What?
ALEXA CRYING: We have
to go. We have to go now.
NICOLE: You're really
freaking me out right now.
SASHA: Guys, if this is some
kind of joke, it's not funny.
MIA: Sasha, behind you!
SASHA: Yeah, right. (SASHA SCREAMS)
- (SHARK HAMMERING AGAINST ROCKS)
- SASHA SHOUTING: Shark!
(SASHA SCREAMS)
(ROCKS CRUMBLING)
SASHA: Swim! Swim! Go on!
(SCREAMS)
SASHA: Guys, come on, move! Move!
The tunnel is starting to
collapse. We need to hurry.
(ROCKS CRUMBLING)
(CAVE WALLS CRACKING)
SASHA SHOUTING: Keep
going, come on, go, go!
- (SOUND OF ROCK FALLING)
- SASHA: Alexa!
(ROCKS SETTLING ON THE CAVE FLOOR)
- (ALEXA SHRIEKS)
- (HANDS PULLING ON ROCKS)
SASHA: What do I do, Alexa, what do I do?
Push. Help me push. Come on.
Push.
Help me move these rocks.
(NICOLE BREATHING FRANTICALLY)
ALEXA: Push.
NICOLE: We're trapped.
ALEXA: There has to be a way out.
ALEXA: Come on.
SASHA: You guys, it's pointless.
It's pointless. Alexa! Alexa!
(ALEXA GROANS)
SASHA: Alexa! Look at me.
SASHA: You said Ben and my Dad
went through a different entrance.
ALEXA: Sasha, this place is a maze.
I would never be able to find him.
MIA: Guys! Guys, there's a line.
Ben... Ben, he had the guideline with him.
It leads back to where they were working.
NICOLE: What about the shark?
MIA: It looked blind. Like the tetra fish.
MIA: It must have evolved down here.
When my dad opened up the new
cave, it must have let him through.
SASHA: Mia, was that a great white?
Yeah, I think so.
Everybody check your air.
SASHA: I have about forty percent left.
SASHA: What about you guys?
MIA: I have forty.
NICOLE: Thirty eight.
ALEXA: Thirty five.
Okay, we don't have much of
a choice, as far as I can see.
Everyone needs to stay close, okay?
ALEXA: But what about the shark?
MIA: We can do this, Alexa.
It's going to be okay.
SASHA: Okay, come on. Let's go.
(SWIMMING SOUNDS)
(EDGY MUSIC)
(MIA'S CLOSE BREATHING SOUNDS)
SASHA WHISPERING: The guideline.
SASHA WHISPERING: I can see it.
(SASHA) Stay close.
SASHA: If we follow the line,
it will take us to Grant.
ALEXA: Yeah. Come on, let's go.
(MIA'S CLOSE BREATHING SOUNDS)
MIA: The line leads down here.
(MIA STRUGGLING)
SASHA: This way.
SASHA: Are you okay, Mia?
MIA: Yeah.
(ALEXA BREATHING ANXIOUSLY)
(NICOLE BREATHING ANXIOUSLY)
(SWIMMING SOUNDS)
(SOUND OF FISH SWIMMING)
(SOUND OF SASHA BREATHING)
NICOLE: Oh, my God! What is this place?
MIA: Catacombs. This city was
built out of their burial chambers.
SASHA: The line's caught on something.
(ALEXA PANICS) ALEXA: Come
on. Sasha, we need to move.
(EERIE MUSIC)
SASHA: Guys.
(ALEXA SHIVERS WITH FEAR)
What are we going to do?
SASHA: We need to keep going.
We're going to die down here.
SASHA: No. Grant has to be close.
SASHA: We can't give up.
(ALEXA CRYING)
(EERIE MUSIC)
(SASHA'S CLOSE BREATHING)
ALEXA: No, no, it's a dead
end. We have to go back.
SASHA: There's no other way.
Where are we going to go back to?
ALEXA: We're going to run out
of air. We're going to drown.
ALEXA: We're going to drown!
Wait! Wait!
- (WATER MOVEMENT)
- (MECHANICAL MOTOR SOUND)
(CLANK OF METAL ON ROCK)
MIA ANXIOUSLY: Where are
they? Sasha, where's Dad?
He must be close. Grant!
- MIA: Dad!
- SASHA: Grant!
- MIA: Dad! Where are you, Dad?
- MIA: Dad!
- NICOLE: Grant, can you hear us?
ALEXA: There's another way through.
- (JUMP SCARE LOUD CRASHING SOUND)
- (ALEXA SCREAMS)
MIA SHOUTING: Get down! (MIA SHRIEKS)
(CRUNCHING OF METAL)
(MIA WHIMPERS)
(MIA SCARED BREATHING)
(SASHA CRYING)
(SHARK SWIMMING SOUND)
(ALEXA WHIMPERING)
(ALEXA CRYING WITH FEAR)
(MIA BREATHING ANXIOUSLY)
(HIGH PITCHED ALARM RINGING ON AIR GAUGE)
Turn it off!
- (SASHA SHRIEKING)
- (ALARM CONTINUES RINGING)
(ALEXA SHRIEKS)
(MIA GASPS)
(MIA SHRIEKS)
NICOLE: This way.
(FRANTIC BREATHING)
NICOLE: Keep going.
(NICOLE SHRIEKS) (BANGING ON METAL GRID)
NICOLE: Go! Go now!
(ALEXA SHRIEKS)
NICOLE: Come on!
NICOLE: Come on, get in! Go!
(NICOLE SCREAMS)
(SHARK CRASHING INTO GRID REPEATEDLY)
(SHARK CRASHING INTO GRID)
- (SCREAMS)
- (SHARK BATTERING THE GRID)
NICOLE SHOUTING: This way!
- (METAL BEING STRUCK FORCEFULLY)
- (ALEXA SHRIEKS)
Come on!
(ALEXA SCREAMS)
NICOLE: This way! Let's go!
NICOLE: Hurry! Come on!
(SHRIEKS) (FRANTIC BREATHING)
(SURFACING SPLASHES)
(GASPING BREATHS) (COUGHING)
ALEXA: Did the shark follow us?
MIA: I think we're safe here.
MIA: It's too narrow
for the shark to follow.
- MIA: Are you okay?
- ALEXA: I'm fine.
(COUGHING)
SASHA: Guys, the air tastes bad.
ALEXA: It's an air pocket.
It's been here a while.
We can't breathe it for long.
MIA: So what do we do?
SASHA: I can't see any way out of here.
SASHA: How much air do you have left?
MIA: I've got twenty two percent.
- SASHA: I'm on twenty.
- ALEXA: Nineteen.
NICOLE: Twenty one.
NICOLE: Do you hear that?
- NICOLE: Shhh. Listen. Listen.
- (DISTANT MUSIC BEATS)
I think it's music.
- That's impossible.
- MIA: Yeah.
MIA: It's coming from over here.
(GASPING BREATHS)
MIA: It has to be my Dad.
SASHA: It's a dead end.
(SPLASH)
ALEXA, SASHA, NICOLE: Mia!
(MUFFLED MUSIC: 'The Look' by Roxette).
(SPLASH)
ALEXA: Mia! Mia, are you okay?
- MIA: There's a gap.
- NICOLE: Okay?
- MIA: Yeah. I can get through.
- NICOLE: Okay.
MIA: I'll let you know
when I'm on the other side.
ALEXA: No. We should stay together.
There's no point in
all of us using our air.
SASHA: Are you sure you can do this?
- MIA: Yeah.
- SASHA: Please be careful.
- MIA: Okay.
- SASHA: Okay, we're going to be right here.
- NICOLE: Yeah.
- MIA: Okay.
(MUSIC PLAYING LOUDLY
- 'The Look' by Roxette)
(SOUND OF A WELDING
EQUIPMENT OVER THE MUSIC)
(MUSIC ECHOES OUTSIDE OF CARL'S CAVE)
MIA: Dad!
(MIA STRUGGLING TO PULL HERSELF UP)
- (CARL HUMS ALONG TO THE MUSIC)
- (WELDING SOUNDS)
(CLANK OF METAL)
CARL: I was mid jam right now.
Grant?
Ben?
(METAL CLINKING IN THE DISTANCE)
(SOUND OF CARL PUTTING
DOWN HIS WELDING TORCH)
CARL: Come on, guys.
Seriously, stop messing around.
(MUSIC PLAYER ERROR MESSAGE)
Track error. Please reset.
(MUSIC PLAYER ERROR MESSAGE) Track error.
(SOUND OF CHAINS MOVING)
(MUSIC PLAYING The Carpenters
"We've Only Just Begun")
(CHAINS CLINKING)
CARL: What?
- (EERIE MUSIC CRESCENDO)
- (CARL SCREAMS)
(EMERGENCY ALARM BEEPING REPEATEDLY)
MIA: What is that?
ALEXA'S VOICE OVER THE RADIO:
It's an emergency alarm.
ALEXA'S VOICE OVER THE RADIO: Designed
to help locate a diver in a cave.
MIA: Dad!
- (CARL SCREAMS)
- (SLICING, SQUELCHING  SOUNDS)
(MIA STRUGGLING TO PULL HERSELF UP)
MIA: I'm through.
SASHA'S VOICE ON THE
RADIO: Can you see anything?
MIA: Dad?
MIA: I can't see anything,
but I can hear the alarm.
MIA: Carl?
(MIA BREATHING ANXIOUSLY)
MIA: Dad!
(SOUND OF THE ALARM GETTING LOUDER)
I see it! I see the alarm!
- (ALARM SOUND STOPS)
- (MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
MIA: Dad!
(MIA BREATHING ANXIOUSLY)
Dad!
- (JUMP SCARE LOUD SOUND)
- (MIA SCREAMS)
MIA SHOUTING: Guys!
(MIA BREATHING FRANTICALLY)
MIA SHOUTING: Guys, I can't hear you!
MIA SHOUTING: Dad!
MIA SHOUTING: Dad! Help!
(WATER MOVEMENT)
NICOLE: Why isn't she back yet?
SASHA: Mia! Mia!
SASHA: Mia!
- (SURFACING SPLASHES)
- (SASHA GASPS)
SASHA: She's not responding.
We have to go help her.
ALEXA: What if the shark got her?
MIA: Guys, guys, I'm
lost. I can't hear you.
MIA: Can you hear me?
(SASHA'S DISTORTED VOICE ON RADIO)
MIA: Guys, I can't hear you.
- (SASHA'S DISTORTED VOICE ON RADIO)
- (MIA BREATHES FRANTICALLY)
Can you hear me?
(MIA SCREAMS)
GRANT QUIETLY: What are you doing here?
We just wanted to see the main
entrance, but then the tunnel collapsed.
Ben and Carl are both dead.
GRANT: Where's Sasha?
MIA: We found a small air pocket.
MIA: She's back there with Alexa and
Nicole, but I can't hear them any more.
GRANT: It's because these columns
are breaking up the radio signal.
GRANT: You're low on air.
- GRANT: We'll get them. Follow me.
- MIA: Okay.
(SWIMMING SOUNDS)
(SASHA'S DISTORTED VOICE ON RADIO)
SASHA SHOUTING: Mia! Mia,
behind you! (BANGING ROCKS)
- SASHA: Over here! Over here!
- (MIA SHRIEKS)
(BANGING ROCKS)
(SASHA SHRIEKS)
ALEXA: Hey! Over here! (BANGING ROCKS)
(ALEXA SHRIEKS) (BANGING ROCKS)
Over here!
(NICOLE WHIMPERS)
(NICOLE BANGING ROCKS)
NICOLE: Over here! Over here!
- (NICOLE SHRIEKS)
- (TORCH SWISHING THROUGH WATER)
(SHARK MOVEMENT IN WATER)
Swim!
- (SWIMMING SOUNDS)
- (ALEXA GASPING)
(NICOLE SHRIEKS)
GRANT: This way!
(FRANTIC BREATHING)
(FRANTIC SWIMMING)
(SHARK MOVEMENT IN WATER)
- (NICOLE SCREAMS)
- (SHARK POUNDS ROCKS)
(NICOLE SHRIEKS)
- (SHARK POUNDING AGAINST ROCKS)
- (NICOLE SHRIEKS)
NICOLE SHOUTING: Swim! Come on!
(FRANTIC BREATHING)
- (BIRDSONG)
- (GRANT GASPS)
- (GASPING)
- (SURFACING SPLASHES)
- (WATER LAPPING)
- (BIRDSONG)
- (GRANT GASPS)
- (ALEXA GASPS)
(ALEXA AND NICOLE GASP)
- MIA SHRIEKING: We did it!
- (SASHA GASPS)
(RELIEVED GASPS)
SASHA: Oh, Mia!
(RELIEVED GIGGLES)
SASHA: You guys!
NICOLE: I love you guys!
- ALEXA: We made it!
- NICOLE: You saved us, Mia!
ALEXA: I thought we were
going to die down there.
GRANT: Okay, girls, this is an ascender.
(GASPING)
GRANT: You got to get
yourself into this harness.
GRANT: Get your foot in this loop.
And this, you got to work up and down.
Pump down, push up. Pump down, push up.
- ALEXA: Yeah.
- GRANT: Okay?
- GRANT: We'll get out of here soon.
- ALEXA: Okay.
- GRANT: You ready?
- ALEXA: Yeah.
- GRANT: Okay. Push.
(ALEXA GRUNTS)
GRANT: Yeah! You got to
use all your strength.
- ALEXA: Okay.
- GRANT: Push and pull.
GRANT: That's it, yeah!
- (NICOLE HOLLERS)
- ALEXA: I'm a natural.
- NICOLE: Alright, go back. Come on.
- ALEXA: Okay.
GRANT: One more time. Hard as you can.
- GRANT: Yeah.
- ALEXA: Okay.
(ALEXA GASPS AND GIGGLES) ALEXA: Okay.
GRANT: Yeah! Keep going.
MIA SHOUTING: Guys! Guys, there's a shark!
(SCREAMING)
- NICOLE SHOUTING: Get me out of here!
- (SPLASHING)
(ALEXA SCREAMS)
ALEXA SHOUTING: Nicole,
I can't pull us both up.
ALEXA SHOUTING: Get off, Nicole!
NICOLE SCREAMING: I got to get out of here!
(NICOLE AND ALEXA SCREAM)
It's not going to hold both of you.
(METAL ROPES CREAKING)
- MIA SHOUTING: Let go, Nicole!
- SASHA: Alexa!
ALEXA: Nicole, you got to get down!
- (SCREAMING)
- MIA: Oh, my God, there's two sharks!
(SHARK MOVEMENT IN WATER)
- (ALEXA AND NICOLE SCREAM)
- (ROPES CREAK)
- ALEXA: No!
- SASHA: Alexa!
NICOLE SCREAMING: I got to
get out of here! I'm sorry!
(METAL ROPES CREAKING)
- GRANT: No!
- ALEXA: Please let go!
(ANCHOR SNAPS FROM ROCK)
- (ALEXA SCREAMS)
- (ANCHOR SCRAPING)
- (SPLASH)
MIA: Alexa!
(ALEXA SCREAMS)
(SHARK MOVEMENT IN WATER)
- (SPLASH)
- (SCREAMS)
GRANT: Unhook yourself
from that harness right now!
GRANT: Unhook yourself!
(ANCHOR RATTLING)
(ROPES WHIPPING AWAY)
- (NICOLE GROANS)
- (ALEXA SCREAMS AND SPLASHES)
(SPLASHING)
(NICOLE GRUNTS)
(NICOLE SHRIEKS)
- (ROCK MOVING)
- (NICOLE SCREAMS)
(NICOLE SCREAMS. SLOW MOTION ECHO)
(SPLASH)
(SHARK MOVEMENT IN WATER. IMPACT SOUND)
- (ALEXA SCREAMS)
- MIA: Alexa!
(SHRIEKING)
- GRANT: Girls!
- SASHA: Mia, quick!
ALEXA SCREAMING: Help! Someone help!
MIA: Nobody can hear you, Alexa.
ALEXA: Someone will hear us.
ALEXA: They'll hear this.
- ALEXA SCREAMING: Help! Someone help!
- (EMERGENCY ALARM SOUNDING)
- ALEXA SHOUTING: Help! Please!
- SASHA: Alexa, no one can hear you.
- SASHA: Turn it off!
- GRANT: Girls. Girls.
- SASHA: Shut it off!
- ALEXA: Don't!
GRANT: Girls! Girls! Look!
(GASPING)
They're gone.
Where did they go?
MIA: They're scared of it.
The sharks... they've evolved blind,
and they have a heightened
sense of hearing.
GRANT: It must be the frequency.
MIA: Maybe we can use the
alarm to scare them away.
MIA: I mean, someone's
going to come looking
for us when we don't
come back tonight, right?
SASHA: The only people that know
where we are, are right here.
GRANT: I just found the
entrance to this cave.
GRANT: I'm the only one
who knows where it is.
GRANT: And there's no way we can
get back up without the ascender.
SASHA: What are we going to do?
GRANT: We got to go back
down. There's no other way now.
- ALEXA: What?
- MIA: What?
GRANT: Listen, this
cave goes out to the sea.
If we follow it, we'll
come out in the ocean.
GRANT: There'll be strong currents there
that are going to try and suck us down.
GRANT: So we're going
to have to keep together.
ALEXA: No. We're going to die down there.
GRANT: If we stay here, we'll die.
We're going to watch each other's backs.
And we can survive this.
Okay? Girls, I believe in you.
- (LOUD SPLASH)
- (GRANT SHRIEKS)
(GRANT SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
MIA: Dad!
MIA: Dad! Dad!
(SCREAMING)
MIA: No!
SASHA: Mia, get back! Mia, get back!
ALEXA SCREAMING: Sound the alarm!
- (EMERGENCY ALARM RINGING)
- (SHRIEKING)
Are they gone?
Are they gone? Can you see it?
I don't see it. I don't see it.
What are we going to do?
We have to do what he said.
- MIA: No!
- ALEXA: Yes, we have to go back down.
I can't. I can't do this. I can't. I can't.
SASHA: Mia, we have to go.
We have to do what he said.
SASHA: We have to go back down.
SASHA: He wouldn't want
you to give up now, okay?
Do we even have enough air?
We have no choice.
What if we're wrong?
What if the alarm has nothing to
do with why the sharks are gone?
We got to try.
You ready?
(ALARM SOUND ECHOES AS IT RINGS REPEATEDLY)
- (ALARM SOUNDS REPEATEDLY)
- (GASPING BREATHS)
- (JUMP SCARE LOUD SOUND)
- (SCREAMS)
(SHRIEKS)
(SASHA SCREAMS)
SASHA: I can't see them. Where did they go?
- MIA: Wait. (SHOUTING) Current!
- (LOUD RUSH OF WATER)
- (SHRIEKS)
- (SOUND OF RUSHING WATER)
(EXPLOSIVE RUSH OF WATER)
(ALEXA SHRIEKS)
(SCREAM)
MIA SHOUTING: Sasha! Give me your hand!
(SASHA SHRIEKS)
SASHA: No!
(SASHA SCREAMS)
SASHA: Help me!
No! No!
MIA: Give me your hand! Come on, I got you.
Help!
MIA: Come on, I got you. Come on.
(LOW AIR ALARM SOUNDS)
(ALEXA SCREAMS) ALEXA: I can't hold on!
The current is too strong!
MIA: Come on! Hold on! Give me your hand!
- ALEXA: I can't hold on!
- SASHA: Mia, help! I'm falling!
Mia! I'm slipping!
MIA: Hold on, Sasha, come on.
MIA SHRIEKING: No! No!
MIA: Sasha!
No! No! Mia!
(SASHA SCREAMS)
Sasha!
(SASHA SCREAMS AND CRIES)
No! Sasha!
ALEXA: Mia! Mia, she's dead.
There's nothing you can do.
MIA: No, you don't know that.
ALEXA: Mia, look at me.
MIA CRYING: I'm going.
ALEXA: We have to keep going,
or we are going to die down here.
ALEXA: Do you understand me?
No!
(MIA SOBBING)
ALEXA: Look. Over there.
ALEXA: That's the way out.
MIA: The current is going to drag us down.
ALEXA: We'll be okay
if we stick to the side.
ALEXA: It's our only chance. Okay?
ALEXA: Okay? I won't leave you.
ALEXA: Grab my hand. Let's go.
(CONTINUOUS STRONG RUSH OF THE CURRENT)
(ALEXA WAILING)
(MIA GASPING)
(MIA GROANS)
- ALEXA: You okay?
- (MIA SHRIEKS)
(MIA GASPING)
ALEXA: Keep moving.
ALEXA: Almost there.
(SUDDEN RUSH OF CURRENT)
ALEXA: Mia! Give me your hand!
- MIA: Alexa!
- ALEXA: Give me your hand!
MIA: I'm coming. I'm coming.
ALEXA: Grab my hand! Grab my hand!
(MIA STRUGGLING)
ALEXA: I got you! I got you!
(MIA WHIMPERING)
ALEXA: Are you okay?
(CONTINUOUS SOUND OF THE CURRENT RUSHING)
(ALEXA WHIMPERING)
ALEXA: Mia, this has to be the way out.
ALEXA: We're almost there.
ALEXA: The exit can't be far.
(ALEXA SCREAMS)
MIA: Alexa!
(MIA SCREAMS)
(ALEXA SCREAMS)
(ALEXA STRUGGLING SOUNDS)
(AIR BUBBLES EXPELLED)
- (MIA SCREAMING)
- (CURRENT RUSHING)
(SASHA GASPS)
MIA CRYING: Oh, my God, you're alive!
MIA: You're alive!
SASHA: We're trapped, Mia!
SASHA CRYING: Mia, we're going
to die. There's no way out.
SASHA CRYING: I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
MIA: Don't be.
SASHA: No, no! it's my fault. If it
wasn't for me, you wouldn't be here.
MIA: Stop! You stop it, okay?
MIA: We can't give up now.
MIA: We can share air. I
have a little more than you.
MIA: Five percent.
MIA: We're not going to die down here.
(CURRENT RAGING)
- MIA: Look!
- SASHA: Where are you going? Mia?
(MIA STRUGGLING)
MIA: Sasha, come here.
MIA: Look. Maybe there's a way through.
SASHA: The current is too
strong, it'll drag us down.
MIA: We have to try.
(MIA AND SASHA STRUGGLING)
(CURRENT RAGING)
(MIA GASPING)
(MIA CLOSE BREATHING)
(SASHA WHIMPERING)
(MOVEMENT THROUGH WATER)
(MIA GASPING)
SASHA: It's a dead end.
MIA: No, it can't be.
MIA: There! Come on!
MIA: I think I can see the sunlight.
SASHA: It's too narrow to climb through.
MIA: There must be another way.
- (LOUD JUMP SCARE MOMENT)
- (SCREAMING)
SASHA: It's circling. Oh, my God! Mia!
- SASHA: Mia! I'm stuck!
- (AIR TANK SCRAPES ROCKS)
(SASHA PANICKING)
SASHA SCREAMING: Mia! It's coming!
(SHRIEKS)
(SHARK HITTING ROCKS)
(AIR TANK SCRAPING PAST ROCKS)
SASHA: I'm stuck! I'm stuck!
(SCREAMS)
(SHARK HITTING ROCKS)
SASHA: Keep going. We
can do it. We can make it.
SASHA: Just keep going. We're almost there.
SASHA: Come on, Mia!
(SASHA STRUGGLING)
Come on, Mia! Keep going!
(MIA AND SASHA STRUGGLING)
SASHA: Come on, Mia.
SASHA: I see light.
(MIA AND SASHA STRUGGLING)
SASHA: Come on. We're so close.
SASHA: Mia, I'm stuck.
SASHA: We're so close.
(AIR GAUGE ALARM FOR LOW AIR)
SASHA: I have to take my pack off.
SASHA: Come on.
(AIR GAUGE ALARM FOR LOW AIR)
MIA: Hold your breath.
(SASHA STRUGGLING)
Help!
(MUSIC CRESCENDO)
- (SURFACING SPLASH)
- (SHRIEKS)
SASHA: Oh, my God! Mia! Mia!
SASHA: Mia! We made it! We did it!
(MIA GASPS)
MIA: There has to be a way up.
MIA: Maybe, maybe we could climb it.
SASHA SHOUTING: Mia! Mia!
SASHA: Mia, look!
- MIA: Oh, my God! Help! Help!
- SASHA: Help! Over here!
- SASHA: Help! Help!
- MIA: Help! Help! Help!
- SASHA: Help!
- MIA: Over here!
Mia, we have to swim.
SASHA: We have to swim. We can do it.
MIA: Help! Help!
SASHA: Come on.
MIA: Over here!
MIA: Help!
(WAVES LAPPING)
MIA: Wait.
(SASHA GASPS)
(DOOR OPENING)
(MUSIC IN CHUM MAN'S EARPHONES)
(SPLASH)
Oh, my God, it's chum! No!
(MUSIC IN CHUM MAN'S EARPHONES)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(CATHERINE GASPS)
CATHERINE: Whoa! Come over here.
CATHERINE: Move!
(MUSIC WITH SENSE OF URGENCY)
(SWIMMING SPLASHES)
(SPLASH)
(SWIMMING SOUNDS, UNDERWATER ECHO)
- (CHATTER INSIDE BOAT)
- CATHERINE: Oh, my God!
CATHERINE: Are you all seeing this?
- (EXCITED CHATTER INSIDE THE BOAT)
- (CATHERINE LAUGHS)
- (SOUND OF HAND HITTING THE GLASS)
- (SCREAMS INSIDE BOAT)
- (HANDS KNOCKING ON WINDOW)
- (CROWD SHRIEKING ON BOAT)
(SCREAMS)
(SHOUTING ON THE DECK OF THE BOAT)
(CREW AND PASSENGERS SHOUTING)
- (LID OPENING)
- (CREW SHOUTING)
(SASHA STRUGGLING)
- (SPLASH)
- (SASHA SCREAMS)
CHUM MAN: Stay back! Stay back!
Sasha!
(WATER SWISHING)
MIA: Get out of my way!
(CLICKS AS FLARE GUN LOADED)
MIA: Move!
(SPLASH)
(SASHA STRUGGLING)
(SLOW MOTION SCREAM)
(SLOW MOTION BURST OF FLARE FROM GUN)
(SLOW MOTION IMPACT SOUND)
- (SURFACING SPLASH)
- (GASPS)
- (CROWD SHOUTING)
- (SURFACING SPLASH)
(SASHA SHRIEKING)
MIA: Come on! Come on!
(FRANTIC SWIMMING SOUNDS)
(CROWD SHOUTING)
(LOUD SPLASH)
(MIA SCREAMING)
(MIA GRUNTS AND POUNDS FISTS)
(MIA SLOW MOTION SHRIEK)
- (SURFACING SPLASH)
- (GASPS)
(CROWD SHOUTING)
CREW MAN SHOUTS: Watch out!
- (SPLASH)
- (SCREAMS)
- (GASPS)
- (CROWD TALKING - SLOW MOTION)
- (MIA SIGHS)
- (SASHA GASPS)
MIA: You're okay?
MIA: Look at me. Look at me.
MIA: Breathe. Breathe.
SASHA SIGHS: Yeah.
MIA: Yeah. Yeah. You're okay.
(UPLIFTING MUSIC)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org