Radio: mariners be advised,
[thunder]
a violent storm
is converging
on the northern
and central california coast
with winds
up to hurricane force.
Man: coast guard base
monterey,
come in. Come in.
There's no power!
The pumps don't work!
Mayday! Mayday!
We're sinking! Mayday!
Rick!
Jason!
Susan: when you're
fighting for your life,
you've got to have a reason
to keep going.
You've got to love someone
or something so much
that you refuse to give up.
I found my reason
after our boat sank
to the bottom
of the pacific ocean.
♪ Jump, hey, girl
♪ come on
♪ come on around here
♪ that's better
♪ what you want, girl?
♪ There's a party over here
♪ uh-huh, yeah
man: look out.
She's on fire today.
♪ And i say, yeah
♪ seems like old times
ooh-whoo! Yeah!
Tip of the day.
Loser buys, all right?
♪ Just wave good-bye
♪ these are the times,
the times of our lives ♪
♪ these are the days
♪ these are the days,
these are the days ♪
♪ of our lives
♪ these are the nights
♪ keep on going
♪ whoo! Come on, now
♪ yeah, all right
♪ hey
♪ i won't be hasty...
let's see, what would
i like to drink?
I can have
anything i want, right?
Nobody likes
a smug winner.
Debbie, give him the cheapest thing on tap.
Nothing for me.
So tell me about
this proposal of yours.
Ok.
How would you like
to make good money
on a beautiful boat
with a killer crew?
This guy i sailed with
last year, rick foster,
he's bringing a 68-foot irwin
up to vancouver next week, ok?
It's a private gig.
He's delivering it to the owner.
We need a crew. We...
matt, i don't know.
Come on.
It'd be a blast.
It sounds great.
I'm sure we'd have fun.
But you know i've given up sailing for a while.
Now, that's the most tragic thing i've heard all day.
Hey, hey, hey.
Rick foster.
Pleasure to meet you,
ms. Clarkson.
Nice to meet you.
You sneak. You planned this,
didn't you?
Guilty as charged.
Plan was
to ambush you.
Now, tell me why
you're landlocked.
Bunch of reasons.
I gotta settle down,
find a steady job.
I understand.
It'll only be
a couple of weeks.
Owner wants the boat in vancouver
by the end
of the month.
I'll pay 500
plus expenses.
That sounds great.
Excellent.
We set sail
next week.
But i can't.
Thanks for the offer.
I really wish i could.
It was nice
to meet you, rick.
See you later, matt.
Right.
I'll call you.
Don't worry.
We got other people we can go to.
Not like her.
So, matt,
how much of this interest is professional?
All of it.
All right.
Well, most of it.
Any luck yesterday?
Nothing i could handle.
$6.00 an hour to give boat rides to tourists just isn't me.
Maybe something without boats would be nice for a change.
Maybe.
Susannah, i, um...
uh-oh.
Uh-oh what?
That's what you used to
call me when i was a kid
and we were gonna
have one of our talks.
But i can't help not wanting you to leave again,
not yet,
not when i feel like we're finally starting to talk.
I'm not leaving.
In fact, i just
turned down an offer
to sail a 68-footer
up the coast.
I worry so much
when you're out there.
I just wish your father
hadn't made you...
he didn't make me
love the ocean.
I just always have.
It's like i never
had a choice.
Such a nomadic
lifestyle.
Constantly moving,
changing friends.
I never know where you are,
whether you're safe.
Mom, stop pushing.
Guess who.
Someone who won't
take no for an answer.
Come on.
You're gonna take the rest of the day off.
It's 10:20. The day
hasn't even started.
Well, all the more reason
to take advantage of it.
No, i can't.
I have to find a job.
Come on.
No, really,
i can't. I can't.
So why is
your mother
so dead set
against sailing?
My dad was a sailor.
Not sailboat racing.
You know, shipyard stuff.
He left
when i was 10,
took a job on some oil rig,
and that was that.
Wow. I'm sorry.
It's ok.
It was years ago.
So why are you
taking this gig?
All i want to do is
build my racing boat,
and that's why i'm taking this job with rick.
That's why i take
all my jobs.
Well, good luck.
Thank you.
Wow.
Matt: she's a beauty, huh?
Go on. Go for it. Rick
wants to show you around.
Keep an open mind.
Not too shabby, huh?
It's an irwin.
Beautiful
craftsmanship.
And she's certainly got all the toys.
So, when did you do
the whitbread?
Um, halfway through my sophomore year of college.
Around the world.
All the way.
Wow. Ha.
Welcome to "no sweat"
sailing.
Go on.
Take a look around.
♪ It's gonna take a lot
to satisfy me... ♪
um, hello?
Hi.
Who are you?
Susan clarkson.
I'm a friend of matt's.
Oh, right.
You must be that girl that rick's been babbling about.
You won the white bread
or something.
I'm allie.
So are you on the crew?
No. The only thing
i do on a boat is tan.
Rick's my boyfriend.
I'm just along
for the ride.
I thought i'd be the only woman on board, but...
no, i'm not going.
Oh, well.
Guess i'll just have to handle those boys on my own.
Nice to meet you, susan.
See you later.
I'm telling you,
it'll be fine.
And i'm telling you,
why do not have enough time.
What, you wanna be
the skipper now,
make all
the big decisions?
Of course not, rick.
I just think you're pushing it here, ok?
And i don't...
susan. Hey.
Hey. How'd it go?
What'd you think?
I just met your,
um... allie.
Oh, yeah?
She's kind of
high maintenance.
Amazing, though.
Kind of
high maintenance?
What are you guys
talking about?
Nothing, just business.
So, anyway, susan,
i don't like to beg,
but we could really
use you on this trip.
Yeah.
I know you want to stay dry for a while,
but we just found out that we have less time
to make vancouver
than rick thought.
We need experienced crew like you.
I wish i could, really,
but i promised...
who,
your boyfriend?
My mother.
Oh.
She's trying to make up
for lost time,
and i told her i'd hang around for a while.
Just 8 days, susan.
8 days. I'll pay you
750 all in advance.
Why are you so anxious?
Well, the truth...
um, i messed up
on my last job.
I mean...
messed up.
There's no need
for detail.
I was going
through a hard time,
let a few things slide,
and my reputation sank.
I need this one
to re-establish myself.
I'm a good captain
with dozens of successful runs under my belt, susan.
My goal is to, uh...
is to deliver early.
Permission to come aboard!
Aye, aye, matey.
Jason, my man.
How are ya?
Good.
You know matt.
Hey.
And susan clarkson.
Susan.
Oh, i didn't know
you were gonna be here.
Jason, how's it going?
Good.
Take it you two
know each other.
Yeah. Well, kind of.
We grew up in the same town.
Small world, huh?
Yeah, i guess it is.
So you gonna be
crewing up with us?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Susan: there's nothing worse
than looking for a job
you don't want.
Sailing's all i cared about.
Everything my mother hated
about it, i loved.
Maybe that was part
of the attraction.
Why don't you just
get rid of those?
Because i like to know i'm stronger than they are.
You're just making it
harder on yourself.
You know what they say?
You should remove the temptation.
They don't live my life.
I do.
It's up to me.
And you know
how proud i am of you.
I mean, 6 months sober
is huge.
But?
But it's hard
to just... forget.
I'm trying.
I really am.
For so many years,
i mean...
i came home not knowing
what to expect.
Would you be drunk, angry, irrational,
passed out...
or my mother?
All i can say is it was
a very different time.
I counted on your father to take care of me,
and when he didn't...
my world fell apart.
And then i turned around and did the same thing to you.
And no matter
how long it takes,
i'm determined
to prove to you
that things
have truly changed.
I hope they have.
There's something else.
Isn't there?
Yeah, there is.
How would you feel if...
if i went away
for just 2 weeks?
Look, mom...
susan.
I know i said
we would stick around
and we could work things out.
We will. I promise.
Mom...
it's only a couple
of weeks.
Just tell me one thing.
What has changed since this morning?
Nothing. Nothing's changed.
It's just...
i need to go do this.
Please.
You'll call me
every day?
All right, all right.
Every other day.
That's the best
i can do.
Deal.
♪ Every day
is a brand-new start... ♪
come on. You gotta
name all 7.
Ok, don't tell me. Uh...
sleepy, sneezy,
doc...
oh. Yeah, now i remember.
Dopey.
Oh, very funny.
Very funny.
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Hey,
i'm getting wet.
On a boat? Impossible.
Hey, susan,
could you hand me that vise grip there?
This thing's
all goofed up.
Sure.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Looks good. We're done.
Break time.
Let's get out of here.
Where?
Who cares?
It's a good point.
We'll be back
in a little while, ok?
Yeah, all right.
♪ I don't care
what the people say... ♪
whoo. Thanks.
Oh, i forgot
my sunglasses.
Ok.
♪ The way i feel,
they can get some air ♪
♪ i know you'll
always be there... ♪
so you want me to stay
and help you out?
No. This is
a one-person job.
Go on. Have fun.
You've earned it.
Ok.
I just wish this boat was in better shape,
you know?
It looks good,
but it's like...
hey, you coming
or what?
You'd better go.
Yeah, i guess i better.
See you later.
[Dance music plays]
matt: come on, susan.
Kick off your shoes. Dance a little.
Susan: all right.
Let's see if you can keep up.
Hello? Don't block my sun.
Sorry.
So what's the stor
with you and jason?
No story.
Let me guess.
Puppy love
gone to the dogs.
I don't mean to sound rude,
but it's really none of your business.
Ooh. Touchy, touchy.
Must have been
a really bad breakup.
Either that or he's
the one that got away.
Look, jason and i
are just old friends.
We've sailed together,
and, yes,
we used to be together,
but now we're better off
as friends.
Whatever you say.
Hey, could you
get me some ice
as long as you're
headed below?
[Sighs]
hmm. Ha.
Yes, sir.
I know, sir.
At the latest.
That's right.
Yes, you can.
You can definitely
count on me, sir. I...
♪ i just can't wait for
the clock to move its hands ♪
want a refill on that?
No, thanks.
So what made you
do the whitbread?
Wanted to see if it was
as tough as everyone says.
Yeah? Was it?
There were times.
Yeah, that's great.
That takes guts, you know?
You gotta be real good
to survive that race.
♪ Help me understand
♪ when i'm in your arms
i know it's right ♪
♪ when you use
your charms ♪
♪ i just want you
to hold me tight ♪
♪ it's the way
i'm thinking about you ♪
hey. I'm glad
you're all here.
I got a little piece
of news.
I don't want you
to all yell at once here.
We're going to leave
tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Why the rush?
I haven't even run a maintenance...
owner wants the boat sooner.
Aren't we waiting
for parts?
Don't worry about it.
I got it covered.
They'll be waiting
for us in san pedro.
Here's to the good ship
"sea-brook,"
her award-winning crew.
Anybody staying for dinner tonight?
I'm buying.
♪ Driving me crazy...
like that.
Like that.
♪ My heart is beating faster
♪ tonight there'll be no maze
♪ so, honey, please hurry
home and stay ♪
♪ the sun's down,
i just can't wait ♪
♪ let's live for now
and leave the rest to fate ♪
hi.
Hi.
♪ When i'm
in your arms... ♪
it's for good luck
on the trip.
Thanks.
Hey, have i told you how psyched i am that you're coming with us?
Not really.
Well, i am.
♪ It's the way
i'm thinking about you ♪
hey, susan, i need you...
uh... uh, i'm sorry.
I didn't...
mean to interrupt.
I need you both on the dock.
I'll take care of that later.
Don't worry.
Oh, what happened?
Is he ok?
Yeah, yeah,
he's fine.
He was partying hard down at the roost,
got into a fight.
Oh, man.
Where's allie?
Oh, she went back to get his things,
pay his bill.
Come on, buddy.
Rick.
He's a mess.
Yeah, i know.
Yeah, he was on the short end of the fight.
He'll be all right.
Come on. Up.
This is our skipper?
I'm getting
a bad feeling here.
Aw, he was probably
just blowing off steam.
We cannot worry
about this, ok?
I sailed under rick at the fastnet last august.
He did a great job.
I hope you're right.
Hey, guys, we all know
if push comes to shove,
any one of us
could skipper this boat.
Well, that's
certainly a point.
Yeah, so let's not
worry about it.
This is one trip we're never gonna forget,
i promise you.
♪ When i was young,
so very young ♪
♪ i didn't have a hero
♪ too much time
and not enough goals ♪
♪ hanging with the zeroes
♪ still, i couldn't
stop myself ♪
♪ from chasing
empty shadows ♪
♪ now it seems
i've lost them again... ♪
allie, susan,
photo time.
Self-timer's
in the bag.
♪ The reasons
why i'm leaving ♪
♪ i just know i've got to go
♪ if i cannot be here
♪ i'd just be
somewhere else ♪
♪ sitting with that
and that's a fact ♪
whoo!
♪ Lost my mind
a couple of times ♪
♪ at least i thought i did
♪ you'd think by now
i'd seen those signs ♪
♪ and keep fightin'
with my head ♪
♪ still, i couldn't
stop myself ♪
♪ from chasing
all those rainbows ♪
♪ looking for
that pot of gold ♪
♪ all i found is i got old
♪ i don't want reasons why...
[alarm clock beeps]
♪ i'm wonderin'
♪ what i'm doin'
♪ i'm feelin'
♪ out of place...
i hate night shifts.
There's coffee
in there.
I could use it.
Wow. That's amazing.
What?
I'd have polish
halfway up my leg.
Just a matter
of practice.
You want to try?
Those nails could
use some color.
Why bother?
Nobody notices my toes.
Oh, i'd say there are a couple of people on board
who notice your toes and everything else about you.
Look, jason is
just a friend.
And matt?
Just another friend?
Where the hell is she?
Right here.
I'm sorry i'm late.
Sandman's calling.
Good night, all.
Jason: good night.
♪ Tryin' to find
the clues... ♪
so, how'd you sleep?
You up late?
Not really.
You should get
some sleep.
The midnight watch is a solo gig if i remember correctly.
Yeah.
Ok.
♪ I'm wonderin'
good night.
Night.
♪ How i'm feelin'
♪ your charms
♪ come and go
♪ it's hard to decide
♪ there's no easy road
where are we docking
in san pedro?
The end tie.
[Alarm sounds]
jason: hey, rick!
Got a problem down here!
Sounds like he's
in the engine room.
All right.
Hold her, susan.
She's slipping!
Oh, man.
We gotta get
some sail up.
Susan: the current's
dragging us into the dock.
It's jammed!
Uhh!
We're gonna hit the dock!
Matt!
Matt, get up here!
I'm here. I'm here.
Take the helm.
I'm gonna go let
the jib out.
Matt: get it out quick!
Jason: i am!
Get the stern!
Hurry, jason!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on, jason!
Watch it!
Hey, watch out!
Get out of the way!
Come on.
Too close.
Susan: get ready
to fend off.
Jason: looks like
we're gonna make it.
Yeah!
Whoo.
Can you believe that?
I thought
we were toast.
What happened?
Impeller went,
engine overheated.
We're in san pedro.
Patricia:
is everything all right?
Great. We're
making good time.
Good. I'm... i'm sorry
i got so angry, susan.
I just... i don't know...
i hate it when
i get like that.
I know.
So when do you
think you'll be back?
Depends on what
the owner has planned.
Can't be soon
enough for me.
Mom, look, i gotta go.
I'll call you from
my next stop in 2 days, ok?
Take care.
I love you.
Love you, too.
How's mom?
Fine, but she
worries too much.
I didn't tell her how we arrived in san pedro.
That should have
never happened.
Rick should have
taken care of that.
Did you tell him?
Yeah, i told him the impeller shaft was rusty, yeah.
Well, that is one of the parts we have waiting here.
Rick never said
it was urgent.
I just figured
it was routine upkeep.
It wouldn't have mattered if the engine hadn't overheated, really.
That's not
the point.
I mean, rick
dropped the ball.
How much do we really know about this guy anyway?
Look, guys,
i've sailed
with him, ok?
And i've hung out with him at the roost.
He seems ok to me.
Look, the bottom line is
with us crewing for him,
he's gonna be fine.
No matter what, he's gonna be fine.
You're right.
We're acting like this is some trip around the world.
Come on.
We'd better hurry up and get those parts.
He wants to shove off right after dinner.
I liked college, but
i just couldn't help it.
I had to get away, sail.
I'm sorry,
but living on one of these things for 3 years
sounds like
a living nightmare.
And for me, it was
a dream come true.
You never feel like
you're in prison,
just totally cut off
from reality?
No one can tell me
what to do here...
or pull on me.
Someday i want to sail solo
across the pacific.
Hey, allie, how about
making some sandwiches?
I'm not hungry.
Rick: well, we are.
Come on. Help out a little.
You do it.
I'm on watch.
So that makes me the cook?
I don't think so, rick.
I'll make 'em.
No, no.
Allie will do it.
Forget it.
You're part
of this crew.
It means you work
like everybody else.
Sleeping with you
is plenty of work.
You always
pull this crap.
I swear, allie,
you're not gonna ruin this job, too.
It is so typical
of rick to blame me
for getting fired
off his last boat.
He knew the owner didn't
allow drinking on board.
What's with you two?
You seem so different,
i can't figure out
why you're together.
Rick helped me when i split up with my husband.
It got pretty ugly.
I didn't know
you were married.
Yeah.
Rick's a sweet guy
who loves me
and doesn't
expect much,
and that's
just what i need
till i get to canada
to start over.
And he's ok with that?
Every relationship doesn't have to be a lifelong commitment.
Look. Dolphins.
Those aren't dolphins.
They're sharks.
Mmm. Mmm.
I thought you
were getting coffee.
That's
too much trouble.
And i thought
this was a dry boat.
It's just a little whiskey
i brought for cold nights.
It won't hurt anything.
I don't drink
when i'm on watch.
Oh, and you've never
done 60 in a 55?
It's not the same.
Ahh.
Ok.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Don't mention it
to rick, ok?
I guess i, uh...
i also drink sometimes when i'm nervous.
It takes
the edge off.
What are you nervous about?
You.
And me. Us.
Us?
Yeah, you know
what i mean.
The other night before we left san diego.
Yeah, i remember.
Look, matt...
i like you a lot,
but i just can't...
it's jason, isn't it?
There's a story there.
I know it.
What? No. I was
gonna say i'm wary
about getting involved
with someone i'm sailing with.
Hmm. Didn't seem to be
a problem with him.
A perfect example
of why i'm wary.
Hey. I'm sorry.
I'm...
being a jerk.
Give me another chance.
Matt, look,
i didn't...
no, don't... don't worry.
You don't have to spell it out, ok?
If you want to go off and relight some fire with jason,
that's fine.
That's fine, really.
I gotta go. I gotta
go get something.
No, matt, look,
i don't...
it's one afternoon, rick,
a couple of hours.
Besides, it was 4-1.
You lost.
As if this were
a democracy.
Where'd you find this place anyway?
Friends of mine and i stumbled across it a few years ago.
Owner has a house on the other side,
but he's never home.
Allie: come on.
Hmm?
Come on. Take
some chances, rick.
Beautiful island.
[Excited chatter]
♪ the sun is low
♪ still, the people
who see is where i belong ♪
♪ let the waves...
now, this...
this is beautiful.
♪ I know they'll take me
out to sea again ♪
♪ let the waves...
yo, rick.
♪ Help me to see...
when do you wanna
turn this puppy in?
I think we can
be there in 5 days.
Wow. That's pretty fast.
Are you sure we can?
Yes, i'm sure.
Hey, uh...
rick, at that pace,
we're gonna have to work
around the clock just to...
i said i'm sure.
Don't worry
about it.
Look, we get there
on time,
bonuses all around.
♪ Let the waves come
rollin' in ♪
♪ 'cause i know they'll
take me out to sea again ♪
♪ let the waves wash
my cares away... ♪
hey.
Is this seat taken?
Nope. All yours.
Ahh.
Whew. How's it going?
All right.
Rick's making me
a little nervous.
It's like he's on a mission or something.
Yeah. Yeah,
i know what you mean.
Looks like we'll be working
harder than we planned.
At least it's
a short trip.
So, matt, matt seems
like a nice enough guy, huh?
Yeah. He's a little hyper sometimes,
but he means well.
How long have you known him?
A few months,
maybe more.
How come?
Oh, um, i don't know, um...
i guess...
i guess i remember
a time when, uh...
when i was the one
you were looking at.
I'm not looking
at matt.
I appreciate that,
but you don't need
to protect me, you know?
I already know.
Know?
I saw you the other night in the cockpit.
Well, then you
missed the part
where i said i just want to be friends.
Really?
Really.
So you two
aren't, uh...
and you're not...
aw, jeez.
Aw, susan,
that's great.
I mean, the minute i saw you,
my heart was just like...
i mean it was like we weren't even apart.
I just
kept thinking,
maybe this means that we can still, uh...
i'm sorry. I mean, that's...
that wasn't right.
Just because you're not interested in matt doesn't mean...
it's not that, jason.
Look...
i thought
about you, too,
a lot, but...
the reason
we broke up...
it's still there.
The reason i never understood,
i remember.
I just wasn't ready
for what you wanted.
All i wanted was...
was you, susan.
That's it.
I know.
I wanted that, too,
but every time i thought
about the future, you know,
us being together...
i just wasn't ready
for that kind of commitment.
Yeah.
I miss my best friend,
though.
Me, too.
I'm glad
you're here.
Matt, buddy,
what's wrong?
Huh? Nothing.
Let's just say
i'm as anxious
to get to vancouver
as you are.
[Thunder]
hey, matt.
Grab some rest.
Me and susan are up for the night shift.
Yeah.
I bet you are.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Stay outta my face, ok?
Is this about susan?
'Cause if it is,
you're way off, matt.
This is...
we're just trying to patch up an old friendship, ok?
That's it.
Ha.
Well, if that's what you really think, jason,
you're dumber
than i thought.
Look, we got a long way to go, matt.
Ok? Let's just forget about this.
Let's just...
let's just
drop it.
All right?
Are we cool?
Yeah, we're cool.
All right.
Just stay outta my face.
Something wrong?
Well, barometer's
dropping,
which usually means
a storm's coming,
but the weather service
predicted clear skies,
plus i can't find
this one chart.
You mean we're lost?
No. We're not lost.
I just...
i was wondering how much time we could save
by skipping our pit stop at morro bay.
Hey...
don't put so much pressure on yourself, ok?
Not everything is riding on this one job.
Yeah, i know.
Don't worry, ok?
I'm fine.
It's all gonna be...
fine.
Come on.
[Thunder]
where'd all this
weather come from?
Don't know.
Last report said conditions were supposed to be good.
Heh.
That's our tax dollars hard at work.
Maybe we should stay
in morro bay
until we see
what this turns into.
We're not going
to morro bay.
We passed the channel
about an hour ago.
We what?
Why?
'Cause i made a decision
based on the reports.
I had no idea we were
getting into this.
Radio: a violent storm is battering the northern california coast.
Tv 8 has just received word that winds up to 70 miles per hour
and waves
cresting at 30 feet
are causing widespread damage from monterey bay to san francisco...
sitting at home with mom is sounding pretty good right now.
Oh, yeah.
This rigging's
too loose.
All this jibing's
gonna snap a mast.
Roll in the jib and take down half the main.
Yeah.
God, i hate
this stupid rig.
We need some help.
I guess you should
go get matt.
Go.
Matt, wake up.
Come on, wake up.
I think
he passed out.
Perfect. We're up there fighting a gale,
and he's drinking?
It's pretty
rough out, isn't it?
How would you know?
You've been down here all night.
Look, i didn't
mean it, ok?
I'm just wiped out.
Aah!
You ok?
Yeah.
Man,
what's going on?
We need your help
up on deck.
Can't handle a little
foul weather?
Give me a clue,
matt.
You gonna be
a jerk all night,
or are you gonna
come up and help?
Somebody get up here fast!
Rick!
Rick, we need you.
What happened?
We're trying
to reduce the sail.
The rig is jammed.
Ok.
Allie,
put some gear on.
Take it down.
I'm gonna
reduce the sail.
Ok. Fasten
your safety line.
I'm trying to reef the main,
but it's bound off!
Rick!
Ohh!
Rick, hang on!
Hang on, rick!
Rick, are you ok?
I'm all right!
Allie, what
are you doing?
I want to help.
It's too dangerous.
Get below.
No.
[Muttering]
far enough!
Hold it there!
Hold on!
Jason!
Susan:
jason, are you hurt?
No, i'm...
i'm all right.
Need help
on the stern.
Make sure you fasten
your safety line.
Secure the lines
and clear the deck!
Ok!
Aah!
Ohh!
Allie!
Rick!
Rick, allie's hurt!
She's on the stern!
Ok, i'm coming!
Allie, i'm here.
You ok?
Baby, what happened?
I was trying to help.
You shouldn't
have been up here.
I know.
I hit my back.
It really hurts.
We got to get allie
to a hospital.
We'll never make it
in this storm.
Rick, please,
the coast is deadly.
We've got to move away from land,
not closer in.
Look at the chart.
I can't.
I can't find them.
Somebody lost them.
You're kidding!
No. I wish i was.
This is crazy...
look out!
All right, that's it.
That's it.
We're going in.
I'll put in a call
to the coast guard.
You guys bring her down.
Ok. Come on. Come here.
Watch your back.
Oww...
i got you.
Rick: we've lost our charts.
Can you assist us? Over.
"Sea-brook,"
i need your position.
What are your
coordinates? Over.
Ok, coast guard.
Um, my coordinates are 35 degrees, 33 minutes
by 121 degrees,
29 minutes.
Copy that,
"sea-brook."
Got it.
Wait. We're showing your position to be morro bay.
Over.
Uh... uh, that's
right, coast guard.
That was my last position.
My mistake.
I feel horrible
about allie.
Aw, she shouldn't
have been up here.
She wouldn't have been up here if it wasn't for me.
I was yelling at her
for not helping out.
It's my fault.
All right!
The coast guard says san simeon's our closest dock.
Rick wants us to change the heading to 300 degrees.
That's a bad idea,
matt.
We'll be broadside
to the waves.
We'll risk...
nobody asked you.
Just do it, susan.
Matt, we're
gonna be swamped.
Matt, you're
not thinking.
You don't know
what you're say...
change course now!
No, i won't.
It's suicide!
My god, matt,
you're jeopardizing all of our lives!
You're both relieved of your duties effective immediately!
You and rick can't handle this boat
by yourselves
in this storm.
Aw, forget it.
He'd rather kill us all than look weak.
If you don't get down below,
i'll drag you down myself!
No. No. I am staying
here to help...
matt, stop it... aah!
Jason!
Jason! Oh! No!
No, jason!
Jason!
Susan: that's enough.
Stop it!
Jason!
Aah!
What happened?
I didn't mean to.
What happened,
susan?
They had a fight.
Jason went over.
Jason!
Where is he?
Susan,
it's too late.
He's gone.
No! Don't say that.
Jason!
Susan: jason!
Rick: jason!
Please, where are you?
[Gasping]
there he is!
Jason, over here!
Swim for it!
Grab it!
Grab the line!
Hold on!
Pull, pull. Help me.
Hang on!
Jason, please!
Hold on!
Ok, come on.
Pull! Pull!
Pull!
We got ya!
Come on!
Come on. Yeah!
Hey, how ya doing?
I'm ok.
Is jason all right?
Yeah. He's fine.
Looks like it hurts.
Uhh...
only when the boat moves.
Here. This should
cushion the bumps.
Thanks.
So how are you guys
doing up there?
It's tough,
but we're
hanging in there.
It's bad, isn't it?
"Sea-brook"
can handle it.
Yeah, but can rick?
I guess i really don't know what kind of captain he is.
He's doing fine.
Don't worry.
All this pounding,
it feels like we're just falling apart.
I'm gonna
go back up, ok?
"Sea-brook," "sea-brook,"
request to know your situation. Over.
Uh, roger, coast guard.
This is "sea-brook."
Um... my radar shows
the storm moving west.
I think
we're gonna be ok.
Seas are
pretty rough out here,
but i think we're
gonna make it.
We're heading into
san simeon. Over.
Roger, "sea-brook."
Glad to know
you're ok.
Coast guard out.
Roger. "Sea-brook" out.
Will you
file that report?
Come on, baby.
Oh... shee...
man, the owner's
gonna have rick's hide.
Well, at least she's
still floating.
Jason...
i was so scared
when...
i know.
Thank you.
[Beeeeep]
no. No, not again!
Oh, man.
Check the engine, rick.
Check the engine!
We need more sail.
Ok. I'll go let her out.
Can you hold her?
Yup.
Careful, susan.
Ease her out slow.
I'm trying.
Slowly...
i can't clear it.
Aah!
Jason! Help me!
Susan!
Jason!
All right. Hold on.
Hold on.
I got you. All right,
don't let go.
Pick your feet up.
I can't.
You can. Come on.
There you go.
Come on,
it's all right. I got you.
I got you.
Hang on to me.
Get up. Ok.
All right.
I'm ok.
I'll finish
loading up the main.
No, no. No, forget it.
The storm's too big.
If we can't fix the engine,
we gotta call for help.
You all right?
Yeah.
Huh? You ok?
Rick, what
are you doing?
You're supposed to be fixing the engine, remember?
Could you fix
the mainsail?
I couldn't free it.
That seals it.
We're done for.
Rick, what about
the engine?
Forget it.
We're screwed.
Rick, get off your ass and start acting like a captain.
Radio the coast guard
for help.
The storm,
i think it's moving west.
The hell it is.
We're right in the middle of it.
If i call
the coast guard...
i'll never work
again.
What?
You're sitting here thinking about your career?
Rick, we're in trouble,
big trouble.
We've got to call
the coast guard
and pray we can hold on
till they get here.
What was the name
of the vessel, ma'am?
The "sea-brook."
It's sailing
up to vancouver.
I'm afraid it may be caught in this storm.
Uh, ma'am, we are
very busy right now.
But i'll see if i can
raise them on the radio.
Call us back
in an hour, ok?
Please. It's...
it's my daughter.
We're gonna do our best.
I promise.
Lieutenant, i just saw a report on the "sea-brook."
It seems
they called in
and said they were safely en route to san simeon.
Good.
Coast guard?
Coast guard,
come in.
Rick, i cannot
hold her alone!
Aah!
Oh, my god.
Jason,
start the pumps!
I can't get up!
Matt! Matt,
we need you!
Help allie.
I'm getting
the life raft.
Come on,
we gotta go!
Aah!
There's no power.
The pumps won't work.
Mayday! Mayday!
It hurts to walk!
I'm popping the raft.
Abandon ship!
We're sinking!
Mayday!
Stay right here.
I gotta launch the zodiac.
Aah! No!
Uh...
uh...
jason, let's get outta here!
We're goin' down!
Aah!
Help!
Somebody help me!
Aah!
It's ok, allie.
Hold on...
hold on.
Ok, you're free.
Swim away from
the boat. Hurry!
Jason!
Allie!
Susan, over here!
Over here!
Where's allie
and jason?
I don't know.
Allie!
Jason!
Rick... rick!
Over here, matt!
Over here!
Rick! Ohh...
you ok, baby?
My legs hurt.
Hold on!
Where's jason?
I don't know.
What happened
to the other raft?
I couldn't
hold on to it.
Jason!
What do you mean,
you couldn't hold on to it?
That had all our
emergency supplies.
We're in the middle of
a storm here, remember?
We're dead
without that stuff.
Stop it!
It's over!
It's all over!
Shut up, rick!
Shut up!
Jason!
I can't hold on.
Hold on, baby.
Just hold on.
Let's flip the zodiac
and get in.
Ok. We'll take the back.
You take the bow.
All right.
That's a good idea.
Ok, you ready?
Hold on, baby.
Hold on.
1... 2...
3!
[Screaming]
come on, baby, swim!
I can't...
you can do it!
Jason, thank god!
I got caught.
I got
dragged under.
Ok, we got to
flip this and get in.
It'll blow away again!
We'll grab the line
over the leeward side
and let the wind
turn it over.
All right,
let's do it.
Go! Go!
Out of the way!
Go to the
other side, allie!
Get ready to pull!
Ok. I'm ready.
Go ahead.
All right... aah!
Give me your hand!
Here!
Give me it!
Oh, my god...
your legs.
It was the rigging.
This wind
is so cold.
It's killing me.
I'm telling you,
we're better off in the water.
He's right.
We should get back in.
No!
I can't.
Maybe if we bunch up...
conserve body heat.
Rick: it's too
cold out here.
Please don't make me
get back in.
Ok. We won't.
Let's just stay close.
It's over.
I just
know it's over.
Oh, shut up!
Come on, guys, we
have to work together.
It's our only hope
until we get rescued.
Somebody must have
heard your mayday.
They're not coming.
Stop saying that!
No, i mean,
they're not coming.
I told them
not to come.
What?
I saw you talking... i mean,
before the boat went down.
I tried. It was
waterlogged by then.
Damn!
We are gonna die.
No. We're gonna survive.
In the morning they'll
be looking for us.
We can certainly
hold out till then.
There are sharks
all through these waters.
There's great whites.
But we should be
safe in here.
This is my fault.
This is all my fault.
Susan: when day
finally broke,
what i saw scared me.
Of course, our boat
was long gone...
resting quietly on the bottom of the pacific ocean.
Plus we had no supplies...
no food, no water,
and no captain.
As rick had lost all hope,
he had nothing to offer
in terms of leadership.
Allie was in terrible pain,
trying hard to be rong,
and matt was edgy
and quick-tempered.
It was up to me and jason to keep everyone's spirits up.
I was scared as hell.
We need a cover.
Jason...
do we have anything
to make a canopy?
Um...
yeah. Um...
this will work.
Let's set it up,
and then we can take
turns keeping watch
until a ship comes.
Hey...
get up, guys.
Help us ou
we're gonna make a canopy.
What are you doing?
Stop. Don't drink that.
It'll make you crazy.
A small amount
won't hurt.
You're better off drinking your own urine.
You drink what you want,
i'll drink what i want.
Here you go, baby.
Have a little water.
No!
Damn it!
You little...
aah!
Stay away!
Aah! Get off!
Hey, what are
you doing?!
Oh, man!
It's ok.
I'm fine.
It's just my leg
hurts so bad. [Sobs]
it's ok.
It's ok, baby.
Oh...
oh... what have i done to my beautiful baby?
What have i done?
I've ruined
everything.
At least the storm passed.
Here comes the sun.
I don't think i can stand
another night here.
This is the last
one, allie.
We'll be rescued
tomorrow.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Rick, do you think so?
We don't need
to be rescued.
I see shore.
Where?
Rick:
over there.
We're off
mission bay.
We're nowhere near
Yes, we are.
I recognize the buildings.
Are... are you sure?
Rick, you're
seeing things.
You've been drinking too much sea water.
You're confused.
No, no, no.
It's there.
Come on, buddy,
sit down.
Sit down.
Allie: rick...
what are you doing?
Rick, no!
Rick!
Come back!
Rick, please,
don't leave me!
I gotta go
after him!
No, no!
It's pitch dark out there.
You'd both be lost.
It's suicide.
I know.
Oh, my god!
Aah!
Ow!
Come on, susan, wake up.
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
Oh, i think
i'm losing it.
No, no, you're not.
It was just a bad dream,
just a bad dream.
Ok. I'm ok now.
We're all just so hungry and thirsty.
It's ok to lean on me
a little bit, you know.
No, it's not.
We have to be strong.
You can't be expected
to do it for both of us.
This is not
a competition, susan.
What's going on?
Nothing, allie.
Go back to sleep.
I'm just gonna
cover you up, ok?
No, i don't
wanna wake up.
Shh.
I don't.
I don't wanna
remember...
or feel this pain.
And now rick...
i don't think
he made it.
Do you think
he made it?
No.
But we're still here.
We're gonna live through this.
It just seems so much easier to die now...
like he opened
the door.
Rick didn't die.
Allie, he killed
himself.
Rick gave up when
the boat sank, allie.
After that, all he
cared about was you.
I... i don't wanna die.
[Sniffling]
please don't let me
give up.
I won't.
[Train whistle blowing]
don't tell me to wait.
My daughter could
be lost out there.
Listen, i understand
your concern,
but we have no evidence
of any trouble.
Now, last we heard,
they were headed north.
And i am telling you,
i know my daughter.
I want to talk to the officer in charge.
He will be here as soon
as he possibly can...
i'm lieutenant belwick,
ma'am.
What seems to be
the problem?
The trouble is my daughter's boat is missing.
Everybody keeps saying her boat is safe,
but nobody seems to know where it is.
You must be
mrs. Clarkson,
and yes,
last we heard, "sea-brook"
was safely on its way to dock in san simeon.
It never arrived.
She would've called me.
I understand,
but maybe she just forgot during all the confusion.
She didn't forget.
Something is wrong.
My daughter is in
trouble out there,
and i am not going
to risk her life
because you're satisfied that she's safe.
Please, come in.
Where are my cigarettes?
They were right here.
What are you
talking about?
My damn cigarettes.
Who took 'em?
Ok, guys,
i want my cigarettes back right now.
They were right here.
Matt, they sank with the boat, remember?
No. I'm talking about
the other cigarettes.
What other cigarettes...
the ones i bought
at the store, man!
I bought beer,
and i bought... matt!
Whoa, matt.
If you went
to the store...
look at me...
why did you
come back?
"Sea-brook."
"Sea-brook,"
come in. Over.
The skies have been
clear for 2 days.
They should be answering.
All right.
Let's mark their last known coordinates,
see if any other vessels
are in the area.
2-way radio:
all stations,
this is united states coast guard,
los angeles group.
Be on the lookout
for "sea-brook,"
a 68-foot,
blue-hulled sailing vessel with 5 people on board,
last reported 16 miles southwest of morro bay, california.
Matt, don't!
I'm thirsty!
You'll kill yourself.
You saw what
it did to rick.
Leave me alone!
I've been drinking it all day!
Stop it!
Hey, hey, hey...
tell her to shut up!
It's not her business!
Leave him
alone, susan.
We can't let him
kill himself!
You can't make him survive if he doesn't want to.
Fine. Let him die.
I'm sick of fighting with him.
Oh... shee...
look at this filth.
Ugh... it's poison,
man. Look at it.
Ugh... ugh...
matt.
We're sitting in poison, man.
It's gonna kill us!
Matt...
no, it won't.
We gotta get
out of here.
No, matt. How?
Listen...
we gotta
dump it out.
Flip the raft,
There's sharks
all over the place.
You gotta think
about this, ok?
God, it's
burning me.
Stop it, matt.
Allie's too weak to swim.
Turn it over now!
We gotta empty it!
What's going on?
Are we being rescued?
No, but we're dying.
This water's killing us.
Matt, no!
No, no...
uh... aah!
No, jason!
Matt, damn you!
Come on in!
It's perfect!
Ah! Something
just bumped me.
Susan: sharks!
Jason, hurry, get in!
Jason:
kick, allie, kick!
Hurry, jason, get in!
Move your legs!
Come on,
help her up.
Grab her.
I got you, allie.
Susan:
jason!
Matt! No, what
are you doing?
Get in the raft!
Come on!
Matt, no!
Matt... grab my hand!
Help!
Get in the raft!
[Grunting]
aah!
Jason:
matt! Matt!
Aaaaah!
Don't look.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
[Moaning]
she's pretty bad.
I think it's blood poisoning.
What should we do?
A tourniquet
around her leg
might help stop the infection from spreading.
A tourniquet.
Um...
well...
oh, here.
Here, use this belt.
Listen, allie,
i'm worried about your leg, ok?
We're gonna put a tourniquet on it,
all right?
Tourniquet?
To help you.
Why?
All right?
It might hurt a little...
but it'll stop
the infection
from spreading,
ok?
Ow!
All right.
Just hold still for one second, ok?
What are you...
[gasps] oww!
Guys, get away from me!
All right,
all right!
Stop! Get off!
All right, all right!
It's off, it's off.
All right.
Don't touch me.
It's ok,
it's ok, it's ok.
[Sobbing]
it's all right. It's over.
It's ok, it's ok.
I'm just gonna play it real straight with you, mrs. Clarkson...
we cannot find any evidence
that your daughter's boat
ever reached san simeon.
And, uh...
what are you doing
to try to find her?
We are checking every harbor and marina up the coast.
We have a watch alert out to all vessels in the area.
Uh, what about airplanes, helicopters?
We're considering
that, too.
Considering isn't
enough, damn it!
You just get the hell out there and find her!
2-way radio: point reyes,
this is coast guard 1503,
on scene,
commencing papa-sierra search at minute 0-8.
Major axis is
1-3-5 degrees true.
Tracking space
is 5 miles...
ah... ahh... ohh...
so hot. There's no breeze.
There's no nothing.
Let's get in the water
and cool off.
Come on, susan,
come on. No, you can't.
No, i have to cool off.
Susan, stop it.
Come on, stop. Stop!
What... what
are you doing?
Please, you can't...
you can't leave me here.
We're not going
anywhere, allie.
Look... look.
Ah! Ha ha!
I caught one!
I caught it!
Ha ha ha ha!
What's going on?
We caught a fish.
We got something to eat.
Heh heh.
Oh... oh.
Ok. All right.
There. Here.
Give some
to allie, first.
Yeah, yeah.
Here, allie. No.
Yeah, come on.
It'll help.
Protein will fight the infection.
I can't.
Here. Let me try.
Come on, allie,
just a bite.
No.
What was that
back there?
I don't know.
I just...
i woke up and i just remembered wanting to cool off.
Don't worry.
It won't happen again.
You are determined
to go through this alone,
aren't you, susan?
No, but i pull
my own weight...
damn it, susan.
Haven't you seen enough dying
on this raft?
We need to help
each other, susan.
Don't you
understand...
that it's ok
to need each other?
I know.
[Thunder]
ah!
Wake up, wake up.
It's raining.
Come on, allie,
drink.
Oh! Ahh! Yes!
Oh, no.
No.
It's time to go.
What?
Where?
Home.
Time to go home.
Come here, allie.
Lie with me.
Come on. Shh.
It's ok.
It's time to go.
Allie, can you
hear me?
[Humming melody]
what is it?
She's slipping away.
[Whispering] the lord is my shepherd.
I shall not want...
i can't tell
what she's saying.
Maybe she's...
yeah...
talking to god.
Our father,
who art in heaven,
hallowed by thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done
on earth as it is
in heaven.
[Sobbing] give us this day
our daily bread...
she would've made it
if she hadn't been hurt.
She was strong.
She didn't deserve to die this way.
I can't believe
she's gone.
She had this
in her pocket.
Rest in peace,
allie.
[Grunting]
jason, stop.
No, no, let go.
It's not what you think.
Sorry. I thought you were
drinking sea water.
I can't stop throwing up.
Well, that's...
that's a good sign.
Your body's getting
rid of the toxins.
No, not anymore.
It just dry heaves now.
It hurts.
I'm sorry, susan.
Sorry? About what?
I know how much
you hate weakness.
I just hate feeling like my life is out of control.
Does that make
any sense?
About as much sense
as any of this makes.
I'm scared, susan.
I'm scared i'm gonna die
on this godforsaken raft.
Stop it.
Don't you dare give up on me, ok?
We're gonna live
through this.
And i'm trying.
I'm trying.
I'm just, you know...
well, try harder.
It hurts so bad.
Look, we're gonna
make it, ok?
I need you
to try harder.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Did you hear something?
[Distant engine rumbling]
susan: when i finally
saw the ship,
i thought it was a mirage.
I was just losing it again.
There was no way we were
really being rescued.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[Horn blowing]
ah, ha ha ha!
Susan:
then i heard jason...
and the excitement
in his voice,
and figured we couldn't both be dreaming.
They found
a raft.
Oh, thank god!
They still have to get them both on board.
Both? A man?
A woman? Who?
I don't know
for sure.
They're
on board.
Who?
Young man... and
a young woman.
Jason o'donnell...
and susan clarkson.
Ha ha ha!
Thank you!
Oh, thank you, thank you!
Thank you
so much!
[Car approaching]
ah!
Oh...
susan:
it wasn't until later
that i realized
what my mom did.
Susannah.
She refused to give up,
and she helped save our lives.
I guess, in a way,
jason and my mom
were both trying to teach me the same thing...
there's nothing wrong
with needing people.
That's what makes us strong,
that's what makes us human,
and that's why
i'm alive today.