my senior year at the chandler
academy private school
began like any other.
unfortunately, rich kids
whose parents sent them
to private school either
out of tradition or
the misguided notion that if
you pay tuition to go to
high school, you're somehow
better off
than in public school.
wrong.
this place is as bad
as a public school.
maybe even worse.
the uniforms, the bureaucracy,
the conformity and most of
these guys conformed,
except for my friends.
this is marcus rattner,
one of my two best friends.
i think if you said marcus
was a trouble maker,
that would be an understatement.
i don't think i remember
one week in the whole time
that i've known him
where he was neither in
trouble with the police
nor in trouble with the school.
i don't think he does that
intentionally, he just can't
help himself. of course,
doing dumb stuff like this,
probably isn't making it
any easier. head mrs. grimes,
for some reason
she singled us out,
watched us like a hawk.
maybe because we were
outcasts we became
easy targets for her.
if marcus was the troublemaker,
then matt slaton,
my other best friend,
was the con-artist.
always playing poker,
starting betting pools,
and working some scam.
as you can see, i had
my work cut out for me,
because the law of
averages states,
for every john van-owen,
a.k.a. me, there has to be
an equal and opposite number,
and there he is,
harlan ratliff.
i mean, look at this guy.
he's prettier than most of
the girls i've gone out with,
and you just knew this
guy was set for life.
there he is now,
showing off his pecs,
with his two toys,
randall and alex.
now, to set this up for you.
alex, that's this guy here.
he's dating trini,
she's the one on the left.
and meanwhile, ta-da,
that's me, john van-owen,
giving mary,
she's the one on the right,
the thousand-yard stare.
do i even need to tell you
what happens next?
see what i mean?
of course i had no idea
at that time
that headmistress grimes,
harlan ratliff and the whole
rich doggie-poor dog system
at chandler academy was going
to be the least of my problems.
and my life was about
to change forever.
(cards shuffling)
okay guys, now moving
right along.
these are the stocks
of salem's town square,
and they were used
as a form of punishment
for what we would consider
a felony misdemeanor today.
now these are ceremonial
knives, believed to be used by
the celtic-andreotic cults
of that times, in other words,
witches and warlocks.
this dagger called
spirit's tooth
was the main tool
used by a witch or warlock
during this period.
and they used it
in their sacrificing, in
their practicing of alchemy,
in the creation of their spells
and incantations,
and to create a bond
among the members
of the covenant.
the bodily fluids were shared
or anointed, particularly
blood and tears, things that a
witch or a warlock believed held
a particularly strong bond.
needless to say, the spirits
hey, we should have
taken pottery instead.
shut up you idiot, shut up,
you'll get us both in trouble.
hey, did you see
who's in our class?
mary stewart, your dream girl.
really?
well, in other words,
for every evil that exists,
there is an equal
and opposite good
that is just as powerful
to balance it out.
but of course, we know today
that witches and warlocks
really had no true powers.
any questions so far?
any big words you guys
want me to explain?
(cards shuffling)
well, well, well, what's this?
it looks like you're setting
up for a game of poker.
we don't get to the poker
portion of the curriculum
till the second term.
oh, i'm sorry ms. stevens.
were these cards
distracting you?
no, but they might be
distracting you.
because i'm selfish when
it comes to teaching a class.
i like to have everybody's
undivided attention.
well, actually, i've listened to
every word that
you've said so far.
well, i find that
hard to believe,
with you looking like
a las vegas black jack
dealer back here.
i'm listening to you.
really?
yes, now that you ask,
i can tell you that i
disagree with much of what
you've just said.
you don't say.
you know, you stand there
and you sneer at witches
and warlocks, yet i know that
you wear a crucifix
around your neck.
now, isn't that
a little hypocritical?
how can you be unbiased if you
favor one religion over another.
ross, you're agnostic.
quite the contrary,
i know exactly
what i believe in.
well, i'm happy to hear that.
however, you have to
give up these cards.
personally, i believe in magic.
okay, that was a good trick.
teach that one to me now
that i have a new deck
of cards, i mean.
oh, i'd love to teach
you a trick or two.
class dismissed.
hey john, you got a minute?
it's nothing heavy, i promise.
i just want to congratulate
you on your history paper.
you got an a.
really? wow.
it's my pleasure. believe me,
it makes me feel like
i'm doing something right.
well, i always did love history.
well, it shows. look, i know you
feel like you get
dumped on around here.
but you are an
excellent student,
and i like having you
in this class.
i know it's tough to
fit in a place like this.
yeah.
just hang in there.
if you ever need anyone to talk
to, if you have a problem,
if you just want some help,
then please come to me.
okay.
you've got someone
looking out for you.
now go catch up
with your friends.
so what did ms. stevens want?
i got an a in my history paper.
hey, not too shabby.
so what's the problem?
look, the reason
i never ask mary out
is because she is one
of the popular people
and i'm not.
do you know what everybody
here thinks of
guys like you and me and marcus?
they think we're freaks that
wound up here by accident.
what?
hey you finally
flipped out john.
i mean, you're not
a bad looking guy.
if you were a girl i'd do you.
don't you ever want to fit in?
just once in a while?
i don't want to be
like everyone else.
i want to be better
than everyone else.
hi john, you got a minute?
oh, how did that happen?
see you around, poor boy.
hi yourself.
i wanted to talk to you.
i'm sorry about earlier today.
oh, forget it, actually,
i'm mad at you.
me? why?
well, i'd been waiting for you
to ask me out for like
two years, you idiot.
i didn't think you
even knew i existed.
well, do you care to
start catching up?
you know, you're
making fun of me.
i need to get to biology.
no, wait, we still have some
unresolved issues to deal with.
what are you talking about?
i'm talking about our
first date, silly.
what?
listen, i'm a
coffee-and-small-talk gal,
so why don't you say,
we go to the v cafe,
friday, around eightish?
i don't put out unless
you spring for dinner.
one hurdle at a time, don juan.
why don't we start out
with the latte?
and then we'll work our way up
to a real date this weekend.
the school's out
for semestral break.
a real date?
yeah.
so, friday, coffee, 8.
don't be late
or i'll kill you.
a real date.
hi marcus.
i'm surprised you jog
as much as you smoke.
yeah, i'm trying to cut back,
on the jogging.
good one, rattner,
you dig it, jogging?
yeah, what's going on, harlan?
i mean, why are you all of
a sudden being nice to me?
hell, man, i'm just trying
to make conversation.
i can't be a jerk all the time.
i figured what the hell,
rattner's okay.
i don't know about slaton
and john van-owen,
but rattner's alright.
i'm flattered man, thanks.
i'm flattered, he says.
that nut.
you mean, he wasn't
bowled over by your
sparkling personality?
how is it going, marcus?
we do this every afternoon.
how come we've never seen you
here before?
oh, you know,
i just started this week.
marcus is alright.
yeah, too bad about
his lame friends.
hey, ease up, okay?
i mean, i'd take it
personally if someone
talked about my lame friends.
screw you, harlan.
it's time to hit the lockers.
i'm done.
me too.
later.
you coming?
well, sure man. you bet.
(showers sprinkling)
man, i'm ready for
semestral break.
you've got big plans?
well, i don't know.
is getting butt-ass wasted
for a week considered
a big plan?
sounds like a good idea to me.
trini's folks
are going out of town,
we've got the whole place
to ourselves.
you guys finally going
to do the deed?
hey man, what is that?
yeah, what is that, alex?
you want to know what this is?
sure.
it's a permanent marker.
india ink, you get it
on your skin and it
almost never comes off.
i don't get it.
stop it, man. come on, guys.
nice view, marcus, are you sure
you've never done this before?
stop, harlan.
keep screaming, marcus.
the doors are locked,
and we're just going to
be in here for hours.
i made sure of it.
what are you doing, man?
you mean, what am i going to
do? kill you, maybe, or worse.
i don't think he's ready to
settle down just yet harlan.
maybe you should have
taken him to dinner first.
well, i can tell you this much,
rattner, it won't hurt you much.
all i want to do is write
a little message,
just an itty-bitty one.
let me go. let me go.
don't make it any worse
than it is.
randall and alex here,
get in a few good kicks,
once i write a little message
on your cute little butt.
hmm, what should we do here?
how about mother?
good choice, but no.
i have something better.
i know, i'll write
my pussy on his back,
with an arrow pointing down.
you guys are going to
get expelled for this.
really? at this point,
grimes would believe me
even if i told her
you did it to yourself,
then showed us like
we were interested.
now don't move or this is
just going to hurt worse.
good morning, fellas.
why don't you breeze
the hell out of here, you kid?
that was easy.
i don't think
you realize just what kind of
trouble you're getting into.
i'm going to kill you,
stop screwing around.
i don't see it
in your eyes, harlan.
i don't see you killing
anybody. as a matter of fact,
would you like to see
which one of us ends up dead?
i bet it's going to be you.
look, we weren't going
to do anything to him.
we were just going to scare him.
well, now that it's you and not
him, i think it's even funnier.
let's see, you were going to
write my pussy on his back.
i like that. instead, i'm going
to write it on your face,
with an arrow pointing to
your cute little mouth.
come on, harlan. i thought
you were going to kill me.
you're dead. you wait.
oh come on, i don't
like to wait.
why don't you and your little
girlfriends come back here
and finish this up right now?
this isn't really a
good town after all huh?
where the hell did
you come from?
not that i'm complaining
or anything.
i'm new, kid.
(thunderstorm)
where the hell have
you been all day?
yeah, we looked for
you at the commissary.
are you guys busy?
i just got to whip
john's butt with a five-card
stud, but otherwise, no.
i've got to start
my latin studies.
well, drop it both of you.
are we going to party?
let's just say i've got
a fourth for bridge.
what the hell are
you talking about?
listen, if i sat down
and told you guys
what happened to me today, we'd
be here all freaking night.
come on, i'll tell
you on the way.
on the way to where?
are you sure about this, marcus?
why?
yeah, shouldn't this place be
locked up or something?
guys, this is a private school.
they would never lock
anything up around here.
besides, this door's
open 24 hours.
come on, he's waiting inside.
who's waiting for us inside?
the new guy.
yeah, you could do
all those card tricks.
of course. i'm luc, and you are?
john van-owen.
matt.
are you guys getting in or what?
i'm game.
so, where are you from
anyway, luc?
all over the place.
your parents move around a lot?
no, i never really got the
chance to know my mom.
i just grew up like
i never had one.
as for my dad, well, me and my
dad don't get along anymore.
i got into some trouble
a while back, got kicked out.
all we do is fight,
even in the long distance.
don't leave me out on that, man.
my parents couldn't give a damn
if i rotted in here or in jail.
except it sounds better
at the country club
when they tell their rich
friends that i'm away at school,
you know, instead of minimum
security over at riverview.
my parents wanted to
put me on prozac.
yeah, this is a great place.
i'm surprised you guys
haven't done this before.
yeah, it sounds like
you're planning to
make this a regular thing.
i would say.
so, what's the deal
with this harlan guy?
you guys act like you
see anti-christ or something.
he's not.
he's just a weak little boy
trapped in a man's body.
would you see him as
he really is?
i tried man, believe me.
well, you're just lashing out
on him because you're angry.
he pushes all the right buttons
and you just go exactly where
he wants you to go.
so, what makes you so special?
well, i'm not that different
than anybody else,
except in one way,
one major way.
you see i'm a student
of the soul,
so i've figured it's
not about people,
and gotten to be
really good at it.
so if you can figure out
how people operate,
you pretty much know
how to get by in this world.
oh yeah? that's bull
if you ask me.
remember what i told you
about yourself isn't
necessarily pretty,
but it was true.
yeah, but it doesn't explain
how you kicked harlan's butt.
i'm here to help.
right.
you guys all have one thing in
common.
you all want something
you can never have.
what if i told you i could
promise you all those things?
right here, right now?
you're just messing
with our heads.
you could rule over
guys like harlan,
and that's just one part of
it, just a small part of it.
you want girls?
you can have them
you want your teachers
to be scared into giving you
good grades and
preferential treatment?
you can have it, too.
you could rule this school.
you could command respect
from your parents,
you could have
anything you want.
oh, yes, all i want to have is
a million dollars in the bank.
all you need is me.
all i ask of you is
your friendship, your loyalty
and your honesty.
you give me these
three things unconditionally,
i'll give you the world. it's
just psychology, hypnosis,
that sort of thing.
some guys in another school
that i went to went through
the same ritual with me.
that's how i started to
learn all the things.
that i'm going to teach you.
should we do it?
i don't know.
it's symbolic.
you have to trust me.
you drink the tears it opens
up your mind. that's all.
your subconscious opens up.
remember when ms. stevens
was talking about witches
and warlocks in class?
it's the same thing.
magic begins when your mind
believes in it. first you
break this taboo,
then i'll show you how
to break ten others.
what ten?
the ones that you're supposed
to follow.
the ten commandments.
you break those and all
the conditions that you're
brought up with just disappears.
what about murder?
symbolic, remember john.
not real.
it seems to me, this is a
perfect place for a baptism.
i don't know about this.
hey what's wrong man?
part of the ritual.
he's not lying, man.
this is awesome.
you guys have to try this.
trust me.
things are about to change.
your turn.
okay.
i need extra proof from you.
i need to know that
you really want this.
taste them.
right to the blue john. that's
why you're here.
god.
god has nothing to do with this.
man, i'm telling you,
this is probably the most cool
friday night we've ever had.
did you ever meet someone who
would sell you the world?
somebody who could seduce
you into believing anything,
20 minutes after meeting them?
that's what luc was like.
we were the freaks and
outcasts in a perfect world,
and this stranger was
promising to give us
everything we ever longed for.
things we couldn't even admit
to each other. and we bought it.
what are you guys doing in here?
hey, randall.
you remember randall, marcus?
he likes to write messages.
look guys, i didn't mean
anything from today.
it's harlan, i mean,
you know how harlan is, right?
things are about
to change, randall.
what's wrong?
you didn't hear?
what's up?
it's randall. they found him in
the pool house this morning.
he drowned last night in the
swimming pool.
yeah, they found an empty bottle
of whiskey by the pool. he
must have gotten drunk and
fell in. but he broke his neck.
hey, it happens.
i guess alcohol and swimming
pools just don't mix well.
guys, randall's dead.
what's going on?
i don't know anything
about it, do you?
he just drowned himself in
the swimming pool. it's not
a great loss, if you ask me.
what's your problem, grimes?
see something you like?
man, if i hadn't seen it,
i wouldn't believe it.
what if she expels us?
she won't.
me and here mrs. grimes have
a whole new understanding.
holy canoly, john.
we're going to be
freaking kings.
thou shall not kill, thou
shall not lie. we had
already begun. luc told us
that we had to break all
ten. and who knows how many
we had already done without
even taking note.
and so it began.
we were on our way to
fulfilling our new destinies
in a manner we never
envisioned before. our score,
our personal lives
and our own goals. we were
the ones running the show
now. not harlan, nor randall,
not alex. we knocked over
the ten commandments
like a stack of dominoes. later,
i would have reason to
suspect that luc used some
wild, unholy mind control powers
on us that night in the
pool house. but now i
believe that this was the
only truth luc ever told us.
the thing driving us was
something that might have
been there all along.
thou shall honor thy
mother and thy father.
jesus christ, lenny,
what's your problem? want
to put the head in head
mistress?
thou shall not take thy
lord's name in vain.
thou shall not
have any god before me.
thou shall not worship
thy graven image.
thou shall not
covet thy neighbor's
possessions.
thou shall not steal.
they had covered
almost all the bases and
somewhere, i knew luc was
getting stronger because
of it.
and even though i felt
like i was living
in some horrific nightmare, i
knew it was just starting.
i was beginning to get worried.
really? why?
well, i haven't seen you
around for a while. you've
been hiding out from me or what?
i, i have just been busy.
well, you know we're going
to have a whole week off
for semester break. you plan
on being busy then, too,
or is it safe for me to
go ahead and buy that
diaphragm?
what?
i'm sorry, i was trying
to get your attention
off that damn table top.
oh, no, i'm sorry. i'm really
screwing up this date.
well, you just seem to be
jumping on every word
i say.
oh my god. is that a smile?
it's a start.
thank god, for a second there,
i thought i was losing my touch.
no, no, it's definitely not
you. it's just that,
the schoolwork is starting to
pile up on me, that's all.
are you sure?
i'm totally sure.
i mean, is there something
going on? because you've
been acting totally
different. i mean all three
of you guys, you know. it's
like you've changed.
why? do you think it's bad?
because i have nice clothes?
because i care about what i
look like? or because i have
confidence now? look,
i don't know about you, but
i think it's a change
for the better.
hey, whoa, just calm down,
okay? that's all well and
good but i liked you
just fine before,
okay?
i'm sorry.
listen, i think i know why
you've been acting so weird.
really?
well yeah, i mean, you're
afraid, you know. you just
have this whole thing
in your head
about how i might be in
a different class
of people than you are in,
that i couldn't possibly be
attracted to you.
sounds like you've been talking
to good old matt.
well, it's possible. but it's
also possible that i
might have asked him.
listen, i like you a lot,
okay? i wouldn't be here if
i didn't. so there must be
something unique about you,
yes?
really?
really. i won't lie to you.
of course, unless you were
stinking rich and wanted
to put me in your will.
well, i guess i just have to
bear that in mind when i
inherit my first million.
promises, promises.
what's wrong?
i've got to get back
to the dorm.
john, wait, john.
what the hell?
i suppose i've had worse dates,
only i don't know when.
i was hoping you'd come
here to see me.
did i interrupt something?
what do you want?
you don't seem very happy
that i'm here, john.
no, it's not that.
john, i like you. i like
marcus and matt, too,
but you're on another level
entirely. you follow your
own drummer, i like that.
you're good. you're honest.
you're a true friend. and
i've told you nothing but
the truth no matter how crazy
the truth sounds. i
said this would happen.
you said what would happen?
do you really think she'd
be with you if it wasn't
for me?
we made this date before
i even met you.
i gave mary to you.
i watched you from afar
i admired you. i watched you
grow. mary is a gift.
and i have many more gifts for
you as long as you
give me something in return.
you're crazy.
you didn't give me mary.
you haven't
given any of us anything.
it's just some sort of mind
control.
you're not so
sure of that, are you john?
now, i'm offering you a chance
to belong and belong
to the winning team, but
you keep on turning me
away. i think you're jealous
maybe. can't you see what
i've become to your friends?
what do you want from me?
you haven't been doing
your share,
john. you're awfully low on
the old commandment-breaking
scale. it's time i gave
you an errand.
what kind of errand?
it's an easy one.
i want you to talk to trini
for us. you know,
mary's friend.
no way, you do it.
you have a reason to talk to
her, john. you're dating
mary, she trusts you. so what
you do is you go over
to her dorm room and tell her
you'll do some homework
with her, that's all.
why would i do that? maybe i
should just walk away right
now and see what happens.
you know what happens, john.
mary leaves you, your
friends leave you and i leave
you. and that one
fleeting chance that you have
at success, wealth and
power, it's all gone. now think
about that. do you really
want to take that chance?
i want you to talk to trini
tonight. you have an hour.
choose wisely.
and i did. i can't say why i
did it. i think i was making
a choice, or i thought i was
making one. i wanted to be
with my friends again, even
though i couldn't quite see
their own personalities
anymore. when i looked
into their eyes, all
i saw was luc.
so, how are things going with
mary? she can't stop
talking about you.
is that good?
ask her yourself.
what the hell are you
guys doing here?
well, we knew that this is
where john was and we
couldn't resist the chance
to break into the girls'
dorm room.
everybody, put your clothes
back on, please.
you guys wish.
it's got to be a little
hard to be romantic
without the wine, isn't it?
is that?
yup, alcohol. boys in
the girls' dorms.
is headmistress grimes is
going to be pissed.
i'll pass.
me, too.
no, i say a little sip
of wine isn't going
to hurt either of you two.
no.
okay, i guess a sip won't hurt.
wow, it's not as bad as
i would have thought.
what are they doing?
that's what i want to tell
you. they're getting the place
all comfy for us.
i should go.
no, you should watch john.
comfy? for me?
yes.
look guys, my boyfriend alex,
well you know alex.
shh.
i could not help myself.
i was part of this.
part of the brotherhood.
i was drawn into it.
i was under luc's power.
i just couldn't stop.
did you enjoy
yourselves this evening?
i thought we got her
off to a good start.
real good.
that's just the beginning
for us.
is that a?
that's right.
it's a spirit's tooth
of the warlock knife mrs.
stevens was
going on and on
about the other day.
where the hell did you get that?
like you said, it's
a private school.
they don't lock up anything
around here.
they really use that
in witchcraft?
do you think i took it?
i'm a warlock.
how do you think
i've done the things
that i've done? or how you've
gotten the powers
that you have?
i've given you a glimpse
of what i am capable of.
so, you're like dungeons
and dragons,
merlin and the hat,
fireballs and stuff?
no, nothing like that.
i make offerings to certain
forces and certain forces
grant me things in return.
you guys are popular now. you
command respect.
i've given you everything
you've ever wanted,
and that's just a glimpse
of what you could have.
so what are you saying?
i need three more to make
the ritual complete.
three more warlocks.
are you serious, man?
totally.
luc, you've made a believer
out of me.
is that why we're sitting around
like this?
it's the next part
of the process.
i'll give each of you
a spirit's tooth.
when you commit a sacrifice,
you have committed the final
act.
you'll have the power
within yourself.
you mean like murder?
what do you think happened
to randall?
did you?
did you kill him?
i didn't hurt a flea
as far as you're concerned.
you take your souls back
from your enemies,
and you take their souls along
with it.
when you do that, you'll be
empowered for life.
no one will ever cause you
pain or fear again.
you start with breaking the
ten commandments. you have
already broken nine.
just one more.
thou shall not kill.
i don't want to kill
anybody, man.
well, randall's dead
and your problems
at the school are much more
closer to being solved.
you have the power to solve
anything if you really want to.
complete our promise.
this weekend at semestral break,
everybody's going to be gone.
it will be perfect.
you've laid the groundworks
and now you have to build
on that.
like how?
you have to make an offering
to the spirit's tooth.
kill the one you hate the most.
i offer my vengeance.
i bind myself to my enemies.
this is the way it must be.
i offer my vengeance.
i bind myself to my enemies.
we bind ourselves to him.
we pledge to destroy him and
anyone who follows him.
we have but one master.
the dark one, the fallen
angel, prince of lies.
and then we shall be a coven.
hey marcus, guess
who i had a talk
with this morning?
trini, and guess what
she told me?
she said your loser pal john
van-owen came to her dorm
room and got her drunk.
and then.
and then what?
you know what marcus.
i thought trini was
a virgin, though.
i know about you guys.
and after i beat van-owen to
death, i might go on to
headmistress grimes
and the cops,
and tell them what i
know about randall.
you freaks are all going
to go to jail.
oh, i get it.
you're all upset because
we touched your girl.
we touched her.
licked her.
kissed her.
i mean, i guess we got her a
little bit more drunk than
we thought.
bastard.
hey, it happens.
you're right about
one thing, though.
we killed randall.
you know i think his last
words were,
help me. i'm drowning.
you're crazy.
yeah.
you better start running.
yeah, win or break.
you're making a serious
mistake, pal.
shut up, harlan.
what the hell is up
with you guys?
first the new kid shows up,
screws everything up and you
guys turn into big
men on campus.
what's your deal, john?
i said shut up.
what are you going to do?
you're a loser, john.
get the hell out of my way.
i don't think harlan knew
just how close he was to
being murdered.
i don't think i knew either.
but i was relieved i
didn't have it i me.
[clinking of keys]
[bumping sound]
hello?
who's there?
i guarantee anyone not in
their room at this hour
will be expelled.
i won't tolerate it.
huh?
what are you doing?
i thought i'd come and visit.
mr. slaton, do you know
what time it is?
does it matter?
i've seen the way you look at me
recently.
i figured it was just a
matter of time
before we had a
conversation alone.
it's late.
you should be in your room.
i'd rather be in yours.
don't you?
i don't,
i have no idea what you're
saying.
you've gone mad, haven't you?
what do you think you're doing?
oh baby,
you don't know half of it.
hello my friend, you look awful.
i have good reason.
believe me.
i take it, this means
harlan's out
of commission?
yeah.
but i don't want to talk about
it right now.
you did a good thing, john.
this world belongs to us.
you made it a better place.
i said i don't want
to talk about it.
you got what you wanted.
not yet.
i've got bigger plans.
a third ritual at the
pool house. we'll be gods.
i don't want to be a part
of this anymore.
you don't have a choice.
either share my feast
or share my fall.
don't you know that i can
take everything i've given
you away?
i don't want to be a part
of this anymore.
i'm going home, okay?
i'm quitting chandler academy,
the whole nine yards.
just leave me alone.
what about your friends?
they're your friends now.
headmistress grimes.
headmistress. grimes.
it's john van-owen.
i want to talk to you.
headmistress. grimes.
did you have a sudden urge to
confess something, john?
i thought you weren't
going to be a part
of this?
stay away from me, luc.
you look afraid. maybe i
can help you with that.
luc, we have got to tell them.
dude, i wanted to stop
alice's clock for
years.
they made our lives hell, john.
you, too.
so now they're in hell.
guess it all evens up, huh?
i gave them everything
they ever wanted.
i kept my end of the bargain.
and what do you get, luc?
they break the ten commandments.
they kill for you.
so what exactly do
you get from this?
you killed harlan.
you're part of this
whether you want
to be or not.
yeah, johnny.
stop being a wimp and get
on with the program.
you're a warlock now, john.
you're part of the covenant.
do the third ritual with
us and you will get to
go free.
and mary will be yours forever.
you leave her out of this.
you don't have to answer me
right away, johnny boy.
you're still doing this
big plan for tonight.
i guarantee it.
just ask headmistress grimes.
i think it's safe to say
she'll be out
of commission for awhile.
see you around.
i had nowhere to go and
no friends left
to help me.
i wanted to talk to mary,
but i knew the instant i
showed up on her doorstep,
her life would be in danger.
i only had one person
left to talk to.
[knocking on door]
just a second.
are you okay?
well sit down.
look,
i came to see you
because you're the only
person on earth right now who
might still listen to me
or believe me.
what¢á ís happening, john?
marcus and matt, the new kid
put them through some kind
of ritual thing and now they
think they have to kill
people.
what new kid?
he thinks he's a warlock.
a warlock?
i think he's going to do
something terrible tonight.
like what?
i don't know.
well, if you want me to help
you then you and i are going
down to the police station,
and we will tell them all
about this.
but they're going to think
that i'm a part
of this.
not if you're with me.
okay. i'll go with you.
but let me call mary first
to check and see if she's
okay.
they might try to do
something to her.
[phone ringing]
hello.
mary?
hello johnny, what's up?
luc.
that's right pal, it's
your buddy luc.
ah gee kiddo, i'm sorry but
you must have just missed
mary.
she doesn't seem to
be here right now.
what did you do to her,
you sick freak?
nothing yet. in fact she's going
to be accompanying me
to the old pool house.
you remember the poolhouse,
right johnny?
she's our guest.
personally i think she's
going to have one
hell of a time.
what do you want?
you know what i want, john.
i need you to complete
the covenant.
i get credit for the souls of
you and your two friends,
plus all the kills, plus all
the goofing around. and i
get to be leader of the
covenant, destined
for big things.
well, just let her go and i'll,
ah, ah johnny, i make the
deals here not you.
i need you to come to the
poolhouse. we'll settle all
our business there.
if you don't do that for
me, then being a murder
suspect is going to be the least
of your problems.
count on it.
what if he doesn't come?
have some faith.
he'll show.
are you sure you want to go
through this because we can
get this whole thing resolved
by the police you know?
this is beyond anything the
police can help us with.
yeah, but if you go through
with this, you're making the
problem worse.
i'm not going to let
anything happen
to mary.
looks like quite a little
party going on here.
i'm guessing you're not cramming
for my history final.
well, well, if it isn't
ms. stevens.
you look confused.
did you think john was lying?
i thought he was exaggerating
about the situation, but
i guess he wasn't.
it's just her.
john didn't come with her.
john left on his own.
he didn't want to be involved.
so he ran off.
he's probably on his way to
get the police right now.
you lie.
what's the matter, luc?
can't you use your powers to
make all the police go away?
don't mock me.
you're already dead and
everytime you show me
disrespect that death is
going to be a little slower
and a little more painful.
why don't you let
the girl go, luc?
you don't know who you're
dealing with.
right now i'm pretty sure
it's some lost, little boy
who needs a lot of help.
so whatever you want
from me, you can have it
after you let mary leave.
and what do you know?
you deal with these kids
from these upper-crust
families.
nice homes.
kids who have their whole
lives mapped out for them.
their parents enroll them
here at chandler academy,
so they can have the prestige
of having junior
in a private school in hell.
but they don't know the
difference between jesus
christ and ricky martin.
you seem so sure about
everybody, don't you
luc?
i'm not finished.
it's what you get for
not paying attention
to my class, luc.
like i said, the witches and
the warlocks believe that
their opposite numbers exist
and wipe them out.
did you ever wonder who your
opposite number was?
who? john?
no, me.
i was sent to stop you.
and it seems like a pretty
crummy assignment.
i don't care who you are. i'm
running the show here.
welcome to hell.
what's the matter, john?
you don't dig the new look?
i bet you won't tell
on us now, huh?
either you're with us or
against us, johnny.
if you¢á íre against us,
we'll be needing your
intestines.
get back.
crucifix, i'm a warlock.
get your freaking
superstitions right.
leave them alone.
i think you messed up, darling.
it should keep you
away for a while.
stay away from me.
come on, johnny.
you can't even
back up your teacher?
you're an angel.
you're not my friend anymore.
you're not even human.
not so fast, johnny.
remember the girl?
now drop the fucking knife.
you shouldn't have run
from your friends,
johnny boy.
but they were just servants
and so are you.
i forgot to tell you, when
you kill someone
with a spirit's tooth, like
when you killed harlan,
your soul belongs to me.
now give it to me one more
time, take it or leave it.
be my third acolyte.
and i'll let her survive.
i don't trust you.
you don't have a choice.
i own your soul.
now get down on your knees.
good boy. now johnny, i
want you to tell me,
there's no one in
your life but me.
my life but you.
i own your soul.
you own my soul.
now prove it by killing off
your girlfriend mary.
john.
you don't understand, mary,
luc can make me great.
he can make everybody love me.
it's what i've always
wanted, isn't it?
it's good to see you come
around sweetheart.
john, please don't.
mary, i have to.
see that knife,
i've never killed anyone
with a spirit's tooth.
fuck you.
it's time to go, luc.
nice work, johnny.
it's good to know that somebody
listens in my class.
she's gone.
damn it.
why did you have to
hit me so hard?
you guys were asking for it.
i don't know, man, i think
i've got a bump and a dent
in my skull.
thanks to you.
thanks for nothing, john.
what do you say we blow this
joint and go and enroll in a
public school?
you lead the way.
hey john,
do you think a couple
friends can join you
there?
i wouldn't have it
any other way.
even now when i go to church,
i will light a candle against
the horrible night i
almost lost my friends.
and i want
to believe that it's
over, really over.
but you know the old story
by now. it's never really
over for him.
he might be there now.
in your town, in your school.
the new kid, the guy
with the cards,
looking for souls to corrupt,
for minds to
take over.
i don't think we can ever
really stop him,
but whatever you do,
watch for him.
i think he'll be there soon.