♪
What's up?
Street dreams.
- Hey, go, cops, go!
- Stop, do not run.
♪
♪ When I pretend everything
is what I want it to be
♪ I look exactly like what
you had always wanted to see
♪ When I pretend, I can't
forget about the criminal I am
♪ Stealing second after second
just cause I know I can
♪ But I can't pretend this is
the way it'll stay, I'm just
♪ Trying to bend the truth
♪ I can't pretend I'm who
you want me to be, so I'm
♪ Lying my way from you
♪ No, no turning back now
♪ I want to be pushed aside,
so let me go
♪ No, no turning back now
♪ Let me take back my life,
I'd rather be all alone
♪ No turning back now
♪ Anywhere on my own
'cause I can see
♪ No, no turning back now
♪ The very worst part
of you is me
Hey, you see how many cops
there were?
That was ridiculous.
Reese!
I thought you got popped.
Nah, I couldn't believe
that shit,
but the motherfuckers
got my shoe, man.
Fuck your shoe,
be happy you ain't
on your way to jail right now.
Hey where's Mikey?
Boy's probably back there
showing off
his Boy Scout badges
trying to make friends
with the cops or something.
That was real funny, guys.
Could have at least helped me
get my bag over the fence.
Every man for himself,
you know the deal.
- I got a present for you.
- Thanks, dude.
All right, where we going, man?
We can't stand here forever.
How about the West Forest Head?
There's cops all over the place.
They've got cameras up
and everything.
Fuck that, let's go to the
Woodley Ledge.
Oh, dude's got a point.
Go slow, I'm a smoker.
♪ What you about to witness
♪ Has never been done before
♪ High House motherfuckers
♪ I live by this model
till the day that I drop
♪ Young, fly, flashy,
my nigga, it don't stop
♪ With diamonds on my neck
that's cold as a nice pop
♪ With a bank account so large
it'd buy out your block
♪ Fresh crew sweater, nigga,
you know how I diddy-bop
♪ Young is on the block
like Terry,
you make the city pop ♪
♪ Stay humble,
got bitches by the bundle
♪ I ball so much,
you ain't never seen me fumble
♪ Raisin' them jungles with them
killers and drug dealers
♪ Where some wear Raiders,
and some wear Steelers
♪ I stayed on that boy,
pushin' up that block
♪ Now I'm limpin' in the hills
and I'm sitting on top
♪ We fresh, we fly
♪ We got them brand new decks
Fucking kidding me?
Fucking kidding me right now?
Give me that.
♪
Hey, if you stay more centered
above your front truck,
you pretty much got it
right here.
Did I ask you for your advice?
Damn.
I'm just sayin', man,
that's what helps me.
Thanks for your concern, buddy,
but I think I've got it.
Here we go.
♪ But don't test me,
I pack nothing but thunder
♪ They is to skate, I mean,
I'm more like a player
- Easy as yo mom.
- Oh shit, dude.
Look like he's talkin'
about your moms, man.
♪ Love a real nigga 'cause you
know I'm from the hood
What, you don't think
I could do that?
Oh, now the up-and-coming ripper
from Chicago, Derreck Cabrera,
about to take the crown
from out veteran champ,
Troy Vincent,
let's see how he does, folks.
♪
Took you out of there!
Yes!
Out of there.
No, you couldn't.
Hey, take it
somewhere else, man.
It's not like you can't read.
Oh, come on, man,
there's nobody back here.
Look, I don't care,
I don't want to get sued
when one of you guys falls
and breaks your neck.
Nobody's going to break
their neck, it's a little ledge.
Look, if you don't
get out of here right now,
I'm going to call
the cops, okay.
What are you going to tell them,
"Officer, I've got some
skaters back here,
come get them immediately?"
You don't know what it's like
to have your own business.
I bet you don't even have a job.
Yeah, I know, I'm a stupid,
loser skater.
Yeah, you said it, I didn't.
Yo, easy up, Richard Simmons.
It's not like he's...
Oh my good Lord,
look at that side bike.
That thing's beautiful!
Fuck you!
Get the fuck out of here!
I'll tell you,
I'm calling the cops!
You fucking pricks!
♪ We fresh
(TV audio)
♪
Good morning, sweetheart.
Good morning.
Breaking your streak?
Excuse me?
Do you have
to start it right now?
Can't it wait till
he eats his breakfast?
Well, I don't know when I get
a letter that tells me
that my son
has missed seven days
of school this month,
and if he continues
to be delinquent
that he won't graduate.
I don't know about you,
but this sounds like something
that needs to be discussed
as soon as possible.
And guess what?
As soon as possible
is right now.
Shit.
Do you really
have to use that language?
I also got a phone call
that you and I've got a meeting
with the principal
Monday morning.
Does this have anything to do
with Troy and Reese and Cash?
Don't forget Mikey.
Mikey, at least he's got skill.
For your information,
Mikey hasn't missed
more than two days of school
this whole year.
You really spoke to his mommy?
We were concerned.
You know, your education is...
Something I can always
fall back on.
Yes, I may have missed a lot
of school, but I'm not deaf.
Hey.
There's no reason
to get fresh with your mother.
She just wants
what's best for you.
Well then, I guess
what's best for me
is getting my ass to class.
You know where to find me.
♪
We are going to have
a lovely party.
There's going to be
lots of alcohol around.
You guys should definitely come.
So how many kegs are you going
to have for tomorrow night?
- Seven.
- Only seven kegs?
Ace Cooper had 10.
Well, we're going to have
jello shots, too.
Mmm, I love me some jello shots.
I know you do, baby.
So, uh, is your
little skater boyfriend
going to be there, or do I get
you all to myself?
Am I that good in your dreams?
I don't know, let's ask him.
Hi, baby.
Ask me what?
We can see your boxers.
Can't afford pants that fit?
Can't afford a cool haircut?
I didn't know straight guys
rocked blond tips.
So Brad's having
a party tomorrow night.
- You're coming, right?
- Nah, I'm over it.
What, you got a date with your
loser boyfriends Cash and Reese?
That's funny, Brad,
you didn't think you were losers
when you used to skate.
Obviously one of us
has decided to grow up.
Come on, baby, please come
to the party with me.
It's obviously not my scene.
I know, but it's my scene,
and I want you
to be a part of it with me.
Well, what about Sunday?
Do I got to go with you
to your family thing?
Come on, Derreck,
I'll make it worth your while.
And my dad says
he's got something
he wants to talk to you about.
Really, what's that?
It's totally awesome.
You know I love you, right?
Hey, Grind King.
It's cool if I take
your girl to the party?
♪ Excuse me,
I'm talkin' to you
Drink, drink, drink!
♪
♪ I see that look in your eyes,
I wanna touch you, baby
♪ Are you by yourself tonight,
I wanna to touch you, baby
♪ I see that look in your eyes,
I wanna touch you, baby
♪ Excuse me,
I'm talkin' to you, hey
Hey, you miss me?
Baby!
You're here!
And you are wasted.
Am not.
Okay, maybe just a little bit,
but it's a party.
Let's get you a beer.
Come on, baby.
Brad's ready.
Shut up, I told him
I'd think about it.
Think about what?
Keg stand!
I know you like that.
Put me down.
♪ All night long
♪ Let's party,
let's party
Let's go, girl, you can do it.
Come on, you can do this.
Just put it in
your mouth and suck.
Drink, drink, drink, drink,
drink, drink, drink, drink,
drink, drink, drink, drink!
That was totally awesome.
Yes!
Wait, where are you going?
You should totally do one.
Yeah, I can't think of anything
better to do than be upside-down
getting beer
poured down my throat
with my ass hanging out.
Shut up, it's not like
I was wearing a thong,
and everyone's seen me
with my cheerleading outfit.
Yeah, I'm leaving.
We not extreme enough for you?
♪
Are you seriously
going to leave?
You want to come with?
I didn't think so.
Hey, Sam.
Let's do another one.
Who's next on the keg?
You are, bitch!
Do it!
Drink, drink, drink, drink,
drink, drink!
Yo, Mikey.
You still gonna skate the rail?
♪
Dude, I got to get out of here,
these fumes are killing me.
You did not just childproof me!
The security guard
gets off at 11,
so we will wait, right, Reese?
Yeah, the guard's my cousin
Shanita's baby daddy.
So you just randomly
found out what time
your cousin's baby daddy
gets off work tonight?
Actually, he was at a barbeque
talking about his hours,
fucked up and shit.
♪
You didn't tell me
she's fucking white dudes.
Don't worry about it.
You would never get a chance.
♪
It's 11 now.
See, niggas, look.
Don't be tellin' me
I don't know what's up.
♪
Come on.
Aw, dick suckers.
This is bullshit.
Why'd you act like
you scoped this place out?
I did, two days ago
there was nothing on it.
Look at 'em, man, they're not
even normal skate stoppers.
They're just big-ass nuts.
Keep me out of this, man.
Somebody went
weld-happy on this shit.
Fuck this.
Aw, man.
That's some bullshit.
Crock of shit,
let's go back to my house.
♪ Let's go
♪
Give me that.
Yeah.
Man, this is ridiculous.
I'm sick
of all this skate-proofing
and getting kicked out
of everywhere.
- This is where we should go.
- What is it?
It's a skate plaza in Ohio.
Damn, you can get
the sickest lines here.
How far is it?
It's not that far,
it's like eight hours away.
Yeah, Derreck, you can finally
finish your Sponsor Me video.
Please finish that video,
I'm over giving you boards.
I know, man, I just got to
get that final banger.
What's your "final banger"?
♪
I'll show you.
Oh, this ought to be good.
♪
Yeah!
Come on, man.
A 360 flip, crooked grind
on a handrail?
Are you kidding me?
You livin' in
a fantasy land right now.
If this is a fantasy land,
Danny DeVito
would be taking
a dump on my chest.
- That's wrong, man.
- All right, well, look.
What are you going to name it?
Well, I mean, you're so good
that you're inventing tricks.
You might as well
give it a name.
I'm not going
to fucking name it.
Okay, look, look.
Let me help you out.
Why don't you call it the NAC?
That's actually sick.
Right?
Why the NAC?
For Not A Chance.
Aw, come on.
Oh, my god,
yo, let's go tonight.
No, we can't go tonight,
I got to work tomorrow.
We'll leave after I work,
drive through the night,
and we can skate all day Monday.
- I can't go.
- Why not?
Come on, D, it's only
for one day, man.
You got to finish
that video, right?
Yeah, well, kind of promised
Samantha I'll take her...
Come on, man!
The truth comes out.
Did you lose your dick,
or did you just give it away?
I can't even believe
you're still with that chick.
I'll tell you why
he's still with her,
that bitch fine as hell.
- Yeah she is.
- Easy.
I'm just sayin', if I was you,
I'd bang, bang, bang.
Me too, I'd be right up
in that shit.
What the fuck is the matter
with you dudes, man?
That's my girl.
Hey, she won't
miss you too much.
You can tell her
to bring Brad along.
Fuck you.
Hey, dude, I didn't
mean it like that, man.
Whatever, I'm out of here, man.
I hope you bitches
have fun in Ohio.
I'll see you when you get back.
Dude, who took a shit
in your vagina?
♪
What's up, Kenny?
How you doing there, buddy?
I haven't seen you for a while.
Haven't seen you either.
Yeah, how's it going, man?
- Good.
- Let's see what you got.
Oh, nice, you got a little
more pop
than the last time I saw you.
I see your flick mark's
coming in nice.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
How are you?
I'm all right, how you doing?
I feel like shit.
Oh, sorry, Kenny.
It's okay, my mom says
"shit" all the time.
Is it all right if I talk
to Derreck alone for a second?
Sure, I know all about
alone time, too.
All right, Kenny,
I'll catch up with you.
See ya.
So, late night?
Yeah.
I wish you would have stayed.
Well, looks like you were
doing all right without me.
You invited Brad?
Why am I even here?
Because you're my boyfriend,
and I want you to be here.
Hey, hey, how's it going over
here with you kiddies?
I was just talking to
your buddy, Brad, over there.
He is so excited about attending
the University of Arizona
this fall.
But you might want to go
save him from your Aunt Linda.
Mr. Cabrera here and I have some
business to discuss.
Okay.
I'll see you in a second.
Let's go for a walk.
So you and my angel have been
seeing each other how long?
Three years.
You're happy though, right?
Yeah, of course,
she's a wonderful girl.
Yeah, yeah, that she is.
She asked me to offer you a job.
Really, well, that would be
very nice of you.
Hey, hey, It's minimum wage,
but the hours are excellent,
and you can start
right after graduation.
All right, so what would
I be doing?
Thinking I'd give you a job
in the mailroom, you know.
The beating heart
of every company.
Thanks a lot, sir,
but I never pictured myself
as the mail boy type.
Really?
Too good to work
in the mailroom, is that it?
- I didn't say that.
- Hey, don't worry about it.
If the mailroom is below you,
I'll start you in the warehouse
with the rest of the immigrants.
Immigrant?
You just... what the fuck is that
supposed to mean, "immigrant"?
Exactly what I said.
♪
Yeah, hold on.
Derreck, stop.
- Derreck, what's wrong?
- Get off me.
Stop, what's the matter
with you?
- I got to go.
- Why?
Aren't you
excited about the job?
I mean, it's a great opportunity
for someone like you.
- Someone like me?
- You know what I mean.
No, I don't think I do, Sam.
What do you mean,
someone who skates?
Or someone who's failing
out of school?
Or someone who's
a fucking immigrant?
Your daddy made it
abundantly clear.
You know what, Sam,
this is bullshit.
You and I both know it,
alls you want to do
is get fucked up
at frat parties on beer bongs.
You know what, if you think
you're so cool
for failing out of school
for skating,
you're going to turn
into a nobody,
just like your loser friends.
Well, at least
I'm doing something I enjoy
and not just doing what daddy
has planned for me.
It's time for you
to leave, Mr. Cabrera.
Yeah, I was thinking
the same thing.
Don't come crying to me when
your big dreams fall apart.
Don't fucking hold your breath.
Pull up your goddamn pants,
you loser!
He's not worth it.
♪
Yo.
You guys, uh, leave yet?
No, I'm packing up right now.
You got room for one more?
Yeah, of course, man.
D, dude, I'm sorry
for what I said before, dude.
- I didn't mean to...
- Don't worry about it.
- I'll be there in ten.
- All right, cool.
♪ On the road with my home boys,
and they got no place to go
♪ So I'ma go town to town
♪ East to west then down
♪ We go south to north
♪ On the road with my home boys
and they got no place to go
No joke, Mikey.
This watch is $5,000.
Because you're my friend,
I'll give it to you for 500.
Man, that shit is as fake
as the Jackson family noses.
Quit blowin' me up, Cash.
Yo, D.
That little cheerleader
would love to see you
shining like this,
don't you think?
Hey, they broke up, man.
- Mikey!
- Sorry, D.
I didn't know
it was a big secret.
Think of it this way, man,
now you got more time to skate,
so you can concentrate
on your video,
concentrate on
getting hooked up, right?
Your video's gonna be sick!
Still a long shot
gettin' on the team.
Jesus, man, why don't you just
piss on his birthday cake?
I'm just sayin', I mean,
look how long it took me
to get on Flow.
I know it.
I'll tell you one thing,
that's for sure.
As soon as he drops that NAC,
it's going to take
a gaggle of Navy Seals
on angel dust to get my dick
out of his butt.
What?
Oh, come on.
♪ Got a lot of things
I got to do, I'm leavin'
♪ Hold me, baby
♪
Come on, boys, wake up.
It's the golden hour.
Wipe the shit out of your eyes.
Breakfast is on me.
How is breakfast on you?
Dude, you're broke.
One dollar, I can
get you all fed.
What are we going to do,
share a candy bar?
Just get the hell out
of the car, lazy shitheads.
All right, gentlemen and lady.
Check it out.
The magic dollar.
- The fuck is this?
- That's tape, dipshit.
Yeah, we see that it's
tape, but how is tape
all over a dollar
going to get us food?
Well, apparently there's more
than one brainiac in this bunch.
Pay attention, Mr. Wizard.
You take this dollar, and you
stick it into the machine.
- You following me, retard?
- Gotcha.
And?
No way!
Free food and free money.
Free money?
Take it easy.
Let me show ya.
Oh my gosh!
Nice.
Boys, have at it.
Let's go.
♪ When
♪ When I get my big break
♪ Break
♪
Jackpot!
Holy shit!
This place is insane!
♪
Shit, look, there's all sorts
of pros here.
Here comes
your future team manager.
Start kissing some ass.
Yeah, you better pucker up.
- Oh, what's up, Troy?
- What's goin' down, Tony?
- How you doin', man?
- Good, man, how are you?
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming out here, man?
I would have brought
you some boards.
No worries, I'm straight,
what's up?
Like the whole team's
out here right now?
No, man, just a couple of 'em.
Just out here gettin' some last
minute footage for the video.
Video's going to be sick, man.
So, what's up,
is this your crew?
Reese, Cash, Mikey, and Derreck.
So, this is Derreck, huh?
Heard a lot about you, man.
So still waitin' on your tape.
Just tryin' to get
that last trick, you know?
He's still tryin' to get
his final banger.
Well that sounds sick, man,
I'm looking forward to it.
And your footage too, Troy.
I got to keep moving
though, fellas.
You guys have fun, all right?
What the hell, guys,
you gonna sit there
and thumb your ass all day,
get out there and skate!
Come on, Troy,
let's do this shit, man.
♪ Raw, rip it like
you're workin' a chainsaw
♪ From New York to Cali,
New Jersey to Crenshaw
♪ I speak the gift,
while y'all plead the fifth
♪ My team is sick, we eat,
sleep, and breathe this shit
♪ Rough and rugged,
kill 'em soft
♪ We don't leave one standin'
when we're breakin' 'em off
♪ Takin' a loss,
not a chance in your life
♪ If bein' fresh is wrong,
I don't wanna be right
♪ Stop, drop, and roll
we got soul
♪ Safety popped off
when we lock and load so
♪ This is how
we get this done
♪ You can check on the rep,
yep, second to none
♪
♪ Check on the rep,
second to none, yeah
♪ This is how
we get this done
♪ You can check on the rep,
second to none
♪
♪ Check on the rep,
second to none, yeah
♪ This is how
we get this done
♪ You can check on the rep,
second to none
♪ Yo, check the rep,
yep, 'nuff respect
♪ If not for the jewels I drop,
the chunky neck
♪ I'm funk fresh,
equipped with a rusty Tek
♪ Am I the best, well,
I gotta put it bluntly, yes
♪ You can't touch me,
the flows'll getcha
♪ Squeeze breath outta ya chest
like boa constrictors
♪ I'm a killer,
and I usually know my victims
♪ So I catch a lotta bodies
on the homie system, uh
♪ Don't get it twisted,
I'll break ya jaw
♪ You'll be sippin' fried
chicken through a crazy straw
♪ Liquid diet, bitch,
we official pirates
♪ I ghost-ride the ghost ship,
drinkin' and drivin', yeah
That's what I'm
talking about, buddy.
Yeah.
There you go, sweetheart.
Thanks, boss.
So, what, you ready to try
the NAC?
Don't call it that.
Whatever, man, you ready to try?
- Ready to do it!
- Do it.
- Let's do it.
- Go.
- All right.
- Don't fuck up.
Yeah, like you can
do better, Cash.
Easy up, bub, hit the red button
and be happy you got a job.
Hey, you just work
on your tent, all right?
Oh!
That was it, dude.
That was it.
I got it, all right.
Mikey, you got to jump
on this line, I just made.
No way, man, he's grinding
almost perfect right now.
- He almost made the NAC, dude.
- Exactly, he almost made it.
I just made the lines,
it's gonna take me
like two minutes, man.
Come on, man.
What's going on?
I just made these lines, I just
want to film it right now.
Dude, couple more tries,
he's gonna have this.
Dude, I just
want to do it right now.
You know I need footage
for the video.
Why did we even come here,
you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I know, that's cool, man,
get that shit.
All right, I'll be right there.
What's going on?
I got to go film Troy right now.
He's got a line
he wants me to film.
♪
You know, smoking's
bad for your health.
So is landing
without your board.
What do you know about skatin'?
Are you a skater?
Do I look like a skater?
Definitely not.
Skater girls usually aren't
as cute as yourself.
At least, I've never seen one.
So, why are you here?
See that little punk over there?
That's my little bro.
Been drivin' him around
for years.
He can't seem to pass
his driver's test.
Wait, you're Eric Jones's
sister?
Eric Jones is my little brother.
Well, uh, I'm Derreck, my boys
and I, we drove up here...
Okay, Derreck, let me just
save you some time.
I'm not the girl that falls
for the troubled, tortured,
"I have a dream" song and dance.
I've seen it all before and
it has the same boring ending.
Well, no worries here,
I mean I'm not looking
for that cool girl who wears
Chuck Taylors
and purple hoodies.
What's up, sis?
This guy botherin' you?
Nah, he's cool.
So, now I'm cool?
Until proven otherwise.
All right, that's cool.
Hey, man, I saw that back flip,
it was sick.
Aw, shit, thanks, man.
I saw you tryin'
something crazy over there.
What was that?
Oh, trade flip crook?
Yeah, my boys call it
the NAC though.
If he'd commit,
maybe he'd make it.
You should take her advice, man.
She knows
what she's talkin' about.
Yeah, I think
I'm startin' to get that.
All right, well, it was nice
to meet you guys.
I'm gonna get back to it.
♪
♪ This one right here,
this one a pusher
♪ Brooklyn, stand up
♪ With some Miss 40s
fake-ass rappers
♪ Back in the days,
I never snatched pocket books
♪ I just snatch ya mind up
with the flow and the hook
♪ That's right, be on alert,
coming faster
♪ Corny MC's,
body snatcher with the rapture
♪ Dismember ya body
like I was a raptor
♪ Took ya eyes out,
so you can't see my laughter
♪ Don't care how many gold
and platinum plaques you got
♪ I put my foot in your ass,
up in the spot
Hey, yo, man, that is tight,
you want to shoot that?
- Hell yeah, man, I'm down.
- Cool, let's do it.
Thanks.
♪ Rockin' hard body cardigan
with the Timberlands
♪ P.F. drop the beat,
AFU drop the grammar
♪ Was swift with the gift,
old school like cold bangers
Damn, you all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
♪ Chitty chitty bang bangin'
♪ Name your whole rap crew
like I'm gang bangin'
Holy shit,
I should be shootin' Derreck.
It's not like he's
going to make it anyway.
Whoa, where are you going, man?
Somebody's got to film it.
It isn't you, man.
Oh, come on, Troy,
we can film afterwards, man.
No, no, no,
we're leaving afterwards.
I drove us here,
I say when we go.
That's bullshit.
Fuck it, do whatever you want.
I got you, D.
Let's do it.
Now that's a banger.
You mean a hammer?
No, I mean a banger.
Now, if that's B.S.
down 16 stairs
by a flooty, little turd
rockin' young-ass jeans
is a hammer.
A boner-inducing trick,
one of which
your pea-sized brain
can't possibly comprehend,
is a banger.
Now please, stop looking at me
before I reconsider
our friendship.
(groaning)
He gets into it every time.
Hey, you got it, boy.
You got this, man.
Yeah, man.
Come on.
You got this.
Hold up, hold up.
I gotta reload.
- Okay, let's get it, man.
- See that?
Hey, check it out real quick.
Let's go, we're leaving.
What, com...
Dude, he was just
about to land it.
I don't care.
Unless you all want to be
permanent residents of Ohio,
I suggest you come with me.
That's fucked up.
Who put the bee
in your bonnet, dick-socket?
- Jesus Christ.
- Asshole.
Nice meetin' you.
Take care, brother.
My ride's leavin', man.
It's cool, maybe next time.
All right, thank you, though.
Yo, Derreck.
What's up, Tony?
What's going on, man?
So, was that the final banger?
Yeah, man.
Just gotta land it now.
Well, look, man,
if you can give me a tape
with that on it,
I can pretty much
guarantee you
a spot on the team,
no problem.
All right,
well, I'll guarantee you
a tape with it.
All right, man, perfect.
- Hell yeah.
- Good work, buddy.
All right, Tony, take care, man.
Take it easy, man.
Damn, Derreck.
That was sick, man.
Thanks, man.
Your friend's kind of a dick.
Yeah, pretty much.
So, what's the story?
We gonna see you in Tampa
next weekend or what?
I'm not sure.
You gonna be there?
Mm, I might be.
Then I might be too.
Well, man,
I hope to see you there.
All right, man.
Miss Jones.
♪
Come on, boy.
All right, boy.
♪
Hey, what'd Tony say?
Oh, just a little encouragement.
Cool.
(car honks)
Hey, her name's Taylor.
Taylor, huh?
All right.
Nice.
Let's go.
Check ya in a minute.
All right, dawg.
♪
What the fuck?
I can get it.
All right there, boss?
I'm bleeding.
♪
Hey, D.,
who was that chick
you were talking to?
Yeah, you know that dude
who got fourth place
in Tampa last year?
Yeah, Eric Jones, right?
Yeah, she's his older sister.
Shit, he got all rogue
after Tampa last year.
See, dude,
now you have to go to Tampa
because if you drop
the NAC in Tampa,
you're getting on the
team for sure.
One hard trick is not
going to get you on a team.
I just don't want you
to get your hopes up.
♪
Shit!
Are you trying to give me
a heart attack?
You almost gave your mother one
five hours ago.
I had to give her sleeping pills
just to calm her down.
Sorry.
Oh, is that it?
You know what you missed
this morning, right?
We were supposed to have
a meeting with your principal
to discuss, um,
how did she describe it?
Your habitual truancy.
How do you think it looks
when I have to call in
and say, "I'm sorry,
we can't make it
'cause I can't find my son?"
Like you're a bad father?
Is that what you think?
That this is my fault?
No.
Man, you just don't get it.
What don't I get, Derreck?
That school's a joke to you,
and that hanging out
with your friends
is more important
than your future?
That's not how it is!
Then tell me how it is, Derreck.
Because right now,
from where I'm standing,
it looks like you're
just blowing everyone off.
Fine, I'm an idiot.
Are we done?
Don't push me, Derreck.
Whatever it is
that you think you're doing
is gonna stop right now.
Do you understand me?
I said, "Do you understand me?"
I need a verbal response.
Yes!
Good.
I rescheduled
for tomorrow morning,
and Derreck, whatever you do,
do not disappear again.
I'll be there.
Don't disappoint me.
Turn the lights off
when you're done.
Derreck,
I just don't understand.
Your grades, your absences,
I mean, really,
your general demeanor
all seem to suggest
that you have no interest
in graduating.
I cannot make you
do your homework,
and I cannot make you
attend class.
Do you understand
where I'm going with this?
For someone of your age,
and I know
you're not a bad kid
and I can see your...
and without
a high school diploma...
isn't necessarily
what's right for your future.
She's great.
You're so lucky, Derreck.
Okay, so I think you should talk
to your teachers
about what you've missed
and convince them
that you're committed
to bringing up your grades, huh?
I guess.
You guess?
You were just given
a second chance, Derreck.
Doesn't that
mean anything to you?
Maybe.
I don't know.
Yeah, well, I know.
You're gonna start taking life
a little more seriously,
and you're going to start
by accepting that job
that Mr. Reynolds gave you.
Hell no, I ain't workin'
for that racist.
What are you talkin' about?
Nothing, man.
People just aren't
as perfect as you think, Dad.
What, you think
I don't know people?
You think no one's
ever talked down to me?
Treated me
like a second-class citizen?
Come on, Derreck,
you gotta grow up.
Get some thick skin
and take some responsibility
for yourself, man.
♪
I'm going to work,
and when you get home,
I expect you're gonna have
a better attitude.
♪
Hey.
You weren't in school yesterday.
I was busy.
The barbeque
got kinda out of hand.
Yeah.
So...
So?
- An apology would be nice.
- For what?
For embarrassing me
in front of my family,
for starters.
Sam, I'm not sorry.
We're done.
We both know that.
Are you seriously
breaking up with me?
We already broke up.
Samantha Reynolds
does not get dumped.
already got very dumped.
Are you kidding me?
I am the best fucking thing
you ever had.
You are so done.
Nobody is ever gonna look at you
at this school again.
It is what it is, Sam.
Fuck you, Derreck.
Fuck me.
Ooh.
Later.
Peace.
♪
(phone rings)
What the fuck is that?
Damn.
We're cutting the knobs
off the university rail.
Well, go do it, get the fuck
out of my face, dumbass.
I need you guys to help.
Oh, fuck that, man.
We leave for Tampa
in the morning.
There's no way I'm gonna risk
getting arrested
on some bullshit.
Man, you're not
gonna get arrested.
All's you got to do
is look out for us.
Yeah, just go
to the lot across the street
and call us if you see a cop.
Then Reese
will give us a signal,
we'll cut the lights.
Nobody's gonna get caught.
Cut these knobs off,
skate it all night.
Yup.
Fuck it, I'm down.
I have wanted to do
that frontside crooked grind
for a while, you know?
So, you in?
I'm down, let's do this.
(cheering)
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Let's go, boys.
♪
All right,
I'm gonna go around back
in case the pigs
want to get sneaky.
Don't be gettin'
caught up on the phone
with none of these girls, man.
I need you to pay attention.
Don't trip, man.
I ain't gonna miss.
- Let's do this.
- Come on, Mike.
♪
(motor starts)
You ready?
Yeah.
Pop this on.
Cool.
You ever done this before?
Hey, just watch out for me,
all right?
All right, cool.
♪
Shit, that's loud, man.
Call Troy.
See if he hears that.
All right.
Hey, could you hear that?
All right, cool.
Just call us
if you see anything, all right?
Thanks.
No, we're good, dude.
♪
It's pretty easy.
Awesome, man, keep going.
All right.
Let's do this.
♪
Oh, shit!
Don't stop, don't stop,
don't stop, don't stop.
Fuck.
(police siren)
Stop right there!
♪
Cops, cops!
Shut the light!
♪
(police siren)
Drop it, drop it!
Go!
Mikey, leave this shit!
I can't,
my uncle's gonna kill me!
Go!
No, you go!
Mike, fine, go!
Just I'll stay.
Just get out of here, dude!
Do not move!
♪
Want to thank you
for getting here
so quickly.
Absolutely, officer.
Well, as you can clearly see,
Mr. Cabrera,
this is your son
vandalizing private property.
Yes, it is.
I can see that.
It's not like these businesses
hate skateboarders.
It's just they can't afford
to be sued
when one of them gets hurt.
I completely understand,
and it won't happen again.
I know these kids
are just having fun,
but this is going too far.
Okay.
Michael Robbins is free to go.
However, he'll have
to wait 30 days
before he can regain custody
of his equipment.
As for your son,
your signature will release him.
You'll receive some paperwork
in the next few days
about his court date.
Thank you, officer.
Let's go.
You can pick your stuff up
from the cage on the way out.
Um, officer.
Uh, am I going to be charged
with anything?
You wanna be?
- No.
- Then get out of here.
♪
Your keys.
Come on.
Give me your keys.
Get in the car.
Mikey.
♪
Thank you for the ride,
Mr. Cabrera.
Get out of the car, Mikey.
♪
Look, I just have to say
that it's not
all Derreck's fault.
Mikey.
Okay, I'm going.
Please tell your friends
to not to see or speak
to Derreck
till after graduation.
That goes for you too, Mike.
But we go to school together.
How...?
♪
Okay, Mr. Cabrera.
♪ So you think
you've been through it all
♪ But I can't help
but wonder now
♪ Yesterday I found
my worst regret
♪ I'll hide it away
so no one ever knows
♪ I'm dying
♪ I'm trying to leave
♪
Dad, I know you're pissed,
but it's really
not that big of a deal.
Are you kidding me?
Getting arrested
and going to jail
for vandalism
isn't a big deal to you?
It's not like I was trying
to rob the building.
I just wanted to skate the rail.
It's private property,
for Christ sakes.
First you're failing
out of school,
now you're getting arrested?
Don't you realize
you're throwing your life away?
I'm not throwing anything away!
Yes, you are and for what?
So, you can skateboard
with your little friends?
God damn it!
This is fucking ridiculous!
What's ridiculous?
That I'm doing something
I'm good at?
I'm not doing
what you want me to do.
This isn't about me!
- It's about your future!
- No, it isn't!
I'm sorry I couldn't be
a fucking baseball player
like you wanted me to be
and have the life
that you threw away!
I didn't throw anything away!
I took responsibility,
something you know
nothing about!
What do you know, look at you!
You fucking hate your job.
You hate mom,
you hate me for being born,
and most of all,
you fucking hate yourself!
Don't you fucking
talk to me that way!
I gave you my blood and sweat!
Get outta here!
Go out the door!
♪ Every now and then
I feel the end of us
♪ I love the way
you breathe inside my head
He's got to grow up someday.
I fucking hate you!
♪ Let me slip away
I'm barely holding on
♪ Every now and then
I feel the end of us
♪ I love the way
you breathe inside my head
(knocks)
The hell are you doing here?
Let's fucking go to Tampa.
Yes!
♪
♪ I've got a lot things
I've got to lose
♪
All right,
chill out for a second.
I'ma get the room.
Cool.
Oh, look, a buffalo nickel.
(laughing)
Come on, let's go.
Here, hold my hand.
Crazy bastard.
So, have you
talked to your dad yet?
Fuck no.
I just think they'd want to know
where you're at.
I really don't care, man.
He don't deserve to know.
Fuck him.
All right.
You want to play Skate?
Sure, man, I'm down,
let's do it.
Hey, Sean, you ready?
♪ I'ma put it in perspective
Rock, paper, scissors.
All right, I guess I go first.
I got this.
♪
Whoa, coming out fine.
♪ I'm bein' honest
throwin' back to the hottest
♪ I got LeBron callin' his mom
to check his closet
♪
♪ Skills, uh-uh,
you don't wanna do that
What the fuck, fucko.
You want somethin'?
Well, first of all,
whether do you paint them jeans
on every night,
or is it, like, a weekly thing?
Man, fuck you where you breathe.
Easy up, sick bitches.
I just need your, uh,
non-dairy creamers right there.
You want these creamers?
- Yeah.
- Hey, here you go.
Here, take the fuckin' creamers.
(unintelligible banter)
♪ His closet, whoa
♪ The rest can chill,
you shoulda knew that
Man, this kid's no joke, huh?
Yeah.
♪ Testin' me
♪ That must be a fool that
Yeah, Troy.
(claps)
What's up, dawg?
Can I get those creamers?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Don't shoot, don't shoot,
don't shoot!
I'm just fuckin' with you, man.
Easy up, do-rag.
I need that.
(laughing)
Puff, puff, pass.
♪
All right, so you got...
what do you got?
S-K.
S-K-A.
You got it, right?
- Aight.
- All right, right here.
Yeah.
♪ Take it back,
do, do, do, do
Aw, that was T.
One more, you're out.
Oh.
Is that patchouli?
Yeah, it is actually.
Oh, do you ever get
a mid-shaft gash
on your old John Thomas
after screwing
a 15 year old red oak?
Yeah.
(laughs)
Can I grab these creamers here?
Remember guys, save a tree.
Eat some beaver.
♪ Do, do, do, do
♪ Take it back
One more and you're out.
Yeah, I think we got enough.
No, no, no,
we're getting another one.
♪
What do you want?
Oh, dear Lord.
You did not vacation
in this dump, did you?
What did you say, son?
I said, "Hump my ass,"
but that's neither here
nor there.
Can I have those creamers?
Ow.
Get out of here, you punks.
Who jerked off in your Geritol?
Yo, Cash, that old man's
tryin' to bite your style
with that wife beater.
Well, your sister
seems to like it.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ I ain't here to make friends,
that ain't my job
♪ If everybody ain't nice,
that ain't my squad
That's game for you.
♪ This is like a grown man
ridin' a bike again
It's good.
Taste.
All right, you stay down here.
I'm goin' up top.
Take it easy.
You know what I taught you.
♪ You were steppin'
in the name of love
♪ Like left, right,
bring it back
Good game, man.
Yeah, you too.
That was sweet, D.
Thank you, sir.
Hey, I told you guys no skating
in the parking lot.
- What the...?
- Whoa!
What the hell was that?
(laughter)
♪
What the fuck
was that explosion?
Fuckin' dairy creamer!
That shit's flammable!
Oh my God.
What is that smell?
Charred dogs.
It's Cash's face!
(laughter)
I look like an asshole.
I certainly came out of one.
I think it's an improvement.
Hey, hey, hey, yo.
Here's the deal.
Reese, since you and Cash
are obviously gay,
and you're very comfortable
with his dick,
you two can take this bed.
Me and Mikey got this bed.
Well, Derreck can have my bed
since he's gotta skate tomorrow.
No, the fifth wheel
will take the floor.
You can just take my bed, man.
Chances are,
I'm going to be asleep
in a bush with a hooker anyway
if all goes to plan.
Thanks, Cash!
What the fuck
are you doing, man?
We are going drinkin'.
Dude, I can't be goin' out.
I got to wake up early to skate.
Quit bein' such a puss.
You don't even know
if you're going to be able
to skate anyway.
Dude, I don't even got an ID.
Don't worry about an ID.
I can get you an ID.
You need an ID, shit-dick?
No, it's all good,
I got it covered.
- How?
- Look. I got it on me.
Oh, I gotta see this.
Look.
Looks real, right?
Oh, shit.
See?
Oh, God, it actually does.
It's cool, huh?
Now, boys.
You know there be
fine-ass bitches
gonna be down there
and of course,
you know these Florida bitches
are slutty, tan as shit,
and ready to fuck.
(laughing)
You can't go to Tampa
without hitting up
the Ybor Strip, man.
I guess.
You guess?
We'll just go to chill, bro.
We'll be back early.
Fine, let's do it.
(cheering)
He found his dick!
♪ Records, records,
records, records
♪ Uh, uh, uh,
one, two, one, two
♪ Uh, uh, uh, uh,
♪ It's bigger than hip hop,
hip hop, hip hop, hip
Hi, boys.
What's up, girl?
All right.
♪ Hip hop, hip hop
Don't worry, man, I got you.
♪
Yo, Derreck, Derreck.
Man, that was fast.
Know what I'm doin'.
"Edward Chung."
Dude, he's 39.
They don't look
at that crap, man.
Well, he's 5'2" and Asian.
Man, stickler,
I'll be right back.
Are you kidding me?
Get out of here.
Come on, man.
Do you even know
what I look like?
He's the same height.
Dude, he's 280 pounds.
Just tell him
you got your stomach stapled
or something, ad-lib.
Fuck, whatever.
- Go.
- I'll try.
Hey, Chuck, you look great
after that stomach staplin'.
I'll see you at the bar.
♪ Dis, dis, dis
you hit it
♪ Got the digits
quick, quick decisions
♪ Boy, pop the rhythm
don't bet the physics
♪ If ain't no dougie,
then go grab the shovel
♪ And blow up my spot
but don't pop the bubble
♪ I know you, miss
♪
Yeah, I'm from Chicago,
actually.
We're all pro skaters.
See that kid over there?
Yeah, he's ranked number one
in the world.
He's recently single
after splittin' up
with his supermodel girlfriend.
So, you're friend here
says you're the best.
Are you gonna win tomorrow?
Well, you never know.
Of course
he's gonna win tomorrow.
He's ranked number one.
What about you, are you pro too?
Yeah, that's why I hang out
with these guys.
Don't listen to that dude.
He's a pro-nothing.
That's our water boy.
(laughter)
Water boy?
A filmer, filmer.
- Oh, okay.
- Film...
Excuse me, can you tell me
what time it is?
I can't see my watch.
What is that?
Oh, my God.
Ew!
That is so gross!
- You're disgusting!
- I'm gonna barf.
What the fuck I tell you
about pulling out your dick,
you idiot?
You even scared the chicks away.
I didn't even show her the tip.
My God.
Well, that's fuckin' cool
as shit.
Hey, dude!
Cut it out!
That's disgusting, man!
Who's ready to do some shots?
Purple Hooter!
Come on.
Come on, ace.
Man, what'd you do?
Buy out the whole bar?
Just take a fucking shot.
Nah, man, get that shit
out of my face.
Whoa, what, one little shot's
gonna get you so drunk
you're not going to be able
to drop the NAC?
Just take a fucking shot.
Whatever, dude.
You're not gonna
fucking make that shit anyways.
Yo, easy up, man.
It's a newcomer, man.
You got to ease the tip in.
Yo, you and I, shot, shot, shot.
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
Hook me up, hook me up!
♪
Tits.
Again.
♪
(laughter)
- Excuse me.
- Fuck you!
You fuckin' coot.
What?
You heard what I fuckin' said.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ease the fuck up, man.
You better grab your friend
before he gets his ass whipped.
♪
He didn't do nothin'!
Leave him alone!
We got some cops outside.
They wanna talk to you.
Get the fuck off!
Back up, or you're goin'
to the tank with this guy.
Motherfucker!
Get the fuck off me!
♪
Man, Troy is just scandalous.
Somebody's name on this biotch!
Whoa there, drunk ass.
Tell me you saw that shit,
how hard I punked that dude.
Yeah, real hard, man.
You fuckin' sucker punched him
and let Cash
take all the heat, you're sick.
It's not like Cash
hasn't been detained before,
and you know
he can handle himself.
It is fucked up.
He is spendin'
the night in jail.
Well, there's nothin'
we can do about it now,
and I'm starvin'.
Let's eat.
Hold on.
Give me the keys.
You're wasted.
Oh, what is this?
Thanks, Mommy.
- Thanks, Mommy.
- Shotgun!
Fuckin' shotgun.
You never have shotgun.
What the fuck, man?
Watch out.
♪
(chuckling)
Could you believe how hard
I punked that dude?
Oh my gosh,
why are you so psyched
on yourself?
"Oh man, I punked that dude
and let Cash go to jail
while I hid like a bitch.
Oh."
Yeah, you mock me
because you wish you were me.
Man, you must be fucking drunk
to believe that.
Please, you've been ridin'
my coattails since day one.
What coattails, man?
You're 24 years old on Flow.
Really?
At least I'm
making a name for myself.
How about you,
what are you doing?
'Cause all I see is a kid
that takes rides in my van
and mooches off of
my board hook up.
You ain't doin' shit.
Man, I'm over this,
I'm done, man.
Your whack-ass attitude,
being a dick to everyone.
All right, well,
if we're being honest,
that night at the rail,
I let the cops get you.
- What the fuck, Troy?
- What?
Man, fuck you!
Yeah, get your shit
and find somewhere else to stay.
Come on, guys.
Chill the fuck out, man.
What the fuck is going on?
This shit is crazy.
We're supposed
to be friends, man!
So what, man?
♪
Yo, Derreck!
- What up, Derreck?
- Oh, shit.
Did you just get here
all the way from Chicago?
Nah, I kind of lost
my place to stay.
Well, we're actually
heading to our hotel.
You can crash with us
if you want to.
You sure that wouldn't be
too much trouble?
I offered, didn't I?
Hey, that's her way of saying,
"Get in the car."
All right.
♪
Wanna step outside real quick?
Sure.
♪
Make out time!
Shut up.
♪
So, you want to tell me
why you were on a dark road
all alone,
or should I just assume
you're the brooding type?
Uh, it's a long story.
I know a lot of long stories.
Really?
Do you think it's normal
for a 19 year old girl
to be driving around
her little bro
and friends
all over the country?
I just figured
you were cool older sister.
Somethin' like that.
Hm.
So, why does it look like
it hurts for you to smile?
Well, I'm failin' out of school,
just got arrested,
and basically ran away
after my dad hit me.
Well, did he have a right
to hit you?
I don't know.
I guess.
I probably would have done
the same thing.
Sounds to me like
you didn't run away from him,
but you're trying to run away
from yourself.
What are you,
some sort of shrink?
I had some mandatory classes
in the first year of college.
So, why does a guy like you
not have a cute,
little girlfriend by his side?
Well, we just broke up.
Probably a good move,
what with how fucked up you are,
you wouldn't want
to get anyone involved
in that mess, right?
(chuckles)
Right.
And you?
No one's in your mess?
Nah.
I haven't found anyone
who wanted to listen.
♪
(knocks)
Eric!
You little asshole!
What'd you say?
You want to see some asshole?
- Oh, my gosh!
- Ugh!
♪
(phone rings)
- Dad?
- Derreck.
Hey.
Where are you?
I'm in Tampa.
There's a contest here.
Hey, dad, I'm sorry, like...
No, Derreck,
we just want you to come home.
I will.
You know, if I do good tomorrow,
I get hooked up.
Well, then, uh,
good luck then.
Thanks.
Well, um, just tell mom
I love her.
I'll be home in a couple days.
Talk to you later, dad.
- Later.
- Bye.
♪
(sighs)
♪ All aboard
♪ Check, one
♪
♪ All aboard
♪ Check... check it
freedom train progress
♪ All aboard
as we pierce the darkness
♪ Bona fide soldiers
build through mic check
♪ We on track
for our freedom
Welcome, everybody,
to this year's Tampa Am.
This is the biggest
amateur skate contest
in the world, and here is how
it's going to go down.
We have six seats
of 20 skaters each.
Everybody's going to get
two runs to the prelims.
The top 12 scores...
Hey, seriously, thanks
a lot for getting me in here.
All right, man,
no problem, my pleasure.
Let's go warm up.
Yeah, let's do it.
Aight.
(cheers)
This is the future
of the sport, right here.
Hey, hot-ass, how'd you sleep?
Lot better than you did.
How's the tank?
Oh, some big badass
tried to spoon me.
I think he thought
I was a cupcake or something,
trying to find a creamy center,
I gave him Reese's number.
- What, what you say?
- What, he's your type.
Get the fuck out of here, man.
So, where'd you sleep?
Chick from the plaza's here
with her brother.
I knew you was goin' to hit
that shit, dog.
Anyway, did Troy settle down?
He puked all over himself.
He seriously tore down.
Fuck him.
- Aight.
- Good luck.
- Yeah.
- See you in a bit.
All right, boys,
I'll see you later.
Hey, break a leg.
As a matter of fact, break both
so you can be in a wheelchair,
and we can get
to the front of the line
next time we go
to the amusement park.
This is gonna be a good one,
so get ready
at the skate park in Tampa,
amateur competition.
We still got a few minutes
of warm-up left,
so get out there, guys.
♪ Don't sweat
the technique
♪
♪ Don't sweat
the technique
♪
♪ Let's trace the hints
and check the file
♪ Let's see who bit
to detect the style
♪ I flip the script
so they can't get foul
♪ At least not now,
it'll take a while
♪ I change the pace
to complete the beat
♪ I drop the bass
till MC's get weak
♪ For every word they trace,
it's a scar they keep
♪ 'Cause when I speak,
they freak to sweat
the technique ♪
♪ I made my debut
in '86
♪ Wit' a melody
and a president's mix
♪ And now I stay on target
and refuse to miss
♪ And I still
make hits
♪ With beats, parties,
clubs in the cars and Jeeps
♪ My underground sound
vibrates the streets
♪ MC's want to beef
then I play for keeps
♪ When they sweat
the technique
♪
Wow, look out out there, guys.
- What the fuck, Troy?
- You were in my way.
So, you're just
goin' to shoulder-check me?
You don't want
to get shoulder-checked,
stay out of my way.
Riders, get your last
warm-ups in here.
The prelims are about to start.
Don't forget
the heats are posted
in the snack room.
Make sure to check
and see what heat you're in.
Great, 120 people,
I gotta go after this asshole.
♪ Fuckin' posers
♪ Yo, yo, yeah
Hey, welcome everybody
here at the skate park at Tampa.
This is the Tampa Am.
We're going to fire up
the preliminaries right now.
Let's make some noise
and get this thing fired up!
(cheers)
All right, Tampa, this is
the first scene of the contest.
Make some noise for Dylan Perry.
Here he comes in
off the big roll
and gets some good speed.
Ollie above
the centerpiece flat bar.
Nice hurricane grind
down the rail.
Lookin' good so far.
Oh, couldn't quite hang on.
That's all right, Dylan,
you've got a second run
coming up later on.
Coming up for a 50-second run,
let's make some noise
for Ricky Martin!
Here he comes
droppin' in the corner,
comin' up the step up gap
with a clean kick flip shifty.
Got a lot of hot, young talent
coming out of South America.
(cheers)
♪
Will it be enough?
I don't know, we still got
a lot of good riders to go.
♪ It's over now
♪
♪ It's too damn late
to apologize
Am I right, there it is!
First perfect run
we see right here,
number 30, with Patrick Daniel.
♪ You think that you
don't have to ever quit
All right,
were we are, number 14.
♪ You think the light
won't be ever lit
♪ It's almost over now,
almost over now
Tampa, with a big, warm welcome,
let's bring in
our next rider, Eric Jones!
(cheers)
This kid is so amazing.
He's got large tech tricks
like the big, backside flip
270 over the hit.
Pop shove frontside,
nosegrind on the flat bar.
And he pop shoved over the hit.
Fast time for Eric Jones,
another rockin' run.
We're definitely going to see
this kid in the finals.
Tampa, I know it's been
a long day, but this is it.
The sixth and final heat
of the prelims.
Skaters, clear the course.
Let's get ready
for our next rider.
Crank it up for Joey Ragali!
Tryin' to go big
on that centerpiece,
can't quite hang on.
Next up, comin' all the way
from Indiana, Bobby Smith.
Here he comes, 45 seconds left,
what you got?
Oh, throwin' it away.
Still got time for one more.
You want one more?
No, all right, he's done.
Next up, from Uprise Skate Shop,
Troy Vincent.
Here he comes, all the way
from Chicago, Illinois.
Jumpin' on the flatbar,
smooth crooked grind.
(claps)
There he is up
on the corner pipe,
keepin' his rhythm, let's see
as he comes across
the centerpiece ledge,
frontside five-o.
He's got a good run
going right now.
Let's see what he's got
to finish it off.
Frontside lipslide crossin' now.
Make some noise
for Troy Vincent.
Next rider up, let's make
some noise right now
for Derreck Cabrera.
Another skater
from Chicago, Illinois.
All right, look at this,
he's droppin'
at the corner pipe switch.
Startin' out
with some difficulty here.
Switch kickflip, whoa!
♪
All right, here he goes, he's
linin' up for the centerpiece.
What's he got, down the stairs...
Oh, blows the train flip.
That's a tough trick
right there.
You suck!
I'm the only guy that can say
someone sucks,
that and the judges.
First run,
he must have the jitters.
He must be nervous out there.
Coming across centerpiece,
lookin' at the rail,
backside lip... oh, man.
That's all right, Derreck.
Tryin' some hard tricks
out there.
Not quite enough.
Remember, skaters,
it's the best run
out of two.
- But up next...
- Sick run, bro.
What is his problem?
I don't care.
That kind of sucked.
Thanks.
Was kind of hopin'
for some encouragement.
Do I really need to tell you
that was only the first run?
So, are you
callin' me out right now?
Somebody's got to.
All right.
Hold these for me, please?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Let's see what I can do.
(cheers)
That's it for first runs.
Let's go back
to the top of the order,
second runs.
All right, skaters, this is it.
Your last chance.
You're gonna have
to really bump it up
if you want to make it
in the final.
♪
Going out for run number two,
let's hear it for Joey Capelli.
(cheers)
♪ Prevail the merciless
mercenaries of militance
♪ No resemblance to any other
assembly's heritage
♪ Despair will be
the downfall of arrogance
♪ Repairs will be necessary,
too much heavy damage
♪ Counter intelligence
♪ Spy craft flies past
the aviator
♪ Resuscitation, reincarnation,
I'm the re-animate
♪ Greater mind power
than Einstein
♪ Genius and insanity,
we walkin' that fine line
♪ Talkin' 'bout prime time
exposure, face remains poker
♪ Overload the road to stardom
like exploding supernovas
♪ Maintain composure low
visibility violent turbulence
Comin' up for round number two,
let's make some noise
for Troy Vincent.
(cheers)
Here he comes with a drop
at the big roll
tryin' to get some speed.
Nice frontside smith grind.
(cheers)
Frontside nosegrind.
Comin' in the corner pipe,
get some speed
for that euro gap.
That's a trade flip.
Stylish moves right there
from Troy.
Gettin' set-up for the big rail.
Frontside lipslide.
♪
Another frontside smith
on the corner.
What's he got to finish it off?
Frontside bottle.
Oh!
Gettin' a little pumped up
about your run, huh?
Last chance.
Don't choke.
This guy had a tough time
on his first time.
Come on, Tampa,
let's make some noise
for Derreck Cabrera.
All right, Derreck, this is it.
This is your last run.
You really got to put it
together right now.
Looks like he's comin' in that
corner pipe switch once again.
Yeah, nails it!
Solid switch tray up the ramp.
(cheers)
There he goes
headin' for the centerpiece,
linin' up for the rail.
♪
This kid's got a bangin' run
goin' so far.
Here he comes
headin' for the rail.
Looks like it's... oh.
Can't quite hang on,
that's all right, Derreck.
You still got a good run,
plenty of time left.
(cheers)
♪
You still got some time
for one more trick.
Let's see what he's got
to finish it off.
Trade flip on the stairs
and he nailed it.
Solid run right there
for Derreck Cabrera.
That's the kind of run
that'll put you
in the finals.
All right, skaters,
that's it for the prelims.
Top 12 finalists will be posted
in the snack room.
(cheers)
That was sick, Derreck.
- Thanks, dog.
- No worries.
(announcers in background)
Oh, my God.
Are you kidding me?
I have a perfect run,
you bail a trick.
Qualify first,
I don't even make the finals?
Man, you didn't
try anything hard.
Shut the fuck up,
you little rat.
Who you callin'
fuckin' little rat?
Who the fuck are you,
little girl?
- Hey, hey...
- Fuck out of my face.
This is between you and me.
You aren't in the finals
because his ending trick
was better than your entire run.
Shut the fuck up
before I paddle you.
I could give a fuck
who you ride for.
Leave him out of this!
You wouldn't even
fuckin' be here
in the first place
if it wasn't for me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, easy up, man.
Can someone get me
a fluorescent, pink nipple
for my dick so Troy here
can feed on it?
Keep his mouth busy
from bitchin'.
Dude, the little twerp is right.
You played it safe,
and now you're payin' the price.
- So, let it go!
- It's not even that.
This dude wouldn't even be
here if it wasn't for me.
If he wasn't here somebody else
would have phased you out, man.
Why you got a problem with him
in the first place?
He's my fuckin' problem.
He's not tryin'
to take your spot.
He's tryin' to make himself one.
Yo, let this arrogant cocksucker
be a lesson to you.
You didn't come here
to puss out.
Troy, you and I
are going to get some popcorn
and watch our friend
in the finals.
Derreck, man,
don't even worry about it.
You got it.
All finalists, please head...
Wow.
Your friends are like girls.
Yo, my man, let's go do this.
Good luck, boys.
I'll see you later.
(cheers)
♪
All right, Tampa.
Are you ready?
This is the moment
you've been waiting for,
the finals of the Tampa Am!
Come on, let's make some noise
for our top 12 finalists!
We're going to start the finals
right here, right now.
Tampa, are you with me on this?
All right, skaters.
This is how we do it
in the finals.
You guys all got two runs.
The best run wins.
Comin' out of Boulder Colorado,
qualifyin' 10th place,
make some noise
for T.J. Spark.
♪
Trade flip up the euro gap.
Goin' for the rail,
kickflip front.
Oh, and he hangs on to it.
(cheers)
Next up, from Miami, Florida,
Steve Otero.
(cheers)
Qualifyin' at sixth place,
Timmy Newton.
The sex change on the rail,
are you kidding me?
Forget you all.
Backside left slide!
Oh, can't quite hang on.
Next up, qualifying
fourth place,
let's hear it for Sean Malto!
Big pop on the kickflip up.
Comin' switch now
down the stairs.
Big switch flip down the stairs!
Comin' up next,
one of the top finishers
from last year, bring the noise
for Eric Jones!
Here he comes
coming down the big roll
with some good speed.
Frontside throttle
crossing down the rail.
Let's see what he's got
to finish it off.
Backflip to fakie!
That's time for Eric Jones!
This kid's been feelin' it
all day.
Comin' up next,
our number one qualifier,
let's make some noise
for Derreck Cabrera.
♪
Oh, a frontside nosegrind.
Lookin' stylin' right there.
Back the other way
with a beautiful
backside lipslide.
Amazing style out there.
Thirteen seconds.
♪
Windin' up for something big
down the rail.
Oh!
Oh, man.
Wow, rockin'
the family jewels right there.
- You okay?
- Oh, that's gotta hurt.
- Yeah.
- Oh, fuck.
You need an ice pack
or something?
What, are you gonna
ice my balls for me?
- Ah.
- All right, Tampa.
Looks like he's all right.
Let's give a hand
to Derreck Cabrera.
All right, Tampa, we're back
at the top of the order
gettin' things started right now
for second runs.
Comin' out of Boulder, Colorado,
T.J. Sparks.
Kickflip up the euro gap.
What's he got to finish it off?
Headin' for the rail.
Smooth eagle grind.
(cheers)
So, uh, how are your balls?
Pretty sore.
Yeah, man, I saw that.
Looked like it hurt.
Yeah, I think I'll be okay.
♪ Now let's get it
all in perspective
♪ For all
y'all enjoyment,
a song y'all
can step wit' ♪
♪ Y'all appointed me
to bring rap justice
♪ But I ain't
five-0,
y'all know
it's Nas, yo ♪
♪ They shootin',
ah, made you look ♪
♪ You a slave
to a page in my rhyme book
♪ Getting' big money,
playboy, your time's up
♪ Where them gangstas at,
where them dimes at
♪ This ain't rappin',
this is street hop
♪ Now get up off your ass
like your seat's hot
♪ My live niggas
lit up the reefer
That's one solid run.
Skatin' good all weekend long,
let's make some noise
for our next rider, Eric Jones!
(cheers)
♪
Droppin' in on the big roll
and huge kickflip
over the centerpiece!
Kid's had some solid rides
all day long.
He is the man to beat.
Jumpin' up on the front side,
eagle down the rail.
Lookin' stylish.
Workin' the corner pipe trannies
right there.
Comin' up now with some speed.
Gnarly backside up the gap.
Keepin' it clean, tryin' to get
a solid run right here.
Big hard flip down the stairs.
Nice, solid ride for Eric Jones.
What do you say, Tampa,
make some noise!
Last trick comin' up right now.
Come on, Tampa,
let's fire him up!
One big trick, what you got?
Comin' full speed,
kickflip backside
Throttle across and down.
Come on, let's hear it
for Eric Jones!
Without a doubt, that is the run
to beat right there.
♪
- Sick run.
- Aw, thanks, man.
So, uh, I think
you're the only one out there
who can beat me.
I don't know about that, man.
Not if it's anything
like my last run.
Comin' up next
is our number one qualifier,
final skater of the contest,
let's make some noise
for Derreck Cabrera!
(cheers)
Looks like I'm up.
At least drop the NAC
in your run.
- You think so?
- Oh yeah, man.
You'll shock everyone.
All right.
Comin' up next,
he's a first timer up here
and makin' a lot of people
take notice.
Final skater up and coming is...
This is Derreck Cabrera!
Droppin' in the corner pipe,
comin' in switch right here.
Up on the rail
for switch crooked grind.
Pretty clean.
(cheers)
And a trick
over the rim right there
with a novelty frontal flip;
never seen that before ever.
Makin' up tricks
as he goes out here,
Derreck Cabrera.
Goin' full speed,
nailin' every trick out there.
Frontside flip up the gap,
land the fake, switch push up.
Now going forward,
trade flip down the stairs.
Derreck Cabrera
getting' technical out here.
What's he got to finish it off?
Look at this, droppin'
in the corner pipe switch,
headin' for the euro gap.
Oh, switch trade up the gap!
Are you kiddin' me?
Looks like we got
the winning run going right now.
What's he got to finish it off?
♪
Oh, what...
I don't even know what that was.
Oh, tough break
for Derreck Cabrera.
That's gonna be time,
let's hear it for him.
- The NAC.
- Okay, Tampa.
That's gonna finish it
off out here
for the finals.
What an amazing weekend we had.
Stick around because
we've got tons of pr...
Oh, wait, he wants one more!
Crowd, you want to see him
do one more?
Come on, Tampa,
let's make some noise!
He wants to get one more shot.
Come on, everybody,
let's gather around.
Let's get him fired up.
Come on, crowd,
gather around out here.
Let's cheer him on!
That's all right, guys,
come on in!
Get up close, front and center.
Let's see what he's got.
It's after time,
so this won't count
for the contest.
I've just been informed
by the judges,
the trick he's going for
is a 360 flip crooked grind.
You have a chance to be a part
of skateboard history right now.
I've never even heard
of anybody trying
a trade flip crook before.
♪ I got it
(skateboard whooshing)
(cheers)
Whoa!
Unbelievable!
That was so close!
(applause)
Derreck Cabrera's
gonna go for one more.
Come on, crowd,
who wants to see him make it?
One more try, one more try!
Come on, crowd, let's hear it!
You've got it!
One more try!
Unreal, unbelievable,
this is one
of the hardest tricks
in the history of Tampa Am.
This is what skateboard
is all about.
It's about doing it yourself.
It's about making the one trick
that you've been dreamin' about.
He's concentratin'.
Heavy focus right now.
Got to imagine
he's gonna roll away
from this one.
♪
He's now gettin'
his speed set up.
Lenses are out there.
♪
Oh, Derreck Cabrera
sticking the trade flip crooks!
- (cheers)
- Unbelievable!
It's insane!
You just watched
skateboard history
go down right here
at the skate park in Tampa!
Derreck Cabrera throws it down
after time at the Tampa Am!
I can't believe it!
Unreal, 360-flip crooked grind!
Hey, check out this angle I got!
Aight.
♪
It's really amazing, man.
Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, yeah, we're buddies again!
I love you two!
(screams)
Cash, cash, cash!
And in fifth place,
he might not have won
the contest,
but he definitely had
the craziest trick,
give it up for Derreck Cabrera!
(cheers)
♪
Congratulations, Derreck.
That was crazy, right on.
Give it up one more time!
Fifth place right there.
Derreck Cabrera!
(cheers)
- Good job.
- Good job, man.
(applause)
Derreck Cabrera!
What's up, Tony?
Guess you're
the man of the hour, huh?
Aw, thanks, man.
After seein' that, man,
don't even worry
about sendin' in that video.
You're on the team
if you're down.
No way, hell yeah, I'm down!
Congratulations, you deserve it,
welcome to the team.
And the winner,
riding for Road Skateboards,
make some noise for Eric Jones!
(cheers)
♪
Good job out there.
Let's hear it for the winners
of Tampa Am!
And one more time,
make some noise
for the winners!
Eric Jones!
(cheers)
♪
Hey, man, that was
absolutely amazing today.
- Congratulations.
- Aw, thanks a lot.
Man, if you had dropped
the NAC in your run,
it would have been you
taking this thing home.
- Come on.
- Come on, man.
Maybe next year.
Yeah, for sure, dude.
All right, well, hey,
this weekend was amazing.
You killed it,
and I'll see you around.
Hey, thank you
for gettin' me in today, Eric.
- No worries.
- I appreciate that, man.
- We gotta go.
- All right.
So...
♪
I guess I lied.
What are you talkin' about?
♪
I fell for the song and dance.
Well, I guess
that makes me a liar too.
Fell for the cool girl
with the Chuck Taylors.
♪
(car honks)
What the hell is goin' on?
Man, quit tryin'
to get your carrot wet
and get the fuck in here.
Let's boogie.
So sorry about that.
It's cool.
It looks like you got to go.
Well, did I at least
earn the digits?
♪
It's already in the phone.
Well, look at you all slick.
You know, it's just my style.
♪ Break our pact
♪ I'm searching
for the way back
♪
♪ But I'm looking
through a peep hole
Eric!
What are you doing?
Leave me alone!
Why are you a dork?
(cheers)
♪
Well, you owe me
a new pair of pants
because I busted out of these
when I got that goddamn boner
you gave me.
Oh, God.
Street dreams.
♪
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
If we were in fantasy land,
you guys would be naked,
and this would
be a botanical garden...
(laughs)
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪
And for what?
So you can skateboard
with your little friends?
God damn it!
Fuckin' ridiculous!
This shit ain't
gonna fuckin' open!
(laughs)
Okay, back to one.
♪
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
(laughs)
Yeah, that's good.
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪
Fuck this shit!
I cannot believe
I kept fucking that up.
Well then,
let's do another one.
I cannot believe...
That's the...
I didn't do it right.
They're just gonna
tape the mess.
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
Dude, this is a bus pass
for a 92-year-old grandma.
They're not gonna look!
My God, stickler.
How is she even in there?
(laughs)
Cut!
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪
- Get a little...
- Why not?
You know, wear my speedo.
I'll shave mine if I have to,
and I'll wax my asscrack.
That's great, I'm glad.
I'll be right back.
♪
I feel like I'm in the recordin'
studio right now.
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin'
over fences
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪ Hoppin' over,
hop hoppin'
hoppin'
over fences ♪
♪
♪ I'm feelin'
separated ♪
♪
♪ Push, pull, prattle,
indifferences ♪
♪ The bottom feelin'
♪
♪ Now wake up
♪ Destructin'
♪
♪ Toss turn,
toss turn,
losin' fast
while I'm sleepin' ♪
♪
♪ Lie, lie, lie
with me ♪
♪
♪ Pretend,
pretend, pretend
you love me ♪
♪
♪ I needed
separation ♪
♪
♪ I say if nothing,
see it through ♪
♪
♪ Ha, ha, ha, ha
(unintelligible lyrics)
♪ Lie,
lie, lie
with me ♪
♪
♪ Pretend,
pretend, pretend
you love me ♪
♪
♪ Pretend,
pretend, pretend
you love me ♪
♪
♪ Love, love,
love, love ♪
♪ Je'taime,
je'taime,
je'taime ♪
♪ Love me
♪
♪ I'm feelin'
separated ♪
♪
♪ I needed
separation ♪
♪
♪ Ha, ha, ha, ha
(unintelligible lyrics)
♪ Pretend,
pretend,
pretend ♪
♪ Je'taime,
je'taime,
je'taime ♪
♪