[ MID-TEMPO INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYS ]
[ VEHICLE APPROACHING ]
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO ]
[ ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES ]
>> HEY, SHIT, ANDY, YOU SEE THAT
STOP SIGN UP AHEAD, THOUGH?
>> COME ON. SLOW THIS CAR DOWN.
>> DUDE, NO BRAKE!
>> WHAT?!
>> YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME!
>> NO BRAKE!
>> SHUT UP!
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
>> FUCK, NO!
>> HANG ON, GUYS!
>> AAH!
>> YOU GOT TO BELIEVE IN
YOURSELF.
YOU GOT TO BELIEVE IN YOUR
TEAMMATES AT ALL TIMES.
YOU NEVER GIVE UP...
EVER.
YOU BELIEVE.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> GIBSONBURG, OHIO -- HOME TO
ABOUT 2,000 GOOD, DOWN-TO-EARTH,
HARDWORKING PEOPLE.
THE RECESSION HIT THESE PARTS
PRETTY HARD.
YOU'D NEVER KNOW IT, SINCE WE
KEEP OUR HEADS HIGH, BUT WE WERE
HURTING BAD.
THE TOWN DIDN'T HAVE TOO MUCH TO
HOPE FOR.
DIDN'T REALLY HAVE ANYTHING TO
BELIEVE IN.
BUT THESE FOUR GUYS WERE ABOUT
TO CHANGE EVERYTHING.
[ ALARM BEEPING ]
[ BEEPING STOPS ]
ANDY GRUNER...
I HAVE A FEELING THAT IF IT
WASN'T FOR HIM, THERE WOULDN'T
BE MUCH STORY TO TELL YOU RIGHT
NOW.
NATURAL-BORN LEADER AND CAPTAIN
OF THE BASEBALL TEAM.
HIS FAMILY RAN AND OWNED THE
FAMOUS IDEAL BAKERY IN DOWNTOWN
GIBSONBURG.
>> I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THIS BAKERY'S BEEN IN OUR FAMILY
FOR OVER 80 YEARS, AND WE'RE
GONNA LOSE IT NOW.
>> WELL, WE DID EVERYTHING WE
COULD TO HOLD THE CREDITORS OFF.
BUT WE ARE STILL $89,000 SHORT.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO SHUT
DOWN AT THE END OF MAY SO THEY
CAN PUT EVERYTHING UP IN A
SHERIFF'S SALE.
>> HEY.
LOOKS GOOD.
>> THANKS.
YOU'RE ALL SET FOR MORNING RUSH.
I GOT TO GET GOING TO SCHOOL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I LOVE YOU, SON.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> HEY, ANDY, THE PRINCIPAL
REALLY WANTS YOU TO TRY AND HELP
US STOP SENIOR SKIP DAY THIS
YEAR.
HE THINKS THE STUDENTS WILL
LISTEN TO YOU.
>> I DON'T THINK THEY'RE GONNA
LISTEN TO ME AS MUCH AS HE
THINKS.
>> HEY, ANDY.
HEY, WHEN YOU HAVE A MINUTE, WE
NEED TO TALK ABOUT THE PLANS WE
HAVE WITH THE BASEBALL COACH.
>> I'M 15 MINUTES LATE FOR A
MEETING.
CAN WE TALK AFTER THAT?
>> SURE.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> ALL RIGHT, FELLAS.
I'M YOUR HEAD COACH, KYLE RASE.
I LIKE COACHING BASEBALL.
>> LOOKS LIKE MORE OF A PLAYER
THAN A COACH.
>> TELL ME ABOUT IT.
>> YOU GUYS ARE GONNA LIKE
PLAYING FOR ME.
I GOT TWO RULES.
RULE NUMBER ONE -- YOU NEVER
GIVE UP...EVER.
RULE NUMBER TWO -- YOU GOT TO
BELIEVE.
YOU GOT TO BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
YOU GOT TO BELIEVE IN YOUR
TEAMMATES AT ALL TIMES.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ALL I GOT TO SAY.
LET'S GO.
HUSTLE UP.
LET'S GO TAKE SOME B.P.
COME ON!
>> GONE!
>> CATCH THAT.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW THE TEAM
BETTER THAN I DO.
HOW DO YOU THINK WE'LL DO THIS
SEASON?
>> YOU A RELIGIOUS MAN, COACH?
>> A LITTLE BIT. WHY?
>> UGH!
>> Both: OOH!
>> WELL...
I'D PRAY.
>> NOW, THEY WERE ALL PRETTY
GOOD GUYS, BUT, LIKE ANYONE
ELSE, THEY LOVED A GOOD PARTY.
THEY WERE ALWAYS THE LIFE OF IT.
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> HEY, FELLAS, FELLAS, LET'S
ANTE IN A DOLLAR HERE.
>> THIS GUY COMES INTO THE
BAKERY, AND HE'S GOT AN
UNBELIEVABLE "FUPA."
>> FREAKIN' FOOP.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> IT'S LIKE HE'S GONNA HAVE A
BABY ANY MINUTE.
YOU KNOW THE TYPE YOU CAN REST A
CUP OF COFFEE ON?
>> YEAH, I KNOW THE TYPE, MY
MAN.
>> NICE.
>> FIVE BUCKS.
LAST BET.
>> I'M OUT, TOP GUN.
>> YOU'RE CRAZY, BROTHER.
I'M OUT.
>> DUDE, YOU MUST HAVE A SICK
HAND.
I'M GONE.
>> WHAT DO YOU GOT,
CHRIS MONEYMAKER?
>> CHECK IT OUT.
ROYAL FLUSH.
COME TO PAPA.
>> THAT'S A $9 POT, ANDY.
YOU ALWAYS DO SEEM TO GET THE
LUCKY BREAKS.
>> YOU'RE ON A ROLL, BIG GUY.
MIGHT BE TAKE TO ASK KATHY OUT.
>> DO IT, MAN.
>> SHE'S GOT A BOYFRIEND.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
STEVE? HE IS SUCH A DOUCHEBAG.
THAT WILL NEVER LAST.
>> HEY?
>> SHUT UP.
>> YOU GOT ME.
>> THAT'S KATHY COLANER.
ANDY AND KATHY HAD BEEN CLOSE
FRIENDS SINCE THIRD GRADE.
IT WAS NO SECRET THAT ANDY HAD A
LOT OF FEELINGS FOR KATHY.
>> I'M A LITTLE TIRED.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
>> [ Echoing ] ALL RIGHT,
FELLAS.
I GOT TWO RULES.
RULE NUMBER ONE -- YOU NEVER
GIVE UP...EVER.
RULE NUMBER TWO -- YOU GOT TO
BELIEVE.
YOU GOT TO BELIEVE IN YOURSELF
AND YOUR TEAMMATES AT ALL TIMES.
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
>> WHAT'S UP, DEBBIE DOWNER?
YOU NEED SOME COFFEE FOR YOUR
STAKEOUT MISSION?
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> WHAT?
>> WHY ARE YOU STILL HERE?
>> [ SIGHS ]
JUST A LOT ON MY MIND RIGHT NOW.
>> DUDE, THEN, JUST TELL ME,
MAN.
JUST TELL ME. WHAT'S UP?
>> I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
YOU REMEMBER MY DAD'S OLD
CHEVELLE?
>> [ Laughing ] YEAH.
>> HE USED TO JUST PUT US IN THE
BACKSEAT.
WE'D GO OUT AND JUST FLY DOWN
ALL THOSE BACK ROADS.
>> HEY, DIDN'T HE SELL THAT TO
THAT MECHANIC DUDE ON
STATE STREET OR SOMETHING LIKE
THAT?
>> YEAH. HENRY TILLMAN.
HE DRIVES IT AROUND TOWN ALL THE
TIME.
I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA GET IT
SOMEDAY.
BUT, UH...
MY DAD ENDED UP SELLING IT
'CAUSE HE RAN INTO SOME MONEY
TROUBLES.
>> WHAT MONEY PROBLEMS?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> I WASN'T GONNA SAY ANYTHING,
BUT...
WELL...
WE'RE LOSING THE BAKERY.
>> WHAT?!
>> I GUESS MY PARENTS HAVE BEEN
FIGHTING OFF THE CREDITORS, BUT
EVEN NOW, AFTER SELLING
EVERYTHING, WE STILL END UP,
LIKE, $90,000 I THINK WE OWE.
>> Wow!
>> YEAH.
>> OH, MAN, I HAD NO IDEA.
>> NO ONE DOES.
SO...
LET'S JUST KEEP IT THAT WAY,
OKAY?
>> OF COURSE, DUDE.
I MEAN, I'M NOT THE BEST AT
GIVING ADVICE, BUT, YOU KNOW,
EVERYTHING ALWAYS WORKS OUT.
SO...
JUST DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
BUT HEY, I'LL SEE YOU AT THE
GAME TOMORROW, MAN.
YOU'LL CHEER UP ONCE YOU SEE
THIS OLD STUD GIVE A PITCHING
CLINIC TOMORROW.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> ALL RIGHT. THANKS, MAN.
I APPRECIATE IT.
>> LATER.
>> [ WHISTLES ]
ALL RIGHT, FELLAS, LISTEN UP.
WE'RE 3-0 AFTER TODAY'S WIN.
FRANK, LET'S STOP BY THE
McDONALD'S UP THE ROAD TO
CELEBRATE.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
>> AND THAT RIGHT THERE WAS
PRETTY MUCH THE HIGHLIGHT OF THE
SEASON.
THINGS WENT FROM BAD...
TO WORSE...
WAY WORSE.
IT WAS A HOUSE OF CARDS.
ONCE THE FIRST ONE WENT, THE
REST FOLLOWED.
>> GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
IT'S FIRST BASE.
>> IT WAS CONTAGIOUS.
ALL THE SUDDEN, IT WAS LIKE THE
WHOLE TEAM WAS ALLERGIC TO JUST
CATCHING A BASEBALL...
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
PUT ONE IN MY STRIKE ZONE.
>> ...AND HITTING ONE.
>> COACH RASE?
WE'VE LOST 12 GAMES IN A ROW.
DO YOU STILL THINK WE SHOULD BE
PLAYING THE SAME NINE PEOPLE?
[ SIGHS ]
>> NOT TO MENTION WE HAD TO DEAL
WITH THE BEST PITCHER IN THE
STATE.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
TYLER PINKUS.
LOOKED LIKE HE SHOULD HAVE BEEN
IN THE MAJORS...
AND PITCHED LIKE IT, TOO.
NOW, SOME PEOPLE HAVE NIGHTMARES
ABOUT, WELL, I DON'T KNOW, FEARS
OR DEATH OR PAIN, WHAT HAVE YOU.
PEOPLE AROUND HERE HAVE
NIGHTMARES ABOUT THIS WOMAN --
IF YOU CAN CALL HER THAT --
PINKUS' MOTHER.
>> HEY, HITTER, WHY DON'T YOU
SIT DOWN NOW, HUH?!
YOU'RE TERRIBLE!
MY TYLER COULD STRIKE YOU OUT
PITCHING LEFT-HANDED!
ONLY 12 STRIKEOUTS AGAINST THAT
LOUSY TEAM?!
COME ON, TY!
YOU CAN DO BETTER THAN THAT.
WE GOT TO GO ALL THE WAY TO THE
TOP.
COME ON, BABY.
YOU AND ME.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> OKAY?
>> WE WERE JUST WAITING FOR
SOMEONE TO POUR WATER ON HER SO
WE COULD ALL WATCH HER MELT.
>> ANDY!
>> COME ON!
>> MAN, I FEEL BAD FOR THESE
GUYS.
THEY HAVEN'T SEEN AN INNING ALL
SEASON.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SANCHEZ, MAN.
TWO GAMES LEFT, AND HE HASN'T
PLAYED ALL YEAR.
>> YEAH.
STILL WORKS PRETTY HARD, THOUGH.
>> I ALWAYS THOUGHT THE WORST
THING I PUT MYSELF THROUGH WAS
WATCHING THOM BRINKER'S DAD TAKE
ONE OF HIS COWS TO SLAUGHTER.
NOW, IF I HAD TO CHOOSE BETWEEN
THAT AND WATCHING SOME OF THOSE
GAMES AGAIN...
WELL...
I THINK YOU KNOW WHERE I'M GOING
WITH THAT ONE.
>> ANDY...I NEED TO TALK WITH
YOU.
ANDY?
I'M AFRAID I HAVE BAD NEWS.
THE BAKERY'S BEEN HAVING SOME
FINANCIAL TROUBLE, AND YOUR
FATHER AND I HAVE BEEN WORKING
REALLY HARD TO RESOLVE IT.
BUT...
>> WHAT?
>> HONEY, AT THE END OF MAY,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO CLOSE DOWN.
THE CREDITORS WILL TAKE IT FROM
THERE, AND YOUR DAD'S LOOKING
FOR A NEW JOB.
AND WE'RE GONNA LIVE WITH YOUR
AUNT FOR A LITTLE WHILE UP IN
PEMBERVILLE.
>> ISN'T THERE ANYTHING I CAN
DO?
>> OH, I WISH THERE WAS, HONEY.
>> OKAY, MOM.
HEY, DON'T WORRY.
WE NEVER GIVE UP, RIGHT?
[ KNOCKS ON GLASS ]
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP?
>> NOT MUCH.
DO YOU WANT AN ECLAIR?
>> I SURE DO.
THESE ARE THE BEST ECLAIRS EVER.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
>> NO, NOTHING AT ALL.
>> DO YOU MIND IF I VENT A
LITTLE TO YOU?
>> SURE.
FIRE AWAY.
>> [ SIGHS ]
ANDY, I HATE HIGH SCHOOL.
I'M SO TIRED OF EVERYONE THAT
KEEPS TELLING ME THESE ARE THE
BEST TIMES OF MY LIFE.
THESE TIMES SUCK.
I JUST CAN'T WAIT UNTIL SCHOOL'S
OVER, AND I'M OUT OF HERE.
I'M SO TIRED OF ALL THE WORK
FROM THE TEACHERS.
THEY'RE SO UNFAIR.
AND I HATE NOT KNOWING ABOUT
GETTING INTO COLLEGE.
THAT IS ABOUT KILLING ME.
AND I JUST HATE NOT HAVING ANY
GOOD FRIENDS.
>> HEY.
I'LL ALWAYS BE HERE.
>> I KNOW.
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN SO SWEET.
HEY, I'M SORRY FOR JUST TALKING
ABOUT ME.
HOW'S EVERYTHING WITH YOU?
>> UH...I'M ALL GOOD.
>> Good.
>> WE FRICKIN' JUST LOST 17-0.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
NO MORE PRACTICE BETWEEN NOW AND
OUR FIRST TOURNAMENT GAME.
WE'RE ALL JUST A LITTLE SPENT.
BUS LEAVES AT 3:00 P.M. ON
FRIDAY FOR OUR FIRST SECTIONAL
GAME, AGAINST BETTSVILLE.
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
DON'T BE LATE.
>> THANK YOU FOR GETTING ALL THE
BREAD DELIVERIES TAKEN CARE OF,
HONEY.
>> NO PROBLEM, MOM.
>> DO YOU MIND LOCKING UP?
>> NOT AT ALL.
>> OH, DON'T WORRY, ANDY.
THINGS ALWAYS HAVE A WAY OF
WORKING THEMSELVES OUT.
OH, AND BEFORE YOU LEAVE, WOULD
YOU MIND GETTING STARTED ON THE
SHERIFF'S SALE?
YOUR DAD WANTS YOU TO BRING UP
ALL OF THOSE OLD BOXES FULL OF
STUFF FROM THE CRAWL SPACE.
DO YOU MIND?
>> I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
>> THANKS.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
[ SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ LIGHTNING CRASHES ]
[ BATS SCREECHING ]
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
>> GO. GO.
GO, GO, GO, GO!
>> SAFE!
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
>> Hey!
McDonald's!
>> Hell, yes!
>> WHAT'S UP WITH YOU, MAN?
>> NOTHING, REALLY.
>> DUDE, JUST THINK -- SEVEN
MORE WINS, STATE CHAMPS.
>> [ SCOFFS ]
YEAH.
>> DON'T BE LIKE THAT.
YOU SURE NOTHING ELSE IS UP?
>> YEAH. I'M GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> NICE PITCHING TODAY --
12 STRIKEOUTS?
>> WHOA, WHOA.
I THINK YOU MEAN 13 STRIKEOUTS.
>> WHATEVER.
YOU STILL LOOKED GOOD.
>> THANKS, MAN.
I'M SURPRISED TO SAY THE WHOLE
TEAM LOOKED GOOD.
I DON'T EVEN THINK WE HAD ANY
ERRORS, KNOCK ON WOOD.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
YEAH.
HEY, YOU STILL GOING BY
MILLESON'S TONIGHT?
>> OF COURSE, DUDE.
>> I'M VERY HAPPY THAT THE
PRESIDENT OF YOUR LOCAL BANK
DIRECTED YOU OUR WAY.
WE EXAMINED THE COINS.
IF I WERE YOU, I WOULD PUT THEM
IN A VERY SAFE PLACE.
>> REALLY?
>> MOST OF THE COINS ARE RARE
AND WOULD EASILY GET YOU
$120,000, IF YOU WANTED TO SELL.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> HOWEVER, ONE OF THE COINS IS
A 1913 LIBERTY HEAD NICKEL.
THERE WERE ONLY FIVE OF THEM
MINTED SECRETLY IN THE
PHILADELPHIA MINT.
AN ECCENTRIC MAN, NAMED
SAMUEL BROWN, BOUGHT ALL FIVE OF
THEM IN 1913 FOR $50,000.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO THE COINS?
>> RUMOR HAS IT THAT TWENTY
YEARS LATER, IN 1933,
SAMUEL BROWN FOUND OUT THAT HE
WAS DYING.
HE TRAVELED AROUND THE COUNTRY,
HANDING THEM OUT LIKE REGULAR
NICKELS.
HE GAVE THEM TO PEOPLE THAT
TOUCHED HIS SOUL OR FOR SOME
REASON HE DEEMED SPECIAL.
THE ONLY THING HE'D SAY IS,
"I'D HANG ONTO THAT ONE IF I
WERE YOU."
>> HMM.
>> WELL, OVER THE YEARS, FOUR OF
THE FIVE HAVE BEEN RECOVERED.
LAST YEAR, THE FOURTH COIN SOLD
AT SOTHEBY'S AUCTION FOR
$12 MILLION.
EVERYONE ASSUMED THAT THE FIFTH
COIN WAS LOST FOREVER.
YOU HAVE THE FIFTH COIN.
WE ESTIMATE ITS VALUE TO BE
BETWEEN $16 AND $20 MILLION.
>> [ STAMMERS ]
>> CAN YOU TELL ME HOW LONG IT
WOULD TAKE YOU TO BROKER THESE
COINS, EXCEPT FOR THE 1913
LIBERTY HEAD NICKEL?
>> THAT'S AN EASY ONE.
OUR FIRM WILL PURCHASE THE
COINS, AND WE'LL GET YOU A CHECK
IN THREE TO FIVE DAYS.
>> OKAY!
WE'LL HOLD ONTO THE 1913
LIBERTY HEAD NICKEL, AND WE'LL
PUT THAT IN A SAFE PLACE UNTIL
WE DECIDE WHAT WE WANT TO DO
WITH IT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
I'M VERY HAPPY FOR YOU!
>> THANK YOU.
>> IT'S JUST LIKE COACH SAID.
NEVER GIVE UP...
EVER.
HE ALSO SAID WE SHOULD BELIEVE.
>> THAT'S WHAT HE SAID, HUH?
>> DAD...WHAT'S WRONG?
THIS IS GREAT NEWS FOR US.
>> ANDY, LET ME TELL YOU A STORY
THAT MY DAD TOLD ME JUST BEFORE
HE DIED.
LET'S HEAD OUTSIDE.
I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT.
A LONG TIME AGO, A MAN WALKED
INTO THE BAKERY.
THIS WAS WHEN YOUR
GREAT-GRANDFATHER AND HIS TWO
BROTHERS OWNED THE BAKERY.
WELL, ALL YOUR GREAT-GRANDFATHER
AND HIS BROTHERS DID WAS SPEND A
LITTLE TIME WITH THE MAN.
THEY LISTENED TO HIM.
AND THIS MAN GAVE THE THREE OF
THEM AN OLD BOX OF COINS.
HE PULLED OUT ONE COIN AND MADE
A POINT TO SAY, "I'D HANG ONTO
THAT ONE IF I WERE YOU."
BACK THEN, THAT ONE COIN WAS
WORTH A LOT OF MONEY.
I THINK THIS WAS THE YEAR 1933,
A FEW YEARS AFTER THE STOCK
MARKET CRASHED.
WELL, THESE THREE BROTHERS, WHO
WERE THE BEST OF FRIENDS, AS
WELL?
WELL, THEY WERE TORN APART ONCE
THEY GOT THE COIN.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN THEIR
LIVES, ALL THREE BROTHERS WERE
FIGHTING WITH EACH OTHER.
THE STRESS CAUSED ONE OF
GRANDPA'S BROTHERS TO HAVE A
HEART ATTACK.
THE OTHER BROTHER WAS KILLED IN
AN ACCIDENT.
ONCE MONEY ENTERED THE PICTURE,
EVERYTHING COLLAPSED LIKE A
CHEAP HOUSE OF CARDS.
>> RON, YOU NEVER TOLD ME ALL
THIS.
>> NEVER REALLY SAW THE POINT.
IN FACT, TO BE HONEST, I NEVER
REALLY BELIEVED IT.
DAD'S DEMENTIA WAS PRETTY BAD AT
THE TIME.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
DO, DAD?
YOU DON'T ACTUALLY THINK THAT...
>> THINK WHAT, ANDY?
>> THAT THE COINS, YOU KNOW, ARE
KIND OF CURSED?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I THINK
ABOUT THAT STUFF, SON.
BUT HERE'S WHAT I WANT YOU TO
DO.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE THAT BOX, AND
I WANT YOU TO PUT IT RIGHT BACK
WHERE YOU GOT IT.
NOBODY GOES INTO THE BASEMENT OF
THE BAKERY, ANYWAY.
SO, IT'LL BE SAFER THERE THAN
ANY SAFE-DEPOSIT BOX OR BANK.
>> OKAY.
>> AND ANOTHER THING...
LET'S -- LET'S JUST KEEP THIS
REAL QUIET.
>> WELL, LOOKS LIKE OUR SEASON
CONTINUES.
>> I KNOW.
I THOUGHT THE TORTURE WAS OVER
AFTER GOING 6-17.
>> BRUTAL YEAR.
>> I DON'T EVEN UNDERSTAND HOW
WE'RE GETTING PAST ST. JOE.
WE HAVEN'T EVEN BEATEN THEM
SINCE THIRD GRADE.
>> I KNOW.
FREAKIN' PINKUS.
SOMEONE SAID HE'S THROWING IN
THE MID-90s.
>> I HEARD HE GOT A FULL RIDE TO
EASTERN MICHIGAN.
AS MUCH AS I HATE HIM, HE IS
GOOD.
>> BIG DEAL.
WE'LL STILL ROCK HIM IF WE PLAY
HIM.
>> SERIOUSLY.
>> WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
>> HEY, KATHY.
NO ENTOURAGE TONIGHT?
>> NO, JUST ME.
ANDY?
THANKS FOR THE OTHER DAY.
>> NO BIG DEAL.
HEY, IT'S A LITTLE CROWDED IN
HERE.
WANT TO GRAB SOME FRESH AIR?
>> SURE.
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
HEY, IT'S STEVE.
I'M GONNA TAKE THIS CALL AND
THEN WE CAN TALK.
[ URINATING ]
>> WHAT'S UP, BABE?
>> NOT MUCH.
JUST HANGING OUT WITH EVERYONE
AT WES'.
>> WES'? THAT'S INTERESTING.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> Ah, hey.
HEY, TOMORROW'S SATURDAY.
WHY -- WHY DON'T YOU JUST DRIVE
DOWN TO COLUMBUS, COME SEE ME,
HUH?
>> EXAMS ARE COMING UP.
THAT MIGHT BE PRETTY TOUGH.
>> [ Laughs ]
LISTEN.
JUST DO ME THIS FAVOR.
Wes' parents -- they got a
liquor cabinet fully stocked,
all right?
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW THIS?
>> LET'S JUST SAY I PAID IT A
VISIT OR TWO IN HIGH SCHOOL.
>> STEVE?
>> Listen.
Just get on out there.
NOBODY WILL EVEN NOTICE.
GRAB ME A BOTTLE OF JACK.
OH, GRAB ME A BOTTLE OF ABSOLUT,
TOO.
BRING IT WHEN YOU COME SEE ME.
Nobody will even miss it.
Trust me.
NO WAY, STEVE.
I'm not gonna steal for you.
PLUS, I HAVE TO STUDY TOMORROW.
>> THANKS A LOT.
You know, I'm really getting
sick and tired of this
high school bullshit.
>> STEVE...
why are you talking to me like
this?
[ SNIFFS ]
HEY, I-I GOT TO RUN.
THANKS FOR NOTHING.
>> STEVE?
STEVE?
[ SIGHS ]
>> LOOKS LIKE YOU COULD USE A
DRINK.
YEAH!
>> [ GAGS, SPITS ]
>> WHOO!
>> CREEP!
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
>> I'M SUCH A LOSER.
I DON'T REALLY LIKE THE FRIENDS
I'VE BEEN HANGING AROUND.
STEVE HAS BEEN ACTING LIKE
[SIGHS] A REAL JERK LATELY.
AND THEN, THIS MORNING, I BACKED
INTO MY DAD'S CAR.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
I CAN RELATE TO THAT.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE THE SENIOR
YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL AT ALL.
AND GUESS WHAT?
>> WHAT?
>> I JUST HEARD FROM
NORTHWESTERN...
AND I DIDN'T GET IN.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> I BETTER GET GOING.
>> HEY...
GOOD LUCK STUDYING TOMORROW.
>> ANDY?
THANKS FOR BEING SUCH A GOOD
FRIEND.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
>> K-KATHY, WHAT'S -- WHAT'S UP?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN BED SO
LATE?
HEY, I FELT BAD ABOUT OUR
CONVERSATION LAST NIGHT AND
WANTED TO BRING YOU A PEACE
OFFERING.
>> YOU BROUGHT THE LIQUOR?
>> WELL, NO.
>> [ BELCHES ]
>> ME AND MY MOM BAKED YOU SOME
OF OUR WORLD-FAMOUS
CHOCOLATE-CHIP COOKIES.
AND I BROUGHT YOU YOUR FAVORITE
DRINK -- A BIG, GIANT SLURPEE.
I JUST GOT IT.
>> BUT, YEAH, PUT THEM ON THE
DESK.
[ CELLPHONE RINGING ]
HEY.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
YEAH.
>> ENJOY YOUR COOKIES.
>> HERE YOU GO, JAMIE.
>> ALL RIGHT. THANK YOU!
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
HAVE A GREAT NIGHT.
>> BYE!
>> THANK YOU.
>> HEY, ANDY.
>> HEY, THERE.
>> WHATCHA DOING?
>> JUST CLOSING UP.
>> OH?
>> I GOT A TEXT FROM WES.
SAYS YOU AND STEVE BROKE UP.
>> WES IS SUCH A GOSSIP.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> BUT YEAH.
HE'S RIGHT ON THAT ONE.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> KIND OF BUMMED, ACTUALLY.
NOT AT ALL ABOUT STEVE.
I CAME TO LEARN HE WAS JUST A
BIG JERK.
JUST A LOT OF THINGS.
HEY, HOW ABOUT HANGING OUT WITH
AN OLD FRIEND TONIGHT?
>> THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I'LL JUST CALL ALEX AND SEE WHAT
HE'S DOING.
>> THAT'S VERY FUNNY.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
ACTUALLY, I HAVE TO WORK LATE
TONIGHT.
COULD WE HANG OUT TOMORROW?
I GET OFF WORK EARLY AND COULD
BE AT YOUR PLACE BY 7:00.
>> THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
SEE YOU THEN.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
>> SURE.
>> IF YOU HAVE A SITUATION, AND
YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW WHAT TO
DO, WHAT'S THE BEST WAY TO
DECIDE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I WOULD SAY JUST FOLLOW YOUR
HEART, AND IT'LL BE HARD TO GO
WRONG.
I UNDERSTAND...
MORE THAN YOU CAN IMAGINE.
HERE WE ARE, SPORTS FANS.
ANDY GRUNER, CAPTAIN OF THE
GIBSONBURG BASEBALL TEAM, IS
SUPPOSEDLY UP FOR ANY AND ALL
CHALLENGES.
SO, WHAT'S THIS?
A LITTLE COUNTRY GIRL CHALLENGES
ANDY TO A RACE TO THE DOCK.
WILL HE ACCEPT?
CAN HE WIN?
CAN HE CATCH THE SPEEDY KATHY?
>> VERY FUNNY.
>> AND THEY'RE OFF.
NO WONDER THEY WENT 6-17.
GRUNER RUNS LIKE A TURTLE.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> AAH!
THIS FARM HAS A LOT OF BEAUTIFUL
VIEWS, DOESN'T IT?
>> THEY'RE AMAZING.
>> I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THAT
KISS FOR A LONG TIME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
EVERYBODY, BRING IT IN.
FORGET WHAT HAPPENED IN THE
PAST, BOYS.
THIS DAY?
THIS DAY'S A NEW DAY.
IT'S OURDAY!
AND YOU BETTER BELIEVE.
WE'RE NOT JUST COMING FOR THEM.
NO. HELL, NO!
WE'RE COMING FOR EVERYBODY!
EVERYBODY!
ALL RIGHT, BEARS.
LET'S BRING IT IN.
ONE...
>> NEVER...
>> TWO...
>> GIVE...
>> THREE!
>> UP!
>> WHO ARE WE?!
>> GIBSONBURG!
>> [ SCREAMS ]
>> LET'S GO!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
>> AND, JUST LIKE THAT, THE TEAM
WON FIVE TOURNAMENT GAMES IN A
ROW.
ONE MORE WIN, AND GIBSONBURG WAS
IN THE FINAL FOUR.
THE ONLY THING THAT STOOD IN THE
WAY WAS ST. JOE...
AND TYLER PINKUS.
>> ARE WE ALMOST THERE?
>> YES, WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
>> COME ON.
WHERE ARE YOU TAKING ME?
>> I WOULD JUST CALL IT MY
SPECIAL PLACE, WHERE I GO TO
THINK.
I'VE BEEN COMING HERE SINCE I
WAS REALLY LITTLE.
>> BUT WHY IS IT SO FAR AWAY?
>> OKAY, HERE WE ARE.
STAND RIGHT...
RIGHT...
THERE.
PERFECT.
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
>> OH, WOW.
>> WASN'T IT WORTH THE WALK?
>> THIS IS AMAZING.
THANK YOU.
>> IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> YEAH.
IT IS.
[ FIRE CRACKLING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> IF YOU WERE TO WALK OUT ON A
BEACH AT ANY GIVEN TIME, THE
WATER WILL BE MOVING ONE OF TWO
WAYS.
AND WE WALKED INTO THIS STORY,
IT WAS SURELY MOVING ONE
PARTICULAR WAY.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THE THING ABOUT
THE TIDE IS, EVENTUALLY IT
CHANGES.
EVEN AFTER EVERYTHING THAT
HAPPENED UP TO THIS POINT, NO
ONE WAS ALL THAT CONFIDENT ABOUT
FACING TYLER PINKUS AND
FREMONT ST. JOE AGAIN.
>> YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK WE
HAVE A CHANCE TODAY.
>> YEAH, I KNOW, BUT AT LEAST
WE'LL GET TO SEE PINKUS.
MY DAD SAYS THAT IN A COUPLE
YEARS, WE'LL GET TO SEE HIM
PITCHING IN THE BIGS.
>> COOL.
>> IT WAS A WELL-KNOWN FACT THAT
NO ONE HATED GOING AGAINST
PINKUS MORE THAN WYATT.
FOR SOME REASON, EVER SINCE THEY
WERE LITTLE KIDS, PINKUS HAD IT
IN FOR WYATT.
AND HE'D GUN FOR HIM EVERY
SINGLE TIME.
>> LOOKING FOR THIS?
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
>> BALL.
>> GO AHEAD AND HIT HIM IF YOU
WANT TO, BABY!
YOU'LL JUST STRIKE THE NEXT
THREE OUT, ANYWAY!
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
OH, YOU GOT LUCKY ON THAT ONE,
YOU HICKSTER!
TRY KEEPING YOUR EYES OPEN NEXT
TIME, AND LET'S SEE WHAT
HAPPENS!
>> NOW, UP UNTIL THIS POINT,
WYATT KISER HAD NEVER HIT A HOME
RUN IN HIS ENTIRE LIFE.
I THINK ABOUT IT, AND I STILL
JUST SHAKE MY HEAD.
BUT THE GAME HAD ONLY JUST
STARTED.
FOR FOUR MORE INNINGS, PINKUS
DID NOTHING BUT REGISTER
STRIKEOUT...
AFTER STRIKEOUT...
AFTER STRIKEOUT.
>> STRIKE 3!
[ CROWD MOANS ]
STRIKE 3!
[ MOANING CONTINUES ]
>> WHAT?!
>> DON'T EVEN TRY AND TELL ME
SOMETHING PECULIAR WASN'T
HAPPENING.
ALL THE SUDDEN, THE GAME WAS
TIED UP.
>> I JUST GOT TO EAT WHEN I'M
NERVOUS.
I GOT TO EAT.
I'M NERVOUS.
>> AND EVERY SINGLE PERSON WAS
WAITING FOR WYATT TO STEP UP TO
THAT PLATE AGAIN.
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
>> I'M NOT WALKING HIM.
NOT DOING IT.
NO, I'M GOOD.
I'M NOT WALKING HIM, COACH.
NO, I'M NOT WALKING HIM.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
LET'S GO.
WE GOT ONE OUT!
>> BLUE, YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING
ME!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
YOU GOT TO THROW HIM OUT OF THE
GAME!
DID YOU NOT HEAR ME?!
THROW HIM OUT OF THE GAME!
>> WYATT?
>> [ GROANS ]
>> HEY, YOU OKAY, MAN?
>> I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
HEY...
HAVE WE EVER BEAT THESE GUYS?
>> NOPE.
I DON'T THINK WE EVER HAVE.
>> THIS WOULD BE A PRETTY GOOD
GAME TO WIN.
>> YEAH...IT WOULD...
EXCEPT...
I'VE NEVER EVEN HIT A FOUL BALL
OFF PINKUS.
>> JUST MAKE CONTACT, MAN.
IT'LL GO.
>> COME ON! LET'S GO! PLAY BALL!
>> JUST MAKE CONTACT, HUH?
>> JUST MAKE CONTACT.
>> COME ON! COME ON! LET'S GO!
WE GOT ONE OUT! BASES LOADED!
COME ON!
WE NEED SOMEONE TO DRIVE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO! LET'S GO!
>> TAG, TAG, TAG, TAG, TAG.
LET'S GO! LET'S GO! GO, GO, GO!
>> ANDY, I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO
SAY.
YOU KNEW YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO
TAKE THE COIN.
EVEN IF YOU DID ASK, WE WOULDN'T
HAVE SAID YES.
>> DAD, I FEEL TERRIBLE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE IT COULD
BE.
>> WELL, PART OF ME...
PART OF ME THINKS ABOUT WHAT MY
GRANDFATHER DID.
[ CHUCKLES ]
MAYBE HE DID IT RIGHT.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WHAT I MEAN IS, LOOK AT OUR
FAMILY.
WE GOT A GREAT LIFE.
THINGS HAVE BEEN STRESSFUL THE
PAST YEAR, YEAH, BUT THEY ALL
WORKED OUT.
THE OTHER COINS PAID OFF THE
ENTIRE DEBT.
WE WERE EVEN ABLE TO PUT A GOOD
CHUNK OF MONEY BACK.
WE COULD BE HAPPY ABOUT THAT.
>> DAD, I'LL RETRACE MY STEPS.
I'LL GO BACK TO THE FIELD AND
LOOK FOR THE COIN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU DO THINK IF YOU THINK IT'LL
MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
IT'S GONNA BE LIKE LOOKING FOR A
NEEDLE IN A HAYSTACK.
BUT IF YOU FIND IT, GREAT.
IF YOU DON'T...
WELL, I GUESS THAT'LL BE OKAY,
TOO.
LOOK WHAT MONEY DID TO OUR
FAMILY BEFORE.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN US.
COME ON.
LET'S GET BACK TO WORK.
[ WOMAN VOCALIZING ]
>> GOING TO STATES!
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
>> YEAH, THANK YOU.
WE'RE SURPRISING OURSELVES.
>> EVERYONE IN THE TOWN IS SO
PROUD OF THE TEAM, AND I'M
REALLY PROUD OF YOU.
>> I CAN SAY WE'RE HAVING A GOOD
TIME RIGHT NOW.
>> HEY, ARE WE STILL GOING TO
YOUR BARBECUE TONIGHT?
>> YOU BET...
UNLESS YOU'RE TOO BUSY.
>> WELL...
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> JUST KIDDING.
I'VE HAD A REALLY GREAT TIME
SEEING YOU.
>> ALL THE SUDDEN, MY LIFE SEEMS
LIKE IT'S OVER.
AND THEN IT SEEMS LIKE IT
COULDN'T GET ANY BETTER.
IT'S FUNNY.
>> VERY FUNNY.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU MEAN.
>> I'LL PICK YOU UP AT 6:00?
>> SOUNDS GOOD.
SO, WHERE TO NOW?
>> I WAS GONNA DROP OFF THE
BLANKETS AT MY UNCLE JOE'S, THEN
I'LL TAKE YOU HOME.
>> SO SOON?
OH, I THOUGHT WE COULD HANG OUT
FOR A LITTLE LONGER.
NOW WHERE ARE WE GOING?
>> WE'LL JUST TAKE A SHORTCUT
THROUGH BRINKER'S FARM AND PASS
THROUGH THE WOODS.
>> IT'S CLEAR NOW, BUT WITH ALL
THE RAIN THIS MORNING, YOU SURE
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA?
>> HEY, I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ CAR BEEPING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
MY DAD'S GONNA KILL ME.
I JUST FINISHED FIXING THE
BAKERY TRUCK, AND NOW I SCREWED
UP MINE.
[ SIGHS ]
I'LL CALL HIM TO COME GET US.
NICE.
PHONE'S DEAD.
>> NICE SHORTCUT.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
[ SIGHS ]
HEY?
CHECK THIS OUT.
>> IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> GOOD AFTERNOON AND WELCOME TO
THE OHIO STATE BOYS HIGH SCHOOL
BASEBALL CHAMPIONSHIPS, HERE AT
BEAUTIFUL HUNTINGTON PARK IN
COLUMBUS.
IN TODAY'S SEMIFINAL MATCHUP, WE
HAVE GIBSONBURG TAKING ON
JACKSON CENTER.
I'M TIM McMAHON.
ALONGSIDE ME IS KENT MERCKER,
AND CALL IT DAVID/GOLIATH,
CINDERELLA STORY, SEABISCUIT --
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO CALL IT --
GIBSONBURG, 12-17 ON THE SEASON,
THE FIRST TEAM WITH A LOSING
RECORD TO REACH THE STATE
SEMIFINALS.
REALLY SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
BUT THEY'RE TAKING ON THE
UNDEFEATED JACKSON CENTER, A
LEGEND IN THE STATE.
AND, KENT, THEY HAVE QUITE A
TOUGH TASK AHEAD OF THEM TODAY.
>> WELL, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT
AMAZES ME IS JUST TO LOOK OUT ON
THIS FIELD, NOT SEEING THEM ALL
YEAR.
I DON'T THINK DAVID WAS THAT
SMALL.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> I MEAN, A LOT OF THESE KIDS
DON'T LOOK LIKE THEY'RE
135 POUNDS.
BUT EVEN MORE IMPRESSIVE TO ME
IS THEY'VE GOT 6 WINS THIS YEAR
IN THE STATE TOURNAMENT, WHICH
MATCHES THEIR SEASON TOTAL UP TO
THIS POINT.
BUT, EVEN MORE IMPORTANTLY, IF
THEY LOOK TO CONTINUE THAT, THEY
GOT A TOUGH TASK AHEAD OF THEM
TODAY.
THEY GOT JOSH THOMPSON THROWING
FOR JACKSON CENTER.
THIS KID'S ALREADY COMMITTED TO
OHIO STATE ON A SCHOLARSHIP.
GOOD FASTBALL.
THROWS IN THE UPPER 80s TO THE
LOW 90s.
I HOPE THEY BROUGHT THEIR
SLINGSHOTS TODAY, 'CAUSE THEY'RE
GONNA NEED THEM.
>> MY NEPHEW KYLE PLAYS FOR
JACKSON CENTER.
I HOPE THEY LIGHT THAT
GIBSONBURG TEAM UP!
>> YEAH, THEY'RE DEFINITELY
GONNA NEED IT -- PROBABLY A
LITTLE BIT OF LUCK, TOO.
THOMPSON, BY THE WAY, THE THIRD
PITCHER GIBSONBURG HAS FACED
WITH A DIVISION I SCHOLARSHIP.
ALL RIGHT, THE FANS ARE READY.
WE'RE READY.
GIBSONBURG/JACKSON CENTER JUST
ABOUT TO GET UNDER WAY.
HERE WE ARE, IN THE TOP OF THE
5th INNING.
IT'S A SCORELESS GAME RIGHT NOW,
A PITCHING DUEL THUS FAR.
ALEX BLACK ON THE MOUND FOR
GIBSONBURG FACING THE OTHER
PITCHER, JOSH THOMPSON, WHO CAN
DO MORE THAN JUST THROW THE
BALL, KENT.
>> YEAH, THOMPSON'S DEFINITELY A
DUAL THREAT.
DEFINITELY NOT SOMEONE YOU WANT
TO TAKE LIGHT.
BLACK BETTER BE CAREFUL HERE.
>> RUNNER ON FOR JACKSON CENTER.
HERE'S THE WINDUP AND THE PITCH.
BALL HIT TO LEFT CENTER, A NICE
FLARE, NICE DOUBLE FOR THOMPSON.
THAT'S GONNA BRING A RUNNER
AROUND.
MAKES THE SCORE 1-0,
JACKSON CENTER.
HERE WE ARE, IN THE BOTTOM OF
THE 7th INNING.
1-0, JACKSON CENTER.
GIBSONBURG AT THE PLATE, WITH
2 OUTS.
JACKSON CENTER 1 OUT AWAY FROM
THAT STATE CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
>> ALL RIGHT, WHO'S UP?
OH!
THIS GUY CAN'T PITCH OR HIT HIS
WAY OUT OF A PAPER BAG!
>> BUT THE GOLDEN BEARS
THREATENING.
MILLESON ON SECOND, KISER ON
FIRST FOR GIBSONBURG, AND THE
PITCHER, ALEX BLACK, UP TO BAT
WITH A 3-1 COUNT.
>> THAT PITCHER WILL STRIKE
BLACK OUT FOR SURE.
I'VE KNOWN ALEX BLACK SINCE HE
WAS LITTLE, AND HE'S NO --
AAGGHHH!
>> A LOT OF COMMOTION GOING ON
THERE.
HOPEFULLY, EVERYBODY'S ALL
RIGHT.
>> I HOPE THAT ONE HIT AN EMPTY
SEAT.
THAT BALL WAS HIT HARD.
>> HE DID THAT ON PURPOSE!
I'M FILING A POLICE REPORT!
NO, NO, NO!
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
>> BUT, MORE IMPORTANTLY, THE
COUNT'S NOW FULL, TIM, AND WHAT
THAT MEANS IS BOTH RUNNERS ARE
GOING TO BE GOING ON THE PITCH.
SO, IF BLACK CAN FIND A GAP HERE
SOMEWHERE, THAT RUN SHOULD
EASILY SCORE FROM FIRST BASE.
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
>> LOOKS LIKE WE'RE ONE OUT FROM
GOING HOME.
>> YEAH.
LET'S JUST WAIT AND SEE WHAT
ALEX CAN DO.
>> HERE WE ARE, BOTTOM OF THE
7th -- 2 OUTS, RUNNERS ON FIRST
AND SECOND.
BLACK UP TO BAT.
GONNA STEP OUT.
CHECK WITH HIS THIRD BASE COACH.
A LITTLE BIT OF STRATEGY PERHAPS
HERE, KENT.
>> HE MIGHT BE TRYING TO FREEZE
THE PITCHER A LITTLE BIT.
>> PLAY!
>> ALL RIGHT, BLACK BACK UP TO
THE PLATE.
HERE'S THE WINDUP AND THE PITCH.
A HIGH FASTBALL AND BLACK HITS
IT A MILE HIGH, A POP-UP RIGHT
OVER HIS HEAD.
SHOULD END THE GAME.
>> THAT'S A FAIR BALL.
HE'S GOT TO BE RUNNING.
HE'S HEADED BACK TO THE DUGOUT.
>> YEAH, HE'S DISGUSTED, BUT THE
BALL DROPS.
IT'S A FAIR BALL.
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
AND THE THROW TO FIRST IS OVER
THE FIRST BASEMAN'S HEAD.
BLACK IS SAFE.
ALL RUNNERS ARE SAFE, AND
GIBSONBURG WINS THIS GAME.
IT'S OVER.
2-1 THE FINAL -- UNLIKE ANYTHING
I'VE EVER SEEN.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU, KENT.
>> I'VE SEEN A LOT OF BASEBALL
GAMES.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE
THIS HERE.
>> HEY, GIBSONBURG?
ANYONE WANT TO PLAY IN THE STATE
CHAMPIONSHIP?
[ ALL CHEERING ]
ALEX BLACK, I DON'T KNOW WHETHER
TO CHEW YOU OUT OR GIVE YOU A
HUG.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
'CAUSE THAT CRAZY-ASS PLAY JUST
GOT US IN THE STATE
CHAMPIONSHIP.
MEN, I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
SO PROUD!
LET'S GRAB SOMETHING TO EAT, GET
A GOOD NIGHT'S REST, AND GET
READY TO PLAY FISHER CATHOLIC IN
THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP TOMORROW.
[ ALL CHEERING ]
GREAT JOB TODAY, EVERYONE.
GREAT JOB.
[ CHEERING CONTINUES ]
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
REALLY?
HOW DOES A TEAM LIKE US GET TO
THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP?
>> YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT IT, WE'RE PLAYING A LOT
BETTER.
BUT THERE'S BEEN A CRAZY FLUKE
IN EVERY GAME WE WON.
I MEAN, WYATT HAD NOT HIT A HOME
RUN IN HIS WHOLE LIFE.
AND HE HITS 2 HOME RUNS AGAINST
THE BEST PITCHER IN THE STATE.
COME ON!
THEN, THE WEIRD BREAKS WE HAD?
AGAINST VAN BUREN, KALIDA, AND
EDGERTON?
>> I KNOW.
>> AND THEN, TODAY, IF BLACK
WOULDN'T HAVE CONFUSED EVERYONE
THE WAY HE THREW DOWN HIS BAT,
THEY WOULD HAVE CAUGHT THE BALL,
FOR SURE.
I MEAN, JACKSON CENTER WAS ONE
EASY CATCH AWAY FROM BEATING US.
WHAT'S WRONG, RASE?
>> THESE KIDS -- THEY JUST NEVER
GIVE UP.
THEY REALLY BELIEVE WE CAN DO
IT.
DO YOU THINK WE'LL WIN ONE MORE
TOMORROW?
>> JUST LOOK AT ALL THE
FIRST-YEAR COACHES LIKE YOU THAT
HAVE WON STATE WITH A 6-17
REGULAR-SEASON RECORD.
>> VERY FUNNY.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
HEY, I'M OUT OF HERE.
I GOT TO GET SOME SLEEP.
>> ALL RIGHT, COACH.
GET A GOOD NIGHT'S REST.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
>> WELCOME TO THE OHIO STATE
BOYS HIGH SCHOOL BASEBALL
STATE-CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
AND WE HAVE A GOOD ONE FOR YOU
TODAY HERE AT HUNTINGTON PARK.
GIBSONBURG, 13-17 ON THE SEASON,
FACING OFF AGAINST
LANCASTER FISHER CATHOLIC, WITH
A 30-1 RECORD.
BUT BACK TO GIBSONBURG.
THEY WERE RUN-RULED SEVEN TIMES
AND WENT THROUGH A STRETCH THIS
SEASON WHERE THEY LOST 12 GAMES
IN A ROW.
HOW DOES THIS HAPPEN, KENT?
HOW DOES A TEAM LIKE THIS GET
HERE?
>> I DON'T THINK ANYBODY KNOWS
THAT, INCLUDING GIBSONBURG.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU THIS.
WE COULD BE WITNESSING HISTORY
TODAY.
IF GIBSONBURG DOES FIND A WAY TO
WIN THIS GAME TODAY, THEY WILL
BE THE ONLY TEAM, NOT JUST IN
OHIO, BUT IN ANY STATE, WITH A
LOSING RECORD TO WIN A STATE
CHAMPIONSHIP.
>> A REMARKABLE FEAT IF THEY CAN
PULL THIS OFF.
AND VERY SHORTLY WE'LL FIND OUT
IF GIBSONBURG CAN REPLACE THAT
GLASS SLIPPER WITH A CROWN.
WELL, SO FAR, THE
STATE-CHAMPIONSHIP GAME
CERTAINLY LIVED UP TO THE HYPE.
GIBSONBURG AND ALEX BLACK,
RIDING THAT MOMENTUM FROM THE
JACKSON CENTER GAME, GETTING OFF
TO A HOT START TODAY.
>> YEAH, AND YOU JUST HOPE BLACK
CAN KEEP IT UP.
HE PITCHED 7 INNINGS JUST A DAY
AGO.
SO, HE'S RUNNING ON FUMES, AND
LET'S JUST SEE IF HE CAN
CONTINUE.
>> OH!
KISER -- THAT HAS TO HURT.
>> SAFE!
>> FISHER CATHOLIC NOW HAS
5 RUNS AFTER THAT BASES-LOADED
TRIPLE IN THE 5th.
>> DOWN BY 2, TYING RUN ON
FIRST, STATE-CHAMPIONSHIP GAME,
DUDE.
NO PRESSURE OR ANYTHING.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> HERE WE ARE, AT THE BOTTOM OF
THE 7th INNING, 1 OUT, RUNNERS
ON FIRST AND THIRD FOR
GIBSONBURG IN THE
STATE-CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
RIGHT NOW THE SCORE IS
FISHER CATHOLIC 5,
GIBSONBURG 3.
WELLS ON THE MOUND FOR
FISHER CATHOLIC HAS BEEN A BEAST
ALL DAY, BUT HE'S GOT
ANDY GRUNER COMING UP TO THE
PLATE.
AND GRUNER'S ACTUALLY GONNA LAY
DOWN A BUNT.
WE HAVE A SUICIDE SQUEEZE
HAPPENING RIGHT HERE.
MILLESON'S SAFE AT HOME, AND
GRUNER SAFE AT FIRST.
I DON'T THINK THAT
FISHER CATHOLIC SAW THIS ONE
COMING.
>> I DON'T THINK ANYBODY ON
EARTH SAW THAT PLAY COMING, AND
HE EXECUTED IT PERFECTLY.
WHAT A PLAY.
>> AND GIBSONBURG NOW WITHIN A
RUN.
5-4, FISHER CATHOLIC LEADS.
WINNING RUN AT FIRST.
DEREK HETRICK AT THE PLATE.
HETRICK MAKES CONTACT, A DEEP
FLY BALL.
HE'S GONNA GET TO THE GAP IN
LEFT CENTER.
KISER COMES AROUND FOR THE SCORE
EASILY.
HERE COMES GRUNER, MOST LIKELY
BEING HELD UP AT THIRD.
NO, HE'S BEING WAVED HOME.
HE'S COMING HOME.
HERE COMES THE THROW, A PERFECT
THROW.
GRUNER'S GONNA BE OUT BY A MILE.
OH!
[ CROWD CHEERS ]
>> GOT A MESSAGE FOR EVERYBODY
IN THE STATE OF OHIO!
GIBSONBURG JUST WON STATE!
WHOO!
[ ALL CHEERING ]
HERE WE GO! NUMBER ONE!
>> AND THAT ABOUT DOES IT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
BUT NOW IT'S HISTORY.
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T PLAY MUCH
ALL YEAR, BUT I SURE ENJOYED THE
RIDE.
>> WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
[ LAUGHS ]
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> NOT MUCH.
JUST GETTING READY FOR WORK.
>> HEY, HENRY.
>> HEY, ANDY.
FELLAS.
>> WHAT'S UP, HENRY?
>> YOU KNOW, ANDY, WHAT YOU DID
FOR THIS TOWN IS REALLY SPECIAL.
SO, ANDY, AS CAPTAIN OF THE
TEAM, I HAVE SOMETHING SPECIAL
FOR YOU.
>> WHAT?
>> NO WAY, HENRY.
I CAN'T ACCEPT THIS.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
ENJOY.
>> AW!
>> YEAH, BABY!
LET'S GO!
>> YEAH, RIGHT!
>> NO!
>> SHOTGUN!
>> KATHY?
>> NO...YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
>> LET'S GO!
>> ALL RIGHT.
[ CAR DOOR CLOSES ]
>> LET'S GO, BABY!
LET'S RIDE, BABY!
WHOO!
>> YEAH!
GO, BABY!
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> HEY, SHIT, ANDY, YOU SEE THAT
STOP SIGN UP AHEAD, THOUGH?
>> COME ON. SLOW THIS CAR DOWN.
>> NO BRAKES!
>> WHAT?!
>> YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME!
>> NO BRAKE!
>> SHUT UP!
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
>> FUCK, NO!
>> HANG ON, GUYS!
>> SHIT!
>> AAH!
[ HORN HONKING ]
>> HOLY CRAP!
>> [ EXHALES ]
>> ANDY, MAN, WE ALWAYS SEEM TO
GET SOME LUCKY BREAKS, DON'T WE?
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
>> [ Laughing ] WE ALMOST JUST
DIED!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
>> HEY!
>> HI!
IT'S GREAT TO SEE YOU.
HEY.
>> I'LL TAKE THE SPECIAL, SON.
>> THAT'LL BE 25 CENTS, PLEASE.
>> NICE JOB ON THAT CHAMPIONSHIP
GAME THERE, FELLA.
>> THANK YOU, SIR.
>> HEY, SHORTSTOP.
>> WE DON'T KNOW HOW WE DID IT,
BUT IT WAS A FUN RIDE.
>> HEY, THAT LITTLE FILLY IS
REALLY CUTE.
>> YEAH.
>> CAN I GIVE YOU SOME ADVICE,
SON?
>> YEAH.
>> I'D HANG ONTO THAT ONE IF I
WERE YOU.
[ WOMAN VOCALIZING ]