[instrumental music]
[music continues]
[crickets chirping]
[rumbling]
[instrumental music]
[crows cawing]
[leaves rustling]
[engine revving]
[whirring]
[zapping]
[explosion]
[crackling]
That's enough! That's enough!
My ass is on fire!
[laughing]
I thought I smelled
some nuts roasting.
[whimpering]
Call it, Sparks.
- This is Little John
- who shot the sheriff.
- [sighs]
- First weapons test terminated.
Back up all telemetry
and crash reference data.
Nice shootin', Johnny.
- Thanks, Sparky.
- 'It feels good, though.'
- Moving the capacitor
- to the start
- Really helped fix
- the balance.
- Always glad to help.
- And whose idea was that?
[helicopter whirring]
Let's, uh, take
a closer look, senator.
- Bring that video over here,
- Burke.
- On it, sir.
- 'Oh, alright.'
[helicopter whirring]
How's the voltage holding?
Solid.
Still got 57.2 megavolts.
Check the amp-curve.
It's perfect.
You knew alloy
really kept the barrel cool.
Cool, just like you.
- (male #1)
- 'Okay, I'll back up.'
[engine revving]
(Susan)
displays? Everything okay?
Now, what about the data
- (John)
- 'Yeah, it's great.'
Impressive, isn't it?
[sighs]
It's amazing weaponry.
This was maximum power?
Is that what you were told?
Forgive my asking, ma'am.
Uh, what's your
security clearance?
Level four.
- Well, then I guess it's alright
- for me to tell you
- That I've personally made
- some adjustments
That increase
the intensity considerably.
- That would be
- something to see.
Always doing my best in the
ma'am.
service of my country,
Well..
- Keep it up,
- lieutenant..
Nathaniel Burke, ma'am.
- Keep this up,
- Lieutenant Nathaniel Burke
And you'll be a captain
in no time.
Yes, ma'am.
- (David)
- 'Senator Nolan, we're ready'
'for the next demonstration.'
This village
has been set aside for us
as a training area.
- (female #1)
- 'Ammo! Ammo!'
This isn't, uh,
people's rifle.
- No, ma'am,
- it's a sonic cannon.
- It pumps out
- an ultra-low-frequency
Burst of sound energy.
- Can take out
- a whole line of troops.
Without killing them.
Just leaves them stunned.
And you like that idea?
Not killing 'em?
Yes, ma'am, I do.
- Set to a higher gain,
- it can bring down
An entire wall like that one.
Why not the whole building?
We haven't tested
those parameters.
- Everything's set on the street.
- Let's do it.
(male #2)
'Go, go, go, go.'
This is Little John.
Get ready to storm the castle.
- (man on radio)
- 'Copy that, Little John.'
May I do the honors, colonel?
- 'Evacuate the area! Let's
- Alright. Irons, stand down.
go!'
- (man on radio)
- 'Target in sight..'
- Go for it, lieutenant.
- Yes, sir.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[whirring]
[instrumental music]
[indistinct shouting]
Nathaniel, no!
[explosions]
[all shouting]
[Susan screams]
Sparky!
[clattering]
[groans]
[indistinct shouting]
- (male #3)
- 'Let's get the medic!'
Sparky!
[grunting]
When you managed
to remove the concrete
what did you find?
The senator
had been killed, sir.
And Lieutenant Sparks?
(John)
She had a severe spinal injury.
And her legs had been crushed.
She may never walk again.
I can imagine how difficult
it must have been for you.
- Now, we've heard the testimony
- that you shouted out
To Lieutenant Burke
just before he fired.
Did you see how the weapon
was calibrated?
Yes, sir.
What intensity level was set?
The maximum, sir.
- A parameter that had
- never been tested
Or even approved for testing,
is that correct?
Yes, sir.
Burke knew what he was doing.
Oh, is it?
Who recalibrated the weapon?
Lieutenant, who did it?
Burke did it, sir.
[indistinct chatter]
(male #4)
That's all.'
'Thank you, lieutenant.
- Thanks for selling me out,
- brother soldier.
Out of my face with that.
What you did was foul.
I should bust your ass
for what you did to Sparky.
Bust my ass?
Do you know where I was headed?
You know what I could've done
resources?
with those military
You stupid..
- Ugh! Ah.
- Huh. Hey, man.
- (David) - He's lucky
- He just got dismissed
Instead of being sent
to Leavenworth.
- It's been a rotten damn deal
- all the way around
- But you're gonna feel
- a whole lot better about this
When we go back to work.
- Now, we've got to create
- a new unit here and press on.
We got a golden
opportunity here.
"Opportunity?"
These weapons
are far more powerful
than I'd ever hoped.
Come on, you still have those
buildings folded up.
We've created a whole
new generation of weaponry here.
We can't turn our backs on this
kind of potential firepower.
Maybe you can't. But after
what happened Sparks, I can.
Sir.
[indistinct chatter]
[inhales sharply]
- (man on PA)
- 'Dr. Rollinson to ER, please.'
'Dr. Rollinson to ER..'
[chuckles]
[instrumental music]
[sighs]
My hero.
I brought you some flowers.
Sweet peas.
My favorite.
No kidding?
[chuckles]
You..
Service.
So you really did bail, huh?
My tour was over.
After what happened to you
I ain't trying to go back.
Well, I'll come see ya
as soon as I'm back on my feet.
[music continues]
[sighs]
I'm counting on it.
- I'll be checkin' up on you
- every week.
Here. My phone number
and address. Use it.
Where you headin'?
Home.
- [Young Mc singing
- "Bust A Move"]
♪ If you want it ♪
♪ Ah ♪
- ♪ You got it ♪
- ♪ Ah ♪
♪ If you want it baby
you got it ♪
♪ If you want it ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ You got it honey
you want it baby.. ♪
- (woman on PA) - 'Captain has turned on
- The seat-belt sign'
'indicating our final approach
into Los Angeles.'
'The weather is 72 degrees
and beautiful.'
♪ Oh oh yeah oh ♪
♪ Oh oh.. ♪
- What's up, John?
- Welcome back.
Stayin' out of trouble?
- Of course.
- Alright.
- 'Shoot one!'
- Come on!
- Let's go, John.
- Come on.
[indistinct chatter]
I could've did that.
Prick.
♪ Yeah oh oh ♪
♪ If you want it baby
you got it oh ♪
you got it ♪
♪ Ah-ah ah-ah ah-ah ♪
(female #2)
'Dantastic. Good afternoon.'
♪ Oh yeah oh ha-ah ♪
Uh, Mr. Daniels, Mr. Burke
insisted on seeing you.
How are you... Big Willy?
This is a nice setup.
You have come a long way
since the old neighborhood.
But I understand you're still
selling hot weapons.
[siren wailing]
I distribute arcade games,
Burke.
I give jobs
to at-risk kids.
I'm a legitimate businessman.
- How would you like
- to help me deal
The next generation
of super weapons?
'Not to the crooks and punks
on the street'
but to the world.
If you give me a little
seed money for the prototypes..
I'll do a little advertising
and we'll be partners.
What exactly are you selling?
Ah. Mm-mm.
[helicopter whirring]
A little gift from my Uncle Sam.
♪ Ken and Susie sittin'
in a tree K-I-S-S-I.. ♪
- What's up, John?
- What's up, babe? You alright?
- Yeah.
- Alright.
- 'Hey, Johnny!'
- It's my turn. I wanna..
- Hey, watch it.
- Incoming!
- What are you? - Some kinda skud or
- Something?
Nah. You mean, stud.
Hey, why you player hatin'?
Man, I got all kind
of crazy honey sweatin' me.
- Heh, yeah, right.
- Hey, what's up, Martin?
- What's up, Lamont?
- Yeah.
- Alright.
- His brother still locked up?
- [scoffs] - Man, his brother got more time
- Than a clock.
- What about you?
- I ain't livin' like him.
I just be chillin', man.
Why? What did you think?
- I think it's good to be
- home.
[indistinct chatter]
Grandma! Grandma, guess what?
Ai-sho! Now, Martin,
don't you spoil everything.
My bad, but somebody's here
to see you..
[gasps]
- Hey, grandma!
- Shh..
[chuckles]
Oh..
[inaudible]
I'm so glad to see you.
I'm glad to see you, too.
Look like you grew
a little taller.
Oh. Oh, my goodness. Oh.
- Come on.
- 'Shh.'
(Odessa)
sass twiny toes.
Tip-toe on them
Oh, shoot!
- Somebody wanna tell me
- what's going on?
Oh, gone in. It was supposed
to be a souffle.
A souffle?
- It was supposed to be
- all light
And fluffy and full of air.
And it was till
you come stormin' in.
[sighs]
to master the art
Martin, how am I ever supposed
of French cooking when you keep
crashin' in here
like James Brown?
♪ I feel good
na-na-na na-na-na ♪
[John laughing]
"Master the art
of French cooking?"
I'm marrying up
all my down-home recipes
with haute cuisine.
Ain't that something?
Now, this here was supposed
to be harmony souffle.
Yo, she wants to open
a restaurant and call it
Black And Bleu.
[laughing]
[clearing throat]
That's, uh,
that's a cool name.
Don't you patronize me,
young man.
- You just give me
- some more sugar.
[laughing]
Mwah, mwah, mwah.
Martin, you go finish
your studies.
Ugh.
- I don't want
- no more of them notes
From your teacher.
Yes, ma'am.
- The gang still - messin'
- With him?
[sighs]
Worse than ever.
It's hard to keep him straight.
I'm glad you're home.
Now, you go unpack,
give me your wash.
Check out them messages I've put
on your bed. Who are they?
Probably job offers
from weapons builders.
They are really hot after you.
You write your own ticket.
Is that why you left
the service? Make more money?
No, ma'am.
No more weapons for me.
Lot better for my soul.
- I love you, Johnny.
- I love you, too, grandma.
[chuckles]
- (Odessa)
- Where are you gonna work?
- (John)
- I've got a job lined up
Over at Bill Crawley's.
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Superman Superman ♪
Mm.
Mm-mm. Whoo-hoo.
[indistinct chatter]
[elevator bell dings]
[beeping]
[hip-hop music]
- Okay.
- Load it in.
[hip-hop music]
[grunting]
[indistinct chatter]
And then make sure
it's very, very safe, you know?
- Got it?
- Ah.
- Alright, now..
- Yeah.
[beeping]
Alright, Big Willy,
as promised
the first prototype.
The front office said you
a kid you wanted to hire.
had
- Yeah, just a little
- personal score I have to settle.
Giving back to the community.
Surely you understand
something like that.
[upbeat music]
[screams]
Oh, no.
Alright, get him upstairs.
Call 9-1-1, tell them
it was an electrical fire.
'And get some ice on him.'
- What are you gonna do
- about this, Burke?
- Adjust the surge protector.
- 'Here we go.'
I'm talking about him, asshole.
You could've killed him.
- You gotta push the envelope.
- Accidents happen.
I don't believe it. Mr. Daniels,
this guy is out of control.
Duvray, look at the target.
[music continues]
[smoke hissing]
Keep up the R&D, Burke.
Accidents can happen
to you, too, pal.
[thunder rumbling]
[indistinct chatter]
[chuckles]
Great day.
[elevator bell dings]
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, I forgot something.
Basinger, will you
give me a hand?
[intense music]
[elevator bell dings]
Burke..
[crackling]
[whirring]
[screaming]
[crackling]
[clattering]
[indistinct chatter]
I'm looking for someone
I can trust. Is that you?
- 'Yeah. I know, I know.'
- Yeah.
[indistinct chatter]
[sighs]
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
- Your new recruits together?
- Not yet.
- We're still missing
- a couple of heads.
'But we're ready to start
showing off your weapons.'
[instrumental music]
Remember the last time
we were in a car together?
Shh, shh.
Hey, yo, what's up with this
town meetin', man? Sounds whack.
It's gonna help to get the
anti-gang program started.
new
I thought you two
might share some insights
maybe even learn something.
Why learn when I can earn?
- Look, one of my homies
- snagged me down
- To work at a place
- called Dantastic.
They sell
these bomb arcade games, man.
That's great, stayin' away
from those knuckleheads
and doin' somethin' legit.
So that means I don't have
to go to this meeting, right?
Wrong.
Tsk.
[indistinct chatter]
[siren wailing]
- (male #5) - 'Hey, little kitty.
- Tsk, tsk, tsk.'
'How you doin'?'
[cat meows]
[intense music]
[vehicle approaching]
[music continues]
[cart rattling]
Alright, get ready.
- (Singer)
- 'Do it.'
[whirring]
[glass shattering]
Oh, man! Oh, Lord!
Yeah, fire power, kid!
'That's what we talking about!'
- 'Marks, baby.'
- Yeah!
Marks! Yeah, boy!
[indistinct cheering]
[crackling]
- Whoo!
- Come on.
- Let's go! Let's go!
(male #6)
that's enough. Come on.
Alright, that's enough,
- Out, out.
- Come on, come on.
[indistinct chatter]
Marks, baby. Yeah!
Show me the money, baby. Yeah!
Show Slats the money!
- Come on! Come on, let's go!
- Watch your cover.
- Push! Push!
- Get up. Push! Push!
[thuds]
- Whoo-whee!
- Ah-ha!
[indistinct chatter]
- All this money, man!
- Yes.
Yes. Get all the money.
Get the money!
- (woman on radio)
- 'All units in the vicinity'
'possible 2-11 in progress.
2-2-1-8-6-3.'
- 3-Adams-6, I'm three blocks away
- and on it.
- Request backup.
- 'Yeah!'
Let's get ready to rumble!
Ha-ha-ha!
[siren wailing]
[indistinct shouting]
- Hey, we got company.
- We got company.
- Come on, take 'em out.
- Take 'em out.
[indistinct chatter]
Police, hold!
- There you go.
- Oh!
- 'Out of the way!'
- 'Come on!'
- What is that?
- I don't know what it is.
Hold it!
[groaning]
- Ah!
- Martin, stay down.
- 'Last one. Come on.'
- 'Yeah, yeah.'
[music continues]
Martin!
Officers down
at 2218, 6th Street.
- 'We got a big problem here.'
- Come on, get in, move, move!
- Stay down, stay down.
- Let's go, let's go.
[tires screeching]
[groaning]
Not a good move, sugar.
[siren wailing]
[car crashing]
Norma!
But, Johnny, there's fire!
Purple power, baby! Yay! Yay!
[man groaning]
- Hey, man, Cutter ain't here!
- What?
Where the hell is he?
[John grunting]
Johnny!
[grunting]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[intense music]
Ah!
[explosions]
Johnny? Oh.
We gotta get her to a hospital.
[glass shattering]
[grunts]
It's on now.
[intense music]
[siren wailing]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[train horn blaring]
- Ugh!
- Come here!
Damn!
[grunting]
[train horn blaring]
- Hey!
- Ugh!
We're switching!
You'll get killed out here!
- 'Hey!'
- Ugh.
- Hey!
- 'Ugh.'
[grunting]
Hey.
[train chugging]
[groans]
[intense music]
[grunting]
[music continues]
[train brakes squealing]
[grunts]
[clanking]
[train chugging]
Ah..
[train horn blaring]
[grunts]
[music continues]
[grunting]
Damn it.
[sighs]
[zapping]
Ah! Ah!
[grunts]
[groaning]
[creaking]
[grunting]
[thuds]
Yeah!
[instrumental music]
[grunting]
[John panting]
[laughing]
Oh! You better back up
smoked.
off me before you get
- Where'd you get this?
- I found it. Raise up.
- Tell me where you found it
- or you gonna find
My fist in your mouth.
[groaning]
- Come on, man.
- We gotta get up outta here.
[groaning]
[siren wailing]
- So what did you say
- to the police?
What could I say? I know
those weapons are top secret.
- I just wanna know
- how they got on the streets.
Well, the NSA tells me
that every weapon created by us
and our civilian suppliers
is accounted for.
I had it in my hand, sir.
What do you think blew over
their squad car anyway?
A twister?
I saw a street-gang kid holding
a USR model 3.5
sonic eliminator!
Hey, hold it, hold it.
Are you on a secure phone?
What difference does that make?
- What are we gonna do
- about those weapons?
You just calm down, lieutenant.
The NSA is on it.
Now, there is no way
that highly-classified weapons
- could've ended up in the hands
- of some street gang.
- 'I just don't see
- how that's possible.'
- I don't know
- how you could see anything, sir
With your head
so far up your ass!
[car alarm blaring]
[coins jingling]
He was sportin' purple?
- Martin, I ain't playin'.
- Who you protectin'?
You, damn it.
Purple is the Marks.
- Them kids is buck wild.
- Where can I find 'em?
- Where the hell are they?
- Back home at Benny's.
- It's where they usually hang.
- They're gonna hang, alright.
(woman on TV)
buzzing about the incredibe..'
'Everyone in the city is
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Shut up, shut up, shut up.
(woman on TV)
no clues as to the
'...yet the police have
perpetrators'
- 'of this amazing heist
- and robbery..'
Yeah. Oh, shit.
That's your laser, kid.
That's it, right there.
- (woman on TV) - '...over
- A half billion dollar..'
- Ah, what a...
- Yeah!
- That's what I'm talking about.
- Whoo!
That's what I'm talking about.
[upbeat music]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ Alright keep it rockin'
alright ♪
[laughing]
That's what I'm talking about.
Hey, yo, dawg.
Check out
the jolly black giant.
[laughing]
The weapon your boy had,
where did he get it from?
- I don't know what you're
- talking about, man.
You know what the hell
I'm talking about.
- I just wanna know where your boy
- got that weapon from.
Oh, yeah, well, you know
I'd like to know that, too
what,
because that hater
was, mwah, fat.
- I'd like to get me
- one of them.
- I hear that, man.
- Alright.
I thought you was
the man, Slats.
But I see you're just fronting
it in front of your homeboys.
Oh, big boy,
you see a fancy gun? Huh?
- I ain't got nothing.
- Huh?
- Ha-ha-ha.
That's what I thought.
- Now, you best
- raise up, fool
- 'cause the next time
- you go down
You might not get back up!
- 'Yeah.'
- 'Word.'
- Where'd you get
- the weapon from?
Oh, heh, look at me, man,
I'm shaking like a leaf.
- Ha-ha-ha!
- Tell me what I wanna know!
No, no, no, no, no..
See, we don't play that.
Now, we know you, man.
So don't come around here
no more.
You gonna be knowin' me
a whole lot better.
[clatters]
Chill. Chill.
Hey.
[car honking]
Yeah.
- It's Slats.
- 'So? '
- Yeah, he come in here,
- lieutenant
Like you figured he would.
Alright, nothing changes.
Just keep your idiot friend,
Cutter, out of sight.
That's peace.
Get rid of Cutter.
Set an example for the others.
Got that new webpage ready?
Be online in a week.
We'll be wired for the world.
- 'Terrific.'
- What about Irons?
There is nothing he can do.
- Let's let it roll!
- Thanks.
This has to be a hospital
at Oklahoma City, right?
- But I know that
- Lieutenant Susan Sparks
Is in rehab there.
I've talked to her.
Transferred to St. Louis?
Where?
♪ There's a mountain
in the way we were climbing ♪
♪ We've been living living ♪
(man on PA)
are greatly concerned'
'Authorities in Los Angeles
'about the appearance
of these powerful new weapons'
'on the street.'
'State and federal agencies'
'have so far
been unable to discover'
- 'who is responsible
- for this dangerous'
'escalation of street violence'
- 'and are very fearful
- that it could'
'spread to other cities.'
[indistinct chatter on TV]
Man, oh, man.
- And I thought
- my tax dollars went
To keeping these windows clean.
How you doing, Sparky?
Great.
Is that why you stopped
writing to me?
Didn't you get my letters?
I got 'em. And the wheelchair
you sent. Thanks.
It must be awful for you.
I can imagine how you feel.
No. No, you can't.
You're right. I can't.
I wish I could turn
the clock back.
Sometimes you don't get a choice
about things.
Shit happens.
Tell me about it.
A good cop friend of mine
she's badly hurt
with one of our weapons.
'They're on the streets.'
How is that possible?
- That's what I'm trying
- to figure out.
And I could sure use your help.
[scoffs]
Yeah, I'd be a big help
on the streets.
I don't think so.
- What are you going to do,
- just sit here and look out
The filthy windows?
[glass shatters]
What's going on?
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, good breeze.
I can't.
Girl, you are out of here.
What are you doing? No!
Stop it, Irons.
I don't wanna go!
Listen, Sparks
- sometimes you don't get a choice
- about things.
This here's a prime example
of shit happening.
No. Put me down!
[cheering]
[whimpering]
(Susan)
the hospital was funky.
And I thought
Who lived here before you?
The Sanfords?
Oh, that's Lilly.
She doesn't bite.
- Not your average junkyard
- dog.
This isn't
your average junkyard.
Just wait till you meet
Uncle Joe.
That's a little
work in progress.
And check this out.
Voila.
Very thoughtful.
- We fixed up another one for you
- at Uncle Joe's place.
He's got a spare room
all ready for you.
Johnny, what exactly
am I supposed to be doing here?
The same thing you did at army.
We make our own kind of weapons
to take out the ones
in the streets.
You're crazy. We don't have
the army's resources.
Yeah, I know, but we have
something that they don't have.
[scoffs]
a lot more than that.
It's gonna take
(Joe)
Just make me a list, darlin'.
- Now, don't just
- stand there, beefcake.
Clean off the table.
Thank you. Thank you.
[chuckles]
Hi, I'm Uncle Joe.
Everybody
just calls me Uncle Joe.
[chuckles]
about running a junkyard.
I'll tell you one thing
People will bring you
the damndest things.
That's a mainframe 7200 IBM.
Five-hundred mega-hurtin'
slam-bam, thank you, ma'am
something or other.
Where could you possibly have...
Fella told me it fell off
the back of a truck.
Don't look too dented,
though.
You would be absolutely
moon-eyed to know
just how many thangs will
truck.
fall off the back of a
I'll make a list.
[chuckles]
[squeaking]
Boy, heh,
she's something else.
[chuckles]
what's her story?
What's, what's her,
Her father's dead.
Her mother drinks herself
in and out of rehab.
She's on her own.
Is she really?
[chuckles]
(Martin)
is on the hit, man.'
'Yo, this place
- I'mma own a spot like this
- one day.
That's what I'm trying
to get you put on, man.
- So what's up with this job, man?
- I'm tryin' to get paid.
Man, the dude
that run this stuff is large!
- I want you to meet him.
- And I want to meet you.
- You must be Martin.
- Yeah.
I have heard a lot about you.
I'll take it from here.
'Welcome.'
You can call me The Man.
[groans]
[siren wailing]
[sobbing]
[helicopter whirring]
[instrumental music]
Oh, God.
[sighs]
[grunting]
[panting]
[music continues]
Yes. I told you.
Yes.
[chuckles]
[clanking]
You work out here
half the night.
Don't you ever get tired?
Yeah.
- Then I think about
- who might get blasted
By one of our weapons.
What cop, what kid..
[clanking]
How you doing?
You got everything you need?
Yeah.
Johnny, thanks for
everything.
And for not helping me
with everything.
You understand?
- Hey, yo, y'all.
- Grandma Odessa wants you to come
Check out her Cajun catfish
stuffed with crawdaddy mousse
served with alaron
or whatever that is.
Now, that is an amazing concept.
Yo, what y'all making?
[helicopter whirring]
- Some gadgets.
- Top-secret stuff, huh?
Actually, it is.
[clatters]
I never could make
the free throws.
- Y'all go ahead,
- I'll be down there in a minute.
Alright.
- So how's your new job?
- Oh, it's dope.
And boss made me his main man.
Said if I studied up,
I could make mad cream.
- Be mad powerful.
- Cream?
C-R-E-A-M.
Cash Rules Everything Around Me.
Cream, get the money.
Dollar-dollar bills, y'all.
Some things money can't buy.
Well, what it can get,
I can use.
Yo, you'd blow up at my job.
John Henry says you're a genius.
- John Henry exaggerates.
- Ah.
- Don't believe everything
- he says.
[Marvin Winans singing
["Steel Yourself"]
- ♪ Stand up ♪
♪ You're gonna do
what you gotta do ♪
♪ Come on come on stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ It's all ♪
♪ It's all I've got to do ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ It's time to take command ♪
♪ Time to take it command ♪
♪ Come on come on stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ Because the future's
in your hands ♪
♪ Oh steel yourself ♪
♪ That's when
you start to feel the power ♪
♪ And you'll know you're growing
stronger by the hour ♪
♪ I said stronger by the hour ♪
♪ Stronger by the hour ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ You gotta stand up ♪
♪ Come on come on get up yeah ♪
♪ Ooh stand up ♪
♪ You you gotta get up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ It's what you do hey ♪
- ♪ Hey ♪
- ♪ Stand up ♪
♪ You gotta get up from there ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ Oh yeah yeah ♪
♪ You stand up ♪
♪ You got to stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ I want you to steel yourself ♪
♪ Steel yourself ♪
♪ Gotta steel yourself ♪
♪ Oh you gotta steel yourself ♪
♪ Steel yourself ♪
♪ Come on now yourself ♪
- ♪ And just stand up yeah ♪
- ♪ Stand up yeah ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
Hey, big guy.
Tonight's the night.
Stick it in your ear.
How do you read?
Five-by-five. Receiver?
Transceiver. So be careful
what you say about me.
It's good for 20 miles.
And so is this.
- (Joe)
- 'Whoa, you go, girl.'
Wow. Video.
(Susan)
So I can see what you see.
What is this?
A man named John Henry
has just got to have a hammer.
Of course, I designed it
to do more than pound things.
And I did the metal work.
I especially like the shaft.
What?
Look, guys, I appreciate
what you've both done for me.
But it might get
a little dangerous.
I laugh at danger.
I boogie around danger
like a "Soul Train" dancer.
[laughs]
No, no, no, no. You just do
what you started to do, yeah?
Once I explain this to you, I'm
ready for a little field test.
It is time
to make the final piece.
[intense music]
I know you want to stay away
from weapons work, son, but..
Sometimes you gotta fight
fire with fire.
[music continues]
(Joe)
Well, I'll be damned.
John Henry Irons
has turned himself..
Into the Man of Steel.
[instrumental music]
- such a good actor.
- You think so?
You think he was funny, though?
- Hey. Yo, give me the wallet.
- Oh!
- Let me see some cash.
- Alright.
- Here.
- Break yourself now!
[indistinct chatter]
Please don't hurt us.
You alright?
Can you believe that?
[intense music]
(John)
somebody's family pictures.'
'Not a nice way to treat
Who's that?
I'll shank you, man.
Just give them their stuff back
and we won't have a problem.
I got no problem.
[instrumental music]
Oh, yes, you do.
Surprise.
Whoa!
Whoa! Come on, man,
what you doing?
I didn't do nothin', man!
My God, come on, man.
- Hang around a minute.
- Oh, oh, oh..
I believe this bud
just been born again.
Please don't kill me.
I got a wife and kids.
- Remember how it feels.
- Okay.
Do it again,
and that's your ass.
Okay, man.
I'm cool. I'm cool.
Come on, man!
[laughing]
Look at that.
[scoffs]
9-1-1 is a recording.
Can you believe it?
No, I... can't.
[gasps]
I think this belongs to you.
Uh, thank you.
- Tell the cops
- he's hanging around the corner.
And on behalf of the
of Los Angeles
citizens
I would like to apologize.
[music continues]
Y'all be cool now.
Did you see everything?
- And taped it,
- so you can watch the reruns.
(Susan)
are coming in loud and clear.'
'The audio and video
Your body temp's up a little.
We gotta think about
more ventilation.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
- Hey, bro.
- Hey.
- You told him
- about the gang fight
- Heating up
- down on Hill Street?
Let's not bite off more than
we can chew the first time out.
Get me across street.
[indistinct chatter on radio]
Come on, y'all!
[gunshots]
Faster, faster.
[indistinct yelling]
- Come on. Come on.
- Move. Move. Move.
Come on. Come on.
Behind this car.
- Whoa, whoa, who's this guy?
- Hey, look at this guy.
Let's break up, man.
Damn, hommie,
what the hell is that?
Hey, move out the way, fool,
this is our hood!
Now put the gun down
and there won't be any trouble.
Oh, man, please, I'm about
to smoke you like a blunt.
[gunshots]
Oh, do I wanna look?
One of us has to.
[laughs]
[gunshots]
Well, I'll be damned.
Enough with this stuff.
Let's get a body.
[indistinct chatter]
Uh, Johnny..
[tires screeching]
What's he gonna do?
Hit us with his little hammer?
Run him over, I say.
Get that fool!
[indistinct shouting]
- Sonic is forward?
- Yeah, forward.
- Johnny!
- It's hammer time.
[screams]
[groans]
Well, I'll be dipped in shit
and rolled in bread crumbs.
One of Odessa's recipes?
- Oh, man.
- You should always buckle up.
- Let's smoke his ass.
- Nah, man, he saved us, man.
- No, we don't need no help
- from no cop!
- (male #7)
- 'Man, he ain't no cop, man.'
[grunts]
[clanks]
[indistinct chatter]
[gasping]
Ah!
- 'No way, man.'
- 'What?'
- Go!
- What is this?
- I'm outta here, man.
- I'm outta here!
- Go! Go! Go!
- Yeah, go, man!
(woman on radio)
'Shots fired..'
You're about to have
official company.
- Let's get out of here.
- Yeah, come on.
Watch your back, baby.
[grunts]
[groaning]
Yo, son, this guy has got eyes
in the back of his head.
You got it, and I'll be
watching you. Get out of here!
- Run!
- Yeah.
Good looking out, Sparky.
You be my leg, man
I'll have eyes for you.
[indistinct chatter on radio]
- And you've got
- more blue coming.
[indistinct chatter on radio]
[siren wailing]
From the south and west.
Got 'em.
He knows a way out of this?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I'm-I'm sure he does.
Yeah.
Alright, Sir Lancelot,
move away from those weapons.
Get your hands up. Way up!
[clanks]
[instrumental music]
Well, that is way up.
[grunting]
[siren wailing]
Phew.
- 'I can do this.'
- No.
Don't even think about it,
Johnny.
Piece of cake, Sparky.
No, the rangefinder says
it's too far.
'Are you listening to me,
John Henry?'
In high school, I finished
second in a long jump.
You weren't wearing 75 pounds..
Johnny.
Whoa!
[grunts]
Damn fool.
[siren wailing]
That's one for the computer.
- [sighs]
- Thank you very much.
[grunting]
Yeah. This way. This way.
Martin..
No time to breathe.
Keep going.
- Come on!
- 'Where is he?'
What? Geez.
Ah, we got, we got him.
Man.
- Hey, he jumped.
- Shoot!
[instrumental music]
A hundred-and-thirty feet to go.
'Hundred. Eighty.'
[line snaps]
No!
- Johnny?
- No!
Ah!
Johnny? Johnny, are you okay?
'Johnny?'
- 'Johnny, a-are you..'
- Just a little trashed.
- I guess I better do
- some more work
On the tensile strength.
That's a good idea.
Hey, it's a work in progress.
[intense music]
The cops are right behind you.
[siren wailing]
[indistinct chatter on radio]
Whoa, cool.
[laughs]
They're about a block and a half
and gaining, Johnny.
- Sparky!
- Got a red light, I see it.
I see it. Hang on.
I'm working on it.
- (Johnny)
- Gotta work faster.
[tires screeching]
[car honking]
I still got reds.
[beeping]
- Uh-oh!
- "Uh-oh?"
I don't wanna hear "Uh-oh!"
'Sparky, come on.
I need help here.'
- 'Sparky!'
- Just kidding. We're cool.
We're not cool. Sparky!
It ain't easy being green.
There.
Oh, Lord,
I'm getting too old for this.
This should close the door.
Yes.
[gasps]
No!
[tires screeching]
[car honking]
Move that car. Move it!
[laughing]
- Should be able to give you green
- all the way home.
My boss down at Dantastic
is gonna love me, I can tell.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Lord, have mercy.
- Wow! Ooh!
- Geez, who was that guy?
- Ooh, my..
[chuckles]
Welcome home.
Hee-ha!
Airtech, where the hell
are you?
- (male #8) - Right behind you.
- We'll spot him.
[helicopter whirring]
[tires screeching]
Sparky, what's up?
Don't you trust me?
[squeaking]
[helicopter whirring]
You done good, boy.
What, what, what?
- All they gonna see
- is a pile of junk!
[laughing]
(male #9)
but a pile of junk.'
'Nothing down here
'I'm heading north.'
Where'd that son of a butt
go?
The Bat Cave?
[instrumental music]
[laughs]
since the Mets won the series
I ain't felt this good
back in 1968. Ha-ha!
- '69, Uncle Joe, '69.
- '68, '69, uh, all the same..
- Man..
- That was a long time ago.
- When that wire pulled me up,
- my heart dropped.
Yeah, and when it broke,
my heart stopped.
Work in progress. Did you see
the look on those kids' faces?
- [chuckles] - Looked like they found
- Their Jesus.
- Excuse me,
- but next time will you please
- Trust my rangefinder
- before you jump?
- Boy, you sure are lucky
- this is stainless
Otherwise your butt
would be rusted.
- I've got a printout coming
- so that we can evaluate
All this data.
Sparky.
I don't know what I'd do
without you.
[chuckles]
I'm on fire tonight, Uncle Joe.
[whimpering]
- Well, at least your record's
- intact, boy.
[barking]
Then he came jetting past us
doing, like, 80.
Morning, Martin.
I hear you've become
quite interested
- in our new microchip
- game technology.
Yeah, that new interactive unit.
- It sounds, um, fly. Yeah.
- Fly.
- Why don't you and I
- go take a look at it?
Alright, cool.
- So you really saw
- that man of..
Yeah, steel. Heh.
Last night.
He got some skills.
- And he's a brother.
- Really?
- You think
- he's from your neighborhood?
- Well, he damn sure
- ain't from Beverly Hills.
Mm. Where exactly
is your neighborhood?
[indistinct]
He, he's an
about seven-foot-six.
African-American,
- Yes. Very big.
- As big as a mountain.
- 'And he was covered in
- Yes.
steel.'
And he returned
all of our belongings. See?
And he was,
he was extremely polite.
(male #10)
'Yeah, he was amazing.'
- Wait up for me.
- Why are you going so fast?
- Alright, alright.
- Yo.
What up, lieutenant?
Nice chain. Subtle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
we getting paid.
- Now, what's wrong
- with a little flossing, man?
You floss too much, man,
and your gums are bleeding.
Maybe you'll end up
just like Cutter.
Hot dog?
I don't eat no pork mess.
- That's turkey mess.
- Word?
- Singer will pick
- you guys upstate
Precisely on the schedule.
- How much we give him
- broke off?
A lot. Now, what do you know
about this Steel guy?
Come on, some crazy-ass fool
runnin' around
in aluminum foil.
Sound like a tin man
on steroid.
Never underestimate
your enemy.
- And keep your gold
- out of sight.
Eat the hot dog,
don't be one.
Yes, sir.
(Susan)
no sign of those weapons.
Five nights, and still
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I like having the time
- to make improvements
- on my chair, but..
Stay on point, Sparky.
Something's gonna pop.
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[beeping]
[grunts]
[clanks]
Alright.
[music continues]
Yeah.
[explosion]
[electricity crackling]
[laughs]
[beeping]
Heads up. Something's cooking.
The emergency services
interlink shows, uh
major telephone and power
failure near Hope And Wilshire.
We'll check it out.
I'm zeroing in the land sat.
See if our eye in the sky
spots anything.
Time to make
our major infomercial.
- (male #11) - 'I can't wait to give the
- World'
'a better look
at our new weapons.'
(man on radio)
in Union Station.'
'Two Adam seven. Possible 4-5-9
'Be advised.'
Johnny?
Do you read? Hello?
[static]
Switching to FM.
Shielded sideband,
do you read now?
I read you, five by five.
What happened?
Jamming. Police frequencies
are out, too.
Something is going down.
We're on it.
[dramatic music]
Target in sight.
Proceed.
This is papa bear.
Go. Go.
[rumbling]
Big disturbance
on Sixth and Hope.
Oh, my God.
- (John)
- 'What is it? What's there?'
Only the city's biggest ATM.
- 'What?'
- The Federal Reserve.
- 'Hoo-hoo!'
- 'Yes!'
(male #12)
Open up the bank, baby.'
'Come on, man.
- Ha-ha! Yes! Ha-ha.
- 'Whoo!'
[indistinct chatter]
- Whoa, open it.
- 'Throw it open.'
- Come on. Come on.
- Move it. Yeah.
Two cover the rear. Come on,
move. Let's go. Let's go.
- Outside lines are dead.
- Alarms, too!
I'm heading south!
- Shh, shh, shh.
- Alright. Getting in.
We're getting in right here.
[screaming]
Move, move, move..
[gunshots]
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Go, go, go..
Go, go..
Shut up, shut up, shut up..
- Stock up all you can.
- Ninety seconds we out.
Keep pushing. Keep piling, baby.
Keep piling. Keep piling.
[indistinct shouting]
Let's go. Let's go.
Yeah, baby. More money, baby!
[gunshots]
- 'Who's shooting at us?'
- Oh, no..
- Is he okay?
- Oh, come on!
We've got company.
Open.
[dramatic music]
Now I wonder
who that could be.
- Give it up!
- Ice his metal ass!
[gunshots]
- 'Go, man, hit him.'
- Go outside.
Yeah, read on him. Get a read..
[explosion]
- You're too far away
- to use the magnet.
The alloy of those guns
is not magnetic.
Who's he talking to?
I'm scanning for it, sir.
[gunshots]
- Ah!
- Hey, man.
Hey, get down. Everybody down!
[explosions]
It's got armor
just like yours, Johnny.
- 'What's that?'
- Yo, it's tear gas, man.
Yeah. Come on. Let's-let's go.
- Let's get out.
- Come on, let's go!
You're about to get the blues.
I hear 'em.
[gun firing]
[siren wailing]
Get the sonic gun.
Come on, get some of this.
Take this guy out, man.
Come on.
Whoa!
Johnny.
- This is Airtech, we're 500 feet
- westbound Flower
Towards the Federal Reserve.
[siren wailing]
[grunts]
- You're outgunned, Johnny.
- Bail.
[gun firing]
It's him again.
Try to call it in.
[helicopter whirring]
Alright, let's get your hands
down, down.
Perfect.
Baby Bear, do the chopper.
Slats got something
for your ass.
[explosion]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[crashes]
[tires screeching]
[groans]
[dramatic music]
[engine revving]
- (Susan)
- They're right on top of you.
Turn left on Flower.
'Better use your deterrent.'
[tires exploding]
Damn it!
[siren wailing]
Uh, Johnny, he's closing on you.
[grunts]
[screaming]
[chuckles]
- Hang in there, Johnny.
- Okay, keep going straight.
You'll see the rabbit hole.
'I know you're hurting.
You can make it.'
[siren wailing]
He stopped transmitting
before I could triangulate.
'But I got some parameters.'
Good. Find his home base.
And transmit those video
to the TV stations.
tapes
Mm-hmm.
- (woman on TV) - 'This was the scene
- Moments ago'
'from the LA Federal Reserve.'
'And it's the second time..'
I want some of them weapons.
- Yeah.
- Alright.
(man on TV)
from an anonymous source.'
'This video is transmitted
[indistinct chatter on TV]
[speaking in foreign language]
- 'Ballistics experts are
- stunned'
- 'and they've never seen anything
- like this before.'
[speaking in foreign language]
Pronto.
Oh, my God.
- You may be steel
- on the outside
- But you're flesh and blood
- on the inside.
- Oh, the boy gonna be
- just fine.
- It's just a scratch.
- I'm alright.
Will you cut the macho bull?
You know your rib is broken.
Well, that's tough going,
no question.
- But it's just like what the old
- John Henry had to go through.
- Yeah, and we all know
- what happened to him.
- He died pounding steel,
- but at least
- He beat that old steam
- drill.
But he died doing it.
Well, I guess I can't argue
with you on that.
- Of course, now,
- he didn't have you to help him.
- That's got nothing
- to do with it.
- Of course, it does.
- Looky here...
- Can I have some water,
- please?
Water?
You don't have to do this.
- They got a warrant out for me?
- For the man in steel.
Some of the cops think that
you're all part of the same gang
because you all use
the same weapons.
Somehow they got videotapes
of the robbery.
I think
this.
Nathaniel's mixed up in
I gotta get those weapons
off the streets.
What you've gotta do
is get some sleep.
[telephone ringing]
Rampard Division.
Officer Craft.
Good evening, officer.
- Would you like to know
- where to find
The fancy weapon that shot down
your helicopter?
[siren wailing]
You are really leaning on him.
I noticed at the mill that
the iron that goes through
the hottest fire
makes the best quality steel
on the other end.
Well, if it ever gets that far.
Why are you pressing him
so hard?
'Cause I love him..
And what he's trying to do.
Same reason I love you, Sparky.
- [whispers]
- Evening.
Souffle?
I'mma get it right
if it kills me.
What did you do
to your chin, son?
Oh, I, uh,
bumped into something.
So you did.
You see any of that
big old robbery stuff on TV?
On TV?
No, ma'am.
Times is hard on the street.
Everybody feel like they got
this big old black cloud
hanging over 'em.
Only hope seems to be
that Steel boy.
[chuckles]
Here's a long drink of water.
Big, tall. Like you.
Kinda tired. I think
I'm gonna get some sleep.
What's that in your ear,
son?
It's a, it's a hearing aid.
You never had
no hearing problem.
- Huh?
- I said you never had..
Don't you play with me, boy.
Now, I want to know
the truth.
Are you..
[glass shattering]
[screaming]
[groans]
Doggone it!
Johnny.
Ah!
- Get on the ground,
- get on the ground
- And put your hands
- on your head.
- Now!
- Grandma, what's going on?
- (John)
- I'm down, I'm down!
This is a search warrant.
- John Henry Irons,
- you're under arrest
- 'for suspicion
- of armed robbery, assault'
- 'and possession
- of illegal weapons.'
What's he talking about, Johnny?
- Sir, this was in the basement.
- 'Yeah.'
- Yeah, he definitely fits
- the description.
For what?
To be the man they call Steel.
- You have the right
- to remain silent.
- Anything you say
- can and will be used against you
'in the court of law.'
Number one, step forward.
- Not tall enough.
- No.
- Number two,
- front and center.
Got it, man. I always wanted
to be course line.
Put a sock in it, number
two.
You know, detective,
he was very kind to us.
We wouldn't wanna do anything...
I know, ma'am.
But serious crimes
were committed.
- 'Well, two's not big enough.'
- No.
Officer, the man who helped us
- was on the right side
- of the law.
Yeah.
'And, uh..'
- He's not up there.
- No.
No.
Alright, thanks for
coming in.
- Marcus, come here.
- Yeah.
You got a good look at him,
right?
- Well, look,
- it was kind of dark.
- I mean...
- Hey!
Get in there and ID him.
[door opens]
[instrumental music]
- (male #13)
- 'Just relax, buddy.'
Okay, Sparky, I'm back.
- Why won't they let you
- come home?
- (John) - 'They're holding me
- For questioning.'
- NSA is flying Colonel David
- in tomorrow.
Well, maybe he can help.
Don't count on it.
Did you check on what I said?
'Find out anything?'
- The TV station said
- the videotapes of the robbery
Were sent anonymously.
Big-time infomercial.
- High-tech weapons
- not available in any store.
- And if you act now...
- How does a buyer make contact?
[scoffs]
there's only one way.
In this day and age
- The Internet?
- Damn right.
We can pick up all kinds
of good crap, not just porno.
Have you found it?
Of course.
But now the bad news.
- The big auction is going down
- in 11 hours.
- They give a location?
- Not till the last minute.
Hey, call that detective for me!
Or what? Did you get tired
of talking to the trees?
He's gone to lunch.
Save it for the army, fruitcake.
- He's not gonna be
- that much help.
- Sparky,
- I need to get out of here.
We got you covered.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
[sighs]
Publish is clearing house.
I may be the next
deca-millionaire.
Yeah, yeah,
you get the signature?
And that's a big 10-4.
Coming in clear.
Alright, alright.
(woman on speaker)
the mayor's office on one.'
'Excuse me, sir,
- Yes?
- May I ask who's speaking?
This is District Attorney
Charles Silverberg.
Hello, sir, I'm Connie Levine
with the mayor's office.
- I know it's short notice,
- but he wondered
If you had any free time
this afternoon.
Oh, it is pretty short notice.
'I'll move some things around.
o'clock.'
I could be free by one
Well, don't do anything yet.
I'll call back. Thanks. Bye.
[telephone ringing]
- Holding back division.
- Tillman.
(Susan as Charles)
Charles Silverberg.'
'This is District Attorney
You're holding a prisoner there,
John Henry Irons.
'It is pretty short notice, but
o'clock.'
I want him free by one
- Uh, uh, of course, sir,
- but I'll need to get a...
A written authorization. It's
coming over your fax right now.
'My signature is on it.'
[instrumental music]
(John)
at Alameda Passing.'
'We're cruising
Passing Union Station.
I got you.
- Did you contact Colonel David
- like I asked you to?
- Anonymously,
- through a satellite link
So they can't trace it here.
- Now, they're holding
- at the police helipad
- Until you're sure
- this is going down
And we can give them
a hard target.
Your respiration is still funky.
Those broken ribs are really
bothering you, aren't they?
- Nah.
- I'm worried about you, Johnny.
Going into this with half..
[device beeping]
I've got something.
Off Glendale Boulevard.
Just north of the river.
I'm zooming in the land sat.
Looks like
some kind of old factory.
Okay, Sparky,
we're northbound on..
On the Hollywood
to the Pasadena.
I'm calling the cavalry.
Strike Force David.
[dramatic music]
[static]
Sparky? Sparky?
- We out of range?
- We shouldn't be.
Better keep driving.
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
(Joe)
out of place, don't they?'
'Those limos look a tad
Come on, get up here.
You got that right.
- Hey, hey,
- w-what's the matter with you?
- Hey, what's wrong?
- What's wrong?
[barking]
Hey, come back here.
What the hell is going in?
'Hey, come here.'
[laughs]
Hey, listen,
if you can't reach Sparky
- contact David
- through the satellite link.
Look here, boy,
you be careful, you hear?
- 'Cause you ain't Superman
- and you damn sure
'ain't getting paid.'
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
(Nathaniel)
advanced weapon..'
'...US Army material command
'I know it's been a very long
journey for some of you.'
I would like to thank you all
for making the trip here.
I do believe
it will be worth your while.
With the help of my good friend,
Big Willy, here
I've already made quite a few
of these dandy little toys.
'You've all seen them
at work on TV.'
But tonight I'm going to give
you a live demonstration.
'And once you've seen it,
I'm sure you'll agree'
- 'that what we have to offer
- is the next..'
Excuse me.
[gunshot]
[glass shattering]
[groans]
Oh, so please welcome
Mr. Warm And Fuzzy himself.
Took you long enough.
Uh-uh-uh.
You might wanna
think about that.
You see, that's the difference
between us.
I'd kiss her sorry
crippled ass goodbye
and worry about myself.
Now, gentleman,
here's the deal.
I can supply you
with weapons like these
on a sort of permanent lease.
Lease?
I buy, mate. And that's flat.
- And you're welcome to do that,
- Mr. Weston.
But unfortunately, these weapons
are highly-sophisticated
electronic devices
'which require
specialized maintenance'
and recharging.
And only I can do that for you.
Only we.
[gunshot]
Only I.
That's blackmail.
That's business.
- How much?
- Millions.
You don't need our money.
You can steal all you want.
Uh, this isn't really
about money.
(Weston)
arm supplier to the world.
You'll be the illegal
You want power.
Now, there's an idea.
You gentleman think about this.
- Do you really wanna be
- the only ones
Without my kind of fire power
'when the rest of these
III?'
nice folks start World War
But before you answer that..
Get him out of here.
Let me give you that
little demonstration I promised.
You remember that bank mobile..
- '...and the boys in the
- 'hood..'
[laughs]
who have served their purpose
incidentally.
Ay, what's up with this,
lieutenant?
I always use rats
for the preliminary testing.
Oh, and, uh, Slats,
the hot dog..
- It was pork.
- Kick your ass..
[gunshot]
- Oh!
- Whoa!
- 'Watch it.'
- 'Hey, mate.'
Sparky, you read me?
Damn, we in deep stink here!
Got that right. Step away
from the truck, old man.
Damn. Damn! Damn! Damn!
You don't know
you?
who you messing with, do
- Come here, Lilly.
- Yes.
Yes. I owe you a big stake,
Lilly.
- (Nathaniel)
- 'Keep him quiet over there.'
'Okay, you've seen how
powerful'
these weapons are.
But, gentleman, now I have
developed a new weapon
- that is five times
- more powerful.
- (John)
- 'Only five times?'
- What do you got?
- A water pistol.
My hammer's got
more juice than that.
I find that hard to believe.
See for yourselves. I'll let
my hammer speak for itself.
Just hit it right there
on the bottom.
Don't turn the red switch.
She'll get too hot for you.
Really? We'll see about that.
I was planning to use you
as a demonstration, anyway.
Killing two birds
with one stone, as they say.
- Move it, y'all!
- Come on, come on! Go, go!
[dramatic music]
We're airborne.
Be there in 15!
Yeah, well, I hope
you make it in time.
They'll never make it.
- If he kills me,
- you'll all lose out.
We don't need your help anymore,
except as a target.
[groaning]
The red switch.
Well, you know
I've got to push the envelope.
[beeping]
[groans]
Yeah, I know you do.
- Kill him!
- Maybe not.
[explosions]
[groaning]
[indistinct shouting]
- 'This way, this way!'
- Johnny.
[gunshots]
[explosion]
[groaning]
- Why should you have
- all the fun?
[explosion]
Just get out of here quick.
This quick enough?
[instrumental music]
[gunshots]
[indistinct yelling]
[clanking]
- (male #14)
- 'Go!'
[explosion]
'Come on..'
[groans]
Ah!
Get out! Get out!
'Go on! Get out of here!'
- Come on, let's go!
- Yeah!
Nathaniel, give it up!
First let's see
what's behind door number two!
- My new best friend!
- Let me go!
You understand, Johnny?
- Success has never
- been enough for me.
'I need to see my enemy
panic, cower and fail.'
- So why don't you just
- back off?
- Martin and I are gonna take
- a little ride.
Guess again.
[Joe grunts]
[groaning]
[explosion]
Help!
(Martin)
Pick it up!
There's no way out!
[explosion]
Up there! Throw it! Quick!
- 'Throw it!'
- I never made these.
Oh, hey, bend your knees
and follow through.
Come on!
[dramatic music]
Uh..
Yes!
No!
[explosions]
Damn! Ugh!
Never saw my new toy, did you?
Mr. Steel, let's see how
your armor stands up to this.
- 'You're going
- to the scrap heap.'
Oh, no!
[groans]
(John)
Oh, no!
[clattering]
How do we get out of here?
Uncle Joe, here, here I am.
- Uncle Joe, are you alright?
- Ah..
[explosion]
Go! Come on.
[tires screeching]
[crashes]
Ah! Ah!
- Johnny?
- You Johnny, ain't you?
- Get in the van, quick.
- My own brother is Steel, yo!
- Yo, I wanna help.
- Shut up and get in the van.
Man, I could be Robin.
Yo, I could get a cape.
I could be like Dre.
You could be like Snoop.
- You wanna know
- what you can do to help?
What? Anything.
Don't tell grandma.
Get in the van, let's go.
[explosions]
We were lucky to get out.
Uh, ma'am..
[helicopter whirring]
- Alright, move, move, move!
- Move!
[indistinct yelling]
- Stop the engine.
Out of the car, lady,
and get your hands on your head.
- 'Now!'
- Let's go!
[indistinct yelling]
Break it up, break it up.
Colonel, this one's
willing to talk, sir.
Good work, soldier.
[man coughing]
I'm glad you called.
The SEAL squealed
and fingered Nathaniel.
- The coroner is still
- raking through the rubble
For his teeth.
The SEAL also gave us
another tape of the bank jobs
showing the gang kid
shooting down the helicopter.
You're in the clear, so, uh..
Keep him talking,
we don't have him yet.
So, uh, why don't you tell me
who you are behind the mask?
(John)
does it?'
'Doesn't really matter now,
- I've accomplished
- all I wanted to.
You won't be seeing me anymore.
- Wait a minute, wait a minute,
- we might be able to do
- Some good work together
- in the future.
I might even consider
letting you, uh
use that new hot Humvee.
- (John) - 'Colonel, colonel,
- Tracing this call'
- 'is a complete waste
- of your time.'
Your comm-data person
gonna think we're in..
- Cincinnati.
We got him. They're
at a diner in Cincinnati...
- Forget it.
- 'But, sir, I was... '
- 'That will be all, Nancy.'
- 'Yes, sir.'
Listen, Arnold, I know
this isn't your real voice.
'Tell me the truth, damn it.'
Is this you, Irons?
- (John) - 'Ooh, can't talk anymore,
- Colonel.'
'Phone might not be secure.'
I'll be seeing you around.
Peace.
[kids giggling]
(Joe)
al fresco guy anyhow, huh?
Hey, Odessa, just who is this
(Odessa)
and sit down.
Oh, Joe, you go on over there
- Use your mouth for something
- else besides wise crackin'.
(Joe)
Ooh, a-alright, alright.
(Martin)
today's special, please.
Um, grandma, I'll have
Think you need to find out
what it is first.
Lobster served out of the shell.
With sweet-potato cream sauce
garnished with crisp okra.
[chuckles]
Grandma Odessa, you are amazing.
No, I tell you what's amazing.
- All this stuff we hear
- on the news
About that, uh, steel man.
- Well, uh,
- tell me something, Odessa
How do you,
how do you feel about that guy?
I think anybody
would be mighty proud
to have him in their family.
(Joe)
about that, girl.'
'I think you're right
Now, I have a surprise
for everybody. Ha-ha-ha.
My piece de resistance.
Lay it on us, girl.
[chuckles]
- 'Yeah!'
- 'It's about time!'
Whoa!
You finally made your
harmony souffle.
Of course, I did.
[applauding]
- Hey!
- Ah, shh..
Not so loud.
They'll cave in.
Well, ain't that somethin'?
What a person can do
if they really
put their mind to it.
Especially, when you got
the right kind of help.
And I do like those
new wheelchair modifications.
You haven't seen
the best part yet.
[whirring]
- 'Ooh, look at that.'
- 'Oh.'
- (female #3)
- Look what's she doing.
[chuckling]
I love it, girl.
So do I.
- (Odessa)
- 'Oh...'
[laughing]
Yes! Oh..
[Odessa and Joe chuckling]
- ♪ Stand up ♪
♪ You're gonna do
what you gotta do ♪
♪ Come on come on stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ It's all I've got ♪
♪ It's all I've got to do ♪
♪ Ooh-hoo ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ It's time to take command ♪
♪ Come on come on stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ Because the future
is in your hands ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh steel yourself ♪
♪ That's when
you start to feel the power ♪
♪ And you know you're growing
stronger by the hour ♪
♪ I said stronger by the hour ♪
♪ Stronger by the hour ♪
♪ Some people say it's better
not to get involved ♪
♪ It's easier to let the problem
go unsolved yeah ♪
♪ They say when there's trouble
play it safe and walk away ♪
♪ But I know about that ♪
♪ Let me tell you what I'd say ♪
♪ I say stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ You gotta do
what you gotta do ♪
♪ Oh oh oh stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ 'Cause it's all I've got ♪
♪ It's all I've gotta do ♪
♪ Oh oh stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ It's time to take command ♪
♪ Time to take command ♪
♪ I would like you to stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ Because the future
is in your hand ♪
♪ Girl they say you can't win ♪
♪ So tell me what's the use? ♪
♪ The deck is stacked
you got no chance ♪
♪ You got no juice ♪
♪ But when the odds against you
can't get any higher ♪
♪ That's when it's time
to put your iron in the fire ♪
- ♪ Stand up ♪
♪ You're gonna do
what you gotta do ♪
♪ Come on come on stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ It's all I've got to ♪
♪ It's all I've got to do ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ It's time to take ♪
♪ Time to take command ♪
♪ Come on come on stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ Because the future
is in your hand ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ When you find yourself
with darkness all around you ♪
♪ All around you ♪
♪ Girl remind yourself ♪
♪ Your strength
will astound you ♪
♪ Oh steel yourself ♪
♪ That's when
you start to feel the power ♪
♪ And you know you're growing
stronger by the hour ♪
- ♪ I said stronger by the hour ♪
- ♪ Stronger by the hour ♪
♪ Hey hey yeah ♪
♪ Ooh stand up ♪
♪ You gotta stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ Come on come on get up now ♪
♪ Ooh stand up ♪
- ♪ You're gonna get up ♪
- ♪ Stand up ♪
♪ It's what you do yeah ♪
- ♪ Oh stand up ♪
- ♪ Hey yeah ♪
- ♪ You gotta get up from there ♪
- ♪ Stand up ♪
♪ Oh yeah yeah ♪
♪ Ooh stand up ♪
♪ You've got to stand up ♪
♪ Stand up ♪
♪ I want you to steel ♪
♪ Steel ♪
- ♪ Yourself ♪
- ♪ Put on the ♪
- ♪ Whole armor ♪
- ♪ Steel ♪
- ♪ Yourself ♪
- ♪ Put on the ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Whole armor ♪
♪ You gotta steel ♪
- ♪ Steel ♪
- ♪ Yourself ♪
- ♪ Steel yourself ♪
- ♪ In the midnight ♪
- ♪ Steel ♪
- ♪ Yourself ♪
♪ Yeah yourself ♪
- ♪ You're gonna steel ♪
- ♪ Steel ♪
- ♪ Yourself ♪
♪ You got to yourself ♪
♪ Steel ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Steel yourself ♪
- ♪ And just stand up ♪
- ♪ Stand up ♪
♪ Yay yay yay yay ♪
♪ Yay ♪
[instrumental music]