Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I'd like to be a saint...
but I feel so helpless.
Hello, child.
My little queen.
Oh, sweetheart, thank you.
Mom, I wish you would die.
- Therese!
- Therese, why do you say that?
I want you to go to heaven
and you have to die to get there
<< Unless the grain dies... <<
Normandy, France, 1877
The day Mom died...
I didn't cry,
and I haven't talked to anyone
of my feelings.
I watched and listened,
in silence.
Hail Mary, full of grace
May the Lord be with you,
You are blessed among women.
Blessed is the fruit of thy womb.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
Pray for us sinners
Now and on time
of our death, Amen.
Hail Mary, full of grace
May the Lord be with you
You are blessed among all women...
Blessed be the fruit of your womb.
Holy Mary Mother of God
Pray for us sinners...
Ah, there you are, my child.
Come on. Come on.
Pauline is my new Mum.
After Mom died...
this world seemed sad to me...
and I was dreaming about the heavens.
But when I compared myself
to the saints...
I could see that the distance
between them and me...
was the same distance
that between a mountain
and a tiny speck of sand.
My little queen! Therese!
A fish!
- What a beautiful trout.
- What generosity!
- Thank you. Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
- Let's meet in the visiting room.
- Yes, Sister.
Mr. Martin, you spoil us.
You really do.
I could never
enough to give you thanks.
Thank you for your prayers.
And your daughters are growing up.
I recognize Pauline...
Marie...
Leonie...
Celine.
And Therese is that big girl?
Yes, my mother.
- I'll clean it up.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
It's all right, child.
That's a holy image for you.
Thank you, Mother.
Daddy! Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
What is it, Therese?
Nothing.
What's going on?
Tell me.
I had a horrible dream.
I've done so many sins, Daddy.
You?
And what are these sins, my little one?
You really want me to tell you?
Of course you did.
I took the biggest
piece of cake yesterday.
Oh, I see. I see. Is there anything else?
Oh, yeah, Dad.
I didn't pack my things
when Marie asked me.
I kept reading that horrible novel.
I think God is punishing me.
I have bad thoughts.
Listen to me, Therese.
Don't take your scruples too seriously.
Confess them and forget them.
Jesus forgives you.
I think he's even smiling
of your peccadilloes.
Maybe you're right.
Therese...
sleep.
In nominates Patris, and Filii,
and Spritus Sancti. Amen.
I don't want to get up.
Come on, I let you sleep,
but we have to go now.
Why do I have to go?
I hate school.
I can't stand
Sister Scholastica.
She's an old witch.
She can die.
Don't say that!
Oh, the sister's pet.
You think you're so pious
and so good with your curls.
I'll tell you what I think of you.
You're spoiled and rotten and no one
can't smell you.
Except maybe your family of slaves.
That's not true! You're lying!
That's right. Everybody's...
is laughing at you.
Natural Law is the law that
God has written in the hearts of men.
That's how he's capable of
to distinguish right from wrong.
Who can tell me now what...
other law God gave us?
Yes, Therese?
Divine Positive Law?
All right, fine.
And both parties
of Divine Positive Law are... ?
The New and the Old Law.
That's it.
I want all of them...
except Therese Martin,
were going home tonight
turn the page on the difference
between Divine Law and Natural Law.
Let us pray.
Blessed be the Father, the Son
and the Holy Spirit
now and forever,
Amen.
ln Nomine Patris and Filii
and Spiritu Sancti. Amen.
You may go.
A thousand thanks.
It must be hard to be so perfect.
It's so good to be all together here.
Daddy, I wish I could have seen you
dancing with Mommy.
You must have been
a beautiful couple.
We've never danced...
Your mother and I. We were
probably too pious.
I regret it now.
She was so graceful.
Very, very graceful.
Dad, have you thought about it?
You told me you'd think about it.
- To what?
- At school, Dad.
I don't want to go back.
But you have to go to school,
how are you going to learn?
Pauline can teach me,
I promise to be studious.
Pauline, are you sure about this?
It would be fun, and I know
that she'd be happier...
and that she'd work better.
Well, that's understood.
Let's give it a try.
until the end of the year.
Thank you, Daddy.
Thank you!
Let's review your Bible verses.
Have you been working?
I've recited them 50 times.
I think I know them.
Saint Mark 10, verses 13 â 16<<
They brought him children
so that he could touch them.
And the disciples ...
- pushed them away...
- and the disciples pushed them away...
<< Jesus, seeing this, was indignant
and says to them:
Let the little children come to me.
Don't stop them.
For the Kingdom of God
is for their fellow man.
I'm telling you the truth...
Whoever does not receive the kingdom
of God like a little child...
will not enter it. <<
Wonderful!
Am I winning a prize?
You win a prize.
Your tortoiseshell wallet!
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
I know you love him.
...it's yours.
Oh thank you thank you!
You're the sweetest
sister of the world!
No, it's you.
But I corrected
your algebra lesson.
Oh, no, you don't. How was it?
Two strikes. Pretty good math.
Dad, did you hear that?
Only two faults.
All right, fine. Keep it up.
Try not to overdo it.
you two have fun.
Oh no, we're very serious.
I'm convinced of that.
Let's get to work, girls.
You want to stay with me
for the next chapter,
or do you want to go upstairs
read it quietly?
I want to stay with you.
I could get eaten up
by a second-degree equation...
you'll have to catch me.
and brings me back to the surface.
All you have to do is scream if they...
attack you and I'll save you.
Mom, I love you so much.
Therese...
What's on your mind?
I was thinking of the faraway desert...
where we'll always be together.
I have to finish it by Thursday.
and I'm only at the bottom of it.
Can you help me?
you draw flowers so well.
If you want, I can try.
Pauline, where have you been?
I went to the convent
bring fresh bread to the sisters.
How's your painting coming?
I haven't made much progress,
I only painted the background.
I'm trying to give him
an air of spring.
idyllic and pastoral.
That's exactly right.
The colors are good.
But look at the perspective
from your cottage.
If you extend the line
from the roof like this...
you see how that includes
in the landscape?
Oh that's much better!
Beloved mother I still want
to be with your son Jesus...
like a little child.
- You're gonna have to tell him.
- I know we have to tell him.
I don't know what I'm waiting for.
She's not a little girl anymore.
- She'll take it well.
- Maybe she will.
But it will be hard for her.
What did Mother Mary say
of Gonzaga?
That I had no reason
to delay my entry.
The date is set.
It's for the 2nd in October.
So soon?
Pauline, I envy you.
Therese, I found our desert.
Did you find him?
A beautiful desert...
full of roses...
where Jesus is waiting for me.
All I want...
is to be alone with him.
I'm going into Carmel
next month, Therese.
You're not going to wait for me.
No.
Does such a place really exist?
Yes, my darling.
I lost Pauline.
Thank you. Thank you.
Goodbye, Celine.
Bye, Daddy.
Leonie,
God bless you.
Bye, Daddy.
When Pauline left me,
life was no longer...
that separation and suffering
continuous,
and I fell into a
deep melancholy.
She seems so happy in her letters!
He doesn't miss us at all.
It'll be good to see her anyway.
Oh the fruit!
Daddy, did you take them?
Don't worry.
It's at the front of the carriage.
Therese, do you feel bad?
It's just my head.
It feels heavy to me.
Aren't you coming, Therese?
I'll wait in the carriage.
Are you sure?
Pauline's going to be so disappointed.
I can't. I can't. I want to rest.
It's going to get better.
Let her rest, Celine.
My little queen.
Are you feeling better, my darling?
Yes, Daddy, thank you.
I beg your pardon.
It's all right, Therese.
Pauline's got it all figured out.
How's she doing?
She's happy and healthy.
She misses you very much.
What did she say about the food, Dad?
Let's see, now... Let the roast chicken from
He missed victory...
but that she was feasting
of bread and cheese.
Feasts, I doubt it, but...
she didn't look hungry.
When I saw her with her veil...
she looked much older.
She reminded me of your dear mother.
I was delirious for two weeks,
and I didn't seem to be recovering.
Blessed Virgin, please,
heal my little girl.
Mommy!
Dr. Notta says
that it's very serious.
He's never seen anything like it.
last so long.
Go away!
Holy Mother of God...
I'm begging you...
Have pity on me.
Daddy... (Sighs)
I'm hungry.
Are you sure you want to come in?
Yes, I'm sure of it.
Hello, Mum!
You're very skinny, sweetheart.
I'm told you're cured, but...
you need to rest
and heal you well.
I'm fine. I'm fine,
I'm telling you.
If only we could not
so worried about me.
Well, all right.
How are your battles going
with the equations?
It's hard.
I persevere.
My little hermit.
The desert is here,
isn't that right, Pauline?
And there I will find my beloved.
Yes. He's here. He's waiting.
Then I'll come to him.
Write to me, girls,
check in.
Soon, two of my sisters
were leaving the family nest.
Mary entered Carmel.
And be good.
God bless you.
And Leonie among the Franciscan Sisters
of the Blessed Sacrament,
I love you both.
From our big, happy family...
There wasn't much left...
than the two younger ones.
I just don't understand
why everyone's leaving.
That's what kids do.
They always leave.
Don't cry, little one.
The doves must leave the nest.
You and Celine
will also fly away one day.
God had a little miracle in store for me
to allow me to mature.
This took place during a
unforgettable Christmas Eve.
That night...
I have received the grace
to leave my childhood behind.
It was a beautiful mass.
But being up till two o'clock
in the morning, it's a little long for me.
I'm going to bed.
Celine, there's nothing in the slippers!
Oh, that's right, the slippers...
Go upstairs and tell Santa Claus...
can bring the gifts.
But hurry, it's late.
Thank God it's the last time.
She's a little old for that.
In an instant, I changed.
I realized that I had to forget myself...
and make other people happy.
Therese?
What's going on?
Celine...
I'm not the same.
I've decided not to cry.
Merry Christmas, Celine.
I had an immense thirst
to save souls.
I was burning to tear out souls...
great sinners...
to the flames of hell.
We were talking about a terrible murderer...
sentenced to death.
He seemed certain that he was going to...
to die without repentance.
I wanted to save his soul
at all costs.
My God, I'm sure
you'll forgive Pranzini.
I thought it was...
even if he went to his death without
give a sign of repentance...
or without confessing.
Lord Jesus, I trust
absolute in your pity.
But make him repent,
that would be a consolation to me.
Please, Lord...
he's my first child!
Father give me the crucifix.
Pray for me when I'm dead.
My son, God will not abandon you.
Celine...
What am I going to do?
You're gonna follow your heart.
He'll think it's because of Pauline.
It's not, is it?
What's more...
he won't be alone. I'll be with him.
Don't worry.
What is it, my little queen?
Tell me.
I don't want to hurt your feelings.
Don't be afraid.
I have to fly away.
You're young enough to take
such a serious decision.
Maybe in a few years,
when you're older...
No, Daddy. I'll be right there.
Jesus is calling me to the monastery.
I can't resist His Love.
All I want...
is for you to be happy,
and please God.
Look at this little flower.
Imagine how God loves him,
for creating it...
and keep her alive in the moss.
It still has its roots.
Maybe it's his destiny
to live in another land...
more fertile than moss.
Daddy, thank you.
Let's go ask the bishop.
And if he objects
we'll ask the Pope.
Mr. Martin l Nice to see you.
Please, sit down.
What can I do for you, my child?
My lord, permission to enter
to Carmel immediately.
Jesus is calling me, and I can't resist...
longer to His Love.
How old are you, my little girl?
I'm fifteen years old, Monsignor.
You look like a big girl!
She pulled her hair up for you.
Oh, I see. I see.
You've longed for a long time...
get into Carmel?
Yes, my lord, a very long time.
Mr. Martin, don't worry.
I'm with you against
your daughter's whim.
I can assure you, my lord,
that this is not a child's whim.
I'm convinced that God
called her.
That's highly unusual.
I need approval
of the superior of the monastery...
before you even think about it.
He already said no.
I'll talk to him again,
We'll see what I can do.
Thank you, Monsignor.
Don't worry. Everything's going to be all right.
Once we get to Rome,
I begged Jesus for a miracle.
I prayed that the Pope
accept my request.
But when the final day arrived...
They told us that he was defended...
to talk to the Holy Father.
Speak up.
Most Holy Father...
...I have a huge favour to ask you.
In honor of your Jubilee...
let me come in
in Carmel at the age of 15.
I don't get it.
Holy Father, this child wants to enter
in Carmel at the age of 15.
The superiors are in the process
to consider the issue.
Do what your superiors tell you
Holy Father, if you say yes,
everyone will agree!
Mademoiselle Martin,
pull yourself together.
Come on, you're going in,
God willing.
But, Holy Father...
After this great disappointment
I was filled with sadness.
But I never gave up hope
that God would grant my wish.
- Good morning, sir.
- Morning, sir.
Thank you
It's for you! The Bishop's seal!
Come on!
Open it.
<< Dear Miss Martin.
I am pleased to inform you
that after seeing the superiors...
I've decided to let you in.
at the Lisieux Carmel...
at the unusual age of 15.
However...
in view of the extraordinary circumstances
of your situation...
your entry will have to wait three months...
until Lent.
At first, I didn't know how
I could handle waiting three months.
But I was so grateful to God...
that I gave myself
to a life of sacrifice.
It's not that I'm accomplishing
great things.
My sacrifices consisted of small
acts that no one noticed.
I can't express how much
this waiting...
left me with fond memories.
Daddy, I love you so much.
You know how happy I am,
and yet...
I'm heartbroken to leave you.
Life is so short, my darling.
We will be reunited...
for all eternity...
very soon.
Go, my queen.
Go, I bless you.
Deo Gratias.
I'm here forever.
You anoint my forehead with oil
my cup runneth over
Glory be to the Father,
to the Son,
and to the Holy Spirit.
Now
and forever
Amen.
It's extremely important...
to clean up the choir.
I don't want to see a squall
of dust when this is over.
Yes, sister, I'll do my best.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
I know you'd rather have been
with your sisters...
But the Mother thinks you'll be
more useful here with me.
Sister Augustine, I'm
very happy to be here.
Let's get to work. I'll be back in a minute.
in a few minutes.
Sister Therese!
how negligent of you to break that vase...
and then cover it up.
I'm surprised at you.
But Sister I...
Yes, Sister, I'll do more
be careful next time.
This little victory of will...
cost me a lot.
I saw that when I was doing
my duty without flinching...
no one was paying attention.
But every mistake was
immediately noticed.
<< But the English attacked
...and the French retreated.
"" "Don't be afraid to hit them.
shouted Jeanne.
"" "Their defeat is in your hands.
<< On the Levis Bridge.
Jeanne was always fighting.
A whole troop attacked him.
"" Surrender! they shouted
"I swore an oath and gave my faith
to another," she says bravely.
"" and vowed to keep my promise. ''
<< But she resisted in vain.
They grabbed his clothes...
knocked her off her horse
and captured her. <<
Not long after I came in...
the health of our dear Father
began to decline.
We lost him little by little.
His mind, always so clear and sharp...
became foggy and dark.
You take the beater...
and you beat the laundry, hard, like this.
- Yes, Sister.
- I want to see you do it.
No, harder, like this.
Just like that?
Yeah, well, sort of.
My striving for perfection...
were greeted by more than
of thorns than roses.
Pleasing God and the other sisters
was difficult.
I knew how to be a very small soul...
who could only offer
little things to God.
and I was wondering if it was enough.
You can't not see...
that our cloisters are being swept away
by a 15-year-old child.
Sister...
clean this up,
and pay more attention to the future.
Then I found him on the floor.
That's how he died, poor Papa.
I was only five years old.
I must have grown up fast, that's for sure.
I was neither coddled nor spoiled.
I never have a single moment
doubted my calling.
But suddenly, to the old lady of
...to take my final vows...
I was overcome by fear and doubt.
My mother! My mother!
I need to speak to you urgently,
do you have a moment?
Of course, my boy,
What's up?
What's going on?
I can no longer avoid
to face the truth.
What's happened?
I just realized
that I don't have the vocation.
I have to go back to the world...
and not stay here at Carmel
and do what I want.
I'm worthless, I fail
...to all my duties.
My dear girl!
God didn't bring you here
to take away your calling.
Tomorrow is the day
of your final vows.
Are you happy here, child?
You can leave if you want.
But do you want to stay?
I find this life difficult, but...
my heart grew here.
Let me tell you what I think.
You're a simple soul, child.
and while you're growing up in love...
you'll become even simpler.
The closer you get to God...
the simpler you get.
I don't need to grow up.
I need to become
smaller and smaller and weaker.
Now go get ready...
to your profession of faith.
Yeah, I remember his hot chocolate.
Sister, your altar cloths...
are so pretty!
How do you do it?
I have years of experience.
Embroidery requires a lot
patience and skill.
I can see that.
Not everybody gets it.
I was wondering if you
could teach me.
To you?
If you have time.
Maybe I could teach you
simple points.
Thank you, Sister,
I'd like that very much.
>> Let me come to me...
little children. <<
I finally found in these words
my own way...
to become a saint.
It's ten to six.
I need someone to
take me to the mess hall.
Let me help you, Sister.
I don't need to reach
the level of the great saints.
Here you go, Sister.
I just have to be myself...
a small child.
- Be careful.
- Yes, Sister.
- Easy, you're pulling me!
- Forgive me, Sister.
I'll try like this.
It's too abrupt!
Give me your arm.
I'm not made of wood, you know.
Well, let's go.
On winter nights when
I was doing my job...
I heard music.
and I imagined a ballroom...
filled with elegant young ladies
conversing with each other...
trying hard
of compliments...
and doing mundane things.
Stop it! You're going too fast!
I'm out of breath.
I'll go slower.
But the music I heard
was the music of my heart.
and I wouldn't have traded
one minute of humble charity...
against a thousand years of festivities
and social events.
What are you looking at that's so beautiful?
- Get moving!
- Forgive me, Sister.
That night I felt
such love...
that I couldn't have
do better...
that if I was leading Jesus himself.
Thank you very much, Sister Therese.
Thank you, child.
You're very kind to help
an old lady like me.
Sister Therese!
There you are.
I've been looking all over for you.
I'm so happy to see you!
Could you help me?
Sister Vincent needs it
in the kitchen.
You don't seem to have
a lot of energy.
I don't know what I'd get
done without you.
Tell me, Sister Therese.
what do you see in me?
Every time I see you,
you smile.
I'm smiling because I'm
Good to see you.
Can he hear us?
I don't know about that.
I talk to him all the time...
and sometimes he shakes my hand.
Oh Celine, what a burden to you.
Daddy.
You remember our
evenings in the garden?
Mom used to make lace...
and you were gardening
while we were playing.
I wish we were
all together again!
I have to go, he's very tired.
I'll bring him back soon.
It's getting very difficult.
He seems to be declining every day.
Take care, sweetie.
Bye, Daddy.
Bye, Daddy dearest.
I love you, Daddy.
Heaven.
Must weigh a ton.
Here, let me give you a hand.
It's not too heavy for me.
After Dad died...
My dear little sister was free
to enter Carmel...
She's wanted him for so long.
What a joy for me to live
under the same roof again...
and to share the joys and sorrows
of my childhood companion.
Ah, the Martin sisters,
how bourgeois you are!
You should all
put you to work...
instead of wasting your time
...to play actresses.
Wait till you see
our program tonight.
It was so realistic!
I can't wait to see
the developed photo.
Let's hurry, we have to
be ready by 7:30.
We must surprise our Mother,
she doesn't suspect a thing.
Another picture of the actress
and the author please.
The rest of you can go.
You're beautiful!
One more.
I can hardly wait.
We have to tie him up.
There, that's good.
A little higher.
No, get a little more
...to the left.
There, that's better.
- Are you all right?
- Must be the smoke.
It's all right now.
Jesus Christ.
What's your response
to my follies?
Is there a smaller soul,
more helpless than mine?
Not all of them are apostles...
Isn't that right?
Not all of them are prophets.
Aren't they?
Not all of them teach
Isn't that right?
Not all have the gift of healing...
And yet they desire
sincerely have gifts...
And I'll show you
a more excellent way.
We can kiss...
faith, hope, and love...
The three of us...
But most importantly...
is love.
Well, I mean...
I feel at peace.
I understand that the Corps
of Christ has a heart...
and this heart burns with love.
At the heart of the Church
my Mother...
I will be Love.
And so it will be all...
and so my dream
will come true.
Fire!
Water!
Sister, quickly,
help me!
Cough please.
Try to get some rest.
How long has this been going on?
For several months now.
I must confess...
that she coughs a lot, but
I didn't think it was a big deal.
Sister Pauline...
this is an advanced case
of tuberculosis.
Oh no!
God have mercy.
I had no idea.
My beloved.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'm gonna die, Mom.
I know, I know, I know, I know.
Jesus allowed my soul
or invaded by a thick night.
The thought of heaven...
once so sweet...
is nothing but torment.
Everything I wanted so badly
has disappeared.
All I have in front of me
is death...
and emptiness.
I can't eat anymore...
and I want all kinds of things.
A chocolate éclair for example...
I didn't expect to suffer this much.
I'm suffering like a little child.
I'll see you again...
and your heart will rejoice...
and no one's gonna take that away from you.
You'll see.
I will send to Earth...
a shower of roses.
May God in his mercy...
delivers you from all your sins.
God save you...
and loves you, gives you eternal life.
Amen.
Sister, Corpus Domini
nostri Jesu Christi custodiat...
Father, she can't swallow anymore.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Mama... (Sighs)
Mom, I'm suffocating.
Oh, my darling.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I love God.
Yes, he's very good.
My God will never forget me.
He never gave up on me.
My God won't abandon me.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Anything you want...
But have mercy on me!
My mother.
Is it agony?
I'm gonna die, aren't I?
Yes, my dear, it's agony.
I love her.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I love You!
Heaven.
My mission is about to begin...
That others love God
just the way I like it.
My Heaven will happen on Earth...
until the end of the world.
Yes, I want my heaven...
is to do good on Earth.
After Therese Martin's death in 1897,
the Carmelites published his autobiography...
which became a spiritual classic
all over the world.
She's loved by millions
of people of all faiths.
In fact, Mother Teresa of Calcutta...
took the name Therese...
and dedicated his mission
â << The little way <<.
<< Therese's little way of loving...
God can be followed by all...
and many miracles attributed to his
intercession confirm his promise:
<< I'll send a shower of roses to Earth. <<