(upbeat marching music)
* Storm is headed to this town injustice, greed and pride
* The innocent will bear the brunt
* Can no one turn this tied
* Battle is of light and dark will good or evil reign
* The railroad or the widow
* Her loss will be their pain
* What will she do does no one seen tragedy, tragedy
* Who will turn this wrong to right
* God is watching day and night
* He will win this fight
* He's the widow's might
* A faithful little woman
* The widow prays for strength
* The sheriff wants the railroad
* He'll go to any lane
* She'll pray for our defender
* For the self and for her land
* Send dangers to protect her
* God show your mighty hand
* What will she do does no one see tragedy, tragedy
* Who will turn this wrong to right
* God is watching day and night
* He will win this fight
* Because he's the widows might
(upbeat marching music)
- Hi there.
- Gator, what are you doing here?
- Whoa. Uh.
Excuse me. Whoa.
(door crashing)
- Cut.
(slow ominous music)
- John, we're running out of time.
We need to shoot this last scene.
- Let's do it.
Hi.
My name is John Moore.
I live here in Ringer County.
And my friends and I produce the film you're watching now.
When we first started,
we didn't realize how big this would all become.
This thing began when Jim Morton decided to ...
... nah, just.
- Tell it from the beginning.
- It all began about two months ago,
in your average Tuesday afternoon.
Hi there.
John here, on your average Tuesday afternoon.
Cameron is behind the camera this time.
I'm here to introduce you to our families.
So, you've seen a lot of us in different videos
but you don't really know who is who.
This is my youngest brother Gator.
- Hi.
- You may be wondering why
a 10-year-old is wearing an eye patch.
But it's due to a little known thing called refracto,
reflecto--
- Refractive Amblyopia.
- Exactly.
Which basically means severe lazy eye.
- The patch is covering my good eye
and forces my lazy eye to get back to work.
This ain't no union head.
(water splashing)
- And that's Jack and David,
two of my other brothers.
They're very helpful sometimes.
Cut it.
* These are the only words
* Until I write the rhyme
* These words are for my song
* Just 60 seconds long
- That's beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Well, that story may have been a little off topic
but we had to know.
- Had to know what?
- If they could walk on water
by putting Jell-O in the swimming pool.
- Well I remember that.
The chlorine ruin the flavor though.
- This is my sweet sister Reagan.
She loves music, and especially singing,
much like Cameron's sister, Angela.
Cut.
Angela, I'm telling you.
- And I'm telling you too.
Wait, what do we tell her?
- Learn to love the camera.
It's your friend.
- Breakfast is about done everyone.
Wash up.
- So, what do you guys working on now?
- That's a short film for the blog.
The idea is to introduce our family to the fans.
- The fans?
- Well, whoever watches our films.
- Yeah.
This project really doesn't have a point.
- But people will watch it.
See, they think our short productions are good.
- Especially our latest one.
- Should we tell them?
- What?
(soft calm music)
- Dear Cinema Blog Productions,
concerning your submission to the first stage
of the American View Finer Film Festival,
we have reviewed your film
and are pleased to inform you
that your film is a semifinalist.
(family applauding)
And, and, and!
And it will be screened at the Royal Oak Star Cinema
in Dallas, Texas.
Finalists in the local level competition
will then produce a new film
for the state level competition.
Congratulations.
We look forward to seeing you at the festival.
- Well, congratulations.
- Hey, good job, guys.
- Hey, who knows,
this could be our big break.
- There's a lot of history in Ringer.
And with recent surges of industry combined
with how a construction and development,
it would likely continue its record setting pace of growth.
Who knows what the future may hold for the citizens
of Ringer County?
(crowd applauding)
- And now ladies and gentlemen,
the producer of the film, Vince Warner.
(crowd applauding)
And now for our last contestant,
Cinema Blog Productions.
- Here we go.
(upbeat music)
- Hello?
- How can I help you, young lady?
- Well, I have a mystery.
* We park in our driveways
* We drive in our parkways
* Whoever thought of that
* What were they thinking
* What we're they drinking
* Did you see the Braille sign
* driving through the drive-through
* Whoever thought of that
* What were they thinking
* What were they drinking
* Somehow it seems this world is confused
* By the names that they give
* And the turns that they use
* Through one lazy eye, it appears that they see
* A world of their own that is different indeed
* What will the answer be
* Who would solve the mystery
* Let's look at apartments
* They should be apart but built so closely
* Whoever thought of that
* What were they thinking
* What were they drinking
* And there's a ship where there's cargo in the car
* With the shipment
* Whoever thought of that
* What were they thinking
* What were they drinking
* Somehow it seems this world is confused by the names
* That they give and the terms that they use
* Through one lazy eye
* It appears that they see
* A world on their own that is different indeed
* What will the answer be
* Who will solve the mystery
(crowd cheering)
- Well?
- I'll take the case.
- Thank you.
I knew you would understand.
(crowd applauding)
- And now the creators of "Lazy Eye",
Mr. John Moore and Cameron Cavillo.
(crowd applause)
Gentlemen, that was fantastic.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
- So tell me, how long have you been on film?
- Well, it's been a hobby of ours for a few years now,
mostly short films for the internet.
You can do a lot with scotch tape and glue.
(crowd laughing)
- Well, you gentlemen are doing a great job.
- Thank you. - So, keep it up.
(crowd applauding)
- Good morning. How are you today?
- Hey Wally, how are you?
- Good. Very good.
Oh, it looks like it's time for a break.
So, I heard you did well last night.
- We sure did.
Wait, how did you know?
- Oh, you guys, you're just very talented.
And I saw you cheering through the window.
I promise, I don't read your mail.
I use logic.
- Hi, Wally.
Any news from the Mortons?
- I just talked to them.
They're just settling in.
Did you hear about Widow Jackson?
- Nerd.
- No?
It's terrible, I'll tell you.
Absolutely terrible.
That poor helpless woman.
She's gonna lose her home through ties for closure
because she can't pay her taxes.
- You don't mean Grace Jackson,
Robbie Jackson's wife?
- Yeah, Grace Jackson.
I deliver over there from Scott's Bessy.
- She's not really gonna lose her home now?
I mean, somebody is doing something about this, right?
- Well, not that I know about.
Well, I got to go, guys.
It was good talking to you.
See you.
- Poor Grace.
She's such a sweet lady.
- Hey Ange,
do you know how to get to her place?
- All the taxes here
are being getting worst and worst.
For a long time,
Robbie was a good provider.
And we had a good savings.
But it's running out fast.
Our boys would help
but they're both in the military.
They really can't do much.
- What about your church?
- Oh, they're wonderful people.
They help with a lot.
And I know I'd never be without a place to stay.
The problem is this new highway.
Overnight,
they say my land is worth a fortune.
And the taxes are based on that.
- This is ridiculous.
It's got to be some kind of mistake.
But I can't believe it's gone unnoticed this long.
- I've done everything I know.
I've called and wrote the mayor,
I even wrote a letter to the governor.
- I've heard of things like this before,
but right here in Ringer?
- The politicians don't care.
- No, I've met Mayor Warner.
He's a great guy.
He would do something if he knew about this.
- Yeah, why don't you talk to him, John?
Set a big, great lesson in reality.
- Hey guys, I'm busy right now.
Can we reschedule this?
- This will take just a minute.
- Okay. What's on your mind?
- Grace Jackson.
- Sorry, that name doesn't mean anything to me.
- Well, she has written you letters.
Her property taxes are outrageous,
and she can't afford to keep her home at these rates.
- Is that the widow down by the new highway?
- Yeah.
- Okay, I know who you're talking about.
That's really too bad.
Is she gonna sell that place?
- Well, no.
It's her home.
And besides, that's not the issue.
The recent appraisal has skyrocketed her taxes.
And her house isn't even worth that.
- But the property is.
In fact just for commercial development alone,
the property is worth a fortune.
And putting businesses along that highway
will be terrific for the city.
It's unfortunate that some people are against that,
but it helps keep the balance.
- Balance?
That doesn't sound like balance.
It sounds like good for you and bad for Mrs. Jackson.
- Gator.
- Yeah?
- I was gonna say be polite
but I agree with you.
- Well, why is he here anyway?
- Well, I needed a cute kid
to get pass your secretary.
- Look, if you guys wanna bring me
a feasible solution to this,
then I'll be willing to look at it.
But I'm really busy.
And next time,
be sure to set an appointment, please.
- Come on.
- You call that justice?
Power corrupts, pure and simple.
Who is buying you off, Mr. Warner?
- Things didn't go too well, huh?
- No.
The man is heartless.
He seems to think that losing your home
is the equivalent of getting kicked out of your apartment.
Well, let's get to work.
- What?
- The ink jet printer is mightier than the sword.
- Flyers.
Hundreds, even thousands of flyers.
By tomorrow afternoon,
half the city will be up and arms for our cause.
- Sir, would you like a flyer?
Ma'am, how about a quick read?
Ma'am, would you like a flyer?
Hey sir, would you like a flyer?
Pick one flyer.
- Hey, may I have a flyer?
- Sure.
Yeah. Yeah.
Take two, three. Here.
In fact, give one to all your friends and relatives.
- That's ok, I just need one.
- Okay. Well, thank you.
Be sure to visit the website.
- Yeah. Thanks, kid.
- See John,
there is hope for Mrs. Jackson.
Hey, that's 24 cents of ink and paper.
That could have gone to pay the taxes.
- Hey.
(soft music)
- John,
what exactly are property taxes?
- That's where the government charges you
for stuff you already own.
- That's kinda stupid.
- Yeah.
And the harder you work,
the more valuable they say your stuff is,
the more they charge you.
- Well, why can't dad
just pay for Mrs. Jackson's taxes?
- Even if we did pay the taxes,
it would only help things for a little while.
- Why?
- Because they charge you for the same stuff every year.
- Well, wait,
they've never charged me for any of my stuff.
- No.
Just the big stuff,
houses, cars, things like that.
That's why dad's been speaking out against it for so long.
Politicians think they're helping people,
but they're hurting the people they tax.
And some people end up losing their homes
like Mrs. Jackson.
- Are you guys gonna stay up there all night?
- Hey.
- So how did you guys do?
- We gave out less than 40 flyers.
- 30 of which went to a guy with a smoothie,
who turned them into paper airplanes
and flew them off the bank building on 8th and Main.
- 8th and Main?
How do you know that?
- The only legitimate person who took a flyer
was a policeman.
- Who, after taking a flyer,
walked down to 8th and Main
saw the paper airplanes,
turned around, walked straight back to us
and wrote us a ticket.
- Maybe we're going about this all wrong.
- The problem isn't the format, it's the material.
Here.
"Fellow citizens of Ringer,
"there is an issue of pressing consequence
"in our fair county,
"one which beckons our utmost attention."
We might as well have written a page from the dictionary.
"Boring, to make a whole
"or the act of making someone bored."
- All right, that's it.
- Get in.
- Go. Go.
Go.
(laughing)
(classical music)
(door bell ringing)
- Vince?
- Uncle Sam.
- Come in.
How can I help you?
- I just wanted to remind you
about the interview tomorrow.
- Yes.
- Anything in specific you'd like to talk about?
The Widow Jackson?
- These guys were just in my office the other day.
Let's focus on plans for city expansion.
- Sure.
- You know, it really doesn't matter anyway.
This election is in the bank.
- Hmm?
- Well, between my history and your press.
- Don't count your chickens before they hatch, uncle.
(classical music)
- What about a Noir detective story?
- Yeah.
It's pretty cliche, really.
It don't help Mrs. Jackson at all.
- Well, what would you suggest?
- I think we should just stick with something musical.
- Yeah. It's got to go way beyond
our previous films though.
- What about a remake of "Pirates of Penzance"?
It's musical, comedic,
and I can wear my eye patch as a pirate.
- I don't wanna do a comedy again.
It seems like a copout.
I've got it!
Aren't you supposed to yell "four" or something?
Gentlemen, we're dealing with a conflict here
that is inherently American
like apple pie or baseball.
In the world of cinema,
what is the American icon?
- Cute little kids.
- Puppies.
- Boston Tea Party.
- Cars.
- Apple pie.
- Baseball. - Baseball.
- Cowboys.
- So, what's the story?
- It's a musical western
which outlines Mrs. Jackson's situation
and shows these high level thieves
to be exactly what they are,
a high level thieves.
- Perfect.
- I'm happy because it's a musical,
you're happy because it's a western,
and we're all happy because it helps Mrs. Jackson.
- I'll write it up now.
- Mayor Warner is on it too.
And after reading this,
I think we might find it very interesting.
- "Sam Warner, uncontested in political race."
- Sam Warner is four-time mayor or Ringer City,
and wildly recognized as the single most influential man
in Ringer County.
And we're with him in his home today.
Good afternoon, Mayor.
- Good afternoon, Vince.
How are you?
- Well, big news about Mr. Trent today.
- Yes.
I was surprised he dropped down.
Mr. Trent is a fine man
and I expected him to do well in the race.
- Now, you're a very seasoned politician.
Do you feel that Mr. Trent dropped out of the race
because he was intimidated by your political experience?
- Well, I did think he had a good shot at it.
I mean, I don't have a monopoly on the mayorship.
- You have been the most popular mayor of Ringer to-date.
I would venture to say that any candidate wanting
to come up against you would have to have
an incredibly strong platform.
Speaking of which,
what is your campaign platform currently?
- Well, with the major developments on the southern side
of the county we're hoping to--
- I'm not voting for him.
- You're just not gonna vote this year?
- On the contrary,
I think we all need to vote for a candidate
that understand the principles that create a free society.
We got to find him first.
And I think I may know the perfect candidate.
- Well, let's make a movie.
(dramatic music)
- We'll be taping as you read through your lines.
It's a western, so there are several parts,
we got a cowboy, a balladeer,
a sheriff.
What would you be trying out for?
- I was thinking about the sheriff.
- Okay. Okay. Very good.
Well, go ahead and take a seat,
relax, give us your natural rendition to the piece.
I'll be your reader for the scene, okay?
- Action.
- You'll never get away with this.
- This is my town.
A railroad means this could be a boom town,
a spot on the map.
I'm not letting some old woman
take that chance away from me.
- Cut. Cut.
Thank you.
(bright comedic music)
Are there any other parts you wanna try out for?
- No.
- And action.
- You'd better back down.
I'm not gonna give in, Sheriff.
This isn't a matter of money,
it's a matter of freedom, pure and simple.
- This home is important to me.
It's all I've got (laughs).
- It's not an issue of fairness,
it is an issue, no.
It is an issue of fairness.
It is an issue of justice,
so don't you see?
- Great.
So, which one of you will be auditioning?
- Us? No, not us.
- Ryan wants to be in the movie.
Don't you, Ryan?
- Hello.
- Hi there.
- I was born a cowboy,
and I'm gonna defend our freedom to the death.
(laughing)
- I wanna try the sheriff lines as well.
- Come on, son.
Say your lines.
- Do it, Seth.
Just like we practiced with daddy.
Say, "You're under arrest."
- Under arrest.
- Isn't he great?
- I have to admit, he's the best so far.
- I find my self discouraged.
- These are amazing.
- This home is so peaceful.
(calm music)
How long have you lived here?
- 42 years.
- You must have so many good memories.
- Yes.
Good and bad.
That mighty oak in the front,
it was just a puny little thing when we first moved here.
It was just struggling to survive.
- That's amazing.
- We were struggling to survive too.
That summer was almost unbearable.
There was no running water clear out here,
and Robbie had to go into town,
and bring back drinking water in a barrel.
Time sure were different then.
It was so hard to live here,
but he worked hard for this place.
He used to say,
"No place is God forsaking grace,
"not even Ringer."
We were so young then.
- What do you think, they'll it by the deadline?
- I don't know.
They're doing what they can.
What about you?
- Well, I've been thinking about it.
Warner certainly doesn't care about Mrs. Jackson's situation
and there aren't any other candidates, but--
- You think you're not the guy?
- No. I mean, I'm a contractor.
I'm a businessman,
I'm not a politician.
- You've got the head for it.
You've got the heart for it.
- What about you?
- No.
No, I can't control my tongue.
I'm not the diplomatic type.
But you,
you could give Warner a run for his money.
- Name?
- Vince Warner.
- Hey, how are you?
- I'm well. Thank you.
- Great.
So, what part are you trying out for?
- Oh actually, I'm not here to audition.
I just was in the area.
I thought I'd check it out.
So, how's your film coming?
- Good.
Script is finished,
and Angela is working on lyrics for the songs now.
- Singing cowboys?
That should bring them in.
So you've got the actors you need?
- No.
Actually, we haven't received the kind of interest
we thought we would.
- That's unfortunate.
When you guys start filming you should call me.
I'll do a story on your production.
Free publicity.
- Hey, awesome.
Thanks.
- Anything that helps Mrs. Jackson.
- Absolutely.
Just give me a call.
- Thank you.
Now what?
We still don't have any actors.
- Not for all the major roles.
We can rearrange the script a little bit.
You and I can be elites.
- And the widow?
- Angela can do it.
- I don't know.
Should we reconsider this whole project?
- What's to reconsider?
- It's a western musical
for which we don't even have
the major songs all recorded yet.
It's almost half an hour long
and we've got less than three weeks
to turn out an award winning video.
And this is our fourth project?
- We'll do it.
I can feel it.
- That's reassuring.
(bright dramatic music)
- Sandy, can I see you, please?
- He's entering too late to be effective.
He's not gonna be a threat to you in any way.
- I know.
So, why is even entering at all?
- I don't know.
- I need you to keep tabs on this guy.
And keep me up-to-date on the campaign
if you would, please?
- Yes, sir.
- Hey, Vince?
- Hey, John.
The cinematographer can't make it.
We've got to find someone to run this camera.
You and I are both acting,
and there's no one else here really qualified
to run it.
- You mean we've got nobody?
- Gator knows more about the camera
than anybody else here.
No. You're not serious?
- I can do it.
- He's light,
he'll be perfect for the crane work,
and we don't have anybody else.
- And I read that many one-eyed individuals
make excellent photographers.
It makes them look at things more creatively.
- There you go.
Well, climb aboard.
All right, everybody in their places.
Let's do this thing.
- All right.
(soft music)
(crane whirring)
(dramatic music)
- Action.
* Busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy
* Plow the ground and sow the seeds
* Milk the cows and pluck the weeds
* Busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy
* Apathy, apathy
* Many pressing situations
* Don't have time for confrontations
* Busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy
* Tragedy, tragedy
* Chop the wood and shoe the horses
* Feed the kids and sweep the porches
* Busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy, busy
* Hear me now
* The Widow's fight insanity
* We feel her pain, we see her need
* We wish we could but there's no time
* To take a stand by her side
* Surely someone will do something
* Was there something
* Can there something might do something
(dramatic music)
- Cut.
Great job, everyone.
(crowd applause)
- Everyone. Everyone.
We have to reset and shoot this all over again.
- No.
- We got to do it a few times to get the angles we need.
- Hey John.
I got to run to get things set up for the rally tomorrow.
- I'm going with him.
We're expecting a strong turnout.
- All right.
Well, we'll see you guys later then.
- Don't get in trouble.
- No, sir.
All right. Come on down from there.
We're gonna move that to the other end of the street.
- Can't I just ride up here?
- Sure, why not.
- John.
- Yeah?
- That was awesome.
- I know.
If we keep this up,
we'll have no trouble meeting the deadline.
- Oh, check this out.
- What is it?
- It's a blank cartridge.
Jackie and David have been making a bunch of them for us.
- How?
- Using fireworks.
I've been taking them apart and using the patterns
to make my rounds.
- That's genius.
All right.
- Okay guys,
right about here.
Yeah, this is perfect.
- Hey, John.
Look who's here.
- Hey, look.
- Hey, wait for me.
(soft music)
Hello.
- Hey, how you doing?
- I'm well. Thank you.
- It's good to see you.
- You too.
Figure today was as good today as any?
- Can somebody help me?
This thing is not working.
(soft music)
- Whoa. Whoah.
(machine whirring)
(dramatic music)
Help!
- Things have been going pretty well.
Well, tell you what, shoot whatever you like,
and we'll do our best to stay out of your way.
- I can't get up here.
I need some help.
Uh-oh.
(explosions going off)
- All right, get the fire.
Get the fire.
What happened here?
- Well, I was up on the crane,
and the whole thing was malfunctioning.
So, I tried to fix the wire,
and there was no one here to help me,
and it caught fire in Jack and David's fireworks.
- Okay look, we don't have time for this.
This film is too important to Mr. Morton's campaign,
to Mrs. Jackson's home.
And the fact is, somebody could have been hurt here.
Okay, we need to wake up and pay attention.
Well, let's say a prayer
and thank God that nobody was hurt.
Dear Lord, we thank you for your providence,
that we will be able to use this film to help Grace Jackson.
We thank you that we are protected from any harm today.
And we ask that you would put your hand
of blessing on this work.
In the name of Jesus Christ, Amen.
- Amen.
- All right, let's get back to work.
Well, we really wanted to do something with this film
that was a lot more meaningful than our previous films.
We have something put together with a lot of punch in it.
- And you're all homeschooled?
- Yes actually.
All of us involved in the production
are either homeschooling our children
or are homeschoolers ourselves.
- So, you have radical political views
and you're homeschooled,
does this cause you problems socially?
- Well, I wouldn't say that our views are radical.
I mean, we have different views in some people
because we were raised differently than some kids I guess.
But even if we had radical views
about property taxes, that's not the issue.
- For me, it's really about helping Mrs. Jackson.
No one else would do it, so that leaves to us.
- How do you know Jim Morton?
- We know him through the Moores actually.
He just moved down here
and started attending church with us.
Jeff Moore feels that Mr. Morton is a wise man
and encouraged him to run for office as public servant.
- Against Sam Warner?
- Sam Warner has done fine job of building a city
and encouraging city development,
but he really puts this tremendous strain
on property owners.
We're just speaking out against what we believe
is an unjust taxation.
Is this really pertinent to our topic?
I thought this was about the film?
- Yes. Yes.
Forgive me.
So little guy,
what is this film all about?
- Well, I've been studying the American Revolution
and it's kinda like that.
We need to protect ourselves from an oppressive government.
The goal is to start a revolution.
It'll start with the mayor
and end in a complete political takeover.
Really.
We have Jim Morton on our side.
He's gonna win, you know.
- Well, good luck.
- I think it's great that Mr. Morton is willing to do this.
- Somebody has to.
Jim will do a good job.
Are you ready?
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
- My lady.
Thank you, sir.
- Come.
(calm music)
- Well, everything we're doing I guess involves
getting knocked down a few times,
you just got to get back up.
- Yeah, that's right.
We're just starting.
We haven't even had time to get the word out yet.
- Well, Vince's report is airing today,
he did promise to tell your campaign to the film project,
so, that should get you some publicity.
- We'll keep you informed on further developments.
And now, a special report from Vince Warner.
- Film has been used for variety
of different things in history,
making political outcries is certainly one of them.
Now in Ringer,
a group of local film makers have come together
to produce a film of their own.
On the surface, it appears to be a harmless western film
full of fun and adventure for everyone.
The producers of the film say that their real goals
are much different.
- Well, we really wanted to do something
with this film that was a lot more meaningful
than our previous films.
- We're just speaking out against what we believe
is an unjust taxation.
- Further question revealed,
the Cinema Blog Production
is closely tied to Jim Morton
who is somewhat considered politically extremist
for his anti-taxation stance,
and who is now currently running for mayor of Ringer City.
How do you know Jim Morton?
- We know him through the Moores actually.
He just moved down here
and started attending church with us.
A lot of us here on set go to the same church.
- Another cult?
You decide.
Not only does this group attend religious services together,
but they've also made the collective decision
to remove their children from the public schools.
The project is being headed up by John Moore,
whose father is the leader in the religious group.
- I wouldn't say that our views are radical,
I mean, we have different views
than some people because we were raised differently
than some kids.
- But John's younger brother, Gator,
shares his view of the team's motivations.
- The goal is to start a revolution.
It will start with the mayor and end
in a complete political takeover.
Really, we have Jim Morton on our side.
- Their film, the "Widow's Might"
will be a part of the state level competition
of the American View Finder.
When contacted about the project,
officials at the American View Finder declined to count--
- Vince, that was low even for you.
- What do you mean?
I presented the facts.
- Facts devoid of contact.
- You don't know that.
They might really be cultists.
- I know these people and they're decent.
And I know you and you haven't changed.
I didn't ask you to do this.
All I wanted was to know Jim Morton's motivation
for running for mayor, that's all.
- I didn't do this for you, uncle.
I did this for me.
Just remember,
Jim Morton may be your competition,
but those producers are mine.
(ominous music)
- No, I understand.
Thanks anyway.
- Now where's our extras?
- They can't make it.
It looks like they saw Vince's report,
they don't want to be connected to the project.
- Well,
the movie has the festival screens,
let's see what it's all about.
- Yeah, but if we don't get some people out here,
it won't matter.
We'll miss the deadline.
We need to consider doing a smaller project.
- We'll just reschedule.
We'll have some folks from church come up.
- Time is ticking away.
Angela hasn't even finished her main song yet.
- She's working on it.
- This is my town, boy.
The railroad means this could be a boom town,
spot on the map.
I'm not gonna let an old widow woman take
that chance away from me.
(upbeat dramatic music)
* We built this town on storyland
* What a high price if we demand
* Take and take, and you never give
* To sort of build this place you live
* You play with fire to heed this day
* Your wicked plans will not prevail
* Injustice like this you all should fear
* For the widow's cry, Jehovah will hear
* The widow's cry, Jehovah will hear
(soft music)
- Nice, isn't it?
- Yes, it's wonderful.
I know now why you could never leave.
- It's beautiful.
It wasn't this way when we started.
There was very few trees on the property,
just a few short bushy things.
But Robbie wanted to plan a home for us.
I still laugh at some of his wild ideas.
But he built this place day by day
into a real shelter for us.
- What a wonderful man.
- Yes, he was.
- How old were you when you got married?
- Robbie was 23 and I was 19.
I had so much to learn about life,
but Robbie was a good teacher.
He promised me he would make this a good life.
I hated it.
I was afraid.
I was lonely.
I wanted my own life.
But he kept his promise.
It was a good life.
And I promised him one thing.
- What's that?
- I promised him I wouldn't leave.
I swore I'd take my last breath on this land.
(soft music)
- How'd the filming go today?
- Yeah. We didn't get nearly enough footage.
Most of the extras didn't even show up.
- Because of the news cast?
- Vince's report scared them off.
I just still can't believe he'd do that to us.
- He's your competitor, Sam Warner's nephew.
It's obvious he wasn't raised
with the same principles as you were.
- I still expected him to have some integrity.
- It shows you the power of the media, though.
It doesn't necessarily have to display the facts,
it's how the reporter chooses to show the facts.
We can't let Vince play us like that again.
- Yeah.
(cellphone ringing)
- Excuse me.
Hello?
- Hi. John?
It's Carl Kilgore, the festival director.
After today's report, we've been receiving calls
from our producers and sponsors trying to figure out
just what kind of operation we're running.
- Sir, I can explain.
That report completely--
- I don't want an explanation.
I'm giving you an ultimatum.
Do not drag your political
or religious agenda into our production
or you will be disqualified from the competition.
Understand?
- Yes, sir.
I do.
- Goodnight.
* To think of all I had
* For me, it makes me laugh
- How's this?
(soft music)
- This is good.
- Really? You think so?
- This is really good.
This is great.
When did you come up with this?
- Grace.
(knocking at the door)
- Hey.
John, you have to hear this.
Angela just finished writing the lyrics of this song
and I built a score, and that little tune she wrote, great.
- Hey, Cam, I'm sure it's great but we can't do this.
- What do you mean?
- Carl Kilgore called and he says we have to change
our project or drop out of the festival entirely.
- No way.
- I'm not gonna quit just because
we were rejected for some talent show.
- Some talent show?
Cameron, this is a once in a lifetime opportunity.
If we pursue this now,
we can come back to Grace when we have more time.
- Are you serious?
You're backing out?
I thought you'd be man enough
to see this through to the end?
And for the record, you were the one
who invited Vince out to the set to begin with.
- Are you saying this is my fault?
- Basically, yes.
- I'm the director.
I deserve a little respect.
- So, now what do we do?
- It doesn't look like we've got
a lot of a choice at this point.
- I disagree.
Everything involves making a choice.
To get involved in the beginning was your choice.
You said you wanted to protect and defend Grace Jackson.
Now the way I see it you have another choice to make,
whether to stand with your family and friends,
do the right thing and be proud of your actions,
or take the coward's way out.
Follow the spotlight
and find somewhere else to sleep.
So, gentlemen, where do we stand?
- I'm in.
I'm in all the way.
Let's make a movie and change the world, huh?
- Before you go, let me hear the song.
- That good, huh?
- That good.
(calm music)
* I made this my home
* As we are one
* Fresh out of my life
* My love and I
* Yesterday's so far away
* A sweet and distant memory
* To think of all I've had
* For me, makes me laugh
* It makes me cry
* This is where I belong
* My shelter from the storm
* Lord, faithful to you I've been
* I'm begging you again
* We made our start here
* This is my heart here
* My life has been here
* Don't take it all away
* We raised our family
* To know your glory
* This home devoted
* Solely unto you
* Suffer, fear and doubt are rising in me
* Please Lord, hear my cry
* Show me mercy
* God I pray
* Make a way
* Lord, you are my refuge and my fortress
* Will you not protect me I am helpless
* Make a way
* This is where I belong
* My shelter from the storm
* Lord, faithful to you I've been
* I'm begging you again
* We made our start here
* This is my heart here
* My life has been here
* Don't take it all away
* We raised our family
* To know Your glory
* This home devoted
* Solely unto You
* These memories are too much for me to bear
* A lifetime of this life that we once shared
* How can they take away
* This land I call my home
* Oh God, I'm helpless fighting this alone
* This is where I belong
* My shelter from the storm
* I'm right here on my knees
* This song it is
* I'm here
* My husband died here
* My heart is tied here
* My life has been here
* Don't take it all away
- So how does our tragic tale end?
Be in the Widow's Field on Friday at eight o'clock
and we'll all see how this tale comes to a close.
(soft melancholic music)
- Time to talk to a mailman.
- So how's the production going?
- Yeah, pretty well.
We've been disqualified from the festival.
- What?
- Yeah.
See, after Vince's report, the festival directors called
and told us not to bring our political agendas
into the competition.
- That's ridiculous.
I wish there was something I could do.
- There is.
- Awesome.
Do you want me to play the sheriff?
- No, not exactly.
See, without the festival we have no way of getting
the film in front of people before the upcoming elections.
- So what are you looking for?
What do you want to be done?
- We made a DVD that has most of the film on it
and an explanation of where they can see the rest.
We need to get this DVD into the hands
of as many families in Ringer City as we possibly can.
And you deliver to over half of them.
- Wait a minute.
I'm not gonna do that.
That's ridiculous. That's illegal.
You're asking me to go around town taunting your DVD
and then you don't even make me your sheriff.
The audacity!
- Wallace.
Wallace, these people are your friends.
Give them the DVDs on your "break time".
- I'll lose my job.
(slow bagpipe music)
- Aye.
You may lose your job,
but lying on your bed many years from now.
- Okay, I'll do it.
- Good.
I'll get you those DVDs tomorrow.
And, Wallace, thanks.
- They can take my job but they can never take my freedom.
(car starting)
(dramatic music)
- Mr. Moore?
- Yes? - Yes?
- Mr. Kilgore can see you now.
- Dad, aren't you coming?
- No, this is your appointment.
You'll do just fine, son.
(dramatic music)
- Mr. Kilgore?
- Yes?
(dramatic music)
- Let me guess.
You wanna be a cinematographer one day?
- Yes, sir.
- Well, how can I help you, young man?
- Well, sir, our family put together a movie
for your festival, but it got disqualified.
- Well, we don't allow films
with overt political or religious tone.
It reflects poorly on the festival.
- You're just saying that because
of the news report by Vince.
- That had a lot to do with our decision, yes.
- Well, the guy who made that is our competitor,
Vince Warner.
He's also moving on to state level.
- Really?
I wasn't aware of that.
Jenny?
- Yes, sir?
- Put me through to the reporter who contacted us
for comments about the cult group.
Alleged cult group.
- Right away, sir.
- Hello. Vince Warner.
- Hello Vince.
This is Carl Kilgore, press agent and selection manager
for the American View Finder.
- Oh yes, sir.
How are you?
- Doing fine.
I've a quick question.
It has been brought to my attention
that you're not only a contestant
on the American View Finder,
but you're also the reporter
who did the story on the Moore Family.
Is that true?
- Yes, sir. It is.
- I have a gentleman here
who believes your participation in the festival
has influenced your angle on the story.
- Who contacted you?
- Their cinematographer.
(Vince laughing)
- Ridiculous.
Of course he's upset.
And he'd tell you anything to get back in the festival.
The only reason they're going to state
is that the little cyclops got sympathy votes
for his eye patch story.
A cheap tactic, sir.
- Thank you.
You've told me all I need to know.
- Anytime.
And sir?
I'm looking forward to meeting you
in person one of these days.
It will be a tremendous pleasure, I'm sure.
- Have a good day.
Well, that certainly complicates things.
Let me do some research and I'll get back to you.
- Thank you.
And, sir, you can start your research by watching this.
It's the first 20 minutes of the film we've been working on.
Once you know what we've been working on, it might help.
- Sure. Why not.
Thank you for coming.
I need to get back to work.
(upbeat dramatic music)
- I like it.
- I'm glad our singing's pre-recorded.
- Huh?
- I'd be too afraid to sing in front of a live crowd.
- That makes two of us.
- Hurry up!
We're already late.
The movie's almost over by now
and we have to be live in 10 minutes.
(calm music)
- You won't have to play this up.
- Get your gear and start setting up.
Get the real radical stuff.
Anything that looks violent.
Come on. Go!
(upbeat dramatic music)
* Did you ever have the chance
* To do something really noble
* But then the fear and doubt
* Rendered you immobile
* Set aside your selfishness
* Your wishes and desires
* And do for someone now's a thing
* Which decency requires
* You know you should
* You know you can
* This is the time
* This is the plan
* Be brave and have good courage, men
* You cannot live in bondage, men
* Step up and send your ground and then
* We'll have justice once again
* Follow me, I do confess
* Together we are braver, yes
* Go and set your ground today
* Together we must save her
* If this was your affliction
* The trial that you posses
* Would you not pray for help, my friend
* The evil to suppress
* This burden is too much for her
* She simply could not bear
* Would you not lend a hand, my friend
* Relieve her from despair
* You know you should
* You know you can
* This is the time
* This is the plan
* Be brave and have good courage, men
* You cannot live in bondage, men
* Step up and stand your ground and then
* We'll have justice once again
* Follow me, I do confess
* Together we are braver, yes
* Go and stand your ground today
* Together we must save her
* For far too long in selfish pride
* You set aside and compromise
* The justice that this town desires
* And build it with your wicked lies
* Side by side in one accord
* Stand up, be strong do not ignore
* The widow's cry for help you hear
* The laws of God you should reveal
(upbeat dramatic music)
- Well, where do you stand?
Are you with justice?
- If we don't let the railroad company
have the widow's home
then Foster County gets the train station
and we become a ghost town.
I'm all for keeping this town alive.
- As my friend, but at the expense of justice?
To steal from a widow and the town?
Must we pervert the law to grow?
Tom?
- Yeah?
- If you stood on your land
and the sheriff and his men told you at gunpoint to get off.
What would you do?
- I'd tell them to get lost.
We pay for this land that we lay in.
- But if you were gone
and your wife were held at gunpoint, what then?
Can't you see?
An individual has no chance against
this breach of justice, this rampage of greed,
the hearts of men filled with lust.
Is this progress?
When we trample on the weakest and dearest of our citizens?
- Yeah, he's right.
Deal with the sheriff.
- Yeah, down with that tyrant.
- Wait.
(people disagreeing)
- Wait a minute.
(gunshot)
- Whoa!
- Listen to me.
Sheriff's not the problem.
For all practical purposes,
he's just a misguided public servant.
He doesn't care about the railroad.
He listened to your demands, followed your desires,
you are the tyrants.
(creaking door sound)
- Look to each other if you want to see
who's trampling the widow down.
In this land where freedom is every man's greatest pride,
and order is held high, how could it be
that the defenseless would become oppressed?
Oppressed by the very neighbors that, in another time,
would've given their lives to defend one another.
You've become so removed from each other
that you don't even see how your actions
lead to a widow's loss.
But if a wall can be torn down and can be built up again,
together restoring equity to your law and to your city,
God's hand of blessing makes a mighty nation,
not a railroad.
(crowd applause)
(calm music)
- Well, what do you say?
(upbeat dramatic music)
- What happened?
- I don't know.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
we're having some technical difficulties.
We'll try to be back up in just a few minutes.
Thank you.
- Live in 60 seconds.
- Did you queue mob sequence?
- Yeah.
- Hey, Vince is here with his news posse.
- John, look at this.
- Do we have another cord?
- Yes, but I can't plug it in.
Someone must have ran over with the cable.
The tip's broken off inside the jack.
- Now what?
- Okay, guys.
It's time for phase two.
- You know, this probably means losing the election.
- Sometimes you gotta lose a battle
to win the war, guys.
I'm not in this to win a competition.
We're in this to help Grace Jackson.
- Isn't this part where I tackle you?
- Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for coming
and giving your time to support this movie.
I'm sorry for the difficulties.
Cameron's working on getting the DVD going now.
- Ten seconds.
- We're back with further developments on
the group of families and their controversial film project,
"The Widow's Might".
Today, the families have rallied supporters
at the widow's home just off the highway in Ringer County.
Vince Warner is live on the scene.
Vince?
- Thank you, Sarah.
I'm here in the Widow's Field where protesters
have assembled and drawn quite a crowd.
- And how are they able to do that?
- They drew in a lot of interest
with the premiere of their film, "The Widow's Might",
which is screened here for the audience.
I had an opportunity to see the film
which strongly suggest mob action
as the answer to political problems.
- Yeah, he's right.
Down with the sheriff.
- Yeah. Down with that tyrant.
- Yeah.
- They have a frightening amount of support
from fringed residents of Ringer.
- So what's currently happening at the location?
- And now we'd like to bring up a very important man.
- It looks like they're about to bring up Jim Morton.
- A candidate in the current race for mayor of Ringer.
And the man who, in his own way,
got us started on this project.
Mr. Sam Warner.
(crowd applause)
- Thank you.
Thank you people of Ringer.
Well, that was a great story we just saw there.
Our own Ringer County was much like
that little cow town in the film
but just not too many years ago.
And we have roads, we have fine schools--
- Do you think this will work?
- We have public utilities--
- The people are amazing.
They'll even do what's right to get what they want.
- The issue of Grace Jackson and her home is one
that has weighed heavily on me
since I learned about it several weeks ago.
As mayor of Ringer, I pledge that I will do my best
to alleviate taxes on the elderly,
and I believe that I can safely say
that Grace Jackson will not lose her home.
(crowd applause)
- Cut the feed after this.
- Vince is requesting a feed cut.
- And now ladies and gentlemen,
we'd like to bring up a woman who,
despite being under tremendous pressures,
has maintained the spirit of charity and peace.
- It's attracting a lot of viewers.
We can't cut.
- Ladies and gentlemen, Grace Jackson,
or as you know her, the widow Grace.
(crowd applause)
- Thank you.
I appreciate all you all being here.
I want to thank all my friends for all their support.
And especially for these families
that have worked so hard, not just for me,
but so no one would ever have to lose their home.
You all have allowed me to hope.
Mr. Warner, I appreciate your offering
to make my case an exception
and I promise I will hold you to that if you were reelected.
But I want all you all to know
that my vote will be going for Jim Morton.
(crowd applause)
- Cut the feed!
- I can't.
- Shut the camera down.
They'll get the idea.
- Look, I'm just doing my job.
I'm not gonna lose that job so you can keep yours.
- Well, first of all, I'd like to thank you for coming out
in support of Grace Jackson.
I know a lot of you saw in the news features
about our families.
That kind of misrepresentation and slander,
be it national news or a personal blog
can cause unbelievable damage to a good name.
- Looks like you've step in it, son.
You Vince Warner?
- Yes. And you?
- Carl Kilgore, Regional Manager
for the American View Finder.
- And now, I would like you to see
for yourselves who we really are.
I would like my family, the Moores, Cameron and Angela.
Come on the stage, please.
(crowd applause)
- I'm looking forward to seeing your entry
into the state levels competition.
But even more than that, I'm looking
for an accurate report on the Moore Family.
You see what I mean, son?
You really did step in it.
- Have we got anything?
- We've got the video but no audio.
- Man, how are we gonna do this?
We can't just keep stalling.
- Wait here.
Derek.
- Psst! Hey! We're still live.
- Shut that camera off!
- It looks like the guys have a solution.
- What's this?
- In giving the film, we have to do the audio ourselves.
- That is crazy.
- We have to.
- There is no way that I can sing
in front of all these people.
I'm sorry.
- Look, stand behind the Moores and the Mortons.
They've stood behind us this whole production.
- They'll miss the whole scene at the end with the sheriff.
- No, they won't.
- All right.
We didn't fix the audio issue
but we have a solution anyway.
We're gonna do it live.
(crowd applause)
In the last scene, we saw a cowboy
coming to face the sheriff.
And the last line was--
- Well, what do you say?
- Yes.
I'll stand with justice.
And you know what?
I'm sorry.
We should've never let this injustice slide by.
We should've never supported it.
I let my own greed for power stand in the way.
But no more.
Grace Jackson and all the residents of this fine town,
never be trampled under again.
Not on my watch.
- Do you hear him?
Will you hold him to that promise?
(crowd applause)
- And you, will you hold them to theirs?
- I will.
I swear that I shall.
I swear before God above, to you, the people,
and to the widow Grace.
* I made this my home as a young bride
* My life built on faith my love and I
* Yesterday and still today
* We chose that day where we would serve
* Our lives' with you without reserve
* Day by day you give us strength
* This is where I belong
* My shelter from the storm
* Lord, faithful to you I've been
* I'm thanking you again
* We made our start here
* This is my heart here
* My life has been here
* Because of you I'll stay
* She made her start here
* This is her heart here
* Her life has been here
* It's only right she stay
* We were courageous
* Our faith contagious
* We put our trust in you
* To show the way
* You who gave me hope and taught me patience
* Help me how to show you my devotion
* You who stood by her when she was all alone
* You heard her cry
* You heard my cry
* Now here I pray
(slow melancholic music)
(crowd applause)
- Gator, come here please.
- Yes, dad?
- Gator, John told me you were not very respectful
to Mr. Warner when you went to see him.
- Yes, sir.
- I think we better go see the mayor.
- Mr. Mayor?
- Yes?
How can I help you, young man?
(upbeat music)