(gentle music)
- Hello?
Hello?
Help!
(intense beeping)
Oh no.
Oh no, no, oh no.
Help.
Help!
Hey, hey.
Hey.
Hello, oh my God.
Hey, you've gotta help me, I
think there's been an accident,
there's some people
back there that are hurt
really really bad, look,
I don't know where I am
I'm losing my mind here,
you've gotta help me, please,
there's some people
that hurt really badly.
Please, will you
please just help me?
Please, please,
you've gotta help me.
(soft groans)
(intense music)
Hello?
Anybody here?
I need to use a phone.
Hello?
Goddammit.
Where the fuck is everybody?
What the fuck.
Where the fuck am I,
what is this shit?
Where the fuck is everybody?
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
Fuck.
God fucking damn it.
(wheezing)
I need your help, man.
Hey.
I really need to find a phone.
Hey man, I've been
in an accident.
There's some people that
were hurt really, really bad.
I gotta get some help.
I need to find a phone.
Fuck.
- I'm okay, too much
breakfast maybe.
- Hey, listen man,
I appreciate the ride
but I really need
to find a fucking phone.
Look, I'm really lost,
I can't even remember
fucking nothing.
And I don't even know
where you're taking me,
but I trust you realize
this gun is fucking loaded,
so don't even think
of trying anything.
I need a phone, man,
why are there no
people around here?
- Making omelets tonight.
(wheezing)
Secret recipe, lots of cheese.
On some garlic, I
use lots of garlic.
Salty, I like that.
Take two or three eggs, no
less, a little bit of milk,
little bowl, let them cook.
Let them cook for a while.
They flush easy,
let them cook for a while.
- Hello?
Hello?
- [Voiceover] Dial again.
Dial again. Dial again.
(phone malfunctions)
- Happy birthday.
(dial tone)
(laughter)
(banging)
(shouting)
- You fucking bitch,
you fucking skanky
fucking bitch.
- Baby just calm
down, just quiet down-
- Shut up, cunt,
you fucking cunt.
- Baby, I don't know what I did.
- You are such a fucking
cunt, I fucking loved you
and know this pussy is
like a fucking outhouse.
You'll let anybody
shit in it, won't you?
You just anybody
fucking shit in it.
Where is he, where is he?
- Who? I don't know-
- Shut the fuck up, where is he?
Where the fuck is he,
you fucking bitch?
- Baby, you're scaring me.
- Oh really, want
to talk about it?
Want to get some therapy,
you fucking cunt?
Do you want to do that?
I have fucking seen him
in those trees, okay,
watching, waiting, looking
at me like I'm like
some fucking cuckold, right?
- Herm?
- Herm, herm.
You thought you had a
nice little fucking hiding
place here, didn't you?
But y'all fucked up,
because I saw him.
- You know, fuck you, Herm.
- Fuck you, bitch.
- You kept me in this prison
for I don't know how long.
Trapped.
- I seen him out in that tree.
- You're out of
your fucking mind.
- You don't love me
anymore, is that it?
Look at you, you fucking,
look at you, fucking
I loved, I...
I loved you, pure
and simple, I did.
- What's your name, sweetheart?
- I don't know.
- New beginning. Here's to it.
(growling)
(gasping)
(screaming)
(gentle music)
- These trees, they have a code.
That's not for
our understanding.
They'll make room for us,
if only for a little while.
Did you ever remember your name?
- No.
- You changed here
between the trees.
You'll change some more.
- I only see you in
these dark places.
- Darkness shines bright here,
drear's not its complement.
|I hope you find what's next,
then you'll see me
in the daylight.
Follow my friend.
He's not always around.
- Come on in, sweetheart.
* Once we were contenders,
* Nothing but the
stars in our eyes
* Free as a wind
blowing out on the sea
* Happy, loving life
* Yes we were
* Once we were contenders
* Trying to get a leg in
* Wearing them hose in
them tight-fitting clothes
* And sexy girlfriends and man
* That old house
that we lived in
* Strangers sleeping in our beds
* The only thing cool
about supper time
* Would be beers who
got a drinking stick
* Any day now,
* As I tossed in here from show
* I'll take a look
in the old crack mill
* And I'm feeling
feeling a whole lot old
* We're still contenders
* Being blessed in
spite of the change
* We got luxury cars
and a country club bar
* Our agents in the hour erased
* They got fancy
- Hey lady.
* Surround the places we live
- You got any water?
* But I'm telling you
son it's a lot more fun
* When you're dreaming
how to make it big *
- Huh?
- You got any water?
(screaming)
- Morning.
- You should have
never come here.
(grunting)
(laughter)
- Hi, hi daddy, hi.
Hi daddy.
(laughter)
(shouting)
(gentle music)