How's it looking?
Signal's getting strength.
Looks like she's homing in.
What are we gonna do with Iris
One after we win the war on drugs?
It's a highly versatile system,
I'm sure it'll be
put to good use.
Now, let's not get ahead of
ourselves here, gentlemen.
Never underestimate
my boys, Ross.
I guarantee you.
Delta will give Salvatore a
blow he'll not soon forget.
Either that...
or they'll end up like the two
DEA teams before them, Norm.
What are you
talking about, Alan?
Well, ask Jensen there.
He oversaw the ops.
Is it true?
Why was I not made aware of it?
A decision was made
to deny any knowledge.
Cut the disclaimer
horseshit, Jensen!
Is it true what Alan was saying?
Two teams?
12 men each.
So you're telling me that 24 men have
died attempting the same mission?
I'm afraid so.
Captain, I just wanna say
I think we got no business...
Hutch! Not now!
She's homing in.
Bingo.
Tell the guys we got a 909er.
Ability base, this is river rat.
We've got a confirmed
target lock.
Repeat.
Confirmed target lock.
Americanos!
Captain, talk to me!
Get us to the other side!
Vengas! Rapido!
Nobility Base,
we're ground zero
and closing on target.
Where the hell they all go?
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Clear!
Move out!
Move up!
Hell of a party, fellas?
We like it, Cap!
Lombi, take point!
Lombi, take point.
Right, Cap!
Lombi!
Say "happy."
Happy.
Lombi!
Say "birthday."
Right, Cap.
Let's do it.
It's time to rock and roll!
Watch your step, Doc.
Don't worry about me.
Just keep your eyes open.
Clear.
Pretty clean, Cap.
Guess Salvatore never figured
anyone would make it this far.
What?
Shit.
Lombardi, move!
Move! Move!
Move!
Fuck!
Cap!
Shit!
Lombardi!
Lombi's down, Cap.
Okay.
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Go! Go!
This is not good, Cap.
This is not good.
Give all you got, Doc.
Come on, baby.
You give me all you got, Doc.
I want all you got!
Clear! Clear!
Go!
You gotta stay with me.
You gotta stay with me, okay?
Stay with me.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Clear.
Pay dirt.
Man, this is
a cokehead's wet dream.
Not for long, it ain't.
Hutch, why's it so
damn quiet out there?
Nothing left to kill, Captain.
Job well done.
Stay with me, okay?
Talk to me.
You're gonna talk to me.
Let's talk about Becky, okay?
Talk to me about Becky.
Stay with me.
You gotta talk to me.
Skip!
Nice toss, Cap.
Come on, Mac, set the timer.
Let's get the hell out of here!
Come on, fucker!
Let's get out of here.
Let's go!
Americans? Sí.
Do they know who
they're dealing with here?
Because, I mean,
this is... you know?
This is a fucking insult, man.
They insult me!
They insult my family!
Find out how they knew
and find out now!
Sí.
One comma 8 billion.
Stupid fucks!
Who the fuck do they think
they're dealing with?
You just got yourselves a war!
The world has been
led to speculate
on the details of the raid
which reportedly destroyed
a stockpile of cocaine
with an estimated
street value of $1.6 billion.
It's rumored, however,
that President Farrington
will address the issue in his keynote
speech at the U.N. later this week.
In other news...
War on drugs.
Right.
What a fucking joke.
What's the problem, Hutch?
Captain, this is not our fight.
When have we ever been able
to pick our own fights?
Come on, Cap!
War on drugs?
We are just pissing in the wind.
That's what burns me.
What you talking about, Mac?
He's talking about Lombardi in
there, fighting for his life.
Why?
Why? For what?
Because some fat-ass bureaucrat
decided that fighting drugs
is the fucking flavor
of the goddamn month!
You wanna know
what the bottom line is?
That until you start writing
the checks or calling the shots,
you're under complete and total
obligation to follow orders, period!
I'm sorry, gentlemen.
There's been no change.
Me? I don't know shit
about satellites.
But I got someone who does.
I'm known as a hacker.
I'm wanted by the FBI,
the CIA, Interpol,
Mossad, the Russians,
the French,
etcetera, etcetera, etcetera.
Wanted for what?
Cyber theft.
I steal codes.
Burgle information.
You know, all with
Mable's help, of course.
Welcome to the Nineties,
my technologically
challenged friends!
The world is computerized...
and it's all at my fingertips.
Stocks, bonds, utilities,
insurances, communication,
even the military.
If it's networked,
it's accessible.
With a few exceptions,
of course.
Once I'm in,
people like Sal pay me to observe,
to manipulate, to sabotage.
Now, a couple days ago,
Sal came to me with
this problem of yours.
And here it is in all its glory.
The Iris One constellation.
Say hello to the American
navy's finest, gents.
The U.S.S. Roosevelt,
the first in
a brand-spanking-new class
of ultra-quiet attack subs.
Ultra-quiet attack subs.
Why are you showing us this?
What do the subs
have to do with satellites?
Chill!
I was getting to that.
You see,
the Navy talks to its subs
via another satellite
network known as the SSIX.
Mable and I have cracked
the SSIX, gents,
which means
I can talk to the subs.
Start sending a message.
Z08375...
from com sub...
to
U.S.S Roosevelt...
one...
emergency test...
low... system..
Mr. Wallcox.
Sir.
A possible defect in workmanship
of the valves
in the emergency system?
"Please test the system immediately
and report any anomalies."
That's what it says,
Mr. Wallcox,
so I suggest we get to it.
And if there is a problem,
don't you think it would be
better to know sooner than later?
Okay, flood the tanks
so we can get on with this.
Captain.
Yes, sir.
Standby to flood the tanks!
All hands, this is the Captain.
We've been ordered to perform
an emergency blow drill,
to test for a possible
defect of the system.
Batten the hatches, men.
We're taking the express
elevator to the roof.
The drill will commence when
all sections are reported in.
Captain out.
Surface preparation!
Prepare to surface!
Come on!
You're behind on your drill!
Let's go!
Come on!
Chemical clear.
Sub is secure.
Forward-weapons hatch open.
Sal, you got yourself a sub.
How long before the
equipment's up and running?
8 hours, more or less,
if the guys know
what they're doing.
They know how.
Believe me, they know.
How many hours overdue\is
the transmission?
24.
Theories?
Well, she wend down.
She was torpedoed.
If she's on the bottom,
it'll take weeks to find her.
For God sakes, we're not at war!
At least not yet.
Lombardi's dead.
Cap called.
He died half an hour ago.
Jesus, Paul.
I'm so sorry.
I told him to go.
We were at the top
of these stairs...
and I told him to go first.
And then I saw
the laser tap him,
and I told him to move...
and he fucking froze.
I told him to fucking
move, and he froze.
Honey, you did
everything you could.
This wasn't your fault.
Maybe Mac's right.
Maybe this isn't our war.
But right now,
you know what I want?
I want him dead.
I don't care if they
legalize drugs or they don't.
I want Humberto Salvatore dead.
God, it's Frank.
What the hell?
This is Humberto Salvatore
using live pictures from the U.S.S.
Roosevelt.
Surely you've been wondering
what happened to the sub.
Well, wonder no more.
It's mine.
Get me a VPA now!
If it is him,
he's got to be bluffing.
Then how in hell did he
know the sub's gone missing?
He's got to be
staging this somehow.
It's just not possible.
My men have already replaced
the conventional warheads
on the sub's cruise missiles
with warheads containing
mustard gas.
I have the ability to strike
at any four cities
on the eastern seaboard
from the sub's current position.
My people tell me
that you can push a button
that will destroy your eyes in the
sky, Iris One.
I give you 24 hours
to push that button,
or I'll push mine.
Your only choice is
to decide what you lose...
A few satellites
or millions of innocent lives.
You wanted a war.
You got one.
I'll be in touch.
Come on.
He's got to be
bluffing about that.
Would you take a chance
on that, Ted? Would you?
If we nuke it, it won't matter
whether or not he's bluffing.
If he's on the open sea, sure.
But what if he's parked 25
miles off the coast of D.C.?
Okay, what have we got here?
We've got the quietest
sub in the world
poised to strike
the eastern seaboard
with chemical weapons.
What I want to know is,
what the hell are we
gonna do about it?
Skip Lang.
Skip. Norm Henshaw here.
If you and the boys are up for
another crack at Salvatore,
we've got a real situation here.
We've decided to strike
directly at him.
Unfortunately there's no time to
mobilize and deploy a large force.
Naturally, your unit was
at the top of the list.
No, I will be honored
to cooperate
in every way posible, Señor, sí.
And I give you
my personal guarantee
that everything will
go smoothly, sir.
The President is very,
very grateful personally,
and buenas noches.
Thank you. Good-bye.
Borrega assures me
everything will be in place
for Operation Trap
by the time Delta arrives.
Norm, this is my protégé,
Ariana Decker.
She helped me design
and install the safeguards
for the Iris One network.
She also had a hand in the computer
enhancements on the Roosevelt.
Captain, too bad you
weren't around
to help with the SSIX.
Well, we're pretty sure we know
who Salvatore's
point man was on that.
Here, let me show you.
Sure.
All right, gentlemen.
It's time we get
down to business.
As you know,
Salvatore's grubby fingers
reach into every nook and cranny
of the Colombian military.
So open communication to base
is out of the question.
Out of the question!
I know it's contrary
to standard procedure,
but that's the way that
this op's going down.
Any questions?
Where are we staging from?
It's a small town
called St. Crystal.
We'll ride a train in
across the tracks
into his territory.
Slip up under his nose.
Kick him in the fucking teeth.
I love that.
Two.
Three. Kilo, kilo,
alpha, 9-1-4.
Three, kilo, kilo, alpha, 9-1-4.
Completed one.
All automation systems normal.
Bearing, 072.
Range, 44,000.
Automated systems
responding accordingly.
Turning.
Okay, gentlemen.
There are two phases to this op.
Phase one.
Infiltrate the compound,
locate the target.
Phase two.
Capture and/or eliminate
the target.
This will be our optimal
L.C. here.
As we cross the border,
it will be our secondary.
Any questions?
Captain.
We're approximately six
minutes away from the border.
Let's synchronize
our watches to 0700 hours
in 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Hey, hombres. Venga.
Vayanse!
Rapido!
Vamamos.
Rapido! Rapido!
Vamos.
Andele.
Rapido.
This is General Borrega.
Do you wish to purchase
any information?
Yes.
You sound like
a smart man, Admiral.
Everybody makes a mistake
from time to time.
That is human nature.
And yours was wasting your time
planning a strike against me
when you could have put
that time to better use
convincing your President
to destroy Iris One.
Speaking of time, Admiral,
it's ticking away.
You have eight hours
to get President Farrington
to pull the plug on Iris One.
Borrega.
I'd say we're looking up
a dead horse's rectum, Norm.
Yeah.
Cap, we got to get
this train moving, man.
Go, go, go!
Beggars, go airborne!
One in the hole.
Hutch, Vicks,
juice up the birds.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Battery on.
Come on, Cap!
You get back here, goddamn it, Sparks!
That's an order!
Circuit breakers on.
Phase two, circuit breakers on.
Shit!
Fuel pump, check.
Adonde? Adonde?
Where are they?
Son of a bitch!
Hydraulics engaged.
Shit!
Let there be light.
Son of a bitch!
Aw, shit!
Sparks is hit!
Sparks!
We'll come get you in five.
It's coming around
1:00 high.
Got you covered.
Go, go, go!
Move it!
Take it up!
Going up.
Tango. Tango.
Son of a bitch!
Hurry, Cap!
Incoming!
We're coming!
Come on!
Get on!
Go!
We're gonna land
the thing over here.
Let's go.
Good work, guys.
That's definitely one
for the record books.
I think it's time we go rain
on Salvatore's parade.
Come to Thane.
He loves you, baby.
Thane loves you.
Yeah.
So, General Borrega,
tell me about the train.
So where are they now?
Jesus Christ!
Hurry up!
Get Thane.
Thane!
Hallway clear!
Hello, Howie.
Or is it HT.com-prick?
You got me mixed up
with someone else, man.
Over here, Cap.
What is it?
Hutch, Vickers,
download this punk.
Mac, Doc, come with me.
What the hell's
he doing down here?
Shit! The current!
Son of a bitch is headed
toward the river.
Hi, Howie.
I'm Hutch.
That's Vickers.
Hey.
I only have one question.
Where's the sub?
Watch the material, bub.
Hey.
See, I know that you
have a com link,
so I know you're
talking to the sub.
How?
Holy jeez.
You guys just really don't...
Don't make me ask you again.
You idiots.
Reload.
Don't shoot!
Howard!
Look at me.
Are you gonna give me
the answers I need?
Or am I gonna have
to convince you?
Hold on. I really...
I really don't know.
I really don't...
I can contact
the hijackers, okay?
Now we're getting somewhere.
Get your ass over there
and call 'em off.
It won't help.
They were only supposed to set
up the equipment and take over.
They're superfluous now.
Don't you patronize me.
What... do...
you... mean?
I designed the system
to completely automate the sub.
That's what Salvatore wanted.
So what would happen
if his demands were met?
Fuck, I don't know!
Fuck!
And I liked him.
Okay.
Shit!
I want you to tell me again.
The SSIX.
Only Salvatore knows the codes.
Where is the Roosevelt headed?
The hijackers were supposed to...
We know that!
He asked you where the
Roosevelt was headed.
Where's the sub?
Cap!
So fucking close!
I take full responsibility
for Salvatore's escape.
At ease.
What's up?
We have a clear target, Captain.
Where?
The sub is headed
for New York City.
Shit!
Is that true, Thane?
Is that true?
It's true.
We're going airborne, gentlemen.
Get this loser out of here. Sir.
What the hell are you on?
Captain, we cannot
break radio silence.
I have to break protocol, Mac.
We have no choice.
Captain, listen... It's a
matter of national security!
Track leader to Nobility Base.
Do you read?
Get up, goddamn it.
Come on in, Skip.
Let's hear it.
Admiral Henshaw.
We thwarted the ambush
on the train without incident,
but, Salvatore got away.
Shit!
However, we did grab Thane.
Did you get the code?
Negative.
And, sir,
it looks like the Roosevelt
is headed to New York City.
What?
New York City?
Okay, Skip, change of plan.
Rendezvous ASAP on board
the U.S.S. Coral Sea.
I'll update the President.
Nobility Base out.
Good to have you back, dude.
All over it, Cap.
Morning, Admiral. Joe.
Ten-Hut!
Take it easy, boys.
Carry on. Captain. Sir.
So this is our infamous
Mr. Howard Thane.
Yes, sir.
Howdy, Gramps.
Um...
I really need my medicine.
He's talking about these, sir.
We took 'em off
him at the villa.
Whatever they are, he's got
a pretty strong habit going.
Admiral.
Do we have any news from
the Roosevelt yet, sir?
She's on a holding pattern
up in New York Bay.
And our course of action?
Well, I've got to get
you boys on board, don't I.
You're wasting your time.
Even if you get past
those hijackers,
you're never gonna
override the program.
Get that thing out of here!
I want to talk to my lawyer!
I still got rights, you know.
I'm an American citizen
for Christ's sake!
Well, Captain, at least
we stand a chance
of finding the sub.
And then what, sir?
Look, I know Howard.
Maybe I can talk to him.
Maybe we should
think about evacuation.
Evacuating what, General?
Just 'cause the submarine's
heading for New York
doesn't mean New York's
the target.
Hey, Howard.
You're looking better than ever.
Wish I could say the same.
You said Salvatore's
the only one
who knows the code to remotely
access your automation system.
That's what I said.
What about overriding it
from inside the sub?
What about it?
Howard, don't be like that.
Help me and I'll help you.
How?
If you cooperate I can fix it
to where you're not
wearing a tutu
for some 300-pound
murderer named Spike.
You're gonna have to do
better than that, Ariana.
I look great in a tutu.
I bet you do.
Bet you'd like one of these
right about now,
wouldn't you, Howard.
What would you do with it?
Let it slowly dissolve
on your tongue?
No. Bet you'd chew it
to a fine paste
so it would get in your
bloodstream a little faster.
Like I said...
you help me and I'll help you.
Each major system
has its own program.
They can each be
shut down individually.
How?
By entering the right codes.
Can I please have my pills?
What do you got yourself
hooked on, Howard?
Painkillers?
Please.
Choke on 'em, Howard.
Very funny!
Screw you too,
you fucking bitch!
They're never gonna
mess with you assholes!
Never trust a fucking woman!
Especially one named Ariana.
Excellent work, Ariana.
Thank you, sir.
I'd like you to meet
Delta Team One.
Hello.
Captain, this is the unit that's
gonna get you on board that submarine.
What?
Marcus, I'm really
not ready for this.
One of us has to go.
The Navy may be building
quieter and quieter submarines,
but they're still not
equipping them
with wheelchair ramps.
You're the best person
for the job.
You know that.
DSRV bearing 2-4-0.
Roger that.
Turbulence factor, 18 degrees.
Current, 30 degrees at 4 knots.
Contact. Do we
have contact?
Negative on contact.
Captain.
My God, she's a beast.
We have a hard seal.
Admiral, we are locked on.
Dree, check the escape hatch.
Dree, report.
They...
They gassed 'em, Cap.
H-8-M-2-6-9.
Chemicals negative.
Assume defensive series
8-3-5-L-Z.
Come on.
This ain't potpourri.
Make sure there's no heat-sensors,
booby traps, tripwire.
Doc, I need you to
link us up topside.
Yes, sir.
See anything, Hutch?
Negative on explosive
devices, Captain.
You all right?
Yeah.
Nobility Base, do you copy?
This is Team One. Over.
Got anything for me, Doc?
Nothing yet, Captain.
Captain.
One down.
Mac.
What the hell is this?
That's good-bye, New York.
In just under 30 minutes,
President Farrington
will stand before
the leaders of the world
and deliver the keynote speech
for the 1998 drug summit.
For days now, pundits
have been predicting
that the speech will
serve as a platform
for a major announcement.
But as has been the case
all week long,
no one in the White House
will even hint
at what the announcement
might be,
although this morning
a source promised
that it would be,
quote, history-making.
Captain.
What is it?
None of the codes
Thane gave us were accepted.
What!
Son of a bitch lied.
No!
I don't think he did.
Salvatore's hijackers
must have changed them.
Let's just trash
the freaking main-frame.
No!
I know how Thane works.
I'm sure he's incorporated
some safeguards
to make this whole system
sabotage-proof.
We have 28 minutes, gentlemen.
Mac, man the helm.
Sir.
Attempt a manual override.
Doc, what do you have for me?
Still got nothing.
Got to do better than that.
I need to speak with
Henshaw immediately.
Yes, sir.
Cap?
What's the problem?
We got nothing.
Hutch.
Sir.
Prepare the emergency blow system.
Yes, sir.
Everybody hold on.
We're going topside.
Brace yourself.
Ready to fly
in 3, 2, 1.
Blow.
Shit.
Hutch?
No response, Captain.
Let's go again.
Sir!
Okay?
In 3, 2, 1.
Blow!
She's wired!
Damn it, why am I not surprised?
Hutch, clear that passageway!
Yes, sir!
You okay?
You all right?
Nobility Base, this is Team One.
Do you copy? Over.
Come on.
Nothing, Captain.
Keep trying.
Nobility Base, this is Team One.
F1, shift. That will
reboot the system.
System's rebooting.
We have a frequency.
Nobility Base, do you copy?
This is Team One.
Over.
Admiral, they've
secured the cockpit.
You're on speaker.
This is Nobility Base, Captain.
You've shut the system down.
Negative, Admiral.
The codes weren't accepted.
The hijackers somehow transposed.
Thane's emergency
fail-safe sequence numbers.
Captain.
Can you at least
tell which cities
the missiles are targeting?
Negative, sir.
Ariana's trying to work
on that program now.
Prepare to fall-back
contingency.
Keep us posted.
Nobility Base out.
Hutch and Vickers,
move to weapons lockers.
See what you can do to
disengage the firing mechanism.
Mac and Doc.
Take care of Ariana.
Sir.
Cool.
Okay, baby, okay.
Talk to me.
The spheres... Son of a bitch,
the spheres Vickers
brought in, Cap,
I knew I'd seen 'em before.
In the Gulf.
So it is biological.
Yeah, sir.
Which means it'll be
an airborne virus
and it'll be deadly.
Can you guesstimate
the area of contamination?
Based on the size
of that sphere,
depending on how many there are,
I mean, I'd say we're looking at
Manhattan, minimum.
That's 10 million people, Hutch.
Dead people.
What the hell is this?
Cap, we got something.
What do you got, Mac?
Cap, it's right behind
the sonar now.
Son of a...
Confirmed.
Got a problem.
Hutch we got two in the bush.
You're flying solo on this one.
Great.
Vicks.
Mine's down.
Get down!
Come on.
Three down, Cap.
Fail-safe.
Ho, ho, you are clever.
You are...
What is that?
Sounds like the reactors
are swelling up.
We're accelerating.
How the hell
are we accelerating?
There's no one
driving this thing.
It's the codes.
Shit.
Now we're turning.
She's breaking
our holding pattern.
Maybe they got
control of the helm.
No, sir.
She's headed towards
the mouth of the East River.
What the hell's going on
in here, Mac?
Heck if I know, Cap.
Goddamn thing's driving itself.
Sparks.
Sir.
Contact Henshaw.
Yes, sir.
Vicks. Sir.
Scope up.
Yes, sir.
Nobility Base,
this is Team One. Over.
Roger, Admiral. You're on
speaker to Captain Lang.
This is Nobility Base, Captain.
Have you got
control of the helm?
Negative, sir.
At the moment we're belly-up
and on a guided tour.
You are heading
up the East River.
What?
Vicks?
Affirmative, sir.
Son of a bitch.
Salvatore's planning
on making a statement
at the international
drug summit.
What are you talking
about, Captain?
There's a biological bomb and three
Tomahawk missiles on board, sir,
all prepped and hot.
They're headed
for the U.N.
Ladies and gentlemen,
presidents, prime ministers,
it is with the utmost pleasure
that I stand before you today as
the bearer of remarkable news,
news of an historic
turning point
in the worldwide war on drugs.
We got the helm.
Vicks.
Sir.
Have we got enough water
to turn this baby around?
Yes, sir.
Hard to port, sir.
Hard to port!
Eight hundred.
Seven hundred.
Six hundred and closing.
I speak of a surveillance
satellite network
called Iris One...
Come on, come on, turn.
A network so sophisticated that
it will enable us to pinpoint
with great accuracy...
Two hundred.
She's starting to turn.
Even the smallest
amount of narcotics...
One fifty.
She's turning.
As the recent raid
on Humberto Salvatore...
She's turning.
Keep it hard.
Keep it hard over.
Hard over!
Convincingly demonstrated.
At 100.
Hold on.
Armed with this
potent new weapon...
We're clear, Captain!
We're clear! Clear!
Victory in the war
against drugs is ours.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Now for the bomb.
Give me good news, Hutch.
We've got a tanker dead ahead.
Can we avoid her?
It'll be tight.
Starboard!
Come on, baby.
Starboard, Mac, starboard!
Shit! Sons of bitches!
Damn it! Goddamn it!
Clear of the bridge.
Cap...
last phase is complete.
I don't have the codes
to access the trigger
mechanism, Cap.
I understand.
Cap, you got to tell her.
Tell her I need those codes.
You tell her I need those codes!
I understand.
Ariana.
Hutch said he can't
disconnect the last phase
until you give him the codes
for this triggering mechanism.
Cap, we got a problem.
This clock has gone crazy.
It's just jumped from 11 to 9.
There's too many codes.
The odds are against us!
Come on, Ariana.
You're better than that
doped-up little turd.
There's got to be something.
Seven minutes.
What the hell was that, Vicks?
Bottom side, sir.
Three minutes.
Come on!
Look, solider.
We have done our job.
You have got to get
in this guy's head.
You've got to think
like Thane thinks.
What motivates him?
What makes him tick?
Is it money, power, greed?
The dope? What is it,
goddamn it?
What is it?
Come on.
It's me.
A.
R-I.
N.
A.
It was you.
Good work.
Hey, Cap.
Good God, Sergeant.
Yeah.
This sub, sir,
she's breaking up.
Vicks, I need a hand please.
Nobility Base, Nobility Base,
this is Team One.
We have a slight dilemma, sir.
Sub appears to be
taking on a lot of water.
We have, however, defused
the biological bomb,
but it appears we won't be
able to contain her speed.
She's runaway, sir.
Admiral Henshaw, sir.
Presently we are in
possession of eight spheres
of an airborne
biological virus, sir.
We have not had time
to defuse the Tomahawks.
Set your wheel to 3-5-3.
Your priority is to get those
chemicals off that vessel.
Abandon ship.
That is an order.
You heard 'em, people.
We're abandoning ship.
Set the course for 3-5-3.
Let's get the hell out of here.
3-5-3. Lock.
3-5-3, sir.
Pick it up, people.
We're running out of time.
Jesus Christ!
Let's just hope the DSRV's okay.
Goddamn it.
There's a major malfunction
in the seal.
What?
The coupling's cracked.
Must have happened when
we scraped the bridge.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
Hull damage.
Mac, get the hell up here.
We're flooding the tanks.
Captain.
Mac, that's an order!
Get up here!
Captain!
What?
The coupling's shot.
We're not going anywhere.
We're all gonna die.
Unless what?
Feed my cat, Cap.
Mac!
He jammed it.
Whoa.
You got to order him
to get out now!
Skippy!
Finally I'm in.
Mac!
Mac. Mac.
Mac.
Get him on his side, Cap.
Keep his head down
and get him on his side.
Mac.
Come on, buddy.
Keep your head down.
Good job.
Hey, soldier.
What?
No mouth to mouth?