[Guitar playing]
♪
[Cash register beeping]
That'll be 62.03.
[Sighs]
Uh...my money seems
to have mysteriously
disappeared, so...
You want to
put something back?
Yeah.
Um...
I guess
the toilet paper.
[Register beeps]
Did you get them?
You won't be getting...
If you don't quit stealing
money out of my purse.
Oh, yeah. I had to
borrow 20 last night
to pay Pete back.
"Oh, yeah."
All right!
[Music playing]
Yeah, dude.
Now we're going
to some party
up on montrose.
You should
come by, man.
Ha ha ha!
Damn it, Zane,
will you slow down?
Let me just call you
back later, all right?
[Siren]
What the...
No. This cannot
be happening.
What?
This cannot
be happening!
Zane, you don't have
anything in here, do you?
Be cool, ok? Keep
your...Mouth shut.
License and
insurance, please.
There a problem,
officer?
There will be if
you don't hand over
your license
and insurance.
[Sighs]
Here.
You know why I
stopped you tonight,
Mr. Richter?
No. Not a clue.
I clocked you
going over 50.
The speed limit
is 45, man. Come on.
Try 35.
Oh.
Man, look, my girlfriend
and I got in a fight.
I probably missed
the sign, man.
Come on.
It's late, dude.
Just wait here
a minute, please.
What?
Unit 412.
Man!
The car.
I can get
in the car myself!
Get in the car!
Well, looks like we
got something here.
[Sighs]
Yeah. Now would be
a real good time
to start praying.
[Handcuffs click]
[Telephone ringing]
[Beeping]
[Telephone rings]
[Buzzer]
[Ring]
Man: White residence.
Hello?
I, um...
I didn't know
who else to call.
Hannah.
Where...where are you?
Are you all right?
I'm...
[Buzzer]
I'm, um...
Just tell me
where you are.
I'll come get you.
Just tell me
where you are.
Hannah white.
Yeah?
Let's go. Dad's
here to get you.
Hey, Barbie, see if
your old man will
bail US out, too.
Tell him we'll make it
worth his while.
Ha ha ha!
Thanks for coming.
I didn't know about
the drugs. I swear.
Shh. It's all right.
Everything...
Is going to be
all right.
Um...I'll get you
a blanket.
Thank you.
So, we have good news
and bad news.
The bad news is,
the police found enough
drugs in your vehicle
to charge you
and your boyfriend
with intent to sell.
It wasn't mine.
Let me finish.
I just talked to
the da's office.
They're willing to reduce
the charge to possession
if you agree to
testify against Zane.
Ok. What's the
good news?
That was
the good news.
I'm not testifying
against Zane.
Oh...
The man is
a drug dealer.
With two priors. Ok?
Odds are, he's going
to jail for a long while.
There's no reason you should
have to go with him.
Ok. We have one other
option, and that's to try
to convince the judge
that you didn't have
any knowledge that drugs
were in the vehicle.
It's not going to
be an easy sell,
especially since
you live with the guy.
But since this is
your first offense,
you'll possibly get
deferred adjudication.
Layman's?
She'll get off,
providing that
she stays out of trouble
the next 6 weeks.
And there will be a fine.
Ok, well, what if
I don't have the money?
Then you'll go to jail.
I'll pay the fine,
on one condition.
You come home for...
I knew this coming.
Actually, that could
work in your favor.
The judge is more likely
to be lenient if he knows
you'll be living in
a stable environment.
Fine. Whatever.
As long as I don't
have to testify.
Ok.
Man on radio: The son had
disappeared into another realm,
stronger than
his inhabitants...
Congregation:
♪ this is my story ♪
♪ this is my song ♪
♪ praising my savior ♪
♪ all the day long ♪
♪ this is my story ♪
♪ this is my song ♪
♪ praising my savior ♪
♪ all the day long ♪
Blessed assurance,
Jesus ismine.
Let US pray.
Heavenly father, we thank you
for this beautiful day
and for all of these people
who have gathered
in your house
to worship you.
I ask that you be with me
today, heavenly father,
as I deliver your words.
Let them fill
our hearts and minds
with the spiritual
nourishment we need
to be more perfect
servants for you.
In Jesus' name, we pray.
Amen.
[Many people talking]
Thank you.
Sir.
Good to see you.
Always a pleasure.
Good sermon,
daddy.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Hey, you ready for
voice lessons tonight?
When do you think
she'll be ready to get
up and sing for US?
I don't know.
That depends on Hannah.
[Chuckles]
Boy: Hey, look
at the freak.
Woman: Oh, now, Caleb,
that's not very Christian.
The poor girl has
been through a lot,
living with that so-called
mother of hers.
Who is she?
That's
brother Tate's
daughter Rachel.
Looks like she's
going to be
staying with him
for a while.
She may need
a new friend.
You want me
to be her friend?
Hey, it's our
job to reach out
to people
in need.
Looks like
she could use
a positive
influence
in her life
right about now.
Just as long as
you don't let her
influence you.
♪ We're stuck
in this place ♪
♪ we don't want to
look back at our lives ♪
♪ and find out
they were a waste ♪
♪ it's time to
follow our dreams ♪
♪ take a good look
around ♪
♪ can this be
all there is? ♪
♪ I don't want to get
stuck like my... ♪
I don't remember seeing
that one in the hymnal.
Ha ha ha!
Yeah.
It's a little
something I wrote
back when I wanted
to be a rock star.
You wanted to be
a rock star?
Shh.
Don't worry. Your secret
is safe with me.
You ready
to get started?
Come on.
So, when you sing,
always breathe
from your diaphragm.
Ready? Let's go.
My what?
Your diaphragm.
You...
Ok. All right.
Right there.
Ok. Now, focus
your breathing
where my hand is.
Breathe in.
[Inhales]
And out.
[Exhales]
Breathe in.
[Inhales]
Breathe out.
[Exhales]
Nice.
Ok. Try that
singing.
[Singing scales]
[Stops abruptly]
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
That's all right.
That was good.
Don't worry
about it. Come on.
It takes time
to learn how to
breathe correctly.
You're doing
good. You'll get
the hang of it.
Come on. Let's try
something else.
Don't get me wrong.
I love the
traditional hymns.
They're great and all,
but if we are going to
grow as a church,
we got to liven things
up a little.
We got to bring in
more upbeat music,
draw in a younger crowd
on sunday mornings.
Well, good luck
with that.
Dad is pretty old-fashioned
about those kinds of things.
Which is precisely
why I'm glad you're
taking these lessons,
because he won't mind
so much if it's you
up there singing...
that and, well...
Kids are more likely
to relate to you than
an old fogey like me.
You're not that old.
Yeah, well.
I feel like I am.
I just...I don't know
about getting up there
and singing in front
of all those people.
What if I forget
the words or something?
You might.
I'm not going to
lie to you.
It's scary the first
time, but, you know,
the more you do it,
the easier it gets,
same as anything.
Hey.
Look at me.
God gave you
that beautiful voice
for a reason.
Don't waste his
gift by not sharing
it with others.
Hey.
Hi.
Hmm...
Well.
Looks like someone's
got their eye on you.
Jeremy?
Yeah, right.
Oh, I don't know.
He seemed pretty
interested to me.
Even if he were,
it doesn't matter.
I'm not allowed to
go out with guys.
Oh, well.
I guess I'd better get
you home, then, huh?
Caleb, stop that.
You know she don't
eat meat.
You don't?
Father:
She's a vegetarian.
Oh, you don't know
what you're missing.
Lanette here makes the
best chicken-fried steak
this side of paradise.
Lanette:
Oh, come on!
Rachel, have
you started back
to school yet?
Yeah. Today.
She had to
get a shot.
Shut up.
What for?
Her mother wasn't
very good about
keeping up with
her health records.
You know, I'll tell you,
schools today are
so full of bureaucracy
and so devoid of god.
That's why
we home-school.
No politician is
going to tell US how
to raise our children.
Father: Amen.
So what would
2 to the power of 3 be?
Um...uh...
8?
Good.
[Telephone rings]
Now try the next one
on your own.
[Ring]
[Whispers]
Thank you.
Hi.
Hey.
It's Rachel, right?
[Shutter clicks]
Uh, Hannah.
We had dinner
last night.
So, um...
Are you headed home?
Where else?
Cool. Um...
Me, too.
Your dad
lets you smoke?
Never asked.
My parents would
totally kill me.
Not like it's
a sin or anything.
Tell that to my dad.
Where exactly in
the Bible does it say
smoking is a sin?
Well, it says that
your body is a temple,
and anything you do
that's bad for it
is considered a sin.
You mean like eating
steroid-overdosed cows
deep-fried in lard?
That's a really
cool camera.
Are you in photography
class or something?
What photography class?
They don't teach it here.
"There's not enough
money in the budget."
Of course, there's plenty
of money for the football
and baseball teams
to get brand-new
uniforms every year.
It's such bull.
At least you get
to go to school.
You don't like being
home-schooled?
It's ok, I guess.
I don't got to get up
every morning and worry
about my hair or what
I'm going to wear,
but I miss out on
other things, like
homecoming or dances.
Not that my parents
would let me go
to a dance even if
I were in school.
They did seem a little
overly protective.
A little?
Try no makeup,
no dancing,
no listening to
secular music.
Man.
I don't know what's worse...
parents who are too...
Or parents who
couldn't give a...
Soundtrack: ♪ take a while
and take a breath ♪
♪ and let yourself down slow ♪
♪ gather up your memories ♪
♪ hold on to what you know ♪
♪ and everything's been
moving way too fast ♪
♪ you thought that you'd found
something that would last ♪
♪ and it passed ♪
♪ so if you find that
in your mind ♪
♪ you're putting up
your guard ♪
♪ trust me when
I say it's not ♪
♪ supposed to be this hard ♪
♪ you'll fall again ♪
♪ and it'll feel so fast ♪
♪ and every single fear
♪ and every single fear ♪
♪ will pass ♪
Oh!
I can't believe
you're home!
Caleb. Oh, my god.
Look how big you are.
It's amazing how much a person
can change in 4 years.
Are you hungry?
I've got some
roast left over
from last night.
I can make you
a sandwich.
No. I'm fine.
Brought you
some fresh linens.
I have to go to the
grocery store later.
Is there anything you
need me to get for you?
You sure you don't want
something to eat?
No. Um...I'm actually
pretty tired from the drive,
so I think I'm just
going to take a nap.
Ok, then.
Ok, mom, you're going
to make me cry.
I'm just so glad
you're home.
[Sighs heavily]
Is your back
bothering you again?
A long drive.
How was she
on the way up?
[Sighs]
She didn't say much.
Smoked like
a chimney.
You think she's telling
the truth about the drugs?
She was living with
the guy, Maxine.
I'm going to go
lay down.
♪ You're the glory
of my longing ♪
♪ the glory of my tears ♪
Remember your breathing.
♪ The glory...♪
Keep your back straight.
♪ That seemed to last
for years ♪
Project your voice.
♪ To be...
oh, I can't do this.
Ok.
[Music stops]
Yes, you can.
You just got to relax.
That's all you got
to do, all right?
Now, listen to me, ok?
This is real simple,
but you cannot sing correctly
if your shoulders
are up like this.
All right?
The key to singing
is to allow the air
to flow unobstructed
from your lungs,
through your
windpipe, and out.
That's it.
Ok?
Ok. Now, open your mouth.
There you go.
Wider.
Ok. Good.
Good, good, good.
All right. Now relax
these shoulders.
Nice. Ok. Keep them
straight.
Ok.
Relax the arms.
Relax the back.
Ok.
Good. Ok, now,
breathe in with
your diaphragm.
[Inhales]
That's it. Ok.
And out.
[Exhales]
And in.
[Inhales]
And out.
[Exhales]
One more time. In.
[Inhales]
Now sing.
♪ You're the glory
of my longing ♪
♪ the glory of my tears ♪
There you go.
♪ The glory
of my loneliness ♪
Beautiful.
♪ That seemed
to last for years ♪
♪ both: The glory
of my struggle ♪
Ha ha ha!
Nice.
♪ You're the glory
of my longing ♪
♪ the glory of my tears ♪
♪ the glory of my loneliness
that seemed to last for years ♪
♪ the glory of my struggle
to be who I have to be ♪
♪ the good that came
from everything ♪
♪ that seemed so hard on me ♪
♪ the happy ending ♪
♪ to my story ♪
♪ you ♪
♪ you're the glory ♪
♪ you are the glory ♪
[Applause]
I noticed the reeds
weren't there again.
Yeah. They put Jake
on nights.
Dad?
Mm-hmm.
So some of the kids
from church
are going over to the
lake this afternoon,
and they wanted
to see if I could go.
Which kids?
Just Jeremy and them.
And I was going to see if
Rachel wanted to come, too.
[Sighs]
I don't think that's
such a good idea.
I've heard stories
about what
some of the kids
do out there.
Well, I'm not going
to do anything.
We know, sweetheart,
but that doesn't mean
we want you
around it, either.
But...
the answer is no.
[Footsteps]
Right.
Found that duet
I told you about.
It's got...
What's wrong?
What's wrong, huh?
Come on.
It's nothing.
It's just...
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's...I got
invited to go to a party,
and my dad
won't let me go.
Oh, well, I'm sure
he's just trying
to protect you.
It's no big deal.
He can't
protect me forever.
I'm almost 18,
and I'm going to be moving
off to college soon,
but he still
treats me like I'm 2.
I think your dad knows
exactly how old you are.
And how beautiful, hmm?
Hmm? Hmm?
[Chuckles]
That's better.
So who invited you
to the party?
Huh? Who was it?
Was it Jeremy?
Yeah. I told you he
had an eye for you.
He has a girlfriend.
So? That doesn't
mean he's blind.
Heck, if I were
his age...
What?
You'd have an eye for me?
What am I doing?
I'm sorry, Hannah.
I, uh...
It's ok.
I won't tell anyone.
We'd better go.
What a...Creep.
He is not.
He just got caught up
in a moment of weakness.
He promised it
wouldn't happen again.
What if it does?
It won't.
But what if?
So what if?
Then what will you do?
I don't know.
What?
You want him to.
I do not.
Yeah, you do.
No, I don't.
You're so full of...
No, you are.
No, you are!
[Laughter]
Where did all
this food come from?
The ladies from
the church brought it
to welcome Hannah home.
Wasn't that nice?
All that's missing
is the fatted calf.
[Sighs]
Heavenly father, we thank
you for this food
we are about to receive
to our bodies.
We thank you,
heavenly father,
for having our family
back together again.
[Door opens]
Do you mind?
Ahh.
How many of them things
you smoke a day?
Still my conscience.
I'm also
still your pastor.
If there's anything you
need to talk about...
see, that's the problem
with being a preacher's kid.
You can't confide your
secrets to your pastor
without your dad
finding out.
Well, if you can't talk
to me, then go to god.
He is always there.
Yeah. You know,
god and I aren't really on
speaking terms right now.
Maybe that's why you're
having so many problems.
Uh! Dad, look.
I didn't come
to get saved. Ok?
You weren't expecting
a revival on the first
night, were you?
I wasn't
expecting anything.
I'm just trying
to help her.
As her father
or as her minister?
I am who I am, Maxine.
[Sighs]
I can't just turn
the preacher off and on.
You can with me.
That's different.
Maybe we should
consider having her
see a psychiatrist.
Ha ha! They are nothing
but drug-pushers
with prescription pads.
They'll convince her
that it's our fault that
she's so messed up.
That'll make her
hate US even more.
You know she
doesn't hate US.
She just needs
some time to adjust.
And willingness.
Baptism is
a symbol of rebirth.
It's the purification
of our souls
through the cleansing blood
of Jesus Christ.
But more than a symbol, it is
a real commitment to Christ,
witnessed by god
and this community.
[Piano playing]
So...you play the
piano, too, huh?
[Chuckles]
No. Not really.
I took lessons
when I was a kid,
but I only learned one song
before I got tired of playing.
That's too bad.
Could have been
quite the musician.
Well...maybe you
could teach me again.
[Chuckles]
Hannah, there's
something we need
to talk about. Um...
I think we should
perhaps take a break
from music lessons
for a while.
Why?
Is it because of what
happened the other night?
I told you
I wouldn't tell anyone.
It never should have
happened to begin with.
It's not your fault.
Ok? I take full
responsibility
for what happened.
Lilly and I, we're
just...We're having
some issues right now,
and it just...
it's got nothing to do
with you, just stuff.
And we...
I just...I...
Got caught up
in a moment of weakness.
No.
No, not just a moment.
Every time I'm with you,
I forget who I am
and who i'm
supposed to be.
Maybe I want to forget.
I'm sorry.
No. Um...
No.
It's just...What if
someone comes in?
Soundtrack: ♪ cover me
with your hand of mercy ♪
♪ you said
heaven's in place ♪
♪ shelter me in the
shadow of your wings ♪
♪ reach me with
your warm embrace ♪
♪ cover me with
your songs of freedom ♪
♪ you will form
the universe ♪
♪ revive me with
your words of wisdom ♪
♪ see me with
your eyes of peace ♪
♪ giver of mercy,
be my refuge ♪
♪ king of compassion,
be my peace ♪
♪ healer of sorrows,
be my comfort ♪
♪ lord of creation ♪
♪ console me with
your light of kindness ♪
♪ you are the ocean breeze ♪
♪ restore me to my home,
I'm lonely ♪
♪ hold me still
within your peace ♪
Radio: ♪ giver of mercy,
be my refuge ♪
♪ king of compassion,
be my peace ♪
[Radio turns off]
Hey.
It'll be fine.
Ok?
Television: Thousands
of pro-choice activists
flooded the streets...
[TV turns off]
I tell you, this country is
going to hell in a hand basket.
Amen.
Hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
young lady.
Sir?
Come on down here
a minute.
Come on.
Got your lessons
done for tomorrow?
Yeah. Well, I was just
heading up to finish them.
How was your
lesson with Neal?
Uh...fine.
Did you work
on anything new?
Yeah, uh, a duet.
I can't begin
to tell you
how happy
it makes me,
seeing my little
girl up there
singing
for the lord.
She's not a little
girl anymore, daddy.
She will always be
my little girl,
even when she's
an old granny.
Isn't that right,
Hannah bear?
Dad...
Ha ha ha!
It's just sex.
It's just sex?
That's like the
worst thing I could
possibly ever do!
No, it's not.
How do you think
you got here?
You know what I mean.
What, because he's married?
You know what
he told me?
He said that he
and Lilly haven't...
You know...
Since before
the twins were born.
They don't even
share a bed anymore.
If I popped out
4 of his pups,
I wouldn't let him
near me, either.
Wait, you don't...
You don't think that...
I could be...
I don't know.
Did he, you know...
You've got to be
kidding me.
Hasn't anyone told you
anything about sex?
Just that it's
a sin to do it before
you're married.
Maybe you
should ask Neal.
What?
No! No way.
Why not?
Because...I'd be
too embarrassed.
Embarrassed?
You...you wouldn't
understand.
I'm not as experienced
as you are, ok?
Technically, you are
more experienced than me.
Wait.
You're saying
that you've never...
Then how do you know
so much about it?
Just because I know about sex
doesn't mean I've done it.
I guess sex ed wasn't part of
your home-school curriculum.
Are you kidding?
That's why
I'm home-schooled.
Wait. You are telling
me that your parents
home-schooled you
all this time
to keep you out of sex ed
and then you end up
learning about it
on the sunday
schoolroom floor?
Ha ha ha!
It's not funny.
Ha ha! I'm sorry.
You're right.
It's not.
[Both laughing]
I brought you
some breakfast.
You sure you don't want
to come to church with US?
There's a lot of people
who'd love to see you.
I'm sure.
Morning, Neal.
Morning.
Any messages?
Yeah.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Well, how's Hannah?
Hardly been out of her
room since she got here.
I don't know what's
wrong with her.
Whatever it is, she's
not telling me about it.
Hmm.
Well, you let me know
if there's anything
I can do to help.
I appreciate that.
That be all for you?
Pack of lights,
please.
That'll be 8.32.
Thanks so much.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Oh, oh!
Hannah.
Oh, my goodness.
I almost didn't even
recognize you.
Um, I heard
you were back home.
You did. How?
Same way I hear all
the town's gossip...
the prayer chain.
Ha ha ha!
Great. Why doesn't
he just announce it
from the pulpit
while he's at it?
I'll tell Rachel
that I ran into you.
You know, she's back at
school in New York now.
She's about to
graduate...
I got to go. It was
good seeing you.
Take care. Don't be
a stranger.
Wow, rache,
these are amazing.
You'll definitely
be able to get
into a good art
school with these.
Well, that'd be cool.
Who's this?
My mom.
You look like her.
You think?
How come you don't
live with her anymore?
She decided to
move in with this guy,
and I guess he didn't think
it was too cool having
a teenager around.
But...you're
her daughter.
How could she just
leave you like that?
People leave
their kids all the time.
Not all the time.
So what are you
going to major in?
Music, probably.
Neal thinks
I'll make a good
choir teacher
or something
like that.
Is that what you want?
It'll make
my parents happy.
I think Neal is
worried about me
going off to college
and meeting some guy
and forgetting
all about him.
Well, at least
you'll be able to go
out in public together.
Neal and I go out.
The other night,
he took me down
to the lake.
It was really nice.
I'll bet you didn't
even get out of the car.
We didn't need to.
Oh!
We could
see the sunset
over the lake through
the windshield.
You have
such a dirty mind.
Who's this?
Oh, that's some girl
from our old apartments.
She asked me to take
some photos of her
so she could send them to some
modeling agency or some...
There are two types of
christians in the world.
There are
spiritual christians,
and there are
carnal christians.
Now, spiritual christians,
they seek to please god,
to bring honor and glory to him
in their everyday lives.
Amen.
But carnal christians...
they seek to please themselves.
They yield to earthly pleasures
and, well, carnality.
Now, carnal christians may
seem to be spiritual christians.
They come to church.
They sing the hymns.
They even bring covered dishes
to all the church fellowships.
[Baby coos]
But deep down, they are
drowning in sin...
drowning in sin.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Who took this?
Just Rachel.
Rachel.
Does she know?
She's not going
to say anything.
Oh, my god, Hannah.
Are you...
are you trying
to get US caught?
No. Of course not.
I thought you'd like it.
I don't!
Oh, man.
We have to stop
seeing each other.
What?
No. What. Why?
Because of
a stupid picture?
Because it's wrong.
What we're
doing is a sin.
You never cared
about that before.
Yes, I did.
I just...
I don't know. I just
ignored it, I guess.
I...
God spoke to me
today.
He spoke to you?
Yes. Yes. He laid it
on my heart
to get things right
with my life,
before I lose
everyone that I love.
I thought you loved me.
Hannah, I...
I care about you...
a lot.
So much that it
scares me, but i...
that's why I got
to do this now...
While I still can.
Rachel was right.
You are a hypocrite.
Don't you feel
guilty at all?
You know what?
...Guilt!
My whole life, I have been
told that I was a sinner...
have been since
the day I was born.
So why should I
feel guilty?
Why should I
have to repent
for being the way
god made me to begin with?
If he doesn't like what
he created, then...Him!
Hey.
You look like
you could use an ear.
I, uh...
I don't know what
happened to my family.
Would you like
to pray about it?
Heavenly father, we...
Come to you with
a heavy heart
to pray for John
and his family.
♪ Do I have to let go
and watch you walk away? ♪
♪ Do I have to let go and wish
you would have stayed? ♪
♪ I think I'll just
play the part ♪
♪ I think I'll
just play the part ♪
♪ and you may take some time
before you find that ♪
♪ you're back
to good again ♪
♪ right where
you should have been ♪
♪ and even though the letting go
can be the hardest part ♪
♪ I think it's time you start
living like you're loved again ♪
♪ I don't care where you been,
wish you'd let me in ♪
♪ and show me
how to get you ♪
♪ show me how to get you
back to good ♪
♪ back to good ♪
You waiting up for me?
No. I'm
just reading.
How was
your first night?
Fine. I only
screwed up one order.
Ha ha ha!
It's for the court fees.
It's not all of it,
but I should be able
to pay you back by
the end of the month,
depending on my tips.
You don't have
to do that.
Yes, I do.
Well, uh,
I'm pretty wiped,
so I think I'm just going
to head on up to bed.
Yeah. I guess I should
get to bed, too.
Night, dad.
Night.
[Light switch flips]
I think i'm
going to color it
or something.
I think
it looks fine.
You're just glad
she's not wearing
that wig anymore.
No. I never said
anything about the wig.
I learned
a long time ago
there are two subjects
men should always
avoid with women...
their hair
and their weight.
Praise the lord.
[Telephone rings]
Excuse me.
[Ring]
White residence.
Hello?
Yeah.
Is Hannah there?
May I ask who's calling?
A...a friend.
From Houston.
If this is the
"friend" I think it is,
you're not welcome
to call here.
Oh, so you're
keeping her locked
up in your house?
Is that it?
Whatever it takes to
keep her away from you.
Man, you're blaming
the wrong person, dude.
She was totally
messed up way before
she ever met me.
Please...
Don't call here again.
Here you guys go.
Hannah?
I thought that was you.
It's so good to see you.
Isn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah. You look great.
I didn't know
you worked here.
Yeah.
I just started.
Well,
how are you?
Honey. Honey,
she's working.
Of course. Maybe we'll
see you in church
on sunday, then.
Oh! Sorry.
Whoa.
Watch out.
Uh, yeah.
I need a break.
Can you cover my tables?
Sure. You ok?
Yeah.
Did he say
anything?
Yeah. He said, "that'll
be $24, you little whore."
I'm kidding. Here.
Um...
I...i don't, uh...
How?
I, I...
Ok.
Oh, ok.
Hannah, Hannah.
Hannah,
I could, um...
I could go
to jail for this.
Ok?
I could
lose my family.
I could lose my job.
Oh, god!
Your father
could lose his.
Do you think
abortion is murder?
My dad says it is,
but I don't know.
I'm going to
need some money.
Some of US are headed
over to buck's for drinks.
Want to come?
No. I'm pretty tired.
Maybe some other...
You know him?
Uh, yeah.
Um, I'll see you
tomorrow.
Are you sure?
I can...
no. Yeah.
You go ahead.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I, uh...
I just, uh...
How are you?
Actually, I was sort of
hoping that we could talk.
There's nothing
to talk about.
Hannah, please.
Please, I need to
ask you something, ok?
It's important.
I need to ask for
your forgiveness.
You have no idea how
much this has been
eating me up inside
all these years.
I still think about
what happened,
about you, about
what you had to...
shut up!
Just shut the...Up!
You have no idea
what I went through!
Ok, then tell me.
Hey.
Just tell me.
I was up all night,
trying to figure out...
I don't know.
Something.
Do you think I'm doing
the right thing?
It doesn't matter
what I think
or what Neal thinks
or your dad.
This is
your decision.
You got to do
what you think is
right for you.
What's right...
Mm-hmm.
This should be
the street.
[Crowd chanting]
Stop killing babies!
I knew I shouldn't
have let them get
to me like that,
but I was a different
person back then.
If you didn't go through
with it, what did you do?
I prayed.
I begged to god
to help me.
I thought...
Maybe...
It wasn't murder if
I miscarried, right?
But he never did.
He just wasn't there.
Well, what's the worst
thing they could do
to you if you told them?
They'd never forgive me.
Are you sure about that?
I'm not telling them.
I can't.
I just...
Evening, ladies.
Y'all got some
car troubles?
Um, no.
We're just chilling.
Yeah. Well, you
got to be careful
out here at night,
watch out
for the boogeyman.
I like the earring
on your lip.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Hard to get, huh?
What's wrong
with your friend?
She looks a little
down in the dumps.
Um, nothing is wrong
with my friend.
Oh...doesn't look
like nothing.
What's wrong,
sweetie?
Oh, come on.
Your boyfriend
dump you?
Oh, come on, now.
It can't be
that bad.
Why don't you tell
the gardener?
Maybe I could help.
Hannah: Turns out
he could help me.
He gave me these pills,
said they'd take
care of my problem.
Why didn't you
come to me?
I don't know!
I don't know why
I did anything!
All I knew was that my
parents couldn't find out.
That is all I cared about.
Don't! I can't!
I can't.
I...i have to go.
[Engine starts]
[Telephone rings]
[Ring]
Morning.
White residence.
Hello?
Ohh...
What is going on?
That is the third
time today someone's
called and hung up.
You're resigning?
Yeah. I'm afraid
so, John.
It's Lilly.
She wants to move
back to Oklahoma,
be closer to her
family, and I...
Well, I feel like it's
time that I moved on.
You have another church
lined up back there?
No, no. I've decided to
leave the ministry.
Leave?
Neal.
You are the single
best musical minister
this church has ever had.
Well, it's been a
difficult decision,
but I feel like
it's the right one.
Son...are you sure
this is the direction
that god is leading you?
I'm sure.
John, uh...
Thank you...
For everything that
you've done for me
and my family.
I wish I were half
the man you are.
[Telephone rings]
Hello.
Finally
you...answer.
Zane?
Yeah. I've been trying
to call you forever.
Your...dad won't
ever let you talk.
You're out of jail?
You know they can't
keep me locked up.
Come on.
Uh...
You probably shouldn't
be calling me here.
But, babe, I'm dying
to see you.
I mean, you said
in your letter that
you were going to...
I know.
I know what I said.
Look, I can't come back
to Houston right now.
You don't have to.
I'm here.
You were right. This
town is a piss hole.
What? Wait
you're here?
You mean
you're in Trinity?
Yeah. Can you
meet me?
Where?
[Cartoon playing
on television]
Hey, blondie!
I like it.
Television:
There's going to be
a guy in it named
pat Buchanan.
[Telephone rings]
[Ring]
Hello.
Is Hannah there?
No. I'm sorry. She's
already gone to work.
This is Camille
from the restaurant.
She didn't
show up tonight.
What time was she
scheduled to come in?
Two hours ago.
I was sort of worried
because of that guy.
What guy?
When we left last night,
there was this guy
waiting for her
in the parking lot.
I could tell she was
kind of freaked out
about him being there,
but she said she knew him.
This guy...did he
have a scruffy look,
have tattoos?
No tattoo.
Drives a minivan.
I've seen him in
the restaurant before
with his family.
Got a bunch of kids.
Ok. Thanks for calling.
I'll make sure Hannah
gets back in touch
with you just as soon
as she comes in.
John.
What's going on?
I don't know, but i'm
going to find out.
[Door opens and closes]
[Telephone rings]
Hello.
Lanette, this is Maxine.
I have an urgent
prayer request.
Overlapping voices:
Poor preacher and Ms. Maxine.
Now, I heard
she was his maid.
You know, she went to
the rectory every day...
[Voices overlap]
[Ring]
[Beep]
Hello.
And this rainbow shall
be a token of the covenant
between me and...
I just got a call
from the prayer chain.
Looks like Hannah
has run off again.
[Cellphone rings]
Yeah.
Maxine: I just got a call
from the prayer chain.
Hannah is here,
at the motel.
[Knock knock knock]
Hello.
This is
the motel manager.
I don't think
anybody's in there.
Can we make sure?
Oh, my lord!
Call the police.
Uh!
Ah!
All right, Zane,
it's confession time.
Now, you tell me
where my daughter
is right now,
or I swear to you, boy,
I will rip your arm off!
[Water splashes]
Muffled male voice:
Drowning in sin.
Oh, my heavens!
She's ok.
She just passed out,
I think.
Let's get her
upstairs to her bed!
I'll get her
a wet rag.
Ok.
John.
I...i, um...
I found her at church,
in the baptistery.
The baptistery?
Here we go.
Thank goodness
you found her
when you did.
Yeah.
As far as i'm
concerned, John,
nobody needs to know
about this, ok?
I mean,
the last thing
that I want to see
is her in prison.
She doesn't
deserve that.
You know...
For the longest time,
I've tried to figure out
where it went wrong for Hannah.
I mean, how could somebody
change so suddenly?
I guess I've always
blamed it on the drugs.
But now...
I need to ask you
something, Neal.
Your leaving our church
wouldn't have anything to do
with my daughter,
would it?
Oh, John.
Oh, Neal, why?
Why?!
You listen to me, ok?
Just hear me out. I...
I, um...
I wish I had an
explanation that would
make this easier
for you, but I, I...
I don't.
I never meant for
any of this to happen.
I loved her.
No!
Ilove her, Neal.
I trusted you!
You son of a...
Uh!
Caleb, Caleb, Caleb!
Come here, son. No.
No, son, no. That's not
the way we do it.
No. No, son.
No, son.
It's all right.
You...you get out
of my home!
No, son. No, son.
It's all right.
It's all right, son.
This is a blow
to our church family.
We will not be disrupted
in our choir practices,
in our sunday services.
We'll be able to get assistance
from our sister churches
and have somebody
fill in for Neal
on a temporary basis.
Now...
You thinking you should
have left me in jail?
I was, um, thinking about
when you were little.
You used to love
to come in here.
You'd sit at that piano
all day long
playing the same song
over and over again.
Drove me crazy.
"This little light
of mine."
You remember that.
It's the first song
I ever learned.
Neal resigned.
He's leaving the ministry,
going back to Oklahoma.
[Crying]
You got to let it go,
sweetheart.
Just let it go.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, shh.
I thought I could
protect you.
I couldn't.
I...i failed you.
No. No.
No.
Please don't think that.
You never
gave up on me...
Even after...
Everything
I put you through.
Sweetie, I could
never give up on you.
You're my child.
You're my little girl.
You're a part of me.
But I'm not you.
I know.
I...i know.
[Sobbing]
[Music playing]
So are you back for good
or just visiting?
Just visiting.
I got an internship
lined up when I get back.
That's cool.
I always wonder what it
would have been like
if I'd gone to college.
You could still go.
There aren't many music
schools around here.
There's tons in New York.
New York?
Why not?
I really
missed you, rache.
I did try to call.
I know.
I know, and I meant
to call you back.
It's just...
it's all good. You don't
got to explain.
I get it.
You know
what's funny?
I was supposed to be
the good influence
on you.
What do you say
we get out of here?
Lead the way.
♪ I'm getting used
to the sounds ♪
♪ that this old house
makes at night ♪
♪ and I'm getting
used to the way ♪
♪ this guitar feels
when I play it right ♪