(gun cocked)
- [Man] Money.
Nobody gets dead.
On the floor, asshole.
(people screaming)
Fill it.
Let's do it.
Come on.
Come on!
(intense music)
(shot fired)
Come on!
(tires screeching)
(melancholy music)
(stream running)
(birds chirping)
- Whatever else.
Your daddy was a god fearing
man, Travis.
It ain't right.
- It says here.
I, uh,
I can't read that fine print.
Sheriff, would you mind?
(clock ticking)
- Says here your daddy left
just about everything to that
preacher fella on TV.
Money and stock mostly.
Of course, you do get all the
land.
And he goes on to say
if you work hard
you just may make something
of your life.
Says you get the family
collectibles.
That would be your mother's
embroidery.
This coin collection.
And your mother's thimbles.
- Don't know much about
thimbles.
But as I recall
it's an impressive coin
collection.
That's his daddy's chain,
ain't it?
- Well that's worth a heap of
money.
Maybe you'd like to keep it
down at the bank.
- No.
- Know, your daddy showed me
a couple of confederate bills
once.
They're probably not worth
anything
but uh
I'd be willing to pay top
dollar.
What do you say?
- No.
- Easy, Andrew.
You're starting to drool all
over the judge's table.
He can't break up that
collection.
It's been in his family for
over a hundred years.
- Well, I thought I'd give it
a shot.
- Is that all?
- Well, if you two would sign
this we'll get it done.
(melancholy music)
(chickens clucking)
(horses neighing)
- [Bobby] Hey, Travis.
You up there in the hayloft?
You need to get these stairs
fixed.
- [Travis] Bobby, what a
surprise.
You usually knock.
Come on in.
- Thought you might be
thirsty.
Sorry about your dad.
(bottles opening)
I'm off duty.
So when are you taking off?
- I don't know.
Soon I guess.
- That's good.
You've been talking about it
since high school.
Traveling the world.
Meeting exotic women.
The way I see it
now's your big chance.
- I guess they're not women
that know you.
- Talking about Chris Bodie
again?
God damn.
That was just perfect.
You know she was hitting on
me at the hoe down.
I
- She was my date.
- Gotta move fast.
- You move late.
- You'll never leave.
- You never know.
- Yeah.
I think I do.
Catch you later.
(scary music)
(organ playing)
(country music)
- Thanks for the ride.
(truck engine roaring)
(birds chirping)
Hi there.
Oh boy.
I think I'm lost.
Kelly.
- I'm sorry.
Travis.
- Please to meet you, Travis.
Could you help me?
I was trying to get to
Watkins.
- Watkins?
You're here.
Outside of Astonville.
Watkins is there
30 miles away.
- You know if there's a
bus or anything around there?
- Train runs through town.
You hungry?
- What?
- You hungry?
'Cause if you are.
I was just getting ready to
have some lunch.
You can join me if you want.
And then I can take you back
into town afterwards.
If you're hungry.
- Okay.
Let's eat.
- I haven't really thought
about it
until just now.
Hey.
You forgot your bag.
(clock ticking)
- Oh my God.
How long I was asleep?
- Four and a quarter hours.
- Oh my God.
I'm so sorry.
Could you take me into town?
Get a room at the Traveler's
Club.
- It's too late.
I mean
I'm sorry I let you sleep so
much.
I guess I figured
well I figured that
if it would be alright with
you
that you could
stay here tonight.
It's a big house.
All the rooms.
The doors lock.
Besides I sleep in the
hayloft.
- The hayloft?
How come?
- I just do.
My father lived in the house.
- Oh wow.
Nice collection.
Winchester
1894.
- '92 actually.
You know guns?
- Yeah.
They kinda run in the family.
- Yeah?
Mine too.
It's good 'cause we got 'em
all over the house.
- Do you have to stay out in
the hayloft?
- If you feel safer.
- I'd feel safer
if you stayed in the house.
- Sorry?
- I'd feel safer if you
stayed in the house.
- Sure.
I mean, okay.
Room's this way.
- Travis?
You're a real gentleman.
- [Travis] Station's just a
little further up.
("Somebody's Fool" by David
Allan Morgan)
So what are you gonna do when
you get to Watkins?
- Ricky went there to be an
actor
at that Gem Theater, you know?
- The dinner theater in
Watkins?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
- Sure I'm sure.
- Well.
I think it's been closed for
a lot of years.
- Really?
- I'm pretty sure.
We used to go there when I
was a kid.
- Well shit.
(dramatic music)
- When's the last time you
talked to him?
- Well, we sorta broke up.
Before he left and
I told ya I was gonna
surprise him.
- I'm sorry.
Eat somethin'?
Come on.
- [Jolene] If I had to fly
back to London.
To cover up the incompetence.
I would not be pleased.
Because I told you.
- [Lutie] Hey Travis.
- Hey Lutie.
Where's Earl?
- He's kinda takin' a day off.
Can we get a couple OJ's
please.
- Comin' right up.
Hey, Travis.
Our TV is kinda actin' up.
Suppose you could have a look
at it?
- Sure.
- [Jolene] I'm sick and tired
of you screwing things up
when I'm not there to hold
your hand.
- Who's the girl?
- I wouldn't if you don't
know.
- So introduce me.
- She's just passin' through
town.
- Then I suppose to tell her.
- You're Travis Graham,
aren't you?
- That's right.
- I'm Jolene.
I hear you're looking to sell
some property
in this area.
- News sure does travel fast.
- I'm looking to buy.
Do you think I could see your
place?
- Well, there's really not
much to see.
- You're not gonna sell your
house are you?
- Depends on what she's
offerin'.
- Oh, I'm sure I could make
you
a very attractive offer, Mr.
Graham.
- Excuse me.
Travis, didn't you say
your great granddaddy built
that house?
Can't just up and.
Look I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassing you.
Take it from somebody
who's never really had much
of a home.
Family.
Pretty soon you're gonna
start to miss it.
- Miss Leder.
I appreciate your interest.
But I'm really not sure yet.
- There's no harm in just
taking a look.
Is there?
- I'll let you know.
Nice to meet you.
- Okay.
- Small town.
Nobody minds their own
business.
- Travis, take your hat off
when you're inside.
- Sheriff Bob.
- That's the sheriff?
I've never seen a sheriff
without a gun before.
- He doesn't need one.
- Hey Travis.
You drivin' the Chevy to the
hoedown?
Wouldn't be the same
without an arrival from the
Graham family.
- I hadn't thought about it.
- A hoedown?
I love a hoedown.
- Don't you have some place
to go?
- Nowhere to go.
No money to get there.
Maybe you could use a hand
around the ranch.
- Maybe.
- [Anchorwoman] Two armed
robbers
got away with over $10,000
dollars.
- I tell you.
It's one damn crazy world out
there these days.
(crashing noise)
- You think I'm sellin'?
This is my place.
God damnit!
(screams)
- Put that bat down.
- Earl. - Earl, you put that
bat down
or I'm dropping you where you
stand.
(glass shattering)
- Let's just all calm down
now.
Earl, you drive away your
customers.
- You back down or you're
goin' down.
- You better get your son's
gun out of my face
this is my place.
I ain't fuckin' around.
- Put the gun down, Bobby.
I said put the gun down.
Now.
Earl.
My thickheaded, jackass son's
not listenin' to me.
What I'm gonna do
is walk over there
and take his gun away.
Don't want you puttin' that
bat
upside my head now.
- Do it, Bob.
Do it.
- Bobby.
Give me the gun.
- Please put the bat down,
Sir.
- Deputy, you don't give me
that gun
you can give me your badge.
- There you are, Earl.
You're callin' the shots now.
- Get him out of here, Bob.
- Mr. Yates would like you to
leave his diner.
- What are you lookin' at?
- You think maybe that bat
could use a rest?
Let me get you a cup of
coffee.
You and me and Lutie will
talk.
- Now you know why he doesn't
need a gun.
(crickets chirping)
(soft country music)
(dog barking)
- I'm sorry.
Your mom
she had such nice things.
- Maybe don't tell 'em in
shorts.
That's real nice.
You being here.
- Sorry I'm not more help but
these gloves are so big.
Do you smell that?
- Yeah, somethin'.
- Let's check it out.
Oh my God.
It's so sad.
What happened?
- Must have got separated
from his mom.
Then the coyotes got to him.
- Poor baby.
- Excuse me.
I'm gonna burn it in the
furnace.
- Burn it?
Shouldn't we have buried it?
- Dogs would have just come
and dug it up.
- Wow, I love Paris by night.
- Sorry.
- You know.
There's nothing more romantic
than sharing a late night.
- Sydney?
- I lived there.
- Really?
What was it like?
- Well.
You know.
It's a strange thing but
it's a lot like Astonville.
I'm joking.
Paris.
Paris is breathtaking.
But I personally prefer this.
- Ma'am.
- I'll tell you all about it
when you let me take a look
at your place.
- Well, it's like I said.
I'm not so sure that I want
to sell right now.
- Now.
You don't want to sell
or your girlfriend doesn't
want you to sell?
What about your father?
- What about him?
- He loved that house very,
very much.
- So?
- You know it's a small town
and people talk.
From what I gather.
Your father loved that house
more than just about anything.
(dramatic music)
- I really should be going.
Well, that's just folks
talking about
things that they don't
understand.
- All the more reason to get
away.
Don't you think?
I'm staying at Tanner's Inn.
Not exactly The Savoy but.
I must admit.
I'm used to getting what I
want, Mr. Graham.
I am not a patient woman.
- Whoo!
God, it's beautiful here.
I could stay here forever
and never get tired of it.
Who's place is that?
- Opal and Arthur Del Ripple.
They're out of town for a
while.
Do me a favor.
Remind me that I gotta feed
their cat.
- Sure.
- So anyway
tell me more about Corpus
Christi.
- Yeah, well that's where I'm
from originally, you know?
Texas.
Then Milwaukee.
(rifle blast)
So what was that?
- Almost dinner.
- Shotgun worse than that.
It's a tough shot though.
- Well I just like to try my
luck.
- There's some to the left of
the oak.
- That's a tough shot.
- Yeah, right flank.
(rifle blast)
Steady hand.
Crazy heart.
Runs in my family.
("The Great Divide" by David
Allan Morgan)
Do you think you could give
me a massage?
(fire crackling)
(moaning)
You okay?
- Yeah.
- That's okay.
(erotic music)
What's this?
- Scar.
- From what?
- Football.
(birds chirping)
- Shit.
I was patented.
- You're so cute.
- [Travis] My parents didn't
want me.
- You didn't.
I thought I was a bad kid too.
My Uncle Buddy.
My brother insisted my Mom
told me
Families can be so screwed up.
That won't happen to us.
'Cause we're the best of our
marrow
(car horn honking)
- Hi.
I was on my way to the
property down the road
and I thought I'd stop by and
say howdy.
- Howdy.
Some car.
It's nice to see you.
- Is this a good time to look
around?
(suspenseful music)
- I really don't know.
- Tick tock, Mr. Graham.
Bye.
(car engine starting)
(sneezing)
- Hi cutie pie.
- Hi.
- I found this under the gun
case.
What's it for?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
(clock ticking)
(suspenseful music)
- Travis?
- Yeah.
- Hi, how are you?
- Good, how are you?
- I'm good.
You're handy with TVs aren't
you?
- Sure.
- Well, the one in my hotel
room
there's something wrong with
it
and nobody's come by to take
a look at it
and well
do you think you could spare
the time
just to have a quick look?
Please?
- Well, I really.
- Oh, it won't take too long.
Please Travis.
- Sure.
Loose cable
just like a food mixer.
- Really?
That's a coincidence.
I'd like to give you
something.
I wrote this.
I hold my hands so tightly
together
that they begin to sweat.
The skin cracks and peels
from the center of my bones.
Teeny
tiny
baby chickens.
Will not be your finger.
Stand
silhouette mans.
One of them is turned off.
And the other
the big fancy car.
No.
No, no.
It's okay.
It's love.
It's meant to have a sort of
ironic humor.
- I really should be going.
- No, no.
Come and sit down.
I have a little presentation.
- I don't understand.
Mr. Anton's on the island of
Corfu.
But
he called it be it's Greek
name.
Kerkyra.
I was only 19 years old.
He had to have been more than
twice that.
He told me many things.
Oh, oh,
this one.
This one is my favorite.
The world becomes miserable.
These light things.
Sit down.
I took my birth control pill.
Let's go to bed.
Now where do you think I got
that one?
- I don't know.
- Lost.
Because I was magnet.
You see.
I lied to you just now.
It wasn't meant at all.
It was a purposefully sunny
Australian day.
My dear Smith Alec.
- I'm sorry.
(seductive music)
We'll have to do something
about all of this.
Shh.
(water running)
(erotic music)
- What are you doing?
- Incense.
(pounding noise)
- How new is the hair cut?
- A hair cut.
- Nice.
- Thanks.
This the bank robbers?
- Yeah, they robbed the bank
out at Two Pines this morning.
The teller got a look at the
two inside. But not the
driver.
Where were you this morning?
- I'll see you later, Bobby.
- Travis.
- Where?
Where is it?
- [Travis] Kelly?
- Yeah?
- What are you doing?
- I'm opening up the room.
It's a little stuffy in here.
- That's not a very good idea.
You shouldn't be doing that.
This was my father's room
and no one's supposed to be
in here.
- Oh, come on.
I'm not hurtin' nothin'.
What's with the hairdo?
It's so short.
And there's no stuff in it.
(water running)
- Turn around.
Soap.
What is this, now?
What's Kiki?
- Me.
Kelly.
Kiki, you know.
My sister
my sister did that.
- Did he call you that?
- No.
Not even in front of the
wrong.
- Okay.
What about.
- That would be.
(country music)
Howdy.
- Hi Travis.
I closed my London deal and I
I had nobody to celebrate
with.
So I.
- So we're celebratin'.
And I'm doin' a little
cleanin'
around the house.
- Aren't you gonna
congratulate me?
- Congratulations.
- I congratulated you already.
- Thank you.
Thank you, both.
- I guess now you can
get that look at my place
that you've been meain' to.
- No, no.
No.
- I didn't look.
- She didn't.
That's true.
She did not look.
I said no
talking about that.
- That's right.
Absolutely
no business.
- [Travis] So slow.
- No, you take the cross.
(screaming)
(laughing)
(clock ticking)
Come on.
You didn't pay your bill you.
- Stay here.
I'll be right back.
- [Jolene] We're scared.
Travis it's dark
and there's fleas and mice.
- Open.
Beer or whiskey.
- Beer.
And whiskey!
- Okay.
(rock music)
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Drinks.
Music.
Wait.
Wait no.
Let me get my.
What do you guys wanna listen
to?
I'm looking at country.
(dramatic music)
- Don't.
That's enough.
- I told you what hand with
the bet.
Now look at you.
Two women in your house
What are you gonna do about
us?
- Tell her yourself.
Please don't.
(erotic music)
- What?
I'll tell you when.
You don't need to be watching.
I guarantee he wishes he were
you.
Hello.
- Good morning.
Where's Jolene?
- She got up early.
And just denied her.
- What about you?
- No one forces me to do
things I don't wanna do.
Nice.
Almost natural.
I was thinkin'.
As long as Jolene's in town
maybe she could stay here.
It's lonely in a motel.
- You serious?
- Why not?
I mean
I don't think it will last
night.
It be fun to have her.
It be like our own family.
- Morning, Travis.
- Morning.
- Usual?
- Yes please.
- [Robber] Alright, everybody.
Quiet.
Money.
Nobody gets dead.
- Andrew.
- [Robber] On the floor, big
boy.
I said get down, lard ass.
- No heroes here.
Isn't that right, Andrew?
- [Robber] You.
Open that drawer.
Give me the money.
- Cops.
Is comin'.
Let's go.
- [Robber] Get out of my
fuckin' way.
- Hey.
Bobby!
(gun shots fired)
- Daddy!
Jesus Christ!
No, daddy!
(gun shots fired)
Freeze you son of a bitch.
(dramatic music)
Get an ambulance now.
Call Sheriff Knight in Hurley.
Tell him to set up roadblocks.
Everything's he got.
Go!
(engine revving)
- [Robber] Fuck you!
We're stayin' here.
Bullshit!
(soft rock music)
(Kelly screaming)
Don't fight me.
Don't fight me, baby.
Well.
Lookee here.
Daddy's home.
Just in time.
'Cause I'm fixin' to fuck her.
- Drop it.
- No, you son of a bitch.
You drop it.
This sweet little bitch.
She's gonna be one big fat
greasy stain on your carpet.
Comprende?
- Okay.
- What's a matter, boy?
You ain't got no balls.
(intense music)
You done fucked up, boy.
Now
I'm gonna cut your dick off.
And then I'm gonna make you
eat it, boy.
(gun shots fired)
- Kelly, don't!
- Fuck you!
(crickets chirping)
(dog barking)
They were sure mad when they
got here.
- They?
- There was a girl.
Think she was drivin'.
She ran off down across the
road.
I don't know what they were
doin'
but they were arguin' pretty
bad.
- You alright?
You Okay?
You don't feel bad or sad or
nothin'?
- No.
I'm okay.
I shouldn't feel bad.
Tried to hurt me
now he's.
His fault he's.
- I gotta call Bobby Jr.
- No.
- Yes. I saw we should trust
him
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
- Baby, think about what just
happened here.
I gotta call Bobby Jr.
He can take care of all of
this.
- No.
It's over.
We don't have to call. We
don't have to call anybody.
- Calm down, it's gonna be
okay
if I just call Bobby Jr,
alright?
Please?
- No!
(crying)
We.
We don't
Don't have to call.
It's you and me, baby.
We can keep this between us.
- His partner's dead too.
I found him in their car.
I really should go and take
care of it.
- When I'm done.
- Ah!
Shit.
- I haven't told anyone this
before.
Three years ago this man
my neighbor
came in to borrow some sugar.
So he said.
When I went to the kitchen to
get it.
Grabbed me by the hair
and bent me over the kitchen
table.
I couldn't.
He lifted my dress
and cut off my underwear with
his pocket knife.
Said he'd cut me too if I
move.
I heard his zipper.
Then he got on top of me.
And I reached and I clawed on
that table.
Then he dropped his knife.
I grabbed it.
He slapped me in the head
and I cut his arm.
He fell forward on top of me
on the floor
and I kept stickin' on him
over and over and over.
Then he died.
They say I was a bad girl
from a bad family anyways
so I must of asked for it.
And he gave his 10% to the
church.
And that makes good.
Daddy didn't believe me
either.
So I ran.
They were gonna stuff me in
this jail with kids
with psychiatrists but
my sister took me away.
She said
nobody fucks with family.
Cops around here will think
I asked for it again.
Know what I mean?
- Nobody has to know about
what happened here tonight.
Alright, you're next, partner.
(car engine humming)
Shit.
- Hi.
What are you doing?
- Just fixing some things.
- What?
- Just things.
- Well.
Hurry up and come inside
please.
I think she's lying to you.
Okay?
How long?
- Two minutes.
I'll see you inside.
- Alright.
Don't be long.
("Catch My Soul If You Dare"
by Stella)
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I forgot.
Let me make it better.
Oh.
- Ow!
- Oh, Travis.
You need to take a shower.
Bad.
Why don't you give us a rest.
Okay?
(water running)
- Didn't take much convincin'.
Said the motel beds aren't as
comfortable as ours.
- Company is better too.
Hi.
- So, now okay?
- Sure.
- Good.
Left.
First second.
Right.
- I'll fine it.
- Four deaths have been
attributed to them.
As well as the theft of
what's believed to be
over $200,000 dollars.
In other robbery related news.
Services for Sheriff Robert
Brody
will be held this Saturday
at the Newport Church in
Astonville.
The Kiwanis Club as acting
ushers.
- I
I know.
- Know what?
- It's okay.
Kelly, she told me.
You did the right thing,
Travis.
No.
It's best for everyone this
way.
Trust me.
So, um.
You didn't like
think of calling the bank or
anything
did you?
- No.
Just keep on.
- Have you looked through it
yet?
No?
- No.
No.
Can't be right.
There's only $7,000 dollars
here.
- What?
- That's it. Just the money
from the bank in town.
- Where's the rest from the
other robberies?
- I don't know.
- They probably stashed it
after each hit, you know?
In case they got caught and
had to leave.
I can't believe all this
stuff.
- What?
- Nothing.
I mean.
Just the plans for their next
job.
Maps.
Timed schedule.
They were gonna hit the bank
up in Hurley.
- So?
I was just thinking if
maybe
we could do
what they were planning to do.
And then dump the car.
I mean
no one would be any the wiser.
- What?
(dramatic music)
- You're not serious.
(laughing)
- Why not?
- 'Cause we're not bank
robbers.
That's why not.
- I'm telling you something,
Travis Graham.
I've been a million different
things
and a million different
places.
I've experienced things
you've never even dreamed of.
And I didn't get to those
experiences
by playing it safe.
- Wait a minute.
- Oh, come on, Travis.
Live for once.
- What if we get caught?
- We won't get caught.
This is the perfect
opportunity.
The real robbers are dead,
right?
And we're the only ones that
know that.
We've got their car.
And we have alibis for the
other robberies.
All we have to do is get away
clean.
What a rush.
God, just taste it.
- Let's do it.
- Not you.
- Why not me?
I'm a good driver.
- Travis, it says right here
that after shift change
there's only two tellers and
one guard.
The manager's at lunch.
So, we're in and out clean.
- Didn't you ever play cops
and robbers
when you were a kid?
Didn't you?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- I'll wait.
Let me guess.
Bobby Jr played the cop.
And you played the robber.
Am I right?
- Yes.
- Bobby Jr. announces you
Travis.
First time I met him.
That day in the diner.
When he told me that you
might wanna sell some
property.
He made
a complete mockery of you.
Now
I'd have thought
you might wanna turn the
tables for once.
- You have no reason to use
this.
- Okay.
Fine.
I mean we're gonna do it.
With or without you.
It be a lot easier with you
but.
Come on, Kelly.
(laughing)
We'll do it.
- I just need a minute to
think.
- What you got to think about?
Come on.
It be a good story for our
grandkids
God dangit!
Rob the bank!
(clock ticking)
- This is crazy.
(rock music)
- [Kelly] Come on!
- Those are different till
right?
- Yep.
- When do I get a gun? - You
don't get one.
- I'm a better shot than you.
- You won't need one.
Don't need to be a robber to
think that.
- Just in case, okay? - I
don't want this one.
You take it.
- Here.
- Take it, Travis.
- I'm so wet right now.
- Ready?
- In and out.
Clean and fast, right?
- Right.
- Right?
- Right, yes.
- Let's do this.
(heavy country music)
- [Travis] Quiet!
Money.
No one gets dead.
Everybody on the floor now.
I said get down on the God
damn floor.
Alright, Macho Man, get down
there.
Where the hell is the guard?
- Don't be afraid, darlin'.
Be nice and you'll be home in
time for supper.
Fill her up.
- Get up.
Where's the guard?
Get out of there.
Where the hell is the fucking
guard?
- Hurry up.
Come on, let's go.
- He's at lunch.
- Shut up.
- Come on, come on.
- Shit.
- Fill her up.
- Please, for the Jesus of
God, hurry.
- Hurry!
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
Fill a bag.
Come on.
Fill her up.
- Freeze!
- Make your choice, Mister.
I said make your choice.
- No!
(shots fired)
- Fuck me!
Come on, let's get out of
here.
Piece of shit.
- Come on, Travis.
- Start the car, Kelly.
I think I just pointed though.
Fucking old man shouldn't
have tested me.
- Did you kill him?
- I hope not.
- Are you okay?
- No, I gotta drive.
(shouting)
- Let's get us a son of a
bitch.
- What you do, man?
(police siren wailing)
- Shit!
(screams)
- Oh, my God!
- Hold on.
I'm gonna blow his tires.
- No, what are you, Travis?
- Come on.
- When you gonna shoot his
tires?
- Throw the bag.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Knock it off.
- Give us a kiss for this.
(shouting)
Cops can't drive.
Let's go.
I wanna fuck.
- Stop it.
Stop it.
- I'm fucking you so hard.
- Travis, don't.
- You want it.
- No.
Stop it, you asshole.
- Shut up.
- Let me go.
You want it.
I know you want it.
Bitch.
Shut up.
I'm fucking done this before.
Just shut up.
- Baby.
You okay?
- Oh, God.
He's gone crazy.
- Who the fuck do you think
you are?
- [Newscaster] Story of the
bank robbers
continues to grow each day.
Oddly enough
the suspects dumped a
thousand dollars worth of
money
by throwing it at the squad
car.
Officer Mike Thorton who had
spotted
and was following the
suspects.
(police sirens wailing)
- Sorry to wake you, Travis.
- No problem.
What's up?
- Another robbery.
Guard got shot.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Strange you know.
The roads around Hurley got
closed off pretty quick.
They're definitely still in
the area though.
You haven't seen or heard
anything have you?
- No.
- Those girls with you here?
Jolene and
- [Travis] Kelly.
- Kelly.
Yeah.
I'm gonna need to talk to
them.
- Sure.
- [Bobby] Were they around
here today?
- Working with me all day.
Why?
- Nothing, it's just.
The witness from the robbery
out in Two Pines said that was
a woman in the gang of three.
What do you know about this
Jolene any way?
This real estate lady.
- She's alright.
Look, um
what difference does it make?
I mean I just got through
telling you
that she was working with me
here all day.
- Right.
Right.
- Bobby?
- I miss him, Travis.
I miss him.
- Your daddy was a
a good man.
And a good sheriff too.
- I just want to do him proud.
You know, I just wanna.
Damnit.
How do you get rid of this
feeling, Travis?
- Things were different
between me and my father.
- Right.
You be careful, Travis.
These people don't seem to
think too much about killin'.
- Go home and get some sleep,
Bobby.
I'll call you if I hear
anything.
- Thanks, Travis.
- Morning.
- I missed you last night.
Sorry.
You know about.
- Whatever.
- What are you doing?
- You know
you hurt her.
Did you hear me, Travis?
I said you hurt her.
- [Travis] Come on, Jolene.
What am I suppose to do?
I told her I was sorry.
- Bobby Jr's here.
(dramatic music)
- Shit.
What's up?
- We're covering the area.
We narrowed it down to your
property
and the Salisbury's just
north.
Down to James parcel in the
west.
And the Del Ripple place
across the way.
- Wow, you think they're
still around?
- Yeah, we're pretty sure.
- Bulldog Murphy saw a black
car
travelin' the harvest trail
just a couple miles
from where Sheriff Knight's
deputy
got run off the road.
- No shit.
- Yeah, they're here.
They're hiding out somewhere.
Listen, Travis.
I'm gonna need you to take me
around your place.
Out to the lake.
Your granddaddy's moonshine
shack.
Any place that you think they
might be hidin'.
- No problem.
Can you hold on just a second?
- Yeah.
I'll be in the truck.
Hurry up.
- He wants to see the back
point.
He might want to come in here
and look around.
So hide everything.
- Wait.
Just in case.
Good luck.
- [Travis] How's the guard
from the bank in Hurley?
- Dead.
He lost too much blood.
You're awful quiet, Travis.
Something you want to tell me?
- Nope.
- You sure?
- Yep.
- Come on, you did it. Didn't
you, Travis?
- Did what?
- You doin' one of those
girls, or what?
- Well, you do what you can?
- What you get?
You get a little pussy
you turn into an asshole.
- I guess it's my turn now.
You jealous?
- Jealous?
Hey
look.
There.
(hard country music)
Red.
Red I got 'em.
I'm in pursuit of the black
lemon.
Heading around the lake
to the Graham property.
Heading north.
(police sires wailing)
Get out.
- What are you doing out here?
- Well, you said to hide
everything.
- That didn't mean to move
the car.
- Well, I thought you guys
were looking around
on the other side of the lake.
You almost got us caught.
You almost fucked up
everything.
Idiot.
- What you think we should
have done
left in the barn 'til these
hillbilly cops
done and looked there?
- [Red] Repeat.
Robbery suspects drivin' down
by Mortimer.
- Roger that. Red, we got 'em
pinned down
at Travis's and Del Ripple
place.
I'm sure of it.
I'm gonna double check
Travis's.
You take the Del Ripples.
Over.
- Jolene.
Come out now. I got rid of
Bobby Jr.
Jolene?
(dramatic music)
Estimated value $230,000
dollars.
Samuel Graham died.
Survived by only living
relative, his son, Travis.
Kelly!
- What?
- Sweetheart.
Do you know anything about
this?
- About what?
- Where's Jolene?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean you don't
know?
You planned this all along,
didn't you?
(screams)
(grunting)
(gun shot fired)
She was trying to rob me.
But I caught her.
Where is it?
Why didn't you just steal it
the first night you were
here, huh?
Now where's the fun in that?
Oh.
I can't.
(groaning)
Just shoot this bat with that
brick.
- Fuck you!
You see
around here
folks will figure
I'd be in my right.
I could kill where you lay
right now.
Put that gun away, Kelly.
Did you hear me, sweetheart?
I said you can put that gun
away.
(police sirens wailing)
How could you do that to you?
- What?
- Jesus.
I told you.
She had nothin' to do with
those other robberies.
- Then you're the driver.
- [Red] We got 'em, Bobby.
Over at the Del Ripple place.
One suspect.
ID'd as a Caucasian female
driver.
We need some layin' down on
the robbery.
Get over here. - The bank job
in Hurley.
That was her idea.
That was your idea.
- It was just for kicks.
Shoot.
You practically came in your
pants.
- You were the real fuck.
- Do it, Kelly.
- Put the gun down, Kelly.
Just put the gun down.
Put the gun down, sweetie.
- Who's gun is that?
Who's fucking gun is that?
- The robber's she killed!
- That's right.
You little lucky chump.
You were about to kill me.
With a bullet in your head.
For piece of plastic valium.
He's coming back to the one
that killed his daddy.
And the guard in Hurley.
Now.
As far as I know.
Kelly and I aren't suspects
in those murders.
If you catch my drift.
I'm tired.
Just shoot him, Kiki.
- Kiki?
- Nobody fucks with family.
(gun shot fired)
(melancholy music)
- Here.
- Sure you can travel?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Just slow while drivin'.
There you go.
Always have to have a
souvenir.
Let's go.
("The Great Divide" by David
Allan Morgan)