The Bank Job
This is Kenny. He spent
in jail for 6 months. The fact that Michael
said something to me that is not.
What a surprise, but honestly
still well and passed.
I honestly do not know why
i hang out with people like Michael
is just asking for trouble.
But we sometimes ask
hell anyway.
Here's what happened.
Please let.
Oh shit, let's go man!
We got it.
Let's go, let's go!
O shades.
Got shades, do not worry I have for you.
No matter how much money have you got clipped, wait!
Subscribe to the chase.
Oh, shit, shit, look at that fence.
This was the gate. Watch it, bro.
Ok, are you ready?
$ 264.
How?
Why are you stopping  auto Kenny?
You go break into a bank and
opljaèkaš only 246 dollars.
- What's the matter with you?
- No man, we have $ 264.
Fuck!
- What?
- Police, police!
I do not believe for 246 dollars.
What could I,
bank was closed.
- Why have not cracked the safe?
- I could not shut it.
What are you robber of banks?
Well, fuck it, I get
car for the robbery, did
work, what did you do?
Keep the money they're yours.
We need to run away, I know.
Come on, come on.
O shit.
Hands up, up!
, Let me see your hands.
Get your hands.
Put ​​your hands on the trunk!
Move it.
How are you?
I have not had this.
Shut up.
Hey Mikey, like old
time, you've pillaged
bank. What are you thinking?
All I know is that
Kenny planning a bank robbery.
Told me about it a few months ago.
I never pillaged banks. You can not
me to sew.
In the car! Relax.
Rica has something behind you.
I'll be quiet!
Ok, ok, ok.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Good work, good!
Michael, here's your hat.
Can you take bath
get out of jail. - Yes
thank you, I love you too.
Fuck you, what helps if
're both in jail?
What if I'm sitting next to you?
Bar you can help me to get out of
18 months with good behavior.
- I'll do anything!
- Mikey shut up!
- Keni help!
- Shut up!
6 months, 3 days, 14 hours later
Hello, hey you stupid!
Kenny!
Kenny that Kenny?
'm Coming for you motherfucker!
Kenny will kill me, shit.
The house Karminive mom.
Hey Carmine.
O thank God, come open.
Hey, get out.
Hey Kenny prosecute me, I
that will remain in æuzi 3 years, but not
. Goes. What should I do?
Now I just need your help.
You owe me five thousand dollars, I want tomorrow
3 thousand in denominations of 100 dollars.
Just save the creature.
I will not do more to help.
- First pay me what you owe me.
- Ok, I'll pay.
I'll pay you tomorrow, two thousand
If today
give me some drugs. - No, no!
You'll give me three thousand
because we owe 5
OK, three thousand tomorrow.
Give me a gram
today.
- Fuck off, fuck off.
Hi.
Hell.
At the same time, the La Cienega...
Yes.
Fuck.
Who the hell are you?
Who's my bitch?
What the hell are you doing?
O God.
Who's my bitch now?
Called me and asked why I did not answer.
As it is obvious that I do not want to talk to
.
Maybe this help. Go to
me.
Hey, how are you?
Give me the phone, what the hell!
If you just apologize I'd give you
use my phone.
De to answer.
Fuck you!
Hell.
Hello, Brendone_
Kenny, when you get out, man?
This morning, where are you?
In a motel.
- You suck.
- No, you're right.
- I figured that you can watch it for a bit?
- Can.
With èijeg phone call?
- Some gay.
- Fuck this gay!
- Come pick me up.
- Of course, where?
- At the corner of third and Santa Fe.
- That's me in a minute.
Honey, I'm out.
Whore're done.
Can I get your phone back?
- You mean this?
- Yes, bawdy cowboy.
Oh, shit!
- Startled me!
- I'm sorry, am I too early?
No, you did not. Let's get this shit.
Yes, poslovaæemo now.
Well, look, I'll just
one show.
If we screw up, you're fucked.
Firstly uniform and weapons
in the trunk.
And explosives at the place where
is a spare tire.
Do not remove until you park in the garage!
- Does this fast?
- No problem, cowboy.
Do I look like the cowboys?
No.
Here's entrance, show their badge when
are you going to park.
Then take a gun and explosives
and go to the third floor.
Here.
This is the control room. He will not let
so easy and you'll have to...
Yes, I'll blow them up, right.
When you come inside the control room
placed explosives under the main control boards
and push the red button.
- And then what? - If you're dead, you'll be
with over 200 000 people in the area.
- It's what you wanted?
- Yes, you'll have all the fish world.
- Well, where are my genge? - What is it?
- My money, you moron.
I have them here.
Here are 20 thousand.
Let's do business.
Thank you.
Good luck with women.
Come on.
Shit!
This is nice.
What is this?
I guess I get my fish.
How did cowboy?
See the big red car.
I love this country.
- Is that why we're here?
- Not.
I swear I'll kill you, and I'll tell
your father that you fell under a train.
I just saw an American.
Good, now go do what you gotta do.
I have a small problem. I killed a hooker
today.
Why did you kill a hooker?
It was an accident.
You called, and she was riding.
I wanted was to get rid of,
so I went to bed and
hit his head.
End of game.
I guess time will pass
before the stink.
So what kind of plan you have, what are you?
I think that Kidney in the country.
Somewhere nice,
Brazil.
- Why in Brazil?
- Because mammals.
Lots of them.
- Besides the beast escaped
from Mexico. - No shit!
- Do you love?
- No.
But I'll have.
How to?
First National Bank.
I brought my 38-cu.
If you want a little bit to show that you come to love.
- I just came out today.
- Come on.
Do not be a coward!
You and I uleæemo and that's it.
Brazil.
Easily.
This garbage will not succeed.
Of course he wants, look, beauty.
New car. Let's go. Lived.
See what it is.
As we just packed in there?
He fucked your sister, get him out.
Fuck my sister.
Rise.
I told you to stay away from her!
I told you that I loved.
On the ground.
Now we're going to kill you.
Where are you going? You're not going anywhere!
On your knees!
He will not start.
Does not work.
Shit.
What is it, dear?
You will not believe what happened.
'm In the middle of something.
I was in the bank, and these two are just
inflammation.
Got clipped the big bucks.
Come on, let's go.
What to do?
What can I do, to fly there?
Fuck it.
Get your ass over here.
Follow them I'm coming.
Ok, I'll call you.
Where are you going?
Stay on your knees.
We have to go.
Finish with this.
Fucking Aziz!
Fuck!
On account that the head?
He's not the boss.
I'm the boss.
I'm doing all this.
What is this?
Do not shoot.
Shit.
Arapu stole that car.
Just follow them and do not be flashy things.
Damn!
I can not believe I shot.
I got to the hospital.
Oh, I'm taking you to the hospital right away.
Hurts.
I think the bullet still inside.
Let's see.
What is your problem?
- Okay, izdržaæeš.
- What are you, a doctor?
No, but I saw when
is out of your legs.
I think it will get infected.
Fuck Mom!
This is not your idea.
Quit whining!
How much money do we have?
Look at this.
- Want a sip?
- Give.
Give!
Better.
Are you sure?
Go to the highway, we need fuel,
get to highway.
Take care.
Aziz?
Someone stole my car.
Where is your car?
This man had a gun
i took the car. - Who? - If you're so stupid
you let it.
He was going to shoot me! Then
could not finish the mission.
Now we do not have any mission!
I called American
far. If you find him...
idiot!
Bitch!
To her eat a Big Mac with buttocks...
I do have the hots for that?
How many have you fucked up now?
One and the smell of McDonalds.
You're fucked.
We're out of fuel,
I have to stop.
So stop.
I'm just saying. Fuck it.
What do I say? I say stop.
I told you not to stop.
Stop.
There's the pump.
O, yes.
I'm a fan of a fool.
I do.
Which exit you out of?
- Coming.
- Hurry fuck him.
'll Lose them.
Shit!
Coming!
Time.
Kenny.
View.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking.
Get out of here!
Come on.
Fuck.
I think you are going for us.
Stop, you have to take the car.
Stop!
Yes, I'm talking to you.
I do not know what you're talking about?
We do not have any money.
're On the wrong address.
Jebaæemo you mom.
Mamu  you!
We also have me puce, bitch!
Align me with them to
they put a bullet among the eyebrows.
It has to look like Hindus.
Son of a drive as the drivers Indy 100
(rally).
Or what was the Indy 500?
I do not have a clean shot.
Gaining on us.
Let the fucking and they and all that crap you drive.
Be careful, watch where you're going!
Who the hell are these?
Mexicans.
Step on it, I got it. Cool!
Drive like an old bitch.
Do the boards, shut up!
Oh, shit.
Look, there's a car on the road.
Watch this shit!
Watch the old car.
Fuck.
- You almost hit that car
- But I did not.
What do you think put the belt?
They are shooting at us!
Fuck.
What is this shit?
Hey, stop shooting!
Fuck, shit!
It seems to me that I hit them.
Oh shit, they fled.
- How the hell knows that we love?
- Why do you ask such stupid questions?
I think they've escaped.
Just tell me yet that we
out of gas!
Fucking shit!
- Go get fuel.
- In the middle of nowhere? - Come on.
Fucking shit!
I can not believe this shit.
Bring us and we èetrdesetku.
Give me a little hilly.
Do not give!
How do you give?
Give me drink.
- There's nothing left.
- Bullshit.
Give shut up!
What the fuck is this?
Plans nuclear power plant.
What?
This is a map or something.
- Shit!
- What is it?
Look at this, it was in the trunk.
- Is it M-16?
- Yes.
Fuck man, this is a serious rifle.
I was full!
Let's get out of here.
- Will you be all right?
- I will.
Get in the car.
- We'll put the drive on all the wheels.
- This is the car for that.
Who's that up ahead?
Who is this and what does he want?
Small Move.
Izbaciæu of speed.
- Where did you come from?
- The eastern L. A's.
- How much is this truck?
- I do not know, not much.
Give me the keys and get out.
Hurry up, man!
Get out and stay there.
- What have you got there? - Do not move! Some grass,
fake gun in the front passenger.
- Where's the grass? Where are you going? Stop right there!
- I'm here.
Stop right there.
Do not check under the hood.
Gimme some gasoline.
If you give me the keys can open
tank.
- Where are the keys?
- So I gave them to you.
- These? - No, no, I think the other.
- Back off!
- Do not break them, it's not my truck.
- Shut up and back off!
I try to be the best they can.
Refueled and hurried.
- Do not rush me!
- Hurry!
Easy, you do not want dirt
in gasoline. Open this.
Hurry.
Going, going diesel ..
- You got something good in this truck?
- Everything's gone, everything.
- Hurry! - What have you got in your pockets?
- I have nothing.
Rise.
What is this?
- The bag of weed. - I see.
Shut up!
- You want to kick your ass now? - I will not.
- Then shut up.
Everything is already gone.
Condoms, which would you kid condoms?
Who will give you some coke?
You're a nothing...
I know, I know, I know.
- Where is your car?
- Do not worry about me.
Take care of yourself.
Give me that crap.
Leave it to turn around.
- Run away, run away.
- From what?
Get out of here!
See this rock? God
did he say to tell you that these
'll get among the eyes.
Get out gubitnièe.
Start to Treis, motherfucker!
- Hey, Brandon, what?
- Give me some of that whiskey.
No, I'm just a little.
- As you cunt! Give a little. - No, I am
wounded need.
Are you hurt?
Motherfucker!
Thank you.
Hurt my ass!
Give me a fucking bottle.
- What upucaæeš me?
- Maybe.
Come on, tell me about the red Mustang.
Bugs.
Fuck.
- Cui Hey, I've got fuel.
- Where are you?
I kidnapped by a white man in his
trucks.
I've just got gas?
Well, you said just gasoline.
Why did not you take the whole truck?
- Well, you just said that! P and what are you waiting for,
pour, I'm tired.
Get your ass.
Fuck.
Fucking shit.
- Police!
- Oh, shit!
A little chase.
Here patrols 22, in pursuit of a red Mustang
Registered Xea 465 California
I need backup. Just passing by
California.
This car was requested so be careful.
Beginners!
Do not shoot at the police, do not!
Here's a little of this.
What's his is mine?
- Is there more police? - Relax
help arrives.
I'll take them.
19 20
0vde 19, I need help.
I need help, I have the terrorists
throughout pustnji.
19, can you hear me?
Terrorists shooting at me.
- Relax!
- I'm not going to calm down.
- 19, what is your situation?
- He's shooting at me!
Send me a help, not
this I can do.
Srešæu and somewhere along the way.
Calm down.
Hell.
Hell, help your mom,
fagots!
Fuck this!
A police officer shot and we need
emergency evacuation.
Send all here.
Now you have! That's it!
Jesus Christ.
Bastards!
Do you want to shoot him or something?
Did you?
No, he's still alive?
Pussy!
Let's go to Brazil.
Come on!
What do you mean where did they go?
I think it turned left.
- They're running to mommy?
- Yes.
You know what, I have a pair of binoculars.
Popeæemo up the hill and pregledaæemo streets.
This time, we'll catch them. Let
Where are they fucker?
- We're not gonna let them get away?
- I will not find them.
- Where are they?
- How do you dig to find his stupid binoculars?
Fucking shit!
If you do not meet me
sebaæu you.
Shit, I think they are.
They must have been, let's go!
Add revolver.
I got it.
Now we will catch them.
Come on, they're catching up.
Let's go.
Just worthless waste your bullets.
Fucker.
- Go get them!
- Come try!
These fucking bend.
Fuck it, give me your gun.
Hell.
Rob a bank. What a stupid idea.
Opljaèkaj casino.
Come check it Kenny.
I tell Brandon! Ma does not know anything!
I am so smart.
- Let's go to Vegas.
- Where is Vegas?
What the fuck is that?
Did you see that?
O shit!
The preleæe over the cliff.
Where did you learn to drive like that?
- I have to go down.
- Fuck him!
- Look out!
- What's going on?
What the fuck?
Why did he stop?
- How can I help you?
- You do the favor to us and give us money.
OK.
Fucking Mexicans!
Where are you going?
In Brazil!