♪♪
[dog barking]
>> I want you out of this house!
I want you away from
my daughter.
You're a freak!
[woman screaming]
No, no, stay away from me,
stay away from me.
Get away from me, please.
Please, don't hurt me.
Don't, stop it!
[screaming]
Help, help!
No!
♪♪
>> Mommy?
Mommy!
♪♪
[siren chirping]
[radio chattering]
[overlapping chatter]
[siren wailing]
♪♪
>> Nancy.
Up here.
>> It's him?
>> Yep, got another one.
Black rose and the note,
"Gone but not forgotten."
>> They said there's bodies?
>> Two.
[helicopter passing]
[camera clicking]
Good break for us.
Bad one for her, though.
>> Scratched him?
>> Hope springs eternal.
♪♪
>> And the other one's
her little girl.
>> How little?
♪♪
>> Looks like her neck
was broken.
>> While she was sleeping.
>> Hallway outside.
Probably walked in on
the killer doing mom.
>> The killer put her in bed?
>> No, her daddy said he did it.
>> What for?
>> She was his little girl.
>> In there.
>> Hey, Nance.
Something, huh?
>> Oh, it's unbelievable.
[quiet chatting]
>> That's Peter Lake.
>> He doesn't look so tough
outside the courtroom, does he?
What do you suppose a place
like this goes for?
A little sensitive for
the job, don't you think?
[quiet chatter]
>> Mr. Lake?
♪♪
[city ambient]
>> Ladies and gentlemen, thank
you for coming here today.
We know that you have a lot of
concerns about how our project
is going to affect your
businesses.
So here to address them, and to
answer all of your questions,
is Martin Darius.
[audience applauding]
>> I want to live in your
neighborhood, not take it away.
But do I plan to be successful?
Oh, yeah.
And if I'm successful,
so will you all be.
I promise you, Darius Plaza
will not change the face of the
frontier district.
And I think even the most
diehard among you will have to
admit that the frontier is not
what it once was.
But don't take my word for it,
see for yourself.
[cell ringing]
Russ, I'mma have to take this.
>> No problem, I'll take over.
>> Martin Darius.
>> Hello, Martin.
Guess who?
It's Vicky Miller.
Is my husband there?
>> Mmhm.
We're in a meeting.
>> Oh, can you get out
of it, Martin?
>> Well, if it's an emergency,
of course I'll be there.
>> Oh, it's an emergency,
all right.
An extremely urgent one.
[Vicky sucking]
>> Russ.
I've got another affair
I've got to get to.
You take over.
>> Oh, yeah, of course.
So folks, please help yourselves
to more champagne.
>> Ladies and gentlemen of the
jury, you've heard a lot of
testimony, you've seen a lot of
evidence.
Andrea Hammermill is accused of
the murder of her husband.
Mr. Page, our illustrious
district attorney, would have
you believe that it was an act
of cold-blooded, premeditated
murder.
But what we have to understand
is that Andrea Hammermill is a
woman who was in a fight
for her life.
After years of physical and
mental abuse at the hands
of her husband.
After years of living in fear
that the next time he might kill
her with his savage beatings.
Beatings that resulted in her
being hospitalized on two
separate occasions.
She took the only step that she
knew would end her suffering and
save her life.
♪♪
[gun cocking]
[gun firing]
♪♪
>> Has the jury
reached a verdict?
>> Yes we have, Your Honor.
>> The defendant will
please rise.
Regarding case C11-2897, The
State versus Andrea Hammermill
in the matter of the
premeditated murder of her
husband, Howard Hammermill,
the jury finds the defendant
not guilty.
[audience murmuring]
>> You okay?
>> Mrs. Tannenbaum!
>> Here they come right now.
Miss Tannenbaum.
[overlapping questions]
>> Did the fact that
you're a woman and your client
was an abused woman gave you a
sympathy vote?
>> The verdict shows that
a person has a right
to defend herself.
>> You mean that murder's legal.
>> Mrs. Hammermill lived in a
private battlefield of abuse.
She had to make a stand
to save her life.
Excuse me.
[overlapping questions]
>> Miss Tannenbaum, how does it
feel to save an abused woman
from prison?
>> Pretty damn good.
>> I am so proud of you,
sweetheart.
>> Thank you, Mom, oh.
Thank you for coming here.
>> Can I take you to lunch?
>> Oh, please.
>> All right.
[press calling]
>> Mr. Page, over here.
Are you disappointed
in the verdict?
Do you think a murderer
went free?
>> This office is always
sympathetic to the plight of
battered women.
But we will always, always
prosecute vigilantism.
>> If Andrea Hammermill had come
to us before taking matters into
her own hands, then her husband
would be the one on trial today.
>> Any leads in the
disappearances of Laura Ferrar
and Wendy Riser?
[cameras clicking]
>> One case at a time, please.
This office is working very
closely with police on that
matter, we'll comment when we
feel it's appropriate.
>> Lots of legalese for
we don't know jack.
♪♪
[camera clicking]
[couple panting]
>> Oh, wow.
>> Oh, God.
>> Oh.
We should get going.
We don't want your husband
getting curious about where you
are all these afternoons.
>> Well, if he found out,
what would you do?
>> Boy, I'd hate to fire him.
Russ is doing such a great job.
>> Oh, you're the devil.
>> Yeah.
[camera clicking]
[distant] I'll call you.
[sprinkler ticking]
[camera clicking]
>> This pile is, uh, better luck
next time.
This pile is, uh, they shut off
your cell phone.
And, uh, these are signed by
some guy named Guido.
>> Look, I don't want you to get
the wrong impression.
Lawyers do actually get paid for
the work they do.
I just happen to represent
people who are broke.
>> Well maybe you should
represent some, uh,
wealthier clients.
>> That's a good idea.
Do you know any?
>> Well, it pays to advertise.
>> Well, that takes money.
Besides, it's a good thing that
we're able to use Jeff's office
while he's gone, otherwise you
and I would be working out of my
apartment again.
>> Well, all I'm saying is a
little self-promotion
doesn't hurt.
>> Give me the list,
I'll think about it.
>> Vicky.
[song playing]
Vicky?
I'm home early, where are you?
[music cutting off]
Hey, Vic, you should have
seen me today, babe.
Darius gave me the football, and
I ran with it.
And I scored big time.
You know, he totally trusts me.
It's all happening just like I
said it would.
Huh, it's totally all happening.
Why are all the lights on?
Hey, Vicky.
[water running]
♪♪
>> Now let's move from the
State House to the courthouse.
Our in-studio guest today,
Betsy Tannenbaum, the
Sacramento attorney who made
headlines across the state and
the nation with her successful
defense in the notorious
Hammermill case.
Miss Tannenbaum is a local
single mother and a graduate
of the UC system who's making
quite a name for herself
as a spousal abuse ace.
[cell ringing]
>> Martin Darius.
>> You want to meet me.
Tidy's Fish Shack in 20 minutes.
>> I don't think so.
>> Wait, wait, wait, wait,
don't hang up.
If you hang up I'll be
gone but not forgotten.
Catch my drift?
Enjoy the rest of your freedom,
Mr. Darius.
>> What do you want?
>> It's not what I want,
it's what you want.
It's always what you want.
And right now you want to meet
me in 20 minutes.
Tidy's Fish Shack.
[dial tone]
♪♪
[patrons murmuring]
Thank you for coming,
Mr. Darius.
>> You seem to have me at a
disadvantage.
>> That I do, that I do.
Calamari?
>> Clogs your arteries.
>> No one lives forever.
>> That's true.
But some live longer
than others.
>> Well, it's your loss,
they make them good here.
You cook 'em too long,
they get rubbery.
Sit down.
>> No thanks.
>> I know what you're doing
in Sacramento.
>> Congratulations, you watch
television.
>> I've been to Hunter's Point.
>> Hunter's Point?
>> Ring a bell?
>> No, I can't say it does.
>> Then how about this?
[chuckling]
>> You got a pretty good
poker face, Mr. Darius,
I like that.
Because the ante to stay in this
game is a million dollars,
in cash.
All hundreds, please.
>> I can't raise that kind of
money in cash.
>> Okay, well, you got 24 hours
to figure out how, and that is
only because, ah, it's so late
in the day now and because
I'm a nice guy.
>> How do I contact you?
>> I'll contact you.
I got your number.
Time's a-wasting.
>> Nice watch.
[phone ringing]
Law office.
>> Betsy Tannenbaum?
>> Speaking.
>> Martin Darius here.
I'd like to meet with you.
Soon, if possible.
>> Of course, Mr. Darius.
[phone ringing]
>> Yep?
>> Rick.
>> You're still at the office.
>> Yeah, um, I need a favor.
>> Uh huh, what's that?
>> Would it be all right if I
came to pick up Kathy a little
bit late tonight?
Something important came up.
>> More important than your
own daughter?
>> Our daughter, she has
two parents.
>> Really?
I only see one of us here,
Betsy.
>> Rick, please do not make
this difficult.
Look, it's just 90 minutes,
all right?
>> 90 minutes to do what?
>> Martin Darius just phoned me
and he wants me meet me on a
legal matter tonight.
>> So?
>> If it was you, you would take
the meeting, I would understand.
>> Okay, fine, make me
the bad guy.
>> Please, I will not be long,
and I will make it up to you.
>> Okay.
You go for it.
I hope it goes well.
Sorry.
>> Okay, thank you.
[pen clicking]
[Martin knocking]
>> Betsy Tannenbaum?
I'm Martin Darius.
>> Oh, yes.
>> I'm sorry if I startled you.
Your door was wide open.
>> Oh, no problem.
>> Boy, nice place.
>> Well, it's actually not mine.
[ringing] >> Yeah, I knew that.
Uh huh?
>> Sound familiar?
Clock's ticking, Mr. Darius.
>> Excellent.
I'll get back to you.
Curse of the 21st Century.
>> Would you like some coffee?
>> That'd be great.
I was at a charity affair for
the Sacramento Opera
the other night; you go?
>> No, I haven't.
>> Too bad.
They're really very good.
>> Milk?
>> Ah, no, no thanks.
I was talking with Maxine
Silver, she's on the board.
We were discussing
the Grieg book.
You read it?
>> The novel by the
serial killer?
>> Thank you.
>> Uh, please, sit down.
No, I actually haven't.
>> I've read some of
the reviews.
It's actually not my cup of tea.
>> Maxine said the book never
should have been published,
solely because Grieg wrote it.
You agree?
>> I wouldn't ban a book just
'cause I disapproved of the
person who wrote it.
>> If the publisher bowed to
pressure from, say, woman's
group, and withdrew it from
circulation,
would you represent Grieg?
>> Is there a point to these
questions, or are you just
making small talk?
[thunder rumbling]
>> Good storm.
>> My answer is yes.
I could represent Grieg.
>> Really?
>> I'd be representing
a principle.
Principles only get tested
in extreme cases.
>> I like you.
Like to put you on retainer.
I've taken the liberty of
drawing you a check.
Consider five thousand of it to
be your consultation fee for
tonight.
The rest is your retainer.
You've placed the odd amount.
>> It's my gross income
last year.
>> Forgive me for having you
investigated.
I'm a careful guy.
As a matter of fact...
let's make it...
an even hundred thousand.
>> What kind of trouble are you
in, Mr. Darius?
>> Absolutely none whatsoever.
I hire the best people
I can find.
Not because I need them
immediately, but because
it helps me control my future.
>> Why me?
>> I heard your interview
on the radio.
I liked what you had to say.
And now that I've met you,
I like you even better.
>> I'm gonna have to think
about your offer.
>> I wouldn't expect
anything else.
♪♪
[thunder crashing]
[phone ringing]
>> It's D.
I need a reverse directory trace
on the following number,
name and address.
[someone knocking]
>> Hey.
>> Hi.
Look, I'm sorry, I'm...
>> Me, too.
You're soaking wet.
>> Yeah.
It's really raining outside.
>> She's asleep.
I'll go get her, bring her in.
Betsy, why does this have
to be so hard?
>> I don't, I...
>> I miss you.
I do.
>> I know you do.
>> Why don't you just stay?
>> I wish it were that easy.
>> It is if you want it to be.
I don't want to lose you.
♪♪
>> Mommy?
>> Hey.
Come on, sweetheart.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Come on.
Come on, I'll take you home.
>> Here we go.
I'll get the door.
>> Thanks.
Here's Leo.
Okay, come on, honey,
I'll take you home.
>> Bye-bye, sweetie.
>> Give your daddy a kiss.
>> Bye.
Bye.
[thunder crashing]
[rain falling]
[bottles clinking]
[thunder rumbling]
[keys jingling]
[machine beeping]
>> Yes, Detective Oberhurst,
my name is Mrs. Winters.
I'm quite certain my husband's
having an affair.
I'd like you to document
it for me.
My cell phone number is
555-3044.
Thank you.
[machine beeping]
[door creaking]
[thunder rumbling]
[gun cocking]
♪♪
[thunder rumbling]
[dial tone]
[phone dialing]
[phone ringing]
[grunting]
[thunder rumbling]
>> Bon soir, Monsieur Viande.
Or do you prefer Mr. Oberhurst?
How about Sam?
Nah, let's stick with Viande.
That's French for meat.
That's what you are, a slab of
meat drenched in cheap cologne.
[Oberhurst choking]
Ew, where's that insect
repellent?
The purpose of meat?
Why, to be butchered.
You really ought to keep your
cutlery honed, Sam.
[Oberhurst choking]
Blade this dull pulverizes
the bone going through.
C'est la vie, say the old folks.
You okay, comfortable?
Not too tight?
Good.
Now, you're going to tell me
everything you think you know
about Hunter's Point.
>> You guys ever see Laura?
>> Laura Ferrar?
>> No, the movie Laura, this
old black and white thing
about a cop who falls in love
with a dead girl's picture.
>> Alan, you got to
get out more.
>> She is beautiful.
>> Hopefully she's not dead.
>> Ah, she's got two
chances of that.
None and slim.
>> You're just a golden ray of
sunshine today.
>> Laura lived.
>> You said she was dead.
>> Three months, three women.
This guy is not going to stop
until we stop him.
>> He's not giving us much.
No prints, no forced entry,
no sign of a struggle, no hair,
no blood, nothing.
>> Nothing?
What about the notes,
what about the roses?
>> It's bait.
He's trying to make us look bad.
>> Well, it's working.
>> What do these women
have in common?
>> They were all well-to-do.
None had a job, none had
children, and all of their
husbands are in the clear.
>> No ransom notes, or any
communication to any of the
families?
>> None.
>> Are there any cults out there
with these things as trademarks?
>> Not in the database, I wish
it were that easy.
>> This guy's starting to get
on my nerves.
[patrons chatting]
[door bells jingling]
>> You're Alan Page?
The DA?
>> That's right, can I help you?
>> I may have some information
about the women who are
disappearing here in Sacramento.
>> And you are?
>> I'm Detective Nancy Gordon.
From the Hunter's Point Police
in upstate New York.
We had the same thing happen to
us 10 years ago.
Four women disappeared from
their homes.
Whoever was taking them was
leaving behind a black rose
and a note that said,
"Gone but not forgotten."
Sound familiar?
>> Yeah.
Yes.
Yes, it does.
Can, can we-- ?
Please.
You said Hunter's Point,
New York?
>> Yeah.
We had a suspect named
Peter Lake.
He was the husband of one of
the victims.
His six year old daughter was
killed, too.
>> So why him and not some of
the other husbands?
>> Those women just disappeared.
Here we had bodies.
>> You said you had a suspect,
what happened to him?
>> Well, we had another suspect.
A sex offender named Waters.
One of the missing women was
found in his basement, dead.
Waters was killed
resisting arrest.
>> But you think it's
Peter Lake?
>> Immediately after the case
was closed, Peter Lake
gave his law practice to his
partners, closed out all of his
bank accounts, abandoned
his house and disappeared.
>> Well, you can't really
blame him, can you?
I mean, the man's wife and child
are killed and
he's accused of it.
>> Two things were never told to
the press about the killings.
The color of the roses
the killer used,
and what was in the notes.
Only the people on the task
force and the killer himself
knew.
Peter Lake leaves Hunter's
Point, and the killings stop.
He comes to Sacramento, and 10
years later you've got the same
crime and the same signature.
>> What, what do you mean he
comes to Sacramento?
>> This is Peter Lake.
>> This is Martin Darius.
♪♪
>> Number 41?
>> I'll be right back.
Yeah, yeah, that's me, 41.
>> There you go, sir, thank you.
[door bells jingling]
♪♪
>> Yes, Mr. President.
Well, my tax returns have
been public record for
thirty some years now.
Mr. President, I will do
everything in my power
to live up to this
great responsibility.
Thank you.
I am truly honored,
and very grateful.
Yes, sir, goodbye.
Huh, that was the call.
I am officially the nominee
as the new Justice of the
Supreme Court of The United
States Of America.
>> Congratulations, Ray,
you deserve it.
I'm sure it'll go well.
>> This is Washington, Wayne.
Nothing goes well.
>> So, what did the
president say?
>> He asked me if there was
anything I had to disclose.
Anything questionable that might
come out in the confirmation
hearings and prevent me getting
the post and embarrass him.
>> And you said no.
>> And I said no.
>> Ray, there is no way
anyone can know anything
about Hunter's Point.
>> That's why I said no.
>> Good.
>> Really appreciate you
agreeing to the article.
Has this newfound celebrity of
yours impacted your life, your
practice, or your private life
in any way?
Positive or negative?
>> Well, um, being a single mom,
I can't imagine becoming any
busier, but it definitely has
impacted my practice positively.
>> How so?
>> I have more and
bigger clients.
>> Doesn't more and bigger
translate to more and
bigger criminals?
>> Well, that's not very
objective.
Andrea Hammermill is not a
criminal.
>> You know, you do seem to have
a very special kind of
relationship with your clients.
Have you spoken to Hammermill
since the verdict?
>> Murder trials are not exactly
something you want to
reminisce about.
>> Working on any special cases
at the moment?
>> No.
>> No, or nothing you can
talk about?
>> Nothing I can talk about.
>> Does this mean we might be
seeing a little more of you on
television in the near future?
>> Well, let's hope not, because
if you do then that means one of
my clients has had afoul
of the law.
>> Ah, that's a good point.
[distant chatting]
>> So she just shows up
out of nowhere?
>> I think she was following me.
>> And she just disappears
into thin air.
Spooky.
>> Yeah.
She tells me this whole story,
but... something doesn't feel
right about what she said.
>> And this Peter Lake guy looks
like Martin Darius?
>> No, Randy, not like him,
it is him.
[phone ringing]
This is Alan Page.
This is Gary Shunt, Chief of
Police in Hunter's Point,
New York.
>> Thanks for getting back
to me, Chief.
>> So you're looking for one of
my detectives, Nancy Gordon.
She was put on administrative
leave, and we haven't heard
from her since.
>> When was that?
>> Oh, about six months ago,
I think.
Why, uh, she looking
for work out there?
>> No, she just showed up
talking about a case there about
10 years ago, group of killings.
>> That black rose thing.
>> Could you send me the files
on that case?
>> I'll see what I can do.
>> Thank you, thanks for
your time.
Curiouser and curiouser.
>> What?
>> That was the chief of police
in Hunter's Point.
Nancy Gordon was a detective
there, but she took a leave of
absence about four months ago.
They thought she had what
amounted to battle fatigue,
that's all he would say.
She winds up here.
>> She goes on leave
four months ago?
Three months ago women start
disappearing from Sacramento.
>> You certainly have a
suspicious mind.
>> And you don't?
We're prosecutors.
[phone dialing]
[phone ringing]
>> Clyde here.
>> Hey, Clyde, it's Alan Page, I
need you to find a woman for me.
>> Desperate, huh?
>> Very funny.
>> Did you get that stuff that I
asked you about on Darius?
>> They're in the machine, if
you want I'll go--
>> No, that's all right.
I can walk that far.
>> You know what's strange?
How they just stop.
>> What do you mean
they just stop?
>> The articles.
There's nothing on him
before 1996.
It's like alien abduction,
except in reverse.
>> Tomorrow I want you
to keep looking.
>> Excuse me,
I got the flash report.
Walk with me.
>> Martin Darius started a
construction company
eight years ago.
Now he's building everything.
Charms people's weak spots, cons
them into believing that they
got the best deal for their
property, when in actuality he's
buying up for peanuts,
developing for a fortune.
>> Buy low, sell high, welcome
to America. >> Mmhm.
>> Hold on.
[phone ringing]
Alan Page.
Yeah, wait, wait a second.
All right, go.
Got it, thanks.
Got an address for Nancy Gordon.
>> What's this all
about, anyway?
>> Just tying up a few
loose ends, sir.
Nothing to be concerned about.
>> Well, I know everything that
goes on at this place.
I wasn't here when she checked
in, but nobody's come
in or out of here.
>> Would you open it, please?
>> Nancy?
>> Thank you, sir, we'll take it
from here.
♪♪
Her bags are still here.
>> The bed's made.
>> She bothered to hang her
clothes up, so she must have
been planning on staying a
while.
What the hell is this?
♪♪
What do you think?
She into the guy, or what?
>> Man, I knew a girl like this
in high school.
No matter where I went,
there she was.
Totally used to creep me out.
>> What did you do about it?
>> I nailed her a couple times
at her parents' house when they
were out of town.
>> You what?
>> I was 16, you take what
you can get.
>> You're a dangerous man,
Randy.
>> Yeah.
What you got?
>> Got a pencil?
>> Who uses a pencil anymore?
Wait a minute, here's one.
>> Thanks.
>> You're not telling me that
actually works.
>> Old school, baby.
Feel like taking a ride?
>> Why would Nancy Gordon come
to a Darius construction site?
>> Let's take a look around.
>> What exactly is it you think
we're looking for?
>> Maybe something like this?
Let's see how far it goes.
>> We're, uh, trespassing.
>> Look, Nancy Gordon could
be in here.
And if she's alive,
she's in trouble.
>> We have cause and
we have moment.
>> And we don't have
a court order.
>> And I'm the DA,
and it's all my decision.
And let's just say you're
not even here.
♪♪
This could be something.
Try not to step in
the tire tracks.
♪♪
Look, they end right here.
[thunder rumbles]
>> You want me to call the cops?
>> For what?
So far all we've seen is a
pit in a construction site.
Shine your light on me so I can
see where I'm stepping.
♪♪
Whoa!
>> Alan!
Alan, you all right?
>> I'm fine.
I did that on purpose.
♪♪
Call the cops.
Call the cops, now!
[helicopter flying]
[police chatting]
>> Officer--
>> No comment, this is an
ongoing investigation.
[press chattering]
>> Hold on, guys, let 'em come
through.
All right.
>> Excuse me, guys?
[press questioning]
All right.
[press chatting]
Thanks.
[police chatter]
Three altogether,
positively ID'd.
It's them.
The three missing women.
Ferrar, Riser, and Miller.
>> None of them is Nancy Gordon?
>> No.
None of them is Nancy Gordon.
>> Any idea how long
they've been here?
>> Not yet.
The way it looks, another few
days, this pit would have been
poured in concrete for the
foundation of this place.
Rain must have held them up.
>> This is Darius' project.
Think he knows the
pour schedule?
>> Techs are gonna do a match
on the tire treads, see what
kind they are.
>> This is going to be all over
the news pretty soon
if it isn't already.
If it is Darius, he's gonna run.
>> We don't have enough
to hold him.
>> We do if we can find
Nancy Gordon.
[siren wailing]
♪♪
[doorbell ringing]
>> Hi.
>> Yes, can I help you?
>> Is Mr. Darius home?
>> No, he's not.
>> Excuse me, I'm Betsy
Tannenbaum, I'm one of
Mr. Darius' attorneys.
>> I see, well, I'm Martin's
wife, can I help you with
anything?
>> Will you be expecting him?
>> Yes.
Uh, Martin should be
back shortly.
Would you like to, uh,
wait inside?
>> That'd be great, thank you.
>> God knows I could use
the company.
>> Well, it's an interesting
house.
>> Can I offer you a drink?
>> Some water would be nice.
How did you meet your husband?
>> Business school.
I was getting my MBA and, uh,
Martin was a guest lecturer.
>> So do you work with your
husband?
>> No.
My husband doesn't want me
anywhere near his business.
He likes me to stay right here.
Says he doesn't want me tainted.
Cheers.
So tell me, what's so, uh,
hot about corporate law?
>> Nothing.
I can't imagine anything
more boring.
>> Really?
Then why did you get into it?
Uh, the money?
>> I'm not in corporate law.
I'm a criminal defense attorney.
>> Criminal?
Why would Martin need a criminal
defense attorney?
He hasn't done anything.
>> Well if I knew that,
I couldn't tell you anyway.
>> Martin won't be back for
quite some time.
I'll show you out.
>> Thank you.
>> So you're telling me the
techs found nothing
in that motel room?
Nothing?
>> We did it twice.
Nothing, it's a motel room, do
you have any idea how many hairs
we pulled out of there?
>> Well, she's officially a
missing person, consider the
report filed by me.
>> You need someone to file?
[phone beeping]
>> I got to go,
I got another call.
Find her, Clyde, will you?
Find something.
Alan Page.
>> Hey, this is officer Eric.
Yeah, the Chief told me to pull
the files on that black rose
murder case.
>> Great.
Thanks, how soon can we
get 'em shipped?
>> There's a little problem.
>> What kind of problem?
Well, actually it's a 'they're
not here' kind of problem.
>> Not there, where are they?
>> I don't know.
They were catalogued
as being here.
No one's listed as having
checked 'em out.
>> Is there a copy anywhere?
>> We weren't making backups
10 years ago.
This would be the only place
where the information would be.
There's nothing here, I'm sorry.
>> All right, listen, uh, this
is really important, this is
beyond important.
I need you to keep looking for
me, and let me know
if something turns up.
>> I'm telling you, there's
nothing here.
>> Please, just keep looking.
Thank you.
♪♪
[dog barking]
[Betsy knocking]
>> Mommy's here.
>> Get it.
>> Mommy.
>> Hi, sweetheart.
>> Hey.
>> Hi.
>> Can I get you something
to drink?
>> No, I'm, I'm good, thank you.
>> Chamomile tea.
>> Great.
>> Okay.
[kettle whistling]
>> So, did you have a good day
with your dad?
>> Yeah. >> Yeah?
>> We're talking with Martin
Darius, CEO of Darius
Construction who made that
hefty donation to the
public library.
Three million dollars is a very
generous donation.
>> Well, it's for a good cause.
>> Arguably, though, there are
a lot of good causes out there.
Why the public library?
>> Yeah, you're right.
There are a lot of good
causes out there.
And reading is really crucial.
You know, when I was a kid I
didn't have much of anything,
and I spent a lot of my time
reading in a public library.
Whatever success I have--
>> Oh, thank you.
>> is due in large part
to that experience.
>> Thank you very much,
Mr. Darius.
Dan and Christina, back to you.
>> Let me see, honey.
>> This is you, this is Daddy,
and this is me in the middle.
And we're all in the same house.
>> Well, that's beautiful,
sweetheart.
>> Thank you.
>> It's a great house, Kathy.
♪♪
[someone knocking]
>> Well, I'm happy to find you
among the living.
Now I'm wondering if I should
have you arrested.
>> Who do you want answering
questions, me or my attorney?
♪♪
>> The women began disappearing
in February.
First it was, um,
Samantha Reardon.
Then Patricia Cross.
Gloria Escalante and, uh,
Anne Hazelton.
I mean, they vanished
without a trace.
No clues except for the roses
and the notes.
Lake's wife and daughter were
killed in October.
♪♪
When a wife is murdered,
where do you look first?
>> The husband.
>> Right.
Only this was different.
I mean, this killer left his
calling card.
♪♪
Which meant that if, uh, if Lake
had killed his family, he was
probably good for the other
women as well.
Still, I didn't believe it was
him at first.
>> Why not?
>> I just didn't.
♪♪
Mr. Lake?
>> Well, we have to give
O'Malley something.
>> Like what?
You got any suggestions?
>> We've been over and
over this.
We haven't even had lunch yet.
>> You want to see about lunch?
>> I'm hungry.
>> I'll tell you, whoever's
doing this is a genius.
I mean, kidnap and kill these
many women, this clean.
>> Hey, wait a second.
This guy, Singer.
The neighbor that's a CPA.
>> What about him?
>> Yeah, right here.
He says he saw Peter Lake come
home at 7:20.
>> 7:20?
>> 911 call came in at 8:15.
>> Mmhm.
>> And in the call he said he
just found the bodies.
>> Yeah, so what was he doing
for an hour?
>> Killing his wife
and daughter.
>> How could a man break
his own daughter's neck?
>> Hey, Frank, Peter Lake is
on his way back
to see you right now.
>> We're leaving right now.
>> Hey, now wait a minute, it's
not enough, it's not evidence.
I mean, he comes home, he finds
the bodies.
He, he's overcome, he doesn't
make the call for an hour.
Who's not to say?
>> You're right.
Even though we have opportunity,
we still need motive.
>> The wife found out something.
>> But what?
And what about the little girl?
I mean, why did she have to die?
>> Maybe the little girl saw
something, didn't know what it
was and told Mom.
>> Or she sees Daddy kill Mommy.
So he has to kill her, too.
>> Yeah, but we still have no
link to the other murders,
the other women.
[someone knocking]
>> Figured you guys
would be here.
>> Hi, Peter.
We're just, uh, going through
the victims' files, to see if
anything doesn't fit.
♪♪
>> Find anything?
>> Nothin' much.
>> I just, uh, thought I'd let
you know that I told the Chief I
thought that guy, Waters, would
be someone to watch.
>> So who was Waters?
>> He was a flower delivery guy
who, uh, who had a history of
indecent exposure.
>> Why not him?
>> He didn't fit the profile.
>> Just tell us what happened
that night.
>> Was she cute?
>> I just wanted to show it
to her, that's all.
>> What made you do it?
>> She didn't think I could.
>> What?
She, she dared you to do it?
>> Oh, she dared me alright.
>> Yeah, what did she say?
>> She didn't have to
say a thing.
They have their ways of letting
you know what they think.
>> But actually the woman never
spoke to you.
>> I know what she wanted.
What they all want.
>> All?
All of them?
You mean, women?
And girls?
[distant siren wailing]
You can talk to me, Henry.
[chuckling]
>> They're all the same.
All of them.
>> What are they thinking?
>> That I can't, you know,
be with them.
I can, any time I want.
>> What about this guy Waters?
>> Waters, the florist
delivery guy?
What about him?
>> Those women would have let
him into their homes, okay?
I mean, if he was delivering
a big bouquet of flowers, they
would have let him in.
That's access.
And he has a history
of sex crimes.
>> Waters was only seen at one
of the crime sites.
There's no other evidence
linking him to any
of the other victims.
And his history of sex crimes
comes down to one questionable
incident of flashing.
>> I just got a feeling
about him.
He can put the women in his
delivery truck
to drive them away.
I mean, who'd look there?
He works for a florist, he can
get black roses easily.
He's a florist delivery man,
and he leaves behind his calling
card, a black rose.
It fits, right?
>> No.
Because nothing else
about him fits.
He lives with his sick
grandfather, he, he's a
high school dropout.
[patrons chatting]
[car starting]
Are you going to be okay?
>> Yeah.
Thanks, Nancy.
>> Oh, it's nothing.
No, Peter, no.
No.
Goodnight.
>> He came onto you?
>> Believe me, I shined it
on at first.
But there was no doubt
what he wanted.
>> Yes, granted, it looks bad.
But...
>> Well, there was more.
Turner found a link between
Peter Lake and all of
the other women.
>> Anne Hazelton belonged to the
same country club.
Cross' husband's law firm did
overspill work for
Lake's law firm.
Escalante and her husband
organized a charity golf
tournament for Sandra
and Peter Lake.
And Reardon and her husband
were on the Hunter's Point
Preservation Committee
with Peter Lake.
♪♪
>> It was way beyond
coincidence.
>> Unbelievable.
>> Yeah.
>> How did you nail the
other guy for it?
>> We got an anonymous tip.
Somebody called and said that
they'd overheard Waters bragging
that he was, uh, holding a, a
woman in his basement.
We had to check it out.
[dog barking]
[Nancy knocking]
>> First player ever with three
consecutive 100-yard games...
[Nancy knocking]
[dog barking]
>> What?
>> Henry Waters?
I'm Detective Gordon from the
Hunter's Point Police.
This is Detective Turner, and
Officers Smith and Mayhew.
May we come in?
>> Hey, what for?
I, I check in with Wheeler.
I saw her last Wednesday, I gave
her a sample and everything.
You can ask her.
>> This isn't about your
parole, Henry.
>> Then what?
>> Just step aside.
>> I, I didn't do anything.
>> Listen, otherwise I'm gonna
have Officer Mayhew cuff you,
and you're gonna be held in
violation of your parole.
>> Ah, come on.
>> Come on, let's deal with him.
>> 100-yard gain...
>> Which way is your basement,
Henry?
♪♪
>> Why don't you stay here
and watch him.
>> You got it.
[dog barking]
♪♪
>> I need you to stay
right here, sir.
♪♪
>> Look at this.
No wonder he didn't
want us down here.
>> That's not what
we're here for.
♪♪
[bulb buzzing]
Look at this.
[gasping]
It's Patricia Cross.
>> What did he do to her?
>> Mayhew!
>> Get in here, come on.
>> I don't want to go in there!
>> Henry, what do you
know about this?
♪♪
[Waters gasping]
>> No.
No, I, I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything!
>> Stop!
>> Stay right here.
[gun firing]
♪♪
>> Body, dead perp, the killer's
signature, all wrapped up in a
nice little bundle.
Waters took the fall.
And we all knew who
was behind it.
[dispatcher chatting]
>> So it was Waters after all.
>> The Chief's holding a
press conference.
We may never find the bodies
of the other women.
Well, you must be happy.
The man who killed your wife
and daughter is dead.
>> I'm satisfied.
>> Yeah.
Yeah, everyone's satisfied.
But I'm not.
I know it's you.
I know who you are, and I'm
gonna get you.
>> We've got to have dinner.
You know, for old time's sake.
♪♪
>> The case was officially
closed.
I never saw Peter Lake again.
>> Will you testify
to this in court?
[car pulling up]
♪♪
[cat yowling] [dog barking]
[dog barking]
♪♪
[someone knocking]
>> Hey Mom, are you gonna
marry Martin Darius?
>> No, sweetheart.
Where you get an idea like that?
>> Daddy thinks you
like him more.
>> No, honey, that's not true.
No, I just work for Mr. Darius.
>> What kind of work?
>> Well, I actually haven't done
anything for him yet.
I just promised him that I would
help him if he needed my help.
Your daddy can be very
silly sometimes.
[both laughing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
>> Betsy?
Martin Darius.
The police are here in my home,
and they have a warrant.
I don't know.
>> Put the officer in charge
on the phone.
>> It's for you.
>> Inspector Barrow.
>> I'm Betsy Tannenbaum, I'm
Martin Darius' attorney.
Until I can verify that the
search warrant that you have is
in proper order and for just
cause, any evidence that you
collect will be subject to a
motion for inadmissibility.
>> And just when are you
planning on verifying
this warrant?
>> I'm on my way.
[police chatting]
I'm Betsy Tannenbaum.
>> Detective Barrow.
♪♪
>> Oh, it all seems to be
in order, Detective.
>> Gee, thanks.
♪♪
Give the place a
thorough search.
We don't want to miss anything.
>> Wait a minute,
I want a list of everything
taken for examination
or marked as evidence.
[police chatting]
>> Making a huge mistake.
>> They have a legal search
warrant, we can't stop them
unless you want to be charged
with obstruction of justice.
>> Excuse me.
Do you mind?
>> Sorry.
>> Thank you.
>> You knew this was gonna
happen, didn't you?
>> No, I didn't.
>> Really? Then why did you
come over here the other day?
>> To speak to your husband.
Which I haven't had a chance
to do yet.
What is this all about?
>> Why are the police
searching our home?
>> I don't have any idea.
I really don't.
♪♪
>> Over here.
>> All right.
♪♪
>> We have a positive match on
the tire tread of the BMW in
your garage to that found at a
murder site, Mr. Darius.
>> What?
>> Martin Darius, I'm placing
you under arrest for the murders
of Wendy Riser, Laura Ferrar and
Vicky Miller.
You have the right to
remain silent.
>> Murder? >> You have the right
to an attorney.
We're gonna handcuff you now,
Mr. Darius, standard procedure.
>> Nobody touches me.
You are not gonna handcuff me.
>> Yes, we are.
One way or another, we are.
>> They're within legal bounds
to handcuff you, Martin.
You must do it, otherwise you'll
be charged with resisting
arrest, just go with them.
Don't say a word.
I'll call the district attorney
and find out what this is about.
>> Get me a bail hearing
right away.
>> I wouldn't go down to the
jail till tomorrow morning,
probably take us
all day to book him in.
We want to make sure we
do everything to your
satisfaction, counselor.
>> Murder?
Martin, what are they
talking about?
>> It's all wrong.
Don't worry, Lis,
I'll be out in a day.
>> Don't count on it.
>> I am counting on it.
>> We're searching the rest of
your house now, Mrs. Darius,
I'm gonna need the keys for
that Humvee for impound.
And don't worry, we'll give you
a receipt for everything.
>> Why is this happening?
[police chatting]
>> As soon as I know, I will
tell you, I promise.
>> I can't believe this.
>> If there is something that
you know about the charges
against your husband, it would
help everyone if you told me.
>> Are you kidding?
I don't know anything
about this.
>> I had to ask.
Look, I need you to go
away for a while, is there
someplace you can stay?
>> Yeah, um, my dad's house.
>> All right, now go pack a bag
and leave quickly.
I'll stay here until they
finish the search.
>> Okay.
♪♪
>> Miss Tannenbaum?
We need to talk.
>> I was just on my way
to see you.
We definitely do need to talk.
>> I'll meet you by the stairs.
>> All right.
>> Mr. Page.
>> Betsy, please, call me Alan.
We are colleagues.
>> Alan, my client was just
taken away in handcuffs.
What are the basis
of these charges?
>> When did you hook up
with Martin Darius?
>> After the Hammermill case.
Think he wanted to align himself
with someone that had a good
track record against the DA.
>> 1-0 isn't exactly
dominance, counselor.
>> Well it's better than 0-1.
What have you got?
>> Your client is facing three
counts of murder one with
special circumstances.
Each one carrying
the death penalty.
>> You're joking.
>> I don't have that
particular skill set.
>> Martin Darius?
>> Let's step outside.
>> So why do you think
it's Martin Darius?
>> 10 years ago a group of
similar crimes took place in
upstate New York.
Some town called Hunter's Point.
There was a suspect named
Peter Lake involved.
>> Again, what does this have
to do with Darius?
>> I've had contact with the
detective on that other case.
Her name is Nancy Gordon.
She had proof that Peter Lake
and Martin Darius
are the same man.
>> Proof, what proof?
>> A photograph of Peter Lake.
He killed six people in
Hunter's Point, two of them his
own wife and daughter.
Three more here makes nine.
I know combat vets with less on
their conscience.
>> The point is, the signatures
in each of the victims' initial
disappearances, both here and
there, identical.
That's why we arrested
your client.
>> What signatures?
>> When each of the women here
disappeared, whoever took them
left something behind.
A black rose, and a card which
read, "Gone but not forgotten."
Exactly like in Hunter's Point.
>> Well, if this Nancy Gordon
has prima-facie evidence that
Peter Lake killed the women in
Hunter's Point, why isn't
he behind bars?
>> Someone else took
the fall for it.
Nancy Gordon believes that
Peter Lake set him up.
Win or lose, Betsy,
this case will hurt you.
Walk away from it.
>> Thank you very much for
the advice, Alan.
But I still believe that
everyone is innocent until
proven guilty.
>> We both know otherwise.
Some people are guilty whether
it's proved or not.
Powerful people get away with
murder all the time.
>> And some people are brought
to trial who are
wrongly accused.
>> Betsy, I have put away tons
of violent individuals
in my career.
This man is worse than any of
them, believe me, I've got a
sense for it.
>> You've got a sense for it?
Then why don't you lock him up
and throw away the key?
I guess we'll be glaring
at each other from across
the aisle again.
>> If I'm glaring, it's
definitely not at you.
Let me show you something.
♪♪
These are the three women that
we pulled out of a pit yesterday
at one of your client's
construction sites.
If it hadn't been for the rain,
they would have been buried in
cement forever.
♪♪
>> You're right, Alan,
they're horrible.
But they don't convict
my client.
Oh, and you're also right
about Martin Darius.
He is powerful.
If you take a swing at him,
don't miss.
♪♪
>> Yes, I am Peter Lake.
Or I was.
10 years ago, in Hunter's Point,
my wife and my daughter
were murdered by a man,
a sex offender, named Waters.
He killed some other women, too.
They found one of them
in his basement.
I know all about it.
>> What happened to Waters?
>> He's dead.
He was shot resisting arrest.
>> Well that excludes him from
being a suspect in this case,
doesn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> But not you.
>> I've been in Sacramento
for 10 years.
If I'm the killer,
what have I been doing
for the last 10 years?
And besides, am I the only
person here who knows about
Hunter's Point?
>> Nancy Gordon.
You're saying that she
murdered those women?
And she's framing you.
Why?
>> 10 years ago, while the
investigation was dragging on,
Nancy Gordon and I
had an affair.
It started out
innocently enough.
She was working on the case, so
we obviously spent a great deal
of time together,
and we became friends.
She was easy to talk to.
She made me smile again.
It soon evolved into
something more.
She gave me the comfort
that I needed.
♪♪
I was alone, lost.
There's no excuse for
what I did.
It was wrong in so many ways.
We met a few times.
I broke it off,
she wanted to keep it going.
I told her I just couldn't.
>> She's framing you for murder
because you ended the affair?
>> You have no idea what she's
capable of.
After I broke it off, she
refused to accept it was over.
♪♪
>> Did you call the police?
>> No, I thought I could
handle it myself.
No, it's not, Nancy.
Nancy, it's not gonna work out.
Now look, stop it, just stop it.
Leave me alone.
>> No, I'm not gonna leave
you alone!
Peter!
[car starting]
[Peter grunting]
>> Under the circumstances,
I don't think anyone can blame
me for leaving.
Changing my name,
trying to get away.
>> 10 years, 3000 miles,
and she's still pursuing you?
>> You'll have to ask her
about that.
>> I have to think about
representing you, Mr. Darius.
If I don't, rest assured, I'll
return the retainer.
>> Betsy, let me tell you why
you're gonna defend me.
This case is gonna make you a
national figure.
It'll make your last case look
like a speeding ticket.
Why?
Because it's me, because there
are multiple victims, but
mainly, and most importantly,
because I'm innocent.
I could get other
representation easily.
I want you.
I did not kill these women.
>> Would you be wiling to take a
lie detector test?
♪♪
>> Is your birth date
January 26th?
>> Yes.
>> Is your name Martin Darius?
>> No.
>> Do you live at
1212 Sunrise Way?
>> Yes.
>> Have you recently donated
money to the public library?
>> Yes.
>> Do you have anything to do
with the missing women
in Sacramento?
>> No.
>> Did you kill Wendy Riser?
>> Are you a registered voter?
>> No.
>> Did you abduct Laura Ferrar?
>> Do you own pornography?
>> No.
>> Do you drive a Ferrari?
>> Yes.
♪♪
How'd I do?
>> You passed.
>> Are you still my attorney?
>> From now on our conversations
are privileged.
>> What's our next move?
>> I start spending your money.
[door buzzes]
♪♪
>> And following his meeting
with foreign dignitaries, the
President is expected to spend
the weekend at Camp David.
Meanwhile, the confirmation
hearing for Senator Raymond
Colby continued today
on Capital Hill.
Senator Colby is widely
considered to be in a strong
position with little
political opposition.
Many, in fact, consider the
debates to be merely
a formality.
Now turning to local news,
over 200 people gathered today
to oppose the construction
of a new shopping mall
on West Wind Boulevard.
A spokesman for
Darius Construction declined
to comment on the controversy.
[guitar music playing]
>> Hoo!
[man scatting]
[laughing]
Oh, my God.
Now it can't be T-Baum.
>> It is me, in the flesh.
>> Well, more like flannel.
>> Well, I leave messages and
you don't call me back.
>> See, no, I, I don't call back
because I know what that's like.
I mean, you know, you're already
into me for like two jobs, and I
don't want us to be about that.
You know, I don't want it to be
about the M-O-N-E-Y,
see now look, there it is.
You made me bring it up and I'm
already feeling bad,
look at that.
>> Well, don't feel bad because
I've got your payment.
>> Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I mean, it's not that I'm eager
or anything, you understand.
Payment in full in tens and
twenties, like you like it.
>> Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
>> Thank you.
>> It's too heavy.
>> Part of it's interest.
And part of it is advanced
payment on the next one.
Uh, advance... for what?
>> I want you to dig up all the
dirt you can on Martin Darius.
>> I hope to God
you're suing him.
>> I'm defending him.
Murder trial.
>> Okay, so, here's the number
for Darius' construction
foreman.
This is the service that
washes his car.
>> Wow, that was fast.
>> I know.
>> While you're being so
efficient today, I need a hard
copy file on any of the archival
news items that you can find on
a series of murders done at a
place called Hunter's Point,
New York.
1994 and 1996, there abouts.
>> '94, '96, okay I can do that.
Uh, is there anything else?
>> Yes, there is.
Uh, find out what you can pull
up on A, black roses,
or B, the phrase,
"Gone but not forgotten."
>> Okay, I'll go look that up
on the internet.
>> Okay.
>> Um, Dr. Keane's outside
waiting for you.
>> Oh, good, I'll be
right there.
Dr. Keane, thank you so much
for stopping by.
>> What can I do for you?
>> Well, I was hoping that you
still had some of your contacts
at the coroner's office.
>> For some reason, coroners
don't make many new friends.
We tend to stick together.
>> I need the autopsies on the
bodies that were found at the
Darius construction site.
>> Do you want the county's
report, or do you want more?
The county doesn't give much
money for an autopsy these days,
budget cutbacks.
>> What do you mean?
>> I'm sure their work could be
more complete if they had more
time and money.
>> Well, we've got money if
it'll get us information.
>> This is a situation where
money can make the dead talk.
>> How much do you think it'll
take to get 'em to
testify under oath?
>> There are limits.
>> How long before you can
get me something?
>> Not long, I'll let you know.
>> Okay, thank you so much.
Bye.
>> Miss Tannenbaum.
>> Lisa.
>> I really need to
speak to you.
>> Is everything okay
at your father's?
>> Never better.
He's delighted that my husband's
been accused of, uh,
being a serial killer.
>> Is there anything I can do?
>> Yeah, I was, uh, wondering,
how long have you
represented my husband?
>> Just under a week.
>> Doesn't that make you
a bit uncomfortable?
>> Why?
>> Well, he hired you only a few
days ago, and now suddenly he's
arrested for murder.
>> Well, the thought did cross
my mind, but I think, like
anyone else, he's entitled to
the benefit of the doubt.
>> Why?
What do you know about him?
>> Nothing more than
his public persona.
>> Mind?
>> Actually, it's a
nonsmoking office.
Sorry.
>> Um, that's why you came by
the other day, isn't it,
to the house?
You were curious.
>> Can I help you with
something, Lisa?
>> I don't know where
he goes sometimes.
It's been happening
a lot this summer.
And when I try to ask, he just
gets cold and distant.
So I've hired a private
investigator.
I have to know.
>> Okay.
>> His name is Oberhurst.
The strange thing is, he hasn't
called me in weeks.
I leave messages, and he doesn't
call me back.
So I'm thinking Martin may have
found out and, and paid him off.
I wanted to give that to you.
Maybe he can tell you something.
>> I'll look into it.
Thank you.
♪♪
Mr. Oberhurst.
Mr. Oberhurst?
♪♪
Anybody home?
Mr. Oberhurst.
♪♪
Hello?
>> This is the office of The
Oberhurst Detective Agency.
Our investigations are
discreet and confidential.
Leave a brief message, and one
of our operators will be back
to you shortly.
Thank you.
[machine beeps]
>> Yes, Mr. Oberhurst, this is
Lisa Darius calling again,
and I'm paying for a service
here, and I'm not getting
anything in return.
So if you don't call me back by
tonight, we're no longer
working together, thank you.
>> It was really creepy, Reggie.
Now what did you find
out about Darius?
>> Our little Martin does not
play well with others.
Once he's targeted an area,
he buys up the property under
market value.
Then he undermines all the
mom and pop shops.
You know, raises the rent, hits
them with code violations,
rezones, whatever, to, to
degrade the neighborhood.
Then, he appears like some sort
of guardian angel, starts a big
project, hypes the value, and
sells before the
construction is finished.
Thereby reaping all of the
rewards and passing on all of
the headaches.
>> Okay, we know he's
not an angel.
The question is, has he done
anything that would make anyone
hate him enough to want
to frame him for murder?
>> T-Baum, in general, in my
experience, framing is something
that doesn't really happen
in real life.
If someone is pissed off enough
that they want revenge, they
usually bypass the middleman and
bingo, they go straight
to the source.
>> They usually wind up in jail.
>> That depends on who's
defending them.
>> Look, all we have now is one
possible candidate who could
possibly hate him enough to want
to frame him for murder.
>> Nancy Gordon.
>> The prosecution's
star witness.
[door opening]
>> Alan, there's a problem.
>> What, what is it?
>> She's gone.
>> Gone, who's gone?
>> Nancy Gordon, you asked me
to swing by and check on her.
I knocked on her door,
I talked to the manager.
He said she checked out.
>> What?
>> Fellas, what's up?
>> Nancy Gordon's in the wind.
>> You're kidding.
You sure?
>> Yeah, without a trace.
Not even the black rose
and the note.
>> But she's half our case.
>> I know that, Randy.
And I don't need you looking
at me like that.
>> Like what?
>> Like you advised me not to
arrest Darius until I had more
than a few tire tracks
for evidence.
>> You're the DA, right?
>> Yeah, Nancy Gordon told me
the same thing.
>> What are we gonna do?
>> Find her, Clyde, all right?
Find her.
♪♪
[woman groaning]
>> Help...
Help me!
♪♪