- Hey bro?
- So "compadre".
- Damn.
- You're okay?
Yeah! I'm fine. I just want to
get my paycheck get out of here.
You broke again?
I laid out a little bit of money last night
No big deal, today is pay day.
- And what's her name?
- Gwnie Diamonds. She didn't show.
Hey, would you look at that?
One day I'm gonna have me one of those.
Yeah, you thinking of leaving
the docks and becoming a driver?
I'm gonna leave the docks all right
I ain't gonna be no limo driver.
One day would be a
very rich man.
You're saying since New Orleans, man.
I hope your dreams come true, Nick.
I could show you that
20 bucks you owe me.
Yeah, we're speaking of money.
I'm gonna get the paycheck.
Look that guy.
Get him out of here now
Hey where do you think you're going?
I want to talk to the foreman.
He's got my paycheck.
- It can wait. Get out of here.
- What wrong with you?
Beat it! Or I'll rip your head off
and bouncing around
like a basketball.
What hell is going on here?
I say we run fo it.
I say good.
Mr. Han.
Mr. Landis, we finally meet.
I am impressed by your accomplishments.
- Take a sit.
- No, thank you.
Very soon my organization will
be the most powerful in Asia.
With the British being ousted in 1997.
We need to expand.
There's too much competition.
Chicanos, Italians, Iranians.
- We need weapons, the best.
- You have the best.
Fortunately weapons
alone will not be enough.
It is the finger behind the
trigger which must be loyal.
A very powerful weapon.
A great journey begins with one step.
Would you like to do some
business, Mr. Landis?
- What would you have me do?
- Can you stand against that wall?
I'm afraid my accomplishments
well exceed your childishness.
I like you, Mr. Landis.
Seems we all have our limitations.
But what about my competition.
you know this James Fratelli?
- Fratello.
- That's him, yes.
- What do you want from him?
- I don't want anything from him.
I want something from you.
I want you to eliminate
Jimmie Fratello e Lopez.
This guy starts yelling
since I'm trying to break
his finger big deal is
trying to break his arm.
I bet that was the last pesky
trying to steal from you.
Nope. Believe it or not same
guy diferent finger 7th degree.
You know we really shouldn't be
laughing, we're out work again.
Yeah I know but after what
I saw those boxes, who cares?
Yeah I saw those.
Those were Mac-10s.
What kind of guys that use those
are like drug runners and assassins.
Whole bunch other guys
you don't want to meet.
I'll drink to that.
Seriously Nick, that's a third
job we've lost hasn't been in LA.
That's all lousy stinking jobs anyway.
I gotta tell you man, it up
to here with LA already.
How can you say that. I mean LA
is the land of opportunity.
In the night I'm at the gym.
I meet this guy his name's uh... Landis.
Anyway this guy pays big
money for full-contact fighters.
Big money, huh?
Big money. See this guy Lance
he sets up the fights underground.
You win the fight you win the cash.
No taxes, no nothing.
No feeling from the neck down if
you mess with the wrong guy, Nick?
You're always looking for an easy buck.
Haven't you learned there's no such thing?
It's called paying your dues, "compadre".
You're crazy. You could get
hurt you could get killed.
Yeah, well uh! I can take care of myself
and so can you so let's give it a shot.
I don't think so.
You don't get it, do you?
I've had enough.
Man, I hear they're
hiring up north pays good.
I'm thinking a heading up that way.
Maybe I'll do it right this time save
some money. Go back to school.
Well, looks like I go it alone.
We've been through a lot together. I mean
New York, Galliston you've been here in LA.
- You go for it you.
- Watch your ass.
Hey, what's gonna bail me out?
Why, should things change
call me if you need me.
He'll be back.
I'm owe 20 bucks.
- Doing something?
- No.
Open this valise.
That's Puccini.
my grandfather loved Puccini.
It was my mother's father
pretty Tommy O'Brien.
We got the name cuz he looked like an
Irish but he wasn't it was Italian.
Through and through the family
came from northern Italy.
But he didn't look at it.
You know he had this sandy, sandy
blonde and it's intense green eyes.
Pretty Tommy O'Brien he got the nickname
because he was a
good-looking son of the gun.
He really was they dressed
dressed to the night.
You know and except it
was a tiny little guy.
With a vicious temper and you never
wonder cross pretty Tommy O'Brien.
It was mean he had a mean side.
Well you know not only would he
whacked out but he cut your head off,
with this machete in amusing
this, this private machete of his.
And have you stole from him you're
not down on he wouldn't even
give you the decency to killing a
guy dead awful you're still alive.
There was a guy in the neighborhood used
to knock down right he knew about it.
For quite a while so this goombas joking
I'm right he's wait he's waiting.
One night he invites him
over for dinner you say
a couple lieutenants grab the guy two story.
Dragged him down on the basement
to hold him down on the floor and
Tommy O'Brien looks right the guy's face
he tells him laughing right in his face.
Stealing from me ain't
nothing lose your head over.
And proceeds to decapitate the
guy right there in the basement.
The guy was screaming for his mother.
There was blood every place.
That's was my grandfather yeah.
He was brutal but very effective.
- You got five minutes of my time, Vanik.
- Solely.
What I thought you guys went to the fight
since when you stopped playing with guns.
You can have as many as you want.
M-16's, Stinger missiles.
You name it.
Why are you coming to me with this?
I got plenty of weapons.
This little war it's
burning between you and the
Iron Tigers we just want to
be on this side that wins.
Maybe one day we need your help.
Maybe we can help you right now.
Why how wide of you. And what does
that help going to we're gonna cost me.
Not much. You buy the hot way from us
and we get 25% of the operation.
This Landis is little strange.
But is he also crazy?
Why would I do something like that?
Because gonna put you over the top.
Unless the Tigers
it's gonna get him first.
Think about, Jimmie.
Thank you again,
for your time.
Frankie.
Yeah boss?
Follow that muscle-bound loader to
find out whether stash of these things.
And whack their head.
I think Jimmie's gonna get a bang others.
Just like the fourth of July.
Oh, my God!
Isn't that impressive.
Nick, I'm confused.
You expected to kill.
You job is to kill.
You didn't.
I don't like that.
I said I'd fight I didn't say I'd kill.
This whole thing is sick. I quit.
Nicky, you don't understand.
You do what we tell you to do.
You're my boy Nick you're gonna
become the prize in my state.
We own now.
Oh yeah? Nobody wants me come on
Goldilocks. See what you got.
Goldilocks?
Nick. this is exactly
what I'm talking about.
Absolutely no regard
for my authority.
I hate a mess.
Take him out of here.
When the phone rings
you take the message
you put the message
here in this basket, Okay?
Excuse me. I'm John Larson
I'm here to see...
Yes. Mr. Larson,
just a few days late.
I'm really sorry about being late
I made a few stops on the coast.
Well welcome aboard.
Thank you I want you to know I'm very happy
to have this opportunity to work here.
Good, that's very good.
By the way a message came for you.
There's something wrong?
Yeah! A friend of mine in Los
Angeles looks like he's in trouble.
I'm sorry.
Well look why don't you come with
me and I'll show you the work area.
Miss McKenna I'm afraid
I can't take this job.
Excuse me?
I got to get back to LA,
my friend needs me.
Mr. Larson we have been holding
this position open for you.
Do you know how many
people want this job?
Yeah, maybe
next time, good day.
Hey mister you got anybody
to watch your bike?
I'll watch it for a dollar. Watch it
real good nobody's gonna hurt it.
Okay.
Watch my helmet.
Want something?
Yeah! I'm looking for a gentleman
by the name of Nick Wallace.
I think he's in the room 52.
Something wrong?
He's been gone for a week.
- What?
- Disappear.
Nice kid. Wants to be a boxer.
You need a room?
Yeah, yes I do.
Sign this.
Work?
40 bucks.
In advance.
- Room 22, up stair.
- Thanks.
Oh, so you have to see Nick can
you make sure tell I'm here.
Don't worry he's
owe me money, remember?
- Hey leave it alone.
- You talking to me once?
- Yeah leave it alone.
- Is that's your, you want it?
It's a friend of mine he's
pay me to watch it for him.
So will watch me
drive away on it then.
You mess with the bike
you've gotta mess with me.
I don't think so.
I warned you.
The girl values my buck.
Of course in the jobs just
go for employee of the week.
- Where did you learn that?
- In the streets.
- Come on, let me take you in home.
- I am home.
- Well, you live here?
- No, around here.
- Where's your family?
- None of your business.
I guess not.
You're hungry?
- Come on, let's eat.
- You're not a pervert or anything like?
So, what are you doing that hotel?
Look before a friend of mine.
What was the last time you ate?
Your friend's in trouble or something?
Yeah, he's kind of like you
he's always in trouble.
You know where he is?
No. I know he's around here somewhere.
- You know your way around.
- Not exactly.
Were you from?
Everywhere. Started off in New York working
the docks, then I move to west.
How are you gonna find your friend
if you don't know your way around?
You need a guide homey. You need
someone who knows the streets.
Well you wouldn't just happen to know one,
would you?
Don't be a jerk I know the streets.
All right what's this gonna cost me?
- Your bike.
- My bike, get real, kid.
I'm not a kid.
I'm Tommy.
If I help you find your friend
you can give me your bike.
Well, you drive a hard bargain kid.
I mean, Tommy.
We have a deal?
No, you never heard the one
about easy money, have you?
You see this guy around?
- Yeah, I see around.
- Have where?
Some private class,
in downtown.
What do you mean private?
Either hard to find unless you
have the right connection.
Do you?
I stay away from those kind of
places they can get pretty hairy.
Your friends hanging
around with this guys,
get a lot of trouble.
Let's say where
I want to find a place?
Chinatown.
POLICE STATION
Thanks.
No, I'm sorry.
I'll try that Danny Richardson.
Thanks, sir.
- Can I help you?
- I'm looking for Danny Richardson.
Sir, up the stairs turn to the
right second door on the left.
Thanks.
Can I help you?
I'm looking for Danny Richardson,
you see him around?
He's not around, she is.
- I'm Danny Richardson.
- I'm sorry, the name Danny...
Short for Danielle. My father's revenge
against my mother for not having a boy.
What can I do for you?
My name is John Larson. I'm looking for
a gentleman by the name of Nick Wallace.
- How'd you find me Mr. Larson?
- I was over at the hospital Sears.
They sent me over here,
Dr. Newman.
That's all I need. My workload
added on to by Peter Newman.
- What did he tell you I would do for you?
- Well he didn't actually say.
This is not a lost-and-found Bureau and
if Dr. Newman told you, that he's wrong.
- Good day, miss Richardson.
- Hold it I'm sorry. Have a seat.
Maybe I can help you
or at least I'm gonna try.
Well he's not in here at
the diner if somebody
found his body at being my computer.
What about your friend
in LA in the first place?
We came here together
work the docks for a while.
And when that ended I split.
He stayed.
- What do you do?
- Longshoreman.
Nick is a kickboxer though
he said who's gonna
fight for some promoter
by the name of Landis.
Paul Landis?
No first names just
Landis that's all I know.
Is there anything I should know?
Paul Landis is a pretty heavy name
if your friend mixed up with him.
What it mean?
Landis is a gangster not the kind of guy
anyone with half a brain would work for one.
Nick wouldn't work
for anybody like that.
You'd be surprised what
people will do for money.
Not Nick, is not like this.
That's I telling you.
Ok, you get me some
more information on this Landis guy.
I've got to find Nick.
If Nick's in trouble I gotta help him.
It will get me in trouble.
But okay meet me across the
street in the park in an hour.
Thank you.
Look here's the deal.
I'll help you find your friend if
you help me get a story out of this.
- A history?
- On Landis.
An expose on him can get me out of it
read apartment and into the newsroom.
- Well, why not, you got a deal.
- Just remember, I call the shots.
Yes ma'am.
Whatever you say.
- She giving you trouble?
- Who's your friend?
Tommy this is that reporter I told
you about, Danielle Richardson.
She don't look
like no reporter to me.
- She's your sister?
- You must be reporter, you're pretty nosy.
- Where'd you find her?
- She's okay.
We just talked to
one of the fight managers...
that said your friend
fought here last week.
No one's seen him since.
- Nobody else?
- That's it.
Is Landis right there.
I saw enough.
Let's get out of here.
Who's the big guy?
Mark Vanik.
We work for Landis.
Looks like a real psycho.
Sort of puts you two in
the same boat doesn't it?
You would also hurt
people for money?
First of all I never fought for the
money I fight from the competition.
Second of all.
I'm not into that anymore.
I grew out of it.
And yeah Nick fights for money.
But he's never permanently damaged
anybody at least not on purpose.
Now what do you say we get started?
- What are we doing here?
- Getting you an audition.
What's that supposed to mean?
I've done a little research on you,
Mr. Larson, once a champion kickboxer.
There's only one way to get
Paul Landis interested in you.
And that's to fight
for one his manager's.
I told you, I'm not in it anymore.
I don't fight competitions anymore.
- Do you want to find your friend?
- You know it does.
Okay look I may be new at this
but at least we're making progress.
If do you haven't been
able to find him your way,
so why don't we try it mine?
Your way could get me her hurt?
Hurt and you could be kill.
- But I bet you find your friend.
- Excuse me, do you have light?
Get lost.
It belongs to me.
Now what'd you go and do that for,
I was just getting to know her.
You see that man over there?
His name is Big Man.
He's a fight manager.
Wait here a minute. Oh, by the way, try
not to touch anything while I'm gone.
May I can take a beer?
Well, you just gorgeous.
What's a beautiful lady
like you doing in here?
You're buying or selling?
- You're Big Man?
- Lionel P. Big Man.
Call me Big Man.
Who's asking, what do you want?
I'm here to do you a favor.
- Do I get to pick the position?
- Biggie, you're so funny.
You see that guy over there at the bar?
He's the best fighter I've ever seen
and he's looking to make some money.
Him?
Don't toy with me.
I got all the fighters I want.
You know, they're all winners.
Look at your guys you he's unproven.
- Yeah, it will be...
- Hey, listen...
- I'll tell you what I do like about it.
- What's that?
His girlfriend.
Make a little deal with
you here's what I'll do.
You well, you take a little
ride on the big man express
and now I'll talk to you
about your boyfriend.
That's your best offer?
It's my only offer and
it's a real good one too.
Because that I'd last a lot longer with you
than you would with my boys.
- Oh yeah, Mr. Big Man?
- You call me Biggy.
I prefer to eat glass.
Your manager over there tells me
you guys claim to be fighters.
- Yeah.
- Well...
I've got a hundred 100
bucks that says the guy
over there at the bar
can kick all your asses.
Have you fine
and let her go.
- That was amazing.
- Not really. They were drunk.
- What's your name?
- John Larson.
Meet your new manager.
Pretty good.
Very impressive.
That was easy.
So, if you'd be in the stakes,
how could I mess up?
I did know tough guys
did that sort of thing.
Even tough guys
appreciate a beautiful woman.
You really laugh.
Try this more often.
- Good night.
You know?
I don't trust Han.
- Let me worry about Ham.
- You just don't get it, do you?
You think a guy like Han is just
gonna let us take over his operation?
If I deliver to Han what
he wants he'll play ball. unless...
- Unless what?
- Unless we eliminate him.
Eliminated?
Are you crazy, man?
Maybe it's time that I make
some decisions around here.
No, don't challenge me
It just wouldn't be healthy.
So we go in there the
collective dough right.
I tell nocking head
to get his piece.
Hey come on you gotta
tell everybody about it?
And then? I look at it?
And I'm looking at it?
- Essa coisa é de plástico.
- Isso foi um erro.
Jimmie just got whacking and
these guys are laughing?
You're worried too much.
He had it coming.
He was arrogant weak and stupid.
And he let his guard down.
Bad mistake.
Never ever did
let your guard down.
You let the guard down, everybody
takes an advantage over you.
Look at me. I took
advantage of my enemy's.
Italian suit,
Italian shoes, a gold watch.
Money and a
200 $ haircut Hey.
What more do you want?
Is that all right?
Look this place.
Is like a fortress.
It's not pretty good
day for you uh, Vincent.
The spirits must really be upset.
Look at your aura,
it's fading.
Lazzard, you bastard.
Is it kid, this ain't no bar brawl.
this is it!
Concentrate, don't worry
about the crowd. Win this Fight.
There are two types of fighters,
there's a chess player
and check the player
A chess player take two
hits and give one.
A check player would never take
any and give four five and six
- What are you?
- Chess player.
OK, let's work.
Work their jab work that jab.
The jab that took to the body.
Jab. kick all my constituents.
Punch, kick, left hook.
Understand that's warrior is about.
You gotta focus.
you gotta control those
motions under pressure.
It's not all hard you hit,
is all right you hit.
Knowledge is power.
Use the power of knowledge
and experience you have, planning up.
Why LA?
It's home. I wouldn't wait for a while
though, you know? College, little travel.
But I came back.
College, huh?
I've been thinking about
going back to school myself.
Maybe someday.
Your folks?
My mom died about years ago and my
dad that's on a ranch outside solving.
But we're very close you know.
It's all the family I have.
An only child I should've guessed.
That one the attitude comes from.
Hey look Buster. On the streets of LA you
need an attitude or you'll be eaten alive.
I guess you got a point there.
You really don't like fighting, do you?
- No no anymore.
- What for?
Three years ago I had my last fight.
I want a championship of the world.
My opponent died in the ring.
- John, he knew the risk.
- Yeah, I know.
He had a wife and two kids.
- What?
- Thanks.
Watch this guy, he's tough.
He's one the best fighters in Japan.
Don't let him get to you
first because if he does,
next thing you're gonna hear
is the fat lady sing, right?
Don't worry.
The world promotor: Landis.
Stay away from him.
- Why?
- Don't worry about that.
You gotta fight for them let's just get out
there and kick this guy's ass, all right?
You gotta focus.
Knowledge is power.
Understand what a
warrior is all about.
Winner! Winner!
Man, you were great!
You kill that guy.
You did good.
You and me gonna be rich.
I hope there's enough
in that deal for me.
Excuse us for interrupt you,
my name is Paul Landis.
This is my partner, Mark Vanik.
- We're our fight promoters.
- Yeah I've heard of you guys.
- Oh good, I hope.
- From another fighter.
- Nick Wallace.
- Wallace? Wallace?
- Something ring a bell?
- Not once.
No I'm sorry. Then I work with
so many different fighters.
- Where are you from?
- I've just got into town from up north.
I see.
- And who is this lovely young lady?
- Danielle Richardson.
My pleasure.
I'm having a little party at
my place tomorrow afternoon.
I'd like you and your young
friend here to be my guest.
- I think you'll find it very profitable.
- Well I'd have to move by my manager.
Oh, by all means bring your funny
little friend along. Will be funny.
I'll have my chauffeur pick
you up say one o'clock?
One would be fine.
Little friend, huh.
I told you to stay away from him
what do you want to drop dead?
Calm down nobody's gonna die.
What harm can come from one party?
Don't be fooled by him.
He could trap you
like a spider traps a fly.
I've seen him do it.
You know where I'm
from there's an old story.
The Emperor once gave our entire province
to a great warlord named Chow Lee.
At first Chow Lee was
very honorable and loyal,
and this came him much
favor with the Emperor.
Who in turn gave him
his prized horse.
Then Chow Lee began to steal
tax monies do the Emperor.
The Emperor had him punished
for his greed in his loyalty.
He had him dragged through the entire
province on the very horse he had given him.
So you see Mr. Landis,
when it comes to greed and loyalty...
they're mortal enemies.
What an interesting story.
Yes fine European craftsmanship.
Rolex, Mercedes, Mac-10.
- Know how they're all the same.
- No, Rolex is Swiss.
They're all the same
doesn't matter.
- How much?
- Ten boxes. $ 500.000.
Shipping cost,
They're be yours.
250 now, 250 on delivery.
We split the cost of shipping.
I supply the ship, you
supply the crew. Deal?
- Deal.
- Ok, we get a deal.
Here comes you majesty.
John, glad you can make it.
Miss Richardson.
The lovely Mr. Richardson.
Why Mr. Landis? Are you always
this charming with all your guests?
Only the beautiful one.
- You think I'm wearing a crystal.
- I don't know much about them.
They do it power you they
could change your life.
Mark, you remember John?
Of course yes.
Excuse me, I'm going
entertain the guests.
- What do you think of our little party.
- That's great. Nice place.
Could you do me a favor
and entertain miss Richardson?
Well, John and I
talk a little business.
- Do you wanna something to drink, John?
- No, thanks.
Sit please.
Ah, my computers.
They are my eyes and ears.
See I have international business interests.
My computers give me a
small edge on the competition.
Once in a while
a slight edge.
- I'm sorry I didn't know that was valuable.
- You have to be very careful with crystals.
This one happens to be
related to my personal aura.
And someone is holding if they
could drain off my energies.
Like my computer's, they give me
a slight edge on my competition.
Crystals, auras.
You hardly seen the type.
If it wasn't for this crystal
I wouldn't be as powerful as I am.
I'm sorry I didn't
mean a disrespect.
I'll come right to the point, John.
I'd like you to fight for me.
I've already got a manager.
I can guarantee you'll make more money
with me and you could ever imagine.
And you and your young
lady comfortable for a long time.
- I'd have to think about it.
- Take your time.
You know where to find me.
But in the meantime...
enjoy yourself.
- Be right back.
- I think I have been sick.
- And your shirt?
- Do not ask.
What a smell.
The shower is over there.
Thanks.
- Are you allright there?
- Yeah. I will Survive. I think.
- You still have a hangover?
- You're an idiot.
- That's supossed to means?
- I know Landis e Vanik.
You know?
You're dumber than a...
housefly with with a metal plate
in his head you know that?
Is that any way to talk the man
it's gonna make you rich?
Listen. Landis will use you.
He puts you in a "Death March".
What it mean "Death Match"?
You know that. Two guys get in the
ring and they fight it out fo somebody dead.
Landis and his rich
buddies bent on that stuff.
I don't believe that.
- You end up just like the other guy.
- What other guy?
It was a fight of the Landis.
He didn't do what Landis wanted him to.
Suddenly he's gone.
Nobody see him since.
- You know his name?
- Something that Wallace.
- Nick Wallace?
- I don't know. I don't care.
- He's dead?
- Could be, who knows?
Really?
Who cares, you know?
You sure?
Yeah. I guess I'm too late.
- We should go to the police.
- Tell them what?
- There is not even a body.
- Maybe he's not dead.
I don't know.
I need something evidences.
I should have my
head examined to go...
along with the plan like this
you're gonna get yourself killed.
No, I won't. You just make sure
here when I get back.
I got to get this computer.
What do you expect to find in there?
I don't know anything to
bring those bastards down.
I had to go.
I'll be back.
Be carefull.
Thanks.
Bingo!
HAN/ARMS SHIPMENT
ACESS DENIED!
What are you waiting for?
Come on in.
Could you go any faster?
I was going any faster
we'd be in the Indy 500.
What's the matter, tough guy?
Brain women driver?
We got one more left.
Let's turn back here.
Someone broke into the study.
Why?
So what did he get?
Enough.
Tell me why.
Just give me one good reason
why I shouldn't kill you right now?
Get out.
Why don't we see what we get.
A rat in the kitchen.
Find him.
What are we gonna do?
We've got to take these files to police.
I wouldn't trust the police.
Landis had his hands on bought at that spot.
Então vamos publicá-lo.
Então a polícia precisa ouvir.
This is true, but
you will lose your story.
I don't get about the
storyright now right now.
We've got more important
things to think about.
Go ahead if you and your friends
want to look like Swiss cheese.
I know I'm really disappointed in you, John.
Very disappointed.
We give you the chance to be
a rich man and what do you do?
What did he do?
- You ripped us off.
- He ripped us off.
I'll give you one minute to tell us
who you are who you work for,
and where the files.
I say who?
Who? The cops? Han?
You think he's losing it?
You're probably right.
But you see he gets real pissed off when
someone breaks into my house and steals.
So let's try it again.
Who sent you?
- Who sent you?
- Nobody sente me, man.
I'm here to find my friend, Nick Wallace,
the fighter I told you about.
Wallace? Wallace?
You're liyng.
Oh no man, it's true.
I don't want nothing from you.
Wallace is here and still alive.
Who knows, maybe I will kill him now.
We get this straight.
You're not with Interpol,
you're not with the
police or that guy Han?
You've been trying to take me
down because of a friend.
Let the girls go and
I give your files.
I'm gonna kill them all except for
the girl who I'm making around.
As far as my files,
you can have to.
- Buster, I kill you, man.
- Correction, we gonna kill you.
- Where are the girls?
- What girls?
That's not why I want to hear.
John!
We're gotta get out of this place.
- I was thinking where were you.
- Don't even think about it.
You'd be dead.
Let the girls go.
Not till after the show.
You wanna play?
Let's play!
- It's all right?
- Better find Landis.
I have to find Nick first.
Nick.
Oh, man!
You move?
You all right?
I've been better.
- You think you can walk?
- I can try.
- Where have you been so far?
- I was in a traffic jam.
That's it we got to get out of here.
Get Nick off the boat.
I'm going after Landis.
Take this.
You may need it.
Come on, we gotta
get you out of here.
Tough day.
Thanks bro, save my life.
What choice that I have?
You still owe me 20 bucks.
- So what's next cowboy?
- Well a shower would be nice.
Honey, think you can
find a cheeseburger?
Course.
Subtitles Dutch: Wess Lee
Translation: Kilo