Verified, Becker 1.
I've got your suspect northbound
on Market, heading right on Basket.
Link at 12, Henry 1.
You can vector at 135.
OK, 43.
Helming a call at 5-4 and Main.
Connect 40 to a backup.
13-A, 43.
22, did you clear?
22 clear.
I need a number identified.
Can you turn that shit off?
Yeah.
- Pasco's double-crossing me now.
He's buying from Lopez. That
son of a bitch owes me 100 grand.
I'm losing my patience.
He thinks he's safe with me in here.
Well, what do you want me to do?
You know what to do.
- All right, don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
Good morning.
You're gonna be late for work.
- I don't care.
What are you doing today?
- I'm on another stake out with Mac.
I gotta listen to his stories again.
You should stay home, then.
I'd better get going.
I'm late now.
I gotta go.
See you later?
See you later.
There's some coffee down there.
Yeah.
Look at the life on this baby?
God, I love cars.
Hey, pal, out of the car.
Can't you read the sign?
No touching the cars.
What did you say?
- I said out of the car.
Hey, Garrett.
Garrett, what's going on?
Can we talk about this?
Too late.
You went behind our backs.
Dealing with Lopez is
not in the contract.
It was a one shot deal, I swear.
I was in a bind.
- You owe us 100 grand.
I'll get it for you.
I swear, I'll get it by Friday.
Friday?
How many chances do
you think you get?
Remember, you buy from us.
No Lopez, no nobody.
Right?
I'll get you $50,000 in an hour.
I swear, I'll get the rest on Friday.
Friday?
What's this Friday shit?
Man, today's Tuesday.
I don't have the time.
Johnny?
Kill her.
Garrett?
Yeah.
All right.
I like his coat.
What time you got?
7:20 in the morning.
20 seconds.
Do you know something?
This is like an anniversary for me.
I'm a real happy man today.
Yeah?
Why?
About a year ago, when I was working
for the Riverside Police Department,
we got this call, right?
Somebody had broken into a house.
So I show up on the scene, I start
checking out the area, and whatnot...
All of a sudden, this guy takes
off from behind some bushes.
The report also said this
guy was armed and dangerous.
And I'm running behind this guy,
and I'm screaming in my most
authoritative voice, halt!
Halt or I shoot.
And he ain't paying no
attention to me, right?
So I get pissed off.
So I pull out my gun, and I take aim.
I start shooting.
I can't hit him, man.
I swear to God, I tried my best.
I couldn't hit the son of a bitch.
Finally I shot like,
two, three, four times.
Fourth shot, hit the ground.
Ricocheted, hit his heel.
The dude went down, I
caught him, I cuffed him.
Funny thing about it,
I got an accommodation
for not killing the guy.
Some TV news reporter did a
story on me, said that I shot
warning shots over the
head of a fleeing felon
who was armed and dangerous.
I couldn't believe it.
Everybody thought I was
like, the big humanitarian.
Truth of the matter was I was
trying to inoculate that son
of a bitch with my 357 magnum.
That's a great story, ain't it, Ron?
Yeah, Mac.
It's great.
- Yeah.
I like it.
I guess I'd better record it.
Don't move.
Now get up nice and easy.
Come on.
You wouldn't shoot
us, would you, officer?
I think I'll start a
collection of these.
How old are you?
I'm 23.
Christ, he's just a kid.
I want you to count to 500 before
you come through that door.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
- Yes.
That's stupid.
We can't let him go.
Let's off him.
He's a cop.
Put the gun away.
Put the gun away!
All right, start counting.
One.
I can't hear you.
1, 2...
That's it.
3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10...
All right, Garrett!
You're something else, man.
Who.
Code 33.
Officer down.
Code 30... 10th and Jay.
Let's go.
- Shit.
Let's crank it up.
Let's get out of here.
Did you see the look
on that cop's face?
I loved it.
- Look, don't get carried away.
This is business, Johnny, not fun.
Dumbass punk.
If it wasn't for Shanks,
you'd be washing cars and kissing ass.
Hey, stop putting me down, man.
I'm going to run this show
when Shanks gives the word,
and you know it.
And now every cop in this
city will be looking for us.
Piece of shit.
Why don't you junk it?
What do you mean, piece of shit?
It's a piece of shit!
It is not a piece of shit.
Christ.
It's Jake's kid.
Two white men.
Tell me which way they went.
They went north.
North on... on the highway.
What were they driving?
Driving a black...
Black Impala.
Custom.
There's nothing we can
do for him down there.
If there's a Heaven, I
hope you're looking down
when I blow these guys away.
Lincoln 44, Lincoln 44, Baker 1.
Lincoln 44, be advised, I have
positive contact on that 1958
black and white convertible.
Lincoln 44, Baker 1.
Be advised, suspect vehicle
is eastbound on Highway 280.
OK, 43.
Handle a call at 54 Main.
This is unit 44.
Do have visual contact, proceeding
to highway, southbound at Merritt,
in pursuit two suspects.
Black custom Impala, custom
paint, flames on the sides.
Texas tags.
Frank, George, Henry, 671.
Request backup.
I'll take this floor.
You go upstairs.
We've got a lot of area to cover.
What about backup?
Fuck backup.
I'm gonna get these sons of
bitches for what they did.
Freeze!
Down on your knees.
All right, all right.
I'm down.
Put your hands on your head.
Now!
Move it!
All right!
Easy.
Don't shoot.
Shut up.
Shut up!
Shit.
Man.
All right, Al Capone.
Stand up.
Come on, let's go.
Stand...
Dumb shit, falling for that, man.
Get the keys.
- Relax.
I'm trying to find it.
The damn thing... relax.
You know, Johnny?
I got a better idea.
What?
Lean forward.
Lean forward some...
What is it, man?
Lean forward!
I... what?
Ron... man, what did you do, man?
Have you gone crazy?
I got hit from behind.
I didn't do it.
Let me have your gun, man.
So what happened to Johnny?
How come you left him?
I told you, we got separated.
For Christ's sakes, man,
it's lucky I got out
of there with my life, myself.
The cop was fucking nuts.
He was a pound short of a shilling.
Any more of this coffee left?
The cop's a dead man.
Shanks was grooming Johnny
to take over the operation.
Johnny.
Johnny was a day late, a dollar
short, and on the wrong train.
He was a punk.
Face it, Garrett,
you never liked him.
And you did, right?
I'd like to take care
of this cop myself,
but Johnny's gone, and
Shanks will take care of him.
We got business to take care of.
We gotta take care of Lopez.
He's getting out of hand.
He's moved his operation to
a bigger warehouse downtown.
This small timer has got big ideas,
and he's giving himself some
muscle to back himself up.
Are you sure of that?
I want you to take care of him.
And don't blow it.
What was that?
I said, don't blow it.
I thought Shanks ran this operation?
I mean, since when did you take over?
Well, la dee da.
So that's what it's about?
I got some parts to move out.
I gotta go.
Yeah, it's getting late.
You know, Garrett, I don't
trust those sons of bitches.
And us here...
I got into this business
because I love cars.
I really love cars.
Well, if you ever feel like you
need to do something
with Clinton and Tulson,
let me know.
Just keep your eye on 'em.
Did you assist with the
autopsy on the victim?
Yes, I did.
And based upon your findings,
what is your conclusion?
I have determined that the
assailant was standing, holding
the weapon approximately 2 inches
from the victim, who was
handcuffed and kneeling.
Detective Maguire, did
you find any evidence
that would suggest that there was
a second suspect in the area?
Look, I'm sure there was.
He probably went out a
window, or something.
That is your opinion.
I am asking you, detective,
is there any evidence
that would suggest
that a second person
might have hit Detective Taylor
from behind, as he testified?
There was no evidence.
Ronald Taylor, you are hereby
sentenced to 15 years to life.
I order that you be placed
in a federal penitentiary
for your own protection.
You will be transferred to a
straight correctional facility
as soon as authorities
deem it appropriate.
Where did you two get all this stuff?
I'll give you $500 for the lot.
6,000.
Come on.
The last batch of stuff
I got from you guys
is still sitting in the warehouse.
500.
6,000.
This stuff is hot.
You guys are crooks.
I'll call the cops.
Andy, Ramirez, come on
over here for a minute.
Bad mistake, my friend.
Bad mistake.
What are you in for?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Touch me again, and
I'll pull your asshole
through that garbage
disposal you call your mouth.
51.
Gentlemen, I'm Senior Corrections.
Officer Michael Prentice.
I'd like to welcome you all on board.
The rules in this federal
penitentiary are very simple.
You will cooperate.
You'll be issued the inmates'
manual, which will tell you
about the rules and
guidelines that you
must follow while you're
in this institution.
For the next 30 days, you'll
be at a reception program
and/or orientation.
You'll be assigned to a team
of correctional professionals
who will manage your stay here.
After this meeting you'll get
your medical examinations,
and you'll be issued
your jail clothing.
My advice to you, you can
make your prison stay as hard,
or as easy as you want to.
Participate in all the
programs, and act like adults.
Any violations of the rules will
result in disciplinary action.
Thank you.
Follow the yellow line.
A, D, and E blocks,
stand in for lockdown.
All right, Taylor.
Here's your new home.
Lock it down!
All lockdown units, report for count.
Welcome to the big league, slugger.
Name's Dieter Guthrie.
Former baseball player from
the state of Tennessee.
How you doing?
Well, there ain't much to the place.
- head bunk's yours, of course.
There's the shitter.
Take turns cleaning it, twice a week.
There's a TV.
Watch anything you like.
As long as you like what I like.
You know... word has it
that you're a policeman.
Now, I don't find any
offense with that.
I figure, live and let live.
But... there' some
boys in this place
that do find an
offense to that, so I'd
watch my ass in more ways than
one, if you know what I mean.
Yeah, yeah.
I met your welcoming committee.
Great bunch of guys.
Well, our welcoming committee
is calling you the executioner.
I'm not an executioner.
Damn.
Another innocent man.
You know, this whole place
is filled with innocent men.
Except me.
I did it.
Say, Maguire, I'm curious...
How does it feel to turn
in your own partner?
You don't know what the
hell you're talking about.
I had no choice.
He was your partner, man.
You stabbed him in the back.
Look, you weren't there.
Neither one of you guys were there.
So why don't you just get
out of my face, all right?
What do we got here,
an attitude problem?
Decided to take the 500?
We came to throw you another offer.
Good catch.
You called?
Hey, what's going on around here?
Other suppliers have tried
to invade our territory.
Our clients, like Ramirez, are
giving our drivers a bad time.
They say they think they can
get parts from other sources.
Make an example of Ramirez.
Well, as usual, Tulson,
I'm way ahead of you.
And by the way, this is
the last time I tell you...
Don't tell me what to do.
That maniac's getting out of hand.
Somebody's going to have to
take over this operation,
and we can't let it be Garrett.
Maybe we should put a leash on him?
Yeah.
Permanently.
Guys.
What are you doing?
Shit.
Jesse.
- Shanks.
Where you been, man?
I missed you.
I've just been so busy.
Personal problems, and all.
You know, Shanks.
Yeah, I know how it is.
Morales has been real
good to you this week.
And you've missed appointments.
You've been avoiding me, man.
And that's not healthy.
You know who I am?
Hey, Shanks, come on, man.
Back off!
You killed Johnny.
He didn't have a chance.
Fuck you, asshole.
I didn't kill anybody.
It's only the beginning, Taylor.
Put a leash on me?
Put a leash on me, right?
What do you know
about this guy so far?
Name is Henry Tulson.
Has a list of priors dating
back to the early '70s.
Chop shop operator.
That sound familiar?
Breaks down cars, chops
'em up, sells off the car
parts for far more
than the car is worth.
Big business.
Who did he work for?
Someone by the name of Shanks had
a multimillion dollar operation
before he went to prison.
The guy Taylor killed
was Shanks' cousin.
Did you know that, detective?
No, I didn't.
You know, this whole situation
is starting to bother me.
I got a bad feeling about Taylor.
Like... maybe he
didn't kill anybody.
Maybe he was telling the truth.
Maybe the DA's office
railroaded him for no reason.
The suspect was handcuffed.
Yeah, I was there.
But Johnny didn't go into
that building by himself.
I know that for sure.
If I could just find his partner...
At least we got a good
lead here, though.
It's the small businessmen
who buy the stuff.
You can take an $8,000 car,
break it down into parts,
and sell it for more than $35,000.
You think they're going to talk?
Taylor was my partner.
It was my testimony
that put him away.
That still keeps me awake at night.
I'm going to find this guy.
And I'm going to put him away.
Prove me wrong, detective.
Prove me wrong.
You bet.
Louis Howard, report to industries.
Well, excuse me.
I have to go see the man now, Ron.
Who's that?
Local pusher?
Flush.
You have a package for me, honey?
Got nothing for you this week.
What are you talking about?
Sit down, bitch.
All right, guys.
Back to work, back to work.
What do you mean?
I was supposed to get
a package every week.
That was the deal.
Hey, holmes, you been late, bro.
You've been missing appointments.
Is that the way you're
gonna repay Shanks
for all that stuff for you?
Morales, please.
I haven't been myself.
I've been sick.
Holmes, you pay me...
Taylor!
Knock off the bullshit
and get back to work!
He reminds me of an
umpire I used to know.
You boys are doing some good work.
Leave me alone.
You fellas know what?
I just love the smell of gas fumes.
It reminds me of home.
Why don't you just go
ahead and ask that driver
for a ride out of here, Jesse?
Hell, I'm sure he wouldn't mind.
You guys ever really
think about breaking out
of this place?
Just about every second I'm awake.
You see that vehicle there?
Man, it just goes right out.
Just right out to the outside.
You gotta understand, Taylor...
Dieter, he's an old timer like me.
But that truck is our
only way out of here,
and we just don't have
the balls to do it.
Speak for yourself, dude.
Ha ha ha.
Hey!
Get over here!
You the guy who called?
Yes, I called.
Let me get this right...
You want a transmission
for a 280 SEL,
you want a rear panel for a BMW 735,
and you want 12 alloy BBS rims?
That's right.
It's exactly what I want.
What are you going to
do with all that stuff?
What you mean, what I'm
doing with all this stuff?
Yeah.
I'm redecorating my house with it.
That's what I'm doing with it.
Man, why you wanna ask me
some stupid questions, man.
I can't sell it to you.
And who the hell are you?
Who am I?
I'm American Express.
I'm Visa.
I'm the Discover Card.
Look, man, my money
is good, all right?
I work eight hours a day,
I work 10 hours a day.
I work Saturdays and Sundays.
I got customers.
I do side jobs, I do
in jobs, I do out jobs.
I'm a job man.
That's what this
whole thing is about.
Jobs, man.
And... wait a minute, newsflash.
Newsflash.
You're not selling to me
because I'm a black man.
That's it, isn't it?
I'm a black man, he
won't sell it to me.
That's right.
You know what?
I'm a black man with five children.
Jamal, Janice, Shaquan,
Shawonga, and...
And Elvis.
That's right, Elvis.
And Elvis is sick.
Elvis is so sick, he
has to live in a bubble.
You gonna bust my little boy's
bubble just because I'm black.
I'm gonna call the NAACP, the SPCA...
Wait a second.
It takes a couple of
days to get these things.
I can't get 'em overnight.
I got a shipment coming in Thursday.
Come back on Thursday.
Thursday.
All right, then.
Thursday's good.
I'll be back Thursday.
Yeah, come back then.
Pleasure doing business
with you gentlemen.
And I like your establishment.
It's so beautiful around
here, and everything.
Just come back Thursday?
Just do me a favor.
And my son will be
able to get that neck
transplant that he needs.
I'm going home to
take care of him now.
Later.
Hey, we got to load up right.
Well, get it.
Let's get out of here.
Everything's here but the radios.
The boss says the radios
will be here next time.
OK.
5,500.
Boss said 7,500.
7,500?
6,500.
Boss said 7,500.
I'm not paying 7,500.
7,000.
7,000?
OK.
Rover unit one, all clear.
East gate.
Ronald Taylor, you have a visitor.
Hi.
Let me say hi to Chelsea.
- OK.
Here, Daddy wants to say hi.
Hi, Daddy.
Hi, sweetheart.
How are you?
Fine.
You miss daddy?
Yeah.
Let me speak to mommy again.
How is it?
It's not that bad in here.
I worry about you all the time.
I love you.
Don't worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
How's Chelsea doing?
She misses you.
How's the money holding out?
There's still plenty in the bank.
And my mom's going to get
me in where she works.
It's only part time.
It'll be good for to get out.
Besides, we could
use the extra money.
I wanted us to have a good life,
and I turned it all to shit.
You don't need this.
You don't need me.
Don't say that.
I love you.
None of this matters.
We only have a short time.
Let's not ruin it, honey.
I want you to divorce me.
What?
It's better for you.
For the baby.
You can start fresh.
But I don't want a divorce.
You can beat this thing.
We know you didn't do it.
Mac called.
He says he's on to something.
I thought he forgot about me.
He wants to talk to you.
He says he'll call
you later this week.
A waste of time.
Visiting hours are over.
Inmates report to block E.
Closing up!
All right.
Hey!
Taylor?
Report down to the kitchen.
They've got a little job for you.
Hey, pig!
You're gona die!
Hey, back it off, man.
Come on!
Sorry about the little
mess downstairs, boss.
Yeah, the jerk set me up.
Everything all right?
Yeah.
There was a monkey down
there waiting for me.
Asshole.
You really think
that shit's gonna work?
It won't stop a knife,
but it'll slow it down.
I wore a flack jacket
for 15 months in 'Nam.
Never thought I'd be
wearing one again.
Especially one made out of
"Newsweek," for Christ's sakes.
You see a lot of shit over there?
Yeah, I saw my share.
I thought, if I could
only survive this,
the rest of my life would be gravy.
You ever kill anybody?
Can't even tell the difference.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you couldn't tell it, man.
Just, looks like you're
wearing an umpire's vest.
You're really hung up on
that baseball stuff, aren't ya?
Good luck to you, man.
Thanks.
Bring 'em in.
It's nice to see you
doing an honest day's work.
Go to hell.
Hey!
Yeah, boy!
Fuck him, man.
Fuck you.
I get it.
No, he ain't shit.
- Yo.
Yo.
- Just come on out this way.
Come here.
Keep going.
Real costume show.
It ain't no show, man.
Them dudes are for real.
You mind your own business,
they leave you alone.
At least most of the time.
You're in the wrong place.
Yeah.
This is for Johnny!
Attention in the yard.
Bend over!
There's nothing worse
than a cop gone bad.
Thomas should have finished you off.
You could have done
us all a big favor.
I won't die in this place!
I wouldn't put any money on that.
Close five.
I won't die in this place!
I won't die in here!
So what are you getting at?
What I'm getting at is Shanks is out.
Look, he's in the joint.
He does nothing.
We do all the work.
Why shouldn't we have
the lion's share?
I don't know about this.
He has powerful friends
in and out of prison.
This is a dangerous move.
Garrett, you know, he's right.
When he finds out
about this, he's not
going to take this lying down.
You can bet on that.
Don't worry about Shanks.
I'll take care of him the
way I did Tulson and Johnny.
So the cop was telling the truth?
Nobody fucks with me.
I've got a bad feeling.
I don't know about this.
I know that you were
really tight with Tulson,
but I think we can
work this thing out.
I really do, all right?
Look, what I do is in the
best interest of the business.
You know, there's always
resistance to change.
Look, why don't you just
think this thing over?
There's no rush, you don't
have to make any big decision.
Just think it over.
OK.
Good.
I'll think about it.
I'll let you know.
Cut me in.
What?
Yeah.
Clinton, I have a brilliant idea.
All right, gentlemen,
stand back from your cells.
Lock it up.
Lockdown.
So there it was, bottom
of the ninth, two men out.
But we got three runners
on, and the score is 4-3.
Army's lead.
Well, who do you expect
comes up to the plate?
That's right.
Old Dieter.
Now, that pitcher is just
scared to death of me.
You see, I already got two
hits off of this turkey,
and he's up there
sweating rosary beads.
So that first pitch comes...
It damn near takes my head off.
Ball one.
Second pitch, low and outside.
Ball two.
Third pitch comes, damn near
knocks me off the plate.
Ball three.
Boy, I got this turkey
right where I want him.
I just cock that big bat back.
I want me a base hit on
this next pitch, though.
Here it comes.
Damn near takes off my head again.
I say hey, run batted
in is a run batted in.
Threw my bat down, started
going to first base.
Umpire says, strike one!
I said, what the hell?
Strike?
I said, all right.
OK.
I went back, got my big stick.
I'm ready for the next pitch.
I wanted a base hit, anyway,
you know what I mean?
Here comes the ball.
Low and inside.
Hell, couldn't hit it if I wanted to.
Umpire says, strike two.
Strike two?
God damn.
Now, that made me mad.
Now, I was hot.
All right.
I dug back into that...
That batter's box, and I'm
ready for that next pitch.
Now, that count's three and two.
Here comes the ball.
I swear to God, Mr. Taylor,
hit in front of the plate
before it crossed it.
I started going to first base.
Umpire said... strike three.
Strike three!
God damn.
God damn, that made me mad!
And I had that... that big, 40
ounce baseball bat in my hand,
and...
I just...
You telling me you killed the umpire?
Well, I ain't proud of it, but...
That's the truth.
In front of 2,500 witnesses.
Christ, listening to you
reminds me of my partner.
God damn.
Strike three.
Why are you doing this, Garrett?
I told you I was going
to think about it.
Yeah, well, I thought about
it, man, and I changed my mind.
You know, I really did.
You've got to anticipate
the future if you want
to get ahead in this world.
And you didn't.
You hesitated.
Now, you know they say about
the quick and the dead?
You're a bad risk, Clinton.
A bad risk.
Please don't do this to me.
Well, I'm sorry.
Fuck you, Garrett!
Fuck me?
Fuck you.
I don't want anymore mistakes.
Don't worry, holmes.
I made one just like
this in San Quentin.
It blew the motherfucker's head off.
You roll this real tight,
pack some matches in it,
some metal from your zipper.
Light the end, and bang,
the motherfucker's dead.
He'd better be dead this time.
One more fuck up, and it's your ass.
What you got?
Come on.
Are those mine.
- Yeah.
Come on.
You don't draw 'em.
Who in the hell taught you this game?
Dieter, come on.
No!
Dieter!
Hey, Dieter, man, stay with me.
It'll be OK.
It'll be OK, man.
Hey...
Strike... strike three, man.
Dieter!
No, man!
No!
Are you going that way?
Hey, man.
Look, I'm sorry I didn't
come to see you sooner.
I really feel bad.
It was my testimony
that put you in here.
There's nothing you could have done.
You're a good cop, Mac.
Yeah, well, I know you didn't
kill that punk Johnny Shanks.
I've been tailing this guy that
runs a foreign car dealership
over on the east side.
You know the place?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know the place.
Yeah, well, I'm pretty
sure that it's a front.
Is he the son of a
bitch that set me up?
Could be.
I can't prove it yet, but
there's been a lot of action
in the streets.
A lot of people being killed
over on the east side,
and every one of the victim seems
to be related to a chop shop.
Well, what can I do?
How can I help?
Well, right now all you
can do is just stay alive
until I can get you
out of here, buddy.
Just stay alive.
Yeah.
It's getting to be a full time job.
Take care.
Can't see you until another week.
That's a long time.
Now I need a big favor.
Name it.
I need fresh vehicles.
I need one a month, every month.
Not too flashy.
They gotta have air conditioning.
My homeboys got a lot of business
to do out in the desert.
Tell me when, and where.
I'll see to it.
I'll give you the specs
in a couple of days.
And Mr. Shanks,
don't disappoint me.
I've never disappoint you, Ralph.
I don't intend to now.
Good.
Let's keep it that way.
And what happened the other day?
I thought Thomas was your main man?
He couldn't even waste that pig.
If some pig killed my
cousin, he'd be dead already.
Don't you worry about Taylor.
I'll take care of him on my own time.
There's a phone call
for you in the office.
Yeah, Garrett, I
need a late model Mercedes.
Something really
nice, like a 500 SEO.
It's gotta have air conditioning.
Yeah, air conditioning.
Right.
Yeah, Garrett, look...
Don't worry about.
I'll take care of it.
OK, I haven't heard from Tulson.
Where the hell is he?
I'm getting worried...
Man, I don't know.
He's been acting
really peculiar lately.
Yeah, I think it has something
to do with his mother,
or something.
Maybe he's down in Florida?
Florida?
What the hell's he doing in Florida?
Look, Garrett, you just get that car.
All right, I'll take care of it.
Look, don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
Have Tulson call me tomorrow.
All right.
All right, the same time...
Now, you'd better start taking
care of business, Garrett.
All right, be well.
You want some?
No.
Did you hear what I said?
I was short by half last month.
I've got a price.
I take all the risks.
Look, we had a nice
arrangement for a time, OK?
We don't need you anymore.
So you're off the payroll.
What are you talking about?
You heard what I said.
We're not going to pay you anymore.
Why are you doing this to me?
I got my orders.
Shanks' orders?
Come on.
You mean to tell me
he never mentioned
anything like this to you?
I've saved his ass a dozen times.
Without me, he's finished.
Look, settle down, all right?
I'm going to let you
in on something...
There's going to be a
change in the organization.
Now, if something should
happen to Shanks...
I'd be willing to put
you back on the payroll.
You want some?
All right.
Did I not do you right?
Isn't that nice?
Top...
Hey, man, this thing
got air conditioning?
Wraps said it would.
I just serviced it myself.
I mean, this thing is
colder than the North Pole.
Yeah, but does it have a stereo?
I brought my tapes.
Top of the line, bro.
I'm telling you, you're going
to get some get down bass.
What a rush you'll get with that.
Yeah, but does it have power?
Does it have power?
This is a luxury car, my friend.
It's nothing but power.
Now look, we're going to have
a better one for you guys
next month, all right?
Here you go.
Enjoy, and drive safely.
OK.
All right.
Have a good trip.
Go with God.
Sayonara, Jack.
Hey man, what's going to?
You set my homeboys up.
Three of my best.
They didn't get more than
a mile from your shop, man.
They got their car, right?
They're dead.
And now you're dead.
Hey, Wrap... hey,
what's going on, man?
Pres?
Pres, back these guys off.
Shanks... cut me off?
Well, we'll see who needs who.
Pres!
You can't do this to me, Pres!
Get your ass over here!
No!
Hey!
I want him!
If you want him that
bad, you can have him.
I should kill you
myself, you son of a bitch.
Well, why don't you?
Because you've got something I need.
And I didn't kill your cousin.
It was his partner.
He set me up.
He set me up, too.
Who is it?
Garrett.
It's James Garrett.
I heard the angels call, but I
don't want to take the fall.
I would wait a thousand
years, my friend.
I'll be with you tonight.
I'll be your guiding light.
You know I've always wanted you.
Yeah.
So give me one more night.
To calm my appetite.
I've been waiting
here too long for you.
Yeah.
Just give me one more day.
And don't turn me away.
I'm the one for you,
and you know it's true.
Hear the thunder,
and does it make you
wonder how you were my girl?
Never turn me down.
You always came with me.
It was no fantasy.
I'll be waiting just for you.
Don't lie to me, I
know you want me, too.
Asking me, one more night.
To calm my appetite.
Well, I've been waiting
here too long for you.
Yeah.
Just give me one more day.
And don't turn me away.
I'm the one for you,
and you know it's true.
Give me one more night.
One more night.
Just give me one more night with you.
So give me one more night with you.
Don't even breathe.
Now, you do exactly what I tell you.
Start the car.
Start it.
Put your hands up on the wheel,
and drive out nice and slow.
Now I remember where I know you from.
It was the restaurant, right?
Wasn't it?
Garrett, you son of a bitch.
It's all over for you.
Really?
Did Johnny have to die, too?
That was my partner that you set up.
Your partner?
Now I understand.
Why'd you do it?
I needed time to get rid of Shanks.
And your partner happened
to have been there.
That's all.
You mean to tell me
this whole damn thing
was just to get rid of Shanks?
Well, Shanks was gonna
groom that idiot Johnny
to take over the operation.
Now, let me ask you something...
Are you here by yourself, or are we
gonna to have a million
copies down our ass?
Yeah.
And they're probably
outside right now.
I don't believe you.
Hey, Taylor?
Got some mail for ya.
Move it up.
Right here.
Taylor.
Good luck.
Help!
Help me, please!
Please, help me!
Please!
Please help!
Please, I can't take it!
No!
Get it off!
Help!
Help me!
Get it off!
Gotta be quiet.
Don't want to wake up mommy, now.
Goodnight.
Ron?
Sweetheart.
You go to sleep now.
Daddy's home.
Everything's gonna be OK, all right?
Go to sleep.
I broke out.
They killed Mac.
I gotta get even.
If I don't do it, no one else will.
They won't listen to me.
It's the only chance
I've got to clear myself.
But they'll be looking for you.
They'll kill you if they find you.
I love you.
Please... please don't do this.
Let's do this the right way.
There is no right way.
Find Garcia, tell him to
get everybody over here.
We gotta get out of here
sooner than I thought.
You come with me.
- Right.
We're going to have some company.
We don't have much time.
Leave that alone.
I'll go to the door, and
check the office window.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Be gentle.
Gentle with that, my man.
Come on.
Come on, easy.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Come on.
Go upstairs.
Drag that along the upstairs door.
You want it?
You've got it!
OK, asshole.
It's time to wake up.
Who's the asshole now?
You killed my partner.
I underestimated you.
You set me up.
You'll never know that
for sure, because you're
not gonna leave here alive.
I don't expect to
get out of here alive.
That's not why I came.
I came for you.
Drop the gun!
Drop it!
Shit.
Ron?
You in a hurry, man?
How about a lift to the hospital?
Hey, man.
Where the hell have you been?
I thought you were dead.
Hey, man, you know me.
I'm too tough to die.
I ain't hearing too well, though.
That's nasty, ain't it?
Look, man, it was 10...
Well, it was two guys, right?
I took 'em on, you know?
And I was fighting them, but
Garrett caught me from behind...
Mac, Mac, Mac...
He had me chained to a chair, man.
He had a knife.
It was a... it was a machete.
And he was cutting
like this, and he...
I moved, and he cut my ear off.
And... I kept
fighting 'em, though.
And... is that your wife, man?
She looks pretty good.