The train woke me up again.
I can't sleep.
Go back to bed, baby.
I'll be back.
Do you want to go
somewhere else for a few days?
Let the kid get a good night of sleep.
You pay me for sex.
My regular life is not for sale.
How much for two nights?
He's not your kid.
I know.
How much?
Excuse me.
Hotel service.
Madam.
Yes.
Yes, I'll call maintenance right away.
Thank you so much.
A woman and her son
are locked inside.
These doors have high security deadlocks
for our VIP guests.
We can't release it from the outside.
I have to drill it.
Okay, but try to keep it down.
Speak!
No fucking way!
Yes, you said that two days ago.
When the fuck is he coming?
What is that fucking sound?
Shit!
What the hell is this?
You know we are in here!
We are so sorry, sir.
What?
We're just...
-Sir!
-Hey, dumbass!
Sit down.
Be quiet.
I need some answers.
-Nod if you understand.
I was sent to kill you.
But it looks
like I'm the target here, right?
Yes.
Do you know who ordered this?
I don't know anything.
I need to make sure
you're telling me the truth.
I'm not lying!
I swear!
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Let's go.
Come on, let's go. Don't look.
Somebody call the police!
You make all this money
from killing people?
We could have been killed up there.
One day...
even you will get killed.
Don't come near me again.