♪ Mon, every time
me go to them clubs, mon ♪
♪ Me go to Bentley's,
me go to Payday ♪
♪ Me go to Silver Shadow,
me go all around, mon ♪
♪ Me see the girls with
the big boom-boom, mon ♪
♪ Me look at them
and me only want to do
one thing, mon ♪
♪ Me just want to bang her ♪
♪ That's all me want to do,
I just want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her,
I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ Knock boots ♪
- ♪ I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ Follow me now ♪
♪ I want to bang her,
I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ Knock boots ♪
- ♪ I want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her ♪
♪ She a dumb girl
and she got a big bang ♪
♪ All me want to do
is just bang, bang, bang ♪
♪ Me standing all alone
and no one is near ♪
♪ Me want to jump up
and put it in her ear ♪
♪ The girl, she wide
with her big bum flauntin' ♪
♪ She lookin' at me,
she know that me want ♪
♪ She tried to run away,
want her nieces and aunties ♪
♪ It much too late,
me already got the panties ♪
♪ So come back, come back,
and take the medicine ♪
♪ Me got the long buddy,
come on and let us in ♪
♪ Jump on mattress,
knock the booties, baby ♪
♪ Me place you on pillow
so you won't bang your head ♪
♪ Me kiss, me lick,
me taste, me lust ♪
♪ Me get real horny
and thrust, thrust, thrust ♪
♪ It lasts a long time,
I'm tired, thank you ♪
♪ I'm all dry now 'cause
I just want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her,
I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ Knock boots ♪
- ♪ I want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her,
I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ Knock boots ♪
- ♪ I want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her ♪
♪ Bang, bang, bang, bang ♪
♪ Bang, bang, bang, bang... ♪
( horn honks )
Hey. Come here.
How you doing?
Fine. You a cop?
No.
Why, are you?
You want a date?
How much?
How much you got to spend?
It depends on what you do.
( scoffs )
I have sex.
I give head,
half and half.
And I do domination.
Uh, is that all?
( scoffs )
What do you mean
"is that all"?
What the hell you want,
a hand job?
I wanna fuck you
up the ass.
You can stick it
up your own, asshole.
( laughs )
I would if I could, bitch.
- Bastard!
- ( horn honks )
Fucking jerkoff!
- Jesus, you hear
the mouth on that guy?
- ( horn honks )
Could just imagine
what it would be like
if he had me alone.
- ( horn honks )
- I mean, if he can't
treat me like a lady
out here on the street,
he sure ain't gonna
treat me like one
- when he gets
my pants down, now, is he?
- ( man retching )
( gags )
Oh, God.
- Ugh.
- What?
What are you looking at?
Why don't you find
a toilet, huh?
- Why don't you find a bed?
- I'm trying to,
but you ain't
exactly attracting business,
you know what I mean?
- Want a date?
( retches )
- Ugh.
I wasn't
gonna kiss you.
- ( horn honks )
- Ugh. Jesus Christ.
- I know the rule.
- This place is a fucking dive!
I wish I hadn't come here.
Spare some change
for Ras?
No!
Don't vex me,
sister.
Me got something
for you.
- What?
- Come, come. Me show.
( horn honks )
- Come. Look.
- What are you doing?
- What's the matter with you?
- ( glass shatters )
- ( gasps )
- For just one dollar, sister,
I'm walking on
real broken glass.
No, don't!
Don't do it!
- You breaking me concentration.
- Here. Take it, take it!
I don't care.
Just have it.
Ah!
There's a guy on
the other side of the street.
He's probably into blood.
Jesus.
If there's two things
I don't need
is a guy puking
on one side of the street
and bleeding on the other.
- Can you believe
what he was gonna do for a--
- ( horn honks )
You know,
this isn't my territory.
I'm sorta on the run.
- I left the fucker yesterday.
- ( horns honking )
I work downtown.
I've got my regulars there.
There's at the
Just the Chicken takeout.
Yeah, us working gals call it
the "cluck and fuck."
There, the cars,
they line up for me, man.
- ( horn honking )
- I'll go back there
as soon as it cools down.
Chicken's not bad
there either.
Well, it's a little on
the greasy side, I guess,
but if you're hungry.
( scoffs )
Let's face it.
Nobody's there
for the chicken.
( horn honking )
( tires screech )
Come on, baby.
Come on.
Come on to mama.
That's it.
Got another sucker.
( window hums )
Hi, darling.
You a cop?
Man:
Do I look like a cop?
No. You want a date?
Right now,
I'm just looking.
- How much for more?
- 50 for starters.
- What's that include?
- Today we're offering straight,
head, or the combo.
Half and half.
- Anything extra?
- Is extra.
Right.
- How's the head tonight?
- House specialty.
I'll try it for 40.
45.
Including tip.
Get in.
( laughs )
You're pretty.
What's your name?
- ( music playing )
- Liz.
Elizabeth.
No, just Liz.
So, Just Liz,
you have a place?
No. We can
go to yours.
Get a room, an alley.
Whatever you want.
Well, the old lady's
not home, is she, Dad?
Hey, forget it.
I don't do incest.
- I'm not his father.
- Relax. He just looks old.
- Fuck you, man.
- But he's got a young cock.
- Real small.
Like a French fry.
- He's bullshitting you.
I got a cock the size
of a Pershing missile.
- Just let me out, please?
- And he comes just as fast,
so don't worry.
How would you know?
- I heard.
- From who?
Who do you think?
That last whore
we picked up back there?
- I'll kill her.
- Hey, I said just let me out,
please!
I'm gonna find
that little scumbag.
Hey, you're
scaring her, man.
I'm not scared.
It's just that
I don't do double.
- Oh, forget this one.
- Not for any price.
What, you don't
do white doubles?
- Only single niggers?
- Come on, man.
- Let her out. You're
wasting our fucking time.
- Yeah.
Fuck, no.
We're just starting
to have fun, aren't we?
- I'll take the head now!
- ( screaming )
Hey. Hey, maybe
you know her.
A little girl.
A Puerto Rican.
Come on, suck it!
I said suck it!
- About 5'2". Blue eye shadow.
- Man, I'm trying to
get off here.
I'm not stopping you.
I just want to talk to her.
I don't want her talng
while she's giving me head.
( screams )
Jesus.
- ( spits )
- She's not giving you
diddly, man.
We're just--
forget it, okay?!
- ( laughs )
- Don't flatter yourself.
I wouldn't waste
my come on you.
Tricks. They're so
predicable, you know?
You get in the car
and you're his.
( horn honks )
And never get in a van.
I made that mistake once.
( man whistles )
Just once.
It happened downtown
a couple of years ago.
It was before I had a pimp
to take care of me.
I guess my mind just wasn't
on my job that night.
Man:
Excuse me, miss.
You're a prostitute,
aren't you?
No. I'm a wet dream
on legs.
How-- how much
do you cost?
What are you looking for?
I don't know.
Something around $20.
20 bucks won't buy
a porno tape.
Double it
and I'll give you head.
I give great head.
All right. All right.
Get in.
So you got a place
or you want it here?
- ( screaming )
- Yeah!
Come on, man!
Give her a good fucking for me!
Fuck her up the ass! Yeah!
Come on, man!
Do it for me, man!
Stick it down her
fucking throat, man! Whoo!
Liz:
There must have been
five of 'em.
They started on me right away.
They were like animals.
Just grunting and laughing.
Grunting and cussing.
- Yeah, come on, man!
- ( screaming continues )
Liz:
Seem to go on forever.
I don't know how long.
When they had enough,
they-- they just got rid of me.
- Man: Later, bitch!
- ( door shuts )
( whimpering )
My God.
Don't be afraid.
Liz:
Yeah, he offered me a ride
to the nearest hospital.
I really should've gone,
but the hospital
would've called the cops
and I couldn't deal
with the cops.
So I told him I had a fight
with my boyfriend
and maybe he could
just take me home.
Then he told me
he was a schoolteacher.
Great, with my luck,
he'll molest me.
He gave me his handkerchief
to wipe away the blood.
The only thing he wanted
was to know
if I needed anything.
I hated asking,
but I needed some money.
He gave me 20 bucks,
his name, and his address.
I guess he thought
he'd never see it again,
but I sent it back
with a new handkerchief
and I wrote him
this little thank-you note.
"Just a line to let you know
that I'm okay."
But he never wrote back.
One look at my spelling
would scare anybody off.
Especially a schoolteacher,
you know?
( air rhythmically rushing )
Looks a little flat.
Need a hand pumping it up?
You are doing it
without a rubber thing?
I pay for it
without a rubber thing.
You prefer what
without a rubber thing?
- Everything.
- What are you, man,
like suicidal?
Yes. I am
liking that, too.
Well, I'm not into
suicides and I always use
a rubber thing.
- I pay extra.
- You couldn't afford extra.
( siren blaring )
He wants it,
but he doesn't want
to use a rubber.
Get a lot of men like that.
I mean, they'll pay extra.
Sometimes even double.
I mean,
that is really stupid.
What if they took
something home to their wives?
Some of 'em never give up,
do they?
Take Charlie for instance.
Man was as good as gold.
Charlie was a regular,
but he didn't want sex.
Well, not straight sex
anyway.
All I had to do
was hit him with his cane
and he'd come.
First time, I got a little
carried away.
Bam. Oops.
Then I found out
just how hard he liked it.
It's funny.
The first time I saw him
all stretched out on the bed
with his skinny
little chicken legs
and his wrinkled little butt,
I mean, I practically
peed my pants.
Just six swats.
That was all he needed.
Easy money.
I must have
a talent for it.
I should open up
a torture chamber.
I make him beg for mercy.
There was this
one day, right,
his grandchildren
were there.
He told them I was from
the welfare department.
That he had to show me
around the house.
We left the kids watching TV
and we went upstairs.
We couldn't do it
in the bedroom 'cause
the lock was broke.
So we did it
in the bathroom,
but I couldn't get
a good swing.
It was just too narrow.
- ( glass shatters )
- ( Liz laughs )
I broke a fucking
light fixture.
He was so sweet.
He always gave me something.
I mean, you know,
besides the money.
Usually something
from the garden.
I know it's stupid to get
involved with tricks,
but he's, well,
he's a client.
And sometimes,
you've gotta break the rules.
Last year,
Charlie had a stroke.
Give me your hands,
Donatello.
♪ Your love has got
a hold on me ♪
♪ Your love's
got a hold on me ♪
♪ Your love has got
a hold on me... ♪
Okay, so he's in
a rest home now.
Don't mean
he has to rest.
Charlie's still
my client.
I always bring him
an avocado.
He thinks it's from
his garden.
Hey, what he don't know
won't hurt him.
But I think
he probably knows.
♪ Your love has got
a hold on me ♪
♪ Your love's got
- ♪ Your love has
got a hold on me ♪
- ( cane whipping )
♪ Your love has got
a hold on ♪
a hold on me... ♪
- ( screams )
- Sorry.
- Mosquito.
- What do you want now,
a dollar for slapping me?
No, no problem.
- No problem, sister.
- Thanks, mon,
but next time,
I think I'll just
let him suck my blood.
But it was free.
( laughs )
- Free.
- Shit.
( horn honks )
Whoo!
Bad move.
Even tricks need a little bit
of mystery, AIDS carrier.
She's a fucking strawberry.
Won't accept cash,
only crack.
And you see,
prostitutes like that,
they have no respect
for themselves.
I mean, I would never pull out
one of my breasts in public.
I would never go out
with a bodysuit on.
I mean, just a bodysuit.
And I would never
open my legs on the street.
I mean, I would never do
none of that shit.
And I don't
wear shorts, either.
Well, I wear shorts,
but I don't wear them
up the crack of my ass,
you know?
And I only wear 'em
during the day.
I mean,
when I was younger,
I used to do shit like that,
I guess. I don't know.
Seems the older I get,
the more mature I get, I guess.
Goddamn
motherfucking shit.
- ( tires screech )
- ( horn honks )
( tires screech )
( music playing )
Give me a dry martini,
please.
Very dry with a cherry.
Not an olive.
( panting )
He doesn't really think
I'm gonna leave him.
Hey, I know what he thinks.
He thinks I'm still
gonna work.
Like I said,
I left my place yesterday,
I went and got this
little motel room.
And see,
what he thinks is
is that I've been
stacking my money, right?
And in a couple of days,
I'm gonna have this
big bankroll for him.
( scoffs )
That's what he thinks,
but I'm not.
No. Not this time.
I've been spending my money.
Oh.
Look at my nails.
I used to have
beautiful nails.
Now I can't leave them alone.
I'm like a dog with a bone.
See, pimps, you know,
they think that they got
this hold on you, you know?
Like you'll stick to them
like fucking crazy glue.
And it is kinda crazy,
you know?
In some sort of sick,
twisted way, they...
they make you believe
that you love 'em.
I knew Blake about a year
and he never asked me out
or even laid a hand on me.
It wasn't that
I wanted him to.
It was that I wondered
why he hadn't.
So naturally,
when he sent me a classy dress
and showed up
at my place in a tux
with pine freshener
on his breath,
I wondered
what the fuck was up.
Um, hey.
Do you think we could sit
at a different table?
I mean, I got this
problem with kitchens.
I used to work at this
greasy spoon, you know,
and it was just
crawling with roaches.
Ahem. Well,
it's your night.
I understand, ma'am.
Please, follow me.
Oh, but I didn't mean
your kitchen was crawling
with roaches, too.
It's just that I get this,
what do you call it?
A phobia about it.
Yeah, that's it.
Liz:
I felt kinda nervous.
You know, like you do
when you're out with
your boss or something.
I didn't think
I could be promoted
and I wondered if a whore
could be fired.
But then he never
would've used breath freshener
and bought me
that classy new dress,
would he?
So now you gonna tell me
what the occasion is?
So what do you want to eat?
( sighs )
A steak.
I'm so hungry,
I could eat a horse.
10-1 it is one, huh?
Steak "tarter."
Yeah, this is a nice place,
but you'd think they'd know
how to spell steak, huh?
- S-T-E-K-E--
- This is a French restaurant.
Then how come there's no
French fries on the menu, huh?
They call 'em pommes frites.
Oh.
Well, I'll have
a helping of that
and a nice, juicy steak.
Steak tartare
is raw steak
minced with
raw onions, eggs,
and Worcestershire sauce.
Oh. Really?
Well, why don't you make
a suggestion, then, huh?
All right.
As a starter,
how 'bout gravlax marinade?
What's that?
It's raw salmon
and it's marinade--
Raw?
Is everything in
this restaurant raw?
I mean, can't they afford
a chef around here?
Hey, raw food
is really good for you.
Don't you know nothin'?
( speaks French )
He wants you
to choose.
( laughs )
What, you found
something?
What's so funny about
crab julienne?
You remember.
Your old whore Julienne.
She had crabs
like you wouldn't believe.
- You remember.
- Uh, yes, madam?
- I don't really know, sir.
- Hey, call him waiter.
You call me sir.
I'll order
for both of us.
Très bien, sir.
We'll have the calamar
a la chinoise.
And would sir
care for some wine?
Hey, can we get
some champagne?
I haven't had champagne
for a long time.
Give me a bottle
of "Low Da Vici."
Very cold.
I presume sir means
"Eau De Vichy."
Yeah, that's what I said.
So now you gonna tell me
what this is all about?
Madam
has a request?
I have an extensive
repertoire.
Uh, how 'bout "Don't It
Make My Brown Eyes Blue"?
I'm afraid
I'm not that familiar with
the contemporary classics.
- Of course not.
- How 'bout the march
from act three
of Wagner's
"Lohengrin"?
I think you mean
act two.
I was wondering when we
were gonna get together,
- but is this like
a proposal or something?
- "Something," my ass.
Don't say you didn't
remember our anniversary.
I've been looking
after you a year now.
A year this very day.
- C'est bon, sir?
- You may pour.
- To our anniversary.
- And the oldest profession.
- The what?
- Ahem.
Uh, prostitution
is commonly known
as the oldest profession.
It sure makes me feel old.
I'll drink to that.
This tastes
exactly like water.
It's sparkling mineral water.
It's good for the liver.
You oughta lay off the booze.
It's got a lot of calories.
- No, put it out.
- Hmm?
We're in a nonsmoking area.
Put it out.
Well, why don't we move
to a smoking area, then?
You wanna take care of yourself?
Smoking is bad for your health.
So is fucking
scabby tricks.
And what is this?
It's calamari and lychees.
What's it look like?
I don't know,
but I've seen one
before, I think.
What is calamar?
It's a kind of octopus,
you stupid moron.
It's fucking octopus.
Ha! I should've known.
They got testicles, don't they?
Though I thought they
had eight of 'em. Looks like
you've been shortchanged.
Looks like a dick.
( spits )
Tastes like a dick.
Look, all I want is just
an old-fashioned piece
of apple pie with loads
of ice cream on it!
- Yeah, well, forget it!
- What-- what you say?!
What, have you gone deaf?
I said forget it!
You're as fat
as a fucking pig!
( scoffs )
I'm-- I am?
Liz:
I guess he was right.
I smoke too much,
eat junk food, and drink
like a fish.
I mean, I gotta get
some satisfaction out of life
or it just ain't
worth living.
Whoring ain't exactly
the job of the future,
you know.
And working out,
doing 50 sit-ups
when I could have been sleeping
wasn't my idea of fun.
Well, it had its moments,
I guess.
♪ Tell me ♪
♪ Tell me all your secrets ♪
♪ Tell me. ♪
- ( buzzing )
- ( Liz groaning )
Our first year together
as pimp and whore
and Blake's idea
of an anniversary gift...
You're gonna see
a big change in yourself.
Psychologically.
Physically,
you're gonna be
a lot more body conscious.
Great. Does that mean
I'm gonna lose my stomach?
Tattoo artist:
You'll be a lot more
committed to self.
And to the one you love,
you'll have a special,
spiritual connection
because tattoos are forever.
So are diamonds,
but they're a lot less painful.
That's the most pricks
I've had in 30 minutes.
Liz:
For a while, he was right.
I felt kinda special.
Till one by one I found out
all of Blake's girls had one.
Hey, not always
on the same body part.
I wasn't special.
I was just a piece
of branded cattle.
One of the herd.
You see,
what pimps do
is they build you up
and then they break you down.
It's kinda like
being a hostage.
They just know how
to make you need 'em.
They don't love you.
Pimps don't love nobody.
Give me another martini,
please.
Air dry.
Getting as bad as Bill was.
Fuck it.
The minute
I laid eyes on him,
I thought
he was real cute.
It was back home
at the local dive
where they had
music and beer
and you could hang out
and shoot pool.
Like I did
with my friend Martha.
It was back in
the days when I was
living the straight life.
- I feel like I'm gonna die.
- Put your bet on him.
- Think I should?
- What's a buck?
Yeah, you're right.
But don't you think
it will look kinda weird,
me going over there
and putting money down
right in front of him?
No, he'll just think
you're some horny bar slut
- that wants to fuck him.
- Stop.
What if I want
to marry him?
Then I think
I better bet on him.
All:
10, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one!
( cheering )
♪ A girl's gotta do
what a girl's gotta do... ♪
Oh, fuck it.
He wasn't my type anyway.
♪ A girl's gotta do
what a girl's gotta do ♪
♪ And this girl
is gonna go home... ♪
I didn't like men
much anyway.
Thanks for
believing in me.
This is for you.
- Congratulations.
- Oh, it was nothing.
- No, it was, really.
- You think so?
Yeah. Hey, you shouldn't put
your talents down, you know?
It's an inherited talent.
My old man's a big drinker.
- Really? So is mine.
- No kidding?
Yeah, well, that's what
my mom told me anyway.
You wanna dance
or something?
- Okay.
- All right.
Here, you can have
this prize.
Oh, gee, thanks.
Liz:
For a while, it was great.
We really loved each other.
The way when
you're a little girl
and imagine
how love would feel.
The way your mom always
told you love should be.
So I thought
getting married
was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
I guess it was
too good to last.
Well, that was one thing
my mom didn't tell me.
♪ I want to bang her,
I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ Knock boots ♪
- ♪ I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ I want to bang her... ♪
- Oh, shit!
Liz:
Well, I guess playing house
is sorta fun when you're
seven years old.
But when you're seven months
pregnant, well, forget it.
I mean, when he starts
getting home later and later,
drunker and drunker
'cause of all the overtime
he's putting in,
when you know
he's been fired and he's
been cheating on you.
Well, that'd be tough
on any relationship.
Still, I couldn't stop
loving the bastard.
So I kept on trying
to please him.
Getting all dolled up
for dinner and setting
the table pretty
and making his favorite salad.
All I really wanted
was a good night's sleep.
And you never knew
how he was gonna react.
It was like living on the edge
of a fucking volcano.
( crying )
( baby crying )
Shut up.
Chrissy.
Shh. Come on, baby.
We're gonna go see Grandma.
Let's get out of this dump.
Woman on TV:
I want my daughter.
I'm not an alcoholic.
Give me Karen.
Man on TV:
Take it off, then.
Woman: Give me
my daughter, please.
Man: Yeah, this is
what you want.
- No.
- This is what it's about,
huh, Bambi?
I want my daughter.
Liz:
Finally, I get it
through my head.
Okay, I married a loser.
No great loss.
A lot of people do it.
So I leave Bill and I
move in with my mom.
Then I get this dream job
at a sleazy diner.
One night it was late,
I was tired, and the tips
were shit.
I just worked a double shift
when this guy walks in.
It was like he walked into
the wrong restaurant.
What's on
the menu tonight?
Chef Pierre is gone
and we're closing
in five minutes.
I can offer you a piece
of cantaloupe, though.
- How's your cantaloupe?
- Ripe.
Is that what you wanted?
- How 'bout a drink instead?
- Sorry, we don't serve--
What do you say I take you
somewhere that does?
What, me?
You mean...
I'm not much
of a drinker.
In fact, I'm not
a big drinker at all.
Sorry.
Keep the change.
- Thanks.
- I'm a big tipper.
I have to go home.
I got a--
You have a what?
A cat. I have a cat
I got to feed, but...
But I think I might have
already fed him.
( laughs )
Liz:
I would have gone out
with him anyway.
It was more money than I made
in a whole week.
I thought, "Who cares?
What do I have to lose?"
I'll just lock up.
It'll only be a minute.
Liz:
Doing it for money--
it's like losing
your virginity.
The next time,
it's a whole lot easier.
♪ I wanna be your fantasy ♪
♪ Can I be your fantasy? ♪
♪ Your little fantasy ♪
♪ I wanna be your fantasy ♪
♪ Can I be your fantasy? ♪
Jerking off these jerks
under a table in the only
classy bar in town
was no fucking joyride,
trust me.
But it sure beat the hell out
of waiting tables.
♪ I wanna be your fantasy ♪
♪ Let me be your fantasy ♪
♪ Let me be your fantasy. ♪
But at least I could
pay my mom for babysitting.
And I knew my little boy
was safe with her.
It was a real nice
arrangement.
Till she went
and died on me.
Sometimes I wish I was dead.
But I'm not brave enough
to do it myself.
But I'm not afraid of dying.
I mean,
even if there's nothing.
No heaven, I mean.
Even if heaven ain't
like they say it is.
All saints and angels.
I mean,
even if it's just
peace and quiet.
I could sure use
some of that.
Hell couldn't be any worse
than this now, could it?
The big tease.
They love it and they think
you love it, too.
They wanna hear
all about it.
( lowered )
"Talk to me," they'd say.
I know what they mean now,
but at first I didn't.
"What do you want me
to talk about," I'd say.
( lowered )
"What do you like doing?"
I don't know.
I like watching TV.
( lowered )
"No, not that.
What am I doing to you?"
"What you doing to me?"
( lowered )
"Yeah. Tell me, tell me.
What am I doing to you?"
I was still young.
I didn't know what
they wanted me to say.
Now when they ask,
I know what they want.
As soon as they
get their dick out
and ask me if I like it.
I whisper to them,
"Oh, honey,
it's a beautiful cock.
It's so big and hard."
( lowered )
"What do you want me
to do with it," they'd say.
I'd love to
really tell 'em.
But instead, I say,
"Oh, my pussy's
really hungry
for your big,
hard cock.
Come on, give it to me.
Give it to me."
Yeah.
But then there
are those who want to do
the talking themselves.
I mean, talk dirty.
Sometimes it feels
like they just--
they just want
to rip you open.
Hey, be a little
gentle, huh?
Shut your fucking trap.
Liz:
So I just shut up
and let 'em do their thing.
I close my eyes.
I don't want to see
the hate in their faces.
They must have
terrible lives.
The men, I mean.
Something must have happened
to 'em to make 'em like that.
They weren't born that way,
were they?
Maybe they're
henpecked at home.
Or bossed around at work
so they feel humiliated.
They want to humiliate
somebody back.
Makes 'em feel better.
More important.
It's nothing personal.
I know that.
They don't even want sex,
you know.
It's more like...
like revenge.
Yeah.
That's it.
They only want revenge.
( water running )
( man moaning )
I feel sorry
for their wives.
Most of the men
who come in here
must be married.
And they come here
because we'll do
the things
their wives
and girlfriends
won't do.
Head. That's what
most of 'em ask for.
I mean,
I don't see why
a woman would have
a problem
with sticking
her man's cock
in her mouth?
I mean,
I guarantee you
if he ain't sticking it
in her mouth,
he'll be sticking it
in somebody else's.
Could be hers,
could be mine.
We're substitutes.
I bet you
he's got his eyes shut
thinking of his wife
right now.
( moaning continues )
Me?
I don't wanna see another dick
as long as I live.
Ugh.
( sighs )
I've lost count
of how many I've had.
Must be miles.
( moaning continues )
I used to love sex.
I used to love
everything about it.
Now when I go to bed,
all I want to do
is go to sleep.
And I bet you
I've had more sex
in places like this
than I've ever had
in a bed.
I should write
a book about it--
"The Toilets
I Have Known."
I met my best friend
in one.
Well, she was.
I was working downtown.
Hanging around
looking for tricks
when this girl comes along
acting like she's stoned
or drunk or something.
And then I see the blood
and I just look at her
and I say,
"What the fuck?"
And she just says, "Blake."
And I see the bastard
had cut her
right across the stomach.
And then I thought,
"If I don't do something fast,
she's gonna bleed to death."
So I go rushing her
into the theater
and I yell to
the chick in the box,
"Get an ambulance."
I guess she must have
just got the manager
'cause after a while,
this bitch comes busting in
and starts laying into us.
Calling us dirty,
filthy sluts.
And I'm trying to stop
the blood, but it just won't
fucking stop.
And the poor girl,
she's starting to go
into shock
and the manager's
yelling at us
about AIDS and trying
to kick us out.
Without getting too close,
of course.
But the blood
just kept coming.
And then in comes Katie.
She sorta took control
right away, you know.
I mean, even got
the manager to help out.
She told her to imagine
it was her daughter.
If it wasn't for Katie,
I don't think the girl
would've pulled through.
Katie wanted to know why
she didn't go to the cops.
I laughed.
I told her Blake pays the cops
to look the other way.
Anyway, he got her
a few weeks later,
but this time, the knife
went straight through.
That was a terrible week.
I don't know what the hell
I would've done without Katie.
She looked after me
like a sister would.
If I would've had one.
Sometimes I wonder why
my parents ever had me.
They must've been drunk.
I guess I was why
Dad left home.
Katie was the only person
I ever knew
that never wanted.
I wanted.
I needed.
There were nights I needed
so badly just to be held.
For my birthday,
Katie bought me a book.
Nobody ever gave me
a book before.
It's called
"Animal Farm"
and I'm telling you,
it's just like life.
It's about animals,
but it's not for kids.
It's the best book
I ever read.
Well, it's the only book
And on the inside cover
she wrote,
"To Liz
with love and all
beautiful things.
K."
Sometimes I used to open it
just to read that.
I just loved
being with her.
She even turned me on
to serious music
for a while.
( music playing )
She was so smart.
She could make almost anything
sound interesting.
Katie worked as a bartender.
She made good money,
but what a waste.
I mean, she went
to junior college.
I kept telling her
she should get a good job
like a teacher or something.
She'd make a great teacher.
God, I wish
I had her brains.
And I told her that.
She said there's
nothing wrong with my brain,
only my education.
My education?
That can't be right
'cause I hardly
finished school.
I mean, I haven't been
in school for so long
that I can't even
remember anything.
( man moaning )
That was the end
of Katie and me.
( woman smacking lips )
Sharp as a razor.
And I'd use it, too.
Once I'd use it on myself.
But now I'd fight back.
That's Katie.
( man moaning louder )
Huh. Dignity.
( bicycle horn honks )
Oh, it's you.
You suddenly takin'
a liking to rubbers?
I thought you might have
taken a disliking to them.
- Not on your life.
- But I'm exceedingly clean.
I'm sure you are.
But look, it's no use
sitting there
because I'm not
gonna change my mind.
I don't care
how much you pay me.
And I'm not gonna do
any business with you
sitting here either,
so why don't you
just fuck off?
And take your
little horn with you.
( horn honks )
Why do you insist
upon a rubber?
Crabs, clap, syphilis,
herpes, AIDS, chlamydia.
Is that enough for you
or do you want more?
I mean, with all that,
what could you possibly have
against a rubber, huh?
It's not that I have
anything against them.
It's just that they are
usually too small for me.
You gotta be kidding.
No. I am not.
I have a very stout
member.
( laughs )
Well, that's the best news
I've heard all day.
I'm thrilled for you.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
But the pleasure is yours.
Oh, Jesus.
You guys still believe
that shit, don't you?
"In a recent
nationwide survey,
eight out of 10 prostitutes
who expressed preference
said that their vagina
preferred small 'members.'"
It sounds like it turns you on,
but it does nothing for me.
Comprende?
It's the cops.
I suggest you get
the hell outta here.
You go down the street
and then you hang a left.
You go onto the freeway
there and it's right there
on your right.
You can't miss it.
The gas station is
open all night.
Uh-huh. Thank you.
You are most kind.
You're welcome.
Come here,
sweetheart.
Now then, you have
two choices, honey.
You can haul ass
yourself
or we haul you off
and take you in.
Yes, sir.
Sorry, sir.
Really, sir.
were you gonna have me
jog alongside of you
or were you gonna
cuff me to your spoke?
( laughs )
Shit.
Cops.
Now there's a confused
bunch for ya.
They don't know
what they want,
so they're always
giving you a choice.
Like this last time.
This vice cop,
he says to me,
"Give me head or
you're going to jail."
So I give him head.
And then the fucker busts me
for jaywalking.
I didn't use the crosswalk
on the way to his dick.
Well, excuse me, Officer,
but if your dick had been
long enough,
I wouldn't have had to
cross the fucking street.
I wish the beach boys
had busted me.
I could use
a night in jail.
Just for the rest,
you know?
Hey.
( gasps )
Missed you, baby.
So how much
did we do tonight?
It's-- it's been slow, man.
Oh, yeah?
So what have you done?
Hey, I told you.
It's been slow.
So you've probably done,
what, four 30s.
You might have caught
a 50 or two? What is that?
- Four 30s, we're talking 120.
- Just forget about it.
Wait a minute.
What did I say?
You said four 30s,
but--
Four 30s and two 50s.
Well, it's been slow, right?
Yeah.
So let's say
you only did
one 50.
You might have gotten bored
and did a quick 20.
Hey, wait a minute.
What the fuck am I thinking?
I forgot about yesterday.
( gasps )
You took off yesterday.
So, uh, what have you
been doing since yesterday?
What are you doing
around here?
Welfare work?
You've been with that
bookworm again, hmm?
- That dyke Katie.
- No. No, no. I--
I told you once before,
reading is bad for your eyes.
Hey, man, I swear.
I haven't seen Katie.
I got this trick
and he took me down here
to this motel
- and it was an all-nighter.
- Yeah.
I just slept in.
I couldn't help it, man.
- You should've
made plenty, right?
- He robbed me!
- Bullshit!
- I told you, it's been slow.
- Man: Me spare some change?
- Don't give me that slow shit.
- You stink of booze.
- I'm telling you the truth.
- How 'bout a dollar, then, mon?
- Get the fuck outta here!
Where is it?
Where's the rest of it?!
Here, mon. Take the dollar!
Leave the woman alone!
- Buzz off!
- Hey!
Liz:
Take your foot off of him!
You're hurting him!
- Listen to the woman.
- Leave him alone!
( gasps )
I don't got any more.
I swear on my mother.
Well, your mother's dead.
So you better swear on
somebody else,
but dust don't count
in my book.
I'm gonna be back
in an hour.
You better have done
four by then.
I don't care what
you have to do to catch cock.
Lie in the street
with your fucking legs
in the air.
Just do it.
Was that third finger left hand
or third finger right?
Take your pick!
I got it.
Who the fuck
does she think she is?
You only need one
like that.
One bad apple
and all the others rot.
And if she thinks
that she can dump me
like I was one of her
fucking tricks, well,
she's got
a big surprise coming.
Protection.
He is my protection.
I mean, we can't even
carry a knife anymore.
You get caught,
they bust you
on a concealed
weapons charge.
You work on your back,
you gotta have a middleman.
Or you could end up
on your back in the morgue.
I got somebody that will
fix her up.
And he'll fix her for good.
They'll never recognize her.
Even if they do,
who cares?
She's a whore.
Hey, it was a trick,
wasn't it?
I mean, there are a lot
of freaky tricks around,
you know?
Sometimes tricks,
they--
they freak out.
What can you do?
There's this one,
right,
he was young,
but he was small.
He was vicious and starts
sticking it in me right away.
All of a sudden,
he starts kissing me.
Man, I never kiss nobody.
You never do.
I mean,
I'll suck their cock,
they can lick me,
they can fuck me,
but no kissing.
And no fingers neither.
I mean, you should
see their nails.
I mean, who knows where
their fingers have been?
No sucking
my breasts neither.
So anyway, this guy,
he starts trying to kiss me.
So I said to him,
"Hey, man, I don't kiss."
He didn't seem to mind.
All of a sudden
he says to me,
( lowered )
"Is it nice?"
I said to him,
"Is what nice?"
( lowered )
He says, "This,"
and pushes it in
even harder.
Now I know he wanted me
to talk dirty, right?
I was still
pretty new to the game.
I didn't understand.
So I said,
"It's all right, I guess."
( lowered )
"All right? All right?"
he says. "Is that all?"
And then he pulls out.
So I asked him why
he pulled out.
And he says,
( lowered ) "Because
you're not enjoying it."
I said, "Hey,
I don't have to enjoy it.
You paid for it.
You enjoy it."
And he goes, ( lowered )
"But I can't enjoy it
if I know
you're only doing it
because I paid you."
Well, if you want passion,
that costs extra.
By then his time was up,
so I asked him if he
was finished.
( lowered )
"Finished?" he says.
"I haven't even started yet.
Kiss me."
So he yanks my head and he
starts trying to kiss me.
And I'm trying to
push him away and then
he starts shouting to me,
( lowered )
"You fucking cunts!
You're all the same!
You're dead, all of ya!
No feelings!"
And then he starts
trying to kiss me again.
Then he asks
for his money back.
I said, "Sorry.
No deposit, no return."
Then I tried to get up
and get out.
Suddenly, he grabs my bag
with one and my hair
with the other
and he starts banging my head
against the floor.
I mean, I thought my fucking
brain was gonna explode.
I'm telling you,
he must have slammed
my head about six times
before that damn door
finally opened.
You oughta be more careful
with who you date.
That's when I realized,
you can't work
without a pimp.
So I became
one of Blake's girls.
Well,
it seems to me
like this pimp
set you up, mon.
Yeah. I thought
of that, too.
And one day I put it
to him point-blank.
And point-blank
he denied it.
Practically knocked
my goddamn teeth
down my throat.
Me and my girls.
I look after 'em.
I'm out all hours
keeping an eye out on 'em
just to make sure
they're safe.
I drive around
just checking.
I know all the places
that they go with their dates.
Sometimes I follow 'em.
You see, we're like
business partners.
They fuck
and I manage.
Tell me something.
How much does
he make off you?
What's his
profit margin?
What's that got
to do with it?
Have some herb.
If I'm not paying
for their rent,
I'm paying for
their goddamn fines.
( sniffs )
I pay for their clothes,
their checkups.
I pay for their rubbers.
( sniffs )
Even at wholesale,
they're still expensive.
Or as I tell you,
they don't come cheap.
( sniffs )
So how much
you say he takes?
100%.
Mon, it's like
you're getting
screwed twice.
Hmm.
Look, it's just like
I was managing a factory.
This, it just happens
to be a pussy factory.
This is exactly why
I'm trying to get
away from him.
Even factories treat
their employees better.
At least
they get benefits.
Mm.
But it's still a factory
with employees
and somebody like me
running things.
I got what they call
"entrepreneurial flair."
I can see a need
and I fill a demand.
The man is a slave driver.
Holy shit.
Just look at that one.
Dumb kid.
( horn honks )
She supposed to be
selling sex.
It looks like she's waiting
for the goddamn bus.
Okay, so it's hot,
your shoes hurt,
and she had an abortion
last week.
Guess who picked up
the tab on that one.
Everybody starts off
by thinking they're gonna
make a lot of money
and get out of it
in a couple of years.
But it never happens.
You just stay doing it.
I've seen some pretty kids
with faces like dogs
after only six months.
You know,
they say you can tell a woman
that's been doing this.
That it shows in her face.
I mean, look at mine.
Does it show?
In my eyes?
That's where it starts,
they say.
In the eyes and then
in the mouth. All hard.
They're wrong.
Yeah.
They're full of shit.
You better believe
they're full of shit.
Yeah. They're full of shit.
You know why?
Because it
starts in here.
It's like a cancer
and then it just starts
eating away at you until
there's nothing left.
Just an empty shell.
They're oversexed
and they're born like that.
Nature's rejects
from the moment that they
came into this world.
All they have to offer
is their bodies,
so they might as well
get paid for it.
They're born
with a price tag.
If somebody gave 'em
a million bucks,
they'd be back on
the streets in a week.
They can't
help themselves.
There's nothing
you can do about it.
It's like being born
black or white.
It's just the way they are.
I must be some use
to somebody.
I mean, there must be
a reason for me.
Right?
You know, years ago,
when I first got started,
before I got things
straightened out around here,
I was always
getting busted
for pandering,
pimping.
Do you think
what I do is wrong?
I think what
a pimp does
is wrong.
I think it's the law
that's wrong.
Katie called him
a parasite.
Parasite.
I like that word.
Look, if it was illegal
to live off the earnings
of others,
then the stock exchange
would be shut down tomorrow.
And all the employment agencies
would be charged with pimping.
I'm like an employment
agency myself,
only I'm not legal.
And I don't want
to be illegal.
You know,
you should be legal.
Then there wouldn't be
a need for him.
You make it legal
and I'll open an office.
Until then,
this is my office.
Some of our regulars,
they phone me.
And they tell me what
they want and I deliver.
Maybe I'm nothing more
than takeout food.
Easy, quick,
and affordable.
I'm sort of
a dial-a-ride service.
And I'm real charitable, too.
I always make sure
I give a little back.
I even make
regular donations
to the policemen's
pension fund.
( laughs )
Do you think
for some men,
even a few,
that I'm a cure
for loneliness?
Maybe a short-term cure.
The more I think about it,
the more I'd really like
to change my life.
If only I could find
a decent man.
Or even a man
that just wanted a...
what you call it?
You know, they got a wife
and then they got a...
a mistress. Yeah, that's it.
I'd really love that.
Where in the hell
am I gonna find that?
( horn honks )
Hey, you wanna move in?
Can you afford
the down payment?
Who knows? Come here.
What sign are you?
- What sign am I?
- Quickly.
I'm a stop sign.
Ow! You're a Scorpio.
- You're a Scorpio, aren't you?
- Yeah, I'm a Scorpio.
- Hey, how'd you know?
- Shit. I need a Virgo.
Do you know where
I can find one?
- I'll be a Virgo for 40.
- No, no. I need a real one.
And my cards say
I can only pay 10.
- ( sighs )
- You have the most
beautiful eyes.
I'll catch you
in another lifetime.
Bye.
What a weirdo.
I wonder what he was into.
Eh, I don't mind
something different
once in a while,
but I don't do
nothing dirty.
You know?
I mean,
I don't take
golden showers
and I don't give
golden showers.
But...
well,
there was this one guy,
right,
he used to like watching me
take a dump, okay?
I mean, he used
a flashlight.
Trouble is,
he always seemed to show up
after I'd already had one.
I haven't seen him around
in a while.
Guess he found someone
more regular.
Yeah, but I got
this other trick,
he's an older guy,
you know.
Real soft-spoken.
I swear, he could be
a judge or doctor or something.
And we have a regular date
every Thursday at 3:00.
And he always pays me
with brand-new money.
Get the money first.
That's my motto.
But before I could get
my pants down,
he's shaking his head.
So I offer him
a tit job.
Strike two.
When I realized he didn't
want straight sex,
I thought,
"Hello, another nut."
And I let him know
I didn't do nothing dirty.
I don't do anything dirty.
Then he just nods
and points to my shoe.
For a minute, I thought
he was gonna fuck me with it.
I mean,
you wouldn't believe
some of the things
they've tried to stick up me.
Then he gives me
this piece of paper
and tells me not to read it
until he says so.
Finally, he gets
his dick out, right?
What do you
want me to do?
Read me the note.
About now, he's starting
to get a hard on.
Liz:
"You naughty boy, Johnny.
You dirty little boy.
Mommy's very, very
angry with you"?
( groaning )
Louder.
Liz:
And before you know it,
he's beating his meat
and licking my shoe.
"You naughty boy, Johnny.
You dirty little boy.
Mommy's very,
very angry with you.
You naughty boy, Johnny!
You dirty little boy!
Mommy's very,
very angry with you!
You naughty boy, Johnny!
You dirty little boy!
Mommy's very, very, very,
very angry with you"!
( groaning continues )
Keep it up.
( yawns )
"You naughty boy, Johnny.
You dirty little boy,
Johnny.
Mommy's very,
very angry with you."
( laughing )
Liz:
Different strokes
for different folks.
Who can figure it?
But that's how Johnny came.
Yeah, I know my lines now,
but he's always quick.
That's what you want, quick.
I mean, some of 'em
take forever.
The nervous ones,
they can be a real bitch.
Sometimes they never get
a hard-on at all.
They're too embarrassed
to ask for their money back.
Hey, they wouldn't
get it back anyway.
I mean, if you go
to a restaurant and you
order a meal
and you suddenly
lose your appetite,
it's not my fault, is it?
The best guys are the ones
in the lunch hour.
They're always in a rush.
Or the older guys.
They're good, too.
I mean, sometimes
I'm putting the rubber on
and then all of a sudden, oops.
It's all over.
"Oh, honey. I needed that,"
I'd say to them
and finish them off
with my hand
and pretend to be
real disappointed and stuff.
You know, so they
don't feel cheated.
( sighs )
But you know
who the worst ones are?
The young ones.
I mean, they're always
laying these head trips on you.
Like, ( whiny )
"Usually I don't have
to pay for it."
I mean,
I don't want to hear that.
I don't got time
for that shit.
And then they start
holding out on you
like they're doing you
some big favor or something.
Thanks,
but no, thanks.
I mean, for them,
I need a meter like a taxi.
No, I like the ones
that just want to hurry up,
- get it over with,
and go home.
- ( clapping )
Yeah, I'm going home.
( playing harmonica )
That's Chris.
Handsome, isn't he?
He's so smart.
He's six now.
Yeah, he's at
that age where--
well, you know,
he's grown up and...
well, if he
was living with me,
how would I explain it?
I mean,
I work at night,
so you could say
I got a night job.
But then when I go to jail
and I don't come home
during the day,
I mean,
how do I explain that?
Everybody says he's smart.
You should hear him read.
He knows all the animals.
I taught him that.
He loves animals.
He sent me this painting
of his cat.
"This is Mandy,"
he wrote on the back.
"She sleeps in
the washing machine."
He's with a nice couple.
They don't have
any kids of their own.
He was sort of adopted.
After my mom died...
the courts said
I was an unfit mother.
Yeah, that's when
I moved on.
Chris seems
happy enough, though.
I wish he was with me,
but I can see him
whenever I want to.
But I have to call first,
but...
uh, I don't go back there
too much.
It kinda upsets me.
Last time I went back there,
I didn't tell him I was coming.
I stood outside his school
and waited for
the class to end.
He was wearing the jeans
I'd sent him for his birthday.
They're probably still
a little too big for him,
but he'll grow into them.
His foster mother Rachel,
she was there waiting
to take him home.
I could hardly stand
to see him go,
but I don't think
I'll go back there again,
you know.
No, not for a while anyway.
I don't want Chris
growing up hating me.
I don't want him to be
ashamed of his mother.
I know he calls Rachel mom,
but he knows who
his real mother is.
What I wouldn't give
for a nice, cool shower.
No, Chris is better off
where he is.
For now, I know that.
He looks just like
his father.
We're still married.
Chances are we'd still
be together if he hadn't
cheated on me.
I never cheated on him.
Hey, what I do isn't exactly
making love, is it?
Hate would be closer
to the truth.
I mean,
it isn't even sex
because sex
has some feelings.
I mean, if you like somebody,
that's sex.
Well, I don't like
any of these shits.
No, there must be
a better word for what I do.
But I don't know
what it is.
It's mechanical.
No feelings.
No.
I mean, maybe if you really
psyched yourself up for it,
you could feel something.
Who wants to
go through all that?
I mean,
when I was younger,
I used to make believe
somebody out here
was loving me.
But then I got to the point
where I just hated tricks.
I hate 'em.
And they don't
like us, neither.
I mean, really like us.
Oh, they want us, all right.
I didn't say that.
But like us?
No. No way.
And you never know
who you're with.
A total stranger
or your own father.
You just don't know.
I mean, they're like
Jekyll and Hyde.
You gotta watch 'em 'cause
they're always up to something.
( bicycle horn honks )
20 bucks, sweetie.
20 bucks.
- Okay?
- Yeah, try her.
She'll probably do it
for a food stamp, asshole.
I'm ready.
You're cute.
( laughs )
Poor old whore.
That could be me someday.
Nah. I'd kill myself first.
( gasps )
( horn honks )
In your professional
opinion...
what do you think
my chances are?
I'd say your chances
are 50/50.
And for 50, I'm willing
to take the gamble.
Let's go.
( music playing )
♪ You are the love of loves ♪
♪ For which I yearn ♪
♪ You are the dream of dreams ♪
♪ My luck has turned ♪
♪ Your touch means
more to me ♪
♪ Than the rainbow
and all the breath of life ♪
♪ By which I depend ♪
♪ This is the
perfect blending ♪
♪ Yours is
the sweetest kiss ♪
♪ My lips have known ♪
♪ Yours is
the heart of hearts ♪
- ♪ For me alone... ♪
- ( groaning )
Oh, there we go.
( grunting, groaning )
Oh, I want your big,
hard cock inside.
Oh, yeah.
That's it.
There it is.
Oh, yeah, baby.
That feels good.
Oh, honey,
I'm so hot for you.
Oh, yeah.
Give it to me.
Mm.
Oh, yeah.
Honey, go, go.
Oh, I really want it bad.
Oh, give it to me, honey.
Oh, yeah.
Go, baby-- oops.
Oh, that's it, big boy.
- Come on. Stick it in.
- Oh!
There we go.
It's okay, honey.
- Hang on.
- Oh!
There we go. Don't worry
about anything, honey.
Mommy's going to
take care of you.
Mm.
Do it to me, honey. Do it.
Do it. I know you can.
I know you can do it.
Oh, yeah, honey. Mm.
Oh, baby.
Yeah, that's it.
That's it.
Yeah, oh.
Do it. I know you can.
( yelling )
( grunts )
Yeah.
- Okay?
- ( exhales sharply )
( sighs )
( grunts )
( zipper zips )
See you in church, honey.
Don't just sit there,
put yourself away.
Hey, I know I'm good,
but this is ridiculous.
Come on, man.
Stop joking.
Hey. Hey, it ain't
funny, man.
Hey. Hey!
Oh, God.
Oh, God! Oh!
- Breathe!
- What the fuck are you
kissing him for?!
- Don't fucking kiss him!
- Let go of me!
What the fuck are you
kissing him for?!
( grunts )
( coughs )
Shit, what the fuck
did you do to him?
- Nothing!
- The fucker's dead.
We gotta do something!
We gotta call an ambulance!
Stop it, damn it!
- Where's his wallet?
- Leave him alone!
Don't!
You stop it!
No, God damn it! No!
Now it's your turn.
He wasn't just a trick!
He had a life!
( crying )
It was disposable.
Just like you.
( screams )
Now which finger was it?
Huh? What was it you said?
I said take
your fucking pick!
Oh, yeah?
You stupid fucking whore.
Well, I pick both!
First I'll break
this one
and then I'll break
the other one.
You can break them all!
Don't you fucking get it?!
There's nothing left for me to--
( screaming )
( bone snaps )
You never gave a fuck
about yourself,
but about your kid?!
Huh?
- What about him?!
- You'll never find him!
- You don't know where he lives!
- Oh, no? I've always known!
- Bullshit!
- Yeah, I make it
my business to know!
2627 Crowley Drive!
The blue house on the corner!
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna give him a few years
and then I'll turn him out
on the street.
He'll make more money
than you ever did!
- I'll kill you first!
- Bullshit!
- ( spits )
- You never did know
when to quit, did you?
Rasta:
Someone sure gonna be
in trouble with the police.
This guy's license
just expired.
( laughing )
( screams )
Thanks for the popcorn!
Yeah, thanks
for the movie.
( zipper zips )
( music playing )
♪ Let me be your fantasy ♪
♪ Let me be
your fantasy ♪
♪ Let me be your fantasy ♪
♪ Let me be
your fantasy ♪
♪ Let me be your fantasy ♪
♪ Make me feel ♪
♪ Let me be
your fantasy ♪
♪ Let me be your fantasy. ♪
♪ Mon, every time
me go to them clubs, mon ♪
♪ Me go to Bentley's,
me go to Payday ♪
♪ Me go to Silver Shadow,
me go all around, mon ♪
♪ Me see the girls with
the big boom-boom, mon ♪
♪ Me look at them
and me only want to do
one thing, mon ♪
♪ Me just want to bang her ♪
♪ That's all me want to do,
I just want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her,
I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ Knock boots ♪
- ♪ I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ Follow me now ♪
♪ I want to bang her,
I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ Knock boots ♪
- ♪ I want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her ♪
♪ She a dumb girl
and she got a big bang ♪
♪ All me want to do
is just bang, bang, bang ♪
♪ Me standing all alone
and no one is near ♪
♪ Me want to jump up
and put it in her ear ♪
♪ The girl, she wide
with her big bum flauntin' ♪
♪ Then she lookin' at me,
she know that me want ♪
♪ She tried to run away,
want her nieces and aunties ♪
♪ It much too late,
me already got the panties ♪
♪ So come back, come back
and take the medicine ♪
♪ Me got the long buddy,
come on and let us in ♪
♪ Jump on mattress,
knock the booties, baby ♪
♪ Me place you on pillow
so you won't bang your head ♪
♪ Me kiss, me lick,
me taste, me lust ♪
♪ Me get real horny
and thrust, thrust, thrust ♪
♪ It lasts a long time,
I'm tired, thank you ♪
♪ I'm all dry now 'cause
I just want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her,
I want to bang her ♪
- ♪ Knock boots ♪
- ♪ I want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her ♪
♪ I want to bang her,
I want to bang her ♪
♪ Every time I see you ♪
♪ You know that
I want to ride you ♪
♪ I want to have you,
hold you, gently fold you ♪
♪ Kiss ya and kiss ya
and let Jimmy just scold you ♪
♪ Keep you coming,
begging, and groaning ♪
♪ Calling me your daddy
and I'll have you moaning ♪
♪ Bang, bang, bang, bang ♪
♪ Bang, bang,
bang, bang ♪
♪ Bang, bang, bang, bang ♪
♪ Bang, bang,
bang, bang ♪
♪ Bang, bang, Bronx,
♪ Queens, bang, bang,
Staten Island, bang, bang ♪
♪ Manhattan, bang, bang,
bang, bang ♪
♪ Even in Jersey,
you got to bang, bang ♪
♪ Connecticut, bang, bang. ♪