Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[Hiccup]
This is New Berk at Snoggletog,
the greatest time of the year.
- The lights, the hunting songs...
- [vocalizing]
...the holiday shopping...
- [man] Oh.
- [woman] Uh-huh.
- Cheers!
- ...the Yak-nog shooters.
- 'Nother round!
- Make mine a double!
The only thing missing...
was dragons.
[whimpers]
It's been ten years since Vikings
and dragons agreed to live apart.
But that doesn't mean we've
forgotten our flying friends.
And the best part
of it all, Nuffink,
- was on Snoggletog Eve...
- [Nuffink] Yeah?
- ...I'd make Toothless his favorite meal.
- What was it?
- Lake trout with a side of sea trout...
- Yeah. Yeah.
- ...on a bed of brook trout.
- We all like trout.
And even though he's gone,
I still make it for him.
A lot of families
do stuff like this.
It keeps our loved ones in our
hearts, even though they're far away.
- So, want to help me catch some fish?
- Good on ya!
We're gonna
feed Toothless!
I don't need
a fishing pole, Dad!
I'll just butt the wee
fishes with me own wee head!
- Ow!
- [sighs]
- Ow! Ow!
- [Hiccup] Come on, Nuffink. Let's get Toothless a snack.
[laughs]
[Hiccup] We were excited about
making a traditional dragon feast.
And then it hit me.
[grunts]
Not everyone was on board.
[giggles]
Yes! It worked!
Zephyr,
what are you doing?
Testing my dragon
defense system.
You and all the grown-ups in New
Berk are leaving them snacks.
- What if one shows up?
- That would be great. We love dragons.
Why?
They're monsters.
[voices screaming]
- Oh.
- Uh...
I found this in the attic.
It was Grandpa's.
How come you never told us
the truth about dragons?
But we did.
Dragons are wonderful.
They're our friends.
Tell me this.
Are they giant?
- Well, yeah.
- Razor-sharp teeth?
- Breathe fire?
- I suppose so.
- Claws?
- That'd be yes.
- What happened to your leg?
- Oh. Oh. Uh...
That's what I thought.
Maybe we don't leave fish snacks
around to attract them.
'Cause you know who doesn't
want to be dragon dessert?
Me!
Nuffink, do you want to be
dessert for a dragon?
Hmm.
Methinks I don't.
Let's kill
the dragons!
How did this
happen?
Our ancestors were terrified of
dragons because they didn't know them.
Astrid, we cannot let our
kids go down that road.
Hmm. Remember when we were
kids back in Old Berk,
- how we used to put on a pageant at Snoggletog?
- [grunting]
Oh, yeah.
Those were fun.
What if we brought
the pageant back?
We showed the children of New Berk
how humans and dragons became friends?
- [Nuffink] Bigger!
- That's a great idea.
But we've only got
four days until Snoggletog.
Three if you don't count
Black Plague Friday.
Yeah,
nothing gets done.
Everybody's just
shopping and coughing.
- [Zephyr] More spikes.
- [pounding]
I think we can do this.
Let's talk to Gobber.
[growls]
- [grunts]
- [giggles]
You got me!
Kid can take a hit.
[sighs]
- Hey. Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
It's just, all this talk of
dragons kind of makes me miss him.
It's hard at the
holidays, you know.
Wonder if Toothless
ever misses me.
[chitters]
[coos]
[both snarling]
[chitters]
[purrs]
[coos]
[grunts]
[groans]
[purrs]
[roars]
[both shrieking]
- [Toothless roars]
- [coos]
- [boy grunts]
- Hit his nose.
[Zephyr grunts]
Yeah!
That's two for me.
Oh!
Curse ye, hellions!
How dare ye desecrate the
statue of Stoick the Vast?
- Who?
- Stoick!
The bravest Viking
in the history of Berk!
He put the "king"
in Viking.
[all] Huh?
Oh, my dear mate,
I miss you so.
Remember the time we
were at that mead-house
and those two Visigoths wagered
I couldn't hold my left elbow
in a boiling pot of
gruel for five minutes?
[laughs]
Good times.
- [clears throat] Gobber.
- Hey, kids.
I was just talking to a statue of
your father as if he were really here.
It pains me how the wee ones of
this town have forgotten Stoick.
I know,
and Zephyr is afraid of dragons.
That's why we want to bring
back the Snoggletog pageant.
- [blows]
- [coughs]
You're in luck.
The script I wrote for the last pageant.
Die, you evil beasts
with twisted souls!
Vikings will forever swim
in rivers of your blood!
[groans]
That's nasty.
This has not
aged well.
Mmm. We may need
to start from scratch.
Why don't we show
when everything changed?
Oh, that would be
fantastic!
Like when I met
Toothless and...
Maybe more
big picture, honey.
When all Vikings and
dragons became friends.
Oh, Astrid, I love that.
I'll start writing immediately.
This is gonna be
just what we need...
to honor our friendship
with dragons and, of course,
my great friend,
Stoick.
Okay.
[chitters]
[snores]
[all chittering]
- [squeals]
- [chitters]
Hiccup,
I've been up all night.
It's just a first draft,
but I'm gonna be honest...
it's brilliant!
Oh! Toothless?
Pretty great,
right?
Amazing!
Wait a minute,
I've got an idea.
We should use this
for the pageant.
Well, yeah,
that's, that's...
Gee, I never would've
thought of that.
I'm gonna make him look
so much like Toothless,
Zephyr's gonna fall
in love with him.
He's beautiful.
But cogs and gears can't bring back
the warmth of your friend's nose
or the light
in his eyes.
Or the sound of your
best friend's voice.
Yeah, I miss my dad,
too, Gobber.
Ah, we'll make them
both proud.
[Hiccup] It was a couple
of days before Snoggletog,
and I was getting excited
about the pageant.
Ah. Uh-uh.
And then it hit me.
[screams, grunts]
- [apparatus clanking]
- [gasps]
- Yes! It works!
- We're going to catch a dragon, Dad!
Knock him cold
so he can't eat us!
Zephyr designed
the whole trap herself.
[Hiccup] Ah, so proud.
[chuckles]
Come on, Nuffink.
Let's set some traps outside.
- Come on!
- We're going to kill a dragon!
- [Astrid] What did I say about using the good knives?
- [Hiccup] A little help here?
- [Astrid] Kids!
- Has anybody...
Okay. This pageant
better work.
[snores]
- [yelps]
- [growling]
[both chattering]
[man] Coming through.
Great news, chief.
After exhaustive casting,
we've found our Hiccup.
Yeah, Gobber,
actually I wanted to ask you
about the whole Hiccup
character in the story.
Hiccup,
present yourself!
- Tuffnut?
- Tuffnut, give us a taste.
Uh, a dragon is coming.
Aah. Help me. Help...
Uh... uh, line?
Me?
- Right. Me.
- [Hiccup] Are you...
Great. Now let's see you
run away in fear.
- [shouting]
- Oh, look at those knock-knees,
- the splayed gait of a newborn lamb.
- [Hiccup] I don't...
I do not run
like that.
- Do I run like that?
- Mmm.
Which brings me
to a bigger point.
I read the script, Gobber,
and I have some notes.
I'm not sure the character
of Hiccup is coming through
quite as heroic
as I was.
I was pretty heroic.
No?
Oh, mate, I think
we got the gist of it.
But that's not,
in any way, me.
Hey, Hiccup.
I was...
Oh.
- Are you serious?
- [chuckling]
[man]
Coming through!
- [sighs]
- [shrieks]
[all chittering]
[chittering continues]
[Gobber] Better luck next time, Haggis.
Nice effort.
- Who's next?
- I... [sighs]
Fishlegs Ingerman reading for
the role of Stoick the Vast.
[exhales]
If I don't return...
Nope. No.
[clearing throat]
[deep voice]
If I don't return,
know that all I am,
all I do,
is for you,
my precious Hiccup.
[gasps] Wow.
So, are you thinking
what I'm thinkin'?
Yes, I am.
This isn't working.
What?
Not working?
You're right.
I should do it.
No, don't try
and talk me out of it.
- I knew Stoick best.
- [whimpers]
[clears throat]
If I don't return,
know that all I am,
all I do...
[sobbing]
I miss him so much!
[sighs]
I just need
a moment.
Da-da-da,
we're doomed.
- [shouts]
- [laughs]
[hisses]
[Gobber sobbing]
[coos]
[sobbing]
Gobber, the pageant's tonight. So, are
you sure you're gonna be able to do this?
I hoped it wasn't
noticeable.
You know, it is.
But, Gobber,
think of the kids.
- We're doing this for them.
- [grunting]
Ay, Hiccup.
Brilliant, as always.
- [squeals]
- [barks]
[Gobber] All right.
I'm all right. I'm okay.
- It's gonna be fine.
- [Gobber] Fine.
[chitters]
[all growling]
What?
[Gobber] Okay, people,
two minutes to curtain.
[man]
Has anyone seen my sword?
[all shriek]
[bleats]
[groans]
[whimpering]
[branch snaps]
[grunts]
Ah?
[growls]
[roars]
[all whimper]
[roaring]
[horn plays]
[chuckles]
[audience applauding]
Hiccup, today is the
day everything changes.
- I have tamed a dragon.
- [audience oohs]
I am so tiny and afraid.
What is that? What is that?
That never happened.
So Gobber took
a few liberties.
I don't know.
There were dragons everywhere,
and people doubting me,
especially my own father.
And then I stood my
ground and touched one.
I touched a dragon.
That's hard-core.
He's got the spirit
of the story.
And that's what this pageant
is really about, isn't it?
Yeah, I guess so.
- Hiccup, you are weak and fear dragons.
- [audience laughs]
I am strong
and understand them.
I don't know if I want
to go through with this.
- You're on!
- Yeah, I...
No. Astrid? I... What?
[audience oohs]
[boy] A dragon!
There he is.
The Night Fury.
[groans]
- [boy] It's Toothless!
- [girl] Toothless.
[audience oohs]
- Whoa!
- Nope.
Mmm. Whatever.
[audience exclaims]
[coos]
This pageant is bringing
up the feelings.
Stoick would've
loved this.
The only thing vaster
than his presence
was his capacity
for mirth!
[blows nose, wails]
Oh, pookie lump.
- Brave father, I remember your wise words.
- [both gasp]
"Hiccup,
you can be a giant,
but face thine enemies
with care."
[yelps] Oh, no.
"Hiccup, you can be
a giant, but face..."
No. Line?
[shouting]
[both scream]
[all exclaim]
"Hiccup, you can be
a giant but face!"
Don't panic.
It's just part of the show.
[shouting]
[screams]
[all screaming]
[grunts]
[all cooing]
[shouts]
Oh! Hey, you...
[screams]
[whimpers]
Do something!
Yeah, I got it.
Maybe this one.
Why would you give it
that functionality?
[screams]
I'm on it.
Yeah, I got it.
[roars]
No, no, no, no, no.
[screams]
Gobber? Gobber?
Is that you?
- Thank you for helping out there.
- [sniffs]
[chitters]
[groans] What did you
have, raw trout for lunch?
Let me just shift my weight so I can...
[shouts]
Uh, Gobber?
How did you lose your last two
limbs, Gobber?
Oh, it was a pageant.
- [Hiccup] Gobber?
- Huh?
Hiccup!
[chitters]
[audience exclaims]
[all chittering]
Whoa!
Nice one, Hiccup.
Greetings,
magnificent creature!
Will you allow Stoick to tame
you with his gentle... touch?
[chitters]
[audience] Aww!
[cheering]
Let man and dragon
be forever bonded
in trust and love.
[giggles]
Yes!
[chitters]
Oh, thank you. Thank you,
thank you. Thank you very much.
Whoa!
That was amazing!
I'm so excited
I could fly!
It's just a show, Nuffink.
It's just Dad in a suit.
Best show yet!
[Nuffink] Way to go, Dad!
[whoops]
Hey, Dad. Dad?
- [growls]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
Hi.
[sniffs]
Little help here?
Gobber?
- [chitters]
- Anyone? Literally anybody?
[purrs]
Oh! [giggles]
I love dragons,
and I love Toothless!
He's beautiful!
Why didn't you tell me you were
really going to bring him here?
I have literally no idea
what she's talking about.
This whole thing was
not what I expected.
[boy] Okay.
How about now?
Up a little.
A bit to the right.
- I am Stoick the Vast!
- I'm Toothless! Let's be friends. [giggles]
[sighs]
You were right.
It was exactly
what everyone needed.
For the kids,
and for the memory of my father.
[clicks tongue]
Aww.
Gobber, you have well honored
my father and your friend.
It was my deepest
privilege to do so.
Thank you,
Hiccup.
Well, guess I'll be
headin' home.
Alone.
Oh, the best Snoggletogs
are spent in solitary,
cavernous silence.
- Gobber.
- If you're free tonight...
- I'd love to!
- [Astrid laughs]
Gobber, wait!
- [chuckles] Oh, that's clever.
- And...
You're good.
[sighs] So proud.
- [gasps]
- Look at that. It's so cool!
It's beautiful.
- Hiccup, did you do this?
- No.
The bowl!
It's empty!
- Toothless?
- Can it be?
[gasps]
[roars]
Toothless!
Yeah!
- [Hiccup] And then it hit me...
- [shouts]
...our loved ones
are always nearby
when we hold them in our hearts.
Maybe it's our turn
to visit them.
[all shrieking]
Hey!
[chitters]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org