Hey, wake up!
Wake up!
Got somethin' in my eye...
Move along!
What is this place?
Why did you bring me here?
No more questions.
Turn around! = no.
Turn around!
No!
Here's your beers, guys.
Hello!
Hey!
No, the fashion
show is tomorrow.
Yeah, it starts at four o'clock.
Of course there is
gonna be girls here.
Why do you always do this to me?
Hey, hey!
Get the fuck out of here!
Did you have a good day?
Hey...
Boy!
Lookee here!
Hey, hey!
Get off of me!
I'm here about the job.
That's good.
- I'm Kai.
- Henry.
Pleased to meet you.
You got to talk to
Rooter about that job.
He's in charge.
In there.
Good luck.
Iwo toilets to northbound I 14
outside the 34 b exit?
For right now?
I'll see what can do.
Two standard units,
no sinks or anything?
For how long do you need them?
Thanks for calling!
Got a rush order, Rooter.
From who?
Frank, they're down at
the site working already.
His boys are gonna
have to hold it in.
Kai is going to
raceway park first.
They got a monster
truck pull tonight.
- Can anybody else go?
- No.
Abdulla and the taco boys
got hours of deliveries.
They're already
fuckin' late for...
Did you want to pay
a bill or something?
I saw your sign about the job.
The guy outside, Kai,
said to talk to Rooter.
I'm Rooter,
who the hell are you?
I'm Henry.
It's good to meet you.
Good to meet you, partner.
This is Cricket.
She's Kais old lady
in case you were getting any ideas.
Fuck you, Rooter.
Hello, Henry.
Uh, you want a job, huh?
I can handle just about
anything you throw at me.
Well, I just had
a guy quit on me
and work's starting to pile up.
So I'll give you a shot.
It pays uh $40 a day.
You gotta start now though.
Long day, huh? = not too bad.
Here you go. = thanks.
Used to do
construction before this.
Drove a mixer.
Getting laid off in the
winter was the pits though.
There wasn't always
work in the summer either.
And when I don't work I drink.
Kai?
I need to rent a room,
a cheap one.
You mean a sleeping
room or something?
Yeah. Something close to work.
That's rough...
Let me think about it.
Have anywhere to stay tonight?
Bet that shower felt good.
Kai's old clothes
look good on you.
Dig in before it gets cold.
I appreciate you taking me in.
We couldn't just let
you wander the streets.
We know what it's like
to be broke around here.
When I get paid
I'd like to give you some rent.
It's just till you
get back on your feet.
- Please!
- Okay.
Whatever you want.
I got to get you a set of keys.
So, Henry...
You have a woman
stashed somewhere?
Not at the moment.
A good-lookin' guy like you
doesn't have a girl?
Me and Cricket been
married 10 years now.
You're lucky to have
such a pretty wife.
Thank you, Henry.
- How's the meat loaf?
- It's great.
Henry, this is my
sister's girl Louisa.
- Hi.
sit down and eat.
I'm not hungry.
Louisa is a great artist.
She helps out at the
handicapped school.
I forgot you had a night class,
how did it go?
It was alright.
She's a great artist.
Henry, you have to
see her drawings.
They're wild.
Makes you wonder what's going
on in that head of hers.
You're a jerk.
It's too bad she can't attract
a man to buy her artwork.
Make us a pile of money.
We could build a pool.
Or put an addition on the house.
Cricket!
Quit.
You must be tired, go lay down.
How you doing, Henry?
Martini night, Kai.
What did you put in
those drinks yesterday?
The usual shit, why?
I woke up in my
car this morning
in a bowling alley parking lot.
I'm going to get ready for bed.
Don't get too fucked up tonight.
Night, hon.
Henry's gonna be staying in our
extra room for a couple days.
Is that so?
I need to talk to you.
Let's go downstairs.
Kai leave already?
No, they went
in the basement.
Okay.
Let's go drink some Martinis.
Good man!
- You know where the spare room is?
- Yeah.
Cricket said to get her
a pack of cigarettes.
I have to get ready for school!
- Oh!
- It's all yours.
I left you some hot water.
- Morning!
Did you sleep alright?
Yeah, fine, thanks.
I made coffee if you want some.
I would, thank you.
Hey, you're running
a little late, aren't you?
I couldn't get in the bathroom.
You look thin.
You eating enough?
Are you taking your medication?
I don't need it anymore.
That's not what the doctor says.
I don't care what
the doctor says.
She's such a brat.
Hey, buddy!
Morning, hon.
That's a shitty job.
Hey, retardo! - Hey, ugly!
Look, it's the creature
from another planet.
Quit it! Assholes!
You're mental!
You're sick.
You little bastards!
Dork! Leave her alone.
Hey!
Find somebody else to pick on.
He pushed us.
Who do you think you are?
I'm telling my dad.
Thanks for helping, Henry.
You alright?
- Kai, get up here!
- What?
Those kids are back
with their parents.
Better go to your room.
What?
- Is this the guy?
- No.
Where's the jerk
who pushed my boys?
- What are you talking about?
- Liar!
Your neighbors
saw the whole thing.
What, are you fucking nuts?
Listen, assholes!
Your two little darlings
have been harassing my niece
and I want it stopped.
You're the assholes!
Oh, I'm gonna take you down.
Tell me where this guy is or
I'm gonna start busting heads!
Son of a fucking bitch!
Better listen to
him, he'll do it!
Oh okay, porky!
Stick a sock in her, will ya?
You' re dead. - Fuck him up!
Come on, bust my head!
I want you to!
Alright, get the fuck
away from my door.
You wear the pants
in the family?
- Fuck you!
- You're a slut.
Get away from the door
or I'll sick the cops on you.
I'll sick the
cops on you, bitch!
They're leaving.
His wife's wiping
the spit off his face.
Did you see that mother?
What a fuckin' cow!
You can come out now, Henry.
They got a lot of nerve!
Why don't you let
me kill that guy?
Oh yeah, then the cops would
have been over here for sure.
She's right.
You need anything
from the store?
No, thanks.
Can we go to the
art supply store?
So long as you don't
take two hours again!
Bye, Henry! - Bye!
Find what you're looking for?
I'm not a firebug.
I'm a torch.
I burn buildings to make money,
not to get my rocks off.
It's all about
insurance pay-offs.
How do you get your customers?
Rooter arranges all that junk.
I never meet
anybody face to face.
Anybody ever gotten killed
in one of these fires?
I don't burn apartment buildings
if that's what you're asking.
How about coming with me?
I pay you 500 bucks.
I know you could use it.
And I could use the help.
You don't even know me.
Is cleaning out toilets for $40
a day all you want out of life?
Look...
I can tell you're probably smarter
than a lot of guys I run into.
I need to work with someone
with a few brain cells left.
Think it over!
I'm leaving at 3:00 a. M.
If you want to come with me.
Pilot lights have
to be blown out first.
They could ignite the chemicals
we're gonna lay down.
An exterminator tank?
For spraying the floor.
I always drop off my supplies
at least a week in advance.
Don't want to be carrying this stuff
in my car when I'm doing a job.
Somebody lets you in?
Everyone thinks
I'm making a delivery.
They don't know what of.
- What's that?
- Accelerant.
Makes the fire burn quicker?
Five million times quicker.
Let's move.
You sure it's gonna go up?
Oh yeah.
Engine company 25, we have a report
of a fire at the chateau restaurant.
Any other units close by?
Here's to raising hell...
Engine company 25,
you've got a hot still and box
going at the chateau restaurant.
The only thing that matters.
Had ten calls about this
baby already this morning.
Don't get your
panties all bunched up.
You want it?
I'll advance you on
the next couple of jobs.
Yeah, okay.
It's nice, Henry.
Go break her in.
This stuff has the same
chemical properties as rocket fuel.
It creates its own oxygen.
So I could start a fire in
outer space if I wanted to.
It burns at 7000 degrees,
hot enough to melt
a whole aeroplane hangar,
concrete, steel...
You'll get everything
in 15 minutes.
Somebody's back there.
Let's get out of here.
What for?
Come out of there.
Gene?
It's alright, Casey.
It's just the police.
Come out of there!
Okay, alright, don't shoot!
Are you cops?
Lie down on the floor,
on your stomachs.
Put your hands
behind your backs.
Engine company 14,
are there any companies available
to take in a fire at the abc warehouse?
Yeah, I've got it, engine 26.
Truck 3 available
to take in the fire.
What are we gonna do?
Please watch out for truck
7 responding immediately.
Your turn.
Maybe there was some other way.
There was no other way.
Why did they have to pick
that building to camp out in?
I'm sure they would've made other plans
if they knew we were coming.
I'v e.
Never killed anybody before.
We could get lethal
injections for this.
You know that, don't ya?
Nobody's gonna miss those two.
So I hear you and
Kai like to start fires.
Excuse me?
No use denying it.
Kai told me everything.
Welcome aboard, Henry.
Be cool and you
make some money.
Fuck up
and I'll kill ya.
From now on you
keep your mouth shut.
You keep your mouth shut.
He's the boss,
it's his operation, remember?
I just hope he don't
find out about them kids.
We'll all be sunk.
You had no right
telling him about me.
He didn't have a problem
about you and me working together.
He likes you.
Slimy derelict!
Hey, guys!
You guys wanna buy some acid?
He just made some up on the way.
We're gonna try it out
at the fire pit later.
You know I nearly
had a heart attack
last time I took that shit.
How bout you?
No.
What a couple of pussies.
Hey, wanna go see my new truck?
Sure!
Goddamn it, Kai.
I ain't cleaning
it up this time!
These are good. - Thank you.
Have you ever tried to draw?
Me? No.
I teach this at school.
I can't draw.
Just try it. - Okay.
Let me see.
- No.
- Henry...
Hey! This is good!
Really?
Yes, I like it.
It's a mule I had
when was a kid.
Called him rocks,
on account of he
used to eat rocks.
He wasn't right in the head but
he was still my favorite animal.
You lived on a farm?
- Sort of.
- Can I keep it?
I don't want it.
This is mother.
She ran off on me
five and a half years ago.
She and her boyfriend
did a lot of drugs.
Maybe she'll come back?
Li Don t think so.
Il was so mad when
she didn t come back.
I cut my wrists. See?
I got real close
to killing myself.
Really?
I was in a motel room with a pistol at
my head and my finger on the trigger.
Why were you gonna do it?
I kept thinking about Becky.
Was Becky your wife? = no.
She was murdered.
Her and her brother Otis.
Becky's body was found
chopped up in a suitcase.
They never caught
the guy who did it.
No evidence, no clues.
Are the police still
looking for the killer?
I don't think so.
That's evil.
Why didn't you do it?
Why didn't you kill yourself?
Why should 1?
There's plenty of people
out there who hate me.
I can't let them win.
That's the last of the
expensive stuff, right?
Yep, right.
Get it on the truck.
This place is going up.
Come on, get him.
Remember me?
You're gonna be
sorry you done that.
For my boys!
For my wife!
Fucking pig!
For your bitch!
I kicked ass.
Cocksucker!
Real fair!
Three against one!
Fuck you!
Shit!
Three against one!
I'm gonna get that bastard!
I'll burn all their
fucking houses down.
Sure you will.
I've got another idea.
Why did you pull in here?
What's up?
You wanna get somebody?
How about him?
I'll start it and you join in.
You're serious?
You don't know him,
he don't know you.
It's a perfect set-up.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
I can't believe
I did that last night.
You did it alright.
Next time
it'll be even easier.
Hi, guys.
Where were you?
Shopping.
Did you stop at the bar too?
Your bruises make
you look so tough.
I am tough.
Yeah, let's go to bed.
Can you guys do us a favor?
Sure.
We were gonna get some vodka
but they wouldn't take my ID.
What's your pleasure?
Two fifths and some tonic.
No, it's on us, it's on us, go.
We'll be in the parking lot.
Ready?
We'll take care of ya...
Why don't we go back to
our place and have a party?
Aren't you guys
married or something?
- No!
- No way!
Do you have any pot?
He does.
The best
about five minutes from here.
Alright!
Oh, there's Lars.
The vodka?
Damn you!
What did I do?
What do you want?
Mother came to visit me.
She had worms all over her face.
It was just a bad dream.
- Go back to sleep.
- No, I won't.
- Quiet!
- I'm scared, Henry!
- Can't I stay with you?
- No.
Why not?
Go back to your own bed.
Henry, she was in my room
and she was dead.
Henry, you have
to let me stay here.
If you don't let me
stay here, I die.
I swear my heart
will just stop beating.
Alright but you
have to be quiet.
It's time!
Good morning.
Hi, hon.
- How did it go?
- Fine.
I'm gonna go take a shower.
You guys had to go far?
A hundred and
twenty miles each way.
It's too bad we're
so busy at work.
You could sleep in.
Looks great!
- Hi, Louisa.
- Hi.
I gotta get ready.
She's such a phony.
Where did you go last night?
Couldn't sleep.
There's no school today.
I'm gonna come
visit you at work.
I'm real busy today.
Maybe some other time.
Oh, okay.
- How did you get down here?
- Bus.
What are you trying to pull?
Henry doesn't want you!
We slept together last night!
- Go home right now.
- No.
I came here to see Henry.
No, I won't go! No, I 't go!
What are we gonna do
about Henry and Louisa?
I don't know.
The last thing we need
is for her to have a kid.
I know.
I just can't throw him out.
I want him out of here
by the end of the week
or I'm leavin'.
Bullshit.
I'm serious.
Quit telling me what to do!
1 want him out of here.
This is my house too.
You know what, Kai?
You got nothing going on.
You're a loser.
You're a pathetic fuckin' loser.
Smart ass bitch!
Don't you ever shut
your goddamn mouth?
Kai?
God, I'm sorry, hon.
I never done nothing
like that before.
I'll never do it
again, I promise.
If you want Henry out,
he's gone.
Come on.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Cricket wants you out of the
house by the end of the week.
You kicking me out?
You can afford
your own place now.
Cricket knows how you been
having your fun lately?
It's time for me
to get movin' on.
Don't worry, leave
at the end of the week.
Thanks.
How about we go out tonight?
- Go ahead.
- No.
We're going upstairs.
Try anything and your wife dies.
Okay. Okay, please don't hurt us.
Please... please...
No... no... no!
Why d'you leave?
Here, smother her.
I don't want to do this.
You think that she
won't identify you?
You woman!
You cowardly little girl!
Mr. big bad arsonist!
You fuckin' animal!
You're crazy!
You animal!
You have to tie somebody to the bed
and cut their fuckin' head off!
Ow!
I could kill you right now!
Do you want me to watch the life drain
out of your chicken shit little face?
Do you want to die?
No...
Henry, please no!
From now on
you do exactly what say.
When I say it. You got it?
Yes...
Oh yes...
Thank you...
Oh...
Henry, are you alright?
Don't come in. - Why?
I'm really tired, Louisa.
I'm going to sleep now.
I thought you
might need something.
I waited up for you.
I just need to sleep now.
But 1 waited up for you.
Good night, Louisa.
Good night, Henry.
Don't you look nice.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm glad we're alone.
No.
Why not?
What's wrong with me?
You'd be better off if we
don't mess around, believe me.
Are you in love with Cricket?
No, I'm not in love with Cricket.
What, don't you like girls?
Yes, I like girls.
Then why won't you be with me?
I'm a bad man.
- You shouldn't have anything to do with me.
- No, you're not.
Yes, I am.
You don't see it.
But I wanted you to
take me away from here.
Away from this house.
1 wanted us to be married.
That's not possible.
Yes, it is.
I have to go now.
Don't go.
You're the only person
that I can talk to.
I have to go pick Kai
and Cricket up at work.
They have a car!
It broke down last night.
No! You're not going anywhere.
I don't want to be alive then.
I don't want to be here
anymore unless I'm with you!
You're twisting things
around in your head.
If you go I'll kill myself.
I don't want to be alive anymore,
I'm gonna kill myself.
You're not gonna kill yourself.
Get back here, you faggot!
I'm gonna kill myself.
You hear me?
I'm gonna blow my
fuckin' brains out!
You got beat up in a bar fight.
And last time you got beat
up by your neighbor.
You lying sack of shit!
Where d 'you get beat up?
They won't admit it.
But I know they must have been scrapping.
Hey, where are you going?
To the John.
I'm gotta go check the steaks.
You shouldn't have done that.
Mind your own business.
This is a good steak, isn't it?
Really juicy!
What's wrong with him?
You put something in my drink.
Who? Me?
Come on in.
Come!
So how ya doin', kid?
Hmmm? You still flyin', huh?
Enjoying the ride? I knew you would!
You're the quiet type, huh?
I like that. Keep your mouth shut
and we get along just fine.
You come down in another...
fifteen hours.
I usually smoke weed
to take the edge off.
It seems to help.
Hey, let's burn one now!
Oh no...
Help me get him
into the bathroom.
Why?
Gotta chop him up.
Hello?
Rooter?
Kai!
What are you doin' here?
Where's Rooter?
Upstairs.
Hey, Rooter!
You wake Cricket!
Rooter!
Did you know that
Rooter was gonna drug me?
Of course not!
Good thing.
Henry?
I want to show you something.
No, don't.
Louisa, stop it!
Henry hates me.
I don't hate you.
I'm not afraid to die.
You don't want to die.
Yes, I do.
Louisa, please don't do this.
Please don't hurt yourself.
You don't care what happens to me!
You all will be so sorry!
Did Henry do something to you?
Louisa, please!
That's my gun.
Please give it back to me.
Louisa, you remember
what we talked about?
I don't have to listen
to anybody anymore!
Give me my goddamn gun!
This is for you, Henry.
No!
I'm gonna bring her
into the bedroom.
It is my fault.
I should have listened to her.
And now she's gone.
Get away from her!
Henry, no...
Don't...
Please don't!
Don't burn me!
Please don't let
me die like this!
Henry...
Open up!
Open the door!
Please!
Please, let me out!
Henry!