(upbeat music)
(laughing)
- [Man] Still got it.
(intense music)
(dog barking)
- No, no, no.
Stay there, pup.
You couldn't keep up with me today.
(eerie music)
(dramatic music)
Morning.
Nice day, isn't it?
- Out of work actor.
(mumbling)
(light guitar music)
(dark eerie music)
That's the stuff.
(clattering)
- I'm planning on running myself later.
- Sorry, I didn't think
you'd be up so early.
I'll start breakfast.
- I can't sleep late even on vacation.
I have this, like,
ingrained sense that there's
something someone forgot to do.
- Well, I'll put a pot of coffee on.
- Oh, I already had coffee,
that's very nice.
I should be leaving soon anyway.
I have a lunch date in Knoxville at noon.
He is six-foot and a realtor
and he has a Cocker Spaniel.
We met on the internet.
His picture is very handsome.
You're about six-foot.
- Yeah.
Gonna need to give
yourself about two hours
to get through the Tail of the Dragon.
- Alright.
- Sunny side up?
- Mm.
- Alright.
- [Voice Machine] You
have no new messages.
♫ A fly stuck on the wall, wall
♫ Down the hall
- Damn, forgot the cumin.
♫ The throwing the pillow
and all of the mess
♫ It’s not my best, but
I swear I can do better
♫ Itchy-gitchy ya-ya-ya
♫ Gonna get in the car, car
♫ Gonna make ya proud, proud
♫ Just to be around a superstar
- [Man] Goddamn!
♫ I put down the top, I drive the car
♫ To the left, to the right, stand up
- Food's up!
- I'll be right in.
- Hey, you getting a connection?
- Well, I do today.
It's a good thing,
'cause I can approve these invoices.
People want to get paid, imagine that.
- Well, your breakfast is on the table.
I'll be up in the cabin,
just give me a buzz on the
intercom if you need anything.
- Ooh ah lamb.
(man chuckling)
(light music)
(pills rattling)
(phone ringing)
- Blue Waters, good morning.
- [Man] Hey baby, how's Appalachia?
- Andy.
God, I have been trying to
reach for you three days.
You're still coming, right?
- [Andy] Yeah, I'm headed
to my Atlanta flight,
plane gets in at two,
should be there by four.
- Yeah, maybe five.
Hey, um, how long can you stay?
- [Boy] Hey, you were a stray once, too,
weren't you, boy?
- [Man] People in these parts shoot first
and ask questions later.
- You look more like you're
going to a beauty shop
than the shooting range.
Besides, bet you don't
even know how to use
that gun you keep tucked away.
Here, try this.
Oh no, not for you.
Good, huh?
Recreational materials.
A little hair color.
Who are you trying to impress,
what's her name?
- Oh, no I've got friends
visiting this weekend.
- You need a pipe?
Just another twenty.
Thought you said you
landed here on the run,
and I was your only friend.
- Is friendship what we're calling it now?
- Yes, sir.
Now I got me friends in high places.
- My state of mind, not state of being.
- Nah, you're the man.
I'd kill for this life you
got here, Grady Wilson.
I can't even scrape together enough
to get my bike out the shop.
- Hope this helps.
- It will, I guess.
I'd sure appreciate it if you got
some work I could do around here.
- Business is bad, Beetle.
Your mom toss you out again?
- Something like that.
Occupational hazard, I guess.
You know, I'd do anything else if I could.
A lot I could do if someone would just
give me a chance.
But I'd be real good
at the hotel business.
I'll work real cheap like before.
(eerie music)
- Okay, do rooms five and nine.
Vacuum, dust, sweep the
front porch and the lobby,
pay you for half a day.
- Whole weekend and a bed to sleep in.
- What, you're negotiating?
- Maybe a little.
Whole day's pay plus a bed,
and I'm yours for the weekend.
- Plus look after the
kitchen for a little?
- I ain't so good at dishes.
- (chuckles) You'll learn.
Half day, room and board, out on Monday.
(Grady whistles)
(dark mystery music)
(light guitar music)
- Excuse me.
I thought you checked out already.
- Who are you?
- I'm Beetle.
I'm just helping out today.
- That's nice.
- Male cardinal's got
hellfire's belly, I tell ya.
Hangs around birds, all
kinds of other birds.
And for some reason he never let's another
of his own kind nest anywhere near.
See this one male cardinal
chasing the other tree to tree?
That shrill sound is anger.
Pure fury on account
that he was here first.
Look at him drowning out the other, yeah.
Hollerin' and chasin' and
chasin' and hollerin'.
Now when he wins, and he will,
on account of he won't stop 'til he does,
he'll return to this here favorite tree,
his feathers all puffed up,
and they'll sing him a victory song.
- What will he have won?
- A place of his own for a while, I guess.
- Alone?
How do you know so much about birds?
- Grandfather told me some stuff once.
I guess it kinda stuck.
Hey, you can spare me some money, right?
I gotta get my bike from the mechanic,
I'm still, like, 200 short.
- You want money from me?
- Yes, ma'am. I do.
(dark eerie music)
(engine revving)
(dark mystery music)
- [Man] We're going every
conceivable direction at once.
How is this possible?
- You know Sophie would
be perfect for the part.
You're not alone in loving her,
there's a lot of interest,
but your back-end points are insulting,
and I'm gonna need to see
another zero on that base.
Listen, Bear, why don't you
just think about it overnight, okay?
I know you're trying to
catch a plan to Mer, Bear?
I lost him.
Hey, the road splits ahead, what do I do?
- Arrive here.
- What?
That doesn't make any sense.
I just, this visiting Grady.
- Grady's doing fine.
- Then I don't know if I have it in me
to do this all over again.
I swear, sometimes I
feel like we should just
cut our losses and run.
(rhythmic music)
- Grady.
- What?
- You got a little problem here.
The john in nine is
clogged and overflowin'.
- Did you try a plunger?
- I tried everything I could think.
- Jesus Christ.
- That's a nice reaction.
You know Arlis, right?
- No.
- He's my bud, I'll call him for you.
- Is he a plumber?
- Yeah, he's a plumber.
Best in town.
Probably the whole county.
- Oh God, I still need
to run and get eggs,
Rye and Karen are gonna
be here at any minute.
- Go ahead, I'll call him for you.
I'll hook you up.
I got your back.
- I sure am sorry to hear
about your mom, Beetle.
- [Beetle] Thanks, Arlis.
(toilet gurgling)
- Got it.
- What's that?
- Looks like a pair of panties.
Ladies' pink panties.
- How you suppose that got down there?
- Well, you won't believe
the kind of things
I find in people's pipes.
Once found a cat.
(register whirring)
- Just put it on my account,
my name's Grady Wilson.
- I know who you are, Mr. Wilson.
- Oh.
I get a little carried away in my head,
I've got a lot going on,
and I forget to be courteous, I'm sorry.
- It's okay, just 'cause
you see some smoke
doesn't mean that there's a fire.
- Excuse me?
- We take things in stride
in these parts, Mr. Wilson,
you'll catch on.
- Yes.
Have a good day.
- [Arlis] I'm used to getting paid
when I finish a job, you know?
- Oh, I know, but he ain't here.
I don't know where he's at.
I'll ask Grady to drop off your pay
as soon as I see him.
You know, with all these rooms,
he's like to need a plumber more often.
You want us to hook you up?
- What exactly you got in mind, son?
- Just saying, you scratch
my back I'll scratch yours.
- What are we talking about here,
a twice-a-year snake job?
- Every other week, snakes and more.
At least as long as I'm here.
I can't get by on what folks
like Grady Wilson will pay.
I imagine it's tough on you, too.
I'm just saying, look around.
He's doing just fine.
It's you and me who's
getting the short end,
if you know what I mean.
- That's my beer money for the weekend.
You best make it worth my while.
- You have my word, Arlis.
Hey, you're adding that
into your cost, ain't ya?
(dark mystery music)
- I want a different birth sign.
- You mean like astrology?
- Yeah, I just don't get along
with other Sagittariuses.
They're too fussy
and focused on one thing at a time.
And they take themselves
way too seriously.
- [Rye] Who else is a Sagittarius?
- [Karen] Grady.
- [Rye] I mean, like anyone famous?
- [Karen] Oh, um, Jim Morrison.
Jane Austin.
- I don't know that I would necessarily
want those two together.
What would you be?
Gemini?
- [Karen] No, they're too passive.
- I'm not passive.
(eerie music)
(footsteps clattering)
- Oh my God.
This is gorgeous!
A big improvement.
- [Rye] Grady!
There he is.
Nice to see you, man.
- Thank you for coming.
You have no idea how much I've missed you.
- It's good to see you smiling.
- I've got an amazing
dinner planned for tonight
and a surprise guest.
- Oh, I've missed your cooking.
- [Rye] Who's the surprise guest?
- It wouldn't be a surprise if I told you.
- [Rye] Come on, Grady, you know can't
keep a secret, man.
- It's Andy.
- What?
- Andy's coming!
- [Rye] When?
- Like now!
It's gonna be the four of us
together again just like old times.
- I need to use the bathroom, oh!
Hello.
- Good afternoon.
I'm Beetle.
Room nine, right?
- That's Beetle.
- Beetle, I'm Rye, this is my wife, Karen.
- Pleasure.
I'm gonna get these things to your room.
And I'll fix something to drink.
- [Rye] Oh, you're the man, Beetle.
Cold beer when you get a chance.
- Ah, no, I'll get that.
- This room's my personal favorite.
It's got the best view of the lake.
And a jacuzzi hot tub with jets.
- Oh, nah, I can't take money from you.
- Yes, you can.
- Think of this as your home.
Just let me know if you
need anything, ma'am.
- Ma'am?
Please, I'm not that old.
- No disrespect intended.
I call every young lady over 20 ma'am.
You are over 20?
- Pile it on, kid.
You know, with your Southern
charm and those looks,
I bet you're quite a handful.
(dark eerie music)
(relaxing music)
- [Rye] Blue Waters Scrabble Championship.
- I think most of them awards
are from the previous owners.
- Everybody come in here and
walk away with something?
- Pretty much, I guess.
- What about you?
- Not yet.
- You and Grady close?
- Yes, sir, I like to think so.
- Is he doing okay here?
Is he happy?
- He gets by about the
best he can, I suppose.
- Is he making any friends in town?
- Suspect it takes a
local some time to warm up
depending on how a new person
presents himself and all.
- I worry about him.
I imagine it's pretty
lonely here in the winter.
- Indeed, it is.
Sounds like you're good buds.
- Yeah, you know, good times and bad.
- Grady has some bad times, has he?
If I may be so bold,
did something bad happen to Grady?
I've often suspected that
maybe what drove him out--
- Hey.
Let's just say we all went through
a bit of recovery period, alright?
Leave it at that.
(dark eerie music)
- This carrot will perhaps just
thwart off my pending buzz.
(chuckling)
I wasn't so sure that you and Andy
were on good terms these days.
- No, no, no, no, we're good.
- Says you or says he?
- Well, both of us, I hope.
I'm gonna ask him to move in.
I want us to be married.
(chuckles) In sentiment if not in law.
It is North Carolina after all.
Oh, I want you to see this.
- Aw, Grady.
- Perhaps the feelings that we experienced
when we were in love
represent a normal state.
- [Karen] Being in love shows a person
who he should be.
- You remember your Russian lit.
- Of course I do.
Mr. Kitrich was hot.
- Mm yeah, he was. (chuckling)
- It's really nice.
I just hope that Andy can
see the person he should be.
Why is it that all the men in my life
have a problem facing reality?
- Did you say something?
- Beetle.
A chef requires more wine,
and I need another martini.
Very dry.
- That's number two.
- I can count, don't worry.
- Wouldn't worry.
Bet mama don't burn the grits.
- Oh, I love the regional vernacular.
Oh, I sound condescending,
I don't mean to be,
it's just that I have this
fascination for colloquialisms.
You from around here?
- Born and raised less
than two miles away.
- [Karen] I bet you're
close with your family.
- Sometimes a little closer in proximity
than I'd like, I suppose.
- I bet it's a big family,
and your dad is the kind, dedicated type
who would work a second job?
- Actually, Ms. Karen, my pop's dead.
Or so I'm told.
No other kids, just me.
- Beetle.
Don't mind Karen over here.
She's sure she has a keen ability
to sum up all the little bits
and pieces of stranger's lives.
- Alright then.
Try me.
Try again.
- Your mom, she was the independent type.
She had to shelve a few big dreams
to focus on the materiality
of raising a son on her own.
- Actually, mom's got the bipolar.
Sweet as pie one second,
raising the steeple the next.
She had a waitress job once.
Got so worked up on a customer,
she threw a pot of scowlin' coffee at him.
They let her go.
- Alright, you have a girlfriend.
- It's not working out so
good this week, actually.
- You went to high school.
- K through 12. Yes, ma'am.
- You did well?
- Mostly.
Feels a little like the
law's coming down on me.
Did I pass?
- You did, I did horribly, though.
- Yeah, she's usually much, much better.
- No, there is something.
There's a certain quality about you.
You know who you remind me of?
A younger version of Rye.
Doesn't he have a similar persona?
- No.
Rumor has it you require more wine.
- No, rumor has it you require sweet buds.
- Grady, you're a good man.
- [Grady] Mm-hmm.
- What ya cookin'?
- Glazed carrots, a
little bit of orange zest,
a little bit of agave,
it's gonna be real good.
Mm-hmm, you hungry?
- Yes, sir.
- Come on, don't take one!
- You reading Oscar Wilde?
- [Beetle] Trying to.
- It's one of my favorites.
- Yeah?
Maybe you can help me then.
I have a little trouble
understanding this right here.
- [Karen] Read it to me.
- Alright.
"It is better not to be
different from one's fellows,
"the ugly and the stupid
"have the best of it in this world.
"For if they know nothing of victory,
"they are at least spared
the knowledge of defeat.
"Shall all suffer terribly
"for what the gods have given us?"
- I think you understand that just fine.
- Anyway.
What about you, Ms. Karen?
- What about me, Mr. Beetle?
I'm gonna need you to be
a little more specific with your question.
- Well, tell me about your job.
- [Karen] What do you think I do?
- Alright, I get it.
God, I won't be much good
at this game, though.
You work behind the scenes
in the entertainment industry.
- Yes.
I am a talent agent.
- And I bet you got a lot
of fancy university degrees.
You go to school for something like that.
- Not a prerequisite.
But this one did with a
master's in political science.
- But it takes a lot more than
education or hard work
to get where you're at.
- Yes, dear Beetle,
I scratched and clawed my way
through the assistant's pool and I waited.
- And what do we wait for?
- We waited for someone to die
or have a breakdown or
screw up and get fired.
All the above.
Anything for an opportunity.
To win big somebody else
has got to lose big.
(mysterious music)
- Karen.
- Hi, Andy.
- Wow.
What a great surprise,
I didn't know I was gonna
get to see you this weekend.
Funny, I was just thinking about you,
meaning to call, how's Rye?
- Rye's in the kitchen with Grady.
You can go ask him yourself.
- Hello.
I'm Andy.
- Something from the bar for you, sir?
- Sir.
Jack on the rocks if you got it stocked.
- We're so stocked back here,
it's fixin' to fall a flood.
- This is Beetle.
He's the newest member
of the Blue Water staff.
Not only does he have
the ear and intuition
of a great bartender,
he is, in my opinion,
the keystone for the future success
of our little venture.
- Hm.
Well, awesome.
What kind of a name is Beetle anyway?
- Just my nickname as a kid.
Guess it kinda stuck.
- Yes, I guess it did.
- Beetle.
So help me out.
Where the hell can I get
cell phone reception?
- Your best bet's probably
out front of the lodge,
on the road above the deck.
- Cool.
Thanks.
Well, I better run and say my hellos.
- What you mean "our venture?"
Are you an investor here or something?
- Does anything get by you?
- I hope not.
- Yes, I am a silent investor, we all are.
But let's just keep it silent, okay?
- Mom's the word.
- Grady! Hi!
I, um...
I didn't know you and Karen
were gonna be here, Rye.
- Surprises abound.
I guess I could say the same for you.
- Listen, I have to make a call.
Work.
- Yeah.
Remember to try out front by the lake.
- I know.
Beetle told me.
He's got me covered.
- Beetle's got Andy covered.
- Beetle's got a lot of things covered.
- I actually feel sorry for him.
(door creaks)
- Mm.
What has Grady told you about us?
- Well, nothing, but I
guess he cares about you,
just 'cause he's got to impress.
- Why do you say that?
- Well, he's been
exercising like a crazy man.
And well, yeah, I can't tell you.
- Well, you started,
now you have to finish.
- Well, he even dyed the gray
out of his hair this morning.
- Really?
Grady's gone gray.
- What?
- Oh, nothing.
No, it looks good.
- Beetle.
Go stir the carrots.
- Let's go shoot some pool.
(dark eerie music)
(sizzling)
- Hey baby, it's me.
Sorry I missed you.
Cell phone reception sucks here.
I'm standing in the middle of a road
in front of a lake below a mountain,
it's like the only place my
phone will work. (chuckles)
Crazy, huh?
Listen, I should probably stay over
and catch a morning plane.
I know that's not what we talked about,
but I'll be out of here
tomorrow, I love you.
(calm guitar music)
- Phone work?
- Yeah, thanks.
You know...
You look so good.
And this place is--
- Thanks.
- Is that tapestry new?
- Yeah.
- What's with you?
- Nothing.
Why?
- It's not nothing, what is it?
- Let's talk later.
- Later?
- Yeah, when it's just you and me.
- You're seeing somebody else, aren't you?
You didn't come here to visit,
you came here to break up.
That's what you've been,
that's why you've been avoiding my calls.
- I'm a horrible person.
Please understand that I,
I don't want to hurt you.
- You can't do this to me now.
I'm so alone here, I need you.
- Baby, baby, baby, I hear you.
Grady, I hear you, I do.
But it doesn't work for you in the city,
and I can't live out here.
I love you, but what do you,
what do you expect me to do, Grady?
(slow dramatic music)
- Andy.
(grunts)
I know you have some trouble
controlling your impulses,
but how could you not even tell him
that you're seeing somebody?
Grady's fragile.
- Oh, come on.
He's not gonna break.
I wanted to see him in person
and talk face to face in private.
- But you put me in a
really awkward position.
- Uh!
I didn't intend to do anything to you,
I didn't even know you were gonna be here!
What, you want me to just go, I will.
- You'll do what you need to.
You always do.
(balls click)
- Karen, seriously,
you are one of the most intelligent,
beautiful women I know.
It kills me to see you this angry.
- Don't even, Andy.
Your bullshit is completely transparent,
and I don't trust you.
- Oh, don't start in on trust with me,
'cause if it weren't for your, uh, deceit,
none of Grady's mess would've gone down.
- [Karen] That's a low blow.
- [Rye] Is something burning?
- [Andy] Manny Knowles, Karen.
You destroyed Grady.
- [Karen] Fuck you, Andy.
- [Andy] Own your guilt, Karen!
- [Karen] Show some responsibility.
- [Andy] What do you think I'm doing?
- [Karen] I don't know, when you left,
you went to New York, Grady's out here.
- [Rye] Serious, something's burning!
- [Karen] You totally deserted him!
- [Andy] What are you doing here?
- [Karen] I don't know
what I'm doing here--
- [Andy] Exactly!
- Everything alright around here?
- There's smoke.
- [Karen] You're making
a mess out of everything!
- [Andy] It wouldn't have been a mess
if you wouldn't have been here.
(confused chatter)
(mysterious music)
(alarm blaring)
Shoot.
- [Rye] Grady!
- [Andy] Disconnect it from the box!
The box!
- What happened?
My lamb vindaloo!
- Which food do you mean,
charred beyond recognition?
- That noise.
Can someone turn that off?
(alarm stops)
- Mama don't burn the grits,
but papa's got issues.
- Got them set about 500
degrees, who did this?
It's ruined!
Why can't I do anything right?
(Rye coughing)
(rhythmic music)
- This orange-colored rice
is really, really good.
(eerie music)
(utensil clinks)
- Sweetheart, are you okay?
- No. No, not really.
I don't know what's going on.
You know, I'm glad you're all here,
but I'm not feeling very well,
so I'm gonna turn in.
(knocking on door)
Come in, Beetle.
- It's chicken soup.
I found it in your deep freeze.
You made it, so it must be good.
- [Grady] I'm not hungry.
- You didn't eat dinner.
I thought you might could
drink a cup of soup.
What ya doing?
- [Grady] Watching.
- Watching what?
- [Grady] Everything.
- Well, I hope you feel real better soon.
- [Grady] Thank you.
(eerie music intensifies)
- Took him some soup,
don't know if he's gonna eat, but I tried.
- What's he doing?
- Watching us.
- Watching us?
- On the surveillance monitors.
- You like working here?
- Happy to have a job,
especially these days.
Guess you know what I mean.
I bet Ms. Tammy and the others
wish they hadn't have quit.
- Who's Ms. Tammy?
- Oh, she was the last housekeeper.
- Why'd she quit?
- Suspect she didn't like him
watching her all the time.
He'd holler down at her over the intercom
if something wasn't dusted
or moved wrong or worse.
- You know Grady, he's
particular about things.
I guess that's what makes
him good at his job.
(dishes clanging)
You do think Grady's
good at his job, right?
- I suppose.
Hey Rye, wait.
I'd really like it if we could be friends.
I know you probably think I'm just some
silly small-town kid.
But I got a lot to offer,
I just don't get a chance to show it much.
All I want's a chance, you know?
A job and maybe a new friend
with a different perspective.
- Sure, Beetle.
I don't see why we can't be friends.
- [TV Announcer] You're
gonna need to do more
than a cleaning with this old girl.
Not if you want to keep your house.
She gets fire in it more
than your fireplace can.
(Karen groaning)
You can salvage lumber
from your historic home,
tailor-made to fit in your room.
- Can you, I'm watching that.
- You're watching a home show
on fireplace restoration.
- I was listening to it.
- I didn't know you were awake.
- I don't have my sleeping pills.
I forgot to pack them.
You shouldn't eat after 10.
- I was talking with Beetle.
- In the kitchen with a sandwich?
He's a nice guy.
- We kind of have similar
personas, don't you think?
- Please, he's a child.
And I like men.
Well, one man.
What's wrong?
- Beetle claims all the
employees here have quit.
He says Grady sits upstairs all day
watching the surveillance monitor.
And every time the
employees do something wrong
he comes down and yells at them.
- Grady wouldn't sit around
watching a surveillance monitor.
Would he?
- I don't know.
But this cable package kind of stinks.
- I just hope he doesn't
hit us up for more cash.
This place could become a money pit,
I mean more than what
it really already is.
You know, I already put
60.000 into this place?
We can't just let him
run it into the ground,
now, can we?
You know, I had to take
a loss in the first two,
and we could deduct 100% of investment.
- That's good then, right?
- Yeah, well it could be.
- Did you tell Beetle I was out of work?
- [Karen] No, I wouldn't do that.
Why do you ask?
- Something he said implied that he knew.
- He's very intuitive.
- That borders on psychic behavior.
- Maybe Grady said something.
- Yeah, must be it.
He needs to keep that mouth shut.
And mind his own freaking business.
(Rye groans)
- [TV Announcer] See if we
can't find a new mantle.
- Night.
- [TV Announcer] Removing
stains and clean up
this whole marble kit, clean up the--
(loud thud)
(yawns)
- Excuse me.
Excuse me.
No towels in room five.
- [Andy] Sorry.
- You're fine.
Night now.
- Night!
(light music)
(mysterious music)
(floor creaking)
- [Beetle] What's the matter, can't sleep?
- What?
(chuckling)
- So you can't sleep either?
- No, I was just going to
the kitchen for a snack.
- Want to smoke a joint?
You ever think Grady could
get like he was before?
- What do you mean?
- You know, the incident.
- You know about that?
- Yes, I do.
- Well, he's made a lot of progress
since his attempted suicide,
and he's been taken care of
by some really great doctors.
Don't worry, I'm sure he'll be okay.
- So you were good to stand by him
as long as you did.
I'd imagine that paranoia and depression
must take its toll on a friendship.
- I managed.
Call me Andy.
- I should really get some sleep, Andy.
- Yeah, me too.
(gentle guitar music)
- [Grady] Morning.
- Now I know you have another choice,
there's always another choice,
but Sophie is your first choice.
No, no, no, we got to
come to terms on this.
No, meet me more than halfway.
Let's get this deal out of the sand trap
and onto the putting green.
Alright, send me an offer.
Alright, you're a doll.
- Got a big one comin'.
- It's fixin' to fall a flood?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Come sit with me, Beetle.
- Nah, I shouldn't.
- Have you eaten?
Catch yourself a plate and sit.
So do you like working here, Beetle?
- Yes, ma'am, I do.
- Apart from the occasional ones
it gets overly familiar, I suppose.
But I love it here,
this is a beautiful place.
And I'm happy just
keeping sure guests are attended to.
- And what to do the customers
and people in town think of Grady?
- It's not really for me to say.
I don't gossip.
- I respect that, but it's not gossip.
I'm his friend.
- From what I know,
it's friends who gossips most of all.
- You might be right.
Regardless, I would like
you to be candid with me.
- Well, I don't know how
things work in the big city.
But around here, a man's
reputation is everything.
- And how is Grady's reputation?
- Look around, there's nobody here.
Not the best, I suppose.
(door rattles)
- Good morning.
- Every day I see this same woman,
and every day she ignores me.
Why does that power walking freak hate me?
- Maybe because you call
her a power walking freak.
- Not to her face.
- How ya feeling?
- About the same.
- Excuse me, Ms. Karen.
I better go see if there's anything
he needs me to do.
(rhythmic music)
- I absolutely cannot focus today.
- Ms. Karen asked me to sit with her.
I told her I shouldn't, but she insisted.
- Oh, that's fine.
Is anybody else up?
- Not yet.
I don't suppose we'll be seeing Andy
for quite some time.
I guess he got real friendly
with Mr. Daniels last night.
I don't understand it,
but if a man wants to
lie with another man,
I suppose it's none of my business.
'Til it becomes business.
What I mean to say is,
I ain't comfortable
receiving sexual advances
at my place of work.
- What?
What? What?
(suspenseful music)
Andy!
(bangs on door)
Get the hell up right now!
- [Andy] Jesus, would
you keep your voice down,
what is it?
- [Grady] You are such a pig.
- [Andy] What!?
- [Grady] How could you do that?
He is an employee, he's a kid!
- [Andy] Oh, that?
Jesus, nothing happened.
- [Grady] You put your
hand on my employee's cock
against his will.
- [Andy] Against?
- [Grady] You are getting
the hell out right now!
- [Andy] Oh, please.
He practically waved
it in front of my face!
- If there is a God and he
truly wants to punish someone,
he starts by making them mad.
- Do you mean furious or insane?
- Both.
- Andy made a pass at Beetle?
- He practically molested him.
We're gonna be lucky if
Beetle doesn't press charges.
- Beetle wouldn't do that.
- Oh, my head is splitting!
- [Karen] I'll get you some water.
- Grady, I want to talk to you.
- How's your back?
Weren't you supposed to be leaving?
- There's a storm coming!
Flights out of Atlanta are grounded.
- You've got a rental, drive!
- To New York?
- Why not?
- Grady, please stop.
Please stop.
- Don't touch me!
Is nothing sacred to you?
(choking)
You hate me and you want me
to go away, don't you?
- [Karen] Grady!
- I won't let you get away with it!
- [Karen] Grady! Stop!
- What are you all trying to do to me?
- Shh!
- You wanna kill me.
- Grady.
- You want me to die, don't you?
- We don't want you to die.
We don't want you to die.
- [Grady] Get off me.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
(music slows down)
- Is there anymore breakfast?
- Okay, I can't stand by
and watch you destroy
everything you've built here.
- You have no right.
No idea what I'm feeling right now.
- I know that you're hurt,
and I know that you're lonely,
and I know that some people close to you
have done some pretty horrible things,
but we love you.
(sighs)
Are you taking your meds?
- There will be within
the next generation or so
a pharmacological method
of making people love their servitude.
- Are you taking your medication?
- Like clockwork.
It's feeding time now.
(eerie music)
They're getting smaller.
- What's getting smaller?
- My blue pills are shrinking.
- Okay, let's just save
that decision-making stuff
for another day.
- Yeah? What's to decide?
- I am really, really worried about you.
- You're worried about your investment.
- I'm worried about your health,
I'm worried about the fact
that you're not fitting in,
I'm worried that people
up here don't like you.
- Who said that?
- You did a minute ago
with that power walker.
- I don't give a damn what she thinks,
she can go to hell!
- Don't be like that.
You have such kindness and integrity,
just hold onto that.
Adjust behavior and fix your reputation
while you have a chance.
I want you to see a doctor.
I want you to consider
resuming treatment in New York.
- I can't, I can't, I can't leave
and go into treatment,
I have a business to run.
- Grady Wilson.
From what I see, you are in no condition
to run a business.
(rain sprinkling)
(mysterious music)
(laptop slams)
- Any luck?
- Its neck is broken.
- At least it wasn't yours--
(creaking)
- [Rye] Hey buddy!
- I, uh, thinking of a filet
and grilled sole for dinner,
kind of a surf and turf.
- Okay.
- Sounds good.
I like sole.
- Great.
I'll run to the store right
after I walk the dogs.
Anybody want anything?
- No thanks.
- A little bit of the bipolar.
- Ya think?
- Don't joke.
- I wish.
He scares me.
- What was the name of
his doctor in New York?
- Ben Fiensburg, Ben Fienstein.
- Which?
(dark eerie music)
- Hey Beetle, listen,
I got a little carried
away in my head earlier,
I'm sorry.
- Can't say that I blame you, not one bit,
I'm sure Andy deserved
everything you threw at him.
- You know, I even considered
snatching Andy's cell
and calling the new boyfriend to warn him.
- Not a bad idea if you ask me.
- No, no, I reconsidered.
So not cool.
- Grady, I hope you don't blame me.
Last thing I want is to
be in any kind of trouble.
I could go if you want.
- It's raining cats and dogs out there,
where are you gonna go?
No, you should stay here.
- You're a good man, no
matter what they say.
I have respect for you.
True respect.
Grady?
Who's Manny Knowles?
- Why?
- Isn't he that famous actor?
- Did someone mention him to you?
- Well, not to me specific,
but I overhead some things.
- Tell me what they
said, exactly every word.
- Well, Andy said to Karen,
"If it weren't for your deceit,
"none of Grady's mess
ever would've gone down,"
and Karen said something like, "low blow,"
and they started calling
one another names.
And Andy just shouted Manny Knowles.
(dark mystery music)
- There are 17 different
Fiensteins in New York.
(echoed voices chattering)
- [Andy] Can't stop.
(echoed voices laughing)
- People up here don't like you.
(chattering, laughing continues)
Who's that?
(door thuds)
- [Rye] Was that the door?
- No, I'm not a relative,
but I am a close friend.
No, this is urgent, Grady
is becoming violent.
No, I'm in North Carolina with him,
he doesn't know that I'm making this call.
Well, Grady thinks that
we're trying to kill him.
Yes, he's had flu-like symptoms,
mood swings, hostility.
He's had tremors and--
- Tell him.
- Oh, he said that he had
a really terrible headache.
I'm sorry, Antidepressant
Discontinuation Syndrome?
No, but I've seen him take his pills.
Oh, you don't have to do that.
- [Beetle] Oh, I'll be out
of your way in a jiffy.
- You're not in my way,
I just have to grab a
sweater or something.
- [Beetle] Is Grady gonna be okay?
- Um, yeah, I hope so.
We think maybe seeing
his doctor in New York
for a few days might help.
Might you consider staying on here
and looking after things for a while?
- I'm here to help out
in any way you see fit.
Doctor visit or not,
a trip to New York
sounds exciting for him.
- Hey, you know, later,
if you ever think about
coming to New York,
I'll do what I could to
help you get started.
- You'd let me?
- Um...
Yeah!
Yeah, I would.
- I'm deeply moved, Karen.
Nobody's ever offered to
help me like this before.
- You're welcome.
(upbeat music)
- Excuse me.
Grady Wilson, from up at the lodge?
- Yeah.
- I hadn't received my pay from you.
- Excuse me?
- I snaked your pipes.
- Oh, you must be Arlis.
Hi, it's a pleasure to
meet you face to face.
Thank you for your excellent work.
- If you're satisfied with my work,
why haven't you paid me?
- Well, send me a bill and I will.
- You have my bill.
For a $160, you do.
- There must be some misunderstanding,
I haven't seen--
- Suppose you pay me now.
- I don't have any cash
on me right now, Arlis.
- Figured that.
Disrespect.
And the way you treat that poor kid,
especially with what happened
to his mother and all,
I pity you, sir.
I shall pray for you.
- What are you talking about?
- Good day, sir.
Enjoy your fancy steaks.
(phone ringing)
- Hello.
- [Man] Grady.
- Hi, Dr. Fienstein.
- [Dr. Fienstein] I have
heard from your friend
Karen Killington.
I'm concerned with your
medication's effectiveness,
I have called in a new
prescription for you.
- I don't want a different prescription.
- [Dr. Fienstein] You don't have to take
anything you don't want, but they say
you're acting very strange.
- You know, it's not me, it's them.
My boyfriend dumped me.
He tried to hit on this
poor kid at the lodge
who's working for me,
I just found out that my best friend
is responsible for
killing my acting career,
and my new business is practically broke.
- [Dr. Fienstein] All the more reason
to adjust your medication now, Grady.
- (sighs) No, I won't do it.
- I understand. Thank you.
Dr. Fienstein says that he believes
Grady's mood swings could be justified.
Did you tell Grady about Manny Knowles?
- No.
- Well, he knew.
Or Grady told his doctor.
He said he called in
a prescription anyway,
but he doesn't think that
Grady's gonna pick it up.
(phone ringing)
Barry, I am sorry,
I'm not gonna be able to talk right now,
I'll have to catch up with you on Mon,
no, Monday.
Thanks.
- Let's go get his prescription.
(intense rhythmic music)
(loud thud)
(whooshing)
- Grady, come on down for a second.
Honey, I'm sorry (mumbling), is that okay?
Hey, no matter how mad you are at me
or what you think of me,
I do have your best interest at heart.
- You'd sell me out or
anyone else for that matter
without a second thought
if it suited your needs.
- What are you talking about?
- Manny Knowles, Karen.
Your new star client,
the one who just happened
to step in and replace me
after my first day on End of the World.
Manny pretended to be my friend.
I introduced him to you.
One day he's a bartender,
the next day he's got my role
on a major motion picture.
- It was political, Grady.
The director met him and liked him
and our offices knew that he
was safe to go mainstream.
- This is about my sexuality?
Nobody knew that I was gay.
- Nobody knew yet.
- So you decided to bury me
before somebody else did.
- I made a decision to invest
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
into the career of a safe bet.
Your behavior after is what buried you.
If I had to do it all over again, I would,
I know that now, forgive me
for your sake, not mine.
- You know, I was gonna ask you for a loan
to keep this place going until spring.
- Whatever you want, it's yours.
- No, no, no, no.
No more guilt money.
God, no wonder you can't sleep at night.
Don't call my doctor,
don't talk to my friends behind my back,
and please don't pretend
to do me any more favors.
- Here you go.
Do whatever you want with them.
(mysterious music)
- So they say they got room on a flight
tomorrow out of Atlanta.
You wanted four seats, right?
- Yeah.
Four seats.
Use my credit card.
About last night,
sorry if my behavior was inappropriate.
It's an unfortunate misunderstanding,
and I hope there are no hard feelings.
- None whatsoever.
If I were you, I'd give a heads up
to that friend of yours in New York.
- What do you mean?
- Grady said he had a mind
to steal your cell and call him.
Crazy way he's been,
there's not telling
the damage he'll do ya.
- Thanks for that information.
I want that card back.
(dark eerie music)
- What are you up to, Beetle?
(keyboard clicking)
"Carla May Hobbs passed away yesterday.
"Sources tell us she battled
long time disabilities
"including manic depression,
"report noted she stopped
taking her medication
"and suspect Antidepressant
Discontinuation Syndrome
"lead to her apparent suicide.
"Toxic level of prescription sleep aids
"was found in her bloodstream.
"Pentecostal Church of Christ announced
"funeral services will be
held as early as next week,
"Mrs. Hobbs is survived by one child,
"Wallace B. Hobbs, age 21,
"Robbinsville, North Carolina."
Beetle, I need your help tonight!
(mysterious music)
- You know, you don't look so good,
I could take of that for you if you like.
- I'm fine.
Karen talk to you yet?
- About what?
- About you staying on
here while I'm away.
- She might've mentioned something.
Whatever I can do to
help out is fine by me.
- Bet you'd like New York.
How old are you? 21?
Same age as me when I first moved there.
Took me years to find an agent.
Karen took me on back
when she was an assistant.
She's gonna rep you, too, right?
You did ask.
- Maybe.
I suppose so.
- To be 21 again.
Starting over in New York City.
God, things I'd do differently.
- I can only imagine.
- You know, our imaginations
can take us anywhere.
Somehow dragging our physical bodies
along with us in the process.
Hey, hey, you can chop
those up a lot finer, here.
Now roll your knife.
(knife swishing)
You know, Beetle,
I've been thinking a lot about
your family this afternoon.
- My family?
- Your mother in particular.
Oh! What time is it?
Shit, I gotta run out for a few minutes.
- What about my mother?
- I wanna found out a little bit more
about her, that's all.
- Now?
- That'd be rather hard
to do now, wouldn't it?
Yeah, well hey, I just need
to run out for an errand.
Oh, God, what happened to that invoice
from your good bud Arlis?
- What invoice?
- You know Arlis the plumber?
Where's the invoice?
I want to drop off his pay today.
- In this weather?
No, wait 'til Monday.
- When do you expect me to pay him?
Before Monday I'd imagine.
- I don't know, perhaps.
- So it wouldn't be ethical for me
to keep him waiting on
account of a little rain.
- I guess not.
I think it's at the desk.
- Let's go check.
- It must be here some place.
Maybe the wind blew it.
- Maybe.
It'll turn up sooner or later.
How much was it?
(dark eerie music)
Which way?
- [Beetle] Take the next
left and go on up to the top.
- You know, one thing
that I've learned that
you might not have picked
up on yet at your age
is never to underestimate anybody.
That's the most brilliant thing about
the human condition and human behavior.
Try as you may, you
can never truly predict
the reactions of another
mortal. (chuckling)
That's exactly what I'm
doing right now, isn't it?
Assuming that you can predict my behavior.
Well, did you, Beetle?
Did you guess my next move?
Did you know I spent my entire career
working alongside games
and players just like you?
Did you know that I often won?
'Til that last battle.
Manny Knowles, you know about that.
I guess after so much
betrayal and humiliation,
I just didn't want to play anymore.
Lost my hope, I guess,
well, you know what happened after that.
Tried to off myself.
Tried to die.
Not today, though.
I like this game too much.
Did you predict that, Beetle?
- I think you're losing
your grip on reality, Grady,
I really do.
You're making me very nervous.
- Why?
You think I'm gonna try
to touch you or something?
- It's on the left.
- Huh?
- His place is on the left.
(brakes squeak)
- Well, come on.
He's your friend.
(knocking)
Hey Arlis.
Sorry to just drop in like this,
but we got some money for you
and some beer if you like.
- Well don't just stand there
letting the cold in,
come on in.
- I sure do apologize for not being there
when you were working yesterday, Arlis.
- It's alright, I guess.
- I just wanna say that
when you came--
- But Beetle here
insisted on coming with me tonight,
see, he feels real bad, don't you?
Don't worry, he'll understand.
See, Beetle feels bad on account of
he lost your invoice.
Seems the wind blew it off somehow.
He never gave it to me.
- Is that right, son?
- Well, it was there waiting for him,
I guess the wind took it.
- Anyway, he wanted to apologize
for putting you and I
in an awkward position.
Is there some way I can make it up to you?
- The beer and the check is just fine.
Accidents do happen, I suppose.
- Yeah.
We should be going.
Got a bunch of folks back at the lodge
waiting on supper.
Come on, bud, we got
hungry guests to feed.
Chop chop!
I couldn't have done any
of this without Beetle.
To Beetle.
- [Karen] What's this
other plate here for?
- Oh God, I thought for
sure she'd be here by now.
- [Andy] She who?
- Beetle's mom.
Can't imagine what's keeping her.
I ran into her in town today.
Now before you say anything, buddy,
I want you to know,
we had a nice talk,
I told her all about your successes
and your new friends,
and she just wanted to stop in and see you
before, you know.
- Before what?
- Before he moves to the big city
and starts his life as an actor
thanks to his new agent Karen.
- Well, I did offer to help
if that's what he wanted.
- Well, it is.
We talked at length about his future.
Good call, Karen.
He's got what it takes.
Maybe even more than I did.
Boy, your mom couldn't have
been prouder of you today.
She's a nice woman,
I see where you get your charm.
She just wanted to see
you and know you're okay.
- I didn't know you even knew her name.
- Sure I do.
It's Carla May.
Carla May Hobbs.
Let's start without Carla May.
(dark mystery music)
I never met a Pentecostal before.
Carla May is Pentecostal.
You handled live snakes in
your prayer services, right?
- Snakes?
- We did a couple of times.
- [Karen] Did you handle a snake?
- Once.
- [Karen] What happened?
- I didn't get bit.
- Wow, you're one of the Lord's chosen.
If you handle a snake in
church and it doesn't kill you,
you're one of God's chosen few.
- Congratulations.
(dark mystery music)
(hissing)
- Clear the left sink,
scrape, put the dishes in to soak
for a couple of minutes
before you scrub them.
What, it'll make cleaning easier.
You're doing well.
- Not doing much of anything.
- Exactly.
That's the way I like it.
Oh, where you going?
- Collecting the rest of the dirty dishes.
- Nah, you stay put, I'll do it for you.
Don't forget those pots
and pans over there.
(dishes clanging)
(rhythmic music)
Yes, it's a much nicer room,
only 35 more a night.
Great.
Alright, bye-bye.
- Grady.
Come sit with us for a second.
- Sorry, work is never done here.
- We want to talk to you.
- Sounds like trouble.
- [Karen] Oh no, not at all.
- Is this act for real?
- Act?
- We have a ticket for
you to come with us.
I mean just for a couple of days,
you know, see your doctor,
make sure everything's okay.
- Look, you don't have
to sell me on the trip,
I'm cooperating.
Beetle can manage while I'm gone.
- Or it is a slow season,
you could just close up.
- Beetle can manage.
After tonight I'll go with you
wherever you want me to go.
Oh, dishes done, Beetle?
- [Beetle] Yes, sir.
- Great, would you care to join us?
Hey, while you're up,
could you put another log on the fire?
Ooh, looks like we're out of wood.
I'm gonna have to go up to the barn
and split some more.
Come on, Beetle.
- I'll help you.
- No, no, no, no,
you're a guest, you sit
and you enjoy your beer.
Come on.
- Beetle, keep an eye on him,
something's not right.
- [Grady] Beetle!
(dark eerie music)
- What are we doing here?
I thought we were going to
the barn and get fire wood?
- I want to show you something first.
- Let's talk hypothetically for a second.
If you were a good-looking poor kid
with a decent head on your shoulders
and absolutely no morals,
what would you do?
- I'd find a gullible
new guy in town and...
Try and take over his life.
- What's all that supposed to prove?
- Don't you know better
than to mess with a guy
who has nothing to lose?
- There you go again.
Not appreciating everything
you've been handed.
- Handed. Handed?
Is that what you think?
Everything comes with a price.
- What would you know about that?
- I know that you killed your mother.
You made it look like suicide.
That's what you do, right?
What did Carla May do?
Catch you dealing,
threaten to turn you in?
- She had it coming.
You'll never prove anything,
who'd ever believe I'd
do something like that?
- I would.
- [Grady] Threaten to turn you in?
- [Beetle] She had it coming.
You'll never prove anything.
- I guess if no one shows us we're wrong,
man's destined to repeat his mistakes,
and that's exactly what
you're doing, Beetle.
Repeating your mistakes.
Police are onto you.
And all they need's a
little bit of evidence.
- There is nothing that Beetle has done
that's questionable.
It's all in Grady's head.
Tell me something that
Beetle has done wrong,
and I'll consider your theory.
- It's just that, a theory.
- If I die, at least I will
leave something behind,
it might even be in national reports.
What ever happened to Grady Wilson?
Tragic.
A victim of society
before the gay movement.
They might even consider me a hero.
- Hero?
Nah.
Tragic, yes, sir.
Homosexuals deny the Lord's path,
and His judgement--
- Your truth.
- Is a far a greater punishment
than I could ever give.
- Do you honestly believe that
God wants you to hate another man,
kill another man?
- You don't know my Lord.
- You don't either, Beetle.
You've committed every
sin in the name of God.
- God helps them that helps themselves.
And the proof is I've already won.
They're sending you to the hospital
and asked me to run the hotel.
- It's a lodge!
And you can't silence me forever.
- [Beetle] Can't I?
Compliments of Ms. Karen.
- I've set you up, Beetle.
I already talked to the police.
They're gonna be here any minute.
- I guess I better hurry then.
How many you think it'll take?
I got 30 here.
(sputters)
- That'll be 29 now.
- This will never work, Beetle.
- Of course it will!
Just come back with some fire wood,
tell them you were tired and went to bed,
and in the morning, you're dead.
Poor Grady, he was so weak.
(intercom ringing)
- [Woman] There's a huge tree down
at the bottom of the
hill on the main road,
there's no going in or out
unless you take the Tail of the Dragon
back into Knoxville.
- [Woman] Is that where
you came from, Knoxville?
(woman mumbles)
(radio beeps)
(suspenseful music)
(gun thuds)
- Well, a little bit of a blackout
never scared me, man.
- Here you go.
- Oh, thank you, that is so nice of you.
No really, don't you all go making a fuss.
(dark suspenseful music)
(grunting)
Where is Grady anyway?
- [Rye] He's out back chopping
fire wood with Beetle.
- I would not turn my back on that one.
Vile creature.
(thunder rumbling)
- Who is it?
- That's Grady.
(rain pattering)
(intense music)
Move him to 11 and set him on a bed.
(woman chatters)
- Do you have a pulse?
- [Andy] It's weak.
- Grady, Grady, talk to me.
- I'm gonna call for help.
- Grady, Grady, come on, bud.
Grady, no.
Grady.
- [Karen] Grady.
- He forced some pills.
- [Rye] You can still roll over.
- [Woman] What can I do?
- Go help Andy.
(Grady gagging)
- [Grady] He's got my gun.
(gasps)
- [Beetle] Did I scare you, Ms. Roslyn?
- You hurt Grady, didn't you?
- I didn't hurt anybody.
I've been chopping wood.
What's wrong?
- I'm tired of loving youth
and kings of deception.
- What are we gonna do?
- Um, it'll be okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
- Damn it.
Got no phone reception!
Roslyn, can I try yours?
Hello.
- [Beetle] Andy.
What the heck's going on?
- I was hoping you could tell me.
- [Karen] Andy, come quickly!
- [Rye] He's gone.
- Grady.
Grady.
- Our Father which art in heaven,
hollowed be thy name,
thy kingdom come, thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven,
give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
that trespass against us
and lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil--
- They're getting smaller.
- What's getting smaller?
- For thine is the kingdom.
- [Grady] The blue pills are shrinking.
- The glory forever and ever, amen.
(dark suspenseful music)
- You did this, you son of a bitch!
- Stop, stop! No!
Don't be ridiculous!
We tried to do everything that we could!
I don't know exactly how this happened,
but we tried to get the pills out of him,
and it was an overdose.
It was another overdose.
There was just too many.
- [Rye] If you were a
good-looking poor kid
with absolutely no
morals, what would you do?
- Thank you for that
lovely prayer, dear boy.
- Roslyn.
Where's Roslyn?
- [Roslyn] I wouldn't
turn my back on that boy.
Vile creature.
- [Grady] Everything will make sense.
Tomorrow morning with you whenever.
- [Andy] Roslyn!
Her car's still here!
(echoed voice chattering)
(suspenseful music intensifies)
- [Karen] Beetle!
Beetle, wait.
- What, Ms. Karen?
(body clattering)
- Oh my God.
(grunting)
(foot thudding)
(gentle guitar music)
- I don't think we have much time left.
- If you grab it all, I've got this.
- The storm took down the whole tree
at the Monouth Pass.
No one was getting or out
'til we got a crane on it.
- Well, I'm glad you're here now.
And hopefully the phones
will be back on soon, too.
- So help me out, Mr. Wilson.
You called the station last night
saying this kid was up to no good.
- Yes, I did.
- [Office] And a few hours later,
he's dead at the bottom of your stairs.
- So sad, isn't it?
I mean, he had such potential.
- You say the boy stayed
in the room with the flags?
- Yeah, room five, just for the weekend.
- Found a mess of drugs and
empty wallet in the vent.
- It appears you were correct, Mr. Wilson.
We'll run a toxicology on Wallace Hobbs,
it appears drugs may have
played a role in his accident.
(engine revving)
- Be happy.
- You too.
(lighthearted music)
Excuse me, miss.
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me!
You're wearing earphones.
- Yeah.
- I'm Grady.
- [Woman] Marcia.
- I see you walking every day,
I just wanted to say hi
and extend an invitation for you to visit
for coffee or water, you know, hydrate.
It gets lonely up here,
and I'd like to get to know my neighbors.
- That's nice.
Another day.
We'll see you later, Grady.
You have a really nice aura.
(chuckles)
("On My Feet Again" by Ken Will Morton)
- I don't know what to say.
- You don't have to say anything.
♫ Maybe I'm a little slow
♫ Maybe my skin's too thin
- Listen.
I left something on your mattress
to get through the slow season.
- What?
- It's waiting for you.
♫ I may not understand the rules
♫ So I might look like a fool to you
♫ I still carry myself around
♫ Despite your ridicule
♫ If you look me over and feel like
♫ You haven't seen much yet
♫ You might be right,
I'm someone to forget
♫ If you’re like me and a
storm is ragin’ from within
♫ Remember you can’t sail without the wind
♫ Through the opening
♫ That’ll send us over to a new beginning
♫ And we’ll get back up
♫ On our feet again
♫ Now if what I’m sayin’
sounds a little glib
♫ Then you don’t know the way I live
♫ Although it’s on my own terms
♫ I’ve got a lot to learn
♫ There’s always someone who’ll sing
♫ Sweeter and more in key
♫ You can look to them
but all I have is me
♫ If it’s true that nothing’s
born without some pain
♫ And nothing grows without the rain
♫ It’s finally sinking in
♫ I’ll pour myself over to a new beginning
♫ And I’ll get back up
♫ On my feet again
♫ I might need a helping hand
♫ When it gets hard for me to stand
♫ If you can’t help to lift me up
♫ Maybe someone else can
♫ I might get lost along the way
♫ To happiness there is no map
♫ You can offer up directions
♫ But I’ll make my own path
♫ To where we’re going
♫ And only then I’ll get
back on my feet again