(classical music)
- [Radio] What are you, bored?
Are we doing this? You
gotta be kiddin' me.
Wait for it. Ah,
oh my fuckin' God.
It's also, oh my fuckin' God,
what's wrong with you people?
It's time for OMFG,
Oh My Fuckin' God.
- [Radio] A 26-year-old
dairy man near Hanford,
about 30 miles South of Fresno
is replacing the fields
of corn and wheat he grows
to feed his cows with a
heartier wheat and rye hybrid
better suited for drought.
He's also working
with an engineer
to create a cow motion sensor.
The system, deployed
in his animal stalls,
would change...
(water rushing)
- [Mark] I never come here.
- [Jonah] You should,
it's so close.
- [Mark] I know.
It's beautiful here.
I kinda like you a lot.
- I kinda like you too.
- Good.
You better.
- Okay.
(laughing)
Hey.
Kiss me
like you just got
back from the war.
- What?
(alarm beeps)
- [Jonah] Babe.
Come on, can you...
Jesus, we talked about
the fucking snooze button.
- I'm sorry.
Hey.
Happy birthday.
- [Mark] No.
- Mmhm.
- [Mark] I wasn't born until
like, 6 o'clock at night.
- Hey.
Hey.
- What?
- I'll be right back, I
gotta run some errands.
- Take your time.
- [Jonah] I love you too.
(phone buzzes)
(he speaks in German)
- Let's try that last one again.
Not quite so evil.
- They're Nazi's right?
- Yeah. Just, you know.
- Okay.
- [Man] It's a
computer game for kids,
client wants to keep
it pretty mellow.
- Mellow Nazi, got it.
(he speaks in German)
- [Man] Great, see what I mean?
- Totally.
- Okay, so now just do
some of the death sounds
on the next page.
(he grunts)
Wait for my signal.
Just skip to the bottom for the
being electrocuted part.
- Um, I'm not sure
how to do the um,
falling down a
cliff while on fire.
- I don't know, I
didn't write it.
You're the actor,
just make a choice.
- Beautiful.
(he moans)
- Great, thank you.
- [Radio] Possibility that
all dinosaurs had feathers,
not just the later
ones that became birds.
Today's guest has an
article in science
about that new find
and the many questions
that come along with...
- [Radio] We know that
birds are dinosaurs,
but when did dinosaurs
start becoming birds?
- You guys gonna
stick with cocktails
or get wine or?
- Wine makes you
tired, remember?
- [Nicole] Wait, whatever
happened to that movie?
Did you hear?
- Nope, still have a pin in me.
- [Nicole] That's awesome.
- [Jonah] He's totally
gonna get this one.
- You keep saying that babe.
- So, what's new with you two?
- Umm, we are taking
a little hiatus.
- [Craig] Jesus Christ.
- [Nicole] What? I just,
I want to enjoy dinner.
- You're doing what?
- We're taking a little hiatus.
- Like a break?
- Sort of.
I mean, we were both
just a little crazy
with the wedding
coming up so soon, so.
- [Craig] We just thought
it'd be a good idea to
play the field one
last time, ya know?
- How little?
- Like three months.
Don't ask, don't tell, you know?
- That makes no fucking sense.
- Awkward.
- Sure, why the hell not.
Knock yourselves out.
- Seriously?
- What do we know?
Stop.
- Come here.
(he sighs)
- What's your name?
- Tequila is not your friend.
- That's a weird fucking name.
- You want some water?
- No, come here.
I was watching you
from over there.
It's your first night here, huh?
- Babe, come on.
- You come on. You're
such a fucking buzzkill.
- Just you and me, okay?
- Imagine you're a straight guy.
- Imagine there's
this guy, Mark,
and it's his birthday.
And he and his boyfriend, Jonah,
are gonna have some
really great birthday sex.
- My birthday's over.
- [Jonah] Hey,
let's make a baby.
- Stop.
- [Jonah] Don't be an asshole.
- Jonah, come here.
- What?
- You're a straight
guy at a video store
and you're browsing.
- [Jonah] I'm not
doing that right now.
- Come on.
- No.
I don't go to video
stores anyway.
- I'm sure there's
one somewhere.
What's your name?
- Babe, seriously.
- Okay, fuck.
Let's just jerk off.
(moaning)
Oh baby.
Oh fuck. Oh, oh, fuck.
(vomiting)
- So this guy, trying
to be a good pet owner,
he takes his dog to the
vet to get his shots,
to get his shots or whatever,
then examines the dog.
It isn't a dog at all.
It's a ferret that was fed
steroids to look like a poodle.
Get outta here.
Get outta here!
- [Radio] I mean, does this
thing even look like a poodle?
No, absolutely not.
- Does it, I mean, does
it look like a poodle?
- [Radio] I got some
photos up on the website.
This guy with his 800 dollars.
- No way, it looks like
a rat with a wig on.
- [Radio] That is a great
business idea, right?
Oh yeah, it's genius.
- Get outta here.
(watch beeps)
- [Phone] Global Talent.
- Hi, may I speak
with Rick please?
- [Phone] He's not
in, who's calling?
- Mark Miller. Could you
have him call me back?
- [Phone] He prefers email.
- Okay, well I did
email him twice,
which is why I'm calling.
- [Phone] Well, just
email him again.
He's had a crazy week.
- Okay, I'll do that, thank you.
- [Phone] Okay. Bye bye.
- Jesus Christ.
(classical music)
Do you want some salad?
Jonah.
- Yeah?
- [Mark] Do you want some salad?
- What are you putting in it?
- Fucking salad.
- [Jonah] Yeah.
- I got avocados.
- [Jonah] Okay,
yeah I'll have some.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- My step-mom
called again today.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
Not gonna leave me alone
with the Christmas stuff.
Are you sure you don't wanna
go there for Christmas?
- Absolutely not.
- Got it.
- They're insane.
- They're my family.
- Okay.
- That's a lot of pills.
- It's just supplements.
They're all natural.
- [Mark] And are they working?
Are you feeling any better?
- Yeah.
- [Jonah] Okay.
- I'm just stressed.
- [Jonah] About what?
- I don't know. You
know, everything?
- What'd you mean
the other night
at the restaurant when you
said, "What do we know?"
- Huh?
- The other night
at the restaurant,
you said, "What do we
know about anything?"
- Oh.
- [Jonah] Yeah.
- I don't know. What do we
know about their relationship?
Relationships are messy.
- So, we're fine, right?
- Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, why?
- I dunno.
I just miss talking to you.
- We're talking
right now, aren't we?
- Yeah. Yeah, we are.
You know what, you
don't have to stop
what you're doing right
now, I'm sure you've got
lots of stuff to
do and everything.
- No, no, I'm good.
- Okay.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- I'm good. How are you?
- I'm good.
- So, what do you
wanna do for Christmas?
- I dunno.
- Could go to Mexico again.
- Yeah, that sounds nice.
- Yeah?
(crickets chirp)
- [Jonah] Goodnight.
- [Mark] Goodnight.
Can you lay on top
of me for a bit?
- Yeah.
- Just make yourself
really heavy here.
- [Jonah] Okay.
How's that?
- Do you think I'm masculine?
- Yeah, of course. Why?
- I dunno.
It's just to know what
I'm missing, you know.
- With video chat apps
and the Neptune Two's
front-facing camera,
(phone buzzes)
with video chats,
chaps, video apps.
With video chat and the
Neptune Two's, Jesus Christ...
Video chat apps and
the Neptune Two's
front-facing camera, you
can chat face to face
with friends and family.
Chat face to face to
family and friends,
with the Neptune Two's
front-facing camera.
Neptune Two's front
facing camera.
(phone buzzes)
(turn signal clicks)
- [Mark] I never come here.
- You should.
It's so close.
- I know.
It's really beautiful here.
I kind of like you a lot.
- [Jonah] I kind
of like you too.
(phone buzzes)
- Shit.
(door buzzes)
- [Woman] TTM?
- [Mark] Yeah, hi, Mark
Miller, I have an audition.
- [Woman] They're at lunch.
- [Mark] When are
they coming back?
- [Woman] Actually,
they're done for the day.
They auditions
ended an hour ago.
- [Mark] Gotcha.
(phone buzzes)
(he sighs)
(smashing)
- [Mark] Fuck!
Jesus fucking Christ!
I'm such a fucking asshole.
Fuck.
- Are you okay?
- What?
Yeah, I got it.
- All right.
Do you have a minute?
- Yeah?
- Hi.
- I'm sorry, who are you?
- Emily, second floor, creative.
- Still nothing.
- Elevator, you spilled coffee
on my dress, beige dress,
said if I ever needed--
- Yes, the elevator,
beige dress,
low up top, high down
below, Melanie, hi.
- Emily.
- Yeah, I know.
- Well, I have submitted
requests for a raise,
but it's been--
- You know, here's the thing
about people saying anything,
didn't really mean anything.
- Really?
- True story, so, if
there's anything else
that you need?
- No, just that raise.
- A kiss?
- A what?
- You know, those things,
they make everything
suddenly better.
- You don't have an
assistant for that?
- He's not my type. (laughs)
- Would it help with my raise?
- Let's just say
it couldn't hurt.
- Okay, I'll take
a kiss, I guess.
I'm good from here, thank you.
- What, you don't
want to kiss me?
- What? No.
I'm not going to kiss
anybody in the audition,
I'm just gonna, you
know, just fake it.
- Come on, we never
make out any more.
- Okay, so we're in a no
kissing phase then I guess.
- Oh really? How long is
that phase going to last?
- [Mark] I dunno.
- Do you like me?
- Huh?
- Not a trick question,
do you like me?
- Yes.
Why would you ask that?
- Because I can't tell.
Wow, that was amazing.
- Sorry. Come here.
- Mark?
- Hmm?
- You know,
like a year ago when you stopped
taking your medication?
You told me if you
ever acted weird or...
That I should let you know?
- Mmhm.
- I'm letting you know.
I just think you
should think about it.
- [Nicole] God, I fucking
love being single.
- We're calling it that now?
- Calling it bookends I guess.
- Looks good.
- What? Don't be judgey.
This is the only way
I'm gonna be sure
that I'm not gonna make a
huge mistake when I say I do.,
God, what is it about those
words that make me wanna puke.
Seriously, I lost seven pounds.
There's like, nothing
like a relationship
to make you fuck up your body.
- You're ridiculous.
- I'm seeing the comic tonight.
- Single Sam?
- I know.
I might love him.
Our chemistry's insane.
- Go ahead then.
- Well, I will.
I dunno, I just think
he's like the one guy
I've always just kind
of wondered, what if.
- How's Greg doing?
- I don't know, we don't
really talk about it,
he hasn't asked.
Why, did you see him?
- No.
Is he dating anybody?
- [Nicole] I want him
to. He's too nice.
- Oh, that word.
- What?
- Nice.
- Jonah thinks if we can
just go back to the beginning
everything will be all right.
- [Nicole] Because you're
the jerk and he's the victim.
People always put you in that
role, it's very convenient.
For what it's worth, you
know, my friend Emily
has this therapist
that she loves.
Totally turned shit
around for her.
You want me to get her number?
- I dunno.
Maybe.
(Eva talks in Spanish)
- [Eva] There's no more bleach.
- [Mark] What?
- Bleach. Can you buy
more bleach for next time?
- Mmhm. Maybe we can use
a little bit less though?
I don't like inhaling
all that stuff.
- Sorry?
- Oh, no, never mind.
Hey, Eva?
- [Eva] Yes?
- How are you?
- Fine, you?
- I'm good.
- How's Jonah?
- He's good, he's rehearsing
for this singing thing.
- He's so nice, Jonah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- [Eva] You're very nice too.
- Hi.
- [Mark] What?
- I said hi.
- Hi.
You want some of this?
- No, I'm good, thanks.
- How was rehearsal?
- It was good.
- Good.
I made an appointment
with a therapist for us.
- Why?
Are we breaking up?
- It's definitely one of
the possibilities, right?
- Oh, okay. Fuck.
- We can't just go back
to the beginning, Jonah.
Yeah, no, you're right.
Okay, thanks for doing that.
- [Mark] Yeah, it's
Thursday at 11.
- What seems to be
the biggest issue?
- Well, we haven't been
very affectionate lately.
We don't talk about
things much any more
and, yeah, we kind
of do our own thing
which isn't what I want.
- What do you want Jonah?
- I want us to act like
a couple like we used to.
Have fun again, I mean,
otherwise, what's the point?
- But I mean, we can't just go
back to the beginning, right?
That's unrealistic.
- Mark, do you feel like
you're looking for reasons
to get out of the relationship?
Or reasons to get into it?
- Well, I dunno.
- Think about it for a moment.
- Well, I'm here, so...
I wanna get in it.
I think.
- Good. Otherwise it's just
a waste of our time, really.
- Yeah, like I said, I'm here.
- How'd you guys meet?
- We met at a bar.
- We were both
looking for a rebound.
- I mean, there's
more to it than that.
- Yes, I know that, it's just,
we had both just
broken up with someone.
- And?
- Nothing.
- How's your sex life?
- It's not really happening.
- Do you masturbate?
- We can't masturbate?
- Well, you jerk off a lot.
You do, you watch a lot of porn.
- Okay.
- I'm not saying I
don't, I'm just, I dunno.
I'm saying, when I do,
I think about us, you.
- You do?
- Wow.
- Do me a favor, get up.
- Right now?
- Yes, stand up and
embrace one another.
Just breathe together
for a moment.
- [Mark] I never come here.
- You should, it's so close.
- I know.
- I'm cold.
- [Therapist] How'd that feel?
- I um, it was...
I dunno.
- It's green.
You all right?
- Yeah, why?
(Jonah hums)
How do you do it?
- What?
- You're just always
in a good mood.
- Hah, I don't know.
It depends on what
you focus on, I guess.
- Right.
I just think we're different.
- [Phone] You have reached the
office of Dr. Grey Wintrow.
You may interrupt this
message at any time
by pressing the pound key.
If you are reaching
us during lunch,
please call back
after 1 o'clock.
Thank you.
(phone beeps)
- [Mark] Hi, this
is Mark Miller,
I was a patient of
yours a few years ago.
I wanted to see
if I could come in
for a medication appointment
as soon as possible.
My number is 310-852-7--
(water rushing)
(slow, ominous music)
(beeping)
- Mark!
Hey, what's up?
You live around here?
- [Mark] Yeah, up on Beachwood.
- Very cool.
Mm, we're practically neighbors.
I live by Larchmont.
- [Mark] No way? How you been?
- I've been good.
I'm on my way to a
fitting for this film,
it's a really cool part.
I'm playing a solder with
post traumatic stress...
Whatever.
- Stress disorder, yeah.
- Yeah.
I had to go in for
it like, four times,
it's been an emotional
roller coaster, you know?
Soon as you feel like you're
losing your mind, right?
- Yeah.
I went in for that, actually.
Be crazy if we got to
work together, huh?
- Yeah, well, they're
shooting the there tomorrow,
so pretty sure it's all cast.
- Gotcha.
- We should hang
sometime though.
- Yeah, it sounds good.
- Neighbor.
You have the same number?
- Yep.
- And you're still
with the same guy?
- No.
- All right.
Good to see you.
- You too, I'll, I'll text you.
- Sounds good.
(phone buzzes)
(he breathes heavily)
- Think about when you
were newly in love.
What were the kinds of things
you would do for each other,
you know, for no special reason,
just to make the other
person feel good.
On your sheet of paper,
I want you to complete
this sentence.
I used to feel loved
and cared about when you
held my hand as we
walked, for example,
or called me up just to tell
me how much you love me.
- You're kidding right?
- [Therapist] It's gonna
feel artificial at first.
- Yeah, you think?
- All right, you're an actor?
Think of it like make-believe.
Putting the cart in
front of the horse,
eventually you will
feel an inner shift.
- I dunno.
- You don't?
- What?
- [Therapist] Humor me.
What do you have to lose?
- Do you need this here?
- No, go ahead.
That's subtle.
- Really?
- What?
- Nothing.
- I'm just saying that
was really obvious,
I didn't say...
- At least I'm making
an effort, are you?
- Okay.
- It's all you got?
- You don't think these
exercises are ridiculous?
I didn't say I didn't like it.
Yeah, I'm an asshole,
what else is new.
Dammit.
- [Mark] Hey.
- Hi.
- [Mark] How are you?
- I'm good, how are you?
- [Mark] Good.
Do you got a minute?
- Yeah, sure.
What's up?
- I wanted to apologize.
- For what?
- Everything?
Seriously, it must be
fucking crazy being with me.
I'm really sorry for all the
stuff I'm putting you through.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, why?
- [Jonah] I dunno.
- Started taking
this new medication.
- You did? Why
didn't you tell me?
- Because I'm me, I
suck, I dunno. Sorry.
But I was thinking, let's
have a date night tonight.
Why not?
I was gonna go get
some champagne.
- Okay.
- [Mark] Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Awesome.
I'll see you later?
- Yeah, I'll be here.
(buzzing)
- Fuck.
Um, it's okay.
(electronic music)
Come on, dance with me.
- This is weird.
- It's only gonna get worse.
The longer you wait, the more
embarrassing it's gonna be.
Come on!
Oh yeah.
Hey.
- Hello.
- You smell nice.
- [Jonah] So do you.
- I'm gonna change
the music, okay?
- Okay.
- You come here often?
- Really?
- I don't really
like leather bars
but I hear they got
good beers on tap.
- Yeah, yeah, they
got good tap beers.
I'm Jonah.
- Mark.
You're hot.
- I'm pretty average.
- If you say so.
- I'm like a six, but I own
it, so that makes me a seven.
You're like an eight
who thinks he's a ten,
so that knocks you
down to a seven.
- Fucking perfect, then.
You wanna get some shots?
- Yeah.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
- Don't move.
Seriously, do not move.
They ran out of limes.
- What do you expect
from a leather bar?
- Seriously.
To us.
Just play the song, please.
- Okay, okay.
? Driving down lonely road.
? A thousand people beside me.
? Walking down crowded street.
? And all I hear is your feet.
? Traffic stop, I'm on my own.
? Today you you called my phone
? alone, alone, alone, alone.
? A thousand miles
and maybe three.
? And I just need
you close to me.
? And is this it,
and is this all?
? Young love will always fall.
? But you can't help but fall
? we fell the right,
? your eyes, the night,
? I lay on you,
? The hill, the moon,
? the smoke, the room,
? the way your made me feel. ?
- That was amazing.
You're so beautiful.
- I feel weird.
- Hmm?
- I dunno.
- Good weird or bad weird?
- Don't be mad.
- What?
- Remember how you said
you want to do ecstasy
again sometime?
- What are you talking about?
- Well, remember that barbecue
we were at at Silver Lake,
and we did E, and
it was amazing.
- Shut the fuck up,
are you kidding me?
What the fuck?
- I just wanted
tonight to be good.
- [Jonah] I have
rehearsal in the morning,
are you fucking crazy?
Fuck.
- I'm sorry.
- [Jonah] Am I good
looking enough for you?
- [Mark] What are you talking
about? You're beautiful.
- [Jonah] I dunno.
Sounds like all your exes
are very different types.
- [Mark] You're perfect.
Fuck them.
- [Jonah] Okay.
- Can I ask you something?
- Yeah.
- You don't really like
sucking my dick, huh?
- I don't know.
Yeah, I guess it's just
not really my thing.
- It's because I'm uncut?
- What? No.
- I know it's kind of weird.
- No it's not, it's natural.
It's the way it's
meant to be, right?
I like your turtleneck.
- Oh my god.
- [Jonah] I can't
believe you drugged me.
- I know, I'm sorry.
- [Jonah] You know
that's like, crazy right?
- I just wanted tonight
to be, you know.
- [Jonah] Yeah, I know.
I am so high.
Hey.
- [Mark] Hmm?
- [Jonah] Let's get naked.
- [Mark] Okay. Yeah.
- [Jonah] I wanna
be naked with you.
- [Mark] Do you remember
when we started dating,
and I twisted my ankle?
I couldn't even walk.
You drove all the
way to my house,
took me to the doctor,
drove me back home,
and got me Thai food.
It was so sweet.
And that's when I knew.
- [Jonah] You know what I
remember about that day?
On the way back
from the hospital,
you put your seat
all the way back
and closed your eyes for a bit.
It was so beautiful.
Like you really trusted me.
- [Mark] Hey, whatever
happens happens, okay?
(classical music)
(distorted humming)
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
- [Phone] You have reached
the office of Dr. Grey Wintrow.
You may interrupt this
message at any time
by pressing the pound key.
- Doctor Wintrow
this is Mark Miller,
it's on the fourth day of the...
I'm not doing so good,
so if you could call
me back whenever--
- Mark.
Mark!
- What? No.
These new meds, my
fucking head, it's just...
- Okay, okay, what can I do?
Mark!
Hey, you wanna go
lie down on the bed?
- There's this sound in my head,
it's just fucking crazy.
- How about some tea?
You want some tea?
- I don't want any
fucking tea, Jonah.
- All right, all
right, fuck the tea.
Here give me your
hand, come here.
Look at me, look at me.
Hey, you're going to
be okay, all right?
Everything's going to be fine.
I'm gonna be right back,
I think we have some Xanax
leftover somewhere.
- I just wanna be alone.
- [Jonah] I'm not gonna
leave you like this,
you're gonna take the
Xanax, or I'm calling 911.
How's that?
- Thank you .
- [Therapist] How was your week?
- It was a fucking mess.
I tried out a different
antidepressant,
and I had a full-blown
panic attack.
It took me two days
to get back to normal
whatever the fuck that is.
- Maybe...
What if you went
back on that stuff
that you were on
when I first met you?
You remember that?
- Yeah, that's
definitely an option.
- You seemed happy then.
- Basically, I have a
lot of fucking shame
taking this stuff.
I feel like I need to be
able to do it on my own.
- Did you try doing
any of those exercises?
- Yeah, we wrote each
other Post-it notes,
and he put his
arm round me once.
- None of that felt good to you?
- I'm not saying that it
didn't feel good, it's just...
- Mark, how about you
share some appreciations
with Jonah.
Pick a couple of things
that Jonah did this week
that made you feel appreciated.
- No, I just don't.
- Take your time.
- No.
I know you have this
system, and you know,
doing these exercises,
it's hard for me.
- We had a really fucking
romantic date night.
- We were high.
- Yeah, because you drugged me.
- I just feel like
I'm banging my head
against the wrong wall.
- [Therapist] What do you mean?
- Maybe you should be with
someone more like you,
and maybe I need--
I can't get to where
you need me to be, okay?
We're spending all
this fucking money
doing all these exercises and,
maybe we're not
right for each other.
Maybe I just don't
love you any more.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to--
- No.
- [Radio] But first, cousin
Charles was infatuated with her,
and they became secretly
engaged before he left
in 1642 to serve in the army
in Germany for three years.
Christina revealed
in her autobiography
that she felt an insurmountable
distaste for marriage,
and an insurmountable distaste
for all the things that
females talked about and did.
She slept for
three hours a night
and was chiefly occupied
with her studies.
(distorted drums)
(doorbell rings)
- [Kyle] Want
another drink, babe?
- Sure.
How long have you lived here?
- [Kyle] A couple of years,
it's my buddy's parents' place.
I made this one kind of strong.
- Perfect, thanks.
How have you been?
- Good.
You?
- Mmhm, really good.
- I know.
Just kidding, I, thanks a lot.
I better look good, I've
been working out twice a day.
- Twice a day, huh?
- Yeah, getting
ready for this movie.
- Right, right.
(porn plays from indoors)
Do you mind if we turn that off?
- Oh, you don't like porn?
- I do, it's just,
it's weird. It's weird.
- Is it--
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Hi.
- Um, hi.
What are you doing?
- What?
- You're holding my hand.
- Uh, yeah.
- So?
- I still...
I still think of you sometimes.
- Really?
- Mmhm.
- How about you?
- This is a hook up, right?
Let's hook up.
- [Nicole] He met someone.
- He tell you that?
- [Nicole] Nope, I saw them.
- Doing what?
- [Nicole] Having dinner at
some restaurant on 3rd Street.
- It doesn't have
to mean anything.
- [Nicole] Then they
made out in his car.
She's like, 40.
You know, he's
always had this thing
for women in their late 40s?
I can't compete with
that, thank god.
But whatever, if that's
his, then that's his thing.
- You should talk to him.
- Are you kidding? You
know, this is my idea.
I just cannot leave shit alone.
Fuck, I'm so sorry,
how is Jonah?
- He's good.
No, we're good.
- Eva, I have your stuff.
- [Eva] Okay.
- Forgot to bring it yesterday.
What's up?
- She was waiting outside.
- Hello Markus.
- Isabelle?
(he sobs)
- [Man] Name?
- Miller, Mark.
- [Man] There you are.
All right, here we go,
tell us your name, sir?
- Hi, Mark Miller.
- [Man] And, hands, please?
Profiles.
You were here for
the explanation?
- [Mark] Yes.
- Okay, here we go.
So, you're gonna start in
the corner of the room,
you're gonna walk in, speak
directly to the camera,
real friendly.
- Hi, I'm your online
concierge, where may I take you?
- All right, let's do
one that's real warm.
- Hi, I'm your online
concierge, where may I take you?
- Okay, just talk to me.
And, here we go, and...
- Hi, I'm your online
concierge, where may I take you?
- [Man] Okay, can we pick up
the energy, just a little bit?
Corner, corner.
- You know what, I'm good.
- [Man] What?
- I'm good.
- [Man] I gotta keep moving.
- Okay.
Listen, I know that
this is what you do,
and you're very nice, I
don't wanna offend you,
it's just...
It just didn't work
for us, for me.
- [Therapist] I'm very
sorry to hear that.
- You're so full of shit.
- I'm so sorry, Jonah.
You're a really
kind, amazing man.
I've never met anybody with
a bigger heart than you.
Fuck, you deserve someone
who doesn't have to work
so fucking hard
to be nice to you,
who likes being in the
same room with you.
I'm not that person.
I'm not.
I'm never going to be.
Thank you.
- For?
- I dunno.
Just thank you.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Come on.
Okay.
(phone buzzes)
(phone rings)
- It's good.
- Told you.
- Hey.
Hey.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- I'm good, how are you?
- Good.
- I thought you weren't coming.
- Changed my mind.
Come on, I'd never
hear the end of it.
This is weird, huh?
- Yeah, a little.
It's good to see you.
- Me too.
Have you seen 'em yet?
- I saw Craig go upstairs
with a bottle of wine,
I think Nicole must be
panicking about something.
- Nicole panicking?
No way. (laughs)
- She said you're
not acting any more.
- Yeah.
Haven't enjoyed it in
a long time, you know?
- [Jonah] What are you gonna do?
- I have no idea.
You look good.
- Thank you.
- My father died.
A while ago.
I never told you.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, I...
- What is this?
- Open it.
- Mark, I don't know.
I'll read it later.
- Okay.
Dear Jonah,
this is a list, in
no particular order,
of some of the things that
I appreciate about you
and will never forget.
If you ever think of me
sometime in the future,
I hope you don't just
remember the bad moments,
but some of the beautiful
ones we shared as well.
I know I will.
Okay, like I said, in
no particular order...