♪♪
Come on, Polly.
Grandma, is it time yet?
I'm all ready to go.
[chuckling]
No, Em... not yet.
I told you
I would let you know
when it was time.
[sighing]
Yeah, yeah.
I know.
I just wanna go now!
Well, all great things come
with patience, right?
Now, hush up
and go play.
I will let you know
when it's time.
Come on.
Go make something
of this day.
[sighing]
Fine.
But, please,
make it go fast.
♪♪
[chimes ringing]
You look so pretty!
Like a little princess.
But... something's missing.
[Polly sneezes]
Aha!
Every princess needs
her tiara!
♪♪
[Polly snorting]
If I were a tiara...
where would I be?
[clatter]
Hey!
Found you!
♪♪
Should I open one?
"Briley."
[Lana McClain]
Cody, I told you
to take your laundry
to the cleaners
three hours ago!
You know if the place is closed,
you're just gonna have to go
to your audition tomorrow
in your underwear.
Please be too late!
I would love to see that.
Wait, I just pictured it,
and I changed my mind.
Ew!
Bryce, grow up.
I know plenty of girls
who would love to see that.
And, Mama, I got this.
I told you I would,
didn't I?
Yes.
I just don't understand
why you wait until
the very last second
to do everything.
You are literally
always late.
Mama, don't worry.
I got this.
[sighing]
Okay.
[mouths silently]
Bye.
[door closes]
I am so glad
I only had one of him.
[both chuckle]
♪♪
[keys jingling]
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wanda! Wanda, please!
Just take this last one
before you go.
Are you ever gonna
get here on time?
Once! Just once
would be nice.
Oh, come on, Wanda.
Where's the fun in that?
Tell you what.
If you take this,
I'll split whatever's
in the pockets with you.
Deal?
Ugh! Come on!
Bring it in and let's see
what we got this time.
[sighing]
Ooh.
Wow, you've really
outdone yourself.
Two pay stubs for parking,
a receipt for...
"The Method Actor Inside of Me"
with your signature?
And $4.37.
I'm rich.
Hey, that receipt
could be worth
a lot of money someday.
I heard a guy sold
George Clooney's signature
on a napkin for, like,
a million dollars.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, no, no, no.
Keep the change.
I'll take the signature,
Mr. Clooney.
[straining]
I'll have these for you
in the morning.
Oh, and I'm serious about
that signature thing,
by the way.
I'd hold on to that,
if I were you.
[Wanda Kim]
I'll frame it!
[chuckles]
♪♪
[sighing]
[bells jingle]
Hmm.
[humming melody softly]
Ooh.
[bells jingle]
♪♪
Hello?
Anyone there?
[giggles]
I don't bite.
[exhales softly]
Hi.
[chuckles]
Uh, I-I'm sorry.
I did-- I didn't mean
to stare or anything,
but... you look familiar.
Uh, have we met?
[chuckling]
Well, I don't know, mister.
I kinda can't see you
through this aisle.
Oh, right.
Uh...
[chuckles]
Oh! I'm so sorry.
My bad.
It's okay.
Um, I mean,
I don't--
I don't think
we've met before.
I'm-- I'm Briley.
And you are?
Oh! Um...
I'm Cody.
Yeah.
[chuckling]
Well, it's nice
to meet you, Cody.
Um, I hope
I see you around.
Yeah. Uh...
Hey, Briley?
Um, there's, like,
a bunch of us hanging out
at the pool later,
if you wanna come.
I mean, you totally
don't have to,
'cause I may not even go,
but... but, like, if I do,
you know, it-- it'd be cool
to see you there.
Yeah.
Yeah, I-- I'll go.
Awesome.
Okay, well,
I-I-I'll see you then.
Uh, right, this way.
Um... bye.
♪♪
Okay, well, I-I'm pretty sure
I just met my future wife.
Ooh!
Cody met a girl.
And did you
actually talk to her?
Yes, I talked to her.
In fact, I invited her
to a pool party later.
You didn't tell me about
a pool party.
I want to go
to a pool party, too.
Can I go with?
Please?
Mom, I-- I didn't tell you
about a pool party
because, well,
there isn't one.
I panicked.
It was the first thing
I could think of.
But I have a few hours.
I'm pretty sure
I can make it happen.
And, Bryce, no,
I can't take
my little sister
on a date with me.
That's not cool.
Doesn't sound like
a date to me.
Shut it.
Okay, Mom.
I'll be back
in a couple hours.
I have a party to plan.
Okay, don't stay out too late.
And, Cody?
Don't propose
on the first date.
Take a towel, and don't leave
your flip-flops at the pool,
and don't leave your towel
at the pool,
and don't leave your phone
at the pool.
You do have
your phone, right?
Yeah, right here.
Okay, bye, Mom.
Cody, you think you're
forgetting anything else?
Mom, wh-- what else could I
possibly be forgetting?
[sighing]
Swim trunks.
Jessie! Jessie!
Please, you gotta come
to my pool party later.
Dude, I'm allergic
to pool water.
You know this.
Please, come.
I'm sorry, man.
It's open mic
at karaoke tonight,
and my mom said
it could be good exposure.
Fine.
Felix!
Oh, hey, Cody.
Dude, come to
my pool party later.
Oh, I have to study and--
[sighing]
Come on!
Who can believe
not one person wanted
to come to a pool party?
And who gets discovered
at freaking Club House karaoke?
Unbelievable.
♪♪
Some pool party.
[titters]
Yeah, well,
you know me.
Love a great party.
There never really was
a party, was there?
Not exactly.
I did try
to plan one, though.
Apparently, attending
a last-minute pool party
designed to, you know,
impress a girl for me
wasn't high on everybody's
Tuesday night plans.
I see, so you were
trying to impress me?
[chuckling]
Well, I think you get
an "A" for effort.
I mean, this place
is really poppin'.
[chuckling]
So, are we gonna
do this or what?
[tittering]
Uh, okay, uh...
How about a walk?
Yeah.
Walk is good.
[Briley]
So, what's your thing?
Like, why are you
out here?
I mean, everybody here
has a thing.
Well, um,
I'm an actor.
Like most people
out here.
I moved here
four years ago
with my mom
and my little sister.
We were only supposed
to be here for a few months,
but then we just
kind of... stayed.
I picked up a few parts
here and there,
and we didn't really have
anywhere else to go,
so... this is home.
Wow.
Four years?
That's crazy.
Mm-hmm.
Have you been
in anything I've seen?
[chuckling]
Uh, well...
you may recognize me
as the young Mr. Metzel
from the very popular
Mr. Metzel's Pretzel
commercial franchise.
I knew that was you!
Yeah, yeah.
You did so good!
"There's no pretzel
like Mr. Metzel's pretzel."
[both]
"We'll bet our spatzle on it!"
[both laughing]
Okay, but what is
actually a spatzle?
'Cause I've always
wanted to know.
No, you don't.
You don't wanna know.
Well, oh.
[both laughing]
What about you?
What's your--
What's your story?
I mean, I'm sure
you're an actress.
You got the looks for it.
Well, yeah,
I'm an actress.
Mm-hmm.
That's actually why
I was here this week.
I was supposed to be doing
a chemistry read
for this musical show.
Mm-hmm.
But they ended up hiring
the lead's actual twin,
so...
Ooh.
Something like that,
you know?
Yeah, that's rough.
But musical though, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, singing's actually
my first passion.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I love acting,
but I just
really love singing.
That's why I was
so excited about this show
because I would be able to do
both my passions at once.
But you cannot compete
with somebody's
real-life twin.
[chuckling]
No.
Gotta love
show business.
Well, I would love
to hear you sing someday.
Well... maybe you will.
Wait, come on.
♪♪
What?
Well, don't just stand there.
Come on.
Okay.
♪♪
[Briley squeals and giggles]
[grunts]
♪♪
Okay, come on.
Ahh, I just love
the feeling of sand
between my toes.
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
I mean, I love the beach,
I love the ocean, all of it.
The beaches in New York
are nothing like
the ones out here.
I wish I could go.
You know the beach is only,
like, 20 minutes away, right?
Well, yeah, I know.
But I was only here
for a few days,
and my dad
hates the beach.
Mm.
Plus, we're staying
with friends,
and so I don't really have
a way to get around.
And...
I'm leaving to go back home
to New York tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Ugh.
[chuckles]
Do you know when
you'll be back?
Unfortunately, no.
My parents aren't
super supportive
of the whole acting thing,
and since this trip
turned out to be nothing,
I don't think they're
gonna be too excited
to get on a plane
back to L.A. anytime soon.
Yeah.
I mean,
it's hard enough
for them to take off work,
and then for me
not even to be able
to audition?
They just don't see
the point in any of it.
But acting.
Is that your only passion,
or is there something else
hiding in there?
[chuckles]
No, not really.
I mean, I like--
I like to write.
But it's not--
no, it's just for me
to get my thoughts out,
you know?
I mean, I haven't even shown
my mom or my sister, so...
But you'd show me?
No.
Especially not you.
That's embarrassing.
[both chuckling]
Okay, how about this?
Hmm?
You promise to write to me
while I'm gone,
and I will sing a song
for you when I get back.
You mean like letters?
Yeah.
I love letters.
They're so romantic.
[chuckles]
Okay. Okay.
But... I think
it's only fair
that you have to sing me
a song right now.
Right now?
Mm-hmm.
Wow, you are putting me
on the spot.
Okay.
♪ Somewhere
♪ Over the rainbow
♪ Way up high-- ♪
[woman]
Hey!
You kids aren't supposed--
Oh, no!
No. Go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
[both laughing]
Wow.
Looks like you had
a nice time.
How was
the pool party?
Mom, it's official.
I'm gonna marry that girl.
That's nice, sweetie.
I'm happy for you.
Where is your towel?
[man]
Come on, honey!
The car's waiting for us!
We gotta go!
Okay, Dad!
I'm coming!
♪♪
[Grandma]
Em, have you taken
Polly out lately?
No, Grandma!
I'll do it in a minute!
[Grandma]
You'll do it when, honey?
[sighing]
Fine.
I'll do it now,
Grandma.
Let's go, Polly.
♪♪
Okay, Polly, remember to lift
your dress up before you go.
♪♪
[plane engine whooshing]
Hey!
Hi!
Oh, it's so good
to see you!
Gosh, I almost
didn't recognize you
without the bangs.
How are you?
How was the flight?
Well, I'm good.
I'm better now.
I mean, I swear they make
the seats on the planes
smaller and smaller.
Yeah, 'cause you take up
so much room.
Never mind.
[chuckling]
Okay.
Hmm.
All right, mister.
You've got me
all to yourself this week.
Where to?
You'll see.
[tires screech]
You look good.
[Briley laughing]
Nice car.
Is it new?
Uh-huh.
One of those
"I'm in a big movie" perks.
[both chuckling]
Man, we have so much
to catch up on,
like how you got
that big movie.
Letters can only tell
so much.
Yeah, it's, um,
it's pretty crazy.
My agent said it's
my big break or whatever.
I mean, I'm already done
filming it and everything,
but it's still so surreal,
you know?
You're telling me.
I mean, your face is
all over New York.
I can't go get
a sandwich
without seeing
your billboards everywhere.
Okay, so, tell me everything.
Was everybody nice?
Was it everything
you hoped it would be?
And, I mean, that girl
that was supposed to be
your love interest,
was she sweet?
[tittering]
Uh, let's see.
Yes, everyone was super nice,
but it was weird.
Like, they were overly nice,
you know?
Like, they treated me
differently 'cause I was
a talent or whatever.
I didn't like that.
I mean, I know that I'm
an amazingly talented actor
and devilishly handsome,
but I can pour my own cup
of coffee, you know?
[chuckling]
And, um...
Yeah, it was everything
that I hoped for.
And more, actually.
I felt more at home there
than I have anywhere
in, like,
a really long time.
And, yeah, uh,
the girl was nice,
I guess.
We're here.
The beach?!
Cody! Oh, my gosh!
[Briley squeals]
[Cody chuckling]
[Briley]
Ohh, we're at the beach!
♪♪
Cody, oh, my gosh!
You just made me
the happiest girl
in the whole world!
♪♪
Ready?
Race ya.
♪♪
[bell ringing]
Who won?
♪♪
Hi, can we get one, please?
Thank you.
You can keep the change.
♪♪
Hey!
[laughing]
♪♪
[both]
Thank you.
Here you go.
[Briley]
Thank you!
No carbs.
I've gotta be-- oh, no.
Okay.
[laughing]
♪♪
[exhales]
This is so beautiful.
I mean, I wish I could
just capture this moment
and live in it forever.
I mean, I'd be
completely content
to just be like this
always, you know?
Huh.
Yeah, I could do that.
♪♪
[both giggling]
["Over the Rainbow"
playing on phone speaker]
Oh, my gosh!
Cody!
[chuckles]
Hey, a deal's a deal.
I wrote you
the letters.
You gotta hold up
your end of the bargain.
Can't believe you.
Okay.
♪♪
♪ Somewhere
♪ Over the rainbow
♪ Way up high
♪♪
♪ There's a land
♪ That I heard of
♪ Once in a lullaby ♪
[Briley giggles]
[Cody]
Well, I know it's not much,
but, uh, here you go.
Hi!
So, you're
the future wife
we keep hearing
so much about!
He hasn't
shut up about you
for ten months.
That's not what-- what?
Well, I-- I would hope so.
I mean,
it would be awkward
if it was
another girl, huh?
I'm Briley.
You must be Bryce?
That's me.
We both have "B" names.
I like that.
And Cody's right.
You do have
beautiful eyes.
Bryce!
[laughter]
It's so nice to have you
with us this week, dear.
And Cody does speak
very highly of you.
Mom! I--
It's okay.
I think it's sweet.
Okay.
Let's get you to where
you're sleeping.
Okay.
Thanks, Mom.
Come on.
[both chuckling]
After you.
Wait, is this your room?
Yeah.
But... where are you
gonna sleep?
Oh, don't you worry.
Uh, you haven't had
a chance to feel it yet,
but we have probably
the comfiest couch
known to man, so...
Is that another one of those
"I'm in a big movie" perks?
No, actually.
Yard sale.
Yeah, I think it's so comfy
'cause the old lady
we bought it from has had it
since she was born, so...
[mimics elderly voice]
They just don't make 'em
like they used to.
[both chuckling]
Well, uh, it's really
sweet of you
to let me stay in here.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah, anytime.
Um... right.
Well, I'm gonna let you
get settled in.
Uh, there are towels
in the closet across the way.
Milk in the fridge.
Cereal in the pantry.
Lots of it.
Bryce loves cereal.
Right, well,
um, good night.
Oh, and, Briley?
I'm really glad
you're here.
Right, well,
uh, good night.
You already said that.
Sweet dreams then.
Sweet dreams.
[door creaks and closes]
♪♪
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
I just...
couldn't sleep.
Do you mind if I...?
Oh! Yeah.
I really like you,
Briley.
♪♪
I really like you, too.
[Polly snorting]
Hold on, Polly.
I'm not finished.
We can go inside
when I'm done.
All good things come
with patience.
Good boy.
[birds chirping in distance]
[door creaks and opens]
Hey, sleepyhead.
I ran to the store.
I hope you like
packaged bagels
and crappy coffee.
Or tea.
I don't know what you--
I'll drink the other one.
Doesn't matter.
Ohh, oh,
you gotta get up.
We got a big day
ahead of us.
We do?
Mm-hmm.
[Cody]
Okay, so, today is all about
seeing everything
that Los Angeles has to offer
from a tourist's eyes.
I can't believe,
five years here
and we never did this.
Yeah, that's because
you never wanted to go.
Please stick around.
I like him better
when you're here.
[girl whispering]
It's Cody McClain!
Okay, we got
a big list here,
so where to first?
♪♪
[no audible dialogue]
[Briley laughing]
♪♪
[no audible dialogue]
Whoa!
♪♪
[camera clicks]
Thank you!
Oh, my God.
So sorry!
Wow!
Mm-hmm.
♪♪
[Briley]
Well, I did not realize how
many people recognized you.
That's pretty crazy, huh?
Oh, yeah.
No, that took
a little getting used to.
But it's cool,
you know?
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
I mean, you are
a big movie star.
Just don't let it go
to your head, all right?
♪♪
[no audible dialogue]
[sighing]
Can't believe
the week's already gone.
Went by so fast.
[chuckles]
Yeah... it did.
Okay, what was
your favorite part?
I mean, you know,
besides the beach,
of course.
You know, seeing
Steve Carell's house
and wax figure
in the same day
kind of had to be mine.
A little smaller
than I thought, though.
On both fronts,
actually.
Hey, you okay?
Look, I'm sad
that you're leaving too,
but, you know,
we had an amazing week.
Yeah, no,
uh... I know.
It's not that.
It's...
Hey.
Look.
I just-- I just don't know
if this is gonna work out.
What?
What do you...
Uh...
Where is this coming from?
Well, I mean, I'm about
to get on a plane
to go back to New York
in a few hours.
And it took us ten months
to get together out here,
and who knows
how long it'll take
to get out here again?
A-- And you've got
your whole big career
and all these great things
happening for you.
You don't need some girl
across the country
holding you down.
It's...
It's just
not realistic.
Hey, look at me.
I don't care how far away
that plane is taking you,
and I don't care how long
it takes to get you back.
I really don't.
We'll figure it out.
Look, I care
more about you
than anything else
in the world,
and that includes
some big acting career.
No, but, see,
I don't want to be that.
I don't want to be
the girl who's possibly
holding you back from being
the best you can be.
No, but I don't
see you that way.
Bri, before I met you,
I hadn't done anything
as an actor.
You'd done that Mr. Metzel's
Pretzels commercial.
Well, yeah.
[laughing]
Besides that.
Look, if you were
gonna hold me back,
it would've happened
by now.
Okay, just because
I kissed you on the beach
doesn't mean that everything's
suddenly gonna change.
I've felt the same way
since the day that I met you.
And we'll make
this work, okay?
I'll visit you in New York,
and-- and we'll write,
but I'm not gonna
lose you now.
Okay?
Okay.
Hold on a second.
♪♪
What is this?
Well, it's a box, silly.
[chuckles]
I found it at this
little place downtown.
I figured you
could use it to hold
all-- all the letters
I send you.
♪♪
Wow.
I love it, Cody.
Thank you.
Just...
promise me you'll never
say something
so stupid again,
okay?
I promise.
♪♪
Hey, Cody?
Yeah?
Remember when you said
that being on set
was the closest thing you had
to feeling like home?
♪♪
This kind of feels
like that.
Yeah.
[both giggling]
♪♪
Hurry up, slowpoke!
[Polly snorts]
Whoa!
Where are you going
in such a hurry?
I, um, I'm reading a story,
and I had to take Polly out,
and I'm really excited
to get back to it.
Must be a really good story.
I don't think
I've ever seen you
this excited
to read anything.
It is, Grandma.
Love you.
And don't forget.
Come and get me
when it's time, okay?
Okay, I will.
I promise.
♪♪
Okay, I'm ready.
[hairspray hisses]
[Cody]
"Briley, I miss you.
"I hope you're happy
in New York.
"Things are going
really great here.
"Things are good.
Really busy,
but it's all worth it."
♪♪
Oh, hi.
Uh, yeah.
Who do I
make it out to?
Mariah.
[Cody]
"Briley, I can't believe
you're doing theater!
"That's amazing!
I know you'll be incredible.
"Oh, uh, big news.
"My movie got picked up
for a sequel.
"Briley, it doesn't happen
overnight.
"Don't worry about it.
"You will find
the perfect part,
and they will love you."
♪♪
"Briley, that's incredible!
"I can't believe
you booked thatshow!
"Of course I'll be there.
I wouldn't miss it
for the world."
♪♪
Hey, you're on.
It's showtime.
Okay, be right there.
Thank you.
[door closes]
♪ Somewhere
♪ Over the rainbow
♪ Way up high
[thunder rumbling]
♪ There's a land
♪ That I've heard of
♪ Once in a lullaby
[together]
♪ Somewhere over the rainbow
♪ Way up high
♪ There's a land
that I've heard of ♪
♪ Once in a lullaby ♪
[shoes clatter on floor]
[zipper rasps]
Briley!
Hey, babe.
Uh, Bri, this is...
Vick. Cody's manager.
He has told me
so much about you.
And the show was great.
Very, uh, cute.
You make
a great Dorothy.
If they ever remake the movie,
I'll know who to call.
Hey, Vick, could you give--
Hey, say no more, boss.
I'll be outside.
And-- oh!
Really great.
I loved every minute of it.
So cute.
[door opens and closes]
Briley, you were amazing.
Cody, do not
try that with me.
You weren't here.
I was here
for enough of it.
Look, I saw the audience
at the end.
They loved you.
Where were you, Cody?
Look, I'm sorry.
I got caught filming
at this stupid
talk show thing.
I couldn't get away.
I tried.
Briley, I-I wish
I could've been here
for the whole show.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Cody,
another talk show
wants to call and confirm
for next week.
Yeah, yeah, that's good.
Okay.
[whispering] Sorry.
[sighs]
Well, let me
make it up to you.
Happy birthday.
My birthday's tomorrow.
And if you think a rose
is gonna make up
for missing my first-ever
Broadway show--
No, it's just the start.
I have a surprise for you.
And I think, in light
of everything this year,
you deserve
two birthdays, okay?
Okay.
But it better be
the best surprise ever.
It will be.
I promise.
Let me just
go tell Vick
that he has off
for the night.
I want you all
to myself.
Okay.
Okay, hold on a second.
Okay, you can
open them now.
♪♪
[Briley]
Wow.
This is amazing.
Madam.
This... is so sweet, Cody.
I mean, I'd say you really
didn't have to do all this,
but... kind of have a lot
to make up for.
[chuckles]
And how am I doing
on that?
You're getting there.
♪♪
How about now?
It's perfect.
Here.
You look
positively beautiful.
♪♪
Wow.
Thank you so much,
Cody.
I mean...
you really know how to make
a girl feel special.
[ice clattering]
Oh...
I'm not 21 yet.
I know, but...
[cork pops]
I mean, I feel like tonight
we can make an exception.
We have so much
to celebrate.
I mean, you've got
your Broadway show...
[champagne pouring]
...and your birthday.
And I've got my whole
movie franchise thing, so...
Okay, tell me everything.
I mean, is it everything
you hoped it would be?
That Scarecrow guy,
he seems sweet.
Aah! I'm melting!
I'm melting!
And then the Wicked Witch,
like, almost fell off the tower
because one
of the Flying Monkeys
ran into it.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, Toto!
We're not in Kansas anymore.
And then out...
and then back in!
♪♪
[shoes clatter on floor]
Wait, wait, Cody.
I-- I've never...
I know.
I love you,
Briley Williams.
Always.
♪♪
[Cody]
"Bri, I am so, so proud of you
and the woman you are becoming.
"I cannot wait to see
what happens next in your life.
"I apologize for leaving
without saying good-bye,
"but my agents called,
and they moved up
"the filming dates
for the movie,
"so I had to be
on the first flight out
"this morning
back to Los Angeles.
"I truly wish I could've stayed
and spent more time with you,
"but you know how it goes.
"I will be on set
for the next few months,
"so I don't know how often
I will be able to write you.
"But I will take
every chance I can to call
"and see how you're doing.
Happy birthday.
Always. Cody."
[groaning]
♪♪
[whimpering]
[toilet flushing]
♪♪
Hey, sweetie?
Do you have a moment?
I could really use
an extra pair of hands
making these cookies.
Well, um...
I was just getting
to the good part
of my story.
Story will still be there
when you get back.
Come on.
♪♪
There!
And then pour it in.
Whoo!
[both chuckling]
Stir, stir, stir,
stir, stir!
And then we mix it!
It's gonna be a lot
of chocolate chips
in these cookies!
Mix 'em up, yes.
Stir it up real good,
real good!
[grunting]
Real good, real good!
♪♪
You're really into
that story, huh?
What kind of story is it?
It's a love story.
Really?
You know, I always love
a good love story.
Does it end happy?
I don't know yet.
I haven't gotten there.
But it has to, right?
All love stories have
a happy ending.
Well, no...
not all love stories.
But it's not always about
how they end, you know?
It's about the journey.
[chuckles]
[oven door opens and closes]
Well, thank you very much
for your help, my dear.
You're welcome.
I couldn't have done it
without you.
Yes.
Can I go back
to my story now?
Yes, you can go back
to your story.
Let me know how it ends?
You betcha!
Love you, Grandma.
Love you, too.
♪♪
Okay.
[sighing]
[phone line trilling]
[Cody on voicemail]
Hey, it's Cody.
I can't get to the phone
right now,
but if you leave
your name, number,
and a message,
I'll call you back.
Thanks.
Hi, Cody.
Um, I just wanted to talk.
Um, it's been
a couple weeks, so...
I, uh, hope you're having
a wonderful time on set.
Um... I miss you.
[chuckles]
Anyway, just, uh,
give me a call back
if you can, okay?
I love you.
Okay, uh, bye.
[toilet flushing]
Hey, Briley, you ready?
We're getting close.
Hey.
You all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Uh... must just be
a little nervous, I guess.
What do you have
to be nervous about?
Everyone loves you out there.
You're packing out the house.
You've done this
a hundred times now
between rehearsals
and shows, right?
Yeah, you're right.
You're gonna do great.
You always do.
[man over earpiece]
Showtime, two minutes.
Two minutes to showtime.
Okay, it's showtime.
Let's go.
[door opens and closes]
[Ben]
Look, I know I messed up,
but I can change.
I can do better.
I know you say that, Ben,
but how can I trust you?
[sobbing]
You lied to me, Ben.
How could you not tell me
you were...
a secret agent?
I didn't have a choice.
Hmm.
Everything I did,
I did to protect you.
The life that I live,
it's dangerous, okay?
I don't want you to have
to be a part of it.
I don't want
to put you in danger.
But don't you see?
You can't protect me
from everything, Ben.
It doesn't work
like that.
If you love me, right,
you'll let me decide
whether I want to take
that risk or not.
♪♪
Do you love me?
More than anything.
[exhales deeply]
Then take me with you,
Ben Pierson,
and let's save
the world together.
That's the sexiest thing
I've ever heard.
Mm-hmm?
Um... can we cut
for a second?
I-I'm sorry.
I just need a second.
Cut!
[man]
That's a cut, everyone!
Sorry.
[man]
Stand by!
That was looking great.
Really fantastic.
What happened?
What's up?
I just, uh-- could I take
a few minutes?
I just need a quick break.
Is that all right?
Cody, we...
Yeah.
Sure, buddy.
Anything you need.
Thanks.
All right, everybody,
that's a five-minute break!
[phone line trilling]
[phone ringing]
[line continues trilling]
[phone continues ringing]
[Briley on voicemail]
Hey, this is Briley.
I'm not here right now.
Please leave a mes--
No, no,
no-no-no-no!
Hey, stud.
They want you back on set.
You got a scene
to finish.
Yeah, okay.
I-I'll be there in a second.
[door closes]
Oh, come on, please.
[phone line trilling]
Cody, please pick up.
[door closes]
[phone buzzing]
[bell ringing]
Great work, kid.
Turned out beautiful.
You had me scared there
for a second.
Just being honest.
But you pulled it out.
I'll see you tomorrow,
okay?
Get some rest.
I will.
Thanks, Ed.
Have a good night.
[Ed]
You too, buddy.
Cody, man,
great work today.
Honestly, you had me sweating
a little bit back there.
[chuckles]
Um, okay, look.
I know it's a lot,
but the guys at the studio
were wanting you to do
some press junkets
with Hayley next week
to promote the movie.
Can you make that work?
Yeah, I guess so.
I mean, don't have much
of a choice, right?
I knew I could count on you.
All right, I'm gonna jet.
Uh... before I go,
just, when you're
in front of the press,
just kind of play up
the flirt factor
a little bit.
They love to see that.
I know.
We gotta sell
the chemistry, right?
You good?
You just,
you seem kind of off.
Oh, no, yeah,
I'm-I'm good.
I just, uh-- long day.
Little tired.
Okay, yeah.
Uh, get some rest.
We can't have you
burning out, right?
See you tomorrow, Cody.
Night, Vick.
Hey, you.
That was a heck
of a scene today.
You almost had me
falling for you for real.
[both chuckling]
Well, thank you.
Oh, and sorry
about earlier.
No, no, no.
Say no more.
I get it.
I wouldn't want
to kiss me either.
No, I didn't mean that.
Oh, so you did want
to kiss me?
No, I j--
[sighing]
[both chuckle]
Look, there's, um...
there's just someone
who means a lot to me,
and I really wanted
to talk with her,
you know?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Um, well...
where is she?
New York.
Ohh!
N-- New York?
Mm-hmm.
Cody, that's
a long ways away.
Yeah.
Oh...
Good night, Cody.
♪♪
[exhales]
[door opens]
[phone line trilling]
Hello?
[woman on phone]
Yeah, hi.
It's Briley Williams.
Hey, Briley.
What's going on?
Yeah, I don't think I'm gonna
be able to make it in today.
Come down with something
pretty bad, like a stomach bug.
Oh, no.
Well, that's no good.
Yeah, uh,
I'll keep you updated.
Hopefully it's just one
of those 24-hour things.
Yeah, hopefully.
I hope you feel better.
Sorry about this.
No, no worries.
Just rest up and get better.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'll try
to get better quick, thanks.
Yeah, of course.
Well, let me know how you're
doing, okay?
Okay.
All right, thanks.
Bye.
[phone line trilling]
[Ed]
Action!
♪♪
Hold! Can we get
the stunt doubles in, please?
[Cody exhales]
Woo-hoo!
Have fun.
Nice job.
And action!
Ooh!
Whoa there, stud.
Don't stop on my account.
[giggles]
That was fun today, huh?
So much better than some,
like, stuffy romantic scene.
Yeah, it was fun.
I just wish they'd let me do
my own stunts, you know?
I think I could
pull it off, don't you?
I think you could pull off
anything you wanted to.
And, no, I'm not talking
about your shirt,
although I'm sure nobody
would be complaining.
[chuckles]
Anyway...
so a bunch of us were gonna
go out for drinks tonight,
and everyone was wondering
if the great Cody McClain
would be gracing us
with his presence for once.
I'm not much
of a partier.
Oh, my gosh!
Come on!
We don't bite.
We'll take it easy
on you, promise.
Uh...
First drink's on me.
Okay, fine, I'll go.
But let's not
make it too late.
You and I both
have work tomorrow.
You don't have
to worry about me.
I'll be just fine.
See you in a bit.
♪♪
[knock at door]
Well, hello, Miss Briley.
How are you?
[door closes]
Oh, what's going on
with you today?
I assume this isn't
a social visit.
No, ma'am,
not today.
Um, I-I've come down
with, like, a stomach bug.
Mm-hmm.
I'm pretty sure it'll go away,
but our theater director
just wanted me
to get checked out.
You know they want me back
and working ASAP.
Mm, I hear you.
I know how hard they're
working you over there.
And the play is amazing,
by the way!
Oh, my God, my...
my girls just adore you.
Oh, most little girls
want to be princesses.
Not mine.
They want to be Dorothy.
Well, your daughters sound
like my kind of girls.
[chuckling]
Yeah, kids are funny,
aren't they?
It's incredible
how you can love
two little humans
so much.
Ah, but what
am I saying?
You're just a kid
yourself.
But, someday,
when you have your own,
you'll understand.
All right,
enough about me.
Let's see what's
going on with you.
Need you to take a couple
of deep breaths for me.
[breathing deeply]
Good. One more.
Good.
All right, now give me
your biggest "Ahh."
Ahh...
Okay.
I see some signs
of recent vomiting...
but no other issues.
Have you, uh, eaten
anything new recently?
Anything that could've
made you sick?
No, nothing new.
Okay.
I haven't had much of
an appetite lately, though.
Okay, well,
anything else?
Have you been
more tired than usual?
Oh, I mean, I guess
maybe a little bit.
Um, everyone has been
making fun of me
for falling asleep
in the makeup chair lately.
[chuckling]
Okay, Briley, when was
your last period?
I don't know.
Um... maybe a couple
weeks ago.
This month has just
been so crazy.
Everything's kind of
blurred together.
I'm not really sure.
Okay...
Well, since we can't
quite seem to know
the cause of the nausea,
I'll prescribe
some medication for you
that will help
with any symptoms
and knock out
any lingering bugs
in there, okay?
Okay, sounds good,
Dr. King, thank you.
But before
I do that, Briley,
I do have to
ask you, honey...
Have you been sexually
active recently?
[dance music playing]
Whew! Well, you look
like you're having
the time of your life.
[giggling]
I'm joking!
You look miserable.
Come on, look around.
Isn't this fun to you?
No, not really.
I mean, I told you,
this isn't really my thing.
What?
I said
it's not my thing!
Oh, come on, this is
everyone's thing!
You just gotta
give it a chance.
Hey, lighten up!
Why are you so serious?
What has got you
thinking so hard?
Oh, what?
Is it "New York Girl"?
No, no, nothing.
I-- Look, I think
I'm gonna go home.
I'm just really not
feeling this, I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Hold up,
just loosen up, okay?
Stop thinking so much.
Most of the people here
weren't feeling it
when they fist
came here, either,
but now look at them.
Come dance with me.
I don't know.
What?
I don't--
I don't want to!
Un-uh, I wasn't asking.
Come on.
[music cuts out]
♪♪
[line trilling]
[cell phone buzzing]
Hey! Hey, Bri,
can you hear me?
Hey, uh, Cody.
Sorry, uh, it's
really late there.
I'm surprised
you're still up.
Is everything okay?
Uh, yeah, everything's--
Everything's great, um...
I just calling to see
how things are going.
Things are really,
really good, actually.
It's just been
so crazy busy here.
I mean, filming's taking up
my entire life, you know?
Um...
Look, I'm sorry I haven't
been able to call much lately.
It's just-- It's been
so crazy, you know?
No, it's okay.
I mean, I get it.
I mean, everything's been
crazy here, too, so...
[cell phone beeps]
So busy.
Sorry, Bri, what--
What was that?
No, it's o-- it's okay,
I was just saying--
[cell phone beeping]
Cody?
Hey!
Come back to the dancefloor,stud, we're missing you!
Co--Cody?
Gimme a second, okay?
Just one second.
Okay.
Cody?
Hey, Bri...
Look, I gotta go.
Um...
Hey, I think we should
just take some time.
You know, I just--
I just need some time
to figure out how to
balance all this, okay?
I'll call you soon.
Bye.
Wait, Cody--
[line beeps off]
♪♪
[dancers cheering]
Thank you for meeting me.
I know we haven't
talked much, but...
I kind of feel like
you're my only friend
out here, you know?
Of course.
I'm happy to.
How are you?
I mean, considering.
Oh, how am I?
I really don't know.
I mean, it's just
the strangest feeling.
Honestly, it just
doesn't even
feel... real.
I mean, how do you
comprehend that there's
this little thing
inside you,
and it's gonna grow
to be a little boy...
...girl...
And that's gonna grow up
to be a man or a woman,
and have to be
living in this world.
Whoa. That's a lot.
Yeah, sorry, I just...
been kind of
lost recently.
Not really sure what
to do about all this.
That's understandable.
I mean, unless you're,
like, planning for it,
I think most people
feel that way.
Yeah, I guess.
Do your parents know?
I'm sure they'd be a good
support base in all this.
Yeah, not so much.
They kind of
haven't been in touch
since I started
to pursue theater.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I hope you don't
mind me asking, but...
What about the dad?
Where's he in all this?
Does he know yet?
No.
Um, I tried to tell him,
but, you know, I just--
I just couldn't
bring myself to do it.
Do I know the guy?
Don't tell me it's one
of the flying monkeys.
No, no, no!
It's not one of the monkeys!
You haven't met him,
I don't think,
but you've probably
heard of him.
Just promise you won't
tell anybody.
Yeah... I promise.
Okay, um,
it's Cody McClain.
Cody McClain?!
Like the freaking
The huge, famous heartthrob
actor Cody McClain?!
Yeah, that's the one.
Oh, my gosh, he's so--
Uh, sorry.
I didn't mean to.
It's okay.
So... why haven't
you told him?
What's stopping you?
Was it just like...
one-night stand
kind of thing?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's nothing like that.
Um... we'd actually been
dating for a couple of years.
But, I mean, he's not
gonna return my calls.
He already told me
he wants to take a break
and really focus
on his career.
Plus, I mean,
I can't just like
jump on a plane
to Los Angeles.
Why not?
They have you blocked out
on the schedule
for the next
couple of days.
Why don't you go
talk to him?
This seems like one of those
in-person things, anyway.
[Cody]
That was pretty good today.
I think they'll--
Oh, hey, I'll see you later.
Hey, you two,
how are you?
Ohh!
Hey, Mama.
Good to see you.
Good to see
you too, son.
This is pretty cool.
It's been a while
since I've been
on a set with you.
This is a little bigger
than I remember.
Yeah, Mom, that's 'cause
Cody's a megastar now.
Well, you're not wrong.
Always humble,
just like I raised you.
Oh, guys,
this is Hayley!
This is my costar.
Hayley, this is my mom,
Lana, and my sister, Bryce.
Nice to meet you.
Same to you.
Nice to meet you as well.
Cody has told me
so much about you!
Bryce, are you
gonna follow
in your brother's
footsteps
and become
a big actor too?
Well, if Cody told you
much about us,
you know
that I hate acting.
I think most actresses I meet
are vain and airheaded.
Bryce!
No, it's fine.
She's right.
Most of us are.
But us airheads gotta make
a living somehow, right?
Not all of us can be
as gifted as you.
Okay, do you guys
wanna go see my trailer?
Yes, let's do that.
Right there.
All righty, hope to see you
around here again soon!
It was nice
to meet you, too.
I'll see you.
Sorry about her.
She's not normally
like that.
It's fine.
I'm used to that.
Most girls don't like me.
I think they feel...
threatened.
Don't for the life of me
know why.
Uh, my-- Oh.
Ed told me about this place
a couple weeks ago,
and I just fell in love.
I mean, the view
and the food.
Guys, oh, man...
I just had to show you.
It's beautiful, honey.
We didn't have to go
to someplace so... expensive.
Oh, Mom, no,
it's totally fine.
Only the best
for my girls.
Yeah, Mom,
let the big shot pay.
I'm not complaining.
Excuse me?
I'd like your finest
Shirley Temple, please.
Make it a double.
Right away.
Thanks, champ.
What?
So, honey, tell us
about filming.
Seems like it's going
really well.
Oh, Mom,
it's going amazing.
I mean, everyone is
so talented,
and I really do, I think
we're making a great project.
Yes, the world is dying
to see what happens
to Ben Pierson,
Secret Agent, next.
She going through
that teen phase thing?
I'm glad you're having
a good time.
You know, we don't get
to hear from you
as much now, and...
Yeah, Mom,
I'm sorry about that.
It's just, you know,
with everything so busy
I barely have time
to think, you know?
And what about Briley?
How is our favorite
theater star?
Yeah, how is she, Cody?
Have you talked to her
about your lovely costar yet?
No, actually, I haven't.
We, uh...
We decided we need to focus
on our careers right now.
You know, with everything
being so crazy--
You know, you can
only use that excuse
so many times before it
gets a little old, bro.
It's too crazy
to keep up with Mom.
It's too crazy to
keep up with your sister.
It's too crazy
to keep up with the girl
who you wouldn't shut up
about marrying some day
for two years!
But it's not too crazy
to go to another
press appearance,
or to go out to the club
with Miss Skankypants costar!
Bryce!
I have
social media, genius.
Bryce, that's enough!
Whatever.
Put it on his tab.
I'm sure he can afford it.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about her.
She's just... missing
her older brother.
You know
she's right, though.
It wouldn't hurt to call.
Check in every now and then.
I better go check on her.
She's probably not gonna
wanna come back in,
so we'll just take
a taxi back home.
Okay.
I love you, son.
I love you, too, Mom.
And, Cody.
I know you may not
be in a place
to hear this right now,
but don't be so quick
to push aside those
who care about you
the most in life, okay?
And Briley...
They don't make
many like her.
She is one of a kind.
Don't forget that.
I hate to see you
throw that away.
Call me.
Soon.
I will.
[woman speaking
indistinctly on PA]
Okay.
[approaching footsteps]
Oh, did someone have
a wild night last night?
Is everything all right?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
I'll be there
in a few minutes.
Okay, uh, just remember
the press is here today.
You know, we have
that onset visit.
So, gotta look
alive, right?
Put your game face on.
And remember, chemistry.
It sells.
Right, you feel me?
All right, champ,
see you out there.
Game face!
Yeah.
Game face.
Let me see that.
That goes well
with this, too.
Honestly, this is
a nice little combination
you got going on.
Hey, you ready
to put on a show?
What do you mean?
Oh, you know, giving
the fans what they want.
[whispering]
Nothing too crazy.
Thank you.
And, young lady,
how can I help you today?
Hi, I'm here
to see Cody McClain.
My name's Briley Williams.
I should be on the Friends
and Family list.
You have an ID?
Yes.
Okay, you know the drill.
This is just a quick live
broadcast from the studio.
So the filming's going well,
what we can expect
from the movie,
yadda yadda yadda.
Nothing new.
Sound good?
Yeah.
Okay, they're
on their way.
You guys look great,
by the way.
Showtime.
He's right, you know.
We do look
great together.
Yep, there you are.
Briley Williamson.
You know
how to get there?
No.
Stage Two.
Follow the line,
can't miss it.
Okay, thank you so much.
You're welcome, thank you.
Hello.
Hi, we're on the set
of "Ben Pierson:
The Shadow Files",
and I have
an exclusive interview
with our two lead actors,
Cody McClain
and Hayley Ryan.
Some of the scenes have
been leaked from the movie,
and they're very steamy,
and I'm just wondering
if any of that
onscreen chemistry
is carrying over
off-screen, if you know
what I mean?
Um--
Okay, well, I'm really glad
you asked this question.
I know it's been hard
for us to keep it quiet.
Hey, Briley, right?
How you doing?
Oh, hi, yeah.
Um, I'm okay.
We're kind
of a thing now!
I mean, it's
so hard not to be
when you have such a strong
chemistry, you know?
I just need to talk with Cody.
Is... he around?
No, actually, he's
super busy right now.
Um, I could take
a message, if you want.
He's probably
gonna be a while.
That's okay.
Can you just...
We practically can't keep
our hands off each other.
Can you just, um,
give this to him
for me, please?
Yeah, no problem.
Oh, you guys,
that's so exciting!
I'm so happy for you,
and I'm sure your fans
are so excited
to know this,
and you guys
heard it here first.
Okay.
See you later.
Emerson, honey,
it's almost time to go.
Are you ready?
Oh, sweetie,
what's wrong?
I don't think this story's
gonna have
a happy ending, Grandma.
It's too sad.
Oh, honey.
Come here.
Now, remember
what I said, dear?
Not all love stories
have a happy ending.
But it's about
how they end, right?
It's about...
Wait.
What was it again?
The journey, Grandma.
That's right,
the journey!
Tell you what.
How about I sit here
with you
and we can read it together
until it's time to go?
Will that help make it
a little less sad?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Let's see.
Where did you leave off?
This one.
"Briley, forgive me
for making this brief...
What was that?!
We're not-- We're not dating!
Why did you say that?
Cody, chill out!
Of course I know
we're not dating,
but they wanted us
to put on a show,
give something
that the fans
could latch onto.
I don't understand
what the big deal is.
Vick, come on, man,
this is crazy!
I mean, I think
it's a good idea.
The press loves
this kind of stuff,
and I say
we roll with it.
Yeah, okay, just until
the movie releases,
and then we could
have, like,
some big tabloid
breakup story.
No big deal.
No big deal?
It's a lie.
We're lying.
Cody, we're actors.
It's what we do.
We act.
It's gonna bring so much
attention to our movie.
What, you don't want
people to think
that we're together?
I'm-- I'm not saying that.
But we're not together.
What am I supposed
to tell my family?
You don't have to
tell them anything.
Nothing, zip.
Look, all we have to do
is go to a few parties,
get photographed in public
together a few times,
just to give the press
something to talk about.
You know, like, keep us
relevant, that's all.
You think you could
manage that?
Come on, Cody, look, I know
it's a little out there,
but this is really good
for your career, trust me.
Besides, that girl
from New York
is out of the picture,
right, what's her name?
Briley.
Right, so there's
no down side here.
Fine, I'll do it.
Whatever.
But just don't-- don't
pull anything like that again
without talking
to me first, okay?
You got it, stud.
Hey, lighten up!
♪ It could be fun
if you let it! ♪
Mmm! Mwah!
She's crazy.
She's an actress.
What do you expect?
You have to be a little crazy
if you want to be an actor.
You're crazy, too.
Anyway, this is what
you signed up for, right?
Ride this out,
and I promise you,
you will not regret it.
See, out there...
You're a star,
Cody McClain.
[reporter]
We can confirm
that Cody McClain
and Hayley Ryan
are official.
We saw their steamy scenes
from the set
of their new movie,
but apparently, these two
are fire offscreen as well.
[sighs]
Wonder what their
celebrity name will be?
Cayley? Hody?
I don't know if those
work at all.
--their celebrity
name will be?
Cayley? Hod--
But I guess we'll find out.
[Judy Garland on TV]
♪ A land that I heard of♪
♪ Once in a lullaby♪
♪ Somewhere
over the rainbow ♪
♪ Skies are blue♪
♪ And the dreams that you
dare to dream ♪
♪ Really do come true♪
So, what did
the big chimney
say to
the little chimney?
What?
You're too young
to smoke.
[all laugh and groan]
So punch at me.
I'm gonna block.
Okay.
And then you're gonna
come quick and jab.
There you go,
yeah, exactly.
Cool.
All right, do that again.
Oh, my gosh,
I'm so glad you came!
Of course!
Thanks for fitting me in
today, Dr. King.
Aw, anything
for you, Dorothy.
[chuckles]
So, I heard the news.
It wasn't a stomach bug
after all, was it?
No... No, it wasn't.
And are we excited?
Scared? Nervous?
All of the above.
Good. That means
you're normal.
Any other bad symptoms?
Has the morning sickness
gotten any worse since
the last time I saw you?
Um... no.
I mean, I've had it
come and go,
but overall it's okay.
I'm getting used to it.
I have had the strangest
cravings, though.
I mean, I had never
thought about dipping
a cheeseburger into
a chocolate shake
before a couple
days ago.
[chuckling]
I remember that.
Now, Briley,
I am required
to discuss all of
your options with you.
You are young
and healthy,
and we don't expect
any complications,
but... are you considering
the possibility
of terminating--
Dr. King... I know
you're supposed
to go over all that
stuff with me, but...
I just can't think
about that right now.
Okay, I just...
I just wanna make you
aware of all your options.
And, uh...
Will the father be
a part of the process?
No.
No, he won't.
Okay.
Would you like to see
an ultrasound of the baby?
No.
No, that's okay.
Okay.
Well, feel free to call me
with any questions, okay?
See you soon.
[door opens and closes]
Hi.
Thank you.
Hi, could you give us a moment?
Sure.
Thank you.
Hi, Lynn, I'm sorry
I'm a few minutes late.
I'll get ready fast,
I promise.
Briley, we need to talk.
If this is about me
getting sick a lot lately,
I'm totally fine.
I won't be getting
anyone else here sick.
I'm sure of it.
Briley, why were
you late today?
I had a doctor's checkup.
I just wanted to make sure
I got the all-clear.
And I did, so...
Well, your doctor called
the theater company
earlier today.
They wanted to confirm
the insurance
for your appointment.
I...
Briley...
I don't know
what to tell you.
The producers just
don't want to take
a chance on you
having complications
because of the pregnancy.
But how can they do that?
I mean, I-I-I-I--
I'll still be able to perform
for a few months
before anything changes.
And isn't Broadway
starting to offer
maternity leave anyway?
Well, some companies
are starting
to offer maternity leave
for their actresses,
but ours isn't one of them.
I'm sorry, Briley.
I wish that there was
more I could do, but...
this one is just
out of my hands.
Lynn, there has to be
something I can do.
I mean, this isn't right.
Honey...
I know this is
hard to do,
but have you considered
giving up the baby?
After all,
you're still a teenager
and you have such a bright
future ahead of you.
I'm not telling you
what you should do.
I'm just saying
that it's an option.
I'll tell the producers
to hold off
on their decision while
you think about it, okay?
Okay.
I'll let you know.
Briley?
I wish this weren't the case,
I really do.
But I just don't see
another option for you.
I'll try and buy
as much time
with the producers
as I can, okay?
[Cody]
I don't know how it all
got so screwed up.
It's like I only saw
one path in front of me
and I kept walking on it
and it led me further
and further away from who I am.
And now, now I'm stuck.
There's no way out.
Literally an entire production
is riding on my shoulders
and-- and I have to play pretend
with my real life
to pull it all off.
What am I supposed to do?
[Lana]
Well, sweetie,
I don't have
an easy answer for you.
This is what you wanted,
isn't it?
A career as an actor?
Yeah.
Yeah, it was.
I just didn't see it
going like this, you know?
Life rarely ever goes just how
we picture it, son.
I just-- I don't think
I know what I want anymore.
For so long, I wanted this
career as an actor,
and now I have it
and-- and I'm just...
Not happy?
Why don't you call her?
No, Mom, she doesn't want
to hear from me now.
I treated her terribly.
I wouldn't be surprised
if she never wanted
to hear from me again.
I can't even imagine
being in her position.
Seeing everything
in the press? I...
I'd be so angry.
Well, yeah.
You're right.
And she has every right
to be angry with you.
But she loved you
and you loved her.
You owe it to her
to at least call.
Yeah.
You're right.
I was scared.
I don't want her to hate me.
Cody, she may.
But you're better off knowing,
if you ask me.
Yeah.
I'll talk to you soon, okay?
All right.
♪♪
I told you
it was a sad story.
Yes, sweetheart.
I had forgotten
just how sad it was.
Grandma, you've read
this story before?
Oh, yes, dear.
Do you know
how old I am?
I have read
a lot of stories.
How does it end, Grandma?
Please tell me
it gets better.
Well, now sweetie,
I couldn't tell you that
even if I wanted to.
That would spoil
the journey.
And it's--
Yes, Grandma.
Get it.
It's all about
the journey.
But you gotta
give me something.
I mean, this is tragic.
Where's the silver lining?
Where's the light
at the end of the tunnel?
I mean, what if it just
keeps getting worse?
[laughing]
Well, child, I can't
promise you that it won't.
But keep reading.
You'll reach the end
of the story
and then you can
decide for yourself
if it has a happy ending.
Now, come on.
We gotta go.
[boy]
Dude, I cannot wait
to see this movie.
The first one was so dope.
Yeah.
Yeah, man, I'm pretty
excited about it.
Dude, you're so lucky.
I'd give anything
to be in your shoes.
I mean, Hayley Ryan.
She's pretty great.
Pretty great?
She's the hottest
girl alive.
If I could just have
five minutes with that...
Yeah, that's great.
Uh...
Could you guys excuse me
for a second?
I just gotta
take care of something.
Thanks.
Oh, hey, big guy.
Where you going?
We're gonna do the toast
by the pool in five.
Is that all right?
Yeah, yeah, I'll be back.
I just need a minute.
Whatever you say.
And there goes my retirement
fund right there.
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
[footsteps approaching]
Hey, you.
I saw you come in here.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I just...
I had to get away
from the crowd for a second.
I'm fine.
[chuckles]
I totally get that.
Um, I can only be
in a big crowd
for so long
until I need a little...
privacy.
[chuckles, sighs]
Um, on the bright side,
we're almost done with
this whole charade.
Hm.
Right?
Although I have to admit,
it's been pretty fun for me.
Not every day you get
to play pretend
in real life, you know?
Uh... you know,
it doesn't
have to be pretend.
It's obvious there's
a spark between us.
I know when you kissed me
in those scenes,
you wished it was real.
I felt that.
[whispering]
All you have to do
is say the word
and I'm yours.
[kissing]
Do you want me,
Cody McClain?
Hayley, stop!
Oh! Whoa!
What is this?
Excuse me!
Hello!
Shut up.
There he is,
the man of the hour.
What is this?
Why do you have this?!
I can explain.
Yeah?
It better be
a damn good explanation.
Look, she came
with the studio
and wanted to give
this to you
and I told her you were busy,
which you were.
She came here...
and you didn't tell me?
Something like this
right now
could ruin your career.
I am just
looking out for you.
What did you tell her?
Okay, look,
I took care of it.
You're welcome.
Vick, what did you do?
Okay, I gave her
some money.
And I told her to...
You know?
Who do you think
you are?
Listen to me,
you little prick,
you would have none of this
if it wasn't for me.
Everything you have
is because of me.
Where are you going?
Just gonna leave
and throw this away
'cause of some girl?
♪ Tweedle deedle dee
tweedle deedle dee ♪
[music plays over conversation]
How much further,
Grandma?
We will be there
soon, child.
Calm yourself.
[crowd chatter]
[nurse]
Briley Williams?
Have you seen
You're Cody Mc...
Yes, yes, Cody McClain, hi.
Have you seen
Briley Williams?
Uh, yeah,
but Cody, she's--
she's at the hospital
right now.
Which hospital?
We're here.
Yay!
Excuse me, which room
is Briley Williams in?
I'm sorry, sir, I can't
give you that information.
Sir!
No, you can't go
back there! Sir!
Am I too late?
No, honey, for the first
time in your life,
you're on time.
Just hold my hand, please.
[female doctor]
Keep breathing, breathe.
[panting]
[monitor beeping]
We have a head.
[baby crying]
[knocking on door]
Hi.
Hi, Mommy.
Hi, sweetie.
Wanna meet your new
baby brother?
Hey, thanks for taking
care of her for us.
Oh, she was an angel.
Oh, you two sure do
make beautiful babies.
Yeah, well,
good genes.
Hey!
Sorry I'm late.
Traffic was a mother.
Hey, Bryce,
how you doing?
How's the little guy?
He's a little stud,
just like his dad.
[laughter]
[female doctor]
Briley, we need to get
some more tests done.
[baby crying]
[baby fussing]
♪ Somewhere
♪ Over the rainbow
♪ Way up high
♪ There's a land
that I heard of ♪
♪ Once in a lullaby ♪
I think you are gonna be
the best big sister ever.
What do you have here,
Emerson?
It's a love story
I'm reading.
I don't know
how it ends yet.
Well, do you mind
if we read it with you?
Sure.
Briley, I...
Excuse me, sir?
Cody?
Briley.
[whispers]
It's okay.
[door slams]
What's that?
It's, um...
Well, it's a letter.
I was trying to figure out
what I would say
and I didn't even know
if I could get it all out.
So I, um...
I wrote you a letter.
Briley, I am so sorry.
I-- I didn't know.
♪♪
You're gonna be a dad.
[both laughing]
Well, is it a boy
or a girl?
Well, it might be
a little too early to tell.
But would you guys like
to take a look?
Okay.
All righty.
Okay, so...
right here,
that is the head.
There's a little
bright light...
right there,
you see that?
Looks like a railroad track,
that's the spine.
The little flicker
right there,
that's the heart.
I love you.
Always?
Always.
[laughing]
♪♪
Here, let's put that
somewhere safe.
[grunting]
Boop.
[chuckles]
[Lana]
We have cookies here.
[Cody]
Cookies!
[Emerson]
I made it.
[Cody]
You made them?
[indistinct chatter]
Who's going first?
Do you have any fives?
Yes, I do.
Oh...
Mom, eights.
Nope. No, dear.
Do you...
Yes?
...have any tens?
Oh...
Yeah, she does.
[music continues over chatter]
♪♪