Captioning made possible by
lions gate entertainment
[Alarm chirps]
[Silenced gunshot]
Man: 10 grand?
Come on, man.
This is Cadillac smack,
Mexican tar.
You gonna make 3-4 times that
on the street, no problem.
Yeah, but it's
still 10 grand.
What about your girl?
She's a piece of ass.
She must be pulling in,
what, 500 a night?
No, she's not doing
that no more, man.
She's, um, you know.
No shit, man.
Yours?
So you
gonna be a daddy.
Listen, 10 grand's fine.
But it's gonna take me
a little while.
Well,
when you get the scratch,
you get the batch.
See ya, daddy-o.
[Grinder grinding]
[Humming]
Hey, sweetie.
Hey, baby.
I got your mail.
So...
How did it go?
Fine.
He said
he wanted 10 grand,
but he thinks we can pull,
like, 30 or 40 with that.
40,000?!
Really?
Do you think
we can do that?
He thinks so.
40 grand--do you know
how cool that would be?
We could
get out of this dump,
out of this
whole damn town,
bring baby up in Phoenix
with mama.
[Moaning]
I love you.
I love you, too, em.
What?
First we gotta
get the 10 grand.
Well...you'll get it.
I know you will.
I'll take a shower.
I got a postcard
from mama.
Oh, yeah?
Well, when
you write her back,
tell her I said hey.
You can tell her
when you see her.
Even better.
C.j.,
what a surprise.
Did you do the job?
Ah, c.J.
Squeaky clean
every time.
Philodendron,
amaryllis--
I wonder who makes up
such ridiculous names
for such
beautiful creatures?
Conch shell.
Flowers
have sweet names.
Violet, Daisy, Lily.
Women are
named for flowers.
Have you ever
heard of a woman
named after a plant?
Fern.
Very good.
But it's not
a pretty name, is it?
Sounds like "carpet."
I asked
if you did the job.
He's dead.
Your job
was to kill the man
who stole from me
and bring back
what he stole.
So I ask you again--
did you do the job?
No.
Hmm.
There's absolutely
nothing feminine
about you, c.J.
What you were supposed
to bring back
in that case
is worth a half mil
on the street.
Find it
and finish the job.
350 bucks?
And all you got
was a massage?
Yeah,
you believe that?
You got ripped off
by a hooker.
That's awesome.
[Imitates his laugh]
I'm gonna take a piss.
[Mocking]
You got ripped off
by a hooker.
Asshole.
[Door opens]
It's my turn.
Whoa.
You can't be in here.
[No audio]
Emily:
We can call this off.
It's gonna be ok.
I don't know, honey.
Look, you wanna go
to Arizona or not?
You know I wanna go.
Yeah, and
we need money to go.
This is the only way
I know to make money,
baby.
So we do this.
But he said 10,000.
I'll take care of it.
It'll be ok, ok?
Ok.
He comes in here
sometimes.
I don't know
his name or nothing.
He ever pay
with a credit card?
You a cop or something?
Am I gonna
get him in trouble?
Honestly,
you'll be helping him
get out of trouble.
[Knock on door]
Man, I ought
to bust a cap in your ass
for bringing
this knocked-up bitch
up in here.
You think
this is goddamn K-Mart?!
Chill out, dude.
She's not gonna bust
all over your shitty-ass,
fuckin' carpet.
Oh, she better not.
Give us the shit for free,
and I'll let you fuck me.
This is sick.
You're a sick,
fuckin' bitch.
Are we gonna
do this shit or what?
[Rap music playing]
Aah!
[Screams]
It's fuckin' over!
Go get me
some fuckin' towels
right now, Emily!
God!
Get 'em! Get me
some fuckin' towels!
[Sobbing]
Hurry!
[Vomiting]
Cheap vodka,
straight up.
Bartender:
You got it.
I got that, drew.
Nice gentleman just
bought you a cheap vodka,
straight up.
Tell him thanks
and bring me
the one I ordered.
[Country-western music
playing]
Thanks.
I'm Rick.
That's great.
Can I buy you
another drink?
No, thanks.
Why not?
Yeah.
Because you asked
"why not,"
because you drink
dark beer,
because
you get a haircut
and a manicure
once a month
at a salon,
because
you're not my type.
Emily: Ow! Aah!
What's wrong?
I don't know!
Aah! Baby, do something!
I'm scared!
Ow!
All right. We're
going to the clinic.
Come on. Let's go.
Watch my hand, baby.
Ok, come on.
Wait just a second.
Just a second.
Ok. All right.
Gonna be ok.
Come on.
Come on outside.
I'll show you
my chopper.
Maybe we can go
for a little ride.
Come on.
Wait. Gotta get my coat.
Oh, forget your coat.
[Chuckles]
Come on.
Hold on. Slow down.
Hey, sweetie.
I'm sorry I'm late.
You been waiting long?
Fuckin' bitch.
What?
Oh, sorry.
Oh.
Oh, I get it.
Look, um,
I had a bad day at work,
and I'm here to get drunk
and get laid
and wake up
in the morning alone.
You think
you can handle that?
Yeah,
I can handle that.
Sure.
Come on. [Mutters]
Fix you a drink?
No.
Uh, may-maybe
you wanna...
Uh, go to the bedroom?
This is fine.
Ok.
I told you
what this is.
No, i--i know.
I thought I could.
But you can't.
All right.
Maybe if we
get a drink first.
Forget it.
Wait.
Look, Rick,
nice isn't my type.
And...
We both know I'm not
what you're looking for.
Aah! [Moaning]
Come here.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
What do you feel,
honey?
Pain! Aah! Aah!
Man: Why is she so sick?
A touch of a cold
made worse by poor sleep.
You try sleeping
with one of these
inside of you.
Have you been smoking
throughout your pregnancy,
Ms. Robin?
Just cigarettes.
Your baby's quite small.
We'll keep you overnight
for monitoring,
but I think you can expect
a rough last few weeks
in this pregnancy.
Thank you.
You ok?
Baby.
Yeah?
When are we
gonna leave town?
As soon
as I make the deal.
Can't we just go,
make the deal somewhere else?
Honey, I've already
got a buyer.
Please, just rest
and take care
of that baby,
and I'll take care
of everything else.
I need some things.
I'll bring them.
Ok.
You take care of this.
Do not let this out
of your fucking sight.
Ok.
I know.
[Telephone rings]
[Ring]
Hello?
Is this
my little fern?
Vernon.
There's word
on the street.
Some kid trying
to unload 20 kilos.
Make sure he's got it
before you do it.
[Door creaks]
C.j.: Hold it!
Shit.
I got it.
So you just moving in?
No. I don't live here.
Oh, you working?
Working?
I'm sorry.
You mean,
am I a hooker?
No, I'm sorry. We
get a lot of those
around here.
You thought
I was a hooker.
[Mumbling]
I'm tired.
I'm sorry.
You are so dead.
How you feeling?
Emily: Good. Thanks.
No problem.
Can I get you anything?
$40,000.
I'm working on it.
A little fresh air?
That I can do.
So...how much
is it worth?
All of it?
Well,
we got about 10 times
what we thought
we were gonna get,
so...maybe 4-500 grand?
Half a million?
Really?
Yeah, but that's selling it
on the street,
and we ain't
gonna stick around
while I sell it
a little bit at a time.
We've got to get rid
of it all at once.
So it's only gonna
be like a hundred.
Well,
I'll take a hundred.
Me, too.
We're gonna build us
a whole goddamn house
with these little bricks.
Help me up.
I gotta pee.
Gotcha.
Careful, baby.
Here we go.
Do it!
Shit!
[Telephone rings]
Can I help you?
[Baby cries]
Yeah, I want
to get an abortion.
[Baby cries]
Ok.
When was the last time
you had unprotected sex?
I don't have
unprotected sex.
Well, unless
you're 2,000 years old
and your name is Mary,
you had unprotected sex
about 5 weeks ago
at least once.
I always use a condom.
Well, maybe it broke.
Maybe it slipped off.
And I'm on the pill.
How could I get pregnant
if I'm on the pill?
All contraceptives
are only 99% effective.
That means that
one out of 100 times...
You can get dressed.
Is the father involved?
You know
who the father is?
How many partners
have you had recently?
I just want an abortion.
Well, as part
of our services,
we require
that our patients
have some
abortion counseling.
Now, there
are alternatives
to abortion.
Adoption, for one.
Look,
I want the abortion, ok?
You want to waste your time
for an hour, go ahead,
but after that,
I'm gonna have an abortion.
If you want to help me, fine.
If not, I'll find
someplace else that will.
All right.
Well,
how about Friday?
Why not today?
We have other patients.
Friday's
the first appointment.
I'll find somewhere else.
I think you'll find
that most centers
can't help you
on a day's notice.
I have counseled
many, many women
in your situation,
miss march.
I find that
given a few days
to absorb the idea
of being pregnant,
they often
have a change of heart.
I don't want
a change of heart.
That's all?
Next Monday.
Ok.
[Sighs]
All right. Thanks.
[Hip-hop music playing]
Another.
You got it.
2 vodkas, straight up.
How are you?
Fine.
You look nice.
You want to dance?
Look...
Rick.
Rick...
You had your shot.
I know, I know,
it's just...
Why can't
we just have a drink,
get to know each other?
'Cause I don't
get to know people.
* come on, come on
* I don't want you
* you wait for me
* I need you
to get away from me *
* I don't want you
* you wait for me
* I need you
to get away from me *
uh-uh. Not here.
Come on.
Ooh, that's nice.
No, all right.
Ok, not like that, all right?
Just do it.
Well, why don't we just
fuck and do it my way?
Fuckin' bitch!
[C.j. Struggles]
[Door opens]
You ok? Come here.
Big strong man.
That way.
I got you.
Ok. Up we go.
What made you
so hard?
Baby.
[Whispering]
[Knocks]
Money.
It's Troy.
Hey, you don't
need that, man.
I'm just here
to talk business.
What you say, man?
I hear doin' business
with you
don't go so well
for some people.
What'd you hear?
I heard your game
clock's running down.
Look, I got 20 keys
for 100.
100? Hmm.
You know, 100 is the--
"I got clean stuff
and time to do business
right" price.
Now, if I were to get
this shit from you,
you could get the, uh,
"I gotta get my punk ass
outta town before I get
capped" price.
How much
would that be?
It don't matter.
Ain't nobody gonna
buy this shit from you.
No matter
how good the deal is,
the price is too high.
So why don't you get
the fuck outta here
before I go boba fett
on your ass and
collect it for myself?
Did you sell it?
What happened?
Nothin'.
Well, are we
still leaving tonight?
Honey,
we can't leave yet.
Look, I don't know
anyplace else
I can sell this stuff
but here,
so who knows how long
it's gonna take?
Just let me find a buyer
and we'll go.
Baby, let's just go,
please?
We got the stuff.
We can sell it
anywhere we want.
I just don't
feel safe here, Troy.
What are you
talking about?
It's a feeling.
Pregnant women
get feelings, you know?
Well, what if
we go to a motel?
On the outside
of town,
would that make you
feel better?
Why are you even
still here with me?
Please don't do this
right now, em.
I need to be gone.
Sell that stuff
on your own.
You're
makin' a fortune.
Why are you even
still here with me?
Because I love you.
And I love that baby.
And I would never leave
either of you for anything.
That's the alcohol.
Shit! What the fuck
are you doing here?
I'm bringing you
breakfast.
Could you put that
down, please?
I want you out.
All right.
Don't get
the wrong idea, ok?
I knew a kid in high
school who passed out
from alcohol poisoning
and never woke up,
so I brought you home,
slept on the couch.
So there's
your breakfast,
and you're
obviously alive and very
well-protected, so...
I'm leaving.
Um...you can stay
for breakfast.
No. I'm gonna leave.
Don't make me
force you.
Someone was
industrious this morning.
Yeah. Um, for years,
we had fresh flowers
in church
every morning.
Church every morning?
Guilty soul?
Probably.
I was a priest.
You're kidding.
Swear to god.
See, I can say
that kind of thing
now that i'm...
Not a priest
anymore.
So what was
the other night?
Just can't get past
those celibacy vows?
See, they tell you
that your love of god
and his for you
is enough...
But it wasn't.
Maybe that makes me weak
in the eyes of god,
but I needed
earthly love.
I have to go to work.
Where do you work?
I'm a bean counter
at a commercial
real estate company.
You like it?
Yeah. Pays the bills
when I show up.
Right.
Thanks for breakfast.
It was great.
Am--am I a masochist
if I ask for
your phone number?
Right. I left mine
by the phone.
T-Take it easy
with the alcohol.
You never know who
might wind up coming
home with you.
[Door opens
and closes]
Would you put that out
while I'm trying to do this?
I'm scared. I smoke
when I'm scared.
You smoke
24 hours a day.
Didn't the doctor
tell you it was bad
for the baby?
Well, I guess
I'm a shitty mom,
then, aren't I?
All right,
gimme that stuff.
Promise me we'll
leave tomorrow.
Stop fuckin' around, em.
Just give it to me.
Promise me we'll
leave tomorrow.
Baby, I told you,
I have a bad feeling
about this.
Promise me we'll
leave tomorrow.
Deal or not?
Ok, fine,
just give it to me.
That stuff hurt?
Aah!
Fuck!
Hi. Is--this is c.J.
Um, ok.
Uh, dinner...My treat.
Uh...bacachina, 7:00,
on orchid.
[Beep]
Fuck.
[Telephone beeps,
dial tone]
Hi, this is Rick.
Leave a message
and I'll get back
to you as soon as I can.
[Answering machine
beeps]
Look, no dinner.
Just forget it.
[Telephone beeps]
[Knock on door]
[Silencer shoots]
You workin'?
Yeah, baby,
I'm workin'.
I know you get asked
this all the time,
but what's a pretty
girl like you
doin' in a place
like this?
It's not what you think.
Never is, sweetie.
Man.
I ain't got no toys,
but I'll go down
on you for 20.
I'm looking for Troy.
I don't know no Troy.
I'll give you 100 bucks.
You don't even
have to go down on me.
Look, I just told you,
I don't know
no fuckin' Troy, all right?
Take
the 100 bucks.
Please.
Just take it.
A'ight.
Give me the 100.
Hal: So how do you
know pokey?
Um, from the street.
Oh. The street.
Come on
into my office.
Have a seat.
So what do you got?
I'm sorry?
What are you selling?
Is this place real?
What?
Offices and
secretaries
and shit?
I mean, what are
you guys doing here?
The only business
you have to worry about here
is what you bring.
I got 20 keys
of tar.
Ready to go.
Where'd you get it?
What the fuck
do you care?
It affects the price
and how I dispense of it.
You want to make a deal,
answer straight.
You don't, shoot it
all up yourself.
O.d., die,
I don't give a fuck.
Brought it
in from laredo.
45.
I told pokey 100.
Pokey ain't buyin'.
80.
55. Final.
L-L-Look, hal,
with all due respect,
this is 20 fuckin' keys
we're talkin' about here.
I need at least 65.
Did you hear me
say "final"?
55.
Fine.
Ok.
Tomorrow, call this number.
Someone'll tell you
where to bring it.
Have a good day.
Thanks for comin' in.
You, uh, you oughta
get that hand looked at, huh?
Yuppie-ass fuckface.
Bitch, chill.
You make me spill this,
I'm gonna fuckin' smack you.
What did I say?! Huh?!
[Knock on door]
Money.
Who's that?
C.j.: I'm lookin'
for Troy.
Come on in.
It's open.
Troy!
I ain't seen him!
Left or right?
Ok, fuck!
I got his number.
Some shitty motel.
Hello?
Yeah. Do you guys
have any vending machines?
Across the street?
That's it?
Ok.
Thanks.
Hostess: One?
Ok. Would you like
to sit at a booth?
Um, I don't think
we could fit at a booth.
Do you guys
have a bathroom?
Oh, sure.
Right back there.
Can I start you
with some coffee?
Oh, jeez, please.
[Laughs]
Emily: Excuse me?
Yeah?
Is there any toilet paper
in that other stall?
Uh-huh.
Have you
ever been pregnant?
No.
You have to pee,
like, 100 times a day.
[Urinates]
Ohhh.
They say that
it's the best thing
a woman can do,
but it sure as hell
doesn't feel like it.
* dance with me
* let's dance
What are you doing?!
Stop it! Stop it!
Leave me alone!
Take it out!
C.J., take it out!
C.j.
* dance with me
get out!
Aah!
Just leave me alone.
Leave me alone.
Whose is it?
It's mine.
I don't want it.
Why? I mean,
like this?
What are you
doing here?
You invited me
to dinner.
I canceled.
I ignored that part.
Did you--
is it gone?
Doctor: I take it you
don't want this baby,
Ms. March.
So I'm still--
yes.
You did an excellent
job of lacerating
the internal wall
of your vagina,
but you didn't
reach the uterus,
so for a while,
you'll find sex
painful,
urination
excruciating,
and there's a good
chance of infection.
You have
an appointment
for tomorrow.
Why on earth
would you do this
to yourself today?
Well, they
never tell me why.
I don't know
why I keep asking.
All right,
Ms. March,
if you don't want
this baby that much,
then let's
get it over with.
Are you gonna
do the abortion now?
I am.
And I don't mind
telling you
it's gonna hurt
like hell.
Ms. March.
Ready?
Carol Jean.
I'm sorry?
My name. It's Carol Jean.
Don't worry, Carol Jean.
You'll be fine.
Right in here.
Rick: I'm here
with c.J. March.
Uh, she's been
back there a while.
I just wanted to make
sure everything
was all right.
Oh, I'm sure it is.
The procedure takes
about a half an hour.
Procedure?
Mm-hmm.
Doctor: Now don't
you worry, Carol Jean,
everything'll be fine.
All right, you relax.
It doesn't take long.
All right now,
scoot down, lean back.
Just relax.
I don't want to do it.
Get me off of this table.
All right, c.J.
No one's gonna force you
to do anything.
It's all right.
It's ok.
Rick: It's ready.
Come on.
You invited me
to dinner, remember?
The least you can do
is eat.
You lived here long?
I never asked you.
Where you from?
Seattle.
My mom and dad
still live there.
Karen. Frank.
She's a schoolteacher.
He's an airplane mechanic.
Happy little life, huh?
Yeah.
So where's
the part about being
so against having a child
you're willing to mutilate
yourself come in?
C.j.
I want you
to leave my house now.
No. You want me
to leave,
then you're gonna
have to force me
out at gunpoint.
Heh!
Otherwise,
I'm staying,
and we're getting
to know each other.
[Sighs]
I'm not gonna talk
about that.
Ok.
For now.
Troy: Oh, you gotta be
fucking kidding me, man.
Are you gonna take
this shit off my hands
or what?
[Grinding]
Hey!
Do you mind?
No, no, it can't
be tomorrow, man.
It's gotta be tonight.
Are you sure?
All right. Fine.
Tomorrow.
Damn it!
[Grinding]
Would you
turn that off? Emily!
You said
we were leaving today.
Yeah, well, now it's
gonna be tomorrow.
Well, I don't want it
to be tomorrow, Troy.
I told you I have
a bad feeling about this!
The only bad feeling
you've got
is that 10-pound
deadweight
in your stomach.
It's your baby.
How do I know
it's my baby? Huh?
You know what?
Who knows whose
fucking baby it is?!
[Sobbing] Oh, my god.
Sorry, honey.
I didn't mean that.
I wish we didn't even
have this damn baby.
Honey, don't.
I mean it. I can't walk.
I can't sleep.
I hate this thing
inside of me.
Baby, don't. Please.
Ow!
Aah! Don't you
dare hit me, you fucker!
You'll hurt the baby.
I'm sorry!
If you ever hit me again,
I will kill you.
You hit my fucking
hand! I'm sorry.
I didn't
fucking mean to.
Fuck!
You sure
you don't want to try?
I'm sure.
* help me see the greed
in my head *
* hold me now,
don't leave me, god... *
I guess they don't
teach rollerblading
at the seminary.
* canned dreams
on the breeze *
* crosses of gold,
help me, please *
* oh, please
* hear the songs
in my head *
* how odd feeling
* are you going crazy?
* inside never goes
* dream to anyone
that knows *
* secret
* I'm not walking...
Heh!
That your mom?
Yeah.
Karen.
No.
I can't believe
I'm pregnant.
Having a kid
is so...
How could anybody
be so cruel?
Having children is
supposed to be beautiful.
That's why
you're not my type.
You're too
fucking cheerful.
My mom
was a prostitute.
My father was...
One of
a thousand sweaty,
faceless fuckers
with 20 bucks.
She died
when I was 7.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
You don't want this.
Let me tell you.
You don't want
to be with me.
I do.
Well, you can't.
Why?
Because you had
a bad childhood?
A rough life?
My life.
You have no idea
how many bad lives
I've listened to.
Horror stories.
Sins of flesh.
Sins of faith.
Crimes against people.
Crimes against god.
You know what the worst
of them all was to me?
Loneliness.
The people who had
the chance of love
laid out before them
who chose loneliness
because they were afraid
no one would forgive them
for their crimes.
You think you have
the power to forgive me?
No.
But you do.
Emily: Ow! Aah.
What does it mean?
It means I'm gonna
have this baby.
Right now?
Unh! Soon!
I'm gonna take you
to the clinic,
all right?
Oh! Do the deal.
Baby,
forget the deal.
Baby, just do the deal.
Please
just get the money.
I'll be back
by 4:00, ok?
Yeah. Ok.
Are you sure you're
gonna be all right?
Uh-huh.
[Moans]
[Telephone rings]
Hello.
Vernon:
I want to see you.
Vernon?
Vernon: Ivy.
What?
Ivy.
Another plant name
that women take.
Oh. Right.
Hearty plant, Ivy.
Tough.
Frost. Rock. You
just can't kill it.
Delicate flowers
can't live through
the winter time,
but a hearty plant
will always survive.
Take off
your clothes.
What?
I said, take off
your clothes.
Disrobe.
No.
Don't play tough
with me.
The bra.
No, that's enough.
Turn around.
How long have you
been pregnant?
I'm not--
don't be coy.
I said,
how long have you
been pregnant?
5 weeks.
Leave them there.
What are you
going to do?
I'm gonna keep it.
Is that right?
Yeah.
And I imagine
you'll want time off
from work, then?
Uh, what do
they call it?
Maternity leave.
I'm gonna stop, Vernon.
Stop? You mean
quit your job.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
You can't just
walk in and out
of this life
as you please.
I've been in
for a long time, Vernon.
I've always
done my job.
Then why
don't you do
your fucking job?!
Why can't you
kill this guy
and bring me
my shit?
It's the girl,
isn't it?
The pregnant girl.
I think motherhood
is making you soft, c.J.
Unh!
I want this job
finished today.
Is that clear?
Unh!
Get dressed
and go to work.
[No audio]
[Knock on door]
Housekeeping.
[Moaning]
Can you just
come back--ohh!
Sit!
Who are you?
Where is it?
What?!
Don't! Don't!
Please don't kill me.
Where is it?
Aah! My husband took it!
He took it to sell it!
Where?
Aah! At the train yard!
Please
don't kill my baby!
Please!
Please don't kill
my baby!
Please! Please!
Your husband
won't be coming
back for you,
so there's no
reason for you
to stay here.
Understand?
Yes.
[Engine starts]
Leave it.
Ohh!
Uhh.
Aah!
Unh!
Oh, god.
Ah, fuck.
Em.
Baby?
Honey, we gotta go.
Oh, my god.
We gotta go, honey.
Oh, my god!
Did you get the money?
Honey, will you
get me some towels?
[Whimpering]
Come on, baby,
I need you to focus.
Go get me some
towels. You gotta
stop the bleeding
and help me
get to the car.
No! Baby!
Aah! I can't
carry you like this!
I can't do it!
Baby, help me up.
Please.
Someone came here
today.
Someone came
looking for you.
A woman?
What are you gonna do?
You can't
drive like this.
I can get us
out of town,
and we'll find
another place
to live.
Baby.
I can't run with you
like this.
Honey, no!
Aah!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, my god.
[Telephone rings]
[Ring]
Hello.
Rick: Hi.
Rick.
I didn't think
you'd be home.
I was just gonna
leave a message.
Yeah. I, um...
I was just
grabbing some stuff,
and i'm
on my way out.
How about
dinner tonight?
Yeah. Great.
Bougainvillea
room, 8:00?
Bougainvillea room,
8:00.
All right. Well, um,
I'll--so
I'll see you later.
Yeah. Great.
Rick: Bye.
Good-bye.
[Beeps]
Unh! Oh!
Hello, flower.
I've been expecting you
all afternoon.
I--
uh, uh, uh!
"How to explain this
away," she wonders.
Were you
going someplace?
I was coming
to see you.
I did the guy.
It couldn't be
that you were leaving,
quitting your job,
ditching that
nice young boy Rick?
Leave him out of
this. He has nothing
to do with it.
Look at you.
Some microscopic Berry
in your belly
siphoned all your resolve,
plucked your pluck.
Is he any different
from all the others?
You haven't really
gotten that close
that you wouldn't just
put a bullet in his heart
if I paid you 20 grand.
Fuck off.
Let's see how deep
these new maternal
instincts fester.
Do the girl,
bring me my shit,
or I will hire myself
for one job
at the bougainvillea room
at 8:00.
C.j.? If it's a boy,
would you name him
after me?
Oh!
Aaaah!
[Answering machine beeps]
It's me.
I have to cancel.
I'm--i can't
do dinner.
I'm sorry.
Good-bye.
Help me, please!
Help me! God!
Somebody, goddamn it,
help me right now!
Dr. Martinez,
we need some help
out here!
Oh! Ohhh!
Aah! Aah!
[Screaming hysterically]
Try to calm down!
Aah!
You have to calm down
or I can't do anything.
Get it out!
I need you to calm down.
No!
Breathe.
Calm down.
That's
a good girl.
Good girl.
All right, now
let's have a look.
Receptionist:
I just can't. I'm sorry.
I just want to see
if she had the baby.
You know, say hello.
Sorry.
Do you even know
where she went,
or are you saying no
on principle?
Look, you wouldn't
want me to give out
your personal
information,
now, would you?
Your contractions
have started,
but you're
not dilated yet.
I'd say this baby's
birthday is gonna
be some time tonight,
maybe tomorrow morning.
I want it out now.
I don't blame you.
Just a few more hours.
You can stay
right here. Relax.
Your baby will be along--
no!
Ms. Robin, please!
I really have to go.
Ms. Robin,
you really should stay--
I'm going!
Call the police.
Just give me
the bag!
Aah!
Just give me
the bag!
I'll let you go.
Fuck you!
Aaah!
[Horn honks]
Oh, my god.
Did you see
what happened?
Help her.
We need
to help her now.
What's your name?
Don't move.
Really, you shouldn't.
You shouldn't move.
Unh!
Honey,
are you ok?
Oh! Whoo! Oh, my god!
Are you
having that baby?!
Walt, I need
a hand out here!
Unh! Unh!
Aah!
Unh!
Ambulance is on its way.
Ambulance ain't gonna make it!
Tina, get some towels.
Walt, honey, you always
like to play doctor.
Aah!
Where's that woman
who--that--
ma'am,
you gotta wait
for an ambulance.
Woman: That's it.
Emily: Damn! Fuck!
Fuck! Oh, fuck!
It's coming out.
That's it! Just breathe!
Aah! Goddamn it!
Here's his head.
Aaaah!
Ohh.
It's a boy.
Is he ok?
Why isn't he crying?
He's ok. He's small,
though, real small.
[Baby gurgles]
Can somebody
just cut this thing?
The paramedics
will be here soon.
You want to hold him?
[Sobs]
I'm gonna
go wash up.
We'll be
right out that door.
I'm so sorry.
You're so small.
I'm so sorry!
C.j.: Excuse me.
Tina: Oh, my god.
Are you ok?
Yeah. No, I just--
I'm worried
about my friend.
She came in. She was
pregnant, and she--
oh, yeah. She's fine.
She's right back here.
[Baby crying]
Where'd she go?
Aaaah!
Stop!
Aah!
No! Please don't
kill me! Please
don't kill me!
I don't want to die!
You know what's funny?
The only reason
I didn't kill you before
was because
you were pregnant.
[Gunshot]
Please. Here's the bag.
Just, please, you
don't have to kill me.
Why don't you just
leave the bag and go?
Uhh!
Aah!
Hello, flower.
It's over, Vernon.
No, I don't think so.
[Gunshot]
[Whimpering]
C.j.!
C.j., c.J., c.J.
Hey, c.J., c.J.,
I'm here.
C.j., I'm here.
It's ok.
What...are you
doing here?
I canceled dinner.
I know.
I ignored that part.
It's gonna be ok.
All right?
I just have
to get the ambu--
c.j.
C.j. Hey, c.J.
C.j., c.J. Hey, c.J.
I'm gonna
call an ambulance.
C.j., c.J.
* and I don't need
your revolution, hmm *
* and I don't like
your war solution, hmm *
* and I don't need
your institution *
* all it did
is just raise confusion *
* yeah, all it did
is just raise confusion... *
[rock song continuing]
Captioning made possible by
lions gate entertainment
captioned by the national
captioning institute
--www.Ncicap.Org--