♪
♪ I've gotta go ♪
♪ and find another direction ♪
♪ I wanna get your attention ♪
♪ I am so sorry
that it went this way ♪
♪ I just can't hold on
anymore ♪
♪ the feeling's gone
i must move on ♪
♪ there's nothing left
worth fighting for ♪
♪ I can't love you ♪
♪ anymore ♪
♪ go ♪
♪ find what
you're looking for ♪
♪ go ♪
♪ you romanced me
that's for sure ♪
♪ I've gotta go ♪
♪ find another direction ♪
♪ I wanna get your attention ♪
♪ for once ♪
♪ I've never been
in love before ♪
♪ but this is where
it has to end ♪
♪ I just can't love you
anymore ♪
♪ don't even want you
as a friend ♪
♪ I can't love you ♪
♪ anymore ♪
♪ go ♪
♪ find what
you're looking for ♪
♪ go ♪
♪ you romanced me
that's for sure ♪
♪ I've gotta go ♪
♪ find another direction ♪
♪ I wanna get your attention ♪
♪ for once ♪
♪ it all started
in another dimension ♪
♪ you may have took my rep today
don't take my dedication ♪
♪ they say that love is blind ♪
♪ they say that love is blind ♪ hey, Maggie.
Hey, Ryan.
♪ They say that love is blind ♪
♪ I've never been
the leaving kind ♪
What'd you do last night?
You know, the usual:
Had the driver take me shopping,
hit a couple clubs.
Then I wound up at some after-hours
talking fashion with the Beastie Boys. You?
I picked up Ashley grant
in the Ferrari,
had dinner at one of my restaurants, mm-hmm.
Reluctantly made an appearance at some v.I.P. Awards show party.
You know,
same old thing. Right.
Watched TV and made a mix tape.
Played the accordion.
♪ I've gotta go ♪
♪ I wanna get your attention ♪
♪ for once ♪
♪ I've gotta go ♪
♪ I can't love you ♪
♪ find another direction ♪
♪ anymore ♪
♪ I've gotta go ♪
♪ I can't love you ♪
♪ I wanna get your attention ♪
♪ anymore ♪
♪ I've gotta go ♪
♪ I can't love you ♪
♪ anymore ♪
Thanks, dad.
Ryan,
I'm only saying this because we're friends,
but you need to get over
this Ashley grant thing.
Because? You've been into her forever,
and it's just not healthy.
You're obsessed or something.
So?
So, Ryan, every guy
in school likes her.
You'd get crushed.
Hmm. Here comes
the steamroller now.
Upload by anyink
for 01.nonton.com
Hi, Ashley.
Whoa. Yo, baby.
Oh, hi!
Yeah.
Hey, Ashley.
There she is.
Whoa!
Did you see that?
Are you okay?
Ashley grant wants me.
Hey.
Hey, Floyd. You know what?
I'm gonna miss this place.
The games, the parties,
all these lovely women
diggin' me.
All but one of them.
Maggie Carter.
Breaks my heart.
But I still got four weeks.
Come on, man.
How many times you gonna ask her out?
And be completely shut down.
This time I got a plan.
Oh! Sorry about...
Your mouth.
That's the first complaint
I've had about it so far.
"Sorry about your mouth."
What the hell is wrong with me?
You suck with women,
especially fine ones like Ashley grant.
Way to go, champ.
Thanks.
Relax, Ryan.
It could be worse.
Oh, really?
Speaking of,
your mom's on stage in her nurse's outfit.
- Hi.
- Hi, Mrs. Woodman.
Attention, everyone.
Could you please
take your seats?
Everybody find your seats
quickly, please.
We have a very exciting
lecture today,
and I'm sure you won't want to miss it.
Watch this.
You're gonna get dissed.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Oh, gotta pay the toll.
You want me to kick you
in the face?
That depends.
Would you be naked?
School's almost out,
and you're still saying no to me, Carter.
Say it isn't so.
Really, man. The master
has lost his touch.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Katie woodman, school nurse,
and since summer's
approaching...
I thought I'd talk to you
a little bit about safe sex.
As you know,
the safest route is abstinence.
But if you're going
to be sexually active,
there's a few things
that you need to know.
Okay?
Where is it?
All right.
Speaking of wood, man.
Yeah!
That from mommy's
personal collection?
Shut up.
Those of you who may not know,
this is the penis.
Okay, this is the male sexual organ...
come to my house after school.
You want to? I'm having some friends over.
It will be fun.
The penis also carries urinary responsibility.
I can't.
I got plans.
That means that this
goes hand in hand with...
The latex condom.
Yeah!
Oh, man.
To be effective,
it needs to be pulled down all the way.
God,
that was like a bad dream.
Every man needs a dream,
and mine is to become
the next Virgil Doolittle.
You know what
he got expelled for?
Yeah, he stole gilmore's neck.
That's right.
Cooper gilmore has no neck
all because of Virgil Doolittle.
He got arrested.
And was charged with mayhem.
Mayhem! How cool is that?
The man's a legend.
The man went to prison, Floyd. Allegedly.
And besides, who cares?
It's been 21 years, and Doolittle lives on.
You know,
a recent survey showed that most women do prefer a man of danger.
What's up, cosmo?
How's it going? Cool.
♪
Hey. What's up?
Do you think accordion players have groupies?
I mean, really good ones.
Why do you ask?
It's three weeks to prom.
Oh, that's right. I don't know,
I think it might be nice to go.
I figured,
who better to go with than my lifelong neighbor...
Best buddy and partner in crime?
- No prospects, huh?
- Have you seen me with any lately?
- You gonna make me beg?
- Yeah, maybe a little.
Guess you'll have to go stag
with Floyd and the boys.
- No, you got yourself a date.
- Thanks, Ryan.
I should be thanking you.
Good night.
One out now.
Here we go!
I hear you're going to prom
with Maggie. Are you?
Where'd you hear that?
Stand up there,
Betty boop. It's all over school.
Maggie told me.
You excited?
Woodman my ass.
You got no lumber.
You're stickless.
You got no stick.
- Floyd, it's Maggie.
- Maggie's fine.
Dig in now here.
Closer.
Look, I know everything
there is to know about Maggie.
- Closer.
- It would be like kissing my sister.
Which isn't a terrible thing
in some parts of the world.
Walk it off.
Hey.
How many fingers?
Eleventy-seven?
Close enough.
Serrin, come on,
you're next. Let's go.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
The coach hit you.
Asshole. Ow!
Let's get out of here.
Walk it off.
I got a surprise for you, buddy.
Where the hell we going?
Right on time for the floor show.
- Can we come in?
- It's 20 bucks.
- You said ten.
- In five seconds, it goes up to 30.
God!
Come on, let's go.
For one.
What? What?
Go! You owe me!
I want instant recall!
Rent-a-cop!
Excuse me, sir.
Come on. Let's move.
Sir, I don't know
where we're going.
It should be empty now.
You got two minutes.
You go right into the cage.
You get busted, you do not know me.
Go on in. You don't have all day.
Move. Go.
Can I borrow your brush?
Yeah.
Here it is.
Great. Thanks.
Five minutes!
Did you get a good look?
Hey, hold up.
Wish I could, my brother,
but you know how it is, right?
Maybe we can hang out sometime,
troll for some skank
or skank for some troll.
What?
What's up with Maggie Carter?
Yeah, man, what's up
with that little sassy?
Why do you ask?
Maybe I'm interested.
In Maggie Carter?
Trust me, I've known her my whole life.
She's not your type.
Actually, grant's not yours either,
but I could hook you up.
Homestyle's got the hookup.
Who says I'm into Ashley grant?
Oh, come on.
I seen you checking her out all year.
Just thought I could help you out.
- What's the catch?
- Why does there got to be a catch?
I don't know.
Maybe because you haven't said dick to me in four years,
and suddenly you're
trying to help me out.
You're right. I don't know you.
You don't know me.
But prom's coming up.
I'm into Maggie. You're into Ashley.
She ever mention me?
No.
- Bitch.
- So what makes you think I have a chance with her then?
You don't, but Ashley's my cousin,
and I can help you.
Same goes for me with Maggie.
I don't know.
Why Maggie?
You could date any girl in this school.
But Maggie's special.
I can tell.
What do you say?
You be me, and I'll be you.
Chris.
I need to talk to you.
Deal.
Do you know what this means?
You're validating
our entire species here.
I'm serious.
This is like Lyle lovett and Julia Roberts.
Floyd... quasimodo and the notre dame chick.
Tommy Lee and...
Everybody.
Yeah! Of course,
he's somewhat gifted.
Studies show that 84 %
of all women polled...
Prefer technique
to physical size.
Don't tell me you can't
grasp the greatness of this.
You compared me
to the hunchback.
Next to Ashley grant, you kind of are.
I'd like to hunch her back!
Ashley's gonna love this.
I can't send her that.
You just did.
No. She's gonna hate me, man!
Hey, exactly.
I sent Maggie poetry from you.
Every guy in school wants to say something nice to Ashley grant.
Big deal. You gotta stand out,
be different.
Yeah, but
"your hair looks butch"?
Yeah.
Look, it will work.
Hey, Ryan,
your mom's heading this way.
Cosmo, get your hand
off the frickin' dick.
Don't worry, man.
Hey, Chris.
Hey, girls. You know Brian?
Who are your friends?
- That's Ryan.
- Yeah, I think so.
- You're new, right?
- No, I've been around.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I've seen you.
Where you been, c-man?
With Brian.
That's Ryan.
That's me.
Do you know about the party?
That's right. Ashley grant's, 9:00.
- Be there.
- Stop it. Bye, bri.
Bye. Bye. Bye, Brian.
Bye, Brian.
Hey, bring someone, huh?
Hey, good hanging with you guys.
Hey, wait up.
Good going, Brian.
I gotta go find Maggie.
Sweet!
We got ourselves an occasion.
The things I do for you.
You realize we're gonna be
the biggest idiots in there.
We're here! Thanks, dad!
See you, Floyd!
No, we won't.
Excuse my tardiness.
I had to kill a man.
Cosmo, what the hell
are you wearing?
Floyd said to dress up.
I look good, right? Yeah.
Hey, Uncle Floyd's in the house!
We're in.
♪
Smells like teen spirit, huh?
Drinks!
Yeah, yeah, let's go.
Is this what you had in mind?
Yes.
♪
Darn. That's what
i was gonna wear.
♪
Care to dance?
Go ahead.
That's okay.
- Why not?
- He's gotta take a shit.
Ashley, I have to... I don't know...
♪
What's he all dressed up for?
His mom died.
Earlier today.
Ladies...
Sit tight.
Oh, yeah!
♪
So she says,
"true or false?"
And I said,
"hello. News flash.
If you have to ask,
false."
She's such a liar.
So the liar.
Then she said,
"I can't believe you're acting like this."
And I said,
"I can't believe you're dressing like this."
Marnie, is that my dress?
No.
She knows you're here.
She wants to talk.
It's all good.
I'm on this.
Sloane got drunk and made out with that hairy guy.
You're lying.
You know you made out with him.
Oh, okay, whatever, marnie.
Ashley?
Hi.
Did you get my e-mail?
Oh, my God, was that you?
Yeah.
♪
Hey.
Did you get my words?
Poetry.
I didn't know you had it in you.
A little surprise. You liked it, huh?
Pretty freaky stuff.
Get you hot?
What?
Oh, man,
that was whack. Jesus.
Hey, Chris.
Thanks for your help.
Yeah, like Carter really liked your crap.
You see what just happened?
People saw that. Well, damn, man,
you're too cocky.
What?
I saw you groping her.
Look, it doesn't matter what I write,
Maggie's not gonna go for that.
She volunteers at a nursing home,
for God's sake.
Why?
That's what I'm talking about.
Grant isn't exactly
all hot for you either.
That's great. The idea was "Ryan impresses Ashley,"
not "Ryan depresses Ashley."
"Ryan gets pickle in Ashley,"
not "Ashley
gets Ryan in pickle."
Look, man...
Chicks dig assholes. Okay?
Check out stu and Harris.
They're both gonna
get laid tonight.
Come on, I'll show you.
Let's find Ashley.
Remember in grade school when you always picked on the girl you liked?
It's kind of like that.
Some girls are just insecure.
You're saying
Ashley grant is insecure?
She's the head cheerleader
of insecurity.
And if I treat her bad,
she'll go for it?
Absolutely.
That doesn't make any sense.
You've dated how many
of these girls?
That's what I thought.
Now check out grant.
Ashley. Hi.
Simple question.
Do you want her or not?
Well, yeah, but...
Okay.
There you go.
Now you're in the game.
You asshole!
♪
I got something for you!
Oh, forget it.
I'm out of here.
How could you have done this?
This was cashmere! How could you do that?
Because I'm an asshole?
Move, jerk!
Asshole!
What are you doing, man?
Those chicks were digging us!
Him. Him.
Yeah, that loser.
Kick his ass.
Want to see the rest of the house?
♪
This isn't working.
Sure, it is.
Grant asked me 20 times if I thought
the e-mail guy was right about her hair.
Look, even if everything you said is true,
I don't want to be mean to her.
Right, seeing as how
she's so sweet to you.
Listen... you know what Ashley said to me today?
She's looking
for something special.
I can get you there.
You can be that guy.
You just have to help me
be that guy for Maggie.
I thought I was being abducted.
How come you bagged on the party?
I had better things to do.
Like sleep.
You should try it.
So I talked to Chris Campbell.
I bet that was educational.
Actually, it was.
He's not that bad once you get past the jock stuff.
He asked about you.
Yeah, I got some
goofy e-mail from him.
You didn't like it? I mean,
uh... did you write him back?
- Be serious.
- Why not?
You haven't been
on a date in forever.
You think I enjoy
asking you to prom?
Hanging out with you
and the guys every weekend?
- I thought you liked hanging out with us.
- Yeah, some weekends. Some.
Okay, then e-mail him.
Why not send him the famous Maggie Carter soul quiz?
That would be good for a laugh.
Maybe. But maybe he'll ace it.
Then you won't have to spend another miserable weekend with me.
You know what I meant.
Yeah... I know.
Good morning.
What's up?
You guys get dressed in the dark?
It's mismatch day.
Maybe I should
go home and change.
You and Ashley grant...
I think that's your mismatch.
Opposites do attract.
Thanks, cosmo.
Probably not that opposite.
Hey, Brian, Carter sent me
like this midterm, you know?
Questions. I know.
It's a soul quiz.
It's movies, books, music.
If you pass that, you're a new man.
Famous. Of course,
there is one small hitch.
You do realize
Ashley grant hates me.
Clear the pool!
Man, she doesn't hate you.
She's confused by you.
She's trying to act
like she doesn't care,
but, believe me, Brian,
she cares more than you think.
She just can't figure you out.
It's driving her nuts.
You're this "new guy" Brian,
who's not into her for some reason.
- But I'm not Brian.
- Hey, Brian. - Hi, Brian.
Hi.
There they are!
Step off.
What a doofus.
You girls are hot.
What's up, dudes?
Who's the gerbil?
I'm Floyd.
You know, Ryan's friend.
The chicks want me.
See you.
Come on.
You got a soul quiz to take.
Do you want to see
what I'm writing?
No, just make me look good.
Not too cocky.
Is everything okay?
The last book he read
was nine stories.
Salinger. Wow.
It gets worse.
The Beastie Boys, the eels
and old cheap trick.
He aced it.
Movies?
Stripes, Casablanca
and anything by monty python.
That's great.
No, it's not.
It's horrible.
Chris Campbell.
Maggie, it's not that bad.
"Not that bad"? Man, he's gorgeous.
What am I gonna do?
- After tonight's double date?
- Not a chance.
Why not? Because as far as I can see,
there is nothing special about this person.
That's what he said about you.
He did not.
I'm serious.
He said those things.
He really likes you, okay?
It's just one date.
Trust me.
Hello.
When any chick goes on a talk show with her fiance...
And has a deep, dark secret,
has it ever been anything
other than "I'm really a man"?
Your fiance invites you on TV to tell you something,
she's packing sausage.
Come on, man.
I gotta get ready.
I know. Listen, that's why I'm calling.
Be careful tonight.
Maybe pat her down before you get in the car,
just to be sure.
- I've got another call.
- So what? Let it go.
It might be Chris.
Inbreed!
- Hello?
- I'm sorry, Ryan. I can't do this.
- I'm calling Chris.
- What?
Maggie, you have to.
It just doesn't feel right.
What doesn't feel right?
He passed the soul quiz. Ryan...
Maggie, i need your help.
No, you don't.
You're gonna be fine.
Sorry.
- Yeah?
- What kind of mongrel leaves a guy on call-waiting?
Floyd, I gotta go.
Cosmo says to check for an Adam's apple,
all right?
- Talk.
- Hey, Chris?
- That's me.
- Hey, it's Maggie.
- Hey, Maggie.
- Listen, I'm calling you about tonight.
Yeah, yeah... can you hold on one second?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Talk.
- Maggie's gonna call you. Don't answer.
- I already did.
Shit. She wants
to cancel the date.
The soul quiz?
She liked all that stuff.
I don't know what happened.
- Maybe she's nervous.
- Nervous stomach?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, probably the pill.
Put me on hold, and I'll try
to talk you through this.
But keep coming back
to me, okay?
Let's start with...
"I was really looking forward to seeing you tonight.
We seem to have a lot in common."
Yadda-yadda.
No, I don't think
"bitch, we had plans" will work.
Hold on.
Maggie?
Sorry about the wait.
It's cool.
So...
Great. Now that's my other line.
Can you hold on a second?
What happened? Oh, my God!
Your mom fell down the stairs!
- What?
- Mrs. Carter, are you okay?
Chris, can I call you back?
Talk.
I just bought us a few seconds.
Dude, you let her go.
She's not going.
She is going.
Tell her you need to talk to a friend tonight.
- Why?
- You're depressed. Your grades suck.
- Your father's on crack.
- My dad played pro football.
- Perfect!
- You're getting your ass kicked for that.
I don't know what your problem is, Ryan.
Okay, she's back.
Now, don't screw this up.
Hold on.
Hello.
Sorry.
Hello? Chris?
Chris, are you there?
Y-yeah, I'm here...
Baby.
Are you okay?
'Cause you sound kind of different.
Yeah, well, um...
Oh, yeah, see, um...
The battery's running low on my wireless,
so I have to put you on speaker.
- Can you hang on?
- Okay.
Just a second.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
Can you hear me now?
Yeah, sort of.
Listen, I hope you're not sick.
Well, you know... I'm sick
about this not happening.
I mean, I know I'm a jock.
I'm brainless,
conceited, in love with myself.
At least, that's how
you must see me.
But let me tell you
how I see you.
The you I see...
Has a big heart.
She's smart,
fun to hang around with,
she's smart,
doesn't take my shit.
And I like that.
I like that you look nervous
sometimes for no reason.
And when you do,
you bite your lip.
I like that you probably rifled through your closet tonight...
And settled with
what you'd started out with.
I like your smile.
I don't usually talk
this way, but, uh...
I think being with you
wouldn't be irrelevant.
You know what I'm saying?
Or maybe I should just stop
with all this weak shit.
- No, it's nice.
- Oh. All right.
So let's do this, huh?
You know? No pressure.
We'll go hang out, the four of us,
get to know each other.
- We could talk, maybe...
- Swap some spit.
- Okay.
- Famous!
- What?
- I said, uh, thank you.
Oh, yeah.
♪ Hey
do it ♪
♪ once I was a boogie singer ♪
♪ playing in a rock and roll band ♪ ♪
♪ Yeah,
there was dancin' and singin' ♪ ♪
♪ And movin' to the groovin' ♪
♪ and just when it hit me ♪
♪ somebody turned around
and shouted ♪
♪ play that funky music
white boy ♪
♪ lay down the boogie and play that funky music till you die ♪
♪ till you die ♪
♪ yeah ♪
So, uh...
You thirsty?
Yeah, sure.
Great.
Why don't you get me one too?
Hey, good one!
That's funny. That's...
No, we'll get it.
Okay, Ashley?
Okay.
Let's go.
Jesus, I'm dying over there.
Rejection, man.
You gotta piss her off.
Tell her... Her breath is rank.
I'm not telling her that.
Whatever, man.
I'm telling Carter she needs a tit job.
I'm just pulling your dick.
What do you want me to say?
Why don't you just be
the strong, silent type?
If you decide to talk to her,
be nice, all right?
Tell her she looks nice.
Tell her you like her outfit.
Okay.
You should probably tell grant her ass looks big in those jeans.
Uh... you look nice.
I like your clothes.
- Thanks.
- You want some?
Oh, my God, you guys, there's that octopus thing.
Come on, Marge, there's no line.
Whoa. Sorry, cream puff.
No beverages. What?
That's okay.
I'll just wait and hold it.
Whew! Let's go.
All right, tickets.
Have a nice ride.
Hey, midget man.
Munchkin guy,
make it go fast, all right?
Yeah!
Having a good time?
Yeah.
This is kind of fun.
Yeah!
Oops.
Sorry.
Yuck!
Hi. Hey.
Hey. Hey.
- Did you throw up?
- No, not exactly.
Sorry, bri.
Let's go.
Hey, man,
can I borrow your shirt?
No way, man.
I'll get cold.
Hey, girls, wait up.
What do I gotta do
to win a t-shirt?
You break it, you rake it.
Could you help me out, pal?
I got puke all over my shirt.
So?
Yeah!
Let's go, kids!
Who saw it?
He gave you his shirt?
A Ferris wheel.
Let's go.
What, man?
She was cold.
Wait up, girls.
Cute shirt.
Thank you.
Madge, who do you hang out with at gilmore?
Because I never see you around.
Mostly just Ryan.
Ryan?
Yeah. Ryan.
See, th-that's me.
Ryan's my last name.
Wait, wait. Your name is Brian Ryan?
Cruel parents.
I've told you a million times.
You've got to get
a faster modem.
So, um, you were right,
that e-mail you sent me.
My hair looks terrible. No, no,
your hair doesn't look terrible.
But it hides your eyes.
You have really amazing eyes.
Really pretty, wandering...
Besides, compared to your jeans,
your hair is a work of art.
So it's really great
that you like the eels.
I mean, other than Ryan,
I really don't know anyone else who likes them.
Uh-huh.
The eels?
Yeah, yeah.
They're... electric.
I can't believe you don't like these jeans.
They were really expensive.
- Even worse.
- Shut up!
It's the rhinestones,
isn't it? For starters.
- Who else do you like?
- I like you.
Mommy, can I have some cotton...
Anything else you
don't like about me?
- I could do without those shoes.
- What is wrong with my shoes?
- They're monstrous, bigfoot.
- Shut up.
I like that shirt.
♪ Did I find you ♪
♪ did I find you ♪
♪ hanging on the edge of the crowd ♪ sloane,
you did not.
♪ Hanging on the edge of the crowd ♪ sloane,
Oh, my God.
Later, Chris.
See you, Brian.
I gotta go.
Bri.
Well, thanks.
Bye.
Good night.
The things I do for you.
You didn't like him?
I don't know.
What's the problem?
I'm just not sure he has any heart.
Okay, it's a beautiful
spring day outside.
Most of you are graduating soon.
You've got your entire lives ahead of you,
so let's talk about death.
We all know lung cancer's a serious killer in this country,
what? As is aids,
leukemia and diabetes.
How'd I do last night?
What is the leading cause of death in America?
Okay, but she says you don't have enough heart.
"Heart"?
Thank you, Mr. Campbell.
Heart disease
is the correct answer.
Oh.
Nice.
Last year alone...
Okay, make sure
you finish chapter 14.
I guess it could be worse.
Grant doesn't think you have any stones.
What?
She said that? Yeah.
But you're gonna play football with me and some of the guys today.
She'll be there?
Yeah. She loves it.
We'll make you look great.
Hey, man, is Ashley okay?
She's a little different
than I expected.
Did you go out with your dream girl,
and you don't like her?
No, it's not that.
It's just...
- Good.
- Bad. Yeah.
Oh, she was nervous.
She gets that way
when she really likes somebody.
Hey,
you gonna play with us today or what?
Touch football, right?
Of course.
Get up, man. She's watching.
Okay, time-out. You said
this was touch football.
It is. These guys
just touch hard.
I am not doing this, okay?
These guys are like some huge government experiment gone wrong.
Come on.
Grant's loving it.
God.
Ouch.
Get up, man.
I used to play a little ball
back in the day.
Back in what day?
Ready to end this thing, Brian?
Who the hell is Brian?
Nice. Okay, you snap it to Brian.
You follow me.
Ready?
Break!
Hut!
Go, baby.
Go, baby! Yeah! Go home!
Go! Go, baby!
Yeah!
All right, Brian!
Oh! Oh! That's cheating!
Yeah!
We're here for you, buddy.
Hey... nice game.
Pick me up tomorrow morning
at 7:00.
Okay.
Well, I've done my part.
Now let's go get me that heart.
What are we doing here?
She wants heart.
We'll give her heart.
You want her to fall for you, right?
Not like this.
These people smell.
This better work. Trust me,
this will work. Okay?
Wh-what are you doing?
She's not eating it.
Maggie's gonna be here any second.
All right. Wait.
I give her the speech.
If she digs it, then what?
Then I don't know.
Try talking to her.
- Tell her how you feel.
- See if she needs a lift home.
All right,
I'll think of something. Okay.
She's coming.
Put that jell-o down!
Hey, could you maybe...
God, no... shh!
Chris?
Hey, you work here too?
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
I, uh...
I like to come here
from time to time...
Uh, to visit
with the sickly and old.
You think that's gay?
No, I think it's nice.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Well, that's what I do.
- Who ate my jell-o?
- Pipe down, you old bag.
- I want my jell-o.
- Fine.
Brian, give me that jell-o.
Hey, that's my jell-o.
Here it comes.
Mmm-mmm-mmm.
I think it's sweet
that you come here, Chris.
Mm-hmm. Don't you think it's sweet,
miss Simms?
- Just heavenly.
- Yeah.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Number two.
Okay.
You want me to take you to the bathroom?
No.
- You want Chris to take you?
- That would be nice.
- Do you mind?
- I was hoping that she'd ask.
Now, don't drop me.
Well, I guess this room's
in good hands.
Yeah.
I should get going.
Oh... okay.
That is a really nice outfit.
Ride home.
Do you want a ride home?
No, I have some stuff to do at the school theater.
There's a school theater?
Since when?
I mean, uh... that's cool.
I don't mind.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'll meet you downstairs in 15 minutes?
Fifteen minutes.
Okay.
The theater.
That's perfect.
Yeah, right.
Look, nobody better see me there.
So... are you in a play
or something?
Me? No.
I'm not much of a thespian.
Yeah, well, I hope not.
I'd be wasting my time
if you're only into chicks.
So do you like plays?
Oh, yeah.
We got this one...
It's a power 41 q.B. Follow.
I fake it off to the halfback.
Then I crush skulls
up the middle.
I meant stage plays.
Yeah. I was just joking.
Man, where have you been?
I'm dying over here.
Will you help me out?
Shh.
Hey, Chris. Yeah?
Let me ask you something.
Okay.
Why are you so interested in me?
We don't really make sense
as a couple, do we?
Well, uh... yeah, well, uh...
Sometimes the best things in life don't make sense.
Sometimes the best things
in life don't make sense.
Like rainbows.
And flowers
that bloom in winter.
Flowers blooming in the winter.
Besides, I think you could help me to be a better person.
Besides, uh, uh...
Uh...
I mean, um...
I think you could help me
be a better person.
You know?
How do you mean?
Well, uh...
Um... like be grateful for what I have.
Like be thankful
for what I have.
Sh-show some gratitude.
Show 'em some attitude!
Gratitude.
- Wow, she's really beautiful.
- You're really beautiful.
What'd you say?
Did you say
that I look beautiful?
Uh... yeah.
Uh... just like
a little flower.
Mmm.
Hasn't anyone ever told you
you're beautiful?
that you're beautiful?
In a very different way
than anyone else.
Upload by anyink
for 01.nonton.com
You know, I should be
pissed at you.
- You should be pissed at me?
- For making me fall for Chris.
He's great.
He tries to put on
this big jerky act.
Then he has these
amazing moments.
- So he's okay?
- Yeah, he's okay.
You know,
I can remember summer nights when I was younger,
just lying in bed and listening to your
father play the accordion for your mom.
"Melt with you."
It was her favorite.
I can remember feeling so safe and happy listening to that song.
Just wondering if one day someone would be that good to me.
He used to say he played
every note just for her.
This feels so strange.
You know, me and Chris,
you and Ashley.
It's almost like somebody messed with fate.
I'm gonna call it a night.
Hey, Ryan.
He'd be proud of you,
you know...
Your father.
Yeah.
You guys want to check out my prom date finalists?
Taylor and cinnamon.
Whoa.
Hookers?
Escorts.
Their people tell me they're interested.
You talked to their pimp?
We prefer "broker."
Floyd, you can't bring
hookers to the prom.
No way, dude.
I guess not.
Bet you Virgil Doolittle went stag anyways.
I'm sure he did.
I just had my legs waxed.
Oh, and look. It's new.
Do you like it?
'Cause I can take it out.
It works.
Sorry.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Look at those freaks. They're staring at me.
What? Go!
Hey!
Drive, Brian.
Please? Fine.
What the hell was that?
Maybe he didn't see us.
Ryan.
Hey, Ryan.
Hey, Ashley.
They look good together, huh?
You think?
I'm really excited
about tonight.
Wow, three more of those and you walk today...
Kind of like me this morning.
Scared of the ball, miss?
I'm sorry, man, but you know how it is.
Yeah, I guess so.
Get back in the box,
you girl!
When you quest for greatness,
victims happen.
Here we go.
Get up, you wuss!
So... what are we gonna do tonight, huh?
Dude, let's go bowling.
Yeah.
Hey, guys.
What up?
New school?
What's up, ladies?
Hi, everybody.
- You kickin' with these geeks?
- Why do you call them geeks?
Hey, is anyone doing anything
tonight? Because I'm free.
Ashley, come on.
Brian, I saw them waving
at you this morning. Please.
These guys?
No way. These guys.
You're with them
right now there, guy.
Yeah, "with." But we're all
"with" everyone, right?
So... anyway...
Stu, this game this week
doesn't look that tough.
So, sloane,
I thought maybe we could go shopping.
I'm looking for something short.
All right, look, you guys said it,
they're geeks.
Actually,
geeks doesn't even do it.
Give me a letter
of the alphabet, Chris.
"J."
Okay.
Jerks, jokes, jackasses.
- Try "p."
- Punks, pissants.
- Peckerheads.
- "F."
No, this is not...
freaks.
- Fools.
- Fungus?
"D." Dipshits.
- Douche bags.
- Defectives.
Dickheads!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
He did not just say that.
No way.
So...
I'll see you tonight then.
Floyd, wait up.
I'm sorry, okay?
But I'm this close to getting her.
That's great.
Floyd... no, listen,
you crossed the line this time.
I'm not kidding.
Ryan, I know that you're really into Ashley,
but maybe at some point
it's just not worth it.
♪
Ready?
Oh, yes.
Is the sea bass smelly?
It's a fish.
Hmm, no. You know what I'll have?
I will have a house salad...
With Italian vinaigrette on the side and I'd like a bottle of water,
only if it comes in one of those pretty blue bottles, okay?
If not, I'll have a pelligrino.
If so, not in the bottle. Thanks.
- And for you, sir?
- Some ice.
- Crushed?
- Definitely.
Oh...
That's okay.
Here, here.
Let mama rub it.
♪
Good party, huh, Maggie?
Check it out!
Full moon tonight!
Oh,
my God! Oh, my God!
Get used to it, girl.
Sloane,
that outfit is... great.
I like it too.
Anyone e nope, just us.
Any idea what we could do?
I bought some new underwear
today.
I thought, maybe,
i could model them for you.
They're mostly thongs.
Right.
- I'm gonna take a quick shower.
- Yeah, sure, I'll...
I-I'll just wait.
Maybe you could join me.
Oh, my God! Get out of here!
What did you see?
Nothing! You said
I could join you.
- I wasn't serious! Get out!
- Okay!
Now then, where were we?
♪
Damn!
What happened to your feet?
It's just a rash.
It's a crazy world.
Anything can happen.
If you shouldn't get away...
I mean, if, if something
should keep us apart,
wherever they put you and wherever I'll be,
i want you to know it.
Kiss me.
Kiss me as if
it were the last time.
I wonder if Maggie and Chris
have done it yet.
Could we not talk about her?
If they haven't, they will.
And then Chris will dump her like all the others.
You know, we could do this
some other time...
Maybe when you're more up to it.
Casablanca.
It works.
Guys... What's up?
Take me there.
Hey, Chris, you got a second?
Oh, uh, no.
I gotta go meet Carter
for some quality time.
Oh.
How's she doing?
Well, she's getting there.
What's that supposed to mean?
You did good, Brian,
but I got it from here.
Don't worry, Brian.
He'll treat her right.
♪
So what do you think?
For the grade school.
Can I help?
Nah.
Where's Maggie?
I thought you knew each other's every move.
So did I.
Hmm. You want to play with the puppets?
Not a chance.
You can change your mind.
That's okay.
Hey, ash, can we talk
for a second? I got...
Mmm.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
This cake...
Was terrible.
You didn't like it?
Oh, it was terrible.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Ashley.
Do I know you?
We go to school together. I'm Miranda.
Good.
Can you get me your manager? Thanks.
I'll just, uh,
pay for it myself.
Loser.
What makes her a loser?
Nothing. She just is a loser.
Oh, then what would make her a winner?
Hello? Nothing.
Okay, a tiger can't
just change his spots.
All right? I mean,
just be glad that you're a winner...
Like me.
What? What?
She is a fatty, round
little waitress, okay?
- You tell me what could make her become a winner?
- Okay, I'll tell you how.
- Tell me.
- I will. - Tell me.
I will, if you'd stop your petty, little,
self-important whining...
For just one second.
You know what?
I can't do this anymore.
Is this because of the cake?
Because I didn't like the cake?
You know what? I-I'm sorry.
I loved the cake.
Everyone, I loved the cake.
Could you try the cake? No, it's not the cake.
It's not the cake, Ashley.
Then I don't understand what you're so upset about.
I know you don't, and that's the goddamn of it,
is that you really don't know.
But then you said so yourself:
"A tiger
can't change his spots."
Brian... I'm scared.
Yeah, look,
here's five for the cake.
Five to buy a clue.
This is over.
Brian.
I love you, Brian Ryan!
"I love you."
So, when's the wedding?
Yeah, you picked out your dress yet?
Shit.
You fags be ready come prom night...
For the Chris Campbell
nail-and-bail.
Nice rhyme.
Did you make that up all by yourself?
I'll catch you guys later, okay?
Yeah, all right.
Right on.
So...
So, how does this work anyway?
The old nail-and-bail?
Like you don't know? I saw grant this morning,
blubbering like a whale.
So?
So, you didn't try to sleep with her?
It wasn't like that.
You see, it is like that.
No, it isn't, because you never cared about Maggie.
Neither did you.
I cared about her.
Don't look so surprised.
Nail-and-bail has crushed greater chicks than Carter.
There is not a chance in hell Maggie sleeps with you.
She's better than that!
Maybe she used to be,
but then you stepped in and changed all that.
- Didn't you, Brian?
- It is Ryan! It's not Brian!
It doesn't really matter,
does it?
Get in that box now,
sue Ann!
Have you seen Maggie?
I'm not talking to you, Jack hole!
Well, well, well,
what have we got here?
Someone trying out some pants?
Listen, you can be pissed at me if you want to,
that's fine.
I deserve it.
Just tell me if you've seen her.
Not since you scared her off,
bird-dogging for sniff.
What is this,
some ladies' afternoon tea?
Walk it off.
What are you guys doing
at my house?
What happened between you and Ashley?
Is there someone else?
Was it the hair on her back?
'Cause she is getting that removed.
Uh, that hair.
Isn't there anything
that she can do?
Look, short of camping on my lawn and begging profusely, no.
I cut out today and bought it.
For prom.
What do you think?
Yeah? I think it's great.
I mean, it's... perfect.
Do you think Chris will like it?
You know...
Are you sure about him?
I mean, are you really sure?
What are you talking about?
Chris.
I wanted Ashley grant.
So?
So I told him
what to say to you.
The e-mails,
the nursing home,
and he helped me out
with Ashley.
I'm sorry, Maggie.
I don't believe you.
Look, when you're alone
with him, face-to-face,
does he ever say anything clever
or funny or even sincere?
He's shy. No, he's not shy, Maggie,
he's a dumb ass.
In the theater,
I said you were beautiful. Me!
I meant it...
Because...
I have feelings for you.
You're really pathetic,
do you know that?
Maggie, I...
No.
I'm sorry if things didn't work out for you,
but do you think...
You could just tear me and Chris down
because Ashley grant broke up with you?
Maggie, listen, I...
No, because honestly...
I don't even see that guy you
used to be anymore, Ryan.
I see a liar.
Brian.
If you run your mascara,
it's gonna look really bad.
Would one of you whores
please give me a tissue?
Oh,
you can see her... oh, it's a twosome.
They're gonna get it on.
Oh, it's a threesome.
Hey, did you guys hear
the theme for the prom?
Uh-uh. Uh-uh.
"Titanic dreams."
What? Those people died!
True.
But they have become legends.
Yeah. Like your idol,
Virgil Doolittle.
Take me to the prom!
Please, take me to the prom!
Fine, just go home.
Okay. Thank you.
I want everything tonight to be as beautiful as you look.
Dinner, prom, the hotel.
Aren't puppies cute?
Get out of here, man.
So, I wonder where ash
went tonight.
- Is she not going to prom?
- She's going with Brian.
Yeah,
she was crawling on her knees for him.
Can you blame her though?
Brian rocks.
Give me a break.
He's a geek.
Tell 'em, Maggie.
I heard he plays the accordion.
To prom!
Go, go, go, go.
Hey,
watch the threads. Ouch.
I can't believe
we don't have dates.
I do.
You've got a date?
Well, you don't know her.
She's recently divorced.
Okay.
What?
Sure, cosmo.
Hello?
Where are you?
♪
♪ Yes, you don't look the same ♪
♪ the way you did before ♪
♪ hey, I think you
got a pretty face ♪
♪ but the rest of you
is out of place ♪
♪ you looked all right before ♪
Ashley, um, would you
sign my yearbook?
Twenty bucks. Cool!
I'll go get my purse.
They are so easy.
Let's go have our picture taken before she gets back. Come on.
Hey, what's going on,
hot stuff? Hey, nice ass.
Yeah, what's going on.
Hey, ladies, what's going...
Hey, chickie, what's going on?
Nice... and...
Thank you.
Next couple, please.
Our turn.
You kids next?
Great.
All right.
What's up, cosmo?
Good to see you. Hey, Floyd.
Daddy! No, no,
no. Hold on.
No, that's not daddy.
Remember, we talked about it?
That's mommy's date.
Okay? All right.
Floyd, this is my date.
I'm Floyd. You have a nice rack.
Well, thank you.
Nice. Thank you.
Hurt yourself?
No, sorry.
Buns of steel, partner.
Buns of steel.
Looking good.
♪
♪ All right.
People, listen up!
In a few minutes,
we will be announcing the prom king and queen.
I guess there will be no king
and queen of the prom this year.
I'm gonna go check my makeup.
I'll be right back.
That's great.
See if you can find your face in there, okay?
♪ Don't be a shit to your date, Ryan.
♪ Rolling back the years ♪
Come on, let's dance.
Mom, come on.
♪ Shut up and dance with your mother.
You know, it's getting late.
You're getting old.
It's early yet.
Is it?
Just a little
fatherly advice, kiddo.
It's later than you think.
♪
Gentlemen, the hour is nigh.
Okay.
What's "nigh"?
I don't know,
but I gotta go find my date. Okay.
♪
No, no, no.
Let's go over here.
I thought we were gonna dance.
We are, we are.
No, we're definitely gonna dance.
♪
♪ Put the music back on, man!
What is wrong with you?
This is bogus!
This sucks!
All these notes are for you,
Maggie.
Oh,
my God.
We don't care!
♪
Shakin' it, man!
See the geek?
What in the...
Woodman!
I christen thee...
S.S. Titanic.
Woodman! Get your ass off the stage!
Just get off...
Mayhem.
Get out of the way!
Stop pushing!
Yeah!
You guys should go back to the limo.
Women and children first. I'll meet you there.
Oh, my God.
This is beautiful.
This is the best prom ever, man. Yeah.
Oh, my God!
My dress!
Brian! Brian, help me!
Brian!
- Maggie!
- Help!
What the hell was that?
I'm cold, rose.
I'm so cold.
I'm sinking.
Rose...
Jack! Jack! Jack!
It's mayhem! It's chaos.
Nobody saw anything.
You see anything, Matthews?
No, sir.
I did.
He's the bastard.
He planned the whole thing
himself.
You fink!
They'll never take me alive!
Let's get him!
Never!
Get down!
Put your hands behind your back!
Textbook takedown, huh, men?
Make sure you rough me up
in front of the honeys, huh?
Hold up, guys.
I got this one.
Thanks, man.
I heard his father's in prison.
I heard he slept
with the school nurse.
He's hot!
Oh, he's boiling!
Take me to the hotel, driver.
Somebody's in a hurry for some lovin'.
Chris...
This night is really
important to me, okay?
It's important to me too.
Um, why don't you
lie on the bed...
And make yourself
a little more comfortable?
Good idea.
Ooh, this is it!
On your back, stallion.
Ash, look,
we got all night, right?
Yes, we do.
Okay, well...
Mmm, okay.
Why don't you just wait here,
and I'll go get us some champagne.
Okay.
All right.
Forgot something.
Hurry back.
Okay.
Hey, um,
do they have a jail out here in the woods?
Damn, Carter,
these knots are pretty tight. Summer camp.
Oh, God.
When good girls go bad.
Hey, uh, this isn't like
one of those games when you...
You give me a 30-second head start and then hunt me down,
is it?
Don't move.
Because I'm really slow
and not very cunning.
I'm sure you'd have me
in 45 seconds, tops.
Maggie?
Have you seen Maggie Carter?
Who knew you were such a freak?
I'm surprised you didn't.
I mean,
you knew so many other things about me...
Like my favorite movie.
Casablanca.
And my favorite book.
Ni-ni-ni-nine stories.
By the way,
which one's your favorite...
Of the nine stories, hmm?
The long one?
Sorry, Chris.
Wrong answer. What?
Yeah, uh...
Carter, you're sort of starting to creep me out here.
Shh.
There's just one more question.
Okay.
How's it feel to be played?
What?
Okay.
Smile now, prom date.
You know, Chris,
there's one thing you're right about.
What we do tonight is probably how we'll be remembered.
Hey, Maggie.
Hey, guys.
Is that, um...
Chris.
Yeah.
Tell your friends.
Shh. Don't say a word.
Just have me.
Uh, you do know that people
will be looking for me and...
This is really all Virgil Doolittle's fault.
Sure, I want to be a legend and all, but, hey...
Hey, I was just joking around,
pulling a prank.
You should really
think about it...
Your future.
Yeah. Okay,
I'll do that.
Thank you.
Maggie.
Maggie!
Maggie, I need to talk to you.
Lying and cheating weren't enough?
Now you're breaking and entering?
Ow.
The prince ascends my balcony,
looks deeply into my eyes
and says, "ow."
How romantic.
You didn't let me finish.
I mean, ow,
that really hurts like hell.
But not near as bad
as losing you.
Or knowing that
I can't take it back.
I wish I could, Maggie.
You lied to me, Ryan.
You steered me right
into that world,
made me feel like I belonged.
You do belong.
You belong with me.
You know, talk is cheap, Ryan.
And if there's one thing I've learned from all this,
it's that.
If I let you off the hook,
do you know how much you owe me?
I do.
The things I do for you.
Upload by anyink
for 01.nonton.com
♪
Got your neck back for you,
gilmore.
♪
♪ he's the kind of guy who's always passing by ♪
♪ who never has time
to spend ♪
♪ and he'll take you for a spin
and want to look within ♪
♪ to find out who you are ♪
♪ and he numbs himself
with weed ♪
♪ he's from the coldest breed
who judge by what they see ♪
♪ and I thought
he was smart enough ♪
♪ to know that the girl
on his arm ♪
♪ will never calm his storms ♪
♪ watch out
he'll charm you ♪
♪ smoother than
the L.A. weather ♪
♪ that's how he holds himself
together ♪
♪ he is colder
than the winter ♪
♪ I wrap my coat around
to better ♪
♪ counteract his charm attack
that leaves me hungry ♪
♪ well, I'm no savior
but I tried to save you ♪
♪ with all ♪
♪ my ♪
♪ love ♪
♪ that rage ♪
♪ and hide inside ♪
♪ and he has his minions
with no real opinions ♪
♪ 'cause they all walk
on glass ♪
♪ and your lies
become the truth ♪
♪ and give me the proof ♪
♪ that you really care ♪
♪ with your gorgeous grin
you have the world sucked in ♪
♪ believin'
in everything you say ♪
♪ watch out
he'll charm you ♪
♪ smoother than
the L.A. weather ♪
♪ that's how
he holds himself together ♪
♪ he is colder
than the winter ♪
♪ I wrap my coat around
to better ♪
♪ counteract his charm attack
that leaves me hungry ♪
♪ well, I'm no savior
but I tried to save you ♪
♪ with all ♪
♪ my ♪
♪ love ♪
♪ that rage ♪
♪ and hide inside ♪
♪ smoother than
the L.A. weather ♪
♪ that's how
he holds himself together ♪
♪ he is colder
than the winter ♪
♪ I wrap my coat around
to better ♪
♪ counteract his charm attack
that leaves me hungry ♪
♪ well, I'm no savior
but I tried to save you ♪
♪ with, ah ♪
♪ and he stamps
on every emotion ♪
♪ and he dampens
each and every explosion ♪
♪ and he stamps
on every emotion ♪
♪ and he dampens
each and every explosion ♪
♪ and he stamps
on every emotion ♪
♪ and he dampens
each and every explosion ♪
♪ and he stamps
on every emotion ♪
♪ and he dampens
each and every explosion ♪
♪ stamps on ♪
♪ every emotion ♪
♪ and he dampens ♪
♪ every explosion ♪
♪ and he stamps on ♪