(BEEPING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
TECHNICIAN 1: T2 over four.
TECHNICIAN 2: Check.
TECHNICIAN 1: Input mode.
TECHNICIAN 1: Touch system.
TECHNICIAN 2:
Touch system, check.
TECHNICIAN 1: Body tissue.
TECHNICIAN 2:
Body tissue, normal.
TECHNICIAN 1:
Skin temperature.
TECHNICIAN 2: Level fine.
TECHNICIAN 1:
Time code check.
TECHNICIAN 2:
Report complete.
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
(SIREN BLARING)
(MIMICKING REVVING ENGINE)
* Doctor, doctor
I need a doctor
There you go,
that's for you and you.
See you later.
Oh, Michelle.
-Oh! Hey, listen, did you talk
to Naomi for me?
-No.
(SIREN BLARING)
You can go.
I ask you to do one thing
and you can't do that.
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
(VOCALIZING)
* Naomi!
What are you doing?
Naomi, if, what if,
I asked did you have
any plans for this weekend?
What would you say?
I have and they
don't include you.
Why don't you save
some of that energy
and find yourself
a girl who at least
thinks you're attractive?
Oh! That was good.
You see, with your wit,
my brains, my brother's car,
baby, we can go places.
-You like Italian?
-Italian what?
Politics, football,
underarm deodorant?
No, food.
I hate it.
You see, I hate it too.
We got something
in common already.
Let me get this straight.
You don't think
I'm interesting.
You don't think I'm sexy,
you think
my sense of humor sucks.
And you wouldn't
go out with me
if I was the last man
in this hospital
named Jackson.
That's right.
You see, I think
all those things too.
We were made for each other.
Jackson?
-Yeah?
-Get your ass of my desk.
This floor is off-limits.
Okay, that's far enough.
(GROANING)
What the hell was that?
Be right back.
Hey, don't go
nowhere, all right?
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
You've got two minutes
to clear this area.
(GRUNTING)
You now have less
than two minutes.
-Get down!
-Go on, move it,
move it, move it!
-Let's go, let's go!
What the hell is...
(SIREN BLARING)
ZANUCHI: Okay,
let's go, everybody.
Let's move out!
Oh, shit. Somebody
is having a serious party.
Let's go, come on.
Get out!
Smart people
run the other way
when they hear gunfire.
Which means you must
be incredibly stupid.
Or the hero type.
Which is it?
I guess I'm very stupid.
Hi there, Mr. Trevelian.
Trevanian.
This is Agent Blackwood,
Agent Whiteside.
Blackwood?
Whiteside?
(LAUGHING)
That's cool.
Are you alone down here?
That's right, the computers
and I have an understanding.
They do all the work
and I let them.
(CHUCKLING)
This way.
They told me
I'd go crazy down here.
But I didn't believe 'em.
I like silence.
Know what I mean?
No, I don't.
Yeah.
Ta-da!
(CHUCKLING)
Not bad, eh?
BLACKWOOD: This place
gives me the willies.
WHITESIDE:
What happened
to the heat ventilator?
It's hell to clean
though, man. This way.
And there you go, gentlemen.
Prisoner number 569.
Patrick Dickson, architect.
Crime, murder.
Sentence.
(VOCALIZING) Life.
Life? In this?
Man, why don't they
just take the guy out back
and shoot him?
Because that's too easy.
It's no return value, right?
Right. But a lifetime spent
in one of these babies...
Your body frozen.
Your mind still active.
Forever wandering,
never able to rest.
Hell, if I wasn't so mellow,
it would scare
the shit out of me, man.
I can just imagine.
Now, this guy,
he just got lucky.
Get him up.
(WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING RESUMES)
Anybody got a beer?
-Nice threads.
-They're all right.
-How long
have I been in?
-Just 24 months.
Felt like 24 years.
Hey, I pulled guys out
after 20 stretches,
and they've gone totally
batshit, man.
You got off light.
Hey, who pulled me out?
Beats the hell
out of me, man.
Good luck, Dickson.
Dickson?
Hey, my name isn't...
TREVANIAN: Mr. Dickson?
Trevanian, FBI.
These are Agents Blackwood
and Whiteside.
-Have we met before?
-DICKSON: Er... No.
Why did you guys pull me up?
Look, we don't have
time to explain.
We'll talk on the way down.
BLACKWOOD: Let's go.
DICKSON: Hey, guys.
Look, I'm not going
anywhere till I know
what's happening here.
Mr. Dickson, listen,
we need your help.
-Oh, my help?
-Yeah.
-People's lives depend on it.
-Is that right?
That's right.
Whoa! I'm not leaving
this pleasure palace
until I know what's in it
for me. Okay?
Look, Dickson,
don't be an asshole.
You got a chance here.
You can go along with us.
We'll forget about
the rest of your sentence.
You'll be a free man.
Or you can piss me off,
I'll stick you back
in that tank,
you can keep pushing
your beard up
through your chin.
Full pardon?
That's the idea.
When do we leave?
(SIREN BLARING)
You really know how to
show a girl a good time,
don't you?
You should've come with me
when you had the chance, man.
We could've been
chilling out with some
linguini and white wine.
Now look at us.
Hey, maybe these guys
will let us
phone out for a pizza.
Yeah.
Just say the word, baby,
and I will kick his fat ass.
Go for it, Jackson.
Quiet.
(WHISPERING) Maybe later.
(SIGHING) My hero.
(BEEPING)
For crying out loud,
will somebody get a picture
on these things here?
We only got about
three minutes. Come on.
Three minutes to what?
Hey, how about
a little hint here?
Sir?
President's on the line.
Trevanian.
No, sir. We haven't heard
anything specific yet.
We're due to hear
from them again
in about two minutes.
Yes, sir. Right.
Yes, sir. Yes,
the architect's here, sir.
Right.
President was
asking for me?
Well, this is your
baby, Dickson.
You built the goddamn thing.
Now take a look at this.
Look familiar to you?
Now, we don't draw plans
as good as you,
but best we could do
on such short notice.
It's... It's terrific.
It's a...good effort.
I mean, you got
the scale and everything.
TREVANIAN: Now, the terrorists
have taken over
the top half of the building.
Here. From what we can
figure out, holding
at least about nine hostages.
Nine hostages.
Why is the President
so interested?
Well, one of the hostages
is special.
She's his daughter.
SARAH: Oh, you seem to think
I haven't got this
worked out yet.
I'm your star hostage.
Right?
So there's no way
you're gonna shoot me.
Want some free advice?
I think you should
get therapy.
Let me explain
something to you, okay?
Because I don't know
what planet you people
have been living on.
But obviously,
you don't know how things
work around here.
You're never
gonna pull this off.
The minute you walked
into this room,
you gave up living.
But you see...
I've never lived.
(TYPING)
(BEEPING)
We're ready.
Ten, nine,
eight, seven,
six, five,
four, three,
two, one.
ROMULUS: Who am I talking to?
Trevanian, FBI.
It's 10:15.
In four hours,
if I don't have what I want,
it's gonna start
raining hostages.
And I will save
the best for last.
Jesus Christ.
Say hello to your
father, Sarah.
I'm sure they have a hook up
to the White House.
Say hello
to your father, Sarah.
Don't give them anything.
So predictable.
Just tell us
what it is you want.
$50,000,000.
Where the hell do you think
we're gonna get
that kinda money from?
You figure it out.
Hey, my man.
This guy needs
some serious attention.
If he doesn't get treatment,
he's going to die.
We all die.
Sooner or later.
Bastard.
(CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY)
Whoa, whoa! Hey, you ain't
gotta do that, man...
You ain't gotta do this.
(MIMICS FIRING)
-TREVANIAN: All the stairwells
are booby-trapped.
-Uh-huh.
Now, they've shut down
the elevators here,
here and here.
Except this one here.
They've left it just
below the roof.
Now, that's our way in.
No shit!
The assault team
go through the elevator,
into the ventilation system.
Then the second team goes in.
First team,
disable the booby traps,
the second team,
take out the terrorists.
Yeah, right.
The only problem is,
they may have
booby-trapped
the air ducts too.
So when you get up there,
you'll be looking for anything
that doesn't belong.
When I get up there?
Yeah, they won't be
expecting that we're moving
this quickly.
Okay, look. Let me...
Let me help you out
a second here, okay?
I don't wanna
rain on your parade,
but why don't you just
include me out?
Listen here, Dickson.
You belong to me now.
You jump when I say jump.
Or I'm gonna make sure
you disappear off
the face of this planet.
Look, I'm just
an architect, all right?
Yeah, right.
And nobody's asking you here
to do gung ho.
Good.
Because I don't do gung ho.
(LOUD WHIRRING)
TREVANIAN: Now
once you get in there,
all you have to do is...
DICKSON: ...look if I see
something suspicious.
TREVANIAN: That's right.
And if you see
anything suspicious...
DICKSON: Hey,
that looks suspicious.
Go silent running.
(CHOPPER WHIRRING SOFTLY)
This is Bird Dog.
We're in position.
Roger, Bird Dog.
TEAM 1: (SOFTLY)
Move, move, move, move.
Get down, get down.
Dickson! Dickson,
get your ass over here.
Get down.
-Get down!
-Planting charge.
TEAM 2: Charge ready.
Everybody, head down.
TEAM 1: We're at the top
of the elevator shaft.
Going down.
Go, go, go, go.
TEAM 2: (WHISPERING)
Move out, move out.
That's it. That's it.
TEAM 1: Come on, Dickson.
Hurry up.
-DICKSON: All right.
-TEAM 1: Come on.
TEAM 2:
All right, we're clear.
(WHISPERING) Come on,
step on it. Let's go.
Move it.
Come on, Dickson,
move your butt.
Control panel
has been disabled.
We're gonna
try to bypass.
Bypass complete.
Gonna hook the remote.
Wait!
(TEAM SCREAMING)
Oh, God!
Get the medics down there.
Move it!
(SIRENS BLARING)
All right!
(SIGHING) Of course.
Nobody leaves the party.
TREVANIAN:
There's got to be
a file on this guy.
People just don't appear
from out of nowhere.
BLACKWOOD:
No record of him.
Well, keep looking,
goddamnit!
BLACKWOOD: Wait a minute.
Something.
Subject Romulus.
File status, classified.
Restricted.
Access,
Shadowchaser personnel only.
Romulus Shadowchaser.
-What the hell is this?
-BLACKWOOD: I don't know.
-(BEEP)
-WHITESIDE: Sir?
This guy's skin temperature
is practically non-existent.
There's no blood flow,
no warm areas.
No evidence
of human life whatever.
And his voice is hitting
sub-sonic ranges,
way beyond the capacity
of human vocal chords.
BLACKWOOD: I've got something.
Project Shadowchaser.
Project leader,
Joseph J. Kinderman.
Jesus Christ.
Kinderman.
BLACKWOOD: You know this guy?
Oh, yeah.
He's the head of ATR.
BLACKWOOD: ATR, that's...
WHITESIDE:
Military research guys.
Get him on the phone.
If Kinderman's involved
in this, the shit hasn't even
begun to hit the fan.
Jesus Christ.
Kinderman,
you son of a bitch.
Ha!
Romulus,
you son of a bitch.
I don't know who
or what the hell you are.
But you just murdered
five of my people.
ROMULUS: You've got
three hours left.
I suggest you
don't waste them.
TREVANIAN:
Three hours just isn't
enough time, though.
We're dealing with
a massive political and
bureaucratic problem here.
Well,
I've decided to make
it easier for you.
As you can see,
we have a very
sick man here.
So I've decided
to send him down.
You're a very,
very lucky man.
(SCREAMING)
I'd say that clarifies
the situation.
Very clear.
Trevanian, life is simple.
You live...
Or you die.
-(BEEP)
-I don't believe it.
Trevanian. Trevanian,
can you hear me?
TREVANIAN:
Dickson, what the hell?
We thought you were dead.
Didn't anybody
count the bodies?
Shit!
Listen.
Listen here, Dickson.
Dasilva.
My name is Dasilva.
You got the wrong guy.
-That's impossible.
-Check it out.
My name is Michael Dasilva.
(LOUDLY)
I'm not your goddamn archi...
(WHISPERING) I'm not
your goddamn architect.
Get a hold of that
spaced out dipshit
at the prison.
I want to know what
he's given us here.
-You listen here...
-Dasilva.
I don't give a shit
what your name is!
-What the hell are you
trying to pull here?
-(INAUDIBLE)
Come on, Trevanian.
I mean, I'm in the deep freeze
for years, okay?
You wake me up,
you offer me a pardon.
What was I supposed to say?
"Sorry, mister,
you got the wrong guy."
Well, he does have a point.
-Just get me the hell
out of here, okay?
-TREVANIAN: How?
"How?" How the hell am I
supposed to know?
You got me in this mess.
Now listen to me
carefully, Dickson.
There's no way that
we can come and get you
out at this time.
I suggest that you
hide out somewhere
until this is over.
You understand?
That's your best suggestion?
Boy, you guys really
got it together.
I'm telling you, Dasilva,
stay out of the way.
If the terrorists find you,
they'll think
you're one of us.
You'll be endangering
the rest of the...
Dasilva!
He's gone.
Check this out.
TREVANIAN: Yes, that's right.
I'll back you up.
TREVANIAN: No, that's right.
No. No, Margaret.
-BLACKWOOD: Ahem!
-I don't know
when I'm coming home.
Except... Yes.
Look, I'll call you if I can.
Right.
Is this gonna make me
more unhappy
than I already am?
BOTH: Yeah, pretty much.
"Michael Dasilva,
ex-pro football..."
I knew I'd seen this
son of a bitch before.
Yeah, he killed himself
a redneck in a bar
and claimed self-defense.
And I guess
they didn't buy it.
TREVANIAN:
A football player.
I put a goddamn
football player up there.
(SNIFFING) Oh!
Terrific.
I could have picked
the ladies' room.
Shh!
(CLICKING TONGUE)
Oh, I'm filthy.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
All right, come on out.
(ZANUCHI GROANING)
Don't touch the trigger!
It's a hair-trigger. Don't...
Don't worry. I know
how to handle a gun.
Goddamn it, lady!
You could have killed me.
SARAH: Scared you, didn't I?
ZANUCHI: Come on, let's go.
Yeah, you scared me.
You think he cares
about you?
He doesn't care
about any of you.
You're all expendable.
Yeah. Yeah, it's me.
Let me talk to him.
I don't care if he is busy,
interrupt him.
Damn it!
KING: Stand up.
Up, bitch.
-Hey, where are you
taking her?
-It's all right.
(NERVOUSLY)
Hey, come on, man,
you can't be doing
this kinda shit...
I'll blow your head off.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
-Bitch!
-(SCREAMS)
-(GROANS)
-DASILVA: Hey!
(GRUNTING)
Zanuchi! Zanuchi!
I was only kidding.
Ahhh!
(GUNSHOTS)
Oh!
We got a survivor.
-Deal with it.
-We'll head him off.
(GUN CLICKS)
DASILVA: (GROANING)
Oh, come on.
(GASPING)
I must've been
a real shit in another life
to deserve this.
(CHUCKLING)
We got him.
He is in the elevator shaft.
Ventilation system.
(LAUGHING)
(GUNFIRE)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(BEEP)
Shit!
We've lost him.
Goddamn you.
He's not one of my men.
Now look, you've got
my word on that, okay?
-Tell them your name.
-Romulus, let her go.
-(SHAKILY) Laura Jamieson.
-How long have you
worked here?
-11 months.
Romulus, he's not
one of my men.
-Trevanian,
you're repeating yourself.
-(LAURA SOBBING)
If I tell you
he's one of my men,
you're gonna go ahead
and do this anyway.
So for God's sake,
what difference does it make?
Let her go.
You know, I have to do this.
DASILVA: Hey, asshole,
can you hear me?
I'm not a Fed.
Okay, then who are you?
Just the wrong guy
in the wrong place.
You don't have to
kill the girl.
Look, it's me who you want.
Why don't you
come and get me?
(LAURA SOBBING)
Look, what's the matter?
You scared of me?
I'm up here,
laughing at you, man.
(LAURA SOBBING)
Goddamn you, listen...
(GUNSHOT)
Trevanian, you've got
two hours left.
TREVANIAN: Hey, Dasilva,
can you hear me?
Goddamn it, Dasilva.
Are you listening to me?
Go fuck yourself, Trevanian.
TREVANIAN: I told you
to stay out of the way.
Now, because of you,
we've got another dead hostage
on our hands.
Listen, you son of a bitch.
You think I'm enjoying this?
Look, I don't know
what's gotten into
your head, pal.
But you sure as hell
ain't helping my job any.
You're outclassed, Trevanian.
Don't you understand that?
Why, you asshole!
What do you think this is?
The first and ten
at the Super Bowl?
Hey...
Maybe you need
a manual to tell you
when you're getting
your ass kicked.
But I don't.
Forget about your
pardon, Dasilva.
Not only am I
gonna stick you
back in the freezer,
but I'm gonna make sure
you stay there for the rest
of your goddamn life.
Do you hear me?
Same old Trevanian.
Kinderman.
I see your ulcer
is playing up again.
I want all excess personnel
removed from the lobby.
"Excess personnel"?
What the hell
are you talking about?
This is no longer
a hostage situation.
This is now
a national security matter.
National security, my ass.
You think I'm gonna hand
this over to you and your
stormtroopers here?
My Pentagon clearance
gives me authority
over you at all times.
Isn't that correct,
Mr. Trevanian?
Isn't that correct?
Yeah, that's correct.
Then remove your men.
These two, they stay.
(LAUGHING MOCKINGLY)
Whatever you say, Trevanian.
Whatever you say.
-Insurance.
-(COCKING GUN)
Is anybody down there?
KINDERMAN:
Can you hear me?
Who the hell are you?
I'm Joseph Kinderman.
I'm with ATR.
That's Advanced Technical
Research.
What's the matter?
You lose one of
your lab rabbits?
I understand that
you've been giving
Mr. Trevanian problems.
That won't happen anymore.
I'm in charge here now.
Ah, that's great, Doc.
You've really put
my mind to rest now.
KINDERMAN:
I run a department
called Shadowchaser.
Sometimes known as
the Romulus Project.
Is there any relation
to the fruitcake
running around up here?
(CHUCKLING) Yes.
Your perspicacity amazes me.
Now the aim of the project
was to create a perfect
synthetic warrior.
Intelligent, adaptable,
self-sufficient.
Unhindered by any
sense of morality.
And Romulus is that creation.
DASILVA: An android.
You gotta be kidding.
This psycho's an android?
Android, yes.
Psycho, no.
His mind is not disturbed.
Merely free of the usual
social and emotional
inhibitions.
Well, that's terrific, Doc.
Because this guy's stairs
definitely do not
reach the attic.
Romulus is a billion-dollar
killing machine, Mr. Dasilva.
You have
no chance against him.
I'd advise you
to keep out of his way...
...and mine, until this
situation is resolved.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Don't be stupid!
Come on! Shoot me. Shoot me!
Do I look like
a goddamned terrorist?
Yes.
Well, I'm not.
Well, what are you? You a cop?
Not exactly.
FBI?
CIA?
-Special Forces good guy?
-(GROANS SOFTLY)
They've been fiddling
with that computer
for the last 20 minutes.
They're working on
a newfangled hot idea to beat
the android. (SCOFFING)
BLACKWOOD: Yeah, well,
maybe they're gonna challenge
him to a game of chess.
Yeah, maybe.
(WHISPERING)
Come on. We're leaving.
Oh... Wait a minute.
I have to change.
We don't have
any time for that!
Oh, no, I'm not going
out there looking like this.
I'd look ridiculous.
DASILVA: You'd look
a lot worse
in the morgue, lady.
Close the door.
Please close the door.
ZANUCHI: Any luck?
FRANCO: No,
I haven't seen him.
ZANUCHI:
Well, let's look this way.
SARAH: Ready.
What is that?
I got food poisoning at
the French Embassy.
This is all I have to wear.
-Shoes.
Lose the shoes.
Who the hell do you
think your pushing?
What are you doing?
How do you expect me...
-Listen, lady!
-What?
Out there you may be
the President's daughter,
but in here, you're just
excess baggage.
Oh, you think I'm gonna
tie you down.
Tennis, swimming,
track, archery,
fencing, gymnastics,
horseback riding and riflery.
Now do you think you can
keep up with that?
Look, lady, I've had
a very shitty day.
And if you give me
anymore trouble,
I am gonna leave you here.
Got it?
Yeah. Got it.
One thing...
Keep your paws to yourself.
No, thank you. I don't think
that I'll wear them,
as you so politely suggested.
Smart girl.
TREVANIAN: Dasilva.
Tell him I'm rescuing you.
He says he's rescuing me.
That crazy, gung ho
bastard's got the girl!
Look, Dasilva,
there's no place
that you can go.
Dasilva!
-Romulus, this is Kinderman.
-What the hell are you doing?
-Dasilva is with the girl.
-Are you crazy?
He's not acting on my orders,
he's working on his own.
He has no...
(GRUNTING)
Shit!
Go!
Hey, asshole.
You're supposed
to pull the pin out.
(DASILVA COUGHING)
Jonah, level 38.
Now.
You pull a stunt
like that again,
I won't care what kinda
clearance you've got,
I'll bust your ass!
Look, I have one chance,
just one chance
of retrieving Romulus.
And I'm not gonna let you
or Dasilva stand in my way.
Retrieve Romulus?
You're slime.
You don't care about
the hostages.
You just want
your goddamn robot back, huh?
Yeah. That is correct.
Just tell me,
how are you gonna do that?
That information comes
on a need to know basis.
You do not need to know.
-(SHRIEKS)
-It's only me.
-What?
-I can't climb in this.
Oh! (SHRIEKS)
Please! You have no respect.
-Push me up.
-DASILVA: Come on, get up!
All right,
all right, all right.
Okay.
SARAH: (WHISPERS) Respect...
-DASILVA:
What are you mumbling?
-Respect. It's gone.
Look, don't let it
go to your head, okay?
That 50,000,000?
There's only one guy who
thinks you're worth that.
And he runs on batteries.
My white knight.
(PANTING)
What are you doing?
Catching up on some sleep.
I've only had
a couple of years.
No!
No, no, no, no, no.
This is not naptime.
Why don't we keep moving?
-Where to?
-Oh, out of the building,
away from here.
All the exits are blocked.
You mean this is it?
The light at the end
of the tunnel.
Look, you wanna
go out there and
get yourself killed, terrific.
Me, I got
a couple more things
I wanna do with my life.
(GASPING)
Number four!
Football!
You were in the
Saints play-off game.
That Saints play-off game!
-Right? Am I right?
-You were there?
You bet I was there.
Right! You were
the third strength quarterback
who ran over 100 yards
in the fourth quarter.
-That was so incredible.
-(CHUCKLING)
Yes, that was a great run.
My God, I've never
seen that done before.
And you know, I think
they should've really
started you in that game.
I mean, I knew
that you had an arm.
I had no idea you had
a pair of legs like that.
What wheels, you were smoking!
Man, I knew
the first quarterback...
But you really should've
passed to Andrews
when you had the chance.
What are you talking about?
Andrews was covered by Rudge!
Yeah, yeah. Stoker, no,
he was on the 40,
Hirsthill took him down.
Mmm-mmm.
-Are you kidding me?
-You had time
to make that pass.
Give me a break!
Valentine and Cobley,
they were up my ass.
What was I supposed to do?
Stand still?
Davies, he was smoking
up your ass.
Now if he'd made
the touchdown,
you'd have been dead meat.
No way! I was miles
ahead of him.
He never would've caught me.
That's only 'cause Hal
took him down
before you made the TD.
Well, that's what you call
team-work, babe.
-Yeah. And your timing
was incredible.
-(CHUCKLING)
You really, really did it.
God, what the hell
happened to you?
(SIGHING)
Special Forces good guy.
So, you're just gonna
sit around here
on your ass, huh?
Tell you what.
I'll flap my arms
and I'll fly us
out of here. Okay?
There are only two ways out.
The stairs and the elevators.
And they are all
booby-trapped.
Booby-trapped.
They're all booby-trapped.
Of course!
-What?
-They'd have to.
They'd have to what?
Come on. Come on.
Fox, this is Chicken Hawk.
Do you read?
This is Fox.
What's your status,
Chicken Hawk?
Sir, Blackwood.
What do ya got?
We're picking up
a high frequency
radio transmission.
Put it on the speaker.
ROMULUS: On schedule.
Wait for my signal,
15 minutes before pickup.
Roger, Fox. Chicken Hawk out.
Chicken Hawk.
-That's an old
helicopter designation.
-Yeah, yeah.
Well, it makes sense.
A helicopter's the only way
they could get out of here.
Harris, keep us posted.
Come on.
-Well?
-No, no. Nothing more.
Right, if Romulus is gonna
give his pilot an all-clear
15 minutes before
he's due to pick him up,
that chopper's got to be
parked within this radius.
There are only
a couple of possibilities.
The dump site
and the old factory
on the east side.
The rest is residential.
All right, check it out.
We got exactly one hour
to pull something
out of the hat.
You think if we pull
this one off,
there's a nice,
big, fat bonus?
If we pull this off,
we'll be lucky to keep
what's left of our nuts.
I hear you.
Come on,
let's get out of here!
Trevanian, where are
those men going?
That information comes
on a need to know basis
and you don't need to know.
Excuse me,
I don't mean to ask
a trivial question but...
Shh! I think I just
found a way out of here.
Oh, you've made a decision.
That's because I'm concerned
about your future.
Mr. President, I believe
we have one chance
of overcoming Romulus.
But it will have to be done
face to face.
And the only possible
opportunity
is during the exchange for
the money for the hostages.
Yes, Mr. President,
I'm quite aware of that.
But this will work.
I can absolutely guarantee it.
Thank you, Mr. President.
You won't regret
this decision.
The money's on its way.
Pardon me.
Can you tell me where
the men's room is, please?
Oh, so sorry, I thought
you were a man.
Come on, lady,
let's not go
through this again.
Give me the gun.
Come and get it!
-(CRIES OUT IN SHOCK)
-Yes!
Bye-bye!
Back! Up! Up!
Oh! Hold back! Off!
Oh!
Trevanian, I'm sending
the girl down now.
Yeah!
You bring her down,
I'll buy you the biggest
goddamn beer you ever saw.
See ya.
You're crazy.
Certifiable.
(COCKS GUN) Good.
Let's go.
Hey, Dasilva,
what're you waiting for?
No more heroics.
You want your pardon,
you get the hell
outta there now!
You get outta there now!
Romulus,
this is Kinderman.
Kinderman.
It isn't every day
you get the chance
to talk to your creator.
Should I be honored?
Romulus, you can't win.
Oh, can't I?
KINDERMAN:
I know your limitations.
You can be brought down.
Blind optimism.
It is such an
endearing quality.
Why are you doing this?
You have no interest in money.
ROMULUS: I've learned
that money is freedom.
What was my future with you?
A toy soldier?
Obedient...
Expendable.
There's a lot of me
in you, Romulus.
I don't wish to
see you destroyed.
Oh, am I touched.
Or...
Are you concerned with your
billion dollar investment?
Then I'll have to bring
you down, Romulus.
Then who better to do it
than my creator?
Or I will have to destroy you.
But what if...
The creation destroys
the creator?
Now that would be
true freedom.
(PLAYING TUNE ON MOUTH ORGAN)
Okay, come on folks,
there's a better party
downstairs.
Let's go! Do you think
you can handle this?
No, but I'll figure it out.
-All right,
let's get outta here.
-Come on.
Come on, everybody. Come on.
Listen, I never got a chance
to thank you.
-Maybe we can
talk about it downstairs.
-Let's get outta here.
I can see why they
had to freeze you.
Come on. Come on.
SARAH: Come on.
(BEEP)
-Come on.
-Come on. Come on,
let's go, let's go.
Come on! Move it,
move it, move it!
Come on, let's go!
Oh, shit!
SARAH: Come on! Go! Go! Now!
Ahhh!
(SARAH GASPS)
Let's go.
-Ow!
-DASILVA: Watch it!
SARAH: Quit whining, will you?
(WHISPERING) Wait, wait, wait.
Okay, come on.
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(BREATHING HARD)
Going somewhere?
(WHIRRING)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(BEEPS)
(BOTH BREATHING HARD)
Listen.
Why isn't he following us?
(SIREN BLARING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Go.
(CRIES OUT)
Hold on!
(SARAH GRUNTING)
-(SARAH SCREAMING)
-Hold on!
-Sarah!
-Ahhh!
-DASILVA: Hold on!
-I am!
Sarah!
Romulus.
Time's up.
And I hope for the girl's sake
that you have the money.
-KINDERMAN: It's here.
-I've sent down the elevator.
I'd like the President
to bring it up himself.
Are you absolutely crazy?
That's not the deal, Romulus.
That was never the deal.
Mr. President,
I'm sure you're watching this.
It isn't a difficult choice.
Either you bring
me the money...
Or you watch
your daughter die.
(SIREN BLARING)
KINDERMAN: Now, this dart
contains a compound
of acid and ZSV.
It's a micro-explosive.
I know what the hell it is.
Once injected into
the bio-stream,
the ZSV travels
instantly to the cortex,
where it detonates.
A tiny explosion.
(CHUCKLING)
But a fatal one for Romulus.
A sort of android embolism.
(SIREN WAILING)
-Dr. Kinderman.
-Mr. President.
Sir.
I believe you've been working
on a surprise for Romulus.
Yes, sir, it's ready, sir.
Mr. President,
there's no guarantee
that this half-assed thing
is even gonna work.
Speaking in ignorance again,
Mr. Trevanian.
Gentlemen, at this late stage,
I do not believe
it serves any purpose
in quibbling
amongst ourselves.
Is this your marksman?
Yes, sir. The very best, sir.
I hope so.
As I have discussed
with Agent Trevanian,
Romulus will not
be expecting me
so we can use
the element of surprise.
It will all be over
in a few seconds.
TREVANIAN:
Good luck, Mr. President.
This may be
the last chance I have
to talk to you, Romulus.
You said that if the creation
destroys the creator,
that would be true freedom.
Do you remember?
I remember.
Well, now's your opportunity.
Are you going to take it?
-(GUNSHOT)
-Oh!
Why?
You're a popular man,
Mr. President.
Your policies of
international appeasement
have earned you acclaim
the world over.
And while you have been busy
touting for votes,
our enemies
have been laughing at us.
Laughing at the new America,
the soft America.
Many of us do not share
your vision, Mr. President.
So that when
you step down from office,
you'll make way for
a stronger government.
One that wants to see
this country great again.
Step down from office?
You're insane.
I have no intention
of stepping down!
Wrong.
(SARAH SHRIEKS) No!
Ahhh!
Kill the girl.
DASILVA: Trevanian.
Looks like you've been shafted
good and hard, pal.
Looks like we both have.
Fox to Chicken Hawk.
Come on in.
Go ahead, Fox.
You've got the green light,
Chicken Hawk.
Come and get us.
Roger, Fox. I'm on my way.
(SIREN BLARING)
-Hold it right there! FBI!
-Don't move.
BOTH: Jesus!
Trevanian, the booby traps
have been reset.
And they're counting down.
In 15 minutes,
this whole place
is gonna blow.
Yeah, Dasilva, I know, I know.
Pretty good scam
you just pulled, Kinderman.
You don't know
when you're finished,
do you, Dasilva?
Sorry, but I gotta
settle something with
this freak of yours.
Come on, asshole,
you can do better than that.
Leave him.
He's insignificant now.
Whatever you say.
DASILVA: Hey, sweetness,
my grandmother can
shoot better than that.
And she's dead.
(COCKING GUN)
What's the matter, piss eyes?
You need a fresh jumpstart?
(GUN CLICKING)
Okay, you're not
in the shape you used to be,
but this is one touchdown
you can't afford to miss.
(GRUNTS)
Hut!
Big mistake.
You've been a constant
source of amusement.
Well, try laughing
this off, shithead.
(CRIES OUT IN SHOCK)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Ahhh!
(WHIRRING)
(BEEPING)
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
They'll hunt you down.
You'll never get away with it.
My dear child,
I have got away with it.
(SCREAMING)
(GUNS COCKING)
It's over. Let her go.
(PANTING)
Sarah!
(SNARLING)
No!
WHITESIDE: Come on!
I got ya! I got ya!
Dasilva, hang on! Come on!
Hold on, hold on!
SARAH: Hold on!
WHITESIDE:
Hang on! Pull him up!
Pull him up!
Hang on!
(GRUNTING)
Come on! Pull him up!
Pull him up!
Come on, man.
Just a little bit more.
Come on!
No!
Ahhh!
(INAUDIBLE)
WHITESIDE:
Just a little bit more, pull!
Be strong, be strong!
Come on, now. Pull up!
For Christ's sakes, pull up!
(SIREN WAILING)
Touchdown!
Sarah! Sarah!
Sarah.
Sarah, are you all right?
Sarah, there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
Oh, Sarah.
Come on home.
I thought you said
he was dead.
Kinderman?
He never had a monopoly
on android research.
You son of a bitch.
(INAUDIBLE)
JACKSON: Yo, Dasilva!
(CHUCKLING)
MAN: Hell, if I wasn't
so mellow, it would scare
the shit out of me, man.