- I see you've met
the neighbours.
Ah, just like clockwork.
- I don't think the restaurantis going
to let you in like that.
- We can always order in.
- Or you could put
your pants on.
- Sure.
I love keeping this apartment.
After a long day at the office,
you're tired, lots
of stress.
You need some place where you
can get out of your clothes
and slip into something
comfortable.
- Who's this?
- That is my wife.
She had a stroke
2 years ago, her 2nd.
She slipped into a coma.
The damage was massive and
irreversible.
- I'm sorry,
I didn't know.
- Thank you, but now I've
mourned her, and I want to move
on with the rest of my life.
Do you think
that's heartless?
- No. Life goes on.
- You're very philosophical.
So how about that trip
to Aspen?
- Damn.
- Parker.
[ Telephone ]
- Deaton Investigation,
Parker here.
- [Whispering]: Heads or tails?
- Heads.
- Ooh, sorry.
- Yeah, what's your name?
Lewis. How do you spell that?
- Hey.
- Anything interesting?
- His wife's in a coma...
stroke.
The prognosis isn't helpful.
- I'll be sure to send
my condolences as soon as she
gets back from the spa.
Have you got the tape?
- You should have heard this
guy, Jack. I would have bought
life insurance from him.
- Thanks. Here, I've got another
job for you.
- Yeah.
- It pays $800.
- What's the catch?
- The wife wants to catch her
husband in the act.
- Oh no, forget it. Get Denise,
she gets off on confrontations.
- She isn't working for awhile.
Don't give me a hard time on
this, all right. You're the best
decoy I've got.
Nobody gets those cheating
husbands talking like you do.
- I could use an advance.
- What a surprise.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- I want you to take this.
- Uh, no.
- You know how much it cost
me to get you licensed
and certified.
- And I told you
I don't like guns.
- Well, neither do the bad guys.
Just do it for me.
It'll make me feel better.
Just take it, put it in your
purse. You'll get used to it.
- Happy?
- Yeah.
So, you want to grab a bite
or something?
My treat.
- You know, I just want to go
home and take a bath.
- You need someone
to wash your back?
- I think I can handle it.
Hey Denise. Listen,
Jack said...
- Hey, kiddo.
- Denise, oh my God.
- Jimmy.
- You can't let him keep doing
this to you.
- I know.
It's the last time.
[ Hushed voices ]
- I'm going to call the cops.
- No, look, it's okay.
He was just drunk.
- Denise, you can't let him keep
doing this to you.
- I know, I told him this was
the last time, and I mean it.
This is it.
- Why don't you come stay with
me, okay? You don't have
to go back there.
- Hey, look,
I've got to go sucker an
advance out of Scrooge.
- Denise.
- Look, I'll just...
I'll call you later.
- Hey!
- Hey, killer.
- I thought you had a date.
Oh, that bad, huh?
- A bargain matinee, and a
Chinese happy meal.
How about you?
- I got an invitation to Aspen.
- Oh wow.
Does he have a friend?
- No, a wife.
- Oh, nice.
What is it this time?
- Irreversible coma.
- 9.8 for originality.
So Aspen, huh? Do you think he'd
let you bring a friend?
Guess not.
- What are we watching?
- True story. Okay: this
guy, he kidnaps this girl,
and keeps her in a box for 7
years, and then they
get married.
And what bugs me is that she has
a better social life than me.
- Well, sure, it looks good
right now but in a couple of
years, he'll get bored.
He'll kidnap someone else.
- God, you're cynical.
[ Phone ringing ]
Just leave it, Erin.
Erin, just leave it.
This is Julie.
- [Male voice]: Hello, Julie.
Hello, Erin.
- What do you want?
- [Telephone]: I know you're
there, Erin.
I'm going to make
you pay, you bitch.
- He calls the minute
I get home.
- He's just trying to scare you.
- Yeah, well, it's working.
- Look, why don't you tell Jack?
He can trace it or something.
- No, he'll stop sending me out.
- And that would be bad how?
- I need the work.
- Look, I'll get you something
at the travel agency.
- Maybe you're right.
Maybe he's just trying
to scare me.
I have heard when a wife leaves
her husband's house,
as I am doing now,
that he is legally free from all
his obligations.
You're not
to feel bound in anyway,
and nor shall I.
I'm sorry... can
I try that again?
- Why? That was very good.
- I can do it better. Please.
- All right.
- Listen, Torvold.
I have heard when a wife leaves
her husband's house, as
I am doing now,
he's legally freed from all his
obligations to her.
And now I set you free
from them.
You're not
to feel yourself bound in any
way, and nor shall I.
We both must be perfectly free.
Look, here's your ring back.
Give me mine.
- Erin, Erin, wait up. I just
wanted to tell you
that you were terrific. I mean
it, you blew me away in there.
- What do you want Chet?
- I made a mistake, okay.
- No, a mistake is when you give
a cabbie a 20 instead of a 10.
Getting laid in my bed on my
birthday with my friends
outside...
- Um, yeah...
- ...that's tasteless stupidity.
- Erin, come on, I mean, it
didn't mean anything. I didn't
even know her name.
- It was Jenny.
Excuse me.
- Hey, you know what, maybe I
did it because I was sick of you
being so sure I would!
- Excuse me, could I get a spot?
- Sure.
- Just five.
See anything you like?
- Sorry.
- That's okay,
everybody does it.
- Actually, I come here to get
away from everyone.
- Well then, I'm flattered.
- Max Gardner.
- Erin.
- Erin. Well, you're
in great shape, Erin.
- Hm, thanks.
I work hard at it.
- How come I haven't seen you
here before?
- I don't live around here.
In fact, that's it for me.
Thanks for the spot.
- Anytime.
- Do you know a good
place to eat around here?
- Do you like Italian?
- Yeah, I love it.
- So the lights go on and this
polar bear goes berserk. People
are stampeding off the set.
Cut to me, walking out of the
bathroom, oblivious.
I'm trying to come up with a
concept for this new
laundry detergent.
Suddenly I realize I'm all alone
with this 1,500 lb. polar bear
who's just eaten a Volkswagen.
- Oh my God, what did you do?
- I back pedalled fast,
tripped over a cable, landed on
my butt. My life is flashing
before my eyes.
And in the same instant, I came
up with the perfect commercial.
The next thing I know, the polar
bear's licking my face.
- Get out of here.
- On my mother's life.
- Wow.
- You've got a nice laugh.
- Thank you.
- Good food, huh?
- Delicious.
- So, do you like
where you're living?
- Yeah, yeah, it's pretty.
- It must help to be with
someone you like an awful lot.
Are you?
- No one in particular.
What about you? Married?
Hmm.
- They have great desert.
- Stuffed really.
I mean, dinner was great.
- How about a nightcap?
- Hmm.
Well then, why don't
you get the cheque?
Change your mind?
- No, but you may want to.
Look I... I haven't been
entirely honest with you.
I implied that I'm not married,
and that's not true.
At least not technically.
- And what's that
supposed to mean?
- Short version: I am married,
but it's not working,
hasn't been for a long time,
and it's not going to.
Still want to invite me in?
- I'll let you decide.
Not here.
- It's nice, cozy.
You're going to have to cut me
some slack. I'm a bit out
of practice.
- Max! I knew it.
Why? Why?
I tried everything
for you, Max.
What more do you want from me?
What?
- Just relax, Mr. Gardner.
You've got enough problems on
your hands.
I'm a private
investigator. Erin.
- Erin!
- Why don't you have a seat and
relax, Mr. Gardner?
Take a seat.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Look, don't get down on
yourself just because
some dip got caught with his
hand in the honey pot.
- I know, Jack. Maybe we just
make it too easy for them.
- What, do you think this guy
wasn't dirty before?
Look, I don't even get a call
unless the problem is
too big to ignore.
- Have you ever
cheated on your wife, Jack?
- No, not the first one.
Of course, we were only together
for a couple of months.
The other two,
you know, I don't know.
A couple, 3 times, maybe just
sports sex, it didn't
mean anything.
- Men are such jerks.
- It's chemical,
and in this study
they injected these women
with testosterone.
The only thing these babes
wanted to do was go out
and get laid.
- Do any women buy into this
load of crap?
- No, they're too busy blaming
their bitchiness on PMS.
- That's a good one,
ha, ha, ha.
- You know, I've been told I
give the best hand massage in
the whole state.
Here, give me your hand.
How does that feel?
- Good.
Buy me another one?
- No, I think
you've had enough.
- Oh no. What, are you
my father?
- If that works for you.
- My father was a bastard.
- So am I.
- Hmm... Jack.
- Yeah.
- Maybe I've had a little too
much to drink.
Thanks for the drink.
- Hey...
why don't you come by the office
tomorrow or the next day?
I have something for you.
It won't be like tonight.
That's smooth, Jack,
that's real smooth.
- All's fair in love and war,
and business is war. Don't let
anybody tell you different.
- So what do I have to do
to get ahead?
- Sleep with the boss.
- The boss is married.
- How badly do you want
to get ahead?
- Erin, what a surprise.
What's it been:
2-3 weeks? Mind if I sit down?
- I don't believe we know
each other.
I'm Dale Williams.
- I see you're working again.
- She works for me.
- Is that right?
What exactly do you do?
- We were just discussing that.
And if you don't mind, this is
sort of a private dinner.
- That's okay.
Erin owes me a dinner.
- Max, why don't I call you?
We could get together a little
bit later in the week, huh?
- You don't
have my phone number.
- You could give it to me.
- Mm. I don't think so.
- The lady said she'd call you,
so why don't you take off?
- How's your wife Dale?
You are married, aren't you?
- What business is that
of yours?
- It's not my business.
It's hers.
- Do you know this nut?
- I'm sorry, no, I don't...
- Didn't she give you a resume?
She must have left out
the part about working for
the detective agency.
Did you leave that out again?
- What's he talking about?
- I'm really not sure.
- Tell him, honey. Tell him how
the wives hire you to set up
their hubbies.
How you record them on that
microphone you've got hidden.
Where exactly do you hide
that microphone?
- Look, I was just kidding
about... you know.
I knew who you were
all along.
I was just playing
a little joke.
I love my wife.
You're fired.
- So, what am I having?
Good choice.
I hope you can afford this.
- What do you want, Max?
- It must have been a lot
of fun seeing the look on my
face the other night.
Do you go home, compare notes
with your friends,
have a good laugh?
- Hey, I wasn't the one
cheating on my wife.
- No, but I didn't lie. I didn't
tell you I was someone I wasn't,
and I didn't set you up.
Erin!
[ Erin coughs. ]
[ Car picks up speed ]
- [Scared]: Ah! Ah!
[ Car crashes against
the metal ]
[ Screeching tires ]
[Scared]: Ah! Ah!
- Don't shoot!
It's me! It's Max!
- You tried to kill me!
- What? No way!
- You're lying.
- Erin, put down the gun.
- I was looking for you
to apologize.
I saw you run in the alleyway.
Look, if you don't
believe me,
go to the car and call
the police.
Erin. Please.
You're hurt, you're hurt.
Let me help you.
Erin. Erin.
Now. Shh, shh, shh.
It's okay, it's okay,
it's okay.
Here, it's okay.
Come on, come on.
I'll get you to
the hospital. Come on.
- Just take me home.
I want to go home.
Thanks for the ride.
- You could be in shock. Maybe I
should stay for a few minutes
just to make sure.
- My roommate will be home
any minute.
[ Phone rings ]
Hello.
- [Male voice]: Hi Erin,
who's your friend?
- I told you not to call
anymore.
[ Caller chuckles ]
- [Frightened]: Oh!
- Sorry, you okay?
- It's just
an old boyfriend.
- Why don't you go get cleaned
up? I'll fix you a drink.
Your drink's
on the coffee table.
How are you feeling?
- Oh my God, he was trying
to kill me.
- We should call the police.
- And tell them what? I didn't
see anything.
- What about the car? Did you
get a good look at the car?
- Only that it was the same
colour as yours.
How did you know I would be at
that restaurant?
You followed me?
- I just wanted the chance to
explain about my marriage.
- Look, if you're going to give
me that bit about how your wife
doesn't understand you,
just do me a favour and save us
both the time, okay?
- It's more like I don't
understand her.
Over the last year or so, she's
become so paranoid, jealous.
I have never cheated on my wife.
You would have been the first.
- Am I supposed
to feel flattered?
- No. Look, I liked you.
You need to hear a bit.
My marriage has been over for
a long, long time.
I built our ad agency from a
struggling shop to
a top boutique.
Dina's the largest
shareholder.
- Well, sounds like you
shouldn't have any problem
getting another job.
- Sure, if I want to walk away
from millions of dollars.
The agency is about
to be sold.
If we're married, I get half; if
we're divorced, not a penny.
That's why she hired you.
She needed the grounds
to sue for divorce.
- Okay. Well then Max, if your
wife's so jealous,
why doesn't she just give
you a divorce?
- I know this is going to sound
crazy, but I think she believes
that if I'm desperate enough,
I'll come crawling back to her.
You don't trust anyone, do you?
- Max, I have decoyed
52 married men.
Out of them, 49 tried to sleep
with me and everyone
had a story.
- That still leaves 3.
- One was gay. I imagine the
other two had equally
compelling reasons.
- So all men are lying
lecherous bastards?
- Hmm.
- What was it? A lousy marriage
or a crappy childhood?
- Ooh, advertising by day,
psychology by night.
- I guess I didn't do a very
good job at patching things up.
Don't suppose we could try
dinner again?
- Jack has this silly policy
about dating his clients'
husbands.
- Yeah.
Goodnight.
- Goodnight.
- Erin! Erin!
Wake up, wake up!
Your agent is on
the phone. Get up!
She has a job for
you today!
Come on, come on, come on.
I'm serious.
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Yahoo!
Iceberg Cove,
more chill, less fill.
- And cut...
that was great,
Erin! That's great.
- Thank you.
- I'm almost glad our lead
actress got sick.
I want your agent to call me,
okay? I have some other
projects coming up.
- Okay, great. Well, listen, I
really, really appreciate
the opportunity.
- Don't thank me, thank him.
He's the one who found
your photo.
Got to go, babe.
- You stole my headshot?
- I never said I was a choirboy.
- Well, this doesn't
change anything.
And don't expect me to
feel obligated in any way.
- I don't play casting couch
games. If you weren't right, you
wouldn't be here, okay?
- Okay.
- Good. How about dinner?
- Oh, God!
- That's a yes?
You look good as a bear.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Where'd you say we were
eating again?
- I didn't. It's a surprise.
- You're kidding, right?
- Look, I know this is hard for
you, but try to trust me.
- Wow!
- I've been working on it for
the past 2 years.
I still have lots to do.
- Oh my God, how did you ever
find this place?
- Actually, it belonged to my
grandfather about a million
years ago.
He was a painter.
This was his studio.
- Are all of these yours?
- Yes.
- You're very talented.
- This one is giving me
some troubles.
- I think it's coming
along beautifully.
Did your grandfather
teach you how to paint?
- He taught me how to see.
When I was 9, I could draw an
exact likeness.
You would have been impressed.
Everyone was,
except for my grandfather.
He said my drawings
were lifeless,
that I had missed the shadows
within the shadows.
You see, if I would have
drawn you then,
I would have neglected the
darkening below your cheekbone.
It's almost subliminal. And
there's the fairest highlights,
tightness in the muscle, the tug
in your laugh line.
- I was working 2 waitress jobs,
and just wasn't making
ends meet.
- A lot of lousy tippers?
- A lot of bills.
So anyway, I saw this ad
in Backstage:
good money, plenty
of time for acting.
Still, I wasn't really sure I
wanted to do it.
Then Jack explained to me how
normal surveillance usually
takes months.
It could cost a woman thousands,
and then they might
not even know for sure.
With a decoy,
within a few weeks, they
know for sure.
- What about the guy
that's say, 45,
been bald since he was 15,
married the first woman that
ever smiled at him
who somehow gains 6 dress sizes
on their honeymoon?
Now, out of his fantasy
steps you:
the kind of woman who makes
men buy beer.
Do you ever wonder that it might
be you, and not him?
- It's not like that, because
let me tell you something.
Women are infinitely better at
deceiving themselves
than any man.
I watched my mother do it,
and when he finally had the
decency to leave us,
I watched her crawl into a bed
and stay there for 2 years.
So yeah, yeah, I get paid to
test fidelity, and
you know what?
Most men cheat, but at least
their wives won't have
to wonder anymore.
- I know this is hard for you
right now,
but there are relationships
that work.
Built on trust.
- Yeah,
I think there's a museum
with one.
- You're a hard case,
Ms. Greer.
- It doesn't stop, does it Max?
It just never stops.
- I'm sorry about tonight.
- It's okay.
- The only other time she was at
the loft, she refused to
get out of the car.
- Everything happens
for a reason.
- I guess
I'm not invited in.
- You're invited...
when you're a free man.
- That could be 6 months,
maybe more.
- It'll test your character.
I loved the picnic.
- I want to see you again.
- Make it soon.
Goodnight.
[To herself]: Erin, Erin, Erin,
what are you doing?
Jack is so going to kill me.
- When you break the rules, you
don't screw around, huh?
[ Knocking ]
- I meant in a couple of days.
What are you doing... Jack!
What are you doing here?
- You should check
your messages.
- I was out.
- So I noticed.
- What's up?
- Come on, we've got to go.
We'll talk about it in the car.
- Later.
- Oh my God! Denise.
- What's going on, D?
- All we know for sure is that
she was stabbed 5 times.
No murder weapon. The perp must
have taken it. Her pocketbook
wasn't touched,
nothing was missing from her
apartment, and there was
no sign of a break in.
We're guessing she knew him.
- It had to have been Jimmy. He
was always beating her up.
- Yeah, so I heard. We got an
APB out on him.
- Good.
- Just for the record: where
were the two of you last night
between 9 and 11?
- What are you, kidding?
- Come on, Deaton,
you know the drill.
- I can't even remember what I
had for breakfast.
- Ms. Greer?
- I was out.
- With?
- A friend.
- And your friend can
verify that?
- Yeah.
- Something else, Ms. Greer?
- I've been getting threatening
phone calls lately,
and last night someone tried to
run me down.
- Did you report it?
- No, I didn't see the driver.
- Did you recognize the car?
- No.
- Do you have any enemies you
can think of?
A dispute over
a parking space, anything?
- No.
- What about this guy, Jimmy?
Did you have words with him?
An argument?
- I barely even know him.
- All right, it may just be a
coincidence. But just to be
safe, don't go out alone.
My first thing tomorrow morning
I want you to come in and
fill out a report.
I'll put a trace on your
phone and Jack...
- Yeah.
- If you can remember what
2-buck hooker took pity
on you last night,
give me a call, all right?
- No, I got it now.
It was your wife.
- She's all yours.
- Excuse me.
- We have a lot to talk about,
you and I.
- Oh, would you give me a break,
Jack? I just found out Denise
was murdered.
- I want to know
what's going on.
- Nothing.
Look, I didn't want to tell you
because I was afraid you
wouldn't let me work.
- You're damn right
you're not working.
- You know...
You know I need the money.
- You need money?
Fine. Here.
- Come on, Jack.
- Take it.
- Not like that.
- It's a gift,
and you're staying with me until
we find this guy.
- This is exactly what I'm
talking about. I don't need you
to take care of me, Jack.
- What, did you find someone
else to do the job? Huh?
- Maybe I have.
- Oh wait, now let me guess.
His wife has an
irreversible coma.
- Screw you.
- I'm trying to tell you
something here, Erin. This guy
is bad news.
- You don't know that.
- Oh the hell I don't.
I've been dealing with scumbags
like him for 20 years.
- You're jealous.
- You're talking crazy, here, is
what you're talking now.
- No, you are.
You're jealous.
- Where you going?
- To find a cab.
- Just get in
the damn car.
Look, just get in the
car... please.
- I'm not going
to stop seeing him.
- Look, why don't you come
by the office
next week because I've got some
files that need to be
cleaned out?
- You know, it started out as
such a good day.
I got my first commercial.
- Ah, I guess you won't be
working for me for too much
longer then, huh?
- No, no, I didn't... I mean,
it's... it's only a local.
- No. It's okay babe,
you were always way too classy
for this crap.
You always took
it too seriously.
I'm happy for you, really.
[ Loud crash, dogs barking ]
[ Shouting ]
- Julie, you scared
the hell out me.
- You scared the hell out of me.
- Oh, my God.
What's going on?
Erin?
- Denise was murdered.
- Oh, my God. Jimmy?
[ Faint sound of steps ]
Oh, that son of a bitch.
She was so scared to be alone.
He just picked her apart
until she didn't even know
who she was.
[ Loud crash ]
It's probably just
a pigeon.
No, Erin, just
leave it, okay?
- I won't be able to sleep
unless I'm sure.
- Okay, but...
[ Dog barking in distance. ]
- Erin, come on, you're giving
me the creeps.
Erin, would you just
come back inside?
Erin, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
[ She laughs. ]
What?
- It was just a pigeon.
- I'm going to sleep now.
Bite me.
- Well, that was great, that was
really great.
Let's bring it back next week,
all right?
Thank you.
Erin, hang in for a second?
- You're beating a dead horse.
- I know, forget that.
Did you ever hear
of Sandro Guest?
- Twelve hits, 23 Tonies, yeah,
yeah, I think I might have
heard of him.
- Well, he's heard of you too.
- Really? How?
- From me, for one thing.
He also caught that workshop
with you at the Circle Rep.
He's considering you for the 2nd
lead in his new production.
- Come on, Chet,
don't yank my chain.
- I'm not, Erin. I'm not, I'm
not. I swear to God.
I swear.
- You're serious?
Sandro Guest?
My God, do you have any idea
what this could mean
for my career?
- Well, it would give you 1,
that's for sure.
- Oh my God,
this is incredible.
- Hey, hey, look, look. It's not
100%. He's still considering a
couple of other actresses
but I mean, you're definitely
the front runner.
- This is great.
- I took the liberty.
Saturday night at 9 and this is
where you go.
You know what, I hear that
his place is amazing.
- His place?
- Yeah, you know, so you can get
to know each other.
Hey, Erin, that's
the way it works.
You know that.
- What, you're pimping me out?
- What, are you out
of your mind?
You sleepwalk through this part,
it's a guaranteed nomination.
- I don't think
I want it that bad.
- Listen, listen, you nail it,
it's a statue. I mean
this is it, babe,
this is the rocket ship. Don't
blow it. I'd kill for a
shot like this.
- Then you sleep with him.
- Whoa!
- Hi. What are you
doing here?
- Tough class?
- Yeah, yeah, we learned how to
prostitute ourselves for the
sake of our art.
How did you know I'd be here?
Follow me again?
- No, I only stalk on first
dates. This time I coerced it
from your roommate.
Listen, Julie told me what
happened to your friend.
How are you holding up?
I thought maybe you might want
to grab a bite, and talk.
- I promised my mom I'd
meet her for lunch.
- I'll take you
both out.
- Oh, thanks, but I don't think
that's such a good idea.
- I can be
extremely charming.
- Yeah, a little
too charming.
- Erin?
- Mom, I brought
someone with me today.
This is Max.
Max... Mom.
- It's nice to meet you,
Mrs. Greer.
- [Mother]: Not too many Max's
these days.
- I'll be right back,
excuse me.
- Ms. Greer, we've tried
to be patient,
but I'm afraid you'll
just have to make
other arrangements
for your mother.
- No, wait.
I... have a cheque.
- You two are very close.
- Yes.
- Tell me all about Erin,
Mrs. Greer.
- This only covers half the
bill. I'm sorry.
I'll be happy to recommend
some excellent--
- Please, please, this
place is the best.
My mother deserves it for once
in her life please. I'll sign
whatever you want--
- She kept me up half the
night wandering
the streets, but we
never found him.
Probably got hit by a car.
- I just need a
little more time.
- I bought her another puppy
but she wouldn't even
look at him.
- All right.
- I think she thought he might
run away.
- Just like her father.
- Max, don't you hurt
my daughter.
- I would never hurt your
daughter, Mrs. Greer.
- Let me feel you face.
- [Whispering]: Mom's blind.
- I have no idea
what I'm doing.
I've only been blind a month.
The therapist says I
should practice,
like I've got enough time left
to learn this crap.
- Hey, don't talk
like that.
- You've got nice skin anyway.
- Thank you.
- You like my daughter, Max?
- Yes I do,
very much.
- That's good.
That's good.
- Yeah I know, I know Barry.
I know what she's
trying to do,
but don't worry about it. Of
course, of course.
I've got it taken
care of. Right.
I won't. Okay, okay. I'll talk
to you tomorrow.
Thanks.
- What's going on, Max?
- Did anybody ever tell you you
should be an Ivory girl?
- What's up?
- Leave it.
You've got enough of
your own problems.
- Talk to me.
- It's Dina. That was Barry,
my lawyer. He said that
Dina is going to use the tape
you made to sue for divorce.
- Oh God, I'm sorry.
- For what? For what?
Hey, look.
It's a non-issue.
Dina doesn't know it, but I have
the combination to her safe.
And as of yesterday, she no
longer has the tape.
I'd love to see the
expression on her face.
- Wait, but she can
get a copy.
- I doubt she's thought
that far ahead.
- No, I mean from Jack.
He keeps all the originals.
She can get a copy
from him.
- I'd better
call Barry.
- No wait, I'll...
- What?
- I'll get it for you.
- No, Erin, it's not right. I
won't let you do it.
- Yes, you will.
You wouldn't be in this mess if
it wasn't for me.
It's all my fault.
- Hey.
Are you sure?
- Here you go!
- Thanks.
- Mrs. Gardner, I believe you
know my associate, Ms. Greer?
- Pleasure.
- Yes, of course.
- And this is Parker.
- Hi.
- Right this way.
We'll be in the conference
room, if anyone needs me.
- Erin, you wouldn't
have a cigarette?
- Sorry.
- I guess I'll
just cough.
[ Coughing ]
- Hey listen, why don't you go
and get some?
I'll watch the phones for you.
- Thanks, you're an angel.
- Don't tell anyone.
- I'll be right back,
Mrs. Gardner.
Where the hell is everybody?
Where's Erin?
- I don't know. She was
here when I left.
- [Jack]: You ever thought
about a course in people
skills, Parker?
- Give me a night off.
- Quit smoking.
- Jack!
- What are you doing in here?
- You caught me. It was gonna
be a surprise.
- What surprise?
- I finished organizing the main
files in the office,
and I was going to come in here
and help you out with your
personal files,
sort of just to thank you for
everything that you've done
for me.
- I appreciate that babe,
but you know I kind of have my
own filing system worked out,
and I really don't like anybody
touching my stuff.
- Fair enough.
- But, thanks.
That's nice. I just want to
get something.
If you don't mind,
I want you to
go in the conference
room with me.
There's something
I want you to hear.
I think
it's important.
Okay?
Okay, let's go.
Mrs. Gardner, if you'd please
tell my associate
what you just told me?
- Is it really necessary
I go through all this
again with her?
- Look, I know it's
difficult. Please.
- My husband can be
rather charming
when he wants something, as I'm
sure you know, Ms. Greer.
Most sociopath's
are charming.
I mean, he only married me
for my money. I should
have realized that
when he threatened to call off
the engagement
after my father insisted on a
prenuptial agreement.
But I was in love.
- But he signed the agreement?
- He had no choice. If he
refused, my father would have
cut me out of the will.
- So, why don't you just give
him some money and get out of
the marriage?
- I offered him money, Ms.
Greer, but he's refused!
- If you really wanted a
divorce, you could get one.
- Now, hold it. It's not so easy
in this state.
There's only four reasons for a
contested divorce and you've got
to prove them:
cruelty, abandonment,
imprisonment--
- And adultery.
I have paid you a considerable
sum, Mr. Deaton. I hope I'm not
wasting my money here.
- She will cooperate. You have
my word.
- I will be needing some kind
of protection.
My husband has said that if I
ever try to divorce him, he
would try to kill me.
You don't believe me.
Do you know that my father
was murdered,
Ms. Greer? He was on a
business trip,
and someone broke into his hotel
suite, and smashed
his skull in with a lamp. Max
was in the adjoining room. Slept
through the whole thing,
or so he says.
And my lawyer has filed for the
necessary papers and has issued
a temporary restraining order.
But I believe that once my
husband gets wind of this,
despite what your subordinate
may think, my husband will try
to kill me.
And I'm scared, Mr. Deaton.
He has gotten so
much worse,
and I'm scared.
- Everything's going to be all
right, I promise.
Parker, I want you to go home
and look after Mrs. Gardner.
Don't worry, he's
very good at his job.
Look, you call me if
you need anything.
- This way, lady.
- She's lying.
- Why? She's the one filing for
divorce, Erin.
- She's trying to control him
with the money.
- Did it ever occur to
you that Max
might have been the one that
tried to run you down?
- No.
- You set him up, Erin. You're
being subpoenaed
to testify at his trial. You're
the star witness. Would you give
me a break?
- You don't see it.
She's the one
that's lying, Jack.
- Keep your mouth shut,
bitch! Shh.
- Ahh!
Ahh!
Help me!
Somebody, help!
[ Ripping cloth ]
- I'm going to make you pay!
- [Jack]: Son of a bitch!
- No Jack. Jack! Stop!
Jack that's enough!
Jack, stop it.
- Come here!
[ Police siren ]
It's all right.
It's okay, it's over.
You're safe.
[ Busy office ]
- I take it you know
our boy in here?
- Yeah, his name is
Chester Gortner.
His wife was a client of
mine. Erin tagged him
a couple of months ago.
- Yeah, well, we checked
his phone records.
He made a couple of dozens
calls to your number, mostly
from his car phone.
It seems when his wife
found out about
his activities,
she ditched him. He
blames you, of course.
- So he's the one that tried to
run me down.
- He swears he didn't, but then
again, he claims not to have
made the calls.
I've got a guy going to impound
his car today,
and we're checking his
whereabouts on the night of
Denise Sandler's death.
- But I thought Jimmy...
- No, he's got an airtight
alibi. 30 witnesses have him
passed out at a bar.
We still think that she knew
him. Is it possible that this
Gortner guy knew Denise?
- No, not that
I know of.
- All right, we'll check it out
anyway. If it's any consolation,
Ms. Greer, he was really sorry
for what he did to you.
[ Phone ringing ]
- Hello?
- [Max]: You're finally home.
I've been trying
to reach you all night.
- You paid my mother's bill.
- I may have eavesdropped. I
hope you're not mad.
- No, no I'm not mad.
Thank you, Max.
- You're welcome. There's so
much I need to tell you.
- Me too. Can you come over?
- I can't. Dina somehow got a
restraining order. I'm not even
allowed to be at the...
when she's there--
[ Static ]
- You're breaking up, where
are you?
- I'm at the loft. Look, I can't
talk now, but there's this
awards dinner tomorrow night.
I'm being honoured, and I want
you there with me,
and to spend the weekend.
- What about Dina?
- To hell with Dina and to hell
with the money. I don't want to
wait for you.
- Yes, of course I'll come.
[ Car horn ]
What was that?
- I can't hear you, hello? If
you can hear me... I'll call you
tomorrow, okay?
- Wait, Max, I need to tell
you... Max.
- [Max's voice]: Hi, it's Max.
- Hi, it's me again--
- I'm not home right now,
but please leave a message, and
I'll get back to you as soon as
I can.
[ Tape rewinding ]
- [Max]: So what exactly are you
looking to do?
- [Denise]: I'm interested in
writing but
I would work with you, Max, in
any capacity.
- I'd like to help you
out, Denise.
[ Click ]
I have never cheated on
my wife.
[ Tape rewinding ]
[ Click ]
- [Max]: I'd like to help you
out, Denise. To become a writer,
that is.
Let's just keep it professional.
Otherwise, it gets too
complicated. Agreed?
- [Denise]: Whatever you say.
I can't help but be
disappointed though.
- I'm flattered really but it
has to be this way.
[ Click ]
[ Tape rewinding ]
- [Max]: I'd like to help you
out, Denise, to become a writer
that is.
[ Click ]
[ Dog barking ]
[ Gun cocking ]
- Hi, Erin. Oh, let me
help you with those.
- What are you doing here, Chet?
- Actually,
I was just leaving.
- Hey.
- I bumped
into Chet.
- You're not upset, are you?
- Hey, you're over 18.
You can sleep with whoever
you like.
- No, I can't.
You don't have a
clue, do you?
I mean, men just throw
themselves at you.
- Oh, please.
- They end up with me
by attrition.
- God, you don't even know how
terrific you are.
- Oh please, have you seen my
last 3 dates?
- Julie.
- I get lonely, Erin.
And I know,
I know that
Chet is not Mr. Right. I mean
he's not even Mr. So-So.
But he's easy to look
at, and for a little while
I even got to pretend that he
was here to be with me, and not
just to get back at you.
- Come here.
You are so
stupid sometimes.
- Yeah, yeah.
So what's all this,
huh? Max again?
- It's just some
fancy schmancy dinner.
- It's okay, killer. I'm used to
living vicariously through you.
Come on.
- You look great.
[ Click of a door opening ]
I don't know.
I think the
black strapless.
- What's wrong?
- I've got to talk to Jack.
- Why?
- I've got to stop decoying.
- What do you mean?
If I don't, Max and I don't
stand a chance.
- Well, it's about time.
Oh my God.
So guess what, guess what?
- What?
- I have a date tonight.
- Who is he? Who is he?
Tell me. Tell me.
- Well, I answered
a personal. Okay?
- Oh, geez.
- No, no, no, it's
not like that.
- Come on.
- No it's not like that. He's
smart, and he's got a
good sense of humour.
- And you got all
this in 3 lines?
Oh, I love you.
Anyone that gets you should
consider themselves
unbelievably lucky.
- That's right.
- And do you know why they
should consider
themselves unbelievably lucky?
Because they'll no
longer fear death.
- Oh, you are such a bitch.
You are dead.
[ Phone ringing ]
Hello?
- [Jack]: Julie.
- Hey, Jack.
- Look, I need to speak to Erin.
- Yeah, yeah, hold on.
I'll get her.
Erin?
Jack's on the phone.
Erin, it's Jack. He says
it's important.
Wow!
- No, I'm through with you,
Jack. Why didn't you tell me
Denise already decoyed Max
and he wasn't interested,
instead of trying to convince me
he was just another creep?
- I'm on my way over there.
- No, don't bother.
- So cannot afford this,
even if it does look
unbelievably great.
- How?
- He was guarding Dina.
Somebody shot him.
He probably would have got to
her too if the dog hadn't scared
him off.
- Do they know who?
- No, look--
- Oups!
Ah!
- [Jack on phone]: Look, just
promise me you won't leave.
You may be in danger,
so promise me.
- Okay.
- Ahh!
Ahh!
Erin!
- Julie?
Julie?
Julie! Oh God, no!
Please no!
The doctor says she's lost a lot
of blood.
They won't know anything for
sure until tomorrow.
I'll call you if there are any
changes, okay? Bye.
- Erin, I am so sorry.
- Please don't.
- Why?
- Where were you last
night, Max?
- I told you.
- Yes, Parker and Denise are
both dead, Julie's stabbed,
and here you are again.
- I don't know what's gotten
into you, or what you think
I've done, but you're wrong.
You're wrong.
- I'd like it if you
left, please.
- I don't believe this.
I've got 300 people
waiting to honour me,
but I thought you
might need me more.
If you come to your senses,
you know where I'll be.
I'm sorry
about Julie.
I like her.
I like you, too.
No matter how hard
you make it for me.
- Ms. Greer?
- Yes.
- Will you come
with us please?
- Why? What is
this about?
- Police matter.
- What did I do?
[ Hand slamming table hard ]
Please, I don't know what
you're talking about.
- Cut the crap, Ms. Greer.
Your little game is over.
You got that? Over.
Now you can continue playing
dumb and you're looking at
5 to 10 hard time.
Or you can
cooperate with us,
and you walk away with a slap on
the wrist. Now what's it going
to be?
- Why are you doing
this to me?
- All right, that's enough.
She doesn't know anything.
We're sorry about this, Ms.
Greer. But we had to be sure.
- Sure about what? What is all
this about?
- Do you recognize
this man?
- Yes,
it's Gregory Barnes. His wife
hired Jack to find out
if he was cheating. I had
dinner with him.
He claims she was in a coma.
- [Tape recording - Denise]: I
love skiing, I wish I could go
with you to Aspen.
- [Male voice]: I don't think my
wife would appreciate that.
- We wouldn't have to tell her.
- Sorry, I'm happily married. If
I want to take someone skiing,
it'll be my wife.
Now, if you have a
problem with this, maybe we
should end this lunch.
[ Click ]
- That wasn't me.
That was Denise.
- We know that. But that's the
tape his wife got.
Jack met with
Gregory Barnes
a day after your dinner. He
played him the original tape.
He threatened to give his wife a
copy unless he paid him 5 grand
to stage this new one.
It turns out Barnes's wife
ended up leaving him anyway,
so he's thinking he shelled
out a whole lot of cash for
nothing. So he called us.
- So you're saying that Jack's
a blackmailer?
- Uh-huh, probably a murderer.
Denise Sandler had her
own scam going.
She went to Jack's clients and
threatened to tell their
husbands about the decoys unless
they paid off:
real nickel and
dime stuff.
She gets nailed and cuts a deal
to testify against Jack.
She turns up dead. We also had
Parker by the short and curlies
-- some old beef that could have
cost him his license.
He agrees to testify, he turns
up dead.
That leaves you.
You're the only one left who can
prove a new tape was made.
That knife, it was
meant for you.
- No, not Jack.
- Come on, times
were tough.
He had 3 alimony payments,
ran up some pretty
big debts. People do stupid
things when they're desperate.
- Jack would never do that. He's
always been there for me.
- You're best friend
is in the hospital.
The killer is still out there.
We need your testimony.
Ms. Greer.
- No.
- If you don't cooperate,
we can't protect you.
Do you want to die?
- I need some time to think.
- All right, all right.
Why don't you take some
time, get your head around
it, and call us.
We only want to help.
In the meantime,
be careful.
- Erin, we have to talk.
Erin! Erin!
Son of a bitch.
- Detective Costello please.
Tell him Erin Greer is calling.
- [Receptionist]: I'm sorry,
he's not at his desk. He should
be back very soon.
- Okay, he can reach
me on my cell.
- I'll tell him.
- Hi.
Look Max, before you say
anything, just let me explain.
I know that I've been acting
strange lately.
It's just that I've been so
scared and I just found out that
Jack is actually--
- Shh. I don't care.
All that matters is
that you're here now.
You have to realize
that I would
never do anything
to hurt you.
[ Phone ringing ]
- Hello.
- Erin, where are you?
- No. First, we make a deal.
Okay look, I want to help you
but first, first, we've got to
talk to Jack.
I want to hear his side.
- Jack turned himself in half an
hour ago.
- He what?
- Look Erin, we were wrong.
He admitted to the blackmail,
but he swears he never
killed anybody.
He was concerned for your
safety. That's why he turned
himself in--
- Give me the phone. Erin, it's
me. Where are you?
- Jack, what's going on?
- Where are you?
- At Max's loft. Why?
- Get dressed.
- Why? What is going on?
- Erin, think. What's
the address?
- 335 Pine.
- 335 Pine. Get somebody over
there now. Erin,
get out of there.
You're in danger.
- No, no you're wrong.
- Erin, get out of there
right now. This guy is
going to kill you.
You get out of there right now.
- [Max]: Hey Erin,
you're hungry?
How about some eggs?
Hey Erin, Erin?
Erin, what are you doing? Erin!
Wait! Erin!
Wait! Ah!
- Leave me alone!
- Erin!
Erin!
Come on, Erin.
Erin, I don't know what's
gotten into you.
I just want to talk. Tell me
what happened.
Erin, this is crazy.
Erin, wait!
Don't sell me out!
Erin!
Erin, why are
you hiding?
I'm not going to
hurt you.
This is a
big misunderstanding.
Can we just talk
about it?
This is getting ridiculous.
Erin!
Erin, are you hurt? Come on,
speak to me.
Ow! What are
you doing?
Erin.
Erin!
- Don't you come near me, Max!
- Erin, don't.
- I know all about you, Max.
You killed Denise, you
killed Parker,
you tried to kill me.
- That's not true.
- Last night you said you were
here, but you weren't.
I called you back.
- I was downstairs waiting for
my lawyer.
- Stop lying!
- No, we went to dinner, we
discussed the divorce.
I told him I didn't care about
the money.
I just want to be with
you. Please!
Put down the gun.
[ Door shutting above ]
- Help!
Help me!
Over here.
- You can justify anything here,
but not here.
- Stay back, stay back.
- Look at me. What do you feel?
- No.
- I love you.
- Stay back.
- Do what you have to.
- Ah!
- I didn't have a choice.
She was going to
kill you.
It's okay.
- Yeah, you're kidding.
- [Julie]: No, I'm not. So what
about Jack?
- Jack took the plea bargain.
He's going to get six months.
- Hey, I've got to go. My doctor
just walked in.
- You are so crazy.
- I can't help it.
- I love you.
- Me too.
- See you first thing in the
morning, okay?
- Okay. Bye.
- All right, bye.
- How's Julie doing?
- She's great.
She got asked
out by 2 doctors. She said if
she knew that, she would have
gotten stabbed months ago.
What?
- I just...
if it wasn't for me,
Denise, Julie.
- Hey, Denise brought
this on herself.
She was blackmailing
Dina. They found the
cancelled cheques.
- What about Parker? She
killed him to frame me,
to keep us apart. If I'd just
made a clean break, I...
- Max, she was sick.
Stop beating yourself up over
this, okay?
Thank you for not giving
up on me.
- Thank you for not
shooting me.
- How did you know
I wouldn't?
- I didn't. I just knew that
if we couldn't be together,
I didn't care.
Why didn't you shoot me?
It couldn't have been
trust, could it?
- Maybe.
Well, when I was pointing
the gun at you...
I don't know, it didn't feel
real. I mean, it felt like I was
playing a part,
like when I was decoying.
And I looked at you,
I really, really looked
at you.
I guess I saw the light in the
shadows of the shadows.
Now, kiss me.
Ow! My leg.
- My leg.
- Ow, my leg!
[ Laughters ]