Subtitles by explosiveskull
- Good morning.
- Fuck you.
- Hey.
Hold this.
Clear the ice!
Lily! What are you doin'?
Get off! Come on, bro!
Sean... what the hell, man?!
We're in the middle...
Let's go!
Sean, come on, man!
So, honey, um, guess
who I ran into today.
Sue, George's mother...
do you remember George?
You went to science camp with
him. He was he smart kid.
I don't remember.
Curious George, that's what
you called him.
Anyway, he remembers you
very fondly from science camp.
- So, I was thinking that maybe...
- No.
Um, Maria, you don't even know
what I was going to say next.
Just... don't.
Fine, if you don't want to hear
the rest of what...
- I was gonna say, that's fine.
- No, she does.
You know your mother's trying
to be helpful, right?
Right?
Yes.
Here was my idea, just that
you're here and George...
is here and and you both like
each other...
so the winter prom is coming up,
you could go to it together.
- I'm not going to the prom.
- Why not?
Because it's stupid and I
don't want any part of it.
But it's such a
beautiful tradition.
You're really gonna be missing
out, it's your senior year.
Missing out on what?!
That went well.
I guess she just needs time
to come out of her shell.
Christ, Amy, she's nearly 18.
Well, she's a late bloomer.
- She has no friends.
- She's friends with Lily.
Lily's a habit, not a friend.
She has no social life.
She has no confidence.
As far as I'm aware...
she's never even had a
conversation with a boy.
She doesn't touch her food.
She weighs less than
she did two years ago.
Wake up, Amy! Just look at her!
Look at her!
We have a screwed-up daughter.
You're too hard on her...
you just need to give
her time to blossom.
Blossom into what?
Hey, sweetie.
Dad, um....
- Mm-hm?
- Last night...
I don't really know what
to make of it...
but I... I just wanted to ask
you something.
Did you get any sleep?
Yeah, I... well, I mean...
I mean, no I didn't sleep well
last night.
You look terrible.
You sure you wanna go to
school looking like that?
What?
Honey, look, I know it's
a jungle out there...
but you gotta put your best
face forward.
- Don't you wanna look your best?
- I do, but I...
What's going on?
She didn't get any sleep...
again.
Look, a good night's sleep is
essential for all of us...
but particularly for a
young girl who's growing.
Why don't you do
yourself a favor?
Hop upstairs, put
some make-up on.
You'll look better
and you'll feel better.
Promise you, trust me.
But her omelette
will get all cold.
We both know she's not
gonna eat the omelette.
Go on, upstairs.
Honey, what's wrong?
Sweetie, go... now.
Never mind.
Good morning.
Hey.
So, what do you think?
- It's nice.
- Nice?
Okay, it's... it's really nice.
Nice is a boy you
don't wanna go out with.
This is an acid green,
turbo-charged 911.
This is definitely not nice.
Woo! Woohoo! Woo!
Yeah, I'm coming!
Whoa.
Sorry, Maria.
Sweet ride. Hey, baby.
That's not funny.
Are you okay? I'm so sorry.
I really didn't mean to do that.
Maybe she should
watch where she's going.
You all right?
Wow, Sean, your bar has
really lowered, huh?
You fuck with...!
Oy! Chill! Back up, Paul.
- Hey, baby, it's not worth it.
- Fuckin' punk.
- See you at practice.
- Seriously?
Little bitch! Light's out!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Should we go?
- Okay.
Maria.
You're not real.
I'm imagining you.
Why am I seeing you?
Because I'm here.
Who... who are you?
You don't remember me?
- I don't know you.
- I've always been here.
Look in the window...
I'm everywhere where you are.
Whenever you see yourself,
what you really see is me.
How long have you been here?
How long have you?
- What do you want?
What do you want from me?
I can take your sadness away.
Listen, I'm here for you,
I know you.
I know your secret
desires, your fears...
who you love, who you hate.
I understand you completely.
- But you aren't me?
- No.
- Who are you then?
- Look at me.
- What?
What do you see?
I s... I see what I look like.
What do you look like?
I... you're beautiful.
We are beautiful.
Do you have a name?
Airam.
Hey.
Honey, you lookin' really
good today.
Yeah, I see it, you had your
beauty sleep, I can tell.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hm.
Good for you, honey.
Um, I've decided I'm gonna go
to the winter prom after all.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hm.
Honey, that's wonderful.
So who's the lucky guy?
- No one.
- No one yet.
You know, the main thing
is that she's going. Right?
Which is great. You're making an
effort to be part of something.
Hey, Lily.
Hey, are we gonna hit
the ice today?
You wanna learn how to skate?
Yeah, I'm teaching her
for winter prom.
Oh, that's great, who are you
going with?
No one... yet.
So are we gonna skate
today or...?
Oh shit, no, um, it's Thursday.
I have that bonding date
with my dad.
You Brennans are so weird.
You don't know the half of it.
Okay, well, tomorrow then?
Tomorrow.
She wants to learn how to skate?
- Yeah, you wanna teach her?
- No.
It's just not like her,
that's all.
He's just with a patient,
take a seat, darling.
- He'll be right out.
- Okay.
Okay.
That's 278.
And this one is... 286.
- May I?
- Yes.
Thank you.
What we're gonna do is we are
going to relocate...
your nipples back up here
where they belong.
Slip an implant under here
and here...
and they are gonna be perky
and perfect.
So how's school, Maria?
It's good.
You're lucky to be
in high school.
I miss that time so much.
No worries, all you care about
are guys, right?
Naomi, could you go through the
forms with Ms. Robinson, please?
And schedule a mammoplasty...
and an abdominoplasty
for a few weeks.
Hey, hun... hi.
- Hi.
- Claudia.
Do we have an appointment today?
No, I just wanted to see
if it's coming along okay.
Please?
I really can't today,
my daughter's here for a date.
You're here early, aren't you?
Did we not say 6:00?
Yeah, sorry.
Can't you squeeze me
in for like ten minutes?
Why don't I just check
it right now? Here we go.
All right, here we go.
That is looking just fine.
I'll remember you
just like this.
Yeah.
I thought this weekend
would never come.
Me, too. I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Are you okay, honey?
Yeah.
- Oh.
- Hey.
Maria, hey, oh, what's good?
I don't think we've ever met
before, you must be Dr. Brennan.
- And you are?
- Mark.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Doctor.
I'm actually considering
going into pre-med myself.
I'd love to sit down with
you, pick your brain sometime...
if that wouldn't be too much
trouble.
Sure.
Great, and Maria, I guess I'll
just see you around in school.
That was brutal.
You know, your birthday's
coming up in a couple months.
What would you say to getting
your gift...
a little early this year?
I... I'd say yes.
Swing by the office tomorrow
after school.
Sure.
Daddy.
What?
Never mind.
You really believe he cares,
don't you?
- He does.
- Oh, come on, Maria.
He was embarrassed, that's all.
You're just a stain on his
family.
No, you're wrong.
He does care and he's gonna
buy me my car early...
because he doesn't want me
riding the bus...
with those idiots anymore.
- You heard him.
- I heard him.
What do you know anyway?
Nothing that you don't already.
Shh.
You know, you're
overreacting, okay?
You ready?
Is it in there?
Come on.
It's here.
What?
I know who you see
in the mirror.
It doesn't matter what's real.
What matters is how you feel...
and I wanna make you feel
beautiful.
I'm your dad, think I don't know
why you don't wear your hair...
back in a ponytail? Hm.
So, here's what I'm gonna do.
Take this, which is eight
millimeters...
and this, which is six.
We're gonna round the top
of these pointy bits off...
and they're gonna be amazing.
Then, here, lift 'em.
I know.
Yeah, we're gonna take this
sweet, little snub nose...
we're just gonna slim down
the cartilage at the top...
and just extend the tip
a teeny bit.
It's gonna look sophisticated
and amazing...
and we're gonna accentuate the
cupid's bow...
show those fabulous teeth...
and let that smile come
shining through.
And that's my gift to you.
Say yes.
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Mm-hm.
Let's go eat.
You were right.
You have no one taking
care of you out there.
Well, there's Mom.
She's weak.
She'll do everything he tells
her, and you know why.
Because she still thinks
he gives a shit about her.
That's right.
God, they really are something.
Aren't they?
Hm. I mean, he doesn't
give a fuck and she...
Desperately needs one.
Mom, don't you know
you're supposed to knock?
- Who were you talking to?
- No one.
- I just heard you!
- It's no one.
I thought of something funny.
Are you smoking pot in here?
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Maybe she was on the phone.
No! I w... I was in there
with her!
It was as though there was
someone else there...
in the room with her and she was
laughing strangely...
and I tried to get through
to her, but I couldn't.
- Okay, okay. Ssh-ssh... okay.
- Are you listening to me, Dan?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm listening to you.
She has problems, okay?
We know this.
- No, but...
- This is not news.
Oh, come on. I don't need that.
That's not...
Please hear me out.
Please! I have a very strong
feeling about this.
- You're having a panic attack.
- If you would've seen this...
- Amy! Amy!
- I'm not! I'm not!
Amy, stop, breathe.
Let me help you.
Open up.
Drink up... look.
Okay, now get your breath back,
it's gonna be alright.
Everything's gonna be alright.
You know why?
Why?
'Cause I know what I'm doing
and I'm taking care of it.
- Do you believe me?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Ssh-ssh.
Alright.
Ssh.
They've come back.
The dreams?
Well, they'll go away,
they always do.
But then they always come back.
Oh, the old club house.
We haven't been here
since we were like four.
Yeah, no one really
comes now that it's closed.
It's a shame, it's really
pretty.
Yeah.
- Should we put these on?
- Okay.
That's it! That's it!
Now, I'm gonna let go of you,
okay?
No, Lily, wait. Don't. Please.
We're just gonna go to the club
house, it's fine.
- Okay?
- No.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't. Don't. Don't.
Look at me. You're gonna have
to do it on your own eventually.
You can't hold on to me forever.
- Okay.
- Okay? That's it, come on.
Head up! Head up!
No, I can't, I can't do this.
Ow! Lily, come on, help me up.
- He's mine, you know?
- What? Who?
You know who I'm talking about.
No, I don't.
Where are you going?
Lily!
Lily, come on!
You wanna believe in it,
don't you?
What?
That she's your friend,
that she cares about you.
She is my friend.
But you're not so sure of that
now, are you?
We've been best friends
since we were three.
I was there too, remember?
I remember when she left
you alone in the sand box.
All alone, by yourself...
because she wanted to play
with the other girls.
That never happened.
I was there when you made a pact
not to sit next to each other...
on the first day of grade
school.
No, she was late that day.
- The teacher seated her next to...
- No!
She was there before you
arrived, Maria...
sitting next to little Chloe...
acting like she didn't know
who you were.
And poor little you,
you were there...
in your little, pink dress...
because she told you it made you
look as pretty as a princess.
You didn't remember that,
did you?
But I do, I remember all
of those moments.
I remember when she'd laugh
behind your back...
and roll her eyes when you
weren't looking.
I remember all of those things.
All of those things
that you choose to forget.
Just like you wanted to forget
her leaving you...
lying on the ice today.
No. No. No.
But I won't let
you forget, Maria...
because that's
what real friends do.
They share their pain.
And you have so
much inside of you.
But I can take all of
those feelings away.
Trust me, and you trust
in yourself.
Let me help you, be there
for you...
instead of you.
Come on.
I can fix things.
Give me your other hand.
Kiss me.
Maria?
Yeah, Mom?
I have a surprise for you.
Open up.
This is your time to shine.
Look.
Look at you, like an angel.
Honey, I want you to promise
me something, okay?
Will you promise me that
you will have a good time?
Can you promise me that?
Please, darling,
please promise me.
I promise.
Yeah! Whoo!
Hey, watch it!
Nice!
You want to go?
- What are you doing?
- Let go of me!
No!
- Woo!
- Agh!
Woo-hoo! Fun!
Stop! Agh!
Somebody help her!
Do it! Do it!
Hey, watch out!
You're such a jerk!
Is she okay?
Airam?
Airam, are you there?
Airam, I need you now.
Please come back.
Please come back, I need you.
Maria.
Now... let me take your pain
away.
Just close your eyes...
and kiss me.
Agh!
Oh, it hurts!
Agh, something's wrong! Agh!
Help me! Agh!
So how was it?
How was what?
The prom.
It was perfect, just perfect.
That's so great.
So, tell me more. Did you
have a fabulous time?
Did you... did you dance
with anyone?
Mom, it was everything
I wished for.
- I'm starving!
- We have fresh bagels.
Mm!
Well, someone's got
her appetite back.
I'm sorry, I haven't been
myself lately.
Mm!
- Oh shit.
- Shut up.
Morning, ice queen.
Oh, shit.
Whoo! Yeah! Ha-ha!
You're not laughing.
What? Am I not funny anymore?
Or is that 'cause you get a
hard on every time you see me?
Dude, what happened?
- She was feeling you up.
- Shut the fuck up, man!
Hey!
- You okay?
- Mm-hm.
What happened back there?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
He's still shaking, what...
what'd you say to him?
Uh, I told him...
Wow. Uh...
Oh, um, I think this belongs
to you.
Oh.
Well, what are you doing?
I was just giving Maria her pin
back.
See ya.
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry about what
happened last night.
That was... it was fucking wrong.
- Was it?
- Yeah, it was shameful.
Is that what you felt? Shame?
Hey, look, I didn't do
anything wrong. Okay?
- I tried to stop them, but...
- Sure.
You're not quitting on me now,
are you?
Quitting?
You said you were
gonna teach me to skate.
You still want to?
Why not?
Well, after prom...
What's the point, Maria?
Self-improvement.
Hey, honey. What's up?
Hi, Daddy.
Hey.
Did we have a lunch date
or something?
Did I forget anything or...?
Huh... okay, so?
I missed you.
That's nice.
And I... I missed you, too.
Dr. Brennan?
- Can I send in the next patient?
- Just hold on a second!
Sweetie, what's going on?
Is something wrong? You need
something?
I can... something I can do?
All right, well, I guess
I'll see you at home.
Sharon, he's ready for you.
You want me to call you a cab?
No, I'll take a bus.
Hey, we don't have any more
of that delicious hot cocoa?
You want me to fix you one
for the road?
Hm...
I'll take that as a yes.
Hi, this is Dr. Brennan's
office.
We have an opening for an
appointment...
at 1:00 o'clock, if you're
interested?
Great.
We'll let him know
you're coming.
I took the liberty of throwing
in some marshmallows.
Mm. Thank you, oh,
and I almost forgot!
Dad wants you to have Mom
pick him up here...
for a romantic lunch date
at 1:00 o'clock.
- Sure thing.
- Okay.
Hello? Hi, Naomi.
He does?
Today?
Yeah, he is the best.
Okay... oh, in an hour.
Okay, great, see you,
yeah okay, thanks.
That's a pretty dress.
Oh, thank you, it's Dr. Dan's
favorite.
Where's Daddy?
- Is he working late?
- Mm.
Is he working late?
Probably, yes.
Uh, how's the tofu steak?
It doesn't even look
like you've touched it.
It's just like your marriage.
What?
A stale imitation of the real
thing.
Have you lost your mind?
Where's Dad?
I just told you.
He's probably got some extra
procedures...
and he's going to be
at the office late.
Please stop smiling at me
like that.
Why don't you tell the truth?
It's so liberating.
Try it.
Dad is not working late.
See?
What are you talking about?
- Say it.
- Say what?
Just say that you're tired...
of him fucking all those
other women.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't know what came over me,
I'm so sorry.
I'm not.
What are you looking at?
What do you think you're doing?
Having dinner with Mom.
Why were you so mean to her?
- Was I lying?
- No.
Am I not doing what
you've always wanted to do?
Saying what you've
always wanted to say?
Everything you didn't dare.
Maybe.
It's about time for the truth
to surface, isn't it?
I guess.
Just follow me, stop resisting.
She deserves it, they all do.
It's time they learned that.
- Learned what?
- That they've sinned.
Against who?
Against who?!
You're dead.
- See you later, man.
- See you.
- Later, man.
- Yeah, late.
Fuck! Aw! Fuck, my knee!
Fuck!
Agh! Fuck!
Ssh.
It's good to see you smiling.
Okay.
That's it. That's it!
- Yeah?
- Yeah!
Cool, yeah, that's it!
Maria, that's great!
Jeez, have you been practicing?
Whoa.
Holy shit!
Hm.
Hello?! Can you please
come quick?!
Yeah, I'm here with my friend
and she she's fallen and I...
I think she's dead. Oh God!
Um yeah, we're at the old
club house on Wellington.
Please come quickly!
Please hurry.
We still have a couple
questions for your daughter.
Well, can it wait? I mean,
she's been through so much.
Sure. We'll stay in touch.
Thank you.
Why are you doing this?
Because you wanted me to.
I don't. Do you hear me?!
I don't!
I want you back here behind the
glass, back where you belong.
I want out. I want out!
Did you really want me to
risk our lives to save hers? Hm?
Save? You pushed her to it.
I didn't touch her.
That's right, accidents happen.
She brought this on herself.
I didn't want this to happen.
Can you look at me
and sincerely say...
you want her back in your life?
Good. There are no lies
between us.
Remember, I'm doing all
of this for you.
For us.
Wait. Who are you?
You know me.
I'm sorry for your loss.
- Hey.
Where are you going?
Home. I really can't...
Handle it?
I'm sorry, I um, I didn't
mean to just leave like that.
Hey.
- We'll pull through, yeah?
- Mm-hm.
We're in this together.
You know that, right?
Something for the pain?
I didn't know you smoked weed.
I do now.
I just can't believe she's gone.
I keep waiting for her to come
back and tell me...
it's all just some kind of sick
joke or something.
Stupid, isn't it?
You're just sad, that's all.
I know how that feels.
Sometimes I think it's all
I know.
Are you okay?
Are you crying?
I have a confession to make.
What?
All of those times when I was
with you and Lily...
I'd look at her and I'd just
think, what would it be like...
if it were you touching my hair,
kissing my lips?
And then, when I was
alone with myself...
I'd touch myself...
and I'd imagine your hand
touching me all over.
Stop.
And I'd get so hot
thinking about it.
Stop it.
Maria... don't, it's wrong.
I can't stop now, Sean.
Feel me.
One special som tam salad.
Mm.
- You like?
- Mm-hm.
Not many
Americans order this dish.
They don't know what
they're missing.
Bon appétit.
Thank you.
It's good to see
you enjoy your food.
I'm enjoying everything now,
Daddy.
So, how are you feeling?
I mean, after the accident.
Oh, I'm good.
- You're good?
- Mm-hm.
It was only a couple days ago.
- You two were so close.
- Not anymore.
Daddy, are you ever coming
back home?
It's complicated. Your mom and
I, um, we have problems.
But it's nothing
you can't fix, right?
That's what you do best,
fix things.
Yeah... I try.
Honey.
Hey, clean yourself up.
What are you doing?
Sit in your chair.
Sit in your chair properly.
Cheers.
What do you see? Hm?
You see a sophisticated,
young woman? Do you?
A fiery, independent spirit?
An adult? Is that what you see?
'Cause I'll tell you what I see.
I see a little girl trying way
too hard and looking pathetic.
Now sit in your goddamn chair.
So at the base of the well...
Dante finds himself within
a large, frozen lake.
It's Cocytus, the ninth circle
of hell.
Entrapped in the ice, he finds
the sinners guilty...
of treacheries against those...
who with they had special
relationships.
Now, as Ciardi writes, the
treacheries of these souls...
were denials of love and
of all human warmth.
As they denied human ties...
so were they bound by the
unyielding ice.
All right, round one, Caina,
named after?
Not everyone at once.
It was Cain, surprise, surprise.
And he killed his own brother
in the first act of murder...
that's Genesis 4:8.
Now this roundhouse is the
kindreds...
to their to their treacheries.
So they're allowed to have their
heads and necks above the ice...
and they're allowed to bow just
to prevent themselves...
Maria! Maria! Hey, Maria!
Maria, get back, it's freezing.
Get back in here. Are you crazy?
Stop it, it's cold,
it's freezing.
Oh shit!
Come on.
Hi.
School project, they let us
go early.
Oh... hi, Sean.
Hey, Mrs. Brennan.
How are you holding up
these days?
It must be so hard for you.
Uh... it's not easy, but
we're helping each other.
Oh.
And how exactly are you
doing that? By cutting school?
Go back to sleep, Mom.
Harder.
Hey, I've got an idea.
Isn't it a little bit
early for one of your ideas?
Let's cut school today.
Again? I can't.
I got a physics exam.
Okay, what time is your exam?
Fourth period.
- No, no way.
- Mm-hm. Come on.
There's so much we can
do in a couple of hours.
Mm.
Mom's bottomless liquor cabinet.
You're just full of surprises,
baby.
Hey, Mom?
At school, where else?
Wait. Who... who called?
The police?
Did she say why they
wanted to talk to me?
No, I'm not with her.
I don't know where she is.
I... I didn't get a chance
to tell you about us.
I'm sorry, I... look yeah,
it doesn't matter where I am.
Okay, Mom? I'll get to them
right away.
Okay. Bye.
We gotta go.
The police, they wanna talk
to me.
They wanna talk to you, too.
They found out that we've
been... anyway...
they're waiting for us in the
principal's office, so...
And what do you care?
What?
Well, you've got nothing
to tell the police.
Yeah, but they don't know that.
It's the police, Maria.
We... we gotta go.
We don't wanna get into trouble.
I'm going to college next year.
I'm not going to the police.
What... what are you talking
about?
We... we gotta help them out.
Let... let's do it for Lily.
She's dead, Sean.
You don't still care about her,
do you?
What does that have
to do with anything?
Oh, Sean.
She didn't care about you,
not like I do.
Stay with me.
- Wait, Maria, stop.
- Stay with me.
Please stop.
- Stop. Stop!
- Agh!
Why are you avoiding the cops?
What aren't you telling me?
There's no point.
No point in what?
Can I hold our baby?
Honey, listen to me.
I have seen her,
it's better this way.
We could love her. Just why
can't we just love her?
She's deformed, Amy,
there's no point.
No point in what?
Maria? Hey.
- Daddy.
- Jesus.
I'm not feeling well.
- What's going on?
- I think I drank too much.
Aw, Christ, who gave you
alcohol?
I don't remember.
- Where were you?
- Don't remember.
- Can you help me, Daddy?
- Yeah. Okay.
All right, stay there.
Okay... here, here's
a come on, come on.
- Here, here, here, drink that.
- Daddy.
- Drink it.
- Dad.
Drink. All right, drink it all.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Why are you always such a mess?
Jesus.
Maria, put your shirt on,
please.
Maria! I'm not messing around.
I want your clothes on now!
Put 'em on!
What are you doing? Jesus.
Do you think this...
You think that's sh...
shocking me?
You think I don't see bodies
all day long?
It's not right, you're not well.
Maria... stop it. Whatever it
is, stop it now.
- Do you think I'm beautiful?
- What?
Do you think I'm beautiful?
Of course, you are, now get
dressed.
Just, whatever is happening, I
want you to stop it now, Maria.
- Would you love me if I wasn't?
- What?
Would you love me if I wasn't
beautiful?
- If I was deformed?
- What?
- Why would you say that?
- Would you?
Just put that on, please,
I'm asking nicely, please.
Put this on, okay?
Put it on!
Please, put it on.
Look at me, Daddy.
All right.
See me.
Yes. Yes, I would.
Okay?
Why couldn't you love me?
Why couldn't you just love me?
Maria?
Oh, shit.
Subtitles by explosiveskull