There was a time
I barely remember now
before all of... this.
I have to remind myself
what it was like then.
A time when I had a mother
I trusted, a sister I adored,
a life that was
familiar, safe.
And then time travel happened
and history changed.
You're Connor Mason.
Mr. Mason invented
a time machine
and chose not to tell
the government about it
until it was stolen
by terrorists.
Garcia Flynn, ex-NSA asset
in Eastern Europe.
If Flynn kills people
who aren't supposed to die,
history changes.
Our earliest prototype.
We call this one the Lifeboat.
There's room in there
for three passengers.
To do what? Go after him?
Lucy Preston.
History, anthropology.
You're world-class.
Master Sergeant Wyatt Logan.
Delta Force.
RUFUS: Rufus.
I'm a pilot.
You might want to hold on.
I thought history was
something worth protecting.
Worth dying for even,
no matter what.
Where's Amy?
Amy who?
Since we got back
from 1937,
my sister's gone.
Erased from history.
I didn't know
you were married.
Jessica died.
FLYNN: You were out
with Jessica in San Diego.
She ran into an old boyfriend
at the bar,
and you had a major fight.
She told you to stop the car.
She got out,
never came home that night.
They found her strangled
in the bushes.
You want this
telegram delivered
50 years from now?
Jessica, on Saturday,
February 11, 2012,
go home with Wyatt
even if he's being an ass.
I understand.
I would do anything
to get my sister back.
We can change history.
And somehow we can save
the people we love.
Jessica's alive.
You had been murdered.
In your reality.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
I'm pregnant.
I thought I knew
who the enemy was,
but I was wrong.
Stay the hell
away from her.
Oh, you mean Lucy?
You know she's not
your wife, right?
I know everything about you.
You want to know how I know?
LUCY: I didn't write that.
But you will. Ask them why
they really chose you
for this mission.
It was Rittenhouse.
Rittenhouse isn't a "him,"
it's a "they."
Rittenhouse changed
history and brought
Jessica back.
An organization that
wanted to control the past,
present and future.
And worse, my family
was part of it.
Well, I've got news for you,
my dear.
You're a part of it, too.
We will change history.
My name is Emma Whitmore.
I've always been loyal
to Rittenhouse.
Some of us
aren't royalty, princess.
Some of us had to work
our way up.
I thought
I'd lost everything,
so all that was left to do
was to fight.
Not for the past anymore,
but for our future.
Everyone's future.
Fight for each other.
It wasn't enough, though.
Rufus? Rufus!
And we lost
the only thing we had left.
Hope.
But this can't be
the end of our story.
We've come too far,
we've sacrificed too much.
There has to be a way
to get back what we lost.
To make things right
and save the people we love,
no matter what.
But it's all up to you now.
You have to change history.
Well, what are you waiting on?
You guys want
to get Rufus back, or what?
That's...
Us.
It's not possible.
Well, actually, it is.
Where are you from?
When are you from?
2023.
How are you even here?
In your own timelines...
The side effects...
We're not immune
to the effects.
We don't have much time.
I know.
Why would you
endanger yourselves
like this?
We didn't
have much of a choice.
We can't stop Rittenhouse
without Rufus.
Rittenhouse still exists?
In 2023?
JIYA: Wait.
You said we can get
Rufus back. How?
Everything you need,
it's in there.
Uh, my journal?
W-What are we supposed
to do with it?
Just figure it out together.
Together.
Yes, both of you.
What about the baby?
There is no baby.
Jessica lied to manipulate me.
Us.
Let's go.
Wait.
There's no time,
just focus on the journal.
Okay? Start with page...
What's wrong?
What's happening? Is she okay?
Or, am I okay?
Oh, God.
It's the side effects.
We got to go now.
Take our Lifeboat.
It's a lot easier to fly.
A few upgrades.
You guys can fly ours?
We've learned a lot
in the last five years.
What's wrong with her?
She'll be fine.
Merry Christmas, by the way.
'Tis the season.
To finish what we started.
Correct mistakes.
Create a better world.
But we're doing it my way now.
No more bloodlines
or any cult crap.
So if that's why you're here,
walk away right now.
For those of you
who choose to stay,
all I ask is loyalty.
What's the plan, boss?
You can
set up my office.
Big chair, mahogany desk.
You can handle that?
Right away.
Then, we're gonna do
what St. Nicholas
and Carol couldn't.
We're gonna take out Lucy
and her damn team
once and for all.
What can I do?
Mrs. Logan.
I have a job for you.
It's time to pay our last
sleeper agent a visit.
I'm so sorry, Wyatt.
How could anyone lie
about something like that?
It's Rittenhouse. It's how
they get what they want,
and they're
so good at it, too,
you don't realize it
until it's too late.
My mother was never the woman
I thought she was.
Now that she's gone,
it still hurts.
Are you okay?
Something tells me
Jessica wouldn't have been
the best mother, anyway.
Doesn't matter.
What matters
is getting Rufus back.
You want to do the honors?
What is all this?
Our history.
All of our missions.
It was, uh, my way
of keeping record
of all of it, I guess.
This thing is incredible.
It has advanced
reentry stabilization
and Tipler Cylinders.
Nice work, Jiya.
I'm guessing
you're the one who built it.
I might've made
a suggestion or two.
What are Lucy and Wyatt doing?
Reading the journal,
trying to figure out
where we take this new toy.
Okay, well, how long will
that take? Let's just go.
I mean, if we can go back
to our own timelines then...
Go back to our own timelines?
Are you overlooking the fact
that Future Lucy's head
nearly exploded?
For all we know,
that was their one
and only trip before she...
It wasn't the only trip.
She came to see me
in Sao Paulo
before all of this began.
What are you talking about?
Christmas Eve, 2014,
Lucy showed up
and handed me the journal.
The Lucy we just saw?
It was Lucy.
She traveled to a same time
she existed before.
It's possible.
But not without side effects,
it isn't,
and headaches
are just the beginning.
If you stay too long,
even just minutes,
there are
nosebleeds, seizures,
brain damage,
uh, memory loss, and then...
And then?
Well, everybody's tolerance
is different, but eventually,
insanity and death.
If Lucy and Wyatt are willing
to risk their lives for Rufus,
then so am I.
Jiya, no...
Lucy.
I never meant to hurt you.
I just wanted to do
the right thing.
I know. I know.
Hollywood, Salem...
...Titanic.
This hasn't happened yet.
You and Flynn.
Um...
All right,
I'm gonna let you
finish that one.
Hey, you find anything
in the journal yet?
We've found some... things,
but nothing about
Rufus, though, yet.
Okay, I can look at it
maybe then, and I can see...
Hey. They said me and Lucy.
There's got to be a reason.
If your future selves
are so brilliant,
then why didn't they
just tell us what to do?
Sorry, I'm just...
No, it's... it's okay.
What's this?
Rufus picked it up in 1981,
hid it behind SpaghettiOs
so you wouldn't find it
till Christmas, but...
I think he'd want you
to have it.
"Merry Christopher.
A little pun from '81."
Couldn't help himself,
could he?
Yeah.
Original issue packaging?
Rufus always told me there was
no puzzle you can't solve.
January 28,
1848, near Sacramento.
Lucy?
That's four days
after gold was discovered
at Sutter's Mill,
which instigated
the gold rush,
which basically
made California a-a state.
So Rittenhouse wants gold?
Shocker. A time travel robbery?
Let them have the gold.
Let them have California.
We need to focus
on getting Rufus back.
Listen,
when the Mothership jumps,
we chase it.
That's been protocol
since day one.
What is the point
of getting Rufus back
if we just let Rittenhouse
decimate history?
Are you joking?
Future Lucy said
we need Rufus
to stop Rittenhouse.
Yes.
Rufus trained you
to pilot the Lifeboat
for this very reason.
The world needs saving.
It's what Rufus would want.
We need to find and stop
their sleeper agent.
Whoa.
Hey. Is your arm okay?
It's fine.
You got a little bit
of something here.
Makeup can only cover so much.
Whoa.
This thing has autopilot.
What? As in,
anyone can fly it?
Apparently. You just plug in
the date and location.
I guess Future Me
built a DeLorean
out of the Lifeboat.
That's a joke
Rufus would've made.
I wish
he could see this.
He'll see it, Jiya.
I know he will.
You think
that's the sleeper?
No, I think
that's James Marshall.
Who's James Marshall?
He's the millwright
who discovered gold.
He's bringing it here
to show his boss, John Sutter.
Speak of the devil.
Looks like history's still
on course.
Come on.
I'd like to mine that gold.
Come back, say hi.
Has any woman ever
responded positively to that?
Just admiring the view, miss.
Oh.
We don't see
many women 'round here,
especially pretty ones.
First that redhead
and the blonde this morning.
And now these two.
What were these
other women here for?
Probably gold.
Rumor has it
someone found some
up by the mill.
You think she's here
to activate a sleeper?
Maybe we should talk
to Sutter first.
There's a reason
that Emma didn't go
straight to the mill.
Guys.
They weren't here for Sutter.
Okay.
Now, that's our cue
to steal some horses
and catch up with the sleeper
at Sutter's Mill.
We need to change.
Into what?
You're not fooling anyone
dressed like that.
General lack of females
in the vicinity,
two women on horseback
would've been flagged
a mile away.
All this time,
you knew what was
in the journal.
I told you
it can be unreliable.
I mean, with us.
Oh, so you finally got
to the good part, huh?
Must have been, uh, awkward.
Well? Was it everything
you imagined?
You were imagining it,
weren't you?
Why didn't you tell me that
we were going to be together?
Honestly?
I didn't really believe it.
I'm not exactly your type.
You don't know anything
about my type.
Also, I almost killed you
a few times, so there's that.
In the future,
I must have seen
a different side to you.
I guess I've already
started to.
Oh, then stop.
'Cause if you read
the rest of the journal,
that affair we have?
It ends badly, because...
...your heart always
belonged to someone else.
We have company.
Whoa.
You gringos stole my horses?
It's a lady.
You're Joaquin Murrieta?
Lady seems to know who I am.
Go ahead, tell your friends.
One of the most dangerous
bandits in California.
Your half brother was murdered
and your wife assaulted
after a dispute over a mule.
Then what?
Then you killed the men
who did it.
Not all of them.
I don't like when people mess
with what belongs to me.
Those horses are mine.
Our friend
was murdered, too.
We're just looking
for the people that did it.
Tragic story, I'm sure.
You know they hang people
for stealing horses?
Don't worry, I'll save you
the pain in the neck...
Really? They, uh,
hang people
for stealing stolen horses?
Because each
one of these horses
have a different brand
on them.
All right, look.
We can all start shooting
each other and see who wins,
but then we wouldn't
be able to tell you
where the gold is.
What do you know about gold?
We know where
there's plenty of it.
It's worth a lot more
than these horses.
We'll tell you
where it is
if you just put down your guns
and let us borrow these horses
a little while longer.
It's a deal, for now.
We ride until nightfall.
Vamos.
Hurry up.
Don't fall behind.
Must have been Tornado.
As in Zorro's horse, Tornado?
Zorro was real?
Joaquin Murrieta, he was
one of the Mexican outlaws
that inspired
the legend of Zorro.
Now you tell me.
Were you gonna ask
for his autograph?
I was a little focused
on the fact that he was trying
to kill us. Come on.
Where's Emma?
I'm her lieutenant now.
Come on. Show me the money.
I didn't sleep in the dirt
for three years here
to report to some underling.
How about we sort this out
with Emma in 2018?
How about you hand
the rest over?
Where the hell are you going?
You'll be picked up
when we say the time is right.
You can't just leave me here.
Pleasure doing business
with you.
Where did you get
that gun of yours?
Oh, it's, uh, Prussian.
But it's not
very powerful, though.
Well, I understand
how that feels.
I don't want
your sympathy, gringo.
You can't begin to understand.
My family was murdered, too,
by terrible people.
And?
And I tried it your way,
with violence,
but it didn't solve anything.
It just created
more pain.
But they deserve
to be punished.
Oh, they deserve
But it won't help your family.
Believe me, I tried.
Over and over.
You will just become
as bad as those men.
You have given up
your quest for revenge?
For what?
Ah.
I thought the legend
of Joaquin's family tragedy
was just some myth
from an 1854 dime novel.
I mean, if it's true,
he's about to go
on a murderous rampage
across the state
of California.
Can you blame him?
Wyatt? What is it?
It's Jessica.
What?
I keep rereading these pages,
and everything
leads to the same place.
Jessica is the reason
Rufus is dead.
Rittenhouse brought her back
to distract me or spy on us.
I don't really know.
But I played
right into their hands
when I brought her
into the bunker.
Jiya, she's the one
who kidnapped you,
she's the reason
we went to Chinatown.
There is a simple
equation here.
It has been here all along,
I just didn't want to see it.
It's the reason future version
of you gave me the journal.
So you're saying...
I'm saying because
Jessica lives, Rufus dies.
And to save Rufus,
Jessica has to be taken
out of the timeline somehow,
and I'm gonna be
the one to do it.
I will make sure
that Jessica never
steps foot in the bunker.
You mean,
go back to your own timeline?
No. No way.
It's too dangerous.
You could die.
It's the only way
to save Rufus.
How does it help us
to save Rufus
if it means sacrificing you?
Because Rufus didn't deserve
what happened to him.
You didn't deserve
what I did to you.
I let everybody down.
But I'm gonna make
things right.
Well, you're not
doing it alone.
I'm coming with you.
I am, too.
We'll get Rufus back together.
Well, it sounds
like a noble plan,
but if you all die
trying to save Rufus,
who will be left here to save
the world from Rittenhouse?
Take half of this
and store it.
Use the other half to fetch us
some sisters in arms.
What are you doing?
Santa's got one last chimney
to shimmy down.
But we don't have
any sleepers left.
Going back to 1950 Korea
to buy us one.
Need any help?
Oh, you just take care
of that gold.
I'll take care of the rest.
Wyatt. Where's Flynn?
He rode ahead.
Said he wanted
to scout the mill.
What for?
He didn't say.
Get some rest.
JOAQUIN: Whoa.
Ha! Eureka.
So the rumors are true.
Where is your tall friend?
I thought he was
scouting for us.
That's a good question.
Tell him
he can keep the horses.
You are true to your word.
Unlike most americanos
I have met.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have some mining to do
before your people
destroy the land.
Uh, wait, uh...
Let him go.
We'll find the sleeper agent
on our own.
But what if we need backup?
Uh, Wyatt?
Hands up,
where we can see them.
You didn't tell us all
you were wanted.
Lock them up. It's payday.
I told you,
there's nothing to celebrate
until we have Rufus back.
I'm tired of making scarves.
I need something
to occupy myself while I try
to get my head
around the fact
that five years from now,
we're apparently
still chasing Rittenhouse.
Yes, that's because
we're going about this
the wrong way.
We need to save Rufus
to stop Rittenhouse.
Not the other way around.
I didn't want to send the team
on this mission.
If you want to blame somebody,
you should look in the mirror,
because you're the one who
created the damn time machine
for them in the first place.
You think I don't spend
every day wishing I could
take it all back?
I'm sorry, Connor.
We have to destroy them.
You know that, right?
The Mothership
and the Lifeboat.
We have to destroy them.
Can it be done?
Yeah, of course
we can do it, but...
Oppenheimer. After Hiroshima,
he realized
the terrible mistake
he'd made.
The "destroyer of worlds,"
he called himself.
And everyone agreed:
nuclear weapons,
terrible idea.
Six months later,
the Soviets had one.
The technology
already exists, Denise.
So some new Connor Mason
or Rufus Carlin
will one day create
their own time machine.
And we'll be without
a vessel to stop them.
What then?
They sent you
to protect her, too?
Who, Rittenhouse?
Yeah.
No.
You started this,
you know.
Of course.
It's always my fault.
Couldn't possibly have been
the drunk jerk
picking bar fights.
Please, Jess,
he wanted that fight.
You wanted that fight.
Yeah, that's right. Just keep
defending your boyfriend,
why don't you?
Oh, my God.
We were on a break,
and it was the best six months
of my life, by the way.
All right.
Who was that?
Is that him?
Let me see the phone.
Give me the phone!
No.
Stop it!
You know what? Pull over.
Pull... What are you...
We're in the middle
of nowhere.
I said pull over!
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
Getting the hell
away from you.
Jessica, come on,
get back in the damn...
Fine, you want to walk? Walk.
Get in the car.
No. Drive away.
Get back in the damn car,
will you?
I'll walk!
Come on.
I'm sorry, all right?
Just get back in.
Leave me alone
before I call the cops
and get you busted for a DUI.
Fine. Fine.
Who the hell are you?
Never thought I'd say this,
but we could really use
our "tall friend"
right about now.
Yeah, where is he?
And Joaquin?
Mmm. Probably halfway
to Sonora
with a pound of gold.
What ends up
happening to him?
He gets killed in a shootout
in 1853 by California Rangers.
Mmm. It was never proven
it was him.
Historians disagree.
Oh, it was him.
I saw his pickled head
in a jar in Chinatown
in 1888.
Well, let's just find
a way out of here
before our heads get pickled.
Wait. What is that?
Sounds like Flynn
is really Flynning it up
out there. Flynn!
Flynn, it's us!
We're in here! Help us!
Yeah, it's about time!
Merry Christmas,
you filthy animals.
JIYA: Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, we saved you.
Uh, I'm pretty sure
I'm the one
that did the saving.
Oh. Um...
Let me at him.
Um...
Geez, leave you alone
for one second... Mmm.
I think I'm gonna have to let
you get captured more often.
Rufus... you were dead.
I... was... what?
You died in San Francisco.
1888. Emma shot you.
When was I in 1888?
It doesn't matter, okay?
You're alive now.
Yeah, very much so.
What?
How is that possible?
Flynn did it.
This mean I'm gonna have
to hug him, too?
Rufus!
Did you find your friends?
I need a hand over here!
BRB. Got to go help Zorro.
It's him.
Flynn must have taken
the Lifeboat and...
Taken Jessica
out of the timeline.
Rufus didn't die?
He went with us on this trip?
He's-he's been here all along?
And Jessica is... gone.
I guess this is
why you end up with Flynn.
I don't.
I...
I don't end up with him.
Let's go, you two.
Guys, come on.
You caught the sleeper?
Well,
it's not exactly
my first rodeo.
But Joaquin here
snagged those jerks.
Turns out the real Zorro
is much cooler
than Antonio Banderas.
Who needs a mask, anyway?
Take your share,
or I'll be tempted to spend it
all in one game of monte.
Where we're going,
we don't need gold.
But may we borrow your horses
one last time?
Take them. I can buy
all the horses I want.
Maybe even mustangs.
I can't wait
to show my wife.
Thank you. Thank you.
No problem.
Lucy.
What's wrong?
It's Flynn. He...
He wrote me a note.
My dear Lucy,
if you're reading this,
I guess I didn't make it back.
Well, maybe that's
for the best, when you think
about what I've done
in the past.
To the team. To you.
We both wanted to stop
Rittenhouse, but somehow
you didn't let it destroy you
the way I did.
So if anyone's expendable
on this team, it's me.
Tell Rufus
he can thank me later.
I have to admit,
I don't hate the guy.
I regret the pain
I caused you, Lucy.
And maybe by doing this,
I can find a small way
to make things right,
so you can have
the future you deserve.
I know with time,
you'll forgive Wyatt,
because you love him.
And deep down,
you know he was just trying
to do the right thing.
I hope you get
everything you want in life.
I hope you can be happy.
And one day,
I hope you get to have
a family of your own.
And I hope
you get your sister back.
There are some things
in the journal,
I never could figure them out.
But it's led us this far.
One good thing in my life,
the one thing that I couldn't
hate after I lost my family.
Never give up trying to save
the world from Rittenhouse,
and then maybe you
can save the ones you love.
Well,
guess I'll see you
Christmas Eve, 2014.
You know the place.
All my love...
Flynn.
So after
dispatching Jessica,
Flynn sent the Lifeboat back
to you in 1848
but stayed in 2012.
The, um...
time travel side effects
must have been too severe.
Or maybe he wanted
to go back and see his family
one more time.
Either way,
he's stuck in 2012.
Was. It took some searching,
but the body of a John Doe
was found in the dunes
by the ocean.
So Flynn died,
and you gave up
Jessica for me?
I'd like to propose a toast
to Flynn.
He had our backs.
Sacrificed his life
so that we could defeat
Rittenhouse together.
Let's not let him down.
We owe him that.
To Garcia.
Jessica?
Hello?
Where the hell is Jessica?
You mean Jan?
No, I don't mean Jan.
Tell me where Jessica is.
Who is Jessica?
Jessica Logan.
Wyatt's wife.
I don't know who that is.
They must have changed
something.
Eliminated her
from the timeline.
Changed history.
That's our job.
What do you
think they...
Get the Mothership ready.
What for?
Hell.
Lieutenant Langford?
Husband to Charlotte,
father of Margaret, age six?
Who are you?
I represent
a special kind of insurance.
Sorry, lady. Marines cover
everything I need.
Sure about that?
Because I can make sure
that your family
is very well provided for.
Your daughter would get
the very best
medical attention,
and she's gonna need it.
How do you know
about Margaret?
Her polio?
I just know.
And I'd like to help.
All I ask in return
is one small
big... favor.
Joaquin Murrieta never became
a notorious killer
after striking rich
at Sutter's Mill.
He and his wife
moved to California
and started a family
and a successful horse ranch.
Kind of killed Zorro
in the crib.
Where'd you find that?
That was supposed to be
your Christmas present.
I'm sorry. You were...
Dead.
Yeah.
Yeah. Look at you,
eating Rubik's Cubes
for breakfast and upgrading
the Lifeboat
to DeLorean status.
Yeah, but I didn't do it.
Future Me did it.
Oh, well, Future You
sounds awesome.
Mmm. Mmm?
And really smart.
Mmm-hmm.
And I can't wait
to sleep with her, too.
What?
I'm pretty sure
you're not Harry Potter,
so what's with the scar?
Uh...
Chinatown.
From what at Chinatown?
You don't remember it,
but I-I lived there
for three years
in the 1880s, Rufus.
And it sucked being a woman
in that place.
Someone did that to you?
I got away from him.
Eventually.
Jiya, what happened?
I don't want to talk about it.
Jiya, you can talk to me
about anything.
No. I'm tired.
I'm tired. I just,
I want to go to sleep.
Agent Christopher said
that this is, uh...
Our room.
Yeah.
I guess with,
uh, Jessica gone,
we were...
Together.
Yeah.
But I'm gonna sleep
on the couch, so...
No, you don't have to do that.
I mean, are you sure?
'Cause I don't mind.
Come on, Wyatt, it's fine.
There are... two beds.
Yeah.
It was
really nice what you
said about Flynn.
Yeah, well, I meant it.
I know you did.
You know, he lied to me about
the name of Jessica's killer.
'Cause when
you think about it,
it was him all along.
I spent all this time
trying to find the person
that ruined my life.
I never even
considered the fact
that he was actually trying
to save it.
Flynn told me
something else in his letter,
about Amy.
What's that?
He said there might be a way
that I could get Amy back,
but I can't figure it out.
Besides, Emma
already said that
there was no way I was ever
going to get my sister
back again, so...
If there's a way
to get her back,
we're gonna do it, Lucy.
Not with Rittenhouse
still out there.
You heard what Flynn said.
We have to stop them,
because if we don't, then...
We become those people
that paid us a visit.
I don't want that.
I don't want that for us.
We-we didn't look...
Happy?
Yeah.
I noticed that, too.
I don't want to live
in a world
where we're not
just Lucy and Wyatt.
But after everything
that's happened,
how can we un-know
what we know?
Mothership jumped
to December 24, 1950, in...
Oh, dear...
North Korea.
Well, that's the last day
of the Hungnam evacuations
in the Korean War.
It's just after
the Battle of Chosin.
"Frozen Chosin,"
my grandpa called it.
Said it was the coldest
he'd ever been in his life.
Is Rittenhouse trying
to eliminate you
from the timeline now
by taking out
your grandfather?
No. He was wounded
and sent home
before they started
evacuating on the 10th.
Why did they evacuate?
Well, the U.N. troops
were winning the war,
that is, until
the Chinese Communist army
descended upon them
and forced them to evacuate
to the Port of Hungnam.
It was the Dunkirk
of the Korean War.
Thousands
of Korean refugees showed up,
families just desperate
to evacuate.
Instead of
leaving them behind,
General Edward Almond,
he wanted to see
how many he could save.
But there was a cargo ship,
the USS Meredith Victory,
they were only
supposed to carry
about 60 people, but they
ended up leaving with 14,000.
And nobody died?
Not one. In fact,
there were five babies
born on board. They called it
"The Miracle of Christmas."
Why would Emma
go after refugees?
'Cause she's
the ultimate Grinch.
We'll stop her
and be home for Christmas.
Bundle up.
It's gonna be cold.
Come on.
I'm coming with you.
You don't have to go.
I'm not losing you again.
Did you have to park
the Lifeboat so far away?
Well, we don't want
Communist troops
to come dashing
through the snow to find it.
Oh, God.
Let me see the map.
Here.
Port's a few miles south.
Okay.
So, who's on the boat
that's so important, anyway?
Uh...
The parents of future South
Korean president Moon Jae-in?
And Emma cares about that
because...?
We got to keep moving fast
to stay warm.
Why the Korean War?
I can't for the life of me
think of what Emma
could profit from
or need there.
Well, that's what scares me.
Emma may be a loose cannon,
but she is brilliant,
so there has got
to be a reason.
Mmm.
If our team
can't stop her in 1950,
then we need to catch her
in the present.
Yeah.
Bloody hell.
That can't be.
They're gonna die there?
Must have been a skirmish.
We just missed it.
Fine by me.
Is that a...?
Heliclockter. Copter.
Helicopter.
Must be taking
survivors to port.
Hey, everyone all right?
Yeah. We're good!
Come on.
I got the last chopper
going to Hungnam.
Wyatt?
Are you okay?
Emma set us up.
The pilot, he was
working for her.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. He's dead.
We wrestled
the controls away from him.
Still crashed.
We would have died.
You saved us.
Rufus and Jiya?
They're okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
All right. Come on.
Okay. Ow!
Does it hurt?
No, the, uh, cold air,
it's very numbing.
Here, let me see.
When did you become G.I. Jane?
Chinatown. My friend
Molly taught me.
Doctors were expensive.
Wonder what happened to her.
She died. Bubonic plague.
I looked it up.
According to
the chopper radio,
Meredith Victory
sailed yesterday.
With 14,000 people,
just like she was
supposed to.
So the pilot, North Korea,
all of it was about
her killing us.
It makes sense.
Emma wants to get us
out of the way.
Well, it doesn't get
much more out of the way
than North Korea
in the dead of night.
Sleeper's dead.
Only thing left to do is find
the Lifeboat and go home.
Anyone have
a one-horse open sleigh?
Come on, it's gonna
be light soon.
This is officially the worst
Christmas vacation ever.
And that includes
the Chevy Chase movie.
The protocol.
They might have
left us a message.
Buried...
Sure.
We'll just go dig up a hole
in the middle of North Korea.
So, what,
would you have us
just do nothing?
Just accept that
they're all gone?
I can't.
I won't accept that.
I'm not accepting anything.
I'm saying we need
a better plan.
From what I found,
it looks like they
were in a helicopter
crash on the 24th.
Yeah. Emma's doing.
They survived,
the pilot didn't.
Thanks to our intrepid team,
no doubt. What exactly
happens on the 25th?
They are killed by
Chinese troops in the
massacre of Usang-Ri.
We've gotta get to them
before that happens.
Uh, how? We don't have
a time machine or a pilot.
Rittenhouse has both.
Yes, and I'm sure Emma
would be delighted to help us
if she wasn't the one
trying to bloody kill us all.
So, this is weird.
In my timeline,
you guys are still a couple.
You think you'll get back
together or what?
Because I'm still totally
shipping Team Wyatt.
What? What's that?
You guys are
like Han and Leia.
Uh, Arwen and Aragorn.
Bella and Edward?
You guys have
obstacles, too.
Rufus, it's not like
we got into a fight.
He was married,
to someone else
who he thought was dead.
Who then,
all of a sudden,
wasn't dead.
So he left me
to be with her.
And I know that you don't
remember that,
but it's not something
I'm going to forget.
Well, apparently I came back
from the dead, so anything's
possible.
I hear that,
but I don't want to be
anyone's second choice.
When you were kidnapped
by your mother,
we thought you were dead.
We all lost hope.
Except for Wyatt.
He never gave up on you.
He always swore
you were out there.
He tried to blowtorch his way
out of the bunker to find you.
I know there
was a Jessica,
but he was willing
to give her up to find me.
And I'll tell you,
the guy likes me,
but if he had to
give you up,
I know for a fact
I'd still be dead.
Doesn't sound
like a second
choice to me.
Guys, look.
Where are they going?
Hungnam.
The last boats have
to evacuate today
before the Chinese army
reaches the port.
Or what happens?
North Korea happens.
Anyone who spoke out
against communism or
tried to help the Americans
was, at best, imprisoned.
And at worst?
Beheaded.
So, what about us?
We need
to keep moving.
Chinese just crossed
the border and they
march dark to dark.
We gotta get
to the Lifeboat
before nightfall.
Otherwise communists
get our time machine,
which, incidentally,
is my least-favorite
Christmas movie.
I'm not worried
about the time machine.
I'm worried about
the thousands of Chinese
troops between us and it.
So, what are you saying?
In all likelihood?
We die.
So, how long does
this war go on for?
War lasts another three years,
till the armistice.
But nobody wins.
North Korea shuts its doors.
There are families who haven't
seen or heard from each other
in decades.
Hey, let's check
out that car.
Please, please,
be a car with a heater.
Dead car.
Well, not exactly sure
dead is a forever thing
with us.
Hey, with our
combined skill set,
how long you think it takes
before this is up and running?
Rufus, I...
It'll be safer, faster
and warmer with wheels.
All right. Why don't
you and Jiya go get
warm in the church?
'Cause we're women
and it's 1950?
Because you're
starting to get frostbite.
You look much
prettier with ears.
Good point. Let's go.
Sit there.
In San Francisco, in 1888,
there was this beautiful
cathedral, St. Mary's.
Rufus will probably think
I was crazy, but it made
me feel closer to him.
I'm really happy for you,
for both of you. I mean,
just to have him back.
I love him.
I know you do.
So much, Lucy.
He loves you, too.
He thinks he does.
But he has no idea
who I am now.
What he remembers
as yesterday was
three years ago for me.
And I've changed, Lucy.
I'm not the same person
he fell in love with.
I'm scared I never will be.
Shh!
You need to be careful.
Informants are everywhere.
Sorry.
What are you doing here?
I thought they were
no Americans
left in the north.
We're... We're
war corespondents.
We got separated
from our unit.
I'm Rachel Maddow
and this...
I'm Lucy. This is Jiya.
I'm Young-Hee.
Hi.
Your English is very good.
I went to a missionary school.
Oh.
Are you evacuating?
No.
I came here to pray.
My husband, he's a journalist,
too, but he asked
too many questions.
They ordered him
to print lies.
We heard they
were coming for him.
Did he go to Hungnam?
With my son, Tae-Woo.
I pray they are safe
on the boat.
What about you? What...
What are you going to do?
Wait until our army
pushes the Chinese back.
In a few days,
maybe this will all be over.
Then my husband and son
will come home.
I still can't believe Jessica
was alive, or that I was dead.
My memories are completely
different from yours
after Hollywood.
You know what's crazy?
Yesterday, Jiya was
a year younger than me.
Now, she's two years older.
She looks pretty good
for her age.
Plus, I always had a thing
for older women.
Started in middle
school actually...
Rufus, I gotta
tell you something.
Jiya being stuck
in Chinatown
for three years...
That was all my fault.
Jiya said
it was Jessica's fault...
Yeah, but it was my fault
for trusting Jessica.
Even when I knew things
didn't add up.
You even said so yourself.
And you told me that
you would never forgive me
for what happened to her.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I'd be lying
to you if I didn't.
Hey, Wyatt.
I forgive you.
That's not good.
Come on.
Guys...
We gotta go.
Couple of North Korean
soldiers headed our way.
I'm pretty sure
they're not here
for midnight mass.
Wait, wait, wait!
We have to take her with us.
Is she important to history?
Everybody is important.
Lucy, what do you
want me to do?
We have to take
her to Hungnam.
She is super pregnant
and she put her life
on the line for us,
no questions asked.
The Lifeboat
is ten miles north.
The port is eight miles south.
We can't lose that much time.
She thinks that her husband
and son are coming home.
Quick history in CliffsNotes,
nobody comes home.
Even if they survive,
she'll be separated
from her family forever.
I'm telling you, we're not
gonna make it to the Lifeboat
if we go to Hungnam.
I wouldn't be here
if my parents didn't
get out of Lebanon.
I got a second chance.
Why shouldn't they?
What's the point of saving
history if we don't save
the people in it?
I think we lost them.
Is everybody all right?
Yeah.
We'll be lucky if
we make it through town,
much less to the port.
I... I can't go to the port.
I need to stay and wait
for my husband and son
to come home.
Young-Hee,
those men will find you.
It's not safe for you
to stay here anymore.
If you get on a boat,
then you can catch up
with your family.
You'll be together.
It's only a few days.
What if it's not?
What's that?
Huh?
Oh, St. Christopher,
patron saint of travelers.
Found it at the church.
Thought we could use
a little extra luck.
After everything
you've been through,
you still kept your faith.
Rufus, you
came back to me.
How could I not?
Merry Christmas to me.
Michael.
There you are.
I was wondering...
Mr. Cahill.
I... I didn't know you'd
been released from prison.
Rittenhouse always
finds a way, Emma.
How did you find us?
I know every Rittenhouse-owned
property on the West Coast.
Started with the estates
and took some time to work
my way down to this dump.
We've had
some difficult times
in your absence.
The most powerful
secret society
the world has ever seen,
a family treasure,
reduced to this.
That incredible machine used
so that you could, what?
Collect art?
I'm trying to replenish
Rittenhouse's assets...
Save it.
You're greedy and selfish.
I've been called worse.
I came to say goodbye.
Just give me a reason, Emma.
Thank you for your help,
Mr. Cahill.
Couldn't have found
this place without you.
You sold us out?
I'm selfish, too.
What did she promise you?
The chance to save
my daughter's life.
Lucy still means
something to me.
Plus protection and immunity
for my teenage son.
It's a family thing, Emma.
Something you'll never
have or understand.
How old is your son?
He's eight.
Does he like school?
Not as much as I do.
I'm a teacher.
What do you teach?
History.
It's hard now. The party wants
us to only teach propaganda.
"And the people
without knowledge
"of their past history,
origin and culture..."
"Is like a tree
without roots."
Marcus Garvey.
I used to be
a history teacher, too.
You all right?
It happened earlier.
I'm fine.
Okay.
Come on!
Want to pop the hood again?
We're only
about a mile from port.
I think we just need to
walk it the rest of the way.
Walk? In her condition?
Okay, okay.
Here.
It's not too much farther.
Oh, God!
You're not okay.
Young-Hee, you're in labor!
Should we get
her to the ambulance?
No, it's too late.
Over here. Come on.
Okay. Oh, my God.
Set her right here.
Right here.
Oh, my God.
Okay. Oh, God,
oh, God, oh, God.
All right, just breathe.
Good job.
You've done this before?
Remote village in Afghanistan.
Woman was in labor
for over 22 hours.
Tried to get her to a hospital
but it was too late.
Healthy baby girl.
So you know
what you're doing.
Well, nothing went
wrong that time.
Okay, well, there's...
There's a MASH
facility at the port.
I can... I can
go find a doctor.
Fine. Take Rufus with you.
Okay.
Be careful, all right?
They're shelling the perimeter
to keep the Chinese out.
Come on, let's go.
You got this, Young-Hee.
In just a few hours
they bomb this whole place?
Can't leave any supplies
behind for the enemy.
But everyone makes
it out alive, right?
Thanks to those two.
It's Colonel Forney
and Dr. Hyun Bong-hak.
They're the real heroes
behind this entire operation.
Convinced General Almond not
to leave any refugees behind.
Colonel Forney, sir.
Ma'am, why haven't
you evacuated?
I'm a war correspondent.
Lucy Preston.
I work with Maggie Higgins.
We put Maggie
on a plane days ago.
I know. We got separated.
We need to get
you on a boat.
Of course, of course.
But, uh, Private Carlin here,
he came across a refugee
who's gone into labor.
We need a nurse or a doctor
as soon as possible.
MASH unit's jammed up
with injured patients.
We need everyone we got...
Sir, please!
Ma'am, I got to make sure
every one in this port
gets out safely, okay?
Maybe you can find a midwife.
I'll take care
of this, Colonel.
Really?
Last boat departs
at 1400 hours.
Okay, let's go.
Come on, come on!
Jiya,
run back to the ambulance,
see if you can find supplies.
Emergency blankets, towels,
first-aid kit, anything.
Okay, but the doctor is...
No time to wait for a doctor.
This baby's coming now. Go.
Around that corner!
Up that hill
about a mile away!
Oh! Oh, my God!
Wyatt!
Jiya!
Wyatt! Wyatt!
Artillery fire.
No. Oh, my God.
Wyatt!
Oh, my God.
That was close, huh?
It's a girl.
Jiya! Jiya!
Oh, my gosh.
Oh!
Wyatt delivered a baby?
In the middle
of a war zone.
All right, wasn't a big deal.
What else don't
I know about you?
Guys, we need to
get to the Lifeboat.
I'll try and find us a truck.
We will make you
as comfortable as possible,
but we have to get
you on a boat soon.
But how will I find
my husband and my son?
There was no time
for record keeping.
You will see him
in Pusan, I think.
YOUNG-HEE: No.
No, no, no, Young-Hee,
Young-Hee.
Wait, wait, wait.
Umma!
Tae-Woo!
I think
this little treasure
belongs to you.
The boats
are leaving soon.
Thank you.
For everything.
Of course, of course.
Good luck. Good luck.
Okay.
Guys, problem.
We can't get a truck.
Rufus, there's like
a million of them here.
They're all rigged
with explosives.
They're gonna blow up
the minute the last boat
leaves port.
Anything with four wheels
is a bomb.
You okay?
I'm trying to have
a vision of a hot shower.
Leave me alone.
Cool, cool, cool.
What are the signs
of frostbite again?
Who kills a nun?
Shh...
Communists.
We're surrounded.
We can't outrun them,
we can't fight them.
We need to hide. Come on.
Stop. They'll see us.
What if they find us anyway?
Well, I'll fire
as many rounds
as I have left.
And then?
Good talk.
I just really don't
want to die. Again.
Would you stop it?
We're not gonna die, okay?
Not after everything
we've been through.
Honestly,
I hope you're right.
I hope there is a God
and that he,
or she, saves us.
You'd think he/she would save
the nun, though, right?
Just saying.
See?
You still laugh at my jokes.
I'm glad we're together.
Look, Jiya, I know
things are different for you.
But...
We're still us.
And for me,
there's no one else
I'd rather face a bloodthirsty
army of communists with.
Me, too.
What are you thinking about?
Flynn.
The last thing that he said
to us before he left
to get in the Lifeboat
was if we all run off
to save Rufus,
who will save the world?
If we die tonight...
I'm not giving up yet.
I guess it's all
up to fate.
What?
Just you...
Talking about fate.
So, you were right.
And here you had me convinced
that there was no such thing.
Timing is everything, right?
After that explosion,
I thought you were dead.
And for a moment,
I saw my whole life
without you.
And my world ended, Wyatt.
I just kept thinking about
all this time
that we had wasted.
Just wasted so much time,
and then, all of a sudden,
there you were.
Holding a stranger's baby
that you had delivered.
Then I knew.
You knew what?
I'd fallen in love with you.
And nothing that happened
or didn't happen
or might happen
was ever gonna change it.
I love you, Wyatt Logan.
I've loved you
since the Alamo,
since you kissed me
with Bonnie and Clyde,
since that night
in Hollywood.
What happened after...
I wanted to choose you.
I just felt like
I owed her something.
I wish I could
take it all back.
And the crazy part is,
Flynn already did.
And now, all that we have
between us is a past
that only we remember.
So?
I don't care
about the past anymore.
And we might
not have a future.
Maybe all that matters
is right now.
Oh, my God!
I can't believe
you're here.
I didn't want
to have to leave you here
to die on Christmas.
Plus, I wanted
to time travel
at least once.
What, no hug?
What would Jesus do?
And you brought Scrooge.
Was it the Ghost
of Christmas Past or Future
that got her here?
I think I liked you better
when you were dead.
Sorry it didn't take.
How'd you like time traveling?
Not my choice of destinations,
but still quite the miracle.
Guys, it's just...
Saint Christopher!
Agent Christopher...
Oh, come on!
Hey!
Wait, wait!
I can bring Amy back.
She's lying.
Try me.
I only did it
'cause your mother
ordered me to.
But I can undo it.
It means nothing to me
and everything to you.
The truth is...
I admire you, Lucy.
We would make
one hell of a team.
Screw the Rittenhouse agenda.
We could make history
whatever we want.
I want all of this to be over.
And you want your sister back.
I can make that happen.
You just have to trust me.
I don't.
If she gets any closer
to that ship, shoot her.
Oh! Oh!
Everybody, get to the
Mothership!
Come on!
Rufus is gonna get
the Mothership home, right?
Well, Rufus got us
to the Lifeboat, didn't he?
Maybe our future selves
came back to save Rufus
so that he could save us all.
Yeah, or maybe...
Maybe what?
Maybe they wanted things
to turn out differently
for us than it did them.
You know what,
I think I can handle
this by now.
Well, it's no
problem at all,
ma'am.
Don't you call me ma'am.
What?
We can try to
get Amy back now.
We have both
time machines.
No.
Yeah, but the stuff
in the journal...
No, Wyatt.
I've thought a lot about this.
Look at all the awful things
that Flynn did
in the name
of saving his family.
Look what happened
when you got Jessica back.
I mean, I am so thankful
that we saved Rufus,
but it cost us Flynn.
And if we're willing to use
this machine to get back
the things that we've lost,
no matter the price,
I mean...
When will it end?
We'd be no better
than my mother or Emma.
You sure you're
okay with that?
Of course not.
But everybody loses
someone that they love,
and no matter how badly
they want to,
they can't get them back.
And in spite of that,
they find a way to go on.
That's everyone's history.
All right. Well...
Jiya said auto-pilot, right?
All right.
Looks like we'll be home
for Christmas after all.
We did it.
You did it.
I knew I could do it.
You were scared
out of your mind.
I was mildly anxious.
You did it anyway.
So much fun.
You flew the Mothership!
Too bad it's being
destroyed as we speak.
Maybe we haven't
changed so much after all.
I am so glad
to hear you say that.
So, what now?
What now, what?
Well, we're gonna have
to get new jobs.
I guess so.
Yeah, can't exactly put
"time travel" on my resume.
Mmm.
You get to see
your family again.
They think I died in the
explosion at Mason Industries.
I'm making more
comebacks than Elvis.
You have practice.
Guess I'll finally have
to get my own place.
I guess so.
Still it was a lot of fun
living together, right?
Eh, it had its moments.
Gonna miss it, sort of.
Is this your awkward way
of asking to move in with me?
Way to take a hint, lady.
So, is that a yes?
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
That's a yes, that's a yes.
That's a yes. It'll work.
Hey. Listen to this.
Yeah.
Young-Hee died in 2007.
She lived well into her 80s.
Tae-Woo's a retired
investment banker
in Seoul.
Their daughter is a teacher,
just like their mother.
Two kids.
Wow.
Sounds like a crazy,
ordinary, wonderful life.
Thanks to you.
No.
That was your call.
You're the one who said
everyone's important.
Maybe not to history,
but everybody is important
to someone, I think.
Careful.
How'd that get there?
Apparently, Agent Christopher
has a dirtier mind
than we thought.
I mean, it is a custom.
Mmm.
All right?
Mmm!
That's the first time
we've done that
in the present.
I mean, our present.
I mean, 2018.
Hmm.
Well, it's gonna
be 2019 soon.
True.
So maybe we should...
Make up for lost time?
This one is for you.
Uh, okay.
This one for you.
Thank you.
This one is for you.
Hmm!
Oh.
And there you go.
Wow. You shouldn't
have, really.
Really shouldn't have.
JIYA: It's the thought
that counts.
And the thought
was what exactly?
Hey!
Uh...
It's lovely.
Guys...
We did it.
We stopped Rittenhouse.
We won.
Cheers.
RUFUS AND JIYA: Cheers.
Flynn would be proud.
Yes, he would have.
So, was this our
last morning together?
You know, as a family?
Yep. As of 0900 hours,
you are all free to go.
Except for you.
The paperwork came through.
You're officially assigned
to Special Projects with me.
No one I'd rather report to.
You look bloody ridiculous.
My children compete to find me
the ugliest Christmas sweater.
And Mark won.
I wear it with pride.
Well, at least take
that bloody thing
off your head.
You look like some
sort of drunk elf.
You get a lump of coal
in your stocking or what?
No, just this.
What's that?
All that's left
of the Mothership.
I'm sorry, Connor.
Oh... Don't be.
There's one thing I've learnt.
A machine that powerful is too
dangerous in anyone's hands.
Now, I suppose, we need to
disassemble the Lifeboat.
We're keeping the Lifeboat.
A wise man once told me
that if it's possible
to build a time machine,
someone will build it,
and we'll need
a way to stop them.
So the Lifeboat stays here,
under armed guard.
Uh, Professor Preston?
Yeah.
So, you're saying
that without Alice Paul,
Grace Humiston is just
a detective in New York?
That's right.
How do you know?
Trust me, I know.
Okay.
Hey, have a happy holiday
and don't forget to review
the Harriet Tubman material,
all right?
Okay. Bye.
Okay. See you soon.
Bye, Tegan. Yeah?
Hey.
This was supposed
to be a regular
American History class.
How come we're
only studying women?
I meant to get to the men,
but we just didn't have time.
Maybe in the spring, okay?
Merry Christmas.
Bye.
No, no, no!
Oh, God!
Give me, give me,
yeah, give me!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Back to basic training for me.
Hello!
Mommy!
What are you torturing Daddy
with this time, huh?
Boot camp.
Boot camp?
I hope you didn't
go too easy on him.
Guess what?
What?
I got tenure.
I am so proud of you.
Thank you.
Flynn! Amy! You ready to go?
Come on.
Come over here.
Give me your hand. All right.
You ready for this?
Ready as I'll ever be.
We were hoping to get a better
facility, but funding was even
shorter than usual.
We all started somewhere.
When Rufus and I started
Riya Industries, I wanted
to build a better future.
Rufus,
all about giving back
to the community.
He was just
like these kids once.
It's called a Leyden jar,
and it was actually
the first capacitor.
Yeah, I've seen one
of these before, but
yours is definitely better.
Hey, guys.
Could I
have your autograph?
Yeah, sure.
Thank you.
How come nobody
asks for my autograph?
'Cause you wanted to be
the mysterious one
behind the scenes.
Ah.
Mmm.
You know,
I think it's about
time to, uh, do the...
Rufus Carlin,
if anything happens to you...
Hey, I am the guy
that came back from the dead.
You're never gonna
stop saying that, are you?
Yeah. No, why would I?
The twins are
in their pajamas,
and they are brushing
their teeth.
They're so excited
about their sleepover.
When I told them that Mommy
and Daddy used to live here,
they didn't believe me.
That's because, like most
government-funded housing,
it's utterly uninhabitable
and always was.
Says the man
under federal
contract, right?
Well, it turns out
I liked, uh, saving the world
more than I liked
saving money.
So, you ever miss
saving the world?
Sometimes.
Then I think
about North Korea.
French and Indian War.
The Murder Castle.
Al Capone
trying to kill us.
Benedict Arnold.
Confederate slave owners.
Nazis.
Ready to do it one more time?
We have to,
or all of this
could disappear.
Hey, anybody need a pilot?
No!
Hey!
Hi.
You didn't tell me
he was coming.
Think we'd let
you do it alone?
Yeah. Three of us started it,
so let's finish it.
Okay, but if
anything goes wrong...
It won't.
We get in and we get out.
We got this, Lucy.
Is this seat taken?
Nao falo ingles.
I know you speak
English, Flynn.
Don't worry, I'm a friend.
I mean, I will be a friend.
What do you want?
I don't have a lot of time.
I know about Rittenhouse.
I know what they did
to your wife Lorena,
and your daughter Iris.
Who are you?
Shh!
My name is Lucy Preston.
I'm from the year 2023,
and I know this is
going to sound crazy,
but some day, you and I
are going to work together.
My God!
The time machine!
Connor Mason actually
built it? I knew it!
You were right.
You were right
about everything.
More than you will ever know.
But you...
Okay, look...
You are going to
have to sacrifice
everything for a cause
that almost no one
will believe in.
The world will think
that you're a terrorist
and a traitor.
Even I'm going to think
that at first, but...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, listen to me.
But you aren't
any of those things.
And you're going to think
that you lost your humanity,
but you didn't.
And you never will.
What about my family?
You won't
get them back. I'm sorry.
You're a hero, I promise.
Maybe the greatest
hero of us all.
But you're going to need
my help, okay? So...
You okay?
Here, take this.
You are going to save history.
If you're lost
You can look
and you will find me
Time after time
If you fall
I will catch you
I'll be waiting
Time after time
You say, go slow
I fall behind
If you're lost
You can look
and you will find me
Time after time
If you fall
I will catch you
I'll be waiting
Time after time
I'm always waiting
Paulina! Dinner!
Okay.
Hey! Dinner. Now.
You're working too much.
Okay, I'll be right there.