(moaning)
(thunder rumbling)
(rain pattering)
(muffled laughing)
(wooing)
(hip hop music)
(muffled chattering)
♪ Here we go ♪
♪ Here we are, here we go ♪
- [Man] Raise it up.
Easy.
(muffled shouting)
- Watch it.
- Over here.
- [Man] Steady it.
(muffled talking)
(rain pattering)
(dramatic music)
(thunder rumbling)
(muffled talking on police radio)
(chattering)
- [Reporter] Captain Swaggert can you
give us a statement please?
- Not now.
- [Reporter] Can you tell
us what you found here?
- Do you want to move the
line back a ways Captain?
- [Swaggert] Can't make 'em go away Jimmy.
- [Jimmy] I'd just as
soon turn a hose on 'em.
- [Swaggert] No need for
that tonight is there?
- Captain.
- Sam what do you got?
- [Sam] We've checked with every
hospital and lab in the area.
There ain't no record of any
dumping or disposal like this.
- [Swaggert] Who found it?
- [Sam] A couple of kids
sportsing around near the pipe.
- Well don't let 'em get away
before we get a chance to interview 'em.
- Yep.
- Thank you, Sam.
Morning gentlemen.
- Howdy Captain.
Must be serious when
they get you out of bed.
(suspenseful music)
- Did all of these come
out of that same bag?
- Yes sir, all but the one the kids found.
- So it wasn't sealed up?
- Not quite.
- Jimmy you better call my home,
tell Helen I probably
won't get back before dawn.
(ominous music)
- [Man On Radio] It looks
like we can expect more rain
for the rest of the day and things
will be cleared up by late tonight.
So don't forget your
umbrellas on the way out.
Looks like the forecast for tomorrow,
it's partly cloudy skies
and clearing hot and humid.
Temperatures should be up
in the 90s. (chuckling)
Sounds like a good day to stay inside
with the air conditioner on.
- Hey Jim.
- Morning Captain.
- Morning boys.
Belvin.
- Sir?
- I want the whole forensics
team in here this morning.
- Well Vince just got back
from the examiner's office.
He's gonna hold the night shift over
until Frankie and Scolia get down.
- Good deal.
Foot, I want you to
coordinate two diver teams
on standby and make sure damn they know
what they're getting into down there.
- Yes sir.
Six feet of rapidly moving excrement.
(chuckling)
(phone ringing)
- Get that for me would you?
- What if this rain keeps up Captain?
- [Belvin] Well we're gonna
have to start building an ark.
- Yeah but who do we put on it?
- All the white people.
- It's Pete Sweeny, channel six.
He wants to know about
the numbers on the hands.
- Well you tell him they have to wait
for a press release like everyone else.
- Did you hear that Pete?
Yeah just call back later.
- What else did he want?
- Just smelling around for more news.
- Speaking of news, I got
an announcement for you.
The assistance chief has called in
an outside profiler on this one.
- What FBI?
- No, state crime division.
- Lesser of two evils.
- She'll be coming in here sometime today.
- Whoa, she?
- Special investigator Audrey L. Macleah,
all the way from Austin.
- And what's so special about her?
- Oh, she's a state trooper man.
You know what it takes
to crack that boys' club?
- Yeah, you gotta have
a mustache and no neck.
- You mean she looks just like you.
(chuckling)
- What's she gonna do around here anyway,
except look over our shoulder?
- She's gonna save us from ourselves.
- Suspect profiling, computer modeling,
victimology, databased
analysis, forensics,
trace evidence, chemical
evidence retrieval,
blood pattern analysis.
Y'all want to hear more?
- Yeah, but can she tie her own shoelaces?
- Sounds like she don't have the time.
- Sounds like she wears boots.
(laughing)
(knocking)
Come in.
- Captain Swaggert?
- Yeah.
- I'm investigator Macleah.
- You boys get out of here,
I got some work to do.
Nice to meet you Miss Macleah.
- Nice to meet you.
- May I help you with your bags?
- Oh no, that's okay, I got it.
I know I'm running a
little behind schedule.
I was going to rent a
car, but they didn't have
the model that I wanted
so I took a cab instead.
Which actually probably
saved me a lot of time
since the traffic out there only seems
to be getting worsened.
Cab drivers usually know of shortcuts,
but I think this guy took the long way.
It was okay.
I'll pick up a car later
when we're done here.
- Do you want some coffee or something?
- Do you have any tea?
- Tea?
- Yes, earl gray, Twinings,
english breakfast?
- Have a seat will you?
- Oh, thank you.
- Darlene could you fix a cup of tea
and bring it to my office please?
- [Darlene] Did you say tea Captain?
- [Swaggert] Yes I did,
don't you have any?
- [Darlene] I think we have Lipton's.
- How's Lipton's?
- Oh that's fine.
- That's fine Darlene, thank you.
(clearing throat)
So how long have you worked
for the state division?
- A little over four years.
- And how do you like it?
- I like it very much.
Is it alright if I smoke?
- Be my guest.
- Would you care for one?
- No thanks, I quit.
- I'm working on it.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- And I understand that
your specialty is profiling?
- Yes sir.
Actually we have to call it
suspect analysis these days
because of the big flack with
psychiatrists a year or so back.
I guess they thought we were
encroaching on their turf.
Interesting how a single word can be
that threatening to an entire occupation.
- And you use computers quite a lot?
- Yes sir, we take a victimology matrix
and superimpose it over
a hypothetical framework.
A suspect behavior constructed
on a computer database
and then we look for intersecting
modes to reinforce the model.
(laughing)
If you would like I could have
the Austin office fax you my resume.
- They already did.
(clearing throat)
So you were a year with
the FBI in Quantico.
- Yes, profiling, victimology
classes, that sort of thing.
- And three years on the road?
- Mm-hm.
- What was that like?
- Slow, but it was the only way
to get to where I am now so.
- Bachelors in political
science, med school,
masters in psychology.
- I guess when I was younger
I thought I was gonna save the world.
Another Albert Schweitzer
or something like that.
- What made you change your mind?
- I didn't like the pain
that I saw everywhere.
Actually I suppose that's
what got me into this,
but I didn't want that
kind of responsibility.
- What kind of responsibility is that?
- Healing.
- [Swaggert] Tell me did your
office brief you on this case?
- No sir, they told me
that you would do that.
- Why don't we take a walk down the hall?
(unsettling music)
- Now we have several specimens.
Four right, three left, one likely pair.
According to the numbers in the palms
we have a broken series from two to 13.
- What is the age range of the victims?
- Well we haven't run any tests yet,
but judging from the size they're young.
- Very young.
- Looks that way.
(camera shutter snapping)
Subcutaneous, fascia, veins,
arteries, musculature,
all severed cleanly
with a very sharp blade.
This is not some gorilla
with a meat clever.
- This is Sergeant Footman.
- Morning.
- Sergeant Belvin.
- Howdy.
- There's Lieutenant Creedmore.
Jimmy's my right hand man.
There's Vince from forensics,
y'all have already met.
This is Sergeant Delarand.
The sergeant is our
resident computer guru.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- You may sit over there Miss Macleah.
Alberto, would you kindly
pull those shades for me?
- I'll get these here.
- Thank you Footman.
Also turn off the lights if you would.
(clearing throat)
Now then I know I don't have to say this,
but just for the record I don't want you
talking with your family
or friends about this case
or with anyone outside the department
staff assigned to the case.
As you well know there's
a whole lot of anxiety
in the community, people
are scared as hell.
So just keep your mouth shut.
- Each victim was Caucasian.
There are no blemishes
and no malformations
and no birth marks.
Now the numbers have been
tattooed on with imperishable ink.
And we found traces of formalin
in each of the specimens.
Now that would explain why
they're so well preserved.
Now these tiny punctures you see here
and here all the way around.
Those are suture marks
and each specimen has them
which would suggest they've all
been severed and reattached.
- What about age Vince?
- Well there does seem
to be a relationship
between the numbers on the palms
and the probable age of the victim.
- [Belvin] So the lower the
number the younger the victim?
- That's right.
I'm guessing we're looking
at about five years of age
for the smallest specimen
and about 10 to 12 for the largest.
- Excuse me.
- Miss Macleah?
- Yes, I have a question.
I was just wondering about what efforts
were made to identify the victims?
- Well we fingerprinted
each one of the specimens
of course, but if the hands
all come from children
it's not likely we're gonna get
a match doing an optical bank.
- We requested birth certificates
for local missing children,
but there's no fast way to
match out the hand prints.
It'll probably take weeks to
get through what comes in.
- Well what about DNA fingerprinting?
- Well what would be the point?
We don't have any samples to match to.
- Well what about the
parents of missing children?
- We've already pulLed the national
MP list into our database.
That's over 2,000 names.
- And each one of those would
have to be cross indexed one at a time.
The only rapid search we
could run is our local list.
- So why not take samples from that?
- We don't know yet if the
victims are only local.
- And we'd have the families
of every missing persons case
from the last 10 years
down here on our backs.
- Not if you reduce the list of candidates
to those matching the
specimens for age and gender.
- Miss Macleah you are talking
about contacting parents
who are wondering if their
children are still alive
and asking them to come
down here for a blood test.
They're gonna want to know why?
What do we tell them?
- We tell them that we have remains
which need to be identified.
- They already know about the hands.
- See it really doesn't
matter what we tell them
after we make that call
because they're gonna be
so frightened that it is their child
they're not gonna be able
to think of anything else
and if you multiply that
fear by several hundred
we would have a situation here
that we could hardly control.
- Well it seems to me that
you don't have a crime scene
and you don't have any
identifiable remains
unless you make some assumptions.
Now in order to go forward and profile
a suspect you need a victimology.
I mean without that as a base
you really don't have anything do you?
- Yes, well now that the rain has let up
I expect we're gonna find the
rest of the victims' remains
in the sewers in the next few days
and that is our top priority right now.
- Yes, but if all the victims' remains
were thrown into the sewer
pipe at the same time
they can be scattered
all over the city by now
and why would the hands be placed in bag?
Maybe because the hands were
dumped separately from the bodies.
Maybe the bodies were
dumped somewhere else.
I mean what if those remains are
miles away in another sewer pipe?
- We won't know that unless
we look for them will we?
- Would you close that door please?
Y'all come on a little
stormy in there didn't you?
- I was just speaking my mind sir.
- Well I guess this being
your first day and all
you're just a little too wound up huh?
- Not anymore than usual, no.
- Alright then.
In the future if you have
something to say about a directive
I would appreciate if you
would just say it and drop it.
Don't turn it into a contest, alright?
- Yes sir.
- Good deal.
We got this call this
morning from a doctor
who wants to talk to someone
in person about this case.
Now I want to send you out on this
because frankly I don't have anything else
for you to do around here.
You got a problem with that?
- No sir.
- Alright.
Do you know where the state
psychiatric hospital is?
(train whistle blowing)
(crossing bell dinging)
(muffled talking on loudspeaker)
- Can you tell me where
Dr. Singer's office is?
Thank you.
- Dr. Willis, line two.
(phone ringing)
Dr. Willis, line two please.
(chattering)
Dr. Singer?
- Yes.
- I'm investigator Macleah.
I'm working with the Houston police.
- I'm a little surprised.
I didn't expect someone so quickly.
- You did ask to speak to the police?
- Yes, but I've been hesitant about this
because of case confidentiality.
Because there's no way to fully explain
the situation on the phone.
I need an answer to a question.
- Go ahead.
- The hands that you found.
- Mm-hm?
- The police said that there
were numbers on the palms?
- That's correct.
- Are these numbers in
a series from one to 18?
(unsettling music)
We have a young boy in seclusion
who's been here since he
was four or five years old.
He was passed from the adoption agency
to the state foster program
and well then to us.
He has seizure states
which are very violent.
And one of the traits is
bleeding from the wrist
all way around like an incision.
At first we thought
they were self induced,
but we searched his cell
and we've never been able to find anything
that could create such a wound.
Watch your step please.
For some years now along with the seizures
he's been drawing hands on
the wall of his cell in pairs.
And each new pair of hands that he draws
has a different pair of numbers.
Good morning Danny.
Would you let us in please?
- How many patients are down here?
- Just one.
Thank you.
Right this way.
(suspenseful music)
This used to be our isolation ward.
When we built a new wing we
moved most of the patients out.
- Why is he still down here?
- This is his home.
This way.
Good morning Jordan.
You have a special visitor this morning.
She came just to meet you.
Danny.
This is Miss Macleah.
- Nice to meet you Jordan.
I would like to take a
few photos if I might?
- Sure.
(camera shutter snapping)
- Thank you.
- Danny why don't you take Jordan
to get a clean set of greens.
- [Danny] Okay.
- Where are the hands drawn?
- Here.
(unsettling music)
Did all of them appear at once?
- He's drawn them a pair at a
time over the last 10 years.
We repainted the cell once
but he just scratched them back in again.
- They were drawn in sequential order?
- Yeah.
Each pair was drawn on
the same date each year,
July 16th, his birthday.
- Has he ever been released?
- Not since he was admitted.
- And when was that?
- About 10 years ago.
- Has he ever spoken to
you about these drawings?
- He hasn't spoken since he's been here.
He was diagnosed as an elective mute
when he was five or six years old.
(unsettling music)
(electronic buzzing)
(Jordan humming musically)
- Good morning Jordan.
Jordan I'd like to talk to you
about the drawings on the wall.
I'd like to find out more about them.
I brought some crayons and some paper
and I thought that maybe
if I had a question
you could write down your answers for me?
How does that sound?
(farting)
(screaming)
- He don't like anybody
to touch his doll ma'am.
- Could you leave the room for a moment?
(grunting)
Let's stop pretending for a moment okay?
We both know that you're not stupid.
Now I don't know if you
drew these hands or not,
but if you did you must have a reason
and I would like to know
what that reason is.
I see.
She does all the talking, huh?
Goodbye Jordan.
(door thudding closed)
(horn honking)
(suspenseful music)
(muffled talking on police radio)
- [Man] All clear here,
no sighting so far.
- Go back to that other half.
Little more.
Good.
Easy now, very easy.
- Excuse me, Captain Swaggert.
- Good.
- Morning Miss Macleah.
- Morning.
- [Man] I think we might have something.
(suspenseful music)
- How deep is the water there?
- [Man] Good money says about 10 feet.
Park it right there for a minute.
- May I speak with you for a moment?
- Sure thing.
Alright boys we're coming
in to see what you found.
- [Man] Alright, bring it up.
That's it, that's it, easy now.
- I've been looking over the medical files
for Jordan Thomas, the boy I told
you about from the hospital.
Now his birthday is July 16th,
this is the same date every
year that he has these seizures.
It's also the same date
he draws the hands.
- So what's that got to do with this case?
- Well seven disappearances over
the last nine years fall on July 16th.
Now if you put them into
a series starting 1984
you get a victim set which matches
the specimens for age and gender.
Seven names could be the victims.
Now what I would like to do is
spend more time with the boy.
I think he may be able to help us.
- Well look if you got
a list of names to go on
why don't you focus on that
'cause I need a profile as
fast as you can build one.
- Yeah I know that sir, but
the names are only speculative.
There's no positive ID.
There's no certainty unless
you're able to find something down here.
(suspenseful dramatic music)
- Hey are you alright?
- Yeah, I'm a little dizzy that's all.
I think I need to get some air.
- Alright, I better walk you back.
- No, just give me some room.
I'll be fine.
- Let me help you.
- Don't touch me please.
I'm fine.
I'm alright.
I have a little trouble in
closed spaces that's all.
I'm okay.
- I understand.
Just take it easy now.
- I'm fine.
- [Jimmy On Radio] Captain?
- What is it Jimmy?
- [Jimmy On Radio] It's a false alarm.
They pulled up a mannequin.
- [Swaggert] Say again?
- [Jimmy On Radio] They
netted a goddamn mannequin.
- 10 four.
(muffled talking)
(dramatic suspenseful music)
- I'd like to go in by myself.
- Yes ma'am.
(Jordan humming musically)
- Good morning Jordan.
That's a very pretty song,
did somebody teach you that?
(Jordan humming musically)
I thought that maybe we could start again.
Cute.
Are you enjoying yourself?
Alright you can stop
it now, it's not funny.
Listen to me, this is not a game.
Look, I need your help.
I need you tell me why you
keep drawing these hands.
I don't want to play anymore
games, do you understand me?
Do you understand me?
(growling)
Ouch!
We're fine.
If you ever do that
again I'll bite you back.
So you can write, huh?
Again.
Well if this is all you have to say to me
then I guess we have
nothing to talk about do we?
You want to keep it,
is that what you want?
If you want to keep it write it down.
Write it down.
Good.
It's a start.
(suspenseful music)
- This is Deanne Alberti, age five,
at the time of her disappearance
July 16, 1984 from Twin Pines Park.
This is Susan Lewins, age seven
at the time of her disappearance,
July 16, 1986 from Peace Park.
This is Janie Monahan,
age nine at the time of her disappearance,
July 16, 1989 from Lakeview Park.
Mary Klugman, age 10 at the
time of her disappearance,
July 16, 1990 from Eastwood Park.
All four of these children were identified
by DNA paternity tests.
Bill.
- Captain.
Now, all four IDed victims
were found in different parks.
All four of these parks are
in upscale parts of town
where the patrol watch is above normal.
All four victims were
abducted in broad daylight,
in front of family members
or friends, or both.
- It means our man is one slippery mother.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me, I have a question.
- Miss Macleah.
- We are obviously dealing with someone
who is very intelligent
and very methodical.
He must've received some
formal medical training
so he's highly educated as well.
He's also willing to take great risks,
but he reduces the risk
by choosing his location
in advance along with his victims.
I mean he can't arbitrarily
be choosing different parks
for each of his abductions
and his victims fit a very strong pattern
so he has to seek them out individually
so that nothing is left to chance.
Now the date of significance
to the killer is July 16th.
It's part of his behavioral pattern,
but the last abduction
that fits this pattern
was Mary Klugman, which
was three years ago.
- Uh-huh.
And what is your question Miss Macleah?
- Well it would seem that he
has either become inactive
or he's changed his
pattern which could mean
a whole new set of locations and dates
and maybe even a new type of victim.
I mean he could be evolving
in ways we know nothing about.
- Maybe he just got spooked, you know?
And he just went looking in a
different neighborhood for his kids.
I mean if he is as smart as you say he is
then he knew that he was pushing his luck
with seven kids in seven years.
- You found the hands eight days ago.
Today is the 12th.
For him to dump those
hands so close to the 16th.
I mean that cannot be a coincidence.
I mean it's gotta be
some kind of a signal.
- Maybe he's about to return
to his old hunting ground.
- Maybe we should just take
his hunting ground away.
(birds chirping)
(swings squeaking)
- I know that this is very
difficult for you Mrs. Klugman,
but I need to ask you about that day,
about what you can remember.
- Do you have any children Miss?
- No.
- It's like your whole world just stops.
Just comes to an end.
- How many times do we have
to tell this story to people?
I mean what is it, you
come into our house,
you ask us the same questions
and you write down the same answers.
You just throw that away?
- I'm sorry that this is so hard for you.
- Oh you're sorry?
I want to know why that
thing's still out there
just taking kids off the street.
Why haven't you found him, huh?
Can you tell me that?
Just answer me that question.
- It's alright Martin.
If it'll help then I want to do it.
- Thank you.
- She was just playing with
a group of friends, neighbor kids.
- Do you remember if there were
any adults nearby close to your daughter?
- The park was really crowded that day.
No.
No, she was just with her friends.
Three other kids, I knew them all.
And there were two other
mothers on a bench close to me.
I was taking care of my
neighbor's two little boys
and one of them needed
to go to the bathroom
so I took both of them.
- How far away was your
daughter from the bathroom?
- Maybe, I don't know, about 100 feet.
I'm not sure, maybe a little bit more.
- So did you go inside the
bathroom once you got there?
- Yes.
I helped both the boys.
They were both very young.
But I could see them from the bathroom.
- [Audrey] And how long were
you inside the bathroom?
- Not very long.
10 minutes.
Maybe a little bit longer.
- Do you remember any
sounds from the park?
- Just the sound of children playing
and there might've been a radio playing
or something like that.
I don't even know how I heard it.
And then I walked out with the boys
and all the kids were there, but Mary.
Nobody even seemed to notice she was gone.
And the kids were all playing
like nothing had happened.
They were just laughing.
(dramatic music)
- Yeah.
(chuckling)
- And the bear says you don't just
come here for the hunting do you?
(laughing)
I told you.
It's your joke.
- Excuse me.
Does anybody know what this is all about?
I found it in the reserve's drawer.
- Let me see that Jimmy.
Oh yeah, this.
Yeah I looked at this
till my eyes crossed.
- Well what's on it?
- Well, a neighbor kid was in the park
earlier that day shooting home movies.
- The same park she was abducted from?
- Yes.
Hey, it's two hours of kids' feet,
back of people's heads.
Made me dizzy just watching it.
- Did anybody do a frame
by frame analysis on it?
- That was three years ago.
- Like I said, I looked at it.
So did a half dozen other people.
And now, hey, it's all yours.
- Thanks.
- Yes ma'am.
(chuckling)
(warbling slow recorded chattering)
(suspenseful music)
(ice cream truck music)
(children chattering)
(suspenseful music)
(ice cream truck music)
(phone ringing)
- Delarand.
- [Audrey On Phone] Hi,
it's Audrey Macleah.
- Hello Miss Macleah.
What can I do for you?
- I need you to do a name search
for anyone holding city permits
to sell concessions to the parks.
- Okay, no problem.
I'll do it for you first
thing in the morning.
- No, I need this done right now.
Run whatever you find through
a unit for all prior arrests.
I need as much of a profile as I can get.
- Look, this could take a while.
I need to access a half a dozen data banks
- [Audrey On Phone] Fine.
Fax it to my terminal when you're done.
- Yes ma'am.
(dramatic music)
- Looks good.
That's very good.
(train whistle blowing)
Try...
Stand up on this chair.
Come on.
Now, put this in your hand.
Hold it up to the light, higher.
Higher.
What do you see?
(laughing)
(unsettling music)
- Howard Speckett this
is the Houston police.
We have a warrant to search the premises.
Open the door.
- Let's move.
- Move, go, go.
(muffled talking on police radio)
- [Man] Go.
- Captain.
- [Man] Bedroom's clear back here sir.
- [Man] Bathroom's clear.
(unsettling music)
- I found them in the bathroom.
- Search the premises for anything
sharper than a butter knife.
- [Woman On Loudspeaker] JD,
you have a telephone call.
- He says Speckett didn't
check back in last night.
He's been driving a substitute van
until his regular van is fixed.
- Where's it being fixed?
- It hasn't bene.
It's right down there at the end.
- [Swaggert] Alright, have Belvin
and Foot to check it out, will you?
(ice cream truck music)
(inhaler air whooshing)
(deep breathing)
(suspenseful music)
- Howard Speckett.
(shouting)
(glass shattering)
Shit.
(suspenseful music)
- Over here boys!
You alright?
- Yeah, I couldn't see him.
It's too dark in here.
- Brady, move your units
around the complex.
Looks like our boy
slipped through us here.
(sirens blaring)
(gasping)
- [Officer] Freeze!
Freeze dammit!
(gun firing)
- Ow, ow.
- Stay right there.
Show us your hands.
We got him.
- [Howard] Jesus.
- Spread 'em.
(children chattering)
(ice cream truck music)
(Jordan humming musically on recording)
- Jordan can you hear me?
Good.
Now I want you take a big deep breath.
Now we're gonna play a game Jordan.
Would you like that?
Okay.
I'm gonna ask you some questions
and I want you to write your
answers down on the paper okay?
Okay.
Now we'll start with a very easy question.
I want you to tell me your name.
Jennifer Lynn.
Well that's a very pretty name.
Did Jordan go away?
(dog panting)
- Hello?
Hello?
Is anyone in there?
- Then where are you now?
Under the ground.
Is anyone else in your room with you?
Sometimes.
Who else is in your room
with your sometimes?
Daddy.
Is Daddy in your room with you now?
(suspenseful music)
- Hello?
- Jordan I see hands all together.
Are these hands in your room?
Are there hands in your room?
Daddy gives them to you?
Why does Daddy give you the hands?
So you can play.
(rock music on headphones)
(dog barking)
Can you draw a picture of Daddy for me?
(suspenseful music)
(dog barking)
(rock music on headphones)
And how does Daddy give you the hands?
He makes them?
(dog barking)
(rock music on headphones)
How does Daddy make the hands?
(whimpering)
It's alright Jordan.
(dog barking)
(suspenseful music)
No, no, no.
(grunting)
Hey!
(muffled screaming)
Jordan.
(screaming)
It's alright, come on.
No, Jordan, Jordan, look,
I'm gonna count to three and when I count
to three you're gonna be calm and safe.
One, two, three.
It's alright, it's alright.
(crying)
It's alright.
(dog barking)
Go to sleep.
I'll come back tomorrow, okay?
Jordan I'll come back tomorrow, I promise.
I promise I'll come back tomorrow Jordan.
- Help me.
Help me.
- I know what it's like to be alone.
To be pushed away.
Locked into the darkness
with all that pain and fear.
It's like a terrible secret.
I won't let anyone hurt
you anymore Jordan, okay?
Go to sleep.
(dramatic music)
(train horn whistling)
(suspenseful music)
(phone ringing)
Hello?
- Miss Macleah, it's Delarand.
- What time is it?
- Time for me to get out of here.
I got some data for you.
- Alright, go ahead.
- With first and last name I have three
Jennifer Lynns listed
within the metro area.
As last and first I have none.
As first and middle I have one,
but according to public
record she's deceased.
- What's the date of death?
- July 16th, 1979.
- You want to spell the last name for me?
- Jennifer Lynn Eben, E-B-E-N.
- And where did she die?
- Lakewood Hospital.
But they've been closed for over 10 years.
(suspenseful music)
- I haven't been down
here, but once or twice
since they closed it
down and then it was only
to pull out a couple of old beds.
Now be careful there's
all this crap around.
(snoring)
(tense dramatic music)
(unsettling music)
(birds chirping)
(doorbell ringing)
- Yes?
- I'm Investigator Macleah.
I'm working with the Huston police.
Is Dr. Eben at home?
- No I'm sorry, but he's away on vacation.
- Do you know when he'll return?
- Not for another five or six days.
I hope there isn't any trouble.
- Oh no, not at all.
You are?
- I'm Mrs. Voss, the housekeeper.
- Mrs. Voss would you mind
if I came in for a moment?
I would like to ask you a few questions.
- Well, yes, I suppose.
- Great, thank you.
(dog yapping)
- Could I get your something to drink?
- Just some water please.
- Won't you sit down?
- Thank you.
(off kilter music)
(dog wheezing)
- Here we are.
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Are these pictures of Mrs. Eben?
- Yes.
She's lovely isn't she?
She passed on some years back.
Oh here's my lady.
I never knew the woman, but I hear that
she was a great musician,
a concert pianist.
- Do you know where Dr.
Eben's gone on vacation?
- Oh no, he keeps his plans to himself.
Well, he checks in every now and then,
but he always likes to be left alone.
- So he doesn't tell you where he goes?
- No.
I'm sorry.
- Oh.
Does he take his daughter
with him on his trips?
- You mean Jenny?
I don't know.
Of course he visits her
quite often I suppose.
- Visits her?
- [Voss] She's away at a
private school in Europe.
A very fine school for girls.
- You know I didn't notice
any pictures of Jenny.
I wonder if you have a photo
that I might be able to look at?
- Why yes of course.
Let's see.
Of course I didn't know her myself,
but she's a lovely girl.
Oh here we are.
This is a fine picture.
Isn't she a pretty girl.
She looks just like her mother.
- And where was this taken?
- I don't really know.
- The date on this is 1962.
- Oh.
Well it is isn't it?
Well then this must be
a picture of Mrs. Eben
and the house she grew up in as a girl.
- Yes, could I speak to
Captain Swaggert please?
This is Audrey Macleah.
Well could you get him on dispatch for me?
(suspenseful music)
(horn honking)
(tires squealing)
(eerie music)
(dogs barking)
(wind chimes ringing)
(knocking on door)
(suspenseful music)
(glass shattering)
(eerie music)
(thudding)
(groaning)
(suspenseful music)
(whimpering)
Oh my god.
It's okay, it's okay.
I tell you it's okay.
It's okay, no, no, no, no.
I'm here to help you.
Shh, shh, I need you to be calm alright?
No, shh, I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm gonna help you okay?
I'm gonna take this off your eyes.
I need you stay calm, alright?
It's okay, look at me, look at me.
I'm a police officer,
I'm gonna help you, okay?
I'm gonna take this off your mouth
and I want you to be very very quiet
and nod you'll be very quiet okay?
Okay, okay.
It's okay.
I'll get your hands.
Okay.
And then we're just going
to walk out of here okay?
Walk right out of here, alright?
Shh, don't be scared.
(crying)
No, no, it's okay.
Don't, shh.
(crying)
Shh, shh.
I want you to be quiet.
Shh, it's okay, it's okay, okay?
Be very very quiet.
I'm here with you.
I want you to stay right here.
Just stay right okay?
Don't say anything.
Okay?
(suspenseful music)
Jenny?
It's okay.
I'm gonna help you.
Don't move.
Shit.
(groaning)
Oh, shit.
(banging)
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm gonna help you now.
We're gonna go outside okay?
We're gonna go together.
(banging)
Ouch.
(door thudding)
(floor above creaking)
(crying)
Shh, shh.
It's okay, it's okay.
(crying)
Shh, shh.
Shh, you have to be quiet.
You have to be quiet.
I know you want to go home.
I'm gonna get you home, but
I need you to be quiet okay?
Nod your head you'll be quiet.
Alright stay here.
Shh.
(chuckling)
(applauding)
- And how's my little girl today?
Your Daddy brought you a special surprise.
Happy birthday my pet.
(chuckling)
Now it's time for you to
play a song for your daddy.
(dissonant piano music)
(crying)
(suspenseful music)
(door creaking)
(gasping)
(suspenseful music)
And who would you be?
I asked you a question.
(clanging)
(crying)
Don't be afraid.
I won't hurt you.
Look at you.
You're shaking like a leaf.
Let me see your hand.
Let me see it.
- Fuck you.
- That's not what I had in mind.
(thumping)
(groaning)
(yelling)
(glass shattering)
(grunting)
(screaming)
(groaning)
(clanging)
(screaming)
- Put your arms around my neck.
Good girl, good girl, good girl.
(banging)
Here we go, here we go.
(shouting)
(banging)
Right here.
(shouting)
(banging)
Stand there.
Okay.
(banging)
(shouting)
Okay, okay.
(banging)
(shouting)
Oh shit.
(banging)
(shouting)
Now, there we go.
(yelling)
(banging)
(shouting)
(suspenseful music)
(groaning)
- Jenny.
(gun clicking)
- Oh shit.
- Jenny.
(crying)
(dramatic music)
(shouting)
(gun cocking)
(gun firing)
(groaning)
(piano dissonantly reverberating)
(gasping)
(wind chimes tinkling)
(muffled talking on police radio)
(dramatic music)