Ready.
Gloria Swanson.
Maurice Chevalier.
Ralph Bellamy.
Lon Chaney.
Phillips Lord.
One of my favorites. Humphrey Bogart.
Here's an actress. Snow White.
Ann Miller.
Jean Harlow.
Blank.
Rex Harrison.
Burgess Meredith.
Ray Bolger.
Blank.
Steve McQueen.
Danny Kaye.
Sarah Vaughan.
Jimmy Stewart.
Victor Mature.
Edward G. Robinson.
Blank.
Dinah Shore.
Adolphe Menjou.
Erich Von Stroheim.
Tom Mix.
Rory Calhoun.
Henry Fonda.
Burt Lancaster.
This one, if l had a hat, l'd tip it.
John Ford.
Betty Grable.
Little Richard.
Jimmy Cagney.
Blank.
Van Heflin.
"Richard Widmark."
Richard Widmark. Shit!
That was pretty good, though.
Richard Widmark.
How could l not get that one?
Yeah. How many was that?
-What?
-How many, William?
l thought you were going to count.
How could l be counting?
l'm thinking of names.
Come on, William. l depend on you.
This is important to me.
l think this was my personal best.
l don't ever remember
doing this well before.
This was definitely a better run
than my Debbie Reynolds one.
Debbie Reynolds one?
Now we gotta go back and count.
l gotta count all the stars again.
l can't believe you did this to me.
l can't believe you did it.
Come on. Let's go. We're to count them.
One, two
You don't remember where l started at all?
Think. Maybe if you see it. Three.
How many was that?
What? Five?
How many did we just do?
One, two, three, four, five.
Here we go.
You look good.
Very, very good. Very compelling.
Catches your eye, don't you think?
lf you were riding by, it catches your eye?
Don't forget, this is a big traffic flow area.
A lot of people passing by are seeing this.
Big traffic flow.
You look good. Very, very good.
Very, very compelling.
Sometimes you just got
to invest in your future, you know.
You got to step up and invest.
They did a beautiful job with the artwork.
lt really catches your eye.
Definitely worth the money.
l should probably have a fax or two waiting
by the time we get home, right?
What do you think?
Yeah.
There go the Ortegas.
ls that my phone?
No. No, it's not yours.
Hi. This is Jimmy Alto, actor extraordinaire.
l'm gonna have to get back to you.
l have a very busy schedule.
l'm on the set right now,
so please leave a message
or a fax for me. Thanks.
-Favorite movie?
-Gone with the Wind.
1 939, Selznick lnternational.
First movie you ever saw?
-The Mummy.
-Boris Karloff.
l was a young kid with my dad.
l wasn't feeling well.
My dad let me stay up
and watch Fright Night.
You know what l could
never figure out about the mummy?
The mummy used to walk with one
arm out and a leg dragging behind.
He was still always able to get his victim.
l'm thinking as a kid, "l'm pretty fast.
"Just put some moves on the mummy,
"and the mummy would never get me."
This is what you're thinking about?
Then l realize the mummy
never has to sleep.
Eventually, l'd get tired
of running around the mummy.
That's when he'd get me.
So what did you do?
Scare yourself to death
thinking you were going to sleep
and the mummy
was coming in your room at night?
This schmuck, this mummy is in Cairo.
He's got to take a plane
from Egypt to Philadelphia.
This mummy has got to get a passport,
and you're worried
he's coming in your room at night?
This mummy's got
more important things on its mind.
You know what l could
never figure out about the mummy
was how he used to walk around
with one arm out
-and a leg dragging behind him.
-William.
William, you're blanking.
Did l say that?
Trust me.
l did say that.
Watch the radio.
l got to go to the bathroom.
You see this?
We're going to make a withdrawal.
Oh, God. Of all the people,
you have to pick on me?
l make very little money.
Two hundred's not going to kill you.
Just hurry up.
Two hundred?
l never use these machines at night.
l'm always afraid.
Just shut up and get on with it.
l'm wrong. "Enter again."
Lady, don't provoke me!
Don't touch my back, please.
You make me nervous.
Don't provoke me. Just give me the money!
Wait, wait. "Processing."
"No funds?"
-What do you mean?
-l can't believe it!
l don't have any money in my account.
-All right, give me your purse.
-l don't have any money, man.
l don't have anything.
Pick it up. Pick it up!
No. lf l do, then you'll hit me in the head.
Take what you want. l don't have anything.
Put your hands down.
Okay, pick up the car keys.
Go ahead. Pick up the car keys.
Where's your car?
lt's the blue Mazda.
-Okay, come on.
-Okay, no, listen,
-if you want the car, you have the car.
-No, no, no. Understand? Gun.
-Do you speak English? Okay.
-Yes, yes, yes.
-l want you to get into the car...
-No, no.
Listen to me.
lf you want the car, just take it.
-l won't say anything.
-l just want you to get into the car.
-l don't want to get into an argument!
-Don't touch me!
lf you want the car, you have the car!
Take it!
Oh, shit.
Would you put your fucking hands...
You get up, you big tub of guts.
Jimmy.
-Jimmy.
-Hey.
Some guy just held me up
at the ready teller.
-What?
-He had a gun in my back.
-He wanted $200.
-The lowlife scum.
What the fuck
is going on in this world today?
Will somebody tell me what kind of
sick world this is we live in?
Tell me what happened.
Don't leave anything out.
l couldn't get money from the machine.
l didn't have any.
-He wanted me to get in the car.
-Don't tell me you got in the car.
-You didn't get in the car?
-No.
l threw the keys away, and he ran off.
Lowlife scum. Scum of the earth.
l'll tell you,
it was smart not to get in the car.
l knew l wasn't going to get into the car.
Definitely smart not to get in the car.
-What did he get?
-He didn't get anything.
l didn't have any money in my account.
Honey, l'm sorry.
l'm sorry.
Don't worry.
lt's a good thing l took that money.
-You took the money?
-Yeah. Definitely the right move.
You mean you took my money?
What the hell is wrong with you?
l borrowed the card.
l had a crisis
with my bus bench advertisement.
What are you talking about?
l have a bus bench on Sunset
right near the gates of Bel Air,
big traffic flow area.
They're looking for an actor,
boom, they see me.
Jimmy, you stole my money.
"Stole" is a harsh word, honey.
l used it as an investment in us.
ln us? ln you, not in us!
The phone could ring any moment.
That could be the call.
Next thing you know, l'm in a series.
Then we're living on the Westside.
Bam! lt happens just like that.
We're on our way.
You don't have that bullshit job anymore.
Boom! We're on our way.
You took my money.
How could you take my money like that?
You know how strong l am as an actor.
l'm bound to be recognized.
You really are a sick nut, you know that?
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
"Ring, ring." Any moment.
Boom, we're on our way.
That money sits there at the gates of
Bel Air right now, gathering momentum!
lt was a good thing,
and you should thank your lucky stars
that l got that money out
before that scumbag did.
How many times have l told you
not to go in my purse?
Don't ever go into my purse again.
Ever!
Kid...
I think it'd be a good idea
if you'd hand over your gun.
You want to look for this guy?
You think you could recognize him?
What?
l say you think you could recognize him?
l want to look for this guy.
l'll kill the motherfucker
if l find him, trying to take your money.
Please just spare me this, will you?
Why? You think l'm kidding? Huh?
You think l'm fooling around?
Yeah? l'm fooling around?
See this? l find him, l'll put him away.
-What are you doing with a gun?
-Lowlife scum.
Jesus Christ!
Are you crazy?
Blanks.
William gave me the gun and the blanks.
That's a smart idea. A gun with blanks.
lt's all an illusion. That's all it is.
Put that away, please.
You make me nervous with that thing.
That's the whole point.
That's the point l'm trying to make.
You made it for me.
lt frightens you. See?
A guy terrified you today with a gun.
lt's terrible.
lt was terrifying, right?
A guy pulled a gun on you.
That's why l want to get him.
l mean, you know, it shouldn't be.
-You still scared? You all right?
-Yeah.
Be careful with my heart.
-Huh?
-Be careful with my heart.
Self-promotion.
That's what it's about.
You can't rely on agents.
Do it yourself. That's what l say.
You'll see, those calls
are going to start coming in.
You can bank on it.
Then, with the contacts l make,
you become
Lorraine De la Pena,
haircutter to the stars.
Yeah, but in the meantime,
are you going to get a job, Jimmy?
-l'm working on it. l'm working on it.
-Okay.
-You're handsome.
-Yeah? Well, you know what they say.
The camera can only photograph
what it sees.
Not bad.
-What you doing out here, man?
-Hey. Jimmy Alto. Mr. Meyerhoff sent me.
Oh, yeah, right. Yeah. Come on in.
l been out there since 6:30.
What time you open?
6:30.
You ought to get the coffee going
'cause about 7:00, they're gonna be in here.
Right.
You know how to
work one of these things, right?
-Yeah, sure.
-All right. Cool. Go on to it, then.
-So, Mr. M tell me you an actor, huh?
-Right.
Yeah. l seen you in anything?
You ever see that show Matlock,
the role of Cliff?
You was on that show?
No. l was up for the role of Cliff.
-You was up for the role?
-Yeah, l was up for the role.
Let me tell you something
about this business, okay?
Between you and me, and it goes no further.
No problem.
l gave a hell of a reading for that part,
but l think they felt
l was a little too strong for Andy Griffith.
Really?
l blew Andy Griffith off the screen.
l mean that's how strong l am.
You understand?
l mean, l know this guy. l had that part, too.
But, you know,
there's a lot of politics involved...
-Yeah, lots of it.
-...and not necessarily how good you are.
And l'm a little intimidating, you know?
-l'm so strong, l intimidate other actors.
-Well, you know, man,
l just thought
they wanted to get the best actor.
You know, that's what l thought.
lt's not always about talent.
l hear that.
So, man,
you know what you're doing here, right?
-Stack up about a half dozen of these.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You good to go, right?
You know how to do this, right?
l did this in a Broadway show.
-You was on Broadway, man?
-Well, off-Broadway.
Off-Broadway?
Off-off-Broadway, but they're all the same.
-People don't understand.
-l hear you. l hear you.
Well, you know what?
l'm going to go off-off-Broadway.
-Let's get this cooking started. All right?
-All right.
-You good to go, right?
-l got it.
All right.
l think there's something wrong
with the button.
Well, why don't you try
the off-off-Broadway button?
l'd like a half a cup of coffee.
l only wanted half a cup of coffee.
l'm thinking of putting together
a one-man show.
-Tour de force kind of thing.
-Yeah.
That way you don't have some other
actors dragging you down, you know?
A one-man show, that's the way to go.
l got to find some piece
that really shows my...
My... l don't know, l can't find the words.
Like homeboy with the big mustache?
You know, the Huckleberry Finn dude?
What his name?
-Mark Twain?
-Yeah, yeah.
l could do Mark Twain. l could do that.
But l need something
that stretches me more, you know.
Something that really challenges me.
Something that'll show off
my talents and my abilities.
Yeah, well, why don't you show your
talents and abilities on this here?
Like to go to movie premieres?
-Hey, what the hell is this?
-What up?
What up? There's nobody here.
l mean, how do l know who gets what?
Oh, man.
Where everybody at?
Are they outside?
They're all outside. Something's going on.
Back up on the curb.
-l saw it out of the corner of my eye.
-Everyone, pIease
get back up on the curb!
Back behind the cones!
French toast, right?
Pastry and a coffee, half decaf, half regular.
-Eggs over?
-What, are you on glue?
Portuguese sausage.
-Portuguese sausage?
-That's right.
You were in this restaurant?
-Cream cheese and bagel?
-Lox and bagel.
-Whitefish.
-Whitefish? l've been looking for you.
How am l gonna do this?
Got him!
All right! Terrific! Way to go!
All right for the boys in blue!
And girls, too!
l don't know who gets what here.
Fuck it! This shit's getting cold!
Soup's on!
Has anyone seen the corned beef hash?
Hey, waiter!
Hey, shorty!
Hey, hey. l asked for scrambled eggs.
Scrambled eggs.
These are not scrambled eggs!
-Now they're scrambled!
-What about my egg whites?
-Whitefish!
-l found the whitefish.
l don't know where your toast is!
Give me the bagel.
Another half cup of coffee!
Suck it off the floor.
l like it hot!
Waiter!
You eat this!
Mr. Alto, is this a cafeteria?
No.
Then he says, "That's what l thought."
l hired a waiter,
so this is not a cafeteria.
l said, "Yeah, but l had this problem."
He says, "l can hire. l can fire."
End of story. End ofjob.
-What are you going to do now?
-What am l gonna do?
Sometimes you gotta
take the bad with the strong.
ls that an expression?
l don't know. lt's new to me.
Yeah, it's a new expression.
Hey, there goes John.
He's winding up for the pitch.
Want to watch him again?
What the hell's that all about?
Why does he do that?
l told you.
Tell me that again.
The story goes
they brought him up to the majors.
They brought him in.
Relief pitch, crucial game,
something like that.
First pitch he threw, boom.
Gave up a home run, lost the game
never pitched again in the majors.
Supposedly what he's doing
is always re-enacting that pitch,
trying to get it right,
living that moment.
Boom.
-Any of this sound familiar to you?
-Huh?
Come on. l'll do it again for you tomorrow.
Hell of a thing going through life
living that moment over and over again,
regretting that you never got it right,
you never had another chance. Poor fuck.
l'm not gonna spend my life
living the same moment
over and over again.
l'm going to beat it.
Lorne Greene didn't happen
in his 20s or even in his 30s.
All of a sudden, boom, the guy shows
up on Bonanza he's got white hair.
He hung in there.
You know,
he was in there for the long haul.
l got to hand it to Lorne, he hung in there.
Nothing's ever going to stop me. Nothing.
Bet he was a good pitcher in his day.
What?
What do you want to do?
You want to catch a movie?
l don't know. What's playing?
l don't know.
l'd like to see Gone with the Wind.
-Gone with the Wind?
-Yeah.
Gone with the Wind, you want to see?
l don't know, William.
Nothing from me rubs off on you.
l don't understand it.
From this moment on,
HoIIywood stars wiII be recognized
as unparaIIeIed fundraisers
and morale builders in time of war.
After the war, however,
HoIIywood turns another face to the world.
ln the '20s and '30s it becomes a lotus land
whose godIike inhabitants seem
subIimeIy above common concern.
And this is...
Oh, shit.
One fucking time. Don't tell me.
Don't fucking tell me!
One fucking time
l leave the fucking radio there.
One time. Son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch!
What?
Get out of the street.
-Son of a bitch!
-Come on!
Come on. Get out of the street.
-Come on! Hey!
-Son of a bitch!
Come on! Get the fuck out of the street!
Hey, what is it, what is it?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-Get out of the street!
-Can't you see l gotta...
What are you going to do,
run me over, here?
Hey, hey!
Hey, get out of the car!
Can't you see l got a fucking problem here?
They stole my radio!
Stupid son of a bitch!
Jesus!
-Hi.
-Hey.
What are you guys doing?
Some lowlife scum stole my car radio.
-Oh, where?
-Right outside.
Yeah, they said there have been
six or seven stolen this past week.
That's epidemic proportions.
What is the gun
and the video camera all about?
Well, the police aren't going
to do anything about it.
They don't care.
This is a two-hour battery.
What are you guys supposed to be doing?
l'm gonna catch the thief myself.
Video him.
This is a good idea.
Have you lost your mind?
Have you gone completely and totally nuts?
You know what it's like
to find your car violated, huh?
Your car radio gone.
Something you care about gone,
and nobody's going to do
anything about it?
Yeah. Jimmy, it's just a radio car.
l want something done. l want satisfaction.
You just gonna wait outside,
-wait for someone to break into a car?
-That's right.
l'm going to videotape him in the act,
arrest him, and hand him over to the police.
Some couples,
they spend their Saturday evenings
going to movies or clubs.
My boyfriend is going to be in the bushes,
looking for some thief.
Do you have any idea how absurd this is?
William, will you get that
away from my face?
l'm sorry. l was just checking
the autofocus at a low light.
l'm sorry. l must have lost my mind.
Hey, Will,
these blanks are not all the same size.
l wasn't taping.
-What day is this?
-The fifth.
-lt's not the fourth?
-Fifth.
Wednesday the fifth?
Tuesday the 5th.
ls this the beginning of Tuesday,
or was it Tuesday?
What l'm saying is, is this last night,
or is it now tomorrow, the fifth?
This day is the fifth.
lt has begun the fifth, not ending the fifth.
On the sixth
l got to get my head checked out.
The accident.
lt feels pretty good, though, doesn't it?
Yeah, except for the buzzing and humming,
whatever that is.
Still?
-What did the doctor say?
-When?
You said you had
an appointment on the sixth.
This is the seventh. What did he say?
l don't remember anything that important.
Up or down?
Make sure you don't get me
in the shot, okay?
Okay.
Can't see him very well yet, can you?
No, l'm not focused yet.
The filthy cretin.
This is weird. l feel dizzy.
l don't know why anybody bothers to
roll up their windows.
They steal your radio, and then
you gotta have your windows redone.
Scumbags.
Okay, this is it. Come on. Let's get him.
Okay, scumball, get out of the car.
What are you, cops?
No, FBl. Come on.
Get out of the car. Get out!
Put the radio up. Put it up.
Got that?
What the hell's going on here?
Never mind. We're going to take
a little walk to the squad car.
Come on. Pick your stuff up. Come on.
Got my radio in there, too, probably? Sure.
Who do you work for, Radio Shack?
Now, where do you sell these radios?
Where do you sell these radios?
l will kill you. Don't try me.
Are you gonna fuck with me?
-1 149 North Western Avenue, sir.
-That's a good boy.
Did you write the note for the police?
-Was l supposed to write the note?
-Yes.
What are you doing?
l'm writing the note.
That's a labeling machine.
l know. l just don't want the police
to recognize my handwriting.
Pardon moi.
Here's an unusuaI story.
HoIIywood poIice report
that a robbery suspect
was Ieft in front of the poIice station
early this morning.
Two car radios, which he is accused
of steaIing, were taped to his body.
That, according to a videotape and note
which accompanied the radios.
-Do you want a little conditioner?
-Yes, l do.
No further information is available.
PoIice say the note stated, "To the poIice,
"this guy stoIe two car radios Iast night.
"This is a video of his thievery.
"If you can't do the job, we can.
"Signed, the S.O.S."
There's no information
on the size of this S.O.S.
or what their intentions may be.
We'II keep you updated as more
information on this becomes available.
-In other news, a HoIIywood man...
-Jimmy.
-That my phone?
-No.
Jimmy.
Hey, honey.
l just thought l'd get some sun.
l read in the trades
they're looking for a newcomer
for that new movie Urban Nomad.
Get a little color on my face.
l want to talk to you.
-What?
-l want to talk to you!
Well, sit down.
Not here.
William, you, too.
-So you did it, didn't you?
-What?
The car radio guy.
Dropping him off at the police station.
You actually did it. Didn't you?
Well, it just so happens, yes.
But how did you know?
l saw it on the news.
-News? lt got on the news?
-Yeah.
No kidding?
lt's bad enough what the two of you did,
but did you have to leave that note?
Well, l mean, you got to understand
the circumstances.
So you guys are now the S.O.S.
What?
The note. You guys are now the S.O.S.
-What did you put in that note?
-l just signed it.
l mean, it had to come from somebody.
Yeah, but where'd you come up
with S.O.S.?
lt's that movie producer guy.
What movie producer guy?
lt's his initials.
The guy who did Gone with the Wind.
David O. Selznick?
David? l thought his name was Steven.
No. Steven is Spielberg.
David is O. Selznick.
l love that Gone with the Wind.
Please, this is serious.
The television believes
there's some kind of an organization,
some kind of vigilante organization.
You shouldn't have did that, William.
l mean, you shouldn't have done that.
l wanted to draw attention to the crime,
not the Steven O. Selznick gang.
Just what you need.
The police are looking
for terrorists or something like that.
Jimmy, you has to promise me
that this is finished.
Lorraine, this is no big to-do.
lt's all over with. lt's over.
-Really?
-Yes, it's over with.
She's got a point, though, William.
You know, keeping quiet on this.
"Frankly, my dear, l don't give a damn."
Wasn't that Gone with the Wind?
Yes, that was Gone With the Wind.
And it was also David O. Selznick.
S.O.S. Steven O. Selznick.
How long did they run it?
-Three and a half hours.
-No.
Gone with the Wind was
a little over three and a half hours.
-Yeah, but they...
-l'm asking about the news,
the report on the S.O.S.
lt was three and a half hours?
What'd they do,
a mini-series on the S.O.S. soap pads?
Thought it was Gone with the Wind.
No, it was 1 5 minutes.
l know how long Gone with the Wind was.
What channel was it on?
-That wasn't on that Spanish station.
-No, no, no. English, English.
-BBC? lt was international?
-No. No.
RBR? No. RBZ. RBZ.
We don't have RBZ in this country,
Lorraine.
-ABC?
-No. Other letters.
-NBC?
-NBC! That's right.
Bingo! l feel like l won something.
The suspect was apprehended
by a group that calls itself the S.O.S.
This note was made available
by poIice officiaIs.
"To the Police:
"This guy stoIe two car radios Iast night.
"This is a video of his thievery.
"If you can't do the job, we can.
"Signed, the S.O.S."
The poIice say they have
no previous information
on this S.O.S.
lt seems to be their first act.
The size of the group is undetermined.
Elsewhere in local news...
S.O.S. l like that.
l wish l'd known they were gonna put it
on television though, you know.
l would've made you write
something with a little more flair to it.
Punched it up for you a little bit.
More dramatic.
-The "thievery" l thought was good.
-Which?
What are you talking?
What are you talking about?
l'm talking to myself. Just ranting.
Going on and on about nothing.
Have some more of this tortilla.
She cooks this real good.
l know.
Got potatoes in there, eggs, everything.
lt's good for you. You get eggs.
You don't even have to have breakfast.
They let the guy go,
and they're looking for the S.O.S.
l mean, isn't it amazing?
Here we are, trying to do good,
helping to protect,
and what do they do?
They're looking for the kidnappers
of this lowlife scumbag.
All of a sudden we're the villains,
the S.O.S.
-Hey, is that your ad?
-Yeah.
You look better in your photo.
Fuck you! Fuck you!
All of a sudden
this fucking schmuck knows something.
He knows something.
lt looks the same. lt looks the same, right?
This is crazy. They're looking for
the head of the organization.
They wanna know what his name is.
-Who?
-The head of the organization.
Who is he?
There is no head of the organization.
lf they're thinking there's an organization,
then who's the head of the organization?
l don't know what you're talking about.
Remember years ago,
the S.L.A. with Patty Hearst?
This guy Cinque was the head of the S.L.A.
That being the case,
the S.O.S. needs a spokesman.
That'll be my role. l'll be the spokesman.
The recent decision by the poIice
to reIease the prisoner...
How does it look if l stand like this?
lt looks like you don't have any arms,
kind of. lt looks like...
-No arms? ls that stronger?
-Stronger? l don't know.
-How about this? How about this?
-That's good.
-lt's good?
-l like that.
lt's like, you know,
Superman used to stand like this.
-Remember he used to stand like this?
-Yeah.
All right. How's this?
Don't... Don't go like this.
You just throw me off.
l'm trying to get into the thing here
and you... Don't do that.
-What do you want me to do?
-Well, just nod or something.
l mean, l know it's running,
l know you're ready.
l mean you don't have to...
-l'm pausing it right now.
-This isn't, this isn't...
l'll shake my head.
-Okay.
Are you gonna keep shaking your head?
Don't keep shaking it. You don't have to.
-Just once is enough, okay?
-Okay.
This is J-Three, head of the S.O.S.
No. Let me do it again. Let me do it again.
This is J-Three, cell leader for the S.O.S.
That cell leader's got a nice ring to it.
Don't you think?
-Keep the tape rolling.
-Okay.
Keep tape rolling. Don't stop.
This is J-Five, cell leader of the S.O.S.
The recent decision by... Hold on.
This is K-Four, cell leader of the S.O.S.
Has K-Four been used
for something else before?
K-2 is a mountain. K-9 is a dog.
Like the Js better?
Who am l?
You're the leader of the S.O.S.
l know that, William, but who is J-Three?
What do l think? What do l feel?
How do l know?
You see, William,
you got to think of this in acting terms.
What happened to me?
Where am l at this point in time in my life?
What happened to get me where l am?
They stole your radio.
William, this isn't me.
This is the leader of the S.O.S.
l don't want to play me.
Jimmy Alto isn't the leader of the S.O.S.
J-Three is the leader of the S.O.S.
Who is J-Three?
William?
As an actor, when you know
who you are, it's easy to talk.
When you don't,
you don't know what's coming next,
you don't know where you are.
l'm an actor playing a vigilante.
That's not enough. That's not enough!
Who am l? Who am l?
l have to know who l am.
Until l know who l am,
the S.O.S. can't make a statement.
ls that my phone?
No.
This is Jericho, cell leader of the S.O.S.
Let it be known from this day forth
that lawlessness will not be tolerated.
This is a promise to
aII the good citizens of HoIIywood.
We give fair warning to the poIice
and to the judiciaI system.
Protect and serve
the good peopIe of HoIIywood,
because we wiII be watching and waiting.
This is our pledge. S.O.S. Save our streets.
-Jimmy.
-This tape was given excIusiveIy
-to Channel 5 News.
-What have you done?
We have shown it to the poIice,
who have issued a statement to the effect
that this type of organization
will not be tolerated.
They have further stated that
they wiII fuIIy mobiIize the poIice force
to combat the S.O.S.,
shouId this iIIegaI criminaI behavior
show itseIf again.
As to the leader of the S.O.S.,
the poIice are not discussing any cIues
they may have at this time.
Earlier this afternoon,
a storefront fire in the Fairfax district
threatened several commercial structures.
The bIaze broke out in a vacant buiIding
in the 400 block
of North Fairfax Avenue.
l thought l was pretty good.
What'd you think?
l don't know. lt took 35 or 40 goes to get it.
l kind of lost my perspective.
ls she okay?
l better go see what her problem is.
l wanted to at least let Hollywood know
that there was somebody there.
The way it was left, it felt open-ended.
l had to put a cap on it.
This is the end now.
Really?
-What'd you think of the work?
-The work?
Yeah, the work.
What'd you think of Jericho?
Jimmy, you're playing with fire here,
and you want to know
how your acting was?
Did you believe him?
Yes, yes. l believe him.
Did he seem sympathetic?
See, l felt there was a vulnerability.
l mean, l thought there was toughness,
but, you know, there was vulnerability.
Terry Malloy, On The Waterfront.
-Brando. He had vulnerability.
-Yeah.
Remember that scene l always play for you?
-What?
-Eva Marie Saint. She drops the glove.
He picks it up, tries to put it on his hand.
He was a boxer, a tough guy,
and he's trying to put
a little white glove on his hand.
Macho into femininity.
lt happened all at the same time.
l mean, don't forget,
l was at a disadvantage.
l mean, l was in the shadows.
You couldn't see my eyes.
lt all had to be done with the voice.
You know, put me at a big disadvantage,
but l thought l came across
threatening, tough and vulnerable.
l had vulnerability, too, right?
-Yeah.
Okay. l'm gonna take a bath.
You know, another thing
you got to remember, too.
lt's the first time l played Jericho.
l mean, l'm not gonna do it,
but imagine if l got more familiar with him.
lf l was allowed to do an
80 or 90-minute piece on Jericho
instead of a one-minute clip,
think of it that way.
This is a promise to
aII the good citizens of HoIIywood.
We give fair warning to the poIice
and to the judiciaI system
to protect and serve
the good peopIe of HoIIywood,
because we wiII be watching and waiting.
-This is our pIedge.
-lt's even better with repeated viewing.
S.O.S. Save our streets.
Definitely better with repeated viewing.
Jimmy. Men with ties.
-Detectives, looks like.
-Yeah.
You think they're looking into the S.O.S.?
The car radio guy
could've told them the street.
Wonder if they'll come and question me.
Be interesting questioning me.
Don't you think?
l could do a real number
if they question me.
Where were you on the night of so-and-so?
l could really do a number.
Do you want to go out for breakfast
and leave me at work?
Yeah. Yeah.
You know, if they question me,
l could play it real quiet.
Long pauses, you know.
l'd drive them crazy. Pause. Pause.
l'd play this real deliberate kind of a guy.
l'll make them nuts.
They just didn't know is
what l think they were saying.
They mentioned an MRl and they said
maybe they'd see something.
'Cause l definitely don't
remember things well.
l don't know. What do you think, Jimmy?
l don't know. "This is MRl. This is MRl."
-l think Jericho's better.
-Got you a lollipop.
-ls that root beer?
-No.
No? l like root beer.
You know, when you get this MRl, you're
gonna see everything's gonna be okay.
So don't worry, you know?
You're just a little preoccupied.
That's why you're blanking.
-You think so?
-Yeah.
Look at this.
We gotta get right behind this bus now.
These people, they kill everybody
with these fumes.
They should put something
on these things.
l mean, look. This is disgusting.
-How big is this part?
-lt's a nice little role.
lt takes place in one
of the underground clubs.
Yeah? Well, l mean, if this isn't
a lead role, l might be wasting my time.
Don't you have
some other principal roles there?
No, these are the roles we're casting.
l understand that,
but what about the principal roles?
Were they already cast?
This is what we're casting right now.
l can't tell you about anything else.
Well, l came for a principal role.
Well, this is all we have.
The ad in the trades said a principal role.
This is not a principal role.
This is a little role here, one line.
Do you have a picture and resume?
He's got his own bus bench ad.
He's right.
l have a bus bench right on Sunset.
Right at the gates of Bel Air.
A big advertisement,
cost me a lot of money,
and as we speak l have new pictures
being made. l mean, you...
-Excuse me.
-What? What?
-What's your name?
-Jimmy Alto. Who are you?
-l'm Rob Weiss, the film's director.
-The director. How are you, Rob?
-How's it going?
-We were just discussing over
some roles that are available here.
l wanna read him for Lewis.
l think you'd be interested
in this part of Lewis.
Lewis? Who's Lewis? He's a principal?
-He's a principal.
-Now we're talking. See?
l want to take... He's going to come with me.
l want to do this.
Do you have time to do this?
Well, l just... You know,
l have to run across town.
l have another appointment with a director,
but l can push that appointment off.
l don't think you have
any other appointments.
-lt's a little later, the appointment...
-He's a lot like Lewis.
Listen, l wanna take you with me.
lf you come with us to the end of the hall,
maybe we can do some work.
-Just take a couple of minutes.
-Sure. No problem at all.
Thanks for your help, sweetheart.
You know, Rob,
this girl has a bit of an attitude.
l mean, she tried to dismiss me
like l was some kind of an extra
or something.
Yeah, we'll take care of that ourselves.
So, did you happen to see any of
that S.O.S. stuff on the news last night?
-The what?
-The S.O.S. story with Jericho.
l think you're going way over my head here.
l don't know what you're talking about.
Thought you said that Channel 5 was
the number one news station, William?
Jimmy, l want you
to understand something here.
All right, this is a very inexpensive film,
so it's not really scripted.
Well, there's not a script-script.
So what we're gonna do is
we're gonna improv a lot of it.
-lt's going to be real loose.
-Hey, that's when l'm at my best,
when l'm loose, when l'm free, you know.
Hey, you give me words, sometimes it
pulls me down. You know what l mean?
Listen, l have this guy outside
l know who is going to play Tom.
Okay, l'm gonna bring him in here.
What l want you guys to do
is do some improv for me.
-Hey, no problem.
-So l get a feel, you know?
Get really loose with him.
Hey, it's a principal role. Of course.
Stella! Loosening up my voice.
lt's all right.
Get up now, you big tub of guts.
Hey, the heads of the family,
l want them all here.
So, what do you want to do?
You want to kill him? 'Cause l'll kill him.
l'll kill him if that's what you want me to do.
So, you want to kill him?
What are you saying, l can't?
'Cause l'll kill him.
lt's just that you seemed
a little ambivalent about it.
You see something in these eyes
that says l'm ambivalent?
Guess which one of your favorite actors
got the second lead in Urban Nomad?
-Really?
-That's right.
Jimmy Alto. Remember that name.
Urban Nomad. Probably be out
the beginning of next year sometime.
-ls that my phone?
-No.
Hi, this is Jimmy AIto.
I'm on the set right now,
so pIease Ieave a message
or a fax for me. Thanks.
Hi. This is Linda from Rob Weiss' office.
We've been trying to get in touch with you.
UnfortunateIy, we've had to go with
our second choice for the role of Lewis.
We're very sorry, Mr. AIto.
Thank you again for coming in.
The burden of battle.
Stars like Al Jolson,
Debbie ReynoIds,
Mickey Rooney,
and MariIyn Monroe.
This is a traditional scene,
a traditionaI thing for a star to do,
for it was estabIished Iong ago
that when the nation went to war,
HoIIywood went, too.
lt's a shame. You know that?
lt all happened before l got here.
This was the Mecca for dreams.
This place used to sparkle.
You could rub shoulders with movie stars
walking along the boulevard.
The glamour...
Look at Hollywood now.
No wonder l can't make it.
lt's over. lt's over.
You know something, William?
Gotham had Batman.
Hollywood needs the S.O.S.
l just realized it. They need Jericho.
We got to get some better
television coverage, you know?
Do you believe
the police can't see this shit?
Seems pretty amazing, doesn't it?
We're going to just keep taping everything,
send all the tapes to the TV station.
Put it all on television.
Let the people see
just how fucked up all this is.
Right in plain view.
You remember that Medfly problem?
lt was a little tiny Medfly.
They tracked it down,
and they caught it in Hancock Park,
and they can't find these drug dealers.
But we're going to be the watchdogs,
the guardians.
Look what they've done to my Hollywood.
Relax, William.
What are you guys up to?
l don't think that's any of
your fucking business.
Yes, it is, actually.
My friends, they have a thing
about being taped.
Really?
So, what do you suggest we do?
l suggest you stop taping.
Now give me the tape.
Get away or l'll put a bullet through
your fucking head.
Oh, shit!
He shot his own guy.
William, you okay? William?
Yeah, l'm okay.
This place is crazy. What, does
everybody have a gun? What is it?
l loved that car.
You really didn't have much choice.
lf those guys talked,
they finger the car, we're dead.
Yeah, but l loved that car.
We came to Hollywood together
a long time ago.
These drug deaIers operate openIy
and freeIy in the HoIIywood area.
The wounding of one of
the drug deaIers occurred
when he went up against two members
of the S.O.S. force.
Let this be a signaI. Don't tread on us.
We wiII never initiate aggressive action.
But we wiII certainIy return gunfire
when deemed appropriate.
l can't take this, Jimmy. l can't live this way.
What?
Don't you see how wrong this is?
Don't you understand?
ls there something wrong with you?
Jericho. That's good. That's good.
With William it's understandable.
He doesn't know any better.
At best, he's half there.
Are you telling me that this is not effective?
lt's great acting. l mean, come on,
Lorraine, look how believable this is.
Jimmy, somebody was shot.
You could have been killed. Dead!
We're reaIIy not at Iiberty right now
to taIk about the specifics of the case.
But we do have several leads. Yes.
Oh, my God, Jimmy, they're gonna get you.
They're gonna put you in prison.
-...statement from Jericho...
-Yes!
Look at this! They're paying attention.
They're all paying attention!
lt's a media blitz!
lt works. lt works. Jericho works.
lt's a great role, Lorraine.
-...Jericho warned other law breakers...
-lt's a great role.
...not to chaIIenge them.
l'm gonna be at Janet's for a couple of days.
l have to go. l can't even talk to you
about this anymore.
You can't talk to me? You can't talk to me?
You're out of the Oscar speech!
"Ride the RTD."
Rapid Transit District, my ass.
Six blocks, four hours.
William! Come on. You're zoning.
What are you doing over here?
Now, you gotta blank out?
What do you think?
This is the place the guy brings
the radios after he rips them off?
"1 149." Never forget a number.
Yep. Nobody's making a living
selling this shit. That's for sure.
Hello, there, gentlemen.
What can l do for you?
l thought you might have some radios here.
Radios?
Yeah, you know, car radios.
Well, what you see is what we got.
Yeah, you got great merchandise here.
lt must just fly out of the door.
Listen, l got a very good friend,
says you got some car radios here.
What's his name?
He doesn't like people to mention his name.
Well, l don't do business with strangers.
-Hey, hey, hey!
-Sorry, guys. Sorry, sorry.
l thought there was a bathroom in here.
Who the fuck are you?
What are you, a cop?
lt's obvious they got stolen merchandise
up the gazoo in the back of that place.
What are you thinking about?
You want to get your radio back?
ls that what you're thinking about?
l don't even have my car anymore.
What the fuck would l want my radio for?
So, then what are you thinking about?
l'm thinking the S.O.S.
should torch that place.
At least, l'm sure
that's what Jericho's thinking.
Put that thieving ring out of business.
-The big question is...
-What?
...what do we do for transportation?
Well, where do you wanna go?
Maybe we could do a carjacking.
What's a carjacket?
-What?
-Carjacket?
Not a carjacket, a carjacking.
They stick a gun in somebody's face
and say, "Give me your car."
And the people give them the car
and they go.
But we're not real thieves.
Jericho came up to me
and said S.O.S. needed my car
for one of their missions.
He said they wouId return it.
And they did. With a fuII tank of gas
and a very nice note thanking me.
-You know what l like about you, William?
-What?
You're always right there,
no questions asked. Right there.
l need a gun. You get me a gun.
We're going to burn down a building,
you're there.
Thank you, Jimmy.
You know, there's an advantage
to this memory lapse thing l have.
l keep forgetting all the bad times.
Well, l remember quite a few,
enough for both of us.
What? You were going to
say something. l can tell. What?
-New York.
-What about it?
You know, it's named after York.
And then there's New Jersey.
lt's named after Jersey.
And then there's New Zealand.
Where is Zealand?
Yeah.
Where's Zealand?
The fire began early this morning.
Once again, it seems to be the work
of the S.O.S.
We received this tape
from the S.O.S. Leader, Jericho.
This store was a front for stolen items,
from car radios to televisions and stereos,
most of which were drug-reIated.
The S.O.S. will not allow this operation
to continue with business as usual.
We're out there,
the watchdogs of HoIIywood.
That's all for now.
S.O.S. Save Our Streets.
l just get better and better.
l mean, l don't know.
l hope it's not me, you know,
l'm not putting too much into it,
but l get better and better.
You want to get some breakfast?
We just got through eating.
No. l'm only kidding.
l know you blank all the time,
so l took a shot. l'll be right back.
ls this Janet's apartment?
Yes, it is.
-ls Lorraine here?
-No.
The two of them went to Big Bear
for the weekend, l think.
l'm Holly, Janet's cousin.
l'm visiting from Hawaii for a while.
l'm Jimmy, Lorraine's friend.
You want to come in for a minute?
Sure. Yeah. Sure.
l was just watching a piece on
that S.O.S. group you got out here.
-Pretty wild.
-You think so?
Oh, yeah. Everybody's talking about it.
-Really?
-Yeah.
l had to go to market the other day,
there were people at the register
talking about it.
And what do you think of the situation?
l think it's a good idea.
l mean, there's a lot of crime, and
they're out there making a difference.
Plus, they're not hurting the good people.
Right. And what about this Jericho guy,
their leader? What do you think of him?
l think he's right.
l think it's brave what he's doing.
Do you?
Yeah, well, l've always been really
into that kind of thing.
You know, kind of underground stuff,
sort of adventurous, you know?
Yeah.
-French resistance.
-l'm not familiar with them.
l guess it's unimportant. Doesn't matter.
Do you want something to drink?
Yeah. You got any liquor here?
l'll take a look. l don't know what she has.
Yeah. Nothing with any pineapple.
-So what do you do, Jimmy?
-l'm an actor.
Can you imagine what it's like to be
in some super police military thing?
You know, he's like a Batman or something.
That's right. That's right.
lt's very dangerous.
lmagine putting your life on the line,
not knowing if you're going to live or die.
-This Jericho is some kind of guy.
-Oh, yeah. Yeah.
l mean, he must be a pretty
extraordinary person.
Special.
l wonder if he's like a Bruce Wayne.
You know, a wealthy guy that does that.
Because you'd have to have
some kind of money
to train that whole group
and arm them and everything.
What if l told you
that l know someone in the S.O.S.,
and that someone...
Hello.
Hi, honey.
l miss you, too.
Hold on a second.
l'm going to be on a while.
That's okay.
l forgot that l have an appointment.
-l'm going to run.
-Okay.
Hi, honey.
No, I feeI better. I might be abIe to
waIk down the street tonight.
l think the S.O.S. is doing a really good job.
l'm a big fan ofthose Death Wish movies.
I'm sick and tired of being a hostage...
If this is gonna get rid of
some of the crime, I say, "Why not?"
It's time the bad guys were victims.
l wish l could join S.O.S.
I'm a young girl, I'm singIe,
I'm in this town by myseIf. I don't feeI safe.
The onIy way you fight fire's with fire.
The poIice couId never intimidate them
the way the S.O.S. can.
And I am just...
I'm so happy to have Jericho here.
Jericho. They love Jericho.
...that there's hope for the city
now that they're here.
The S.O.S. is apparently striking
a favorabIe nerve in HoIIywood.
In an unofficiaI teIephone survey
conducted by this station, over 80%...
lt's a hit. lt's a rave review.
lt's as good as a review if it was a show.
80%. 80%.
Look at this. Another drive-by shooting.
You know what's amazing,
it's on Page 3 of the metro section.
l mean, it's become so commonplace,
lt's ridiculous. lt makes me sick.
What do you want to do today?
l don't know. What do you got in mind?
l want to go see a movie.
-l want to go see The Mummy.
-The Mummy?
Will, don't start with The Mummy, okay?
lt's a little early.
My father let me stay up
and watch Fright Night.
That's when l first saw it.
You know what l couldn't figure out
about the mummy?
lt's how he always used to walk
with one arm behind him
and a leg dragging.
Will, Will, l know.
Let me ask you a question.
How come the only time
you mention your father
is with this Fright Night mummy thing?
Don't you have any other memories?
l remember he used to call me "useless."
He did, huh?
Well, let me tell you something.
l was a salesman
and l can size up
people's characters pretty good,
and you have a lot of potential.
A lot of potential.
Don't let anybody tell you different, ever.
You just haven't clicked
with the right thing yet,
but when you do, boom!
You're going to be on your way.
Big things are going to happen for you.
Trust me. A lot of potential.
-Potential.
-Right.
-Who's this?
-Steve.
All right, all right. This time.
Don't bring nobody else new, man.
Stick up your hands, please.
-Don't turn around. Don't turn around.
-You want the money?
-Take the money.
-No, no, no. We don't want your money.
-You don't want the money?
-Yes, we do. Yes, we do.
lt's not cheap running
a terrorist organization, here.
Hey, he's got a gun! He's got a gun!
-Give it up!
-Get it! Get it!
l got it!
-Look this way. Look this way.
-What are we gonna tie him with?
What do you want to do with him?
We can't take him to the police station.
lt's been done already.
Why don't we just keep him captive
like the Hezbollah?
Hezbollah?
Where could we put him?
Can't keep him at my place.
l guess l can keep him
at my place for one day.
l mean, it's safe.
Lorraine's out of town, anyway.
Come on, let's go.
What the fuck was that
you were listening to?
Listen to me clearly.
You have been sentenced to five years
in an S.O.S. holding cell.
-You will be chained to a bed.
-Chained to the bed?
l ain't with no freaky stuff man.
Y'all just kill me right now.
You saw the way
the American hostages were treated?
You will be treated in the same fashion,
-as an enemy of the people.
-Enemy of the people?
l got a few character flaws,
but l ain't no enemy of the people.
l just like nice things.
S.O.S. Save our souls.
That's my parking.
l miss you, Jimmy.
l miss you, too.
l hate myself for coming back,
but what am l going to do?
l don't want to be out of your Oscar speech.
You're not going to be
out of my Oscar speech.
Wait, wait, wait.
l have to go to the bathroom.
He's gone crazy.
Jimmy!
-What?
-Have you lost your mind?
Listen. Let's go in the other room.
l don't want him to hear anything.
Okay, okay.
What the hell is this guy doing
in my bathtub, bound and gagged?
-l didn't know you were coming home.
-That explains it.
There's a fantastic answer.
See, what we're doing is,
is kind of like a Hezbollah kind of thing.
-You say Hezbollah?
-Hezbollah, yeah.
You know, the Lebanese stuff.
-Yeah.
-The terrorist group.
-Yeah. The ones that take the hostages.
See, l just didn't want
to drop him off at the police station.
A drug-dealing thing.
l mean, we've already done that.
So what we're doing is, we're setting up,
like, an intimidation factor,
you know?
Hey, listen, do you know how many tourists
visit Beirut a year? Do you?
-No, no.
-None.
Zip. Nada.
Do you know how many visit LA?
Millions. And there's more killings in LA
than there is in Beirut.
There's more crime
in Los Angeles than there is in Beirut,
-and you know why?
-No.
Hezbollah, Hezbollah.
They're scared shitless about
that Hezbollah kind of stuff. That's why.
What the hell
are you talking about, Jimmy?
What are you talking about?
There is a man in my bathtub.
lntimidating a criminal.
That's what l'm talking about.
The police don't intimidate them.
So, big deal, they get arrested.
They do six months to a year.
They go into the cells.
They watch television.
They do exercises. Big deal.
The S.O.S.,
you know what we're going to do?
The S.O.S. intimidates the criminal element.
Tie him to a bed for five years.
Scare the shit out of them.
So, you want me to actually live
in this house here with the hostages?
ls that the next step, Jimmy?
l get up a little earlier in the morning
and feed the hostages.
-ls that it?
-No, no.
This is a one-day thing.
l'm letting this guy go.
l want him to go back into the community
and spread the message. lntimidation.
To think, a couple of days' work
on a soap opera or something
might have prevented this.
Jimmy, where are we
supposed to go from here?
Well, listen,
l'm going to get rid of this scumbag
right after dark,
but l don't know
what's going to happen from there.
You're becoming
another one of those media freaks,
those people
they keep making into celebrities.
This is not about celebrityism.
This is about the craft of acting.
lt's not a vigilante who's popular,
it's an actor portraying a vigilante.
The people believe Jericho.
That's like the true tribute
to my acting ability.
Lorraine, look...
l love you, but...
Let me at least enjoy the fame a little.
You stay down for five minutes.
Otherwise, l'll be back. You got it?
-Yeah, man.
-Okay, man.
This was supposed to have been
Errol Flynn's house.
Can you imagine overlooking Hollywood?
Looking right down on it.
Warner Brothers right over the hill.
You finish Captain Blood, you come home,
you got a nice living room, you sit down,
the butler gives you
the new script from the studio,
go dancing at Ciro's,
all those things.
lmagine me coming home
in the evening, Lorraine?
We get ready to go out.
You put on a gown,
l put on a tuxedo.
Dancing with the big dance bands.
Going to some grand premiere
at the Grauman's Chinese.
lmagine if l was here back then?
l'd be as big as Cagney,
as big as Edward G. Robinson.
l'd have been right there with them at Ciro's
and the Brown Derby, schmoozing.
"Hey, Eddie G., how you doing?"
"Who's that? Oh, it's Jimmy Alto!
Hey, Jimmy, how you doing?"
"Sit down. You know Cagney."
"Hey, how you doing?"
l'd have been right there with them.
Rubbing shoulders with the best of them.
But there's nothing there anymore.
lt's over.
There's nothing down there now
but a bunch of dead stars in cement.
ln Madrid,
all l ever dream about was Hollywood.
This is not the Hollywood
l see in the movies.
lt's not.
Salud.
Hear that music?
You don't hear that dance band?
-Oh, yeah.
-Let's dance.
Do you have any idea
why a bIack Range Rover
was parked in your parking space
Iast Friday, August 6th?
No.
ln fact, l haven't even been back there
a few days.
-Do you have a car?
-Yes.
WeII, why don't you park your car there?
Because it's... lt's a new one.
I mean, I just picked it up today,
as a matter of fact.
So, until today,
you didn't have a car?
That's... Exactly. l had a car.
l mean, it burned. lt caught fire.
-Burned?
-Burned.
Deader than a doornail.
Remember that?
No.
The Postman AIways Rings Twice.
Johnny Garfield.
Remember he said that to the cop?
That's why l said it to you. You're a cop.
l said to you. He said it to the cop.
The cop said it to him. He said it back.
"Deader than a doornail." Remember?
Don't you remember in Body and Soul
he said,
"What are you going to do, kill me?
Everybody dies."
A lot of people say
l'm reminiscent of Garfield, too.
Yeah, well, you're pretty good.
Yeah.
What you do,
l guess you guys are good, too.
Hey, who knows, maybe we'll work
together again sometime.
Bang, bang.
Yeah.
Well, they're obviously on to us.
They must have a little bit more
than they're making on to, you know?
What do we do? What's the next step?
l don't know. l'm not sure.
l've never been in a spot like this before.
Sure gets your adrenaline going, doesn't it?
Gets you all pumped up?
l feel like we're making
some momentum now.
l mean, they're snooping. We're moving.
l'd like to try something new,
rather than just
making statements all the time.
A monologue, a soliloquy,
some shit like that.
Maybe l just got
to reinvent myself a little bit.
Reinvent yourself?
How do you reinvent yourself?
That's deep acting stuff.
lt's past Strasberg and...
What's the Russian, the Russian...
This Russian guy.
-The other method...
-Gretzky?
Gretzky? That's hockey.
Stanislavsky. That's it.
Hockey. Gretzky.
lt's not your fault.
You're not supposed to know anyway.
lt's my backyard. l'm supposed to know.
lt just slipped my mind.
The name slipped my mind.
Stanislavsky. Yeah, it's deep.
Worry about the camera.
You worry about the camera.
Just get that camera right when l nail it,
'cause l got them right now. l know l do.
Fuck.
l think those detectives are following me.
Don't turn around.
They're following me around now.
So, l think the time has come.
Yeah, what we're figuring is
we're going to get out of town a little bit.
All right, look, meet me at
the Errol Flynn house at 8:30.
Errol Flynn. Okay.
Hey, William.
You want a hot dog? l'll treat you.
Let me have two dogs
and a coupIe of Iemonades.
l don't want a... l don't want a lemonade.
You don't want lemonade?
No, no. My father, he gave me a lemonade
when l was a little kid. He let me
stay up and watch Fright Night.
You know, this might be
a good time to split up, Will.
You and Lorraine?
No, me and you.
You see, if l get in the car and drive away,
those cops will follow me.
You can just walk away, home free.
No.
They'll never find you.
l feel responsible.
l mean l'm the one that got us into this.
You shouldn't have to go through this.
l started the S.O.S.
That's right.
l forgot. You're the founder.
You sure?
Yeah, l want to stay with you.
Thanks.
Hey, where'd you go for those dogs,
the ASPCA?
Let's go. We got cops chasing us over here.
Shake them up a little.
They still there?
These guys must know more
than they're letting on.
They must not have enough, though.
They'd pull us over, right?
Are you going to try and lose them?
Yeah. We got to lose them.
How do they lose those cops
in all those fucking movies?
They always lose them.
Wait, fuck. We just did. We just lost them.
They're at the light.
They got caught in the light.
lf l was a cop, l'd go through it.
Fucking dopes.
So this is for the best, don't you think?
l could've been good for this town.
l think l could've been a hell of an actor.
lt takes more than talent, Jimmy.
l'm sorry l didn't take you dancing to Ciro's.
l would've liked to have seen you
in a tuxedo, just once.
lt would've been fantastic.
lt's just a little too overwhelming.
l don't know what l should do.
Kiss you, hug you,
or slap the shit out of you.
l got to go.
Go.
l can't believe l didn't make it.
l used to visualize
the people back east saying,
"Remember Jimmy Alto?
We used to call him Jimmy Hollywood?
"Went out to California and made it big."
l just can't believe it.
l really feel bad for Lorraine, you know.
She had her heart set
on the whole beauty salon thing.
With my contacts,
she could've became
the first woman hairdresser to the stars.
She could've been as big as
Christophe or Jose Eber, l mean...
She had a great name for it, too,
don't you think?
Lorraine De la Pena.
Like Oscar De La Renta.
At least Hollywood's
going to remember Jericho.
l just wish they knew
that he was played by Jimmy Alto.
-What do you make of this shit?
-l don't know.
Hey, you think
this is that guy that got shot?
l can't tell from here.
l can't tell.
What the fuck
am l going to do here, William?
There might be other guys, other lowlifes.
l knew l should've worn my seat belt.
Motherfuckers!
These guys are playing games.
l hate guys who give me the high beams.
What the hell was that all about, huh?
You think it was that drug guy
we put in the bathtub?
l don't know. l don't know.
l mean, they obviously didn't know
we were the S.O.S., right?
lmagine if we were just average citizens
and didn't know what to do.
We could've got hurt.
Why us? Out of the clear blue sky?
lt just goes to show you, l mean, you know,
the craziness that's going on around here.
lt's crazy.
l don't think we can leave town just yet.
First Jimmy Alto's got to go public.
Before l leave town, l go public.
One last hurrah.
You think that's a good idea?
Yeah.
l mean, if you're going to take
a hit show off the air,
you got to go out in style.
You got to leave them
with some kind of a hook.
Reveal the identity of Jericho.
Jimmy Alto is Jericho.
You know, if l'm going to
make my farewell speech,
l'll need an appropriate setting.
Something, someplace
that speaks Hollywood.
The Hollywood Bowl, that's it.
"Jimmy Alto at the Hollywood Bowl.
One night only."
What do you think?
The Hollywood Bowl.
l mean, look at this. This is great.
What are you gonna do?
You're going to find better than this?
What the hell am l going to say?
What am l going to say?
You know, let's face it, Will.
You know, we actually did some good.
You know? l mean, that was not
the purpose, but what the hell, huh?
Crime is down.
l forget how much, but it is down.
Why was l going public?
l can't even remember the reason now.
You think it was those drug guys
from the other time?
l don't know. l don't know.
lt's hard to tell the lunatics
from one another. l don't know.
lt's insanity. What do you want, motives?
lt's not like this is
Murder She Wrote William.
l mean, there are no motives anymore.
They could've just been playing games.
l don't know who they were.
l mean, it's total insanity.
You want to make logic out of insanity?
What am l gonna say here?
l'm trying to think.
ls today the 1 7th?
l don't know. Why?
'Cause l got my MRl
appointment on the 1 7th, you know?
That's wonderful, Will.
We have police closing in on us,
lowlifes smashing into the car,
they shoot at us.
And you're wondering
about your doctor's appointment?
You'll probably get a bullet
in your fucking head
before you get a chance to do your MRl.
What am l going to say?
What the hell am l gonna say?
What a time not to know what to say.
l mean, l have a chance to say it right
here and be in everybody's living room,
and l can't think of anything to say. Shit.
Wait a minute. This is the 1 7th.
Jimmy, this is the 1 7th!
l got my appointment with the doctor
for my MRl thing today!
William, we are leaving town!
You understand
that we are getting out of town?
l know, but it's going to take forever
to reschedule.
Can't l just go do my MRl thing right now,
then we could both
scoot out of town then?
The sun's coming up.
l want this speech to work
at the appropriate moment,
like Easter Sunday services,
with that light just breaking through.
What do you think? Are you sure?
The vigiIante Jericho
has made his name known
in the foIIowing videotape.
HeIIo, Mr. and Mrs. HoIIywood.
This is Jimmy AIto,
better known to you as Jericho.
lt's a very sad time for the S.O.S.
The poIice are forcing us to Ieave town.
l'll come back and pick you up.
What do you think? A couple of hours?
l don't know. lt could be.
l got the Sony Watchman and the
Hollywood and the Stars tapes,
l'll just watch that. Okay? They're in here.
-Be careful. Don't lose my tapes.
-l won't.
It's just a matter of time
before they get me, but think about this.
Look at the time and energy
the poIice are spending
to find me and the members
of the S.O.S. A task force.
But are we a threat
to the citizens of this city? No.
Has the S.O.S. ever robbed or raped
or kiIIed citizens of this city? No.
Is this same poIice energy
directed towards the S.O.S.
aIso appIied to the criminaI eIement
of this city? No.
PeopIe are afraid to go out at night
for fear of being robbed or kiIIed.
Women are terrified
to go into underground parking garages
for fear of being attacked.
We're guaranteed,
in the DecIaration of Independence,
Iife, Iiberty, and the pursuit of happiness.
No, the police just left.
The shit's reaIIy going to hit the fan now.
-What are you talking about?
-Well, l've gone public.
l made a video saying that
Jericho is really Jimmy Alto.
No, don't tell me that.
l can't talk now but l'm bigger than ever.
l've gone public.
l'm defying them to come and get me.
That's what my message is.
Jimmy, listen to me. Listen to me.
l can't. l can't. l got to run.
The clock's ticking, honey.
l'll call you
when l get wherever it is l'm going. Bye.
Look what's happening
to the quaIity of our Iife.
What kind of Iiberty is it
when the innocent peopIe
have to live behind bars
to protect themseIves?
How can we pursue
our happiness when we Iive in fear?
l think we could sue
the Government of the United States
because our civiI rights are being vioIated.
This is a society that is being strangIed
to death by the criminaI eIement.
And what's being done?
What is being done is
they're trying to get Jericho.
They're trying to get the S.O.S.
He's very convincing.
Yeah, he's a good actor,
but he's not a vigilante. That's the problem.
He's not a vigilante?
No.
Police Chief Cummings had this to say
about the Jimmy AIto speech.
I think this man Jimmy AIto
is missing the point.
The reason we're trying to get him
as quickIy as possibIe
is we can't aIIow anarchy on our streets.
Anarchy? You got anarchy up the ass, pal.
Anarchy with cappuccino.
We cannot sanction that type of behavior.
What the hell's going on?
At the present time,
there are over 150 poIicemen
assigned to track down
Jimmy Alto and the S.O.S.
Detectives on the speciaI task force
estimate there are
50-75 members of the S.O.S.,
and we believe them
to be heaviIy armed and dangerous.
Excuse me. l must be a mirage.
Excuse me.
Do you know where l might find William?
William who?
William. Little guy. Got a hat on.
Head problems.
He's here to see... He's getting an MRl.
l must have a last name, sir.
William, William. l don't know.
l'm sorry. l must have a last name.
William!
William?
Aren't you Jimmy Alto?
l just saw
your Jericho speech on the television.
Oh, yeah?
l think it's a wonderful thing you're doing.
-Thank you.
-l'd love to have your autograph.
-l don't have a pen.
-You're a hell of a guy, Jimmy Alto.
l agree 1 00%.
-What channel did you see it on?
-PBS.
Jimmy.
Where the hell you been?
l've been looking all over for you.
When?
-What do you mean "when"?
-l got you a root beer.
Oh, shit. Look at this.
lt's really dark in here.
Where'd you get that?
The car radio guy.
Let me see that.
What the hell building is this?
Looks like a pyramid, don't it?
Those look like Egyptian hieroglyphics.
lsn't that where they bury mummies?
Don't worry, Will.
He's not even in Philadelphia yet.
What do we do now?
l don't know.
The best thing to do is to wait till dark
and then we'll sneak out of here.
Good afternoon.
Breaking news in HoIIywood.
HoIIywood poIice
have surrounded the Egyptian theater...
-Ten minutes. Ten minutes.
-...where they apparentIy have cornered
the man who calls himself Jericho,
who we now know is Jimmy AIto...
-Did you bring my Hollywood tapes?
-Yeah.
Get them out.
The Egyptian theater
has been derelict for some time,
so it's conceivable
it could be the S.O.S. Headquarters.
We intend to cordon off the area and
make sure the situation is contained.
Do you think
they could have explosives in there?
...and there's been absoIuteIy no movement,
but so far no shots have been fired.
But we stiII don't know from poIice
how many peopIe there are inside...
Police have the situation
basicaIIy under controI.
It's basicaIIy wait and see.
What wiII Jimmy AIto's next move be?
As you can see
from the number of poIice here...
For the hopefuIs who have flocked
to HoIIywood through the years,
the studios were citadeIs to be conquered.
Because there were so many who came
hoping to succeed in pictures,
the producers
hid themseIves from the onsIaught
behind their bars and walls.
From the outside,
the studios can seem as bleak
and uninviting as fortresses.
I think it takes a great deaI
to withhold and withstand
the mad competition that you do have
and to not give up,
because it's very easy to give up.
There are roIes that you think
you're just are on the verge of getting,
and then it turns out
they go to someone eIse.
They stiII come,
the young aspirants to HoIIywood success.
One sees them like moths
fluttering in the gIare of neon Iights.
HoIIywood is a town in transition.
HoIIywood promises to become
part of another supercity,
Iike a Iot of supercities in America.
But the dream persists
that there is stiII magic here.
At night from a high buiIding or hiIItop,
when the Iights of the city
are like beacons down below,
the dream persists.
Can the police estimate
just how many members of the S.O.S.
may be inside the theater at this point?
WeII, HaI, if they can, they're certainIy
not giving us any information about that.
Butjudging
from the manpower they have outside
and the weapons they're carrying,
they're ready to take on an army.
WeII, are they specuIating,
or couId you perhaps specuIate,
on just how Iong
this standoff can last, Paul?
Are the poIice considering
forcing their way into the buiIding?
Great documentary, huh?
Great documentary.
Think l'm just gonna
have a look around a little bit.
Rather quickIy, since earlier today,
when this station received
the latest S.O.S. videotape...
-Jimmy. Jimmy!
-What?
You don't have to go take a look around.
-lt's all right here.
-What are you talking about?
-There's, like, a million cops out there.
Jimmy AIto, an unempIoyed actor
who Iives in HoIIywood...
Holy shit! All those people are out there?
Yeah.
So much for sneaking out
inconspicuously tonight, huh?
...have secured the buiIding.
-We've also received word...
-Yes! Look at this, Will.
Fans. They're our fans.
...covering aII possibIe exits
from the theater.
One thing l want to point out to you
when you see it,
aII these peopIe out here,
it's Iike an oId HoIIywood premiere.
They're a fan club.
The police want Jericho,
or Jimmy Alto, in custody.
These people want to applaud him.
ln Hollywood,
we have the hyphenate of actor/writer,
producer/director.
Well, now we have a new hyphenate,
actor/vigilante.
Jimmy Alto, we know him as Jericho...
Well, there's still a tremendous amount
of police activity here...
Special weapons
and tactics team continue to...
l want to ask about this new information,
that Jericho may actually be an actor.
Well, as far as l'm concerned,
he's a vigilante.
lf he's an actor,
he's playing on the wrong stage.
We've managed to obtain a video
of Jimmy AIto's taped audition...
Look, look, look.
They got your audition tape.
-ApparentIy, he did not get the part.
-Let me see that beauty.
-They're showing it on television?
-Let's take a Iook at that audition tape.
What are you saying, I can't?
Because l'll kill him.
This one l did better in another scene.
Why'd they put that take in there?
-He's not dangerous.
-Think you can get him out here?
He's just an actor.
PoIice have apparentIy persuaded
Jimmy AIto's girlfriend,
Lorraine De Ia Pena, to negotiate with AIto,
in hopes of coaxing the S.O.S. leader
-out of the theater peacefuIIy.
-Jimmy AIto!
-Jimmy! This is the poIice.
-Look here. You're looking up at the ceiling.
We have Lorraine out here, out in front.
She wants to talk to you.
l'd better get out there. Watch on this.
Stay here, just in case.
She is now walking up
to the front doors of the theater...
Hey, Lorraine.
l think it would be good if we talked.
Come on in. The show's about to begin.
Look what happened?
How the hell did you end up here?
Well, William's MRl took a little
longer than we thought it would,
and, l don't know,
one thing led to another, and...
Yes, one thing leads to another,
but not to this.
This building is surrounded.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. lt's like an army out there.
Hollywood Boulevard's
really happening, huh?
You have to come out.
Hey, did you see
they showed my audition tape
-on television from Urban Nomad?
-Yes.
l thought it was pretty good.
What'd you think?
Yes, Jimmy. Very good.
You know, they used to show
classic movies in this place.
Let's get William, and we'll go out together.
Okay?
l'm not going to give up, Lorraine.
Not now. This is the greatest role of my life.
You've got to know how crazy this is.
Jimmy, they will kill you.
They ready.
l'll never get another role
as good as Jericho.
Nothing this good.
You never know.
l do know.
l'm a one-role actor.
Brando...
He's an actor.
Stanley Kowalski, Streetcar Named Desire.
Terry Malloy, On the Waterfront.
The Godfather.
l don't have that in me.
Think of it this way, Jimmy.
Look at all the attention you're getting.
And the charges against you
probably won't be that great.
You'll be out in a couple of years,
and you'll be acting for sure.
This is the role. l'm going to play it out.
You've played it out, Jimmy.
lt's over.
No, it's not over.
Every great role has a great ending.
l am not going to cheat that.
l want you to take William out with you.
-William!
-Yeah.
Come here.
-What happened?
-l want you to do me a favor.
Lorraine, we saw you on the little TV here.
You looked good.
You look very photogenic.
Will, l want you to leave with Lorraine.
You think that's a good idea?
Yeah, l do. l want you to leave.
Okay.
Whatever happened to those
big romantic Hollywood endings?
l don't know.
-Will, you got to leave me these guns.
-Okay.
l need this. This, too.
Hey.
Hey, it's okay.
The mummy's going to stay with me.
You're safe.
Okay?
Okay.
Hey, Jimmy, can you see me?
l'm on TV!
We're not sure, though, who the man is,
apparently one of the members of the S.O.S.
There appears to be
some sort of negotiation taking pIace.
They're apparentIy getting demands
from someone inside the Egyptian theater.
ApparentIy, Jimmy AIto
came out to Los AngeIes
from the New Jersey area
about seven years ago.
He was an aIuminum siding saIesman,
as weII as being invoIved
in kitchen remodeIing,
but decided
that acting was his caIIing in Iife.
It's a very interesting situation
because he's acting out this part.
And we're not exactIy sure
how it's going to end
because he's writing the script.
It's in his hands at this point.
What are you going to do, kiII me?
Everybody dies.
What are you going to do, kill me?
Fuck!
Kill me?
Shit!
What are you going to do...
What are you going to do, kill me?
Everybody dies.
Fuck!
What are you going to do, kill me?
Everybody dies.
Everybody dies. Everybody dies.
l'm coming out!
Keep your hands above your head
in pIain sight and waIk.
l don't have any guns. See?
Nothing in the front of me.
Nothing in the back of me.
Take him down!
Jericho is dead.
Perhaps the most infamous vigiIante
this country has ever known...
And a mighty fine actor, I might add.
I was just a Iost kid on the bouIevard
untiI Jimmy saved me.
He truIy is a genius,
what eIse can you say? He's a genius.
He's a genius in a town
that doesn't embrace geniuses.
To you, you may have kiIIed a vigiIante,
but for me, you kiII
the Iove of my Iife.
You may have cut short potentiaIIy one
of the great acting taIents of aII time.
l think we can all mourn that loss.
Jericho! Jericho! Jericho!
What are they going to do, kill me?
Everybody dies.
l'm coming out!
Keep your hands above your head
in pIain sight and waIk.
l don't have any guns. See?
Nothing in the front of me,
nothing in the back...
-Everybody down!
-Gun shield!
Who was that, James Cagney?
l had to tell them.
l forgot l told you l had blanks.
Some vigilante, huh?
Think of it this way.
ln Hollywood, they always use blanks.
Yeah, yeah. Sure.
Blanks.
Hollywood.
We now go to PauI Jackson
outside the Egyptian theater.
PauI, has Jimmy AIto
ever worked as an actor out here?
WeII, HaI, we've done some checking.
We've found no information to indicate
Alto's ever worked as an actor here.
No motion pictures,
no teIevision shows, nothing at aII.
What about commercials?
How about industriaI fiIms, for exampIe?
No commercials, no industrial films,
no movies, no television shows.
We've checked the gamut
and we've found no information