( Alarm sounding ) Okay, let's go.
Single file against the bus.
You heard me!
Two lines!
Hold it!
You! Get back in line.
The guy fell down.
Keep moving, and keep your mouth shut.
Seventeen from diagnostic, boss.
Welcome to retrieve.
Obey the rules, stay in line,
do your time, go home to your loved ones.
Fuck with US, we'll Bury you here.
You hear something funny, dick brain?
Not me.
Watch it.
That goes for the rest of you ladies.
Gate!
On my command, left face!
Move it up double time.
March! Hut!
Form a line!
Hut! Hut!
Let's go, ladies!
( Sighs ) Hey. How you doin', man?
You remember me?
Diagnostic.
You picked me up.
Thanks, man.
Sure.
First time, right, man?
You look green.
Name's smitty.
I'm with the brotherhood.
A man's gotta have friends in here.
Find some friends, do your time, get out.
Ain't no running from retrieve.
No, no, runnin' at all.
No, best... best find friends fast.
I'm not much of a joiner.
You know, I'd think again, brother.
They got cons in here eat a fish like you
for breakfast. Niggers.
They don't get you, spics will.
Hey, you got to belong.
Thanks for the advice.
You think you can do this alone?
Yeah.
You don't have friends,
what are you gonna do
to make it?
You know what, man?
You're starting to bother me, okay?
Well, it's your ass.
Is he in, man?
What did he say, man?
Is he cool or what?
Is he down?
So, what's your name, sweet face?
Taylor. Julian Taylor. You?
Wet dream.
( Kisses ) Well, it's nice to meet you,
Mr. Dream.
You pimpin' me, boy?
I don't think so.
Well, good, 'cause you're gonna be my girl,
and I don't like my bitches
gettin' sassy with me.
Nah. You're not my type.
You're gonna be my sweet thing,
or you're gonna end up dead.
I'll pass.
You got no choice.
( Choking ) Back off!
( Spits ) What's he in for, Mr. Walsh?
Aggravated assault.
Three counts, sir.
Ah. Well,
it says here he cleaned out a bar in town.
One of the men was an off-duty cop.
( Chuckles ) Stupid bastard.
Well, let's take a look at him.
Prior convictions?
No, sir.
No civil crimes, that is.
Marine corps!
Oh, what's this?
Oh! Dishonorable discharge.
Seems he was court-martialed,
sir, no details.
Ah, light heavyweight champion.
Well, that explains it.
Sorry, sir?
Why he always settles
arguments with his fists.
Stand up for the warden.
So, they, uh...
They ran you out of the marine corps.
No, sir, warden.
I just walked.
Well, boy,
you done all the walking you gonna do
for a long time.
Here you're gonna run,
run the piss and vinegar
right out of you.
You're for the doghouse,
boy, and that ain't just
a figure of speech.
But first we're gonna let
you cool off for a few days.
Mr. Walsh,
have this man escorted to the tank.
Yes, sir, warden, sir!
Guard!
Yes, sir!
You enjoy your stay here, now, okay?
Want a hand?
Oops.
Well, good morning, Mr. Walsh.
♪♪ ( Organ ) Excuse me, captain brown...
Wait.
( Clicks music off ) The warden told me
to bring you this new fish.
How'd he enjoy his time in the tank?
Soften him up any?
Speak up, Mr. Walsh.
Don't be shy.
W-Well, sir...
When we found him this morning, he was
doing push-ups... I mean pull-ups.
( Laughs ) That's all.
Yes, sir.
Not you.
You're one of those red-ass,
hot-tempered sons of bitches,
aren't you?
Nobody pushes you around.
I hold my own.
( Door buzzing ) You believe in fate, son?
Never really thought about it.
Think about it.
( Beep ) ( Growling )
Clyde, meet the new dogboy.
Clyde.
( Slaps thigh ) ( Panting )
Good boy, Clyde.
Good boy.
You sent for me, boss?
Pappy, this here is Julian Taylor.
Warden sent him to US for safekeeping.
Seems he's got an excess
of energy needs to be
run out of him.
Yes, boss.
Show him to his bunk, get him suited up,
and let's see what he's got.
Yes, boss.
Taylor.
( Flash whirs ) Toe the line.
You stay out of trouble, son,
you'll do your time easily.
You give me any crap at all,
I'll have you back in that tank
faster than you can say "honey, I'm home."
Okay.
"Yes, boss."
♪♪ ( Organ resumes ) Funny way of talking,
That captain brown.
He's from the outback.
Out back of where?
You know, down under?
Australia?
Yeah, well,
he sure works overtime at playing
the hard ass.
That ain't play.
That man's hard to the bone.
Punk kid like you can't see the difference,
no wonder he's in here.
This is the stables.
Oh! Oh ho ho, yeah.
Right at home.
What do you think this is,
a goddamn gymnasium
you're coming to?
Your bunk's the last one on the end.
What about that one?
Ain't for you, kid.
That's for the top dog,
best of the dogboys.
You got a long way to go
before you get near that bunk.
Top dog? Is that you?
Hell, no.
I don't sleep in here.
Trustees got their own house.
Oh, yeah?
Well, how do I get to be a trustee, then?
First you come here for life.
Yeah? Who'd you kill?
My wife and the man she was with.
Sorry, man.
I was just...
It don't matter no more.
That was then.
This is now.
Only now counts.
It don't matter who or what you were
before you got here.
Only thing that matters is
who you are here and now.
You got that right in your mind?
♪ Come, rover ( Men and dog barking )
♪ Bend over ( Men and dog barking )
♪ Bend over jeez! Neighbors
are kind of noisy.
You'll be so dog-tired,
you won't even notice.
You'll sleep like a baby.
( Sighs ) Taking care of dogs.
How tough can it be?
( Dogs panting,
barking ) ( Julian panting, grunting )
Captain brown, sir?
Captain, why are we running this man?
I ain't had no chance to
show him any defense.
Then let's hope he does
nothing to rile the dogs, pappy.
Come on.
Good instincts for a rookie!
Track!
( Grunting ) Ah!
Oh!
Get off!
Go on! Go on!
Go on!
Release! Release!
You broke track when you went to water.
Don't do it again.
Pappy, get him back to the compound.
Come on, boy.
Them dogs gotta learn
how the cons run and think.
The dogboy runs the track.
The dogs hunt him down.
More they do it, the better they get at it.
I'll tell you one thing.
After they learn, ain't no con ever gonna
reach that fence.
What about the dogboys?
They gotta be learning, too.
Has a dogboy ever reached the fence?
You get that thought out of your mind.
Nobody beats the dogs.
Hit it.
( Goofy, unintelligible singing )
( Laughing ) ♪ 'cause down here
♪ you don't feel at ease
♪ you wanna say "screw it"
♪ you wanna kill someone ♪ but don't do it
♪ they're just waiting ♪ for you to lose it
what is this?
That's a book, but you have to be able
to read to use it.
No, you don't.
The man's tough, rego.
Better go easy on him.
He don't look that tough to me.
Hey, hey!
( Crying ) We're getting off
on the wrong foot here.
We ain't even been introduced yet.
The name's Taylor.
I don't need to know your name.
You... ( Pats face ) Need to know mine.
Miguel, top dog.
Everything in here is mine.
Even the toilets?
( Puffs ) Even you.
You're making a mistake.
You can tell me all about
it after I kick your ass.
Aah!
( Metal cabinet slams ) ( Dogs bark )
You're dead meat, dogboy.
( Barking ) All right, cinderella,
it's pumpkin time!
Pick it up.
Okay.
Hey, rego, Miguel step on his dick again?
( Laughs ) ( Jamaican accent )
Dogboy, about time somebody
kicked that fucker's ass.
Hey, yo. My name is Owens.
17324. They call me Willy b.
Julian Taylor.
Yes, Julian.
So, that was top dog?
Yeah, mon.
He took over from Chandler
after the dogs eat him up.
No, mon, I just joking.
Just hurt him up some.
What the hell's the matter in here?
Get a new dogboy,
everything turns to rat shit!
You got those pens cleaned out, Willy?
Not yet, pappy.
Shit, mon, yo.
Come on,
no sense me having all the fun. Yo, pappy!
All right, welcome to the real doghouse.
See, we clean these cages twice a day.
Fucking dogs live better than the cons,
what?
Yeah.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
Yo, yo, yo.
You don't want to go
near this one till you get
some understanding, all right?
He's very, very bad.
Yeah, we've met.
Dude, yo, yo, yo!
Don't messing with them, mon!
Clyde belong only to captain brown,
you understand?
Look, that's a purebred German Shepherd.
They're real hunters, you know?
Captain brought him
back as a pup from Europe.
He don't even let US train him.
Clyde, come on, mon!
You know the drill. Move it!
Inside! Hey,
I'm gonna get Julian to come in there
and kick your ass.
( Laughs ) Come on!
Eh. Damn it, I hate this animal.
He's purely evil.
What the hell is that?
It's, uh, where I come from?
It keeps away evil.
Here, you do one.
You gotta be kidding me.
You actually believe that shit?
( Barking ) Then again,
how can I lose, right?
Yeah! ( Laughs ) ( Chuckles ) Tough guy!
( Chuckles ) All right.
( Sighs ) Hey, Julian, you like
comics, mon?
Yes, that's perfect reading
for the doghouse and all.
The good guys always win,
and the villain always lose.
Good triumph over evil,
just like in real life.
So, j., now you that finish your first day,
what do you think of this happy life?
Hmm?
( Snoring ) Mm. That's what they all say.
( Barking ) ( Barking )
( Panting ) ( Whistle tweeting )
( Dogs barking ) All right, everybody,
wake up!
Time for breakfast!
Hear that?
Them dogs are hungry.
Come on, Taylor, move your dogboy ass.
Hey, my friend, you sleep well?
No. You?
Like a baby, mon.
Like a baby.
♪ My wife has gone ♪ she took everything
♪ I'm like a mongrel ♪
up and gnaw on my bone
♪ ow! They're going... move your ass,
Taylor.
♪♪ ( Indistinct singing ) Listen,
you smart-ass!
This nose would find a drop of your sweat
in a space as big as the astrodome.
Well, then I better stock up on speedstick.
When them dogs are on
top of you getting ready
to eat your prick, you're gonna wish
you listened to pappy.
I'm listening.
Have you put him to work yet, pappy?
Yes, just, uh,
teaching him the basics, boss,
and how mighty strong is
the dogs' sense of smell.
Give him a spell in the box.
He'll get the message soon enough.
Right away, boss.
( Tweets ) ( Gate unlatches )
( Men barking ) What's going on?
We're gonna show you how it's done, boy.
Stink up them kennels!
Make it quick!
Every time you touch something,
brush up against something,
pass through somewhere,
your body drips scent,
which in some cases can be a mite strong!
Lasts anywhere from a
couple hours to a week,
depending on how wet or dry the ground,
how rough or smooth the thing you touch.
Can you cover it up?
Sure, water'd cover it up,
but you gotta come out
of the water sometime.
Another animal crossing it would cover it,
but no matter how much
you try to confuse 'em,
that dog, he'll always find his man,
as you're about to find out,
if he's been trained right,
that is.
All right! That's enough.
You don't want them dogs throwin' up!
All right, boy, get in.
Which one? Any one?
Everything they did,
except for the last one.
Then you stay put.
Won't the dog see me go in?
Just do as I say, boy.
( Farts ) Oh...
Oh!!!
( Laughing ) Come on. That's it.
That's good, doggy.
All right, everybody!
The party's over.
Get back to the kennels.
Them dogs need grooming.
That's it. Search!
( Dog panting, grunting ) Come on.
( Growling ) ( Barking )
Heel! Heel!
( Chuckles ) That's a good boy.
That's a good boy.
Can I come out now,
or are we going for round two?
( Chuckles ) Does it bother you at all
that we're training dogs
to track men like US?
Hmm! Not a bit.
Hey, that reminds me... last night,
I heard dogs
barking just like he was
when we were outside.
We had a runner.
Yeah?
What happened?
Well, same thing that always happens.
Dogs ran him down.
Damn.
Come on, I'll buy you a drink.
Thanks.
Man, that's gotta hurt,
running free like that,
and then all of a sudden, boom, right back
behind bars.
Not back behind bars.
Back to the morgue.
He fought the dogs.
They killed him before
we could run up to them.
Jesus.
New fish like you, name of smitty.
He should've asked.
Somebody would've told him.
Can't run at retrieve.
He knew. Knew?
He is the guy who told me
that no one runs from retrieve.
The guy had been here before.
I thought you were a standalone guy.
What you worried about this con for?
( Scoffs ) I'm not worried about this con.
I'm just trying to figure things out,
you know, learn.
Learn two things: You fuck up,
you answer to captain brown.
You run, them dogs will eat your ass.
Understand?
Julian, you still up, mon?
What the hell you doing out of bed?
I'm nursing the sick dog,
mon. What are you doing?
I'm just reading my book.
You are? Reading a book?
Oh, I bet you one of them guys who got some
good schooling, right?
I bet you that you come from a good family
and a good home, right?
Yeah, well, you shouldn't bet, then.
My parents died when I was 13.
I've been on my own ever since.
Oh, shit, hey, I'm sorry, mon.
I didn't know. Nah.
Shit. It's rough, mon,
'cause, you know, a man
needs his friend and
family to come visit him
in a place like this.
You know what I mean?
Who you got visiting you?
Who, me? You know...
I got a girl come by once a month,
you know.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Is she pretty?
Social worker.
( Laughs ) Hey! Either get in the sack
together, or shut the fuck up!
Hey, Julian, just forget it.
( Shouting, dog barking ) We got a runner.
Guard: Let's go get him.
Come on.
Go get him.
Here we go!
Come on, where's he at?
Where's he at?
Let's get him!
( Door slams ) Yo, what's up, rasta?
Prisoner Owens to see his visitor.
That's right, a miss Chadwick,
his social worker.
She brought him this.
A Bible!
Won't do you any good, Willy!
No pictures.
Yeah. You know something, this is mighty
fine paper, though.
Think I'll roll a few joints,
have myself a holy smoke.
You do that,
and you will feel the wrath of god, boy.
Amen to that, brother.
I'm just joking, boss.
Shut the fuck up and get in there!
All right. No problem.
On my way.
Straighten out that hat, asshole.
Hello.
Hi, will! How you doing?
You're looking good.
Looks like they've been feeding you well.
You get the copy of the
good book I sent you?
Yes, yes, great, mon.
It come in real handy-like.
I'll pick it up on the way
back to the doghouse.
By the way,
you're looking pretty chipper yourself
there, miss Chadwick.
Is it all right here, you know what I mean?
Yeah? Oh, yeah!
Safe as houses, mon.
This house is completely
bug-free. That's guaranteed.
Don't worry.
Thank god,
because if we didn't quit this double act
soon I was gonna lose it.
Can we forget the accent for a second?
Yeah, I'll try,
but it's been like second nature
for me now... "Mon."
So, uh, find anything yet?
We sure do have more
than our fair share of runners
for such a high-security prison,
you know what I mean,
but, uh, there's nothing I
can really put my finger on yet.
There's a quadrant of the prison grounds
we never run.
Now, I wanna know why.
Oh, and there's this new guy on the unit.
His name is Julian Taylor.
He's not like the rest.
You know, he's a good kid.
Not your normal scumbag,
if you know what I mean.
Can you use him?
Well, I'm working on it,
you know, gonna give him
a chance to show me who he is,
see if I can trust him.
By the way, ( Jamaican accent
) Have I told you how good
you're lookin' lately?
Keep your hand straight.
Listen up.
You two run together today,
which makes you first-time
lucky, Taylor, with Willy b.
Here to break you in gentle-like.
You listen to him,
you won't come to much harm.
Captain brown wants double tracking.
What's double tracking?
Willy knows the routine.
Lay down two sets of tracks,
split, cross over.
Couple of dogs follow Willy here.
Couple of other dogs follow you.
Why? I don't get it.
Well, sometimes we have
two or more cons who are stupid
enough to think that
they can reach that fence,
and we gotta train them dogs.
Now, is there anything else?
Yeah, I heard the dogs again last...
I want you to keep your eye on the track.
Willy here, he's got the route map.
You don't have to worry
about anything else.
Two for the gate.
Okay.
( Barking ) ( Men panting )
Hi, Hank.
You know, this road is not on this map,
you know?
Hey, neither is that shack.
Oh, man, don't tell me we're lost.
Well, you know what?
I bet you we make a wrong turn
at that downed tree, remember?
I thought you told me
you never broke track,
you never got lost.
"Taylor, mon,
I always know exactly who and where I am."
Yeah, well, there's a first
time for everything, all right?
Yeah, well, let's get the hell outta here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's go check it out.
Why?
Knowledge is a powerful thing, mon.
Yeah, well, we'd better get back on track.
Hey, Julian, stop.
J.! J., j., j., j.!
Look, we have time, mon.
The dogs have just get let go right now.
We have all the time in the world.
What the hell is going on here, Willy?
Going on? I just asked
you for a little help, man.
Friends help friends, right?
We're not friends, man.
We're just two cons running track.
That's not the way I see it, mon.
What do you want me to do?
All right, help me up the tree.
Why?
Uh... I'm gonna go tree to tree,
right, get near
the shack, come back same place.
The dogs can't track me.
So, you coming along?
What is this, fucking Tarzan and Jane?
No, I'm not coming.
I'll get you up the tree,
and then I'm running
my track, all right?
All right, Taylor, mon,
that's very friendly.
Hey, tell me something.
You think you have something
good and you don't want
to mess with it, right?
Damn straight.
All right, here.
Take this map, go on the track,
and I'll catch up with you
before captain brown, okay?
♪♪ ( Organ ) Tragedy struck
In the quiet suburb of wallamaroo,
Sydney, today
in the brutal slaying of
20-year-old concert soloist
Laura brown.
Escaped convict Jake
Henry has been apprehended
and has confessed to the murder.
A graduate of the
Australian school of music,
miss brown was known for her sensitive
interpretations of the
organ music of j.S. Bach.
Friends and colleagues are in shock over
the senseless tragedy which has cut short
a brilliant and promising career.
Another fatality at the scene of the crime
was Laura's faithful dog,
who was slain, it is thought,
while attempting to protect her.
Now, before an update on the weather,
we go over...
Now, what would Freud make of that,
captain? Hmm!
Holy shit.
Shh! Shh! Shh!
Look by the center fence pole.
Now, look on that bush.
You see anything?
No.
Well, look again! Look!
Just look... look, see!
Ah, see? Captain brown likes to test a man,
run him near the fence and see if he makes
a break for it.
Now, you see that?
He puts that guard out there.
He shoots you in the ass,
and you'll be leaving here
for good, feet first.
What do you care for, anyway, man?
You're my friend, mon!
You helped me up that tree!
Come on,
we still have some track left to run.
Hold!
( Growling ) You ran good tracks.
Got off once or twice, it looks like,
but good tracks.
Now get your asses back to the gate.
Hyah. All right, dogs!
Get walking!
Hey, why didn't you say anything?
'Cause I don't know anything.
Yeah, well,
you could've got in good with brown.
What do you think I am, a snitch?
Hey, want to know what I found? No.
Listen,
captain brown's doing some really bad shit.
I think we can stop him.
You got the wrong guy.
No, no, I don't think so.
You two,
stop your bullshitting and double-time
it back to the gate!
Right.
Tch! I really need somebody I can trust.
Well, it ain't me.
No, no, no, I think it is.
Well, think again.
Eh... tch!
( Dog growls softly ) ( Whispers ) Hey,
boy.
Hey, boy.
Good boy.
Kennel up.
( Dog growls softly ) Shh.
( Trapdoor creaks softly
) ( Dog growls softly )
Stay. Stay.
No! Aah!
Aah!
Willy! Willy!
Cool it! Cool it!
There's nothing you can do!
No! Willy! Come here!
Call somebody!
Get outta there!
( Alarm blaring ) Emergency! Emergen...
No fucking shit, man!
Contact infirmary!
Send for medics down here fast!
Man: Hey, what happened?
Come on, guys, tell me what's going on!
Oh, my god.
Kennel up! Bastard!
Rotten! You bastard!
You bastard!
You devil bastard! Bastard!
Drop that, pappy, or I will blow
your ugly head off.
How many times I have to tell you people...
Don't mess with the animals!
Show them some respect.
Clyde, kennel up.
What happened here, cap?
We don't know yet, sir.
This dogboy's supposed to be in bed.
He ain't meant to be in here.
We don't know why he got into Clyde's cage,
sir.
That dog is supposed to
be secured before a man
enters his cage.
Yes, sir, the dogboy knew that, sir.
I want your report on my desk by noon.
Yes, sir.
What the hell are you doing, Taylor?
Nothing, boss.
I just going to help my friend.
Your friend is going
straight to the morgue,
and you are staying
right here and cleaning up
your friend's mess.
Right, now, let's break it up!
Pappy, you come with me.
Yes, boss.
All right, guys, hit the sack.
You heard the man, dogboy.
Start scrubbing.
( Buzzer ) Oh... yes?
Deputy district attorney dern is here.
Oh, yeah. All right.
Ahem.
Adam Wakefield, Mr. Dern.
I'm pleased to make your acquaintance.
Actually, it's Ms. Dern, warden. Mr. Ewing
is my assistant.
Oh! ( Laughs ) Right.
You know, I assumed...
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I do apologize, miss dern,
though I have to admit,
you about the best-looking d.A.
I've seen out here,
and I've seen most of them.
Thank you.
Cigarette?
So, you must be new on the team, dern.
Dern...
Was your father senator dern?
Yes, sir.
Oh! I voted for him.
He was a good man.
So, tell me,
what brings you out to retrieve?
The prisoner death in
the dog unit last night.
Well, you've got some pretty good sources.
We haven't put that out yet.
Of course, we don't know what we got yet.
A dog handler was
killed in one of the cages.
Thing is,
we don't know what he was doing in there.
He should've been in bed.
The name of the prisoner was Owens,
wilbur b.,
known as Willy b.
That's right.
He was one of ours.
One of yours?
Uh, what are you saying?
Owens, wilbur b.,
is... was, really... detective
William mccarver on special assignment
to my office.
You put someone undercover in my prison?
Operation backtrack.
We're working closely with a
number of federal agencies.
I don't give a damn if you're working
with Jesus Christ.
I run this prison,
and you will goddamn well have
the professional courtesy
to inform me when you put
a man in here!
Detective mccarver was investigating one
of your senior guards, sir.
We didn't want to risk informing anyone
in the prison structure.
Oh, ho, I know what that means lady.
That means you don't know whether I'm doing
whatever he's doing, whoever he is.
Eh, well, would you be kind
enough to tell me just who
you're investigating on my staff?
Captain Robert brown.
Cap... uh, cap brown?
What'd he do, break a leash law?
Treasury and DEA have
been running an operation
monitoring money laundering
through offshore banks
in the Cayman Islands.
They picked up brown by
chance on a phone intercept
and traced it back.
Seemed he's made deposits totaling 960,000
in the past few years... not bad for a guy
making 60 a year with o.T.
Well, that's a feather in your cap,
isn't it,
if it's true.
We're treating this like a murder,
unless there's
strong evidence to the contrary.
You got a dead cop,
and I sympathize with that,
but the report says
that he failed to secure
a cage and a dog got loose.
Now,
he was someplace he wasn't supposed to be.
If you had come to me in the first place,
then maybe his death could've been avoided!
Now, obviously,
I will treat this seriously, ma'am,
but any investigation
at retrieve is gonna run
through my office!
I understand.
We will coordinate everything through you.
Fair enough.
But I don't want anyone else knowing about
this investigation.
Thank you for your time, warden.
Miss dern!
I don't want a dirty guard
in my prison anymore
than you do.
If brown's head has to roll,
I'll deliver it
on a silver platter.
All right, on your feet!
On your feet for cap brown now!
Okay, strip search.
Into the washroom.
Stark bollock naked.
Don't be embarrassed, boys.
Y'all been jerking them together, anyway.
Move!
Make it thorough, Mr. Walsh, understand?
Very good, sir.
On the double!
Take the place apart, Mr. Wilkins.
What we looking for, cap?
I'll know it when I see it.
No contraband, sir.
Get me Taylor.
Taylor!
Captain brown, front and center!
On the double!
You and Willy b.
Were getting tight.
I guess.
( Chuckles ) You guess.
You been any closer,
you'd be planning a family.
I've been running cons a long time, son.
I know how it goes.
Ain't no con can keep a
secret when he's got a buddy.
Prison's too hard without sharing.
What was Willy doing in the kennels?
I don't know.
I was asleep.
He didn't tell me.
Where's Willy b.'S stash?
What stash?
Bullshit, son, you are really starting
to piss me off.
Every one of you's got a stash...
Little bit of weed, a shank,
a picture of some bitch.
He didn't tell me.
You know what you are, Taylor?
You're one of those half-smart
boys who thinks he knows
how it works.
You know what happens to them?
My dogs run 'em down,
and I shoot 'em off the fence.
What have you found out
about your dogboy's death?
Nothing yet.
Do you see this causing any problems?
Problems? What kind of problems?
He ain't the first con
that's died because he was
in the wrong place doing the wrong thing.
He was a cop.
( Phone ringing ) Ewing.
Who is it?
It's that dern bitch.
Y-Yeah, but Wakefield could be right,
Jennifer.
The guy was in a cage with a wild dog.
It could've been an accident.
Will mccarver was too smart
to make that sort of mistake.
Now, the last thing will
told me was that there was
this new dogboy that
he thought he could trust.
Don't shine a light on him.
If they kill mccarver, they'll be looking
for his friends.
You think I haven't
already thought about that?
What I'm gonna need are
prison records on the dog unit
going back five years,
but don't ask Wakefield for them.
Find another source.
How am I supposed to do that.
Get arrested.
So, what did she say?
( Chuckles ) Well,
she said... get arrested.
Warden Wakefield, I'd like to apologize
for the way I've gone
about this investigation.
It was arrogant and wrong
of me to insert an agent here
without first consulting you.
I hope you'll forgive me
and allow me to continue
my work here.
Oh, thank you!
That's very handsome.
Do, do sit down.
But, miss dern,
I don't know how you can handle this matter
any better than I can.
Well, maybe I can't,
warden, but will mccarver
was my partner.
You were a cop.
You know what that means.
I have to try.
Where would you like to start?
Well, I'd like to talk to
the men in the dog unit,
and then have a word with captain brown.
( Chuckles ) Sure.
We can do that for you right here and now.
Be my guest.
She can interrogate me anytime.
Great personality.
( Laughing ) Inside, Taylor.
Mr. Taylor,
deputy district attorney Jennifer dern.
Please.
Says here you've only
been in a couple of months.
How do you like working the animal unit?
I'm in prison, lady.
"Like" isn't a real big part
of it. I just do what I'm told.
Willy b. Said he could trust you.
His real name was William mccarver.
He was an undercover
agent working for my office.
We believe captain brown
is doing something illegal
in this prison and will,
Willy b., was investigating it.
Where are you going?
Look, I don't want to know any more.
I don't want to hear any more.
Someone like you comes
in here and starts talking
to someone like me, I'll be dead in a week.
I need your help to find
out what happened to will.
( Scoffs ) Good luck.
( Sighs ) That's the last one, ma'am.
Can I escort you to your car?
Uh, thanks, no.
I have an appointment with captain brown.
Do you know where he is?
I believe he has a v.I.P. Day.
A v.I.P. Day?
Yes, ma'am. Every now and again they like
to come down and ride along.
Captain says it's good for the program.
What program is that?
The dogboy program.
Captain brown will tell you all about it.
Show me the way.
( Grunting ) You think I'd forget, huh?
You think I'd do nothing?
Ain't how it works, dogboy!
Gah!
Your friend Willy b.'S dog meat.
Maybe it's time you feed the dogs too, huh?
God.
Don't do it.
You do it,
you spend the rest of your life in here.
He ain't worth it.
Come on, boy.
Put it down.
You kill him, he's gonna take
your life with him.
( Weight clatters ) All right, you two!
Get him over to the infirmary!
Hey, top dog, you come with me.
I got a job for you.
We appreciate your support,
senator, and here's to you.
( Knocking ) I'll tell you right now,
it's getting harder and harder to come by.
What the hell's this, pappy?
Where's my top dog?
Well, he, uh, he injured himself.
I sent him to the infirmary,
but I tell you, boss,
Taylor here,
he'll run as good a track as Miguel.
Well, if he doesn't, it's on your head.
Gentlemen, this here's our top dog today.
He's gonna lay the tracks we're gonna run.
Don't look like much.
Well, it's not the looking,
Mr. Cates, it's the doing.
This boy can run.
Just don't want to waste my
time with some gutless punk
gives it up before the dogs get near him.
What you in for, boy?
Kicking the shit out of a big old redneck.
If was running this place,
I'd stretch you down
and work the piss out
of you with a bullwhip.
Then you'd be in on assault charges,
too, Mr. Cates.
Well, as I live and breathe.
How nice to see you again, miss dern.
You know warden Wakefield.
Gentlemen, this is Jennifer dern
from the d.A.'S office.
She's been investigating
an unfortunate accident
we had down at the dog unit.
You know, she's been... let me see, now.
It was St. Luke's fundraiser, wasn't it?
You have quite a memory, Mr. Diggs.
Yes, ma'am.
How's your wife?
Why, she's just fine.
She's just as fine as frog's hair.
One big, happy family.
Mm.
I understand you're
running an exercise today.
I'd like to ride along.
Oh, well, I don't know.
That's kind of an unusual request.
Any more unusual than for these gentlemen?
Well, I think miss dern
would be a welcome addition
to our party.
You betcha.
Excuse me, warden, but there's gonna be
some hard riding.
I doubt miss dern will be up to it.
Well, I was raised on a ranch,
captain brown.
Don't worry about me.
Well, now! It's all settled,
then, isn't it?
I suppose it is.
( Barking ) Looks like our query's
gone to earth, gentlemen.
Down the hatch!
Goddamn,
it doesn't get much better than this.
Got a mighty fine pack of dogs here,
captain brown.
Maybe he's not in there.
That pipe could go on for miles!
Oh, he's in there, all right.
Check it out, Mr. Wilkins.
You in there, dogboy?
Fair game. You got me.
Just call the dogs off,
and I'll come on out.
Shall I call them off, captain?
There's only one man
gives orders around here,
Mr. Wilkins,
and it's not that scum in the pipe!
You're to come on out!
That's an order from cap brown, you hear?
What's Clyde doing there?
What is it?
Manhole!
What do you see?
I don't know.
It's pretty dark down there.
Wait a minute!
There's a glimmer of light to the left.
Well, that figures.
What else?
Nothing else! Yes!
For Christ's sake, what is it?
It's a metal grille,
and I guess that means...
He's trapped.
( Chuckles ) Why don't you
send Clyde down after him?
Teddy, we'll smoke the critter out.
( Crackling ) He's trapped.
Clyde'll take care of him.
All right, warden, you've found your man.
You've had your fun.
I think it's time we call it a day.
I really should be getting back to town.
Well, it's all a matter of discipline,
miss dern,
but if you want to go back,
you just follow the river
due south.
We're just keeping
up an old tradition here,
smoking old foxy out of his hole.
Well, it's also tradition
that the fox is always killed
and the youngest hunter blooded.
Is that what you have in mind?
Because I don't want blood on my hands,
warden.
That won't happen.
That boy's gonna come to no harm.
Now, come along, now.
Don't be an old spoil sport.
( Julian coughing ) ( Barking )
Aah! Aah!
Get off!
Call him off!
Aah!
Warden!
All right, Bob, that's enough.
She's getting all high in the behind here!
Damn it.
Whoa. Hold on, miss.
( Fires ) Call him off,
or I'll kill him!
Release!
( Groans, coughs ) You'd shoot my dog?
To save a man's life, yes.
And for your information,
I'm filing a full report
of this incident to the district attorney
first thing tomorrow morning.
Captain brown,
why don't you head on in with the dogs
and show our guests a little hospitality?
I'll, uh, I'll take care of things here.
Thanks for speaking up.
You're welcome.
Miss dern?
You, uh, remount, we'll head on in.
You all right, son?
Yes, sir.
( Dogs barking ) ( Knocking )
You're working late.
Something's going on at retrieve,
something bad.
I'm getting out a report on it for the d.A.
Make your hair stand on end.
Can I get you a cup of coffee or something?
No. Oh, hey.
Come take a look at this.
What is it?
Where'd you get it?
Dogboy named Taylor gave it to me.
Snuck it to me on the sly, actually.
Taylor? Wasn't he the
one that will wanted...
Yeah, he seems cool.
It's a picture of a man with his hands up.
Looks kind of funny.
Did you ask him?
I didn't get a chance,
but I will first thing tomorrow.
I really think we've got something.
Well, it's curious, but it wouldn't put
too much importance on it.
It's a chewed-up photo.
It's gotta be the key.
What do you want?
Please, sit down.
Tell me about the picture.
What about it?
It's okay.
Did you find it on will?
Sort of.
It was in the cage where he was killed.
Now, I gave you that picture,
lady, what the hell more
do you want from me?
But where did it come from?
What does it mean?
You had a cop in here, and he got killed.
What the hell do you
think they're gonna do to me
if they think I'm part of it?
If who thinks?
I don't want to have
anything else to do with this.
No. Wait. Please.
Will was my friend.
He said he could trust you.
I don't know what you're talking about,
lady,
and I can't help you.
( Indistinct singing ) Taylor,
need a word with you.
Hey!
You're running in an hour.
Who's riding?
Me and Wilkins.
Where's captain brown?
I don't know and I don't
care and neither should you.
I got orders to set your
track and run it with Wilkins.
You got orders to run the track.
I don't know why the hell you should care
where cap brown is.
I don't know when the hell
you're gonna learn to keep
that mind of yours to yourself!
Jesus. He's really got your ass tied up,
doesn't he?
Captain brown's got
everybody's ass tied up.
There ain't no shame in
being afraid of cap brown.
He is a frightening man.
You be on time.
So, did you get anything from your dogboy?
Attitude. What'd you get?
Oh, you owe me.
Retrieve's prisoner database
over the last five years.
Inmate files and photos, too.
I had to practically promise
marriage to that 300-pound clerk
in records.
What, the pretty one with the nose ring?
That's her.
Ooh. I'll get the office to
spring for a bridal shower.
Hey, by the way,
thanks for coming in on the weekend.
That's all right.
I had some work to catch up on anyway.
Management out now, pappy.
Let's get going.
I'll be right with you, boss.
Hold on, boys.
Wilkins, take the afternoon off.
Pappy's going out with me and Clyde.
Yes, sir, captain.
Come on, pappy.
Let's go track US a dogboy.
When he says go, you go hot.
Go on, and keep on going.
Uhh!
What?
Oh.
Come on.
Oh...
Good boy, Clyde.
Chased him up a tree.
What's he doing in this area,
pappy? Doesn't he know
that we don't run the northwest?
Yes, sir, boss. He knows.
He does? Why, did you tell him, pappy?
I tell them all.
I told this one right off.
You don't run there.
He must be lost.
Then let's find him, Clyde.
Track!
Holy shit.
( Barking ) You screwed up, boy.
You broke track.
Disobedience will bring you pain.
Time to pay the Piper.
Boss, don't do it.
Pappy, what do you think I'm gonna do?
You think I'm gonna shoot this dogboy?
I don't know, boss.
( Chuckles ) And what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna shoot me, pappy?
Boss, too many people have died already.
You said it was gonna stop.
People? You call them people?
Scum, pappy, that's what they are.
That's why you had
to pull the pin on Willy.
The world's a better place without scum.
You said it was gonna stop.
It is gonna stop, and there isn't gonna be
any shooting, is there, pappy,
but what are we gonna do
about this here dogboy?
Shoot him, pappy, shoot him!
For Christ's sake, what's going on, pappy?
You gonna take orders from a dogboy?
I-I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Boss,
maybe it's best you put that gun down.
What do you think, Clyde?
( Barks ) No, boss!
Jesus!
Dumb shit.
You are definitely fucking
up my little world, Tyler,
and I don't like it.
I finished up. I'm gonna go.
Hey, come in here for a minute.
Did you find something?
Yeah, check this out.
I found this guy.
His name's Walker.
He was killed trying to escape.
Really? Did you find anything else?
Six out of eight attempted escapees
in the past year have ended up dead.
Is there a common factor?
None of the dead ones have any next of kin,
nobody to ask questions.
What does that have to do with brown?
It could be a coincidence.
Everything that goes on in
that prison has something
to do with brown.
What does any of this
have to do with tax evasion?
Stay focused on the big picture, here, Jen.
The big picture?!
I swear, ewing,
if I hadn't been there on that ride-along,
they would've killed Taylor.
You weren't there.
This guy's a psychopath!
I have to go.
I'll, uh, see you Monday.
Oh, my god.
They're hunting them.
Glad you could make
it on such short notice.
Hell, I'd drop anything to hunt.
You got 15 minutes.
I've given him 15 minutes.
Let's make it ten.
( Panting ) Track!
Okay, let's have a look at the cards now!
Oh, oh ho! Dawn,
I'm afraid you lose. It's your turn.
She's the first one,
first one gonna show US...
Oh ho! Yeah!
Brrrr!
Warden! We've gotta get
to the dog unit right now.
Um! Well, now, hold on.
Just let me call down there,
see what's happening.
Ahem. Yeah, this... this is the warden.
Give me a situation report,
and make it real quick.
Who's dealing?
Cheers!
Dealing to the left?
Okay!
Yeah. Yeah, right.
There's no reason to go over there.
We got one man in the infirmary,
we got two working chores,
and we got one running
a track with captain brown
over in the northwest quadrant.
Who's running the track?
Taylor.
He fits the profile.
No next of kin, nobody to look for him.
We've gotta find that boy
before they kill him, warden.
Kill him? What the hell
are you talking about?
I'll tell you on the way.
Yeah, well, just keep playing, girls.
I want to see, uh, want to see a loser
when I get back.
You can't tell a damn
thing from that photo.
It could mean anything!
Well,
how is it that a third of the men who try
to escape die,
and when the ratio of killing went up,
brown began depositing
money in offshore banks?
Damn it! My battery's dead.
Can I borrow yours?
Doesn't work.
I've been meaning to have it fixed.
What?
Goddamn it, I told you it doesn't work!
Oh, my god!
( Grunting ) ( Screaming )
( Spraying ) Aah! Aah!
You bitch! You bitch!
( Panting, coughing) ( Footsteps )
Uhh!
Oh!
What the hell are you doing here?
I was looking for you!
I know what's going on.
They're hunting people
out here like animals.
Well, gee, now we both know.
Wakefield's in on it, too.
I just got away from him.
Shit.
( Dog barking ) Okay, we gotta get
over the fence.
It's our only chance.
The closest one is northwest.
Let's go! You're being hunted, now, too.
Ow!
You okay?
Yeah.
What the hell are you
carrying in your hand, anyway?
Mace.
How do you think
they'll like our scent now?
They're gonna love it.
Come on!
( Whining ) What in the hell's
Going on now?
Ack!
He's got company, female company.
Oh, yeah?
And who the hell do you think
he's eloping with, that nurse?
Had to guess,
I'd say it was that dern bitch.
Am I hearing you right?
She's been hanging around like a bad smell.
Well, now, cap, we're in deep shit.
I'm outta here.
Hey, quit worrying.
You get two for the price of one.
You'll owe me.
Well, that dumb dog of yours is gonna need
a firecracker up his ass.
And who's gonna light the fuse, you?
Come on.
Clyde's picked up the trail again.
Let's go.
Come on!
You're gonna stick by
me when we're out of this?
Hey, you're my only witness.
Yeah, but are they gonna believe me, a con,
going against state senators and all? A con
and a senator's daughter.
You're a senator's daughter?
There it is.
Yeah, come on.
There's no way I'm gonna make it over that.
You go ahead.
No, no way!
Come on, we'll make it together.
Come on! Uhh! Come on!
Come on!
( Barking ) You hear that?
He's saying we're getting close.
Well,
this is one hell of a lousy deal, cap.
The birds have flown, and not even
a single lousy potshot.
No one's ever made the wire before.
Well, I guess I'd better get my money back
before we have company.
( Chuckles ) My whole world's fallen apart.
You want your money back?
Don't fuck with me, bro.
I got too much on you.
You arrogant prick.
You're in this as deep as I am.
You're gonna help me out,
or you're going down with me.
Oh. And who are they gonna believe,
a respected
pillar of society, or a fucked-up cop
with a reputation for killing cons?
Oh, you might've got away
with it back in Australia, just.
Here, you won't be so lucky, I guarantee.
Okay, Clyde, let's go get our meal ticket.
You and me are going on a long vacation.
Now who's tracking who, boss?
This what you're looking for, captain?
You should've gone over
the fence when you had
the chance, dogboy.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I wanna be here when they
drive you back from diagnostic.
Some boys in the tank
are gonna be real interested
seeing you come in.
Stand up.
Put your hands behind your back.
Uhh!
Now, you drop that, or I'll break her neck.
Let her go.
Stop it, you stupid bitch.
I'll kill her, Taylor, I mean it.
All right, all right.
Calm down.
Now, slide it over here.
Now, turn around and put
your hands behind your head.
Uhh!
Leave it right there, brown.
What the hell are you doing, Adam?
Why don't you just, uh,
keep the little lady company?
Well...
You didn't tell me you
were keeping records.
It was insurance for both of US.
Insurance, my ass.
You were gonna take off with these,
and then what,
blackmail US good citizens
from some safe haven?
Well, that could work for me, too.
Kill. What?
I said kill!
Aah!
Back off!
You shot my dog.
( Screams ) Over there.
You can be part of Clyde's funeral pyre.
( Grunting, banging ) It's locked!
Grab Wakefield's gun!
Okay, move!
I'm gonna blast the lock!
( Rifle discharges ) ( Neighs )
Uhh!
( Barking ) God!
You all right?
Yes!
Here.
Shit! No keys.
They must still be on the warden.
Don't even think about it!
If he makes it to the fence, he's gone!
Yeah, ewing, it's me.
I'm at retrieve.
I'm in the northwest quadrant with Taylor.
I need backup now!
We got a man down and a fire.
Got it, boys, huh?
Got the scent? Track! Track!
Taylor! Shit.
Ha! Ow! Ha!
Aah! Get off! Go!
Get off me!
Down! Ha!
( Screaming ) Release!
Release!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
So, you think you can get me off?
For good behavior?
( Siren wailing ) ( Laughs )
You know...
Hey, what are friends for?