Previously on The Heights...
Can I get some help? I found
him in the gardens at the towers.
I hear the towers send
us a lot of business.
I live in the towers.
12 years. No letter. No phone call.
I had my reasons.
- You snake.
- What are you talking about?
He split the pub, a third each.
Sorry, Mum.
(FAINTLY) I'm sorry.
(SIREN WAILS)
- Hazel Murphy?
- Yes.
Hi, I'm Dr Rosso.
How is she?
Look, Shannon's placenta didn't
fully detach after the birth
and it's caused an infection.
But she's stable now and
under some light sedation
to help her body manage the trauma.
But she'll be OK?
Yeah, she should be.
We'll get her through the night
but she should be fine for
visitors in the morning.
And the baby?
He's in great shape,
considering he's had
a bit of an adventure.
Hey?
You can hold him if you like.
It's alright.
Hazel?
There, bubba.
Love the paint job.
When's your flight?
In a few weeks.
You can have her room
while she's in hospital.
- But once she gets back...
- I'll figure something out.
Oh! Bloody thing.
There we go.
_
Anyway, you know where everything is.
I'll see you in the morning.
(LAUGHS)
I nearly had you.
Mate, I was barely out of second gear.
Hey, what are you up to today?
Applying for jobs.
What happened to that demo gig?
Finished up.
Oh, well, there must be
plenty of work about, right?
There's, like, apartments
going up constantly, right?
No, it's not that, man.
I just hate demolition.
Everyone hates their job.
You don't.
Working in Mum's shop?
I've hated that since I was seven.
Being a teacher.
I'm not a teacher yet.
Yeah, but you will be.
And it's something you want to do.
You might even tell your
mum about it one day.
Alright, calm down.
What is it that you tell her you do?
Business management.
(LAUGHS) Business management.
When are you going
to tell her the truth?
You know what she's like.
I'm just waiting for the right time.
What she's like?
I finished my job three days ago.
My uncle's on my case to get a new job.
You have it good.
You know, someone's going
to have to cover my shifts
when I do my teaching rounds.
Me?
Yeah, you. Why not?
Your mum isn't exactly my biggest fan.
Come over tonight. Put on the charm.
We'll get you a job.
You sure?
Yeah, it's the least I can do
after flogging you in that race.
Mate, you think you flogged me.
See, it's perception.
Next time you play in your socks.
- What are these?
- (LAUGHS)
Yeah, your sister might have
had a bit of a go at those.
Dad, these are brand new.
- Well, I think they look alright.
- I'm... I'm going to kill her.
They look alright.
I mean, look, until Michael Voss 20
years ago, no-one wore white boots.
So you're a trailblazer.
Think of it that way.
You are not coming in with me.
Yeah, I want to talk to Mr Fraser.
He needs to be aware of what you need.
Oh, my God, he's
aware. Everyone's aware.
You sent cerebral palsy
info to the friggin' school.
Morning.
Hey, I think we met the other day.
I was the guy who brought the
baby into the hospital. Pav.
Oh, hi.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Yes, hi. Claudia.
Couldn't help but overhearing.
Mich here has Mr
Fraser for homeroom too.
He could show your daughter...
- Oh, sorry. Sabine.
- Hey, Sabine.
He can show your daughter
there if that's going to help.
- Ciao!
- No... Sabine...
Yeah, look, I can't blame her.
I mean, I take one
look at you and I think,
"Oh, my God, that's embarrassing."
Yeah, mortifying, apparently.
How's the baby?
Happy to report the
little guy's doing well.
Oh, great.
What about Shannon Murphy?
She just... I... I know her.
She's a local girl from the towers.
Yeah, she'll be alright.
Oh, great.
Ah, well, I've got to...
I've got to get to work,
but listen, if you find any more babies,
can you send them to St Vincent's?
'Cause I could use a quiet shift.
(LAUGHS) OK, will do.
- Have a good one.
- See ya.
See ya.
Hazel?
You are kidding me.
Hi, grub.
How you feeling?
OK. A bit groggy.
You look rich.
This? Charity shop.
What's with the key?
It's decorative.
At least you didn't
come back with an accent.
It's there. Just wait.
I knew it.
Why'd you do it?
Mum, not right now.
Shannon?
Hello. My name's Jill Sanders.
I'm with the Department
of Children's Services.
I was hoping that we could have a chat.
Work hard. First million
by the time you're 25.
Will do. I'll be back
after 3:00 sometime.
OK.
Oh, and I invited Ash
around for dinner tonight.
What you do that for?
I can't feed the world.
Alright, we'll go to that new
pho place around the corner.
$15 for pho I wouldn't
serve to my enemies.
White people! Bloody hell.
It's cool. I hear they
put croutons in it.
Alright, see ya.
Sully, bring your friend. I'll cook.
Awesome.
I'm fine.
You've had a pretty rough
go of it, haven't you?
My role is to help support you to
do what's best for you and your baby.
Patch.
Just what we're calling him,
until you give him a real name.
Patch.
That's lovely.
Have you given any thought
to what you might want to do
once you leave the hospital?
Not really.
You'll come home, won't you, with Patch?
That's a lovely idea.
Being home with family support
is nearly always the best option.
Have you thought about
spending any time with Patch
up at the Mother/Baby Unit?
There's a lot of support,
plenty of people that can help.
I can set something up if you'd like.
I guess.
Good.
I'll do that, and I'll pop back in
tomorrow to see how you're going.
OK.
Well, thanks for letting me
come and talk to you, Shannon.
I'm... I'm really looking forward
to helping you and Patch get started.
Bye, everyone.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
She seems alright.
For Child Services.
Will be great to see bub.
Yeah, but I've already made up my mind.
I'm putting him up for adoption.
What have you got next?
Art and Design.
With Bathgate?
Come on, I'm in that class.
I'm trying to remember your name.
All I'm getting is Sparkly Boots.
Yeah, that's my stupid sister.
I quite like them.
Yeah, well, I've got to actually
wear them in front of my footy mates.
Any dude who takes the piss out
of someone wearing sparkly boots,
you gotta question his manhood.
Do I?
What's he afraid of?
That masculinity as a
concept is so fragile
that one guy wearing sparkly
boots has to be slapped into line
or the entire male race will collapse
and all of humanity will die out?
Sorry, you probably
weren't after a lecture.
No, but you gave it anyway.
(LAUGHS)
So what are you at this school for?
I got expelled from Hartford.
For?
Satanic worship.
Fair enough.
Hey, bro.
Two bucks. Thanks.
New kid. Need some supplies?
The health food in the
canteen will kill you.
Got a chocolate, yeah?
Nice.
Two dollars.
Why are you starting
in the middle of term?
She got expelled from Hartford.
Oh, what for?
Streaking.
Streaking?
Thanks.
We playing at yours tonight?
Ah, I've got footy after this.
Well, I've got work, so after that?
- Yeah, sure.
- Easy.
Alright, bud. See you round, bro.
See you.
I'm not completely useless, friendo.
Alright, let's get this out of the way.
"So, what's with the limp, Sabine?"
Oh, that! I have cerebral palsy.
"Wow, does it hurt?"
A little bit, especially when
you treat me like a special case.
Can I get these lectures online?
'Cause I'm really late for class.
Why?
Come on, I can barely
look after myself, Ryan.
Why didn't you come to me?
Really.
Because you told me you
never wanted to see me again.
Once. In an argument.
You know I didn't mean it.
You know the first thing I thought
when I found out I was pregnant?
"I'm going to need some
gear to deal with this."
A lot's happened since you've been away.
What about the father?
Long gone.
I can't be a mother.
It's not fair on the baby.
That's why adoption was always the plan.
And the garden?
Was that always the plan?
It came early and I freaked out
and I just wanted to get rid of it.
I knew that if I put it in
the garden it would be OK.
He is OK.
He's in the nursery now.
He's doing good.
And when you're feeling
better, when you're ready...
I'm not going to be ready, Mum.
I'm never going to be ready.
I know you think that now...
Don't talk to me like I'm a child.
I've made up my mind.
I'm not keeping that baby.
OK, but Tex Wylie is way
better than Professor Nangs.
C'mon! He's an amazing MC.
He helps me do my homework.
Your sister does your homework.
Google does mine.
She's new. I've never seen her before.
Sabine.
I got some notes from
Bathgate's art class to give you.
- Thanks?
- And that's Rose.
She's had a chip on her
shoulder since she wet her pants
in Mrs Giddens' class.
That was year three!
Hey, it's OK, Rose. We accept you.
You wanna walk with me?
- See ya, Rose.
Bye.
I don't have any notes.
I figured.
And Rose is full of herself.
I figured that too.
- Sabine.
- Hey!
So this is it.
What a dump.
It's actually pretty nice inside.
This is Mich.
- Mich, this is my boyfriend, Dane.
- G'day.
Hi.
Nice boots.
- Thanks.
- We off?
Yeah. See ya, Mich.
See ya.
Oh. Hang on.
My mum got a promotion.
That's why I moved schools.
So you weren't expelled?
Nope.
So no streaking?
I'm not making any promises.
Oh, Mich!
(BOTH GIGGLE)
Hey, hey!
I see you... taking stuff to the towers.
Taking stuff to the school.
You're stealing my business!
- They're my groceries.
- Oh, yeah?
Hey!
Staff discount, 7%.
Plus delivery fee too, I bet.
I don't know what you're on about.
I'm watching you!
Still as pleasant as ever.
I reckon she's got worse.
Shannon won't listen.
Don't judge her.
I'm not judging her but it's
not... it's not a spare bike.
It's a baby. You can't
just give it away.
That's judging her.
Sorry.
Do you know anything about the dad?
She wasn't seeing
anyone as far as I know.
I thought I would just come
home, bury Bill and go home.
I didn't think there'd be
all this mess to clear up.
(SCOFFS, LAUGHS)
What?
"I didn't think there'd be
all this mess to clear up."
Is that supposed to be me?
You did a runner, Ryan.
You haven't had to clear
up any mess for 12 years.
I don't have an accent.
You are still the same idiot
you were when you were 10.
- Love a whinge.
- I'm not whingeing.
You used to say that too.
Remember Josh Pomano
pushed you in the river?
Cried for hours.
I was 10. I cut my leg open.
Could not shut you up.
What?
What am I looking at?
Josh Pomano.
Pushed me in the river when I was 10.
And?
You don't remember?
I cut my leg.
It was bleeding. I was crying.
You were always crying.
And then what happened?
I punched him in the face.
(LAUGHS)
Seven years old.
My little sister, the enforcer.
It didn't matter that you were
younger or that he was bigger.
You looked out for me, kept me safe.
That's what Patch needs.
That's what you can do.
You done with your Hallmark moment?
C'mon, Shan.
Save it, Ryan.
I know what you're doing
and it's not going to work.
(WOMAN SINGS IN VIETNAMESE)
Hey, Iris. Just a pack
of rolling papers, thanks.
$2.50.
There you go.
- Hey.
- Hey!
That's... that's twice in
one day. What are the chances?
Ah, look I... Sorry, I
just want the sunscreen.
- Thanks.
- Slip, slop, slap.
That's my motto.
$15.
That stuff's toxic.
You know that, don't you?
Well, it's better than
takeaway, isn't it?
Anyway, I've got a date tonight,
so I'm poisoning my child.
Oh, a date. Nice.
Mmm.
Is that from running
the baby to the hospital?
Oh, no, it's a... just an old war wound.
Are you taking something for it?
Well, painkillers
don't really work so...
How'd you do it?
- Uh, on the job.
- Yeah.
- Professional wrestler?
- (LAUGHS)
No, I was a cop.
Yeah, you should have
seen the other guy.
Two busted legs?
No, he was fine but I could
tell he felt really bad about it.
(TURNS UP VOLUME)
Right.
Well, um, enjoy your
date. Hope it goes well.
Thank you.
Iris, I don't want the sunscreen.
I do want the papers. Yes, thanks.
- Thanks.
- She's out of your league.
You better be sure about this.
Come on.
(BABY FUSSES)
Look at that.
He loves his mum.
Do you reckon you could
sleep here tonight?
I think the hospital lets family stay.
Sure, love.
Whatever you need.
Beautiful soup, Mrs Tran.
Pho.
Beautiful soup, Pho.
Beautiful. (LAUGHS)
Ash is actually looking to get a job.
What do you do?
Bit of everything really.
Bit of brain surgery?
Ha, not yet.
Demolition, mainly.
A bit of construction.
Traffic.
Last week I got to
hold the SLOW/STOP sign.
Ah, your two speeds?
Ah, he's actually hoping to
get into project management.
Yeah, yeah. Uh...
(CLEARS THROAT) Would
love to help you out
with a few things around
the shop if you take me on.
What?
If you wanted to make
some changes, I'm your guy.
What did you mean if I take you on?
To cover his shifts.
I'm a really hard worker, Mrs Tran.
I won't let you down.
This your idea?
Someone's going to have to
cover when I do my internship.
Him?
Yeah, why not?
We're not a charity, Sully.
(SPEAKS IN VIETNAMESE)
It was just an idea.
So was communism.
It was my idea, actually.
Dinner, come to charm you, get a job.
He had nothing to do with it, right?
Right.
Obviously it was dumb.
Just popped him back in the nursery.
Best I could do, sorry.
All the folding beds are gone.
Oh, don't worry about me.
That's me done.
Paige will be taking over.
She'll be in in a minute to say hello.
Just buzz if you need anything.
OK.
I'm proud of you.
- See ya, Hazel.
- Bye, love.
Oh, this isn't too bad.
Shan, why did you come back?
What?
To the pub, after you put
the baby in the garden?
Why didn't you just go?
I don't know. I was all over the place.
I couldn't think.
But I guess in all that,
I just wanted my mum.
I'm sorry you couldn't tell me.
It's OK.
Haven't got much right
over the years, have I?
You're alright, Mum.
Sounds like they're all garbage humans.
Some of them are alright.
Hey. Let me kiss it better.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Hi, Mum.
Hello, Sabine.
Dane.
Hi, Mrs Rosso.
I'd better be going.
- See you tomorrow?
- Yeah.
Bye, Mrs Rosso.
Bye, Dane.
His mum know he was here?
I guess.
Mum.
Sorry.
So, how was your first day?
Fine. Did you make any friends?
It's the first day.
What about Mitch?
- Mich.
- Mich?
Maybe short for something?
- He seemed nice.
- Yeah, I think Mich might work out.
Hug your mother.
Enough.
Never enough. More hugging.
Mum!
Love you.
Go and get ready for your date.
- I can do dinner.
- Are you sure?
You have a lot of work ahead of you.
(SCOFFS)
(TOILET FLUSHES)
- Mich.
- Ah, sorry.
What are you doing here? Does
your mum know you're here?
(PHONE VIBRATES)
Ah, I guess not, huh?
Ah, can we... can we please just talk?
I can't take it anymore.
Is this about the boots?
No, no, it's about...
it's about everything.
Her, Grandad, Mum.
You know, they're all on top of
me and I've... I've got no space.
I just wanna come and live with you.
- Oh mate, you can't just, you know...
- Why not?
Well, you can't run
away from the problem.
So you... you don't want me here?
Of course I do.
Then what's the problem?
Well, it... it's kind of,
um... it's kind of complicated.
There are issues, you know.
Alright, let's talk about them.
OK. Um...
(SIREN WAILS)
♪ Tell me things on the
other side will get better ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm sitting in the car
waiting for you to drive me home ♪
♪ It doesn't look that
pretty where I am now ♪
♪ Where, where did the time go? ♪
(BABY FUSSES)
♪ It's funny how
everyone kept changing ♪
♪ We somehow remained the same ♪
♪ And like you killing me softly
with every word you're saying ♪
♪ We both know we're both to blame ♪
♪ Is it bad? Is it bad
that our minds run away? ♪
Do the cops know about this?
I think it's best we
find her first, right?
Let's go.
Nah, I better start
moving my stuff to Dad's.
- Not how I would have broached it...
- Wait, what?
I'm 60 years old. I'm not doing it.
Sooner or later, Shannon's
going to come back.
Shannon's not coming back.
Do you want to go out sometime?
On your pushbike?
♪ I found my getaway ♪
♪ Hold my hand one last time ♪
♪ We're driving... ♪
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -