We have just arrived at the
12,000 block of Willow lane
where police are
responding to reports of pre
dawn gun fire in this upscale
Canyon neighborhood.
Now, news team has learned that
there was apparently some sort
of
a party that occurred at this
home last night
Details are pretty sketchy, but
I have report that
a coroners unit has been
dispatched to the scene
so we will let you know as more
becomes available.
Every room in this house we got
it all on tape--Is that right?
That's right We are going to go
take a look at it now
no matter what you say-- all
right then you want to see
Tonight is Bill s night man He
deserves it
I'll call you later oh I love
you baby
He is a combination of, like
always put your money on the
right guy at the
right place at the right time
and he's here
moron time to get up for the
party
Shauna Shauna
Jude am not dressed yet
Let me make you a story.
What about the man?
What's the matter with the man
Hmmm, nice bouquet (aahh
Cover this up,will you would
you? I dont want them to see
where I really look
This man is so rich, he doesn't
have season, no tape in his
pants
All right, lets party
Thats what I call a party dress
You are a good person
Is Bueno
Here I come
Stuart honey,
Oh, oh, ooh baby, look at you,
you look gorgeous
That looks good, just taste
Oh my, am so good we are going to party
You ever seen a better looking
couple in your life?
Hmm, I think we are the best
looking couple
obviously
Hi,
Cheers
thank you
Say hello to someone you never
met Say hello to Bill
Hey bill, how are you doing?
It's his party tonight
ahh well Congratulations
Man of the year
Man of the year,
man of the year
from the whole brain core to
you man of the year .
all right look we are having a
party, take him upstairs
No no, you
cant come to the party no that's
no and no
Okay we will take the elavator
up and then get you a jacket.
Are you sure about this?
Am positive its fine. sorry i
didnt tell you I didn't know how
to call you I didn't have your numbers
Well I am on a shift you know
for six months its kind of hard
to get hold of me
No voice mail?
yeah I should have called you.
all right just so you know Bill
is the business patner of
Stewart
all right they have had this
amazing years so he is like man
of the year so it was great idea to throw a party.
Hi I am Flora I am Stewart's
little sister. what do I do you
will never believe it
I am structural engineer I am
anexortic dancer
come on lets go
and I have my degree from
dump your husband on New York
city. ]
how are we down there Joe
very good sir
and I havent met you what is
your name?
My real name is..
your real name will be good
Taka
yeah you can call me Taka
or Ababa or ka or Ba..
ka or.. or Ba
or no no
see these glasses?
mmmh
I dont want to see an empty one
during the party okay?
yes sir.
I want happy guests happy--
those glasses will be full
those glasses are full they will
be happy
very happy.
that will be preatty I like it
okay
open it
okay.
okay
you are the boss see you later
bye
He is my boss, I am your boss
Ooh,
okay
comprende? ,
yeah
take a walk
all right bye bye
no more drinking no more
drinking
hey okey
oh let me get a photo of you
I just want to say I cant stay,
just want to say good bye
Baby be easy
Yeah hello, say hello to Bill
the man of the year, what do
you have to say
What do you have to say about
yourself babe?
I thought it was the town of the
year, I just hope..
If its town of the year you are
a little late, go back outside
I don't know what to
say about me, I couldn't have
done it with all the little people
Not only is he man of the year,
he is also man of my life
the man of your life?
Yeah sure
Tell me why you love this
guyYeah why do you love this guy
Why I love him
yeah why do you love this guy ;.
I don't know
Ooh, what is that baby?
I know I love him because he
loves me
She is showing the ring again?
okay see you upstairs?
Is Nick here?
Not yet We've got the big phone
call from Argentina, this is it
Big call? big call
Yeah, they have not called yet
am awaiting. Then we will know
it looks good so good,
We will turn this into a real
celebration we are in the money
we'll turn this into a real celebration
are we going to a party there?
Do you mind? no I think it will
be good ideas.
- What is happening out to be there for a minute?
-  I am So happy
make a wish make your wish
blue make your wish come true
you saw my ring right?
Ooh my God
I know,
Its huge wow
surprised me, the night I didn't
even know it was coming
Stewart got one of this tasteful
movies on it Hello I am Bill,
I know you, am
Stuart's sister, how you doing?
Okay, eehhh Say hello
hi Bill, you are my man of the
decade, the century
When I met him, I thought he was
a great guy, but he is a great
guy, a good looking guy,
he's great looking
he dress as well. I really love
him.
And Mr Bill will never cheat on
you come on he has you
You know what, I don't think he
will cheat on me If I don't
think he would have an affair
but you know what he probably
would'nt cheat on me now he
looks at me just like
he owns me now just like he
thinks am whore he looks at me
like he loves me
What are you drinking here mama,
let me have a sip of that, Wow ,
Its full scotch ?
You have been spinning all
night, haven't you?
I started early
You started early?
By myself
Did you really? How long are you
in town for
oh hi Bill, I hear that you have
been scheming with the 2.3
million dollars I begged from my father
There he is
This is my wife Carol This is
Spur Stuarts sister
Hi Carol hey hello thst
Congratulations Bill, your ship
is coming, your time has come
You have always
been ahead of your time and the
world has just caught up with
you.
You are more than man of the
year
Hey Bill, Congratulations and I
hope it brings you alot of good
things and
I got to get drinking and I got
to bathroom actually
]
Thank you Stuarts
Thank you dad Making my
testicals the size of frozen
peas
the bathroom is occupied Can I
use your bathroom somewhere
hi is
You are Chloe, '
Man of the year I am going to
have a beer on you
You are fine with this one?
oh yeah okay, Bye. okay Have a
nice day
Events like this where they are
recording, somebody needs to
know me
I am Bill's financial secretary
I am Donah
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Hey scooter
Gasper, oh wow I am glad you
came yeah am excited
I wanted to talk to you in
person,
Yea, want something to drink? ,
You get something, I don't want
anything ,
Hey Bill,
hey how are you doing
Hey baby
Hi honey, how are you? we are
going. is that has to do
yeah and congratulation
Hmm Lovely Girl
I would love to talk to you
later on tonight
yeah right Okay And I had love
to talk to to you later on
tonight
I will be here
I will have a business
conversationwith him at some
point
No business tonight come on
ahh well just no I don't
know anybody here
Welcome, welcome, Nice flower.
how do you all feel? I feel so
much like a dead cow
Sylvia we are not going home
aaaaahhh
What was that?
I think she said you know dead
cow
Coming coming coming Wooh
what did you take you have been
like that all night like a punch
bag what are taking
Just get in
and shut up
what are you taking.
good evening
You wouldn't know where any of
the basketball squares are? No
Baby, we said no gambling
No am just interested, am a
sports man
Hi, nice to meet you nice,
nice to meet you too
Hi, am Stuart John John Stuart
This is Sylvia,
Hi, how are you?
Nice to meet you
It's a joy to meet you Donnah
Hi Bill, congratulations on all
your recent accomplishment
We are going to get a drink now,
very nice okay Bye bye cheers
okay
Hi Shauna, thank you for
hosting us .
So do you really think you can
just hang up on me huh?
yeah she is the vice chancellor
in charge of every thing Well I
don't think so
you can't be here now thing is I
am going to get fired if they
see you here
Arent you happy to see me
Naymar?
No am not happy to see you, I
want you to leave right now
Well, am not leaving anywhere .
What do you mean
I'm staying, something is going
on and I'm going to find out Can
you please
take my coat, Butler Stupid
Hi, Hi, am Ridge
Serita
- Master here, Bill man of the year Do sit down and..
- happy new year have you seen
do you speak english?
How do you know if Shauna
do you know how to make
Hey Jose, can I get some
champagne
Are you single
this is Eddy my new boyfriend
Hii, I said my boyfriend Here we
go
Come here Jose God, you know am
not happy that you invited
Sorita here
I can explain it, she came here
She was not an invited guest
Alright, I need to get back to
work. Go on mmmh mmh
Get up close here sorita you
don't have a boyfriend now?
no if you dont act like one I
don't have one
See, that's perfect no Women,
you can't live with them no you
cant live with them
no come here
oooh my world you all right?
you okay?
This is my first party oh my god
are you okay are you all right
I would like to see your license
and registration I'd like to see
it
coming Hey hey Nick,
Man of the year, I thought it
was pain in the rear You have
to give bill a lot of credit,
Bank one
Hey Nick, Excuse me for a
second I will be right back.
flora.. what? this is my wine.
Hey,
hey
I'm Jim
Chloe
Nice to meet you
Tell me something, the newest
Nothing, he hasn't called yet.
No messages nothing, so he
hasn't called
What time did the guy say he was
going to call?
Sometime this evening.
this evening our time? LA time?
could be their time it could be
our time
So the last time you talked to
him, he said he was going to
talk to Zoro and Zoro
is going to give a green light
right?
he was positive
yes he was
totally positive. I don't see
why this thing is not going to
go through
I don't know anybody here
I know
I don't know what you are so
worried about
people pressuring me.
yeah I know Just relax, we've
got $150 million coming in,
maybe 200.
you said 200million thats what
am counting on
I didn't feel it was in my
position to put them on the spot
to have them commit to a figure
so that means that someone
take your shoes off, take
them off
the last time I was here you
writing me off
take your jacket off Whats wrong
with it Its shady
excuse me its time Excuse me
Excuse me
Do you know this bill guy
No no
So is your phone turned on?
My phone is turned on
are you turned on?
I hardly know you Nick, and yet
when am with you, am so happy
You have seen the girls here
tonight
I have seen this girls tonight
That's why I am so turned
do you guys like magic
Yeah
You guys are just like magic
yeah lets go and do some trick
We like magic all the time
excuse me
go home, why didn't you just go
home How am I supposed to go
I told you to take me home
please please can you just stop.
stoop This is a party Please
excuse us
please sit down
I was thinking of going up to
the roof, it's a nice spot
smoke some pot?
Exactly,
Hell yeah
ones its party time There are
this 4 guys named jack.
again?
and they were going to break
into a building, so they all
rented a helicopter
to land on the roof of the
building and they all said they
would split up that
way they could cover the house
easier. So the first Jack
decided he was going to the basement,
he is the one trying the fancy
wines than the wine cellar.
And then the next jack said he
was going to take the first
floor so he could get
the TV and the VCR and stuffs
like that and the 3rd jack said
he was going to take the
upstairs bedroom cause that's
where all the jewelry is. And
the last jack said,
am going to stand on the roof
and make sure the cops don't
come and catch us
can you just relax can't waith
to get away from all these
people
Ooh my God I cant wait
So, sure enough, the cops came
along So they all came up to the
roof so
that all of the Jacks, get away
from the cops and pull off the
perfect crime
That's was a little bit scary
Ahah,
I think we are stuck
Good lord, that's great but I
think
no its magic
well we've got alarm buttons
that dont work, they don't phone
jack, they don't phone me
The only thing that seems to
work is the light
Would you really?would you? You
want to go at it ? You want to
go for that bastard?
Oh, there is a camera up there
hey there we are
stuck
thank you for
We are stuck in the elevator
Make the elevator go up
Open the door of the elevator
How is it going?
Fine huh
yeah Nice night huh?
Right
That's me filming us say Hello
Bill hey hey
music
This is kind of like a second
home to me
This place?
Yeah yeah
I have never seen anything like
this
I went to the university for
philosophy, which I found again
am here
I found it is a pretty much
useless degree
I would like to regulations
we wouldnt probably be-- I
we were talking about the
grands its like we don't have
enough pipeline You know what energy is?
Energy is That's
energy
Why don't we just relax and make
the best of it
okay
Make the best of it, best this
is the best, party of the year
Why don't we just relax a little
How much pot do you have?
It turned out that the oil and
gas industry was in desperate
need of our services
because a lot of their wells
were in very remote locations
and we have micro turbines
for them but
we could be side driven instead
of front driven
yes exactly but the thing they
also needed fuel for our our
turbines
which they have because they
flare the bad gas that comes out
of the wells it called
farting?
I really wanted to go to school
Well it makes you think about
big things, like you know magic,
just my kind of magic,
like love, the right person is
out there certainly you know
I am so glad that you have large
quanties of levels of
relaxation,
you don't even know me
there is a lot of stress in my
job, so it comes in pretty handy
Ooh really? What do you do?
I am an intelligence officer in
the US marine core
oh shit
I would like to thank our lovely
host and hostess, this is
delicious meal
Thank you thank you
I want a toast to my husband,
my man of the year. I love and
adore him
true love thats love
I am just waiting for the right
man that's why I came here to
find this family
to find the right man to find
someone to fall in love with
Its weird that you feel like you
almost grown up here, like it
was fake or
something that you came out
here. I mean I couldn't stay
longer away
that's why I came out here
Look at your clothing, you at
what you wear. I didn't even
tell you to wear this,
Look at you
Why don't you leave
Why don't you leave?
Why don't you just get out of
this house right now
I have had enough get, am going
to go. you know what? I cant
stand you,
get out
you idiot
right nowget off-- I am so
sorry, I am so embarassed,
please I apologise
You will never ever see this
woman again
here here I'll drink to that
You alright?
Yeah am fine, am fine Jesus
Christ, she embarrassed me in
the party
That was really fucked up
This are my friends and this is
this is my business associate
Hi,I am so sorry,
i am so sorry I --
I just wanted to make sure you
are okay
no, I am fine. I just feel some
bad about everybody, I mean here
we are
trying to celebrate, enjoy
dinner and she is swearing and
throwing stuffs around
you know its okay I'm with you
this time you know
I didn't even guess your feeling
is pineapple
I am going to go to the kitchen
and have something heavy, you
want anything?
thank you for the house
I am going to need more funding,
Thank you very much, take care
If there had been any other
marines within a thousand yards,
you would be
black and fucking blue
Oh my God you know what.
the suite fits,
I think it suits its better than
on me
its Pretty good
look You don't know some real
ass spy okay
You know I know a lot of, don't
do that okay. Don't do like you
don't like me
What's your name
what do you know about the
marines?
Do you even remember my name
I am Emma,
Emma, Jonathan
do you remember my name?
Che- Chelsea
And I see you have finally put
the pineapple down
Chloe
my friend, my only friend
chloe was your Yes I remember
your name
I want to live in or St.
Monicah sometimes
I know its exotic sometimes you
know what I mean
the ocean wake up, have a man in
bed with me who would just say
morning Donnah, I love you, you
are beautiful
You want anything, can I get a
drink
Sure,
I can use a drink
Am sure you could
I have a toast,
Ooh toast,
Don't treat me like a child
please I have a toast
Bill I have three things that
are very important to say. First
of all I would
like to toast my wonderful
brother
Thank you very much
Thank you for the hospitality,
thank you
and I would like to say that I
hope with all my heart that the
woman
of your dreams who you deserve
very much
I hope she shows up in your life
soon.
Secondly, I would like to offer
a toast to our mother who is
almost dead.
thirdly I would like to offer a
toast to our man of the year Man
of the year
hear hear hear
Let me tell you something, I
would really like to offer you a
gift or
something that I know you
admired when we were in the
living room.
oh my God am so sorry Its all
for you Am so sorry, she should
be piping
You don't do this, you want me
to take your dress off you right
now?
I am going to take off your
dress
hey hey hey-- guys guys Will you
sit down
Yes you will and you would
apologize to everyone at this
table
I apologise
That's alright, it's the most
unforgettable toast I have ever
heard.
Thank you very much, thank you
You are my hero
thank you very much-- thats
beautiful
everybody come down
You alright
so we will not be having desert
tonight
Ooh my God
I feel so much better than I did
before
I have been a democrat I mean
they take your people, its
people issues its republican
Democrats are Curly cocker in
this state didn't they
he has a point--Yeah well you
know
I was surprised you are still
here
I got no way to getting home you
know We do this all the time,
all we do is fight we
anymore
Democrats are the only ones that
have sense, republicans don't
Don't believe everything I told
you
You are a republican?
I thought what's the best
I am a republican,
well yeah I vote
republican because I know which
side of my bed my butter is on
No no no, I know what you are
saying Yea that's right
Were you drinking tonight?
No I quit drinking, I don't
drink any more. I haven't drunk
in like 8 hours. I stopped
For me,its not the flashing bang
just to have waking up to
beside somebody sick and taking
care of them
waoh oh yes
Watching them get older daily,
wrinkles?
yes having wrinkles together
laughing together laugh like
knowing that its your joke that
put that laugh
Ooh, I know it would be so
wonderful, I hope I find a man
like that
Pass me the bread please,Thank
you so much
Yes someday
So, what was that about?
Its communication, you know we
don't communicate well He
doesn't get
me, and I think he is just such
a ..he is not a sympathetic
person.
And I feel like I wanted got
with him this far I dont even
know am telling you this is bad
No no no please, am asking this
question, its okay
I have an older sister I am the
youngest child
Older sister younger child,
older sister youngest child
there is 2 of you
To have greed is to have
ambition to want to succeed to
want to drive
the other guy in the back we
agreed--we agreed-- not to be
negative
Greed is more than just that
Greed is just got a bad press
Greed is taking more than you--I
dont think it is-- need
that is greed more than you need
there is more than I need I
don't think it is-- thatis
why
Our system is based on a lack
of powers
oooooohh......... mmmmmmmhhhh
Who did you come here with Phill?
My wife
Your wife, right you are married
Vanessa,
am sorry
don't you works for these people
No no
l figured you work for the
foreign office or something
Jonathan works for them
Jonathan in the green suit
yeah
the green suit I see right
no no, I didn't dress him in
that, I suggested he wear
something, a little bit more
thats okay My Wife dressed me
tonight am alright am alright
She did a nice job
since I met Bill my life took a
whole different direction,
I don't know about anybody else
here hear hear
My life would go whatever
direction to leave with Carol
Now my life is taking a
different direction
You are my dream
We all lost Bill when he met
Carol
I have to say that Bill
introduced me too late
In what way?
The first woman I went out with,
we double dated
with the same woman? Are you
going out with anyone now?
No I believe in catch you
release-- another change that
really is
Catch you catch you-- he olny
likes prostitutes-- He is open
about this
he is open about this
You know the thing about
prostitutes?-- what? They are
cheaper
That's true,
You know what Bill? you know
what.
Then what-- Nick--Then what?
good evening, am Micky am here
for the party
Sure just follow the noise right
this way
Mickey Micky what are you doing
here?
I just decided to walk in. did
you invite him?
oh my God how are you just join
us join us we are celebrating
a friend I know Have a seat,
we have got a lot of food drinks
No no No No--come on
seat and eat -- Am not
drinking-- Mickey take a seat
Why don't you seat down?
You are all married
Jose, Jose, bring some more
liquid here-- mikey how're you
doing
You are not going to throw a
drink on me right?
No
I probably could use it actually
You are not going to call me a
bitch are you?
We are celebrating you right,
that's right--we are
celebrating--the man of the year
You didn't hear?
He is The Man of the year, Man
of the hour--just hey micky
micky-- man of the day
remember you are celebrating me
be nice to me okay? all night be
nice
Bill, who is your friend? ,
You buddy
why is that?-- thats rubbish can
I see you for a second?
Sure--I just want to talk to you
Get this out of the way way and
go party alright?
okay-- I just want to talk to
you for a second I would be
right back Now keep your panties
Ehh ehh-- you know what I
thought you said no business am
sorry lets take this up and keep moving
am so glad lets get this done
with --come on take it up and be
done with-- we done in here
I'd like to kiss you right now--
I should tell you
--You would probably get nothing
from me
that am a virgin ,
story of my life Phil
Am sorry it aint my story. My
story is a bit different and
Alright, so I understand
seriously You have no idea
Would you tell me
No
its a beautiful time
I tried to exclude you I just
couldn't tell you.
does this scare you?
You know we are strangers-- you
can tell me because that means
nothing
I'll never see you
again--That's the sweetest thing
I have ever had
So if you kiss me right now, you
would never see me again
Guys lets move over, lets move
the party to the living room
Ooh Jesus Christ
A couple of nice people of
Ooh I haven't noticed,
You are not doing bad for
yourself ahh, I heard you are
the a little of the Peruvian
merchant howdy mmmmh
Thank you doctor
Wait a minute, this is from
Guatemala? Then you should
fucking not be smoking this shit
Why?
Because they probably have
some,
Guatemala is just a land of
under privileged, war torn
people.
and these pot is probably lazed
with castrogenes and ozone shits
that's not good for us
am so glad you are here
Stuarts sister sounds so good,
so sexy and sweet you know am
just staring out here
I just feel like am falling on
my face Sorry,
listen
I am sorry I have not returned
calls to you its just that you
dont know how pressurized
this whole Argentinian thing is,
but Nick is expecting a call and
its really going to be
any minute from the guy Joe
outside of west she is dealing
with this any minute right that joe?
Ready to check it, teeth Teeth,
teeth you are good Clothes,
boobs am I good you are good .
Okay remember Joan I work with
this people, we cant get too
drunk maintain
I have to tell you
something--What? I took a half a
tab of ecstasy in the car,
I have the other half You, do
you want it?
Don't ever try to mock me like
that Am not playing around Its
not even
funny--whats wrong with
you--cause I work with this
people okay Just chill--
Okay,Just be normal And if
anybody, just ignore
Hey, Yeah I know and I --
Its not about me being upset
Bill, its about me being unpaid
Yeah and you are going to get it
you are going to get it We have
in our possession
hi-- we have in our posesion but
we dont know how to grasp about
250 thousand dollars
tomorrow and I can give that to
you
Don't, that is a 100thousand
less than the amount you owe me.
Can you fucking count for me,
can you count for
You know we are sitting on a
gold mine and
because you have been there for
me,
I want to tell you something
that I think you should
This really doesn't suit you,
you are really good at what you
do well that may be true and
that may be so but let me
you had this kind of episodes
with the guys you are with and I
know you are with a lot
of tough tough ass guys and
stuffs like that
How did you know Bill
Vannesa my wife works for bill,
Ooh Vanessa, very beautiful lady.
Ooh thank you very much, I
didn't do anything that wasn't
my doing
and If this thing in Argentina
goes well, you are in town there
with me, you are working with me,
you and I are partners
do you work for Bill?-- that
means
No, I put up the money in--wait
We are partners now?-- Bill's
company
You are kidding me
I have known Bill for a long
time and I bankrolled Bill many
things
You are in LA right now, you owe
me $350,000, I want my fucking
money
he is the Chef you know he has a
gorgeous wife, gorgeous career
First priority man,
you know about business its all
on paper
Dude like you probably be like
what if you know, what if my
shoes came from a fucking dead
cow slaughtered and massacred,
living in a 2 by 2
area that is smaller than this
lift we are in so that you could
wear them on your feet. I mean you know
How is that working out?
I don't know, you tell me
no no am serious,you are a guy,
an investor, how is it working
out?
I dont know thats why I am here
Now what does that painting mean
to you?
Breast, you guys like that
Breast,
this leaks obscene word--breast
look at your boots,they go very
well with this whole outfit
you know what am not going to
let you
perhaps they are from a cow too
You know what what about
this boots, this boots are like
statements themselves
I can give you 350
Bill listen to me, listen to me
you are fucking jambaring on,
you are talking to me about
Argentina, about the culture
there-- where is this coming from?
Do I look like a bank to you?
You look like a reasonable man
I make bets-- yeah yeah I am a
reasonable man--all right I have
been very reasonable with you
I know you have--you understand
that?-- yeah
Its your money or its your
family's money
its my family's money, strictly
speaking
I haven't seen you here yet
I just got here. you did You
know somebody here?
We get to make 10 turbines, each
one is $50 million, thats half a
billion dollars that what you make
So you have been married long?
Yeah for 5 years listen Can we
get back to the money thing for
a second?
Sure, we had rather talk about
women but you talk about money
We can talk about other women I
don't want to talk about my wife
No, I wouldn't talk about your
wife
I just, are you involved in
energy business?
No I just wondered what would
happen if I gave Bill 2.3
million
are you going to get half a
billion dollars tonight?
No, we are going to get the
phone call that is going to
give us the green light
You are going to get a phone
call-- I dont want to bore you
with-- Please bore me with it
The guy who is going to call the
gun shot he is Argentinian, he
is working for the guys in government
called Zoro the guy zoro You
don't need to know their names
cause alot of people are protective about their names
But this guy loves me, we were
down at the party, we were
talking about the energy crisis and that's it
What does this have to do with
me?
Whats your name?
Von--Von, hi Ella
Are you drunk Ella?
No
Are you sure
I absolutely have to thank you
for demonstrating your hatred of
leather by wearing it.
you know what I --It's a bold
bold move
You really think so? Or you
making fun of me
You want to give 2.3million to
somebody? you want to give 2.3
to somebody
Sure I mean for something that
really works, you want to get
your money back right?
I want a big profit
You just have to relax, this is
not a shade, you know where I
live. I know that I owe you this money
Well you know what I didn't get
an invitation tonight and I had
to fucking go looking for you.
Its not my party Micky
Yes am making fun of you And if
you are truly trying to prove a
point then'
Am not talking to you right now,
I'm no longer talking with you
Jimmy
Can we talk?can we talk Sure I
mean this is unbelievebale
Hey..Hey honey how are you you
met mitch?
Mitch this is my husband Phil
yes We were just talking about
you and turbines
and turbines and turbines
a little bit about money
Outside a relationship, who do
you trust more? Men or women
Let me give you the bottom line
what is the bottom line
I want my money-- I know --If I
don't get my money Bill, you are
going to be attending a different kind of party
Okay
I am going to leave you both and
I would see you insider
Maybe we would talk later, yeah
oh yeah you in town for a while?.
A while-- You live here?-- No,
am from
Ridge is from new york
Am a friend and I am here for
you , but I want myfucking
money-- Okay
And as soon as you find out
about this fucking phone call
I'm telling you, you are going
to get it
You look at me and you let me
know allright
I don't trust anybody,
especially not men
Ooh fuck, why did you come here,
why did you come out here I
don't know what you were talking
about he kept asking me
questions I didnt give anything
away
I was this close this close
To what? This close to what
Don't wander out of my fucking
eye sight alright, I want to
know when the call comes in and I want my money
You will be the first to know
Why don't you trust men?
you guys are smooth and you lie
I have a nice going on I have a
really good I had a good time
happening
thanks to people like you thanks
to me its in shit all at ones
Remember we talking about just
being able to be infront of it,
to be in beginning of something
and you know to buy Microsoft
when it wasn't Microsoft
Yeah--That was my fucking moment
right there
How was that your Microsoft
moment? How did I screw that up
I can't beleive you came right
there and then-- I don't know--
what fucking timing do you have
Thanks man we'll get it
together oh shit
I don't want to make you upset,
we get it together
Absolutely You? You are yet to
think about that if you are yet
to think about that,
that proves my point Who do you
trust, men or women? .
He was talking to me and he
left, and I just thought about
him talking to you
I didn't want him to question
you. I thought I was doing you a
favor
- He just looked at me like I was a fucking idiot.
-  Hey, who is your wife?
You know what I feel--you are
the vice president--am just like
all right
something going on here we
go now everybody dance
music
- Yes, get it together, you can pull this off.
-  Just think about it come on you think about it Oh God
throwing up
music
who said we were going home and
who are you to be giving orders
every time
hey Ridge listen whats going on
with you?you are the only person
here who knows who I am
for better or for worse and I
have to tell you that am dying .
I have to ask you this question
listen,
listen to me Ridge I am I need
$500,000 or am going to die ]
music
shit okay nice meeting you in
here
how do you know Bill?
I work with him
you work with him?
but dont tell him I work with
him because
I got a very big gambling debt.
What?-- I have made some very
stupid bets.
How many times have I bailed
you?
I know and I paid you back I
paid you back every time 50%--
more than 50%
come on Ridge
am having a good time at the
party now
good am so happy
you are such a good magician
I can make a lot of things
disappear
oh you want to be maid?
oh oh I want to be maid
Okay okay you play maid and I
will tell you what to clean up.
Are you okay? Cause am not
going to judge you am not going
to do that
you just you are judging me
if I did that then am sorry.
here we go okay go
well its
am your first
well that's marvelous I feel
better already
I told you to give on gambling
I did it just this one I thought
it was a sure thing and it would
have been except that
there were some injuries we got
a big show to promote starring
pictures and I thought that
you gambled on baseball stupid
I know man I know it's not polo
but fuck its America's past time
I want to take our shoes off
because they are both leather
and they are both wrong
so who are you
excuse me excuse you
we got a lot of dishes in there
yeah you want to help me wash
these dishes sure you magic boy
yes so I can feel at least real
if you can write me a cheque,
cash or check I can pay you
well you don't have bank
Bill is a great guy
how did you meet him yeah
hey how is it going
beautiful house you have a
really beautiful house thank
you-- this is something else
thanks I know but am mmh mmh
you alright?
Too many people out there you
know.
Look at me am working sometime
my keeper out here huh so ah
where did you go? where did you go?
no more dead cows no more
dead cows
you have a smoke yeah
ah very married Check your
days
you have $2.3 million of my
money right?
That's right that's business you
going to get that back you are
my partner in that that's
what is this? .
This is an insurance policy. .
An insurance policy?
I want you to sign this policy
in unlikely event of something
happening to you
You are Vanessa's husband aren't
you?
Yeah I am Vanessa's husband.
She is a nice girl
yeah yeah she is great
I will be paying back are you
kidding
you are like my brother I will
pay you back
all right am going to get out of
here who is with me rock and
roll listen Vicky listen
I want you to come up I want you
to see my place I will have you
out don't leave
without coming to say hello to
me me first all right
all right see you later
when I first saw you in the
kitchen I was like wondering
what your deal was
what do you mean you thought I
was gay?
Well I didn't know because you
very put together you look like
jay Cruz kind of gq
this is not even my jacket.
it's a lot of work getting a man
to commit isn't it?
I was easy I was into it
you were easy?
Yeah I was I wanted the
relationship.
No you are going to deal with me
and you are going to sign this
don't make sick we are friends
we don't sign papers like that.
Then friend's sign you don't
have to ask me.
I gave you my word here
that's my word here that's my
word you don't have to give me
that-- sign it
mmmh mmh
hey hey you alright no no
no
fuck am not gay okay? Just am
not am a marine
okay you could definitely be
both but that statement marine
and gay not that am saying
am sorry
hey are you all right like
Shauna bitch
you guys are married?
no no
really? No no how long have you
guys been together?
oh God two years two years two
years and I don't see marriage
coming any time soon imagine that?
do me you are the best ever
mmhh
don't be sheep shagger is this
what what are you doing
]screaming is that it just get out some friend
you make me sick your crotch
hanging out you hairly ass
you want to have kids
oh yes oh my god it's a
How many kids do you want?--
life's dream
how many kids
Three, three but I don't think
that going to go well with
Stuart
sylivia --how dare you-- its
over just get out of here it's
all right darling why don't you stick it all night long.
you know what am sorry am
trying to like calm down and be
like a normal girl you look okay .
- you deserve each other you will get love is that it?
-  You will get more after the boy
Stop talking you want to watch
stay around.
You don't have kids do you?
Mmhh
I didn't think so see.
I am straight. I am straight
You think that am attractive?
Yes I do.
Vanessa
this is about me and you
what is going with you?
I wanted to tell you something
and I want it to be good news
but am afraid that it's not
I need good news go a ahead. I
need good news like you don't
believe go ahead
its not the first thing they ask
for when they see a woman right?
Hey honey can I knock you up?
I don't know I kind of thats
probably a good question right?
you make me sick thank you bad
ass
you know how much I love you I
love you so much you are my best
friend
now if were cavemen don't you
think that would have been a
thing they grab you by hair and go ooh
all I know is that you guys like
to use it but the consequences
just scare you away.
I am pregnant and it's yours and
am going to keep it.
Sweet heart oh God swry I love
you so much I love you so much.
You are beautiful attractive and
interesting
really You think am beautiful
and attractive and interesting?
thanks for the smoke Stuart is
going to wonder where I am so I
better get back inside
you are really beautiful
--thanks
I just don't understand how you
got pregnant now of all
times--oh crap --the worst possible time
what am I am I going to do?
you know what you are going to
do --no-- you have done it
before you know what to do
aww this this beauty so nice I
love the fabric so beautiful
come on
aww look at the candles the
candles are so beautiful .
can I show you the ring Bill
gave me?
Aww--isn't it gorgeousI know.
If I do this with carol now and
you do with Phil we are
nothing.
Do what Carol now?
Leave her for you
yeah what do you have with her
anyway?
Let me tell you something.
You know what she can have what
he has with you with a piece of
bubble gum.
Let me tell you something
music
hey
do you think I am in shape to
raise a kid now?
Oh baby I can do it I know I
just need you to say it's okay.
It's okay I love you very much
please not the way to go into
this.
There is really no room in here
way to go idiot .
I am going into it
no honey you can't do that.
do it by myself.
You cannot ruin your life like
that
It's not going to ruin my life
it will be something real.
Paris, Italy France and if we
have time may be Germany
We just won't do it this time
it's like destroying blue prints
we will make up another batch okay?
Get your other magic trick funny
boy yeah
am like a delicate flower
right? say am like a flower
I cant aaahh
you are my baby you are my
partner you are my lover you
know all of a--but am not sudden
worth having achild with me what
not now
what do you want more do you
know
how much time we spent on this
Argentina deal
so what?-- We get a phone call
and all that changes all that
this has nothing to do with that deal
just wait is there any way we
can say that it's Phil's for
right now?
queen of hearts men she is out
there
oh my god Jimmy I cant God
sorry
you totally screwed that up man.
That kid is not going to see the
light of day that's all that
there is to it okay?
One of us is going to go down
what are you threatening
me--you have
no idea you have no idea of what
is coming down on my head
you know what I can see that for
a second
ooh sure Bill got it for me
- you are not sure that somebody.
- You are embarrassing me .
no its-- no Bill its beautiful I
mean look at -- no am sorry i
just
It's so big isn't it? bigger
than a door knob
okay go ahead take a look
its nice --beautiful
thank you I know I can put it
there yet
Just because I love you know
what I mean
you know love
I know because I love you. I
love you.
I just can't do it
you don't think am a delicate
flower.
You know you are what you are
oh God
you are, you are
you don't think am a delicate
flower
come here
no no I don't want you to
touch me get away from me.
so as your position change in
six years you do the same
thing you did six year ago?
A little bit better in the
back yes and Bill
what's that?
No you don't smell like Bill.
I only smell like cigarettes
you need more wine
A little bit okay
am here for you
I know
and always have been
yeah
giving you alot of last minute
am giving you a lot of time to
bring $350,000 down here
tv speaking
this is the best nights of your
life it looks like it's the
worst what's going on?
can you loan me some money?
loan you some money we are a
phone call away to the biggest
pay of your life.
You are never going to need
money for as long as you live.
She is pregnant
carol? great. what?
The other one.
Vanessa?
Yeah.
I got to be honest with you
because I kind of wasn't I am
marine and I am an intelligence officer
but my socks match my shirt for
a reason.
Put it together Vanessa you got
to tell Phill. He is going to
kill Bill, he is going to kill me first
you ready to be a father?
She is ready for me to be a
father.
No no no
are you ready to be a father?
It's not going to happen
how could you do this? You are
used to be so smart you are such
a stupid woman
I am a little coordinated
what are trying to say?
Hey? Is something worrying you?
What have I got to worry about
I think I might be I think I
might be gay.
- Hey go and be with your friends okay?
-  She is going match it's all going to come out.
Ohh crap
she got a husband just say its
Phil's kid she can say it's
phill's kid
the guy his hardon is like
mashed potatoes. This guy has
been impotent for like 3 years
may be she is fucking around but
he doesn't know who he is
fucking around with
she would have a baby with any
one
I just can't deal I just I can't
deal with that right now.
Fuck this is a night and a half
hello, hello
Brenda aah great
you know what why don't you
just listen come here
hey
how are you doing?
Not so good
really?
Yeah
you dont like the food?
I think about it but we haven't
done anything but
it's okay to think about it
I just really.
Its ok I mean
I love how is amazing
its fine I have been waiting an
hour I have been waiting for an
hour Frank
I want an answer okay don't play
with me.
Carol have some different news.
Are you okay?
Aww So sweet
no I have been waiting for your
call all evening everything
okay? Eh no I can talk
I came here to do a job and am
here to do a job am getting
started
well let me tell you you're
doing your job and I will get
you your money this guy is waiting for
Don't worry about what you
think is wrong or right just let
everything be
open you know you like an open
best soul
am pregnant and it's your
husband's and am going to have
it am so sorry.
I know I remember his daughter
we had a deal you understand me?
You know we had a deal is? come
in get the job done get the
fuck out
I have been hanging around I am
not hired to come hang around a
party for an hour do you got it?
You know what you are hired to
do what the fuck I tell you to
do you understand me?
And this guy waiting
oh oh we are not done yet all
right? I want you to understand
something you and I
are supposed to be on the same
side so act like it act like it
I need things.
You are sorry you are pregnant
or you are sorry its bills
I would like to be happy that
its Bills I love Bill I would
like to be happy with Bill I am sorry
oh no no no you got to be
kidding me what happened what do
we have to do?
Do you want bill?
I don't think Bill really wants
me the only thing I know right
now is that I want that little baby
you are getting paid by me to
do what I tell you to do so when
I tell you to do that kill him
hey you know what he is getting
some sort of a presentation
or award thing just wait till
after that all right?
You got it let me do my job you
go enjoy my cocktail okay? Go
talk to the pretty girl or something
oh it is Mickey oh its today is
mickey day
am so sorry no am in shock.
Am so sorry
I can't make you feel any better
Vanessa.
Yeah I will talk to you soon bye
I can't stay with you.
What is the matter?
I heard what you guys were
saying about the man of the
year.
Is something wrong?
No I got everything
are you sure?
No am fine.
If you say so
mmmmh yeah you okay?
bubbles Yeah I love it.
You ready? Let's do it
you are drinking so much
I don't want you to do anything.
people hear things that they
don't want to hear they say
things they don't mean
I heard what you said
would just take it easy
if you do anything to Bill
anything.
Bill is my friend
I got the phone call.
What's up?
Am in fucking shock
go ahead baby
everybody in the water oh my god
there you go aww that's good
she is going to have his baby he
wanted a baby
You didn't hear me say anything.
am blonde but I am not stupid--I
said nothing-- okay?
I said nothing you know what
Gina-- I heard you-- Come on and
get another drink
there is no deal
there is no deal it fell through
our deal fell through?
Yeah we fell through
what do you mean fell through
now what are we
really partying?
we are really partying, I am
partying
Sheryl can party
you talked to the guy and they
said they are not going with us?
Yeah I talked to the guy
well what is the problem?
Zorro is the problem no not
Zorro you are the problem you
are the fucking problem
just take it easy just take it
easy what the fuck happened?
You remember when we were down
there in September?
Yeah
and you were hitting on some
girl?
It was a party
yeah it was a party you were
hitting on some girl do you
remember?
She looked like Sonya Brown?
She was Zorro's daughter
he got right
it was Zorro's daughter for
Christ sake I don't care whether
you are
fucking innocent in that or not
so what did she say? She didn't
seem to mind when we were down
there.
It's not what she said it's what
is in the note she committed
suicide you fucking stupid fuck
she-- you fucking offended their
culture this man is so fucking
up sad it's so unbelievable
I will just pretend everything
is perfect we'll keep going and
you will be happy and
I want to dust off my resume and
may be get a good attorney
am tired of been a sanitary
engineer-- calm down-- I am
tired of been the sanitary engineer
cleaning after you all the
fucking time I loved you like a
fucking brother man
don't you raise your voice
where is my fucking voice the
whole bottom just fell off this
fucking company.
this company doesn't stand a
chance it's not going to recover
from the
fucking debt it went to trying
to do this deal fucking here--
Bill
I got to get on a plane you are
alone
you spineless punk Jesus Christ
oh shit
come back okay?--okay-- come
back ooh come back okay okay
I want to see the policy you
have I have been thinking about
it you are right
this should be finalized with my
idiocy cause you are my friend
yougot to get something back
this should be finalized with my
idiocy cause you are my friend
yougot to get something back
I am happy with you.
Right I know you do I can be
your delicate flower if you just
let me grow
Music
hey there
aww hi excuse me you just move
over that way just move over am
cold
aww hi excuse me you just move
over that way just move over am
cold
music
oh are you okay?
Now you go home huh?
Yeah that's right
I am not going to hurt you
unless you want me to
hi aah ahh thank you for
coming now I hope I can.
hey mickey it's not going to
happen it fell apart so you know
where to find me
hey mickey it's not going to
happen it fell apart so you know
where to find me
honey I got to go we need to get
out of here
can somebody please come here
music
she is taking all this shit she
is taking drugs
come on
am fine am fine --come on--
leave me alone-- throw it out
throw it out
Phil
you are not going to lecture me
about this party
no am not going to lecture you
mmmmhh Phil crap am pregnant and
its Bill's and I want it
no am not going to lecture you
mmmmhh Phil crap am pregnant and
its Bill's and I want it
we are going to take a break
yeah
what kind of party tonight huh?
Am sorry I suck am a bad wife am
a bad person am a bad everything
but I would like to be a good
mother I am so sorry
seems to be a lot going on.
there is alot going on
I am really sorry what a
horrible way I just told you oh
god
when I was a kid I'd always go
to horror movies
I don't know if I ever told you
about this but there is this one
movie this
woman was married to this guy
who was actually not from earth
I don't expect you to forgive me
or love me or anything
shut the fuck up
and lots of people die finally
he rips off his face I did this
horrible thing
I have to tell you but that's me
you think you are just going to
put it all out all right put it
all out you are fine
that was nice
you know I will ask you the same
question that I asked Vanessa.
Vanessa?
What are you talking about?
You know about Vanessa?
That you are sleeping with her
yeah I know about that one yeah
that was a special one
but I think the thing that
really got me she is carrying
your baby
that got me too.
I have slept with a chic
really?
and I liked it
and you don't consider yourself
gay? No am not gay.
All I have done is think about
with this guy I haven't even
done anything
I have done it am talking about
I have done it.
All the way?
it's not much I haven't done
there is a very angry guy
running around here who want to
slit my throat
mmh--because I owe some very
very bad angry people really
dark evil
people a whole lot of money so
I don't care about the money
Bill I care about you and me
and how could you do that we
talked about having kids
yeah whatever happens in the
future I didn't mean to hurt
youit's just my nature monster of the year
yeah whatever happens in the
future I didn't mean to hurt
youit's just my nature monster of the year
I totally get it I do
this wouldn't have happened
I hate you I hate you
I appreciate it really there
is no one saving me it's not I
would rather be left on my own
come on its cold
now you are going to save me you
are the hero
meeting you in this elevator is
probably the best thing that has
happened to me in a long time.
Shut up.
What would you do if money were
no object?
Really?
mmh
do you see this
I would open up a fashion store
its yours
just like that?
Sure
mickey I need to talk to you
no he is sending his wife now?
Look Bill told me everything
about the debt everything now
you don't know me
and I don't know you but I love
Bill nothing bad can happen to
him.
Nick got the call
the call?
Yeah it's not happening he
flipped out --what do you mean
he flipped just-- I don't know
I don't know he said it's not
happening
why why?
He said that you want to know?
Yes I want to know.
they said that this girl
who I had thing with at this
party get she killed herself and
the note implicating me
I know it's probably not
enough but I think probably most
of it I'll get you the rest I promise
this you got to know this is
just this is the big comedy of
all
her father was that guy he was
Zorro he was
the government guy he was the
green light guy he turned red on
us and--
I put my faith in you I know I
put my trust in you I put my
money in you.
Yeah I know
nice ring Bill is very lucky to
have you
baby --there you are come on
lets go to a party thanks for
having us bye
how could you get men
Serious me do you know how this
makes me look?
I can't quite figure out
everything right now but I think
I know one way out
Bill there you are come on its
time for presentation
Oh look at this man of the year
what did you guys do?
look at this-- man of the year
look at this
what a year what a year take a
look at where we were a year ago
a year ago and how
far we have come you know some
men some men have their place in
life
thrust on them you could say the
position may be bestowed on them
some men some few very few very
special men create their place
from within
maybe we should say from hope
and then some men very special
men share that
place all those around them and
loved ones their friends their
business associates
people who have counted on him
he has been responsible too
I figured who Bill is he is such
a man he has touched so many of
us here tonight has he?
so let me give this to Bill our
man of the year
yes it is good to know that I
didn't do it and I couldn't have
done it alone what is here oh my God
special gift for special man
look at this this is beautiful
I know you didn't want the
well if everybody can see I
cannot tell you what this means
to me
hey hey there is a
black out what happened?
Hey who was that? Who got the
gun who got the gun
did you are doing up there what
is that-- I dont know
somebody got the gun who is not
here
are you kidding me?
I know what you want you want to
kill me
man of the year congratulations
on the real beauty there
oh Phil just wait on the that
gun-- the fuck--
you think am weak get the fuck
off-- its my change over
its my change
you can't change shit
yeah I can
what the fact do you know about
me you you got every fucking
thing yeah you got
every fucking thing you got my
fucking wife you got a fucking
baby anything else you want?
here take this no wait wait no
no you can't do it --the fuck---
do me then do me do me not you
fuck you listen to me I know
about
everything you got to have this
baby with her she wants the baby
she really does love you she
knows that am no good she
knows-- son of a bitch,
listen to me listen to me
I fucking can't get it up I know
I can't fucking get it up
it's all right it's all right
let me help let me have this let
me have this Phil.
I can't even get it up and it
sucks
I know I know hey you got to
pull it together and be there
for her she is a good woman
much too good me you are a good
guy you are a good guy. come
here
Phil Phil Phil
take care of this baby-- all
right that's-- what she wants
she needs you
I don't want to to hear you talk
about it anymore okay? Am fine
am fine am fine
music
What the hell was that?
Jesus I guess he beat me to it
am out of here
no no no no
it's okay it probably went off
by accident guns go off by
accident
no you can't die noooo
hi Bill you are my man of the
decade the century the new
century and
I have known you longer than
anyone else
congratulation Bill your ship is
coming your time has come
you've always been
ahead of your time and the world
just caught up with you.
Bill congratulations from the
whole marine core to you
the whole marine-- core great
guy
I guess that Bill and again he
is my boss I have to suck up to
him so what can I say
man of the year I can't believe
it
congratulations for the wife for
the career and what's more is in
my estimation
hi Bill you have always been
this am really proud of you you
are great.
hi are you the man of the hour
or the man of the year
man of the year am going to have
a beer on you
he is a really good boss am
really happy to work for this
company thank you so much
and I know he is thrilled to
have you.
what do we
don't tell him but he is man of
the year and he is the man of
my life
everything was a lie
this is going to be an exception
night I know it and
why----you never leave
me you promised
music
you are still there you all
this work to do what huh?
can we go on a rich break and
then out there in the pool?
I got $4000 I know I got enough
money from all this the baby can
have the operation
I love you toto lets go home
now
our top story this morning
police report a local energy
executive found
dead in a Hollywood hill
swimming pool details are still
unavailable
the California electricity
situation continues on day 152
of the so called
crisis more rolling black outs
are expected here in LA as the
legislators
continue their hearing on
Sacramento.
Now we are going to have the
best
that was the best
Power companies executive and
energy brokers
are likely to face a grilling by
law makers about charges price
gauging
and manuplation but only if the
investigators have the right
question
ohh baby this time you are going
to stay beautiful.
I know who gets my vote for the
man of the year
we are going to party
as usual the authority says
there is nothing to worry about
just another perfect day in paradise
[song playing[