This is the last time I do that vulgar
contradict allegations.
I have no sexual relations
had with that young man, Mr. Lapinsky.
He was an intern
with whom I have had brief contact.
That was it. Did you come?
But this time almost.
Next time.
After an average of 1 minute 35
we are always ready.
You must always run away immediately
after we...
You know that Kellyx likes you, right?
-How about love?
I get the L word
hard on my lips.
Kellyx wish you ...
- Other was.
Maybe you should next time
wear a uniform.
Then you look like a new man.
I love uniforms.
Assistants, concierges,
the cleaner who cleans your pipes.
Kellyx loves strong men
in uniform.
The idea of ​​the knots
making is so ...
Twice.
I don't know what to do. With that
They come to Viagra for women so quickly.
I really sympathize with you. It's me
also sat to be a sex object.
What is that?
It depends on the uniform. I remember
not even her name anymore.
We have talked about this.
If you want me to be someone else,
Then why are you with me?
You're right.
In what then?
-You can't change.
I'm leaving you.
You meet your dream girl ...
on the day you find out you're a scary
got illness from another.
You have one hour left to live.
What are you saying to her?
Against who?
-To the girl of your dreams.
Is this such a hypothetical question
or a real question?
The perfect girl lives in another
country. They shoot at you at the border.
The relationship issue. Get rid of it. Do you know
What does a relationship do with your overtime?
It's about sex, not relationships.
If I ... No, if I ...
raise the nylon by 2.5 percent ...
then the net weight would be ...
decrease by 2.5 ... by 0.4 percent.
I'm getting promotion today.
Nylon car engines.
They drive really, but the best of them
is that they are not real.
What about the trend against plastics?
Do you have the new silver
seen devices?
I bought a silver telephone.
It is a bit heavy, but very beautiful.
Let us have the graphs
let's see, Joe.
Guy.
-The charts.
Our research shows that there is a slight one
decrease in the sale of plastic is ...
but i think that
in the future ...
Well it will ... it will get better.
We improve sales
with a global campaign.
Plastic can continue to exist.
I don't like such a plastic motor.
People can go through their computer
to travel. I want something with more 'oemf'.
I would recommend a new product
able to design.
At work, people.
I want what women want. They are
our primary consumer group.
A woman must
lead this campaign.
You're ready for promotion, don't you, Kellyx?
I would really like that.
I want Guy on my team
as my assistant.
Okay then. But I give
him no promotion.
I already have this year
given a man promotion.
Those stimulating condoms were
in the mail.
He is a perfect masseur, he shrugs
her was up. He is a slave.
He's a rat.
-He is an art person.
I never guessed. I know
the guy who does his parts.
They make women look so good
look? Not that I need one.
Hello, Rocky.
-Hiroki.
Also fine.
Greta is not like Kellyx. She is too old
to get flesh and blood.
Do you know whoever?
has an art person? Perez.
What are you doing here?
- Please love me.
You know you can't go downstairs
come. Do you want them to fire me?
Stop it.
- Please love me.
It is unfair that men
they may not have.
Would be with a male president
we will be satisfied.
If the boss sees this,
he can shake it.
Hopefully she doesn't see it.
Are you defective? What is your serial number?
Refers to non-programmed
emotions fuse through?
Please don't leave me
have to work for a steel company.
That's not fair.
You also have a toy.
Life is not always
honest for a man, Joe.
Do you and your robot want to get lost now?
Do you know what to do, Guy?
Purchase such a plastic woman.
An art person?
They make them nowadays
very real.
They never tell you to shave,
and otherwise turn them off.
And then end up as Perez.
The loser. Such a toy
can you still hide?
Why don't you take one?
-My credit cards work against it.
Plastic.
Here's a ticket. Call this woman.
Her name is Boyla and she is a robot expert.
I'm really not starting it.
Can I have a wife here?
Yes of course. We have a
public holiday special with redheads.
The eyes are not included. Would you
give me that hand?
I've never done this before.
- Many virgins come here.
May I?
How expensive?
Some take out a mortgage,
but this yields more than a house.
A house?
I absolutely cannot afford that.
-I also have a lesser model.
Does it only have one arm or something?
There are a few small ones
downsides. Little.
Thanks for your time, but I think
that I'm going to find a normal girl ...
in a normal way.
You noticed me. I want you
like to get to know better.
You and I, we are going ...
Hey. My father raised me ...
-Boats.
Hey. I want a romantic,
monogamous relationship.
Excuse me.
Do you know what time it is?
That would...
All right. Not here. I want you
like to get to know first.
That is not...
Put them in the water.
Fork.
Eating more oyster bars, and not
so many vitamins for your brain.
You think too much anyway.
All right. I will think less.
Should women leave you,
like you-know-who?
Mom didn't leave me, but you.
I meant that shikse
who you loved in Paris.
He did not leave, but died.
-Does not matter. You are different.
All my friends have
at least one grandchild.
What should I call you then?
I don't have a name. We have
no names needed here.
Then I will have a name
have to invent for you.
A name. Jesus Christ.
I've been all my life
addressed with millions of names.
I'm better off
with a grunt or moan as a name.
I believe I love you.
I had already been once. Do you have
still that model that nobody wanted?
That cheaper one. Like a chestnut
brown costs less than a ...
Really?
Yeah that would be great. I am coming...
Hey?
Finally someone to talk to.
-With those tubes?
Someone to cuddle at night.
- And she's nice and flexible.
If she nags that she wants some space,
you can turn it off and put it away.
Stop it
staring at that photo.
She was really unique.
You are a smart guy. You can
do not bring the dead to life.
Bet?
She must love basketball.
She must love my favorite beer.
She needs my armbands
to hold.
And sex. Lots of sex.
Twice a day. With an orgasm.
The sex express. No stops.
Even more preferences? Color of it
pubic hair, length of the tongue ...
Smell of the skin? We have berries.
I do not want that. Surprise me.
Unspecified skin odor.
That.
And that.
She has a touch pad on her hips
if you want to reprogram her.
A couple more questions.
Intellect or no sense?
Please understand.
What type? Hellenic? Semitic?
Eastern provincial?
Romanian?
-Einstein meets Groucho Marx.
Look at that.
Smaller.
We will take care of it
that everything is absolutely right.
You can keep her for seven days.
We will recycle her next week.
Can I not keep her?
We needed a low cost plan
think up because you had some problems.
This is also a test model. She's half
from cloned DNA and half from plastic.
Hooves. If only she is
50% artificial?
It is also 50% human, and that is
half more women than you have now.
How do you like it?
-Beautiful.
I want to impress her.
-She's a robot.
Your mantra:Don't be too eager ...
-Do not be an instrument ...
And give her what you have.
What do you think about it?
-Do you have a shoehorn?
I will next time
get some more candy for you.
You are apparently a sweet tooth.
Maybe you try your inner chill
to compensate.
I am ... You already know who I am.
What is your zodiac sign?
You don't have one.
Package for you.
Exactly as stated in the brochure.
I'm Guy.
This is your new house.
Do you like it?
Did I order you?
I froze.
-Really?
I wanted to impress you.
- That's what all the guys want.
All men?
Wait a second. Are you not new?
Your money was not enough
for a new model.
I have a cybrarian
out of 83 seated ...
and with a young sumo wrestler
with a very large ... Do you mind?
Not at all.
You didn't want a jealous partner.
That is in your file.
I get it.
You don't want a jealous partner,
but you can be jealous.
Just kidding. You have a sarcastic feeling
ordered for humor, remember?
I am new.
So I have no memory for you
comparable with previous customers.
This is also the first time for me.
Has anyone ever
sucked on your toe?
Shall we take it easy?
If we have sex tonight,
you will never respect me.
Besides, I don't even know your name.
- But I don't have a name.
Do you want one?
-Do you want me to want one?
Teach me how to feel like a real one
woman must behave ...
so that the company police don't catch us.
I want to be just like the rest.
Nobody wants to be just like the rest.
Why is it so bad?
to be mediocre?
You really have a species
human complex.
Indeed.
I ordered smaller ones.
Okay, this is my camera.
He records and plays.
But don't connect me to the television.
Do I have to feed you, boss?
'Boss? I have never been
previously called boss.
I'm going for a pastrami omelet
make it for you.
A real? My favorite dish.
- mine too.
Plump down nicely
and watch the game later.
It starts in 7.2 minutes.
The bet against our team is 10 to 5.
Do we have...
It was my birthday yesterday.
-Days are just numbers.
Make a wish.
This biodegradable
diapers are actually ...
recyclable.
Has Kellyx approved it?
And what do you have?
Bravo, exactly where my consumers
are looking for.
You better invent something
what people actually buy ...
otherwise you need steel
go learn, Joe.
Guy. My name is G ... Why are you staying?
call me Joe?
All men look like Joe.
That's easier.
That way I remember everyone's name.
Joe, right?
Your cheeks are redder
when you talk about yourself.
Why do you like it so much
to talk? Most are not like that.
Because I was because of my father
brought up, who is an ICQ therapist.
He earns money with the
online treatment of people.
I have more therapy as a child
then got Woody Allen.
Who is that?
A guy who is with his daughter
went to bed.
He has also made a number of films.
Hello, son.
Dad, this is sick.
Were you taking a bath? Shall I call later?
Call me back, yes.
I'm not gone long. I still have to
make contact with a baby shower.
Melissus' son has
have a son ...
although it is slightly smaller
then Towy's grandchild.
Not that you care.
Are you taking a bath with someone?
Something like that.
Why didn't you say that? Together in the bath
is good for you know. Is it Kellyx?
It is someone who can wait.
He wants a family as soon as possible
founding, although he doesn't know that yet.
Dad, stop it.
I really want to see you.
Is it Friday night?
I have to hang up.
I keep my mouth shut.
But you need the horizontal tango
play when I've hung up.
Yet?
My father wouldn't be really happy like him
I heard something about a robot.
He wants me to have children,
no blenders.
Terrible, those politicians who say that
they are going to do something about the ozone layer.
It rains a lot in Paris.
Do I have a big ass in these pants?
Compared to what?
I know your personality
consists of data.
But you have to tell me about yourself.
- Are you really interested in me?
You should see it here.
I work here. Now you have to go home.
I have to hold that promotion
to drag. Although it makes no sense.
Because nobody believes in me.
-I do.
Hello, Guy. Imagine me
not ahead of your girl?
I'm not a girl.
Are you real?
How do you get such a good one?
She likes me for my brain.
You should try it too.
Rooster. I was like that too, so I left him
take off. I have a nicer ass.
Are you sure?
Down?
Maybe I will get a promotion
if I'm going to wear a uniform.
Do not. The imperfections
make you who you are.
Let your guts guide you.
She is perfect.
I could also create something like that.
At least part of her.
Where do women desire
the most nasty?
Think about sex, think of cars.
I think the product for which we
advertising should be practical.
Just give us the results of the
opinion poll among women, Joe.
I am also a consumer.
-I'm listening.
Plastic human body parts.
Synthetic body parts, with
extensive movement options.
A rock climber would further his legs
extend beyond normal.
It has two joints,
what makes you stronger.
Everyone can be a virtuoso pianist.
We can now even more of us
body and perform better.
Consider all the options.
-You can scratch your own back.
New sex positions.
You can turn your head 180 degrees
and look behind you.
A man can meet his own ...
sucking toe.
Not bad, Guy.
-Indeed. He's mine.
I'd like to talk first.
Talk.
You are so cute
if you worry.
I can't believe you're mine.
Put me to the test.
I do everything you say.
That was heavenly.
You're the biggest I've had.
I thought I was the only one.
You are the only and the largest.
Do you want another orgasm?
Is that allowed?
Did your art person do that?
Yummy.
It was crazy, man. She did
everything exactly as I wanted it.
It's kind of weird. It is
like I was doing it to myself.
And the lips?
-I haven't kissed her yet.
I didn't mean that, but okay.
You did it with a machine.
Fantastic.
Don't call her a robot.
That's just what she is.
I don't want her upset.
She has a Pinocchio complex.
Wood, metal, plastic, what does it matter.
She doesn't feel anything.
Maybe ever.
Is that a possibility or a wish?
No idea. I have never
what about a robot.
Accept the pain.
Who am I kidding?
I am not perfect.
Fortunately there is still chocolate.
Do you want me to be perfect?
I wish I were that. For you.
What a beautiful specimen.
Hello Mary, I am ...
I know who you are. We have enough
memory space for 200 friends.
Yes.
You drink iced coffee with aspirin,
amphetamines and antihistamines.
Tell her not to do that again.
-She's mine.
I have seen the receipt.
You don't have to be so selfish.
I recently borrowed you my stereo.
Can't what's my name?
That is not healthy.
- I'll take a shower.
Friends of mine can me
better not share ...
because their companionship is essential
for optimum performance.
I would like this glorious friendship
not want to destroy.
What about that promotion?
I don't want to disappoint you, but ...
How should I state this.
You have too much testosterone
to be creative.
It is an anti-Freudian theory.
If you don't have a penis,
you also have no fear of castration.
We can take greater risks.
I thought I had now proven that
as creative as a woman can be.
Oh, honey. It's not you guys
have no good things.
I have for example
purchased this implant ...
so that I can pee standing.
Very practical.
Sorry.
Good aim is not easy.
You see? You shouldn't be right
if women are, but better.
Do you also have a tango program?
-I do not know.
Sorry.
I meant tonight
want to dance with you.
Out in the computer?
-No, really. And upright.
I love you, Mary.
The correct answer is:me from you too.
Sorry.
I do not know how.
But maybe I can learn.
Of course she can't.
-I was just curious.
She can't love you.
What toaster do you have?
Do you have such a beautiful one that fits in everything?
Does your toaster love you?
Never?
Nobody ever asked for it.
That's what it was all about.
No tears, no crap.
I thought it would be ideal for you ...
but you are clearly different.
Isn't she 50 percent human?
I teach her.
Do what you want, but ask her
do not expose to the sun for too long.
Food leads to a chemical
reaction in the body ...
very similar to emotions.
People combine meat with lettuce
to be balanced.
Just hit one
through my fuses?
Look at this.
Chocolate.
Chocolate kills you.
Chocolate is just like love.
You have to puke ...
and at the same time ... you want more.
That was a bad example.
It is like holding each other's hands.
Bend your fingers.
Why?
-Because it's fun.
I will take you to the park and
show what people in love do?
Really? What should I wear?
-Whatever you want.
I only know what you like.
Then wear what I want.
Preference not specified.
Can we...
-Yeah, we're going to buy candy.
I felt something. A warm wave.
But I don't think you are
that can call love.
I'm hungry.
Me too.
I want a pizza.
Are you really hungry?
I'm hungry if you have that.
I know exactly what you are going to do.
I can also be unpredictable
if you program what you want.
What I want is starting to bore me.
Pastrami omelette?
It is your favorite dish.
-I do not want that.
People grow, people change.
They even outgrow
their favorite omelette.
Tell me what you want,
then you get that.
Would it help if I had more
if that woman was in Paris?
That would be me if you wanted it.
I want you...
but different.
This is what you ordered.
If someone says, "I want you different
', you should get angry.
What if I reprogram you?
If I reprint you ...
You wanted someone you wouldn't
try to change.
Why are you trying me
then change?
I've seen Guy's new girlfriend.
Just like a model. A perfect body.
Perfect body?
Not that yours isn't beautiful.
Have you ever wondered ...
If we women are so beautiful
and be successful and powerful ...
why are we alone?
Let's now
realize that network campaign.
Tonight is not so ... Is that a ...
Look at the time.
Do you want to keep your job? Miss wants
probably not a benefit recipient.
Can she ... I mean, come in?
You keep surprising me.
Don't offer your Kellyx something to drink
or does she have to go get it herself?
I'll make it.
I already have it.
Your favorite drink.
What kind of diet do you follow?
-None.
Fortunate metabolism?
-Something, yes.
I'm Kellyx, Guys ex.
-I'm Mary, Guys current.
So you're from ...
Because you have a slight accent.
-Guy likes accents.
She also imitates people. She can
Warren Beatty very well.
The actor?
-No, the president.
I didn't know he liked accents.
What else does Guy like?
It is very easy.
He wants you to listen to him ...
and toes suck, and kinky sex,
and orgasm twice a day.
Have you been a geisha?
-No, but I know geisha tricks.
She..-
You...
You are really glowing with it. What kind
guy buys a robot at all?
A guy who's too tall with robotic
women like you.
R2D2 agree with you here.
It took me 7200 seconds
to make him forget you.
That you have taken refuge
to buy a girl.
What does that say about me?
I thought I could make you happy.
I don't have the feeling with her
that I have to be someone else.
Slapjanus.
Stop it, Guy.
-I want to explain.
Do you want to go for a steel company?
to work? Plastic flows through your veins.
People are fired every day.
- And I like to fire Joe's.
Alright then, but then
you don't know my plan yet.
A plan?
-A man?
Use the art people
to show the plastic body parts ...
in our advertisement.
You show what the limbs can do
without having to operate on people.
This is how you save on insurance
and on money.
Research shows that there is a secret
desire for art people exists.
Who doesn't want a perfect one
android to bed?
We are going to show people
that with plastic body parts ...
they can do anything
what an art person can do.
But I am in charge of ...
-Sorry, you'll have to assist Guy.
You know, a man at the head
is not as bad as it seems.
TANG SOO Enterprises' new
strategy:A MAN AT THE HEAD
Would you like me without a uniform?
Who knows. Why would you do it
pull it out at all?
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
They say your life partner
but better be your best friend.
Marry me.
I could really learn to love you.
I'm not jealous of your machine.
We can even
maintain a triangular relationship.
I understand.
No thanks?
I'm talking about nepotism.
You make a career, it is going well
with Mary, I want to go further.
Help me further.
-It's not possible.
What a lazy answer.
You know how much effort I had to make
for these advances? Look at this tie.
Ever been in love
on a toaster?
A toaster?
-Yes.
I love you because I can
evenly brown?
It doesn't matter what I feel.
She's just like the tin man.
I have no heart.
She will never love you.
Why?
Guy, take your doll
to the photo shoot. Can she dance?
He has no trouble with it at all
to love me.
He even likes it
a little too much from me.
It is on my nerves.
It looks like you have one
of those new models.
I love you. Do you love me?
You do not love me.
But I love you.
Do not worry.
He always has a stop
if I don't say I love him too.
He has no stubble.
Just baby buttocks. It is lucky.
That's a novelty.
Who wants such a rough chin
when your guy down there is busy.
He also has no touchpad.
- Everything is built-in internally.
That is for safety.
Don't you think that's dangerous?
Someone can modify yours.
You will have a cheap one
have a version.
I have made a good deal.
Art people die of love.
What if I finally love him
and he dies?
And what if he doesn't love me?
Back, please.
I have plans for this space.
I have to free up space.
For nylons and acrylic fibers.
So that's how they end up? They change
in telephones and cigarette holders?
In other art people.
Mary can be a dwarf or a bearded one
Become a Slavic soldier.
Great that you have a boring face and a
sarcastic impact can say hello.
I want her to get gray hair and wrinkles.
If it is not recycled tomorrow,
she crashes.
I was thinking...
Maybe we should
remove your touchpad ...
and give you your freedom.
I don't know if being free
mechanically possible.
What is that?
What are you doing with me?
If this is the last day
of your life was ...
what would you like to do?
I do not know.
Let's go to Paris.
-The real Paris, where it rains?
No, the real Paris is full of thieves
and drunks and French.
I have a much better idea.
How did you get in?
With Guys cardkey.
He gave it to me.
He wants to make love to me tonight. Here.
Men are so fickle.
One day they want a violent one
nun, the next virgin whore.
I can only handle one order at a time.
Listen, honey, a relationship is nothing
then the meat exchange.
You choose whether you want a hamburger
or want to be a filet mignon.
I strive to be a filet mignon.
But I think I'm just a steak.
But that's still not bad if you
consider what kind of meat there is.
Am I a filet mignon?
-Absolutely.
I just want love.
I don't have to be perfect.
We can arrange that.
I mean I can do that.
Really?
Testosterone levels up ...
Why the hurry?
- I have to go to Mary. I'm already late.
From. You know you have to give her up
now the campaign is over.
I know.
Shaver.
To.
So. He will be away from you, honey.
-Really?
I have to leave.
And I loved that laptop so much.
What are you doing?
Her energy fluids. She is dead.
Why is she in your trunk?
-I wanted to recycle her. That how it's supposed to be.
Do you have jumper cables?
Then electrocute your hair.
Turn on your engine.
I'm not going to kill her.
I thought you said she was already dead.
Turn on the engine.
Damn.
What the hell were you trying to do?
-I tried...
Who taught you in the middle of a sentence
to say "damn it"?
Are you crazy? do you want to kill me?
-Unfortunately.
Rotwijf. You deserve each other.
You are insane.
You..-
Mary, come back. You may
best say "damn it."
I don't know what's wrong with Mary.
She keeps saying "damn it."
Mommy.
Don't worry, I adjusted Mary.
She must be normal again.
Normal, right.
You don't want her to love you.
If she does, she will collapse.
I'm late
for my recycling appointment.
I really wish I could be
as you would like.
Is this such a last kiss?
Because I don't see you anymore,
can i sleep then?
But I thought that
They are going to recycle me anyway.
I know you want me to stay asleep.
Tell me what you want.
I would like to sleep with you.
I will miss you.
Do you really care about my death?
It's just a simple one
chemical connection.
Even the oldest models can
to cry.
I would still love you if you did
was a bearded Slavic soldier.
Really?
I love you too.
I learned to love you
because of your love for me.
Come on, Mary.
I already told you that cheaper
models fall apart.
How does that work...
Did I kill her?
- It happens to everyone.
And on behalf of Tang Soo Enterprises ...
we want for a change
thank a man.
I'm not going to talk about plastic.
Do you all want women?
just like men are?
You can continue to wear a skirt
while you rule the world.
There is no superior or inferior.
We all have our problems.
We need eachother.
Do you like sushi?
Your shaver.
That thing didn't work.
In a few days
I would have stubble.
And what about eating and sleeping?
How can I sleep when I think how
it merges with all kinds of devices?
If it is to comfort you:I envy you.
Why?
-Your vulnerability.
That is a quality and not a weakness.
It didn't help me much further.
I just don't know yet.
I would like to feel that way someday.
She makes you happy. What makes it
then whether she is a machine.
What is that?
Has anyone seen Mary?
Put your shirt up. Do you...
I hated that thing.
-What is that? I know you.
I know you. You are the girl from Paris.
Is that you?
My death was meant for you
to give an obsession with my image.
What are you talking about?
I make genetic art people.
I work for Boyla.
We test men's responses
on art people.
I get it.
You were not a robot at all.
You are some kind of necrophilic
cynical bitch.
I am precise
like when you met me.
But I'm sorry
that I am not perfect.
And I thought I was perfect
had to be for you.
I studied you.
I know everything about you.
Every detail.
What you dream about
and what makes you sad.
I liked you before I met you.
They said you were such an old-fashioned man
who still wanted to feel.
I wish you taught me
how i had to feel.
I thought I killed you.
-I had to know if it did you something.
Whether it did something to me?
It wasn't about that.
It was about whether it did something to you.
Wait.
Why? Why did you choose me?
Don't ask me that.
Why don't I have to ask you that?
Why me?
You do not want to know.
Believe me, you don't want to know.
So she's not an art person. So what?
Take the meat.
I can not do that. She's holding something back.
You are hopeless. We will
have a word about me now?
I'm going out with an Australian babe.
She met me without a uniform.
Where is she?
Let me see Paris.
Paris, reference, films.
I've been all my life
addressed with millions of names.
I don't want a name, I'm better off
with a grunt or moan as a name.
Dad.
I was just eating a herring ball.
-Why do I love Paris?
Because you are a woman under one
have met the bridge. She looked sad.
You fucked like rabbits
and used butter with it.
That was a movie.
Last Tango in Paris.
I have to think of a name for you.
It's a sick movie, Dad.
I have been millions all my life
names addressed. I'm better off ...
Nonsense. It rained.
-It was raining like that.
I couldn't do it, so they gave me you.
-Who are 'them', Dad?
I'm sorry if I ...
I just wanted to
that you were normal.
That you were normal.
I do not want to lose you.
There is no knife in it.
Where's that hair?
I want a hair.
Blood replacement
at least tenable until 03-03
It was time you called.
I didn't want to wake you up, but ...
If you can hear me ...
I just wanted to say that I know
that somewhere deep inside ...
you love Me.
As long as we stay together,
we'll manage.
Sleep tight.
Ironic, huh. The most human ...
man I know is a robot.
My heart is too big.
I'm working on that.
Art people have
sweet in an old-fashioned way.
People don't do that. People
don't even want to be people anymore.
But do not worry.
I'm not killing you.
I'm just recycling you.
People don't want to
engage in love.
They want to feel in love ...
without the consequences.
The colder the less you have.
The less it makes you collapse,
the more I sell.
She didn't program you for me
to keep. That came from yourself.
Have we never been to Paris?
-I'm a bad memory writer, yes.
But I am proud of the images
that I stole for your past.
Crazy, huh. You thought you had me
created, but I created you.
I'm actually your mother.
-Wait a second.
I ... We are not compatible.
So what? Then we have
a different life.
You wear me when I'm old, and I make
you if you are defective. Come with me.
Where are we going?
- What about Paris?
I've never been that far away.
Paris is less scary
then fall in love.
I want to know your real name.
At first I thought she was a robot.
-I wasn't that.
That was me.
- He was.
And we have been married for 42 years.
Nine months and 38 days. And this
girl still looks exactly the same.
The same.
Translation:Janneke Zwart
The Service Station