[thrilling orchestral music]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
ALL RIGHT.
WASHINGTON, D.C.,
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING OUT
TO THE TAPING FOR MY
SECOND STAND-UP SPECIAL.
[cheers and applause]
VERY EXCITED TO BE HERE.
BEFORE WE START THE SHOW,
I KNOW THERE'S PROBABLY
SOME SIGNS UP SAYING,
NO PHOTOS AND THINGS
OF THAT NATURE,
AND THAT'S JUST BECAUSE
OBVIOUSLY WE'RE TAPING THIS.
AND ALSO,
WHEN I DO THESE SHOWS,
PEOPLE CAN START
TAKING PHOTOS,
AND THERE'LL BE
A LOT OF FLASHING,
AND ORANGE LIGHTS UP, AND IT CAN
BE A LITTLE DISTRACTING
WHEN I'M TRYING TO FOCUS
ON THE PERFORMANCE.
BUT WHAT I REALIZE IS THAT
PEOPLE DON'T GIVE A SHIT,
AND THEY
TAKE PHOTOS ANYWAY.
BECAUSE THERE ARE SOME SHITTY
PEOPLE THAT COME TO THESE SHOWS.
I MEAN, LOOK HOW MANY
PEOPLE ARE HERE.
SOME OF YOU
ARE SHITTY PEOPLE.
THERE'S NO QUESTION.
IF WE MET
IN ANY OTHER CONTEXT
BESIDES YOU PAYING ME MONEY
TO SEE ME TELL JOKES,
I'M SURE THERE ARE SOME OF YOU
I WOULD HATE WITH A PASSION.
NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
I REALLY HATE
SOME OF YOU A LOT.
SO, WHAT I THOUGHT
WE COULD DO AS A COMPROMISE--
RIGHT NOW,
BEFORE I START THE SHOW,
I UNDERSTAND PEOPLE
LIKE PHOTOS AND STUFF,
SO RIGHT NOW,
BEFORE WE START THE SHOW,
I'M GONNA PRETEND LIKE
I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF A JOKE,
AND YOU CAN TAKE AS MANY
PHOTOS AS YOU WANT,
AND THEN AFTER THAT,
WE'LL HAVE A GREAT SHOW, OKAY?
SO, HERE WE GO.
IF YOU WANT TO SNAP A PHOTO,
GO FOR IT.
SOME FAKE JOKE WHERE I NEED
TO GO THROUGH A CRAWLSPACE.
LET'S ACT LIKE--LET'S ACT
LIKE AN INCIDENT HAPPENED
WITH AN AUDIENCE MEMBER.
LIKE, SIR,
COULD YOU STAND UP
AND ACT LIKE YOU'RE
YELLING AT ME ABOUT SOMETHING?
SO, YOU CAN SHOW
THAT PHOTO TO PEOPLE,
AND TELL 'EM, "YEAH,
AT ONE POINT IN THE SHOW,
"THIS GUY JUST STOOD UP
AND WAS LIKE,
"'WHITES ARE
THE SUPERIOR RACE!'
"AND AZIZ WAS LIKE,
'WHOA, THAT'S NOT COOL, SIR,
YOU NEED TO SIT DOWN.'"
ALL RIGHT, COOL. EVERYBODY GOOD
WITH PHOTOS AND EVERYTHING?
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING OUT.
I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU
COMING OUT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I LIVE, UH--I LIVE
IN NEW YORK RIGHT NOW,
[audience cheers]
AND--YES.
AND I'M SINGLE RIGHT NOW, AND--
[audience cheers]
OH, SHUT UP.
YOU DON'T MEAN THAT SHIT.
AND WHENEVER I GO OUT
TO BARS THERE,
I HAVE THIS ONE FRIEND
OF MINE.
HE'S ONE OF THESE GUYS,
HE'S LIKE, "AW, MAN.
"ANY CUTE GIRL YOU SEE,
JUST GO TALK TO HER, MAN.
"WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN?
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN?
ANY CUTE GIRL YOU SEE,
"JUST SAY SOMETHING, ANYTHING,
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT.
"WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN?
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN?
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN?"
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
THAT GIRL IS GONNA BE MEAN AS
SHIT TO ME FOR NO REASON AT ALL.
WHY DO I WANT
TO DEAL WITH THAT?
"HI, HOW ARE YOU?"
"FUCK YOU!"
"ALL RIGHT, I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
I'LL GO TALK TO MY FRIEND BRIAN.
HE'S ALWAYS NICE TO ME."
AND SURE, THAT'S A LITTLE BIT
OF AN EXAGGERATION,
BUT THAT IS
HOW IT FEELS SOMETIMES.
I ONCE WENT UP
TO THIS GIRL
'CAUSE I THOUGHT SHE HAD
A COOL PURSE ON HER SHOULDER.
I SAID,
"HEY, THAT'S A NICE BAG."
AND SHE SAID, "THANK YOU,"
AND WE STARTED TALKING,
AND SHE SEEMED NICE.
THEN AT ONE POINT,
HER FRIEND COMES OVER,
AND WHEN THE GIRL'S FRIEND
COMES OVER, SHE GOES,
"OH, HEY. THIS IS AZIZ.
HE CAME TO TALK TO ME 'CAUSE
HE THOUGHT I HAD A COOL BAG."
AND ROLLED HER EYES.
AND I THOUGHT,
"WOW, THAT'S REALLY RUDE.
NO REASON TO DO THAT.
I WAS JUST BEING NICE," RIGHT?
SO, I SAID TO MYSELF
RIGHT THERE,
"WHENEVER I LEAVE
THIS CONVERSATION,
"I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
THIS GIRL KNOWS
"I DON'T GIVE A SHIT
ABOUT HER,
AND I REALLY
LIKE HER BAG."
SO, AT ONE POINT, WE'RE SITTING
THERE TALKING, AND I WAS LIKE,
"YEAH..."
[feigns laughter]
"HEY, WHAT'S THAT
OVER THERE?"
AND THEN I STOLE HER PURSE.
YEAH.
THAT BAG'S MINE NOW.
I NEVER KNOW WHAT TO SAY TO
GIRLS IN SITUATIONS LIKE THAT.
IT'S ALWAYS SO AWKWARD.
I WAS HAVING LUNCH
WITH A FRIEND OF MINE ONCE,
AND I TOLD HIM,
"HEY, THERE'S THIS ONE GIRL
"THAT WORKS
IN THIS RESTAURANT.
SHE'S SO CUTE, BUT I DON'T
KNOW WHAT TO SAY TO HER."
AND HE GOES,
"OH, MAN, ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS GO OVER THERE AND BE HONEST
WITH HER FOR A MINUTE."
REALLY?
THAT'S ALL I GOTTA DO?
SO, I JUST NEED TO WALK OVER--
"EXCUSE ME, MISS.
"I JUST NEED TO BE REAL HONEST
WITH YOU FOR A MINUTE.
"I EAT HERE ALL THE TIME,
AND WHEN I DO,
"I STARE AT YOUR FACE.
"AND I IMAGINE US FUCKING
WHILE I EAT MY SANDWICHES.
"LET ME KNOW IF YOU'D LIKE
TO TURN MY FANTASY
INTO YOUR REALITY."
I'M NOT SURE THAT WOULD
WORK OUT TOO WELL.
PEOPLE ALWAYS GIVE YOU
THE SAME DUMB ADVICE
IN SITUATIONS LIKE THAT.
THEY'LL SAY THINGS LIKE,
"OH, JUST LEAVE HER A BIG TIP."
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
I JUST WALK OVER--
"YES, CAN I
GET A MUFFIN, PLEASE?
"HERE'S $100.
"I THINK YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
I'M WILLING TO HAVE SEX
WITH YOU FOR THE PRICE OF $98."
I WAS DOING
THAT JOKE ONE NIGHT,
AND THIS GUY
IN THE AUDIENCE JUST YELLS,
"JUST TELL HER
YOU'RE ON TV!"
YEAH. THERE'S NO WAY
I'LL SOUND LIKE A JERK
IF I DO THAT, RIGHT?
"EXCUSE ME, MISS.
I'M ON TV."
[clears throat]
"I SAID...
"I'M ON TV.
"I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE,
BUT THIS IS THE PART WHERE
YOU START SUCKING MY DICK."
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT SOME DUDES
THINK BEING ON TV'S LIKE.
I JUST WALK INTO BARS...
"WHAT'S UP, EVERYBODY?
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
"SOMEONE THAT'S APPEARED
ON TELEVISION IS HERE.
"SO, IF YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN GIVING ME A HANDJOB
IN THE RESTROOM,
LET'S LINE UP TO THE LEFT."
NO. THAT'S NOT
HOW IT WORKS AT ALL.
HOW IT WORKS
IS I WALK INTO A BAR,
AND FIVE DUDES ARE LIKE,
"OH, MAN, IT'S THAT BROWN GUY
I SAW ON THAT THING!"
[whining groan]
"OH, MAN, OH, MAN, BRO,
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE HERE!
"YOU GOTTA TAKE A PHOTO
WITH ME AND MY PUPPY.
"MY PUPPY'S
BACK AT MY HOUSE, THOUGH.
WE GOTTA DRIVE THERE.
NOW."
THAT DOESN'T SOUND SAFE.
I WAS IN A RELATIONSHIP
FOR A FEW YEARS,
AND I THINK IN THE TIME
I WAS IN THE RELATIONSHIP,
ALL DATING COMMUNICATION
WENT EXCLUSIVELY TO TEXT.
YOU CAN'T CALL
ANYBODY ANYMORE.
IF YOU CALL SOMEONE,
THEY'RE LIKE,
"WHAT? ARE YOU ON FIRE?
THEN QUIT WASTING MY TIME.
TEXT ME THAT SHIT."
AND I DON'T LIKE TEXTING PEOPLE.
ESPECIALLY GIRLS.
THERE'S ALWAYS MISCOMMUNICATION
THAT HAPPENS.
THIS IS A SITUATION
I GET INTO ALL THE TIME.
I'LL TEXT A GIRL,
SHE TEXTS ME BACK RIGHT AWAY.
I TEXT HER BACK RIGHT AWAY,
SHE TEXTS ME BACK RIGHT AWAY,
SHE TEXTS ME BACK RIGHT AWAY.
THEN I'LL SAY
SOMETHING LIKE,
"ALL RIGHT, COOL, SO YOU WANNA
GET PIZZA ON TUESDAY?"
AND THEN I DON'T
HEAR ANYTHING.
AND I'M LIKE,
"WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
"I KNOW YOU READ THAT SHIT.
"YOU RESPONDED TO 20 OTHER
THINGS I JUST SAID.
"WHAT, DO YOU
NOT LIKE ME ANYMORE?
"YOU DON'T HAVE TWO SECONDS TO
SAY, 'YES, I WANT TO GET PIZZA''
"OR, 'NO, I DON'T
WANT TO GET PIZZA'?
"WHAT, DID YOU CHECK
YOUR PHONE INTO A LOCKER
"AND GO RIDE A ROLLER COASTER
FOR A FEW HOURS?
WHAT'S THE DEAL?"
AND AFTER A FEW HOURS OF
NO RESPONSE, I GET REAL UPSET.
AND I JUST WANT TO SEND A TEXT
THAT SAYS SOMETHING LIKE,
"WELL, GUESS WHO JUST GOT
UNINVITED TO THE PIZZA PARTY.
YOU DID,
'CAUSE I HATE YOU NOW."
GIRL ALWAYS WRITES
SOMETHING BACK.
"SORRY, I WAS AT MY NIECE'S
BALLET RECITAL.
WE HAD TO TURN OFF
OUR PHONES."
"WHATEVER. WE'RE DONE.
I FINISHED THAT PIZZA HOURS AGO.
I WENT WITH MY FRIEND BRIAN.
HE'S NICE TO ME."
I WENT OUT WITH THIS GIRL
IN L.A. A FEW TIMES.
SHE WAS REALLY NICE.
AND LAST TIME I WAS IN L.A.,
I CALLED HER UP
AND ASKED HER OUT
FOR DINNER.
AND SHE WAS LIKE,
"YEAH, SURE."
THEN TWO HOURS BEFORE OUR DATE,
SHE CALLS ME UP.
SHE GOES, "AZIZ, I REALLY WANT
TO GO OUT TO DINNER WITH YOU,
"BUT I KIND OF
HAVE A BOYFRIEND NOW.
IS THAT A PROBLEM?"
AND I SAID,
"YEAH, IT'S KIND OF
"THE BIGGEST PROBLEM
WE COULD HAVE.
"WHY WOULD I
GO OUT WITH YOU
"IF YOU KIND OF
HAVE A BOYFRIEND NOW?
"WHAT'S NEXT? 'HEY, AZIZ, I GOT
YOU TICKETS FOR THIS CARNIVAL,
"BUT YOU CAN'T RIDE ANY RIDES.
IS THAT A PROBLEM?'
"YEAH, IT'S A PROBLEM.
I WANTED TO RIDE THOSE RIDES.
"THAT'S THE WHOLE POINT
OF ME GOING TO THE CARNIVAL.
THESE TICKETS
YOU GAVE ME ARE USELESS."
"HEY, AZIZ, I GOT YOU
A PANINI PRESS OFF AMAZON,
"BUT I SHIPPED IT TO MY FRIEND
LISA INSTEAD OF YOU.
IS THAT A PROBLEM?"
"YEAH, IT'S A PROBLEM.
THAT'S NOT MY ADDRESS.
"AND I DON'T HAVE
LISA'S CONTACT INFO,
AND NOW THAT YOU MENTION
PANINIS, I REALLY WANT ONE."
WHAT'S THE BEST-CASE
SCENARIO?
WE GO OUT ON THIS AMAZING DINNER
DATE, HAVE A FANTASTIC TIME,
WE COME BACK TO MY PLACE.
SHE'S LIKE, "AZIZ,
"I HAD A REALLY GOOD TIME
AT DINNER TONIGHT,
"AND I WANT TO GIVE YOU
A BLOWJOB.
"BUT I'M GONNA
USE MY BOYFRIEND'S PENIS
INSTEAD OF YOURS.
IS THAT A PROBLEM?"
"YEAH, IT'S A PROBLEM.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE GONNA
SUCK YOUR BOYFRIEND'S DICK
AT MY HOUSE."
IT'S ALWAYS KIND OF
DEPRESSING TO ME
WHEN I TALK TO GIRLS
THAT HAVE BOYFRIENDS,
BECAUSE WHEN YOU ASK THEM
HOW THEY MET THEIR BOYFRIEND,
IT'S NEVER A SWEET STORY LIKE,
"OH, HE WAS THIS NICE GUY,
"AND HE WAS DOING
VOLUNTEER WORK,
"AND ONE DAY HE SAID
SOMETHING NICE TO ME,
AND GAVE ME A FLOWER,
AND WE STARTED GOING OUT."
NO, IT'S ALWAYS
STORIES LIKE,
"I WAS AT THE CLUB,
AND THIS GUY CAME UP TO ME,
"AND WAS LIKE, 'I BEEN
STARING AT YOUR ASS ALL NIGHT.
"IS IT COOL IF I
TAKE YOU OUT SOMETIME?'
AND I WAS LIKE, 'YEAH.'"
"WHY WOULD YOU
SAY YES TO THAT?"
"I DON'T KNOW, WHAT'S
THE WORST THAT COULD HAPPEN?"
WHAT'S THE WORST
THAT COULD HAPPEN?
HE COULD PUT SOMETHING
IN YOUR DRINK AND RAPE YOU.
THAT'S THE WORST
THAT COULD HAPPEN.
HE COULD MURDER YOU
AND USE YOUR LEGS
TO MAKE STILTS
THAT LOOK LIKE LEGS.
ANOTHER THING
THAT CAN HAPPEN.
BUT THAT'S MY PROBLEM,
IS I THINK TOO MUCH,
YOU KNOW.
GO TO A BAR,
AND WATCH PEOPLE.
YOU'LL SEE TWO DIFFERENT
TYPES OF GUYS.
THERE'S ONE TYPE OF GUY
THAT'S A GUY LIKE ME.
WE'RE USUALLY SITTING IN THE
CORNER, TALKING TO EACH OTHER.
"EH, EH, I DON'T KNOW..."
[whiny mumbling]
"LET'S JUST TALK TO
EACH OTHER TONIGHT, BRIAN."
THEN THERE'S
A SECOND TYPE OF DUDE.
THE DUMB DUDES.
THEY'RE AT THE BAR,
THEY DON'T CARE ABOUT ANYTHING.
THEY'RE LIKE,
"GIMME A SHOT OF JAGERMEISTER!
"DROP IT IN A BEER WITH
A BUNCH OF OTHER SHIT!
"BLEH!
I'LL SAY ANYTHING TO ANYBODY!
WAAH!"
AND THEY GO UP TO SOME GIRL,
THEY'RE LIKE,
"EXCUSE ME, EXCUSE ME.
"UH, I JUST WANTED TO SAY
"YOU LOOK REALLY
BEAUTIFUL TONIGHT.
"AND I WAS HOPING ONE DAY
I MIGHT BE ABLE
"TO PUT MY HANDS
ON YOUR TITTIES.
MY NAME'S KEVIN."
"HI, KEVIN. I'M LISA.
DO YOU WANT TO BE MY BOYFRIEND
FOR THREE YEARS?"
"I DON'T KNOW.
"IS IT OKAY
IF I'M REALLY SHITTY TO YOU,
AND CHEAT ON YOU
WHENEVER I WANT?"
"YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
I'LL NEVER BREAK UP WITH YOU."
THEN THEY LEAVE TOGETHER.
MEANWHILE, I FINALLY
GET UP MY COURAGE.
"UH, THAT'S
A NICE JACKET."
"GET THE FUCK
OUTTA MY FACE!"
AND THEN SOME INDIAN DUDE
THAT RECOGNIZES ME FROM THE TV
WILL INVITE ME BACK TO HIS DORM
TO PLAY VIDEO GAMES.
[cheers and applause]
TELL ME IF THIS
EVER HAPPENS TO YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE EVER AT A PARTY,
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
AND YOU'RE
TALKING TO A GUY,
AND YOU THINK,
"WOW, THIS GUY IS SO DUMB.
"THIS IS THE DUMBEST GUY
I'VE MET MAYBE ALL YEAR.
"WHAT A DUMB PERSON.
I CANNOT WAIT TO GET OUT
OF THIS CONVERSATION
WITH THIS DUMB PERSON."
AND THEN THEY
SAY SOMETHING LIKE,
"YEAH, AND I GOT TWO KIDS."
AND YOU'RE LIKE--
[gasps] "NO!
"YOU CAN'T HAVE TWO KIDS,
YOU'RE SO STUPID!
"WHAT'RE YOU DOING RAISING KIDS?
YOU'RE SO DUMB!
YOU'RE RAISING MURDERERS!"
THIS HAPPENS TO ME ALL THE TIME.
IT'S SO TERRIFYING.
I WAS TALKING
TO A DUDE AT A PARTY.
HE WAS 26 YEARS OLD,
HE HAD A 3-YEAR-OLD SON.
AND I WAS LIKE,
"WOW, THAT'S AMAZING."
THEN A FEW MINUTES LATER,
I OVERHEARD HIM
TELLING A GROUP OF PEOPLE
THIS STORY ABOUT HOW
A WEEK EARLIER,
HE TRIED TO HAVE SEX
WITH A BOWL
OF MACARONI AND CHEESE.
AND I SAID,
"WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
"YOU CAN'T BE A FATHER,
"AND THEN FUCK A BOWL
OF MACARONI AND CHEESE.
"ONCE YOU HAVE A KID,
THE MACARONI-AND-CHEESE-FUCKING
DAYS ARE OVER."
AND HE'S SITTING HERE
TELLING PEOPLE THE STORY.
HE'S LIKE, "YEAH, AND THEN
I PUT THE CONDOM ON."
AND I WAS LIKE, "WHAT'D
YOU PUT A CONDOM ON FOR?"
AND HE'S LIKE, "I'M NOT TRYING
TO GET CHEESE ALL OVER MY DICK."
AS IF THAT WERE A TOTALLY
REASONABLE THING TO SAY.
AS IF I WAS THE WEIRD ONE FOR
EVEN BRINGING UP THE QUESTION.
YEAH, ME.
THE GUY NOT FUCKING MACARONI.
AND I TOLD HIM,
"YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
"IN THIS SITUATION,
PUTTING A CONDOM ON
MAKES EVERYTHING WAY WORSE."
'CAUSE THAT MEANS
THE WHOLE TIME
HE WENT TO GO
FIND A BOX OF CONDOMS,
OPEN THE BOX OF CONDOMS,
TAKE THE CONDOM OUT,
OPEN THE CONDOM WRAPPER,
PUT THE CONDOM ON HIS PENIS,
GO BACK TO THE MACARONI--
THAT WHOLE TIME,
HE NEVER ONCE THOUGHT,
"YOU KNOW WHAT,
MAYBE I DON'T NEED TO FUCK
"A BOWL OF MACARONI
AND CHEESE.
"MAYBE I CAN DO
LITERALLY ANYTHING ELSE,
AND IT'LL BE
A BETTER USE OF MY TIME."
HOW ARE YOU GONNA DO SOMETHING
LIKE THAT WHEN YOU HAVE A KID?
WHAT IF HIS KID SAW THAT?
HE'D NEVER BE ABLE
TO TELL THAT KID ANYTHING.
"HEY, SON, BE NICE TO PEOPLE.
DO GOOD IN SCHOOL."
"REALLY? I SAW YOU FUCK
A BOWL OF MACARONI AND CHEESE.
"SO, WHY WOULD I
TAKE YOUR ADVICE?
"BY THE WAY,
I'M THREE YEARS OLD.
"MY LANGUAGE SKILLS
ARE VERY IMPRESSIVE.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST
RIDE THIS SHIT OUT ON MY OWN."
[cheers and applause]
I HAVE, UH, INTERNET ACCESS
RIGHT NOW,
'CAUSE THINGS
ARE GOING PRETTY WELL.
AND...I'M SURE SOME OF
YOU GUYS ARE ONLINE AS WELL,
AND I LIKE THE INTERNET,
BUT IT'S VERY
ANNOYING SOMETIMES.
DOES THIS SITUATION
HAPPEN TO YOU?
YOU'RE SITTING
AT YOUR COMPUTER,
WORKING ON SOMETHING
REALLY IMPORTANT.
AND THEN YOU THINK,
"MAN, I WONDER IF HOME ALONE 2
"MADE MORE MONEY
THAN HOME ALONE 1.
"I GOTTA LOOK INTO THIS NOW.
SORRY, IMPORTANT WORK.
SOMETHING MORE PRESSING
HAS COME UP."
I DO STUFF LIKE THAT
ALL THE TIME.
AND WHAT'S SO ANNOYING
IS ONCE I START
LOOKING INTO ONE THING,
I'LL SEE SOMETHING ELSE
I WANT TO RESEARCH.
FOR EXAMPLE,
IN THE HOME ALONE SITUATION,
I'LL BE LOOKING AT THAT,
AND I'LL SAY,
"OH, WOW.
JOE PESCI'S IN THAT MOVIE.
"I DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT JOE PESCI.
MAYBE I SHOULD LEARN EVERYTHING
ABOUT JOE PESCI!"
AND THEN I'LL SPEND HOURS
DOING ALL THIS
JOE PESCI RESEARCH,
AND NOW I KNOW SO MUCH
ABOUT JOE PESCI.
BUT IT'S USELESS INFORMATION.
IT'S NEVER GONNA HELP ME.
I NEVER HEARD OF A SITUATION
WHERE A GUY'S BEEN IN AN ALLEY
WITH A DUDE
WITH A KNIFE JUST LIKE,
"YOU'RE GONNA DIE TONIGHT...
"UNLESS YOU CAN TELL ME
THE NAME OF THE ALBUM
JOE PESCI PUT OUT
WHEN HE WAS A LITTLE KID."
"LITTLE JOE
SURE CAN SING?"
"DAMN IT!
YOU'RE FREE TO GO!
"HOW COME SO MANY PEOPLE
KNOW THAT?
"I GOTTA STOP
"INTEGRATING JOE PESCI
TRIVIA INTO MY MURDERS.
PEOPLE KNOW MORE ABOUT HIM
THAN I ANTICIPATED."
I ALWAYS WASTE TIME
LIKE THAT.
THE OTHER NIGHT,
I WAS UP LATE.
I REMEMBERED I'D NEVER SEEN
ANY OF THOSE SAW MOVIES BEFORE.
THEY'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE PARTICULARLY GOOD MOVIES,
BUT A FRIEND OF MINE TOLD ME,
"AZIZ, YOU GOTTA WATCH SAW 1.
THE TWIST AT THE END
OF SAW 1 IS CRAZY."
AND I LOVE TWISTS
AT THE END OF MOVIES.
SO I WENT ON YOUTUBE,
AND I TYPED, "SAW ENDING."
SURE ENOUGH, CLIP COMES UP.
I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
"UH, AZIZ, YOU DIDN'T SEE
THE REST OF THE MOVIE.
THE CLIP WON'T
MAKE ANY SENSE."
DON'T WORRY.
I'M NOT STUPID.
FIRST, I WENT ON
THE SAW WIKIPEDIA PAGE,
AND I READ
THE PLOT SUMMARY.
AND WHEN I GOT TO
THE LAST PARAGRAPH, I STOPPED,
THEN I WENT BACK
AND WATCHED THAT VIDEO,
AND LET ME TELL YOU,
I DID NOT SEE THAT COMING.
SOMEONE RECENTLY
SENT ME A PASSWORD
TO ONE OF THOSE
ONLINE PORN SITES.
AND THE PASSWORD WORKED.
AND I DON'T KNOW
IF ANYONE HERE'S EVER HAD
MEMBERSHIP ACCESS
TO ANY OF THOSE SITES,
BUT IT IS INCREDIBLE.
IF YOU'RE KIND OF
ON THE FENCE, LIKE,
"I DON'T KNOW,
IT JUST DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
IT WOULD BE WORTH IT
TO SPEND--"
DO IT.
NOW, THE TREND
IN THESE SITES IS
THEY TRY TO MAKE IT SEEM
LIKE THIS STUFF
ALL REALLY HAPPENED.
LIKE THIS IS REAL LIFE.
THESE AREN'T ACTORS,
THIS STUFF REALLY HAPPENED.
SO THEY HAVE
DUMB NAMES LIKE,
"REAL-LIFE-DICK-PARTY.COM."
AND THE VIDEOS
ARE ALL THE SAME.
THESE GUYS GO UP TO SOME GIRLS,
THEY'RE LIKE,
"EXCUSE ME, YOU GIRLS
WANT TO COME BACK TO OUR PLACE
AND HAVE A DICK PARTY?"
AND THE GIRLS
ARE ALWAYS LIKE, "UH, YEAH!"
AND THEY GET IN THEIR CAR,
THEY DRIVE BACK TO THE HOUSE,
THEY HAVE SEX,
THEY FILM IT,
AND IT GOES
"REAL-LIFE-DICK-PARTY.COM."
DOES ANYONE THINK
THOSE CLIPS ARE REAL?
IF THEY WANT PEOPLE
TO THINK IT'S REAL,
EVERY NOW AND THEN
THEY SHOULD HAVE A CLIP
WHERE SOME GUYS
GO UP TO SOME GIRLS, LIKE,
"EXCUSE ME, UH, YOU GIRLS
WANT TO COME BACK TO OUR PLACE
AND HAVE A DICK PARTY?"
AND THE GIRL'S LIKE,
"WHAT? THAT'S DISGUSTING!
GET OUTTA HERE,
YOU ASSHOLE!"
"REAL-LIFE-DICK-PARTY.COM."
THEN YOU'RE AT HOME LIKE,
"MAN, I GUESS IT IS REAL.
"THOSE GIRLS DIDN'T WANT
TO HAVE A DICK PARTY AT ALL.
THEY JUST CONTINUED ON
TO WHOLE FOODS."
NOW, THE FIRST VIDEO
I WATCHED ON THE SITE,
THESE GUYS GO INTO
A DOUGHNUT SHOP, RIGHT?
AND THEY'RE TALKING TO THE GIRLS
IN THE DOUGHNUT SHOP,
THEY'RE LIKE, "HEY, SO,
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF US
"MAYBE GIVING YOU SOME MONEY,
AND THEN WE CAN HOOK UP
IN THE BACK
OF THE DOUGHNUT SHOP?"
AND THE GIRLS ARE LIKE,
"OKAY, THAT SOUNDS GOOD."
SHE WAS NOT
A VERY GOOD ACTRESS.
SO, THEY GO IN THE BACK,
AND THEY START HOOKING UP.
SO, THERE'S A GUY
HOOKING UP WITH A GIRL
IN THE BACK
OF A DOUGHNUT SHOP.
NOW, THIS GUY
EVENTUALLY DOES
WHAT ANY REASONABLE PERSON
WOULD DO IN THAT SITUATION,
AND HE PUTS A DOUGHNUT
AROUND HIS DICK.
NOW, THE WOMAN IS PERFORMING
FELLATIO-TYPE SERVICES,
AND SHE'S GETTING DANGEROUSLY
CLOSE TO THIS DOUGHNUT.
AND THEN AT ONE POINT, SHE JUST
TAKES A BITE OF THE DOUGHNUT.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT AS SOON AS THAT HAPPENED,
I JUST WENT,
"WHOA, THAT WAS AWESOME!
WHAT AN AMAZING CHOICE
BY THAT ACTRESS."
I WONDER IF THAT
WAS IMPROVISED,
LIKE THE DOUGHNUT
WAS JUST THERE,
AND SHE'S JUST LIKE...
[chomps]
AND THE DIRECTOR'S LIKE...
[mouths words]
BUT WHAT DOES THAT SAY
ABOUT ME AS A PERSON
THAT I GOT SO EXCITED?
I GUESS I JUST
LIKE FOOD TOO MUCH.
IT'S A GOOD THING I DON'T WRITE
THE SCRIPTS FOR THOSE VIDEOS.
MY SCRIPT WOULD BE LIKE,
"ALL RIGHT, SO, YOU PICK
THIS GIRL UP IN LOS ANGELES,
"AND YOU DROP HER OFF AT
THIS RESTAURANT CALLED ANIMAL,
"AND SHE ORDERS
THE HAMACHI TOSTADA,
"THE POUTINE, THE RABBIT LEGS,
AND THE STRAWBERRY POUND CAKE.
"AND THEY BRING HER EVERYTHING,
AND SHE'S LIKE,
"'OH, MY GOD,
THIS LOOKS SO GOOD.'
"AND SHE EATS EVERYTHING.
THERE'S NOT A BITE LEFT.
"AND SHE'S LIKE,
'WOW, THAT WAS DELICIOUS.
MAYBE THE BEST MEAL
I'VE HAD ALL YEAR.'"
"REAL-LIFE-DICK-PARTY.COM."
YOU KNOW WHAT'S WEIRD
ABOUT THAT DOUGHNUT VIDEO
IS THEY FILMED IT
IN A REAL DOUGHNUT SHOP.
WHICH MEANS THEY HAD TO PAY
A DOUGHNUT SHOP OWNER
TO USE THAT AS A LOCATION.
BUT I GUESS IF YOU'RE
A DOUGHNUT SHOP OWNER,
THE RISK IS PRETTY LOW.
WHAT ARE THE CHANCES
OF SOMEONE AT HOME
WATCHING THE VIDEO
AND GOING,
"OH, NO, THAT'S WHERE
I GET MY DOUGHNUTS FROM!
"THAT'S WHAT GOES ON
BACK THERE?
"I JUST THOUGHT
THEY WERE PUTTING
CHOCOLATE AND JELLY
IN SOME OF THE DOUGHNUTS."
BUT THAT'S GOT TO BE
HAPPENING TO SOME DUDE.
THEY FILM ALL THESE VIDEOS
IN THE SAME TOWN, I IMAGINE.
THERE'S GOTTA BE SOME DUDE
WAKING UP EVERY MORNING LIKE,
"OH, NO, NOT THE BANK TOO!
"I WAS SUPPOSED
TO MAKE A DEPOSIT TODAY!
AND THERE'S
JIZZ EVERYWHERE!"
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THE BEST THING
THAT COULD HAPPEN
IN THE DOUGHNUT VIDEO
IS THE GIRL
TAKES A BITE
OF THE DOUGHNUT,
AND THEN SHE JUST
STARTS WALKING AWAY.
AND THE GUY'S LIKE,
"HEY, WHERE'RE YOU GOING?"
AND SHE'S LIKE, "I WASN'T
TRYING TO SUCK YOUR DICK.
"I JUST WANTED A BITE
OF THAT DOUGHNUT.
THAT LOOKED DELICIOUS."
"BOB'S DOUGHNUTS.
THE BEST DOUGHNUTS IN TOWN.
WE WON'T MAKE YOU
SUCK A DICK FOR YOURS."
I WAS DOING A SHOW
ONE NIGHT,
AND THEY HAD A WOMAN
SIGNING MY ENTIRE ACT
TO THE LEFT OF THE STAGE,
AND WHENEVER I GOT
TO THAT PUNCH LINE
WHERE I SAID,
"JIZZ EVERYWHERE,"
SHE WENT LIKE THIS...
AND IT WAS AMAZING.
I SAID, "JIZZ EVERYWHERE,"
A FEW MORE TIMES
JUST TO MAKE SURE I UNDERSTOOD
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
'CAUSE THAT HAD TO BE
AN ON-THE-FLY SIGN
FOR "JIZZ EVERYWHERE."
SHE'S LIKE, "OKAY, THERE'S JI--
UH-OH, IT'S EVERYWHERE."
'CAUSE "EVERYWHERE" CAN'T BE--
[whines]
YOU'D LOOK CRAZY EVERY TIME
YOU HAD TO SIGN "EVERYWHERE."
"HEY, I'M NEW IN TOWN.
IS THERE A JIMMY JOHN'S NEARBY?"
"OH, THOSE ARE EVERYWHERE.
THERE'S A JIMMY JOHN'S HERE,
HERE, HERE, AND HERE."
THAT'S GOTTA BE
CUSTOM FOR "JIZZ."
"JIZZ EVERYWHERE.
"THE CEILING,
THE CARPET, THE WALLS,
"THE PLATES, THE TUPPERWARE,
THE TELEVISION.
"I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT IT'S EVERYWHERE,
AND I'M REALLY
SORRY ABOUT IT."
I ALSO LOVE THAT "JIZZ"
IS JUST--MEH, THAT'S "JIZZ."
MEH. NO MORE THOUGHT
WENT INTO THAT.
GUY WAS UP LATE
DEVELOPING SIGN LANGUAGE.
"UH, GUYS, I'M REALLY TIRED.
CAN WE PICK UP TOMORROW?
"I AM REALLY BEAT.
I REALLY NEED SOME SLEEP.
"A FEW MORE WORDS? FINE.
WHAT'S THE NEXT WORD?
'JIZZ'? THAT'S 'JIZZ.'"
"WHAT IF IT'S EVERYWHERE?"
"THAT'S 'JIZZ EVERYWHERE'!
"HOW COME I GET
ALL THE DIRTY WORDS?
BRIAN GOT 'PUPPY,'
I GOT 'JIZZ EVERYWHERE'?"
AND THE ONLY REASON
I BRING THIS UP
IS, YOU KNOW, IT COULD BE
DAYS FROM NOW, WEEKS FROM NOW,
MONTHS FROM NOW,
YEARS FROM NOW,
BUT ONE DAY, ONE OF YOU GUYS
COULD BE WALKING AROUND
AND SEE A DEAF PERSON
ABOUT TO WALK INTO A ROOM
WHERE THERE'S
JIZZ EVERYWHERE,
AND YOU'LL BE LIKE...
AND THEY'LL BE LIKE...
AND THEY'LL HEAD
SOMEWHERE ELSE, FREE OF JIZZ.
[cheers and applause]
I'M FROM SOUTH CAROLINA, AND...
[scattered cheering]
THANK YOU.
AND WHENEVER I TELL PEOPLE
THAT, THEY'RE ALWAYS LIKE,
[gasps] "OH, NO.
"BUT IT'S SO RACIST THERE.
AND YOUR SKIN IS BROWN.
HOW DID YOU SURVIVE?"
AND SURE, CERTAIN PARTS
OF SOUTH CAROLINA
CAN BE PRETTY RACIST.
MORE RACIST THAN OTHER
PARTS OF THE COUNTRY.
BUT WHAT
THESE PEOPLE FORGET
IS THAT THE FOOD THERE
IS DELICIOUS.
SO GROWING UP IN SOUTH CAROLINA,
IT'S KIND OF LIKE,
"OH, DID THAT GUY
JUST SAY THE N-WORD?
"OOH, FRIED CHICKEN
AND BISCUITS. NEVER MIND!
NOM YUM YUM YUM YUM YUM!"
EVEN IF RIGHT NOW SOME DUDE
STOOD UP AND WAS LIKE,
"HEY, I'M GONNA SAY
A BUNCH OF RACIST STUFF,
BUT AFTERWARDS
I'LL GIVE YOU A BISCUIT,"
I'D BE LIKE,
"THAT'S A WEIRD DEAL,
BUT I'LL TAKE IT."
'CAUSE I HATE RACISM,
BUT I LOVE A GOOD BISCUIT.
I JUST THINK
IT'S A LITTLE SILLY
WHEN SOMETIMES
PEOPLE ACT AS IF
ALL THE REALLY CRAZY RACISM
IS JUST IN PLACES
LIKE SOUTH CAROLINA, ALABAMA,
MISSISSIPPI, OR WHATEVER,
BECAUSE I'VE SEEN CRAZY
RACIST STUFF HAPPEN EVERYWHERE.
I HAVE A FRIEND IN L.A.
HE'S KOREAN, RIGHT?
AND HE GOT LOCKED
OUT OF HIS APARTMENT.
SO, HE CALLED
A LOCKSMITH, OKAY?
AND THE LOCKSMITH'S
GETTING ALL HIS INFO.
HE'S LIKE,
"WHAT'S YOUR LAST NAME?"
AND HE'S LIKE, "CHUN."
THE GUY GOES, "WHAT KIND
OF LAST NAME IS THAT?"
THE GUY GOES,
"UH, KOREAN-AMERICAN."
AND THE GUY GOES,
"I HATE KOREAN-AMERICANS.
KOREAN-AMERICANS ARE TRYING
TO DESTROY AMERICA."
AND HE HUNG UP ON HIM.
WOULDN'T UNLOCK HIS DOOR.
AND I THOUGHT, "WOW.
SO, THIS LOCKSMITH DOES NO
BUSINESS WITH KOREAN-AMERICANS."
BUT I WONDERED,
"HOW MANY KOREAN-AMERICANS
"WOULD HAVE TO CALL HIM,
BEFORE ECONOMICALLY,
HE COULDN'T AFFORD
TO BE THAT RACIST?"
LIKE, WHAT IF KOREAN PEOPLE
JUST KEPT CALLING?
WOULD HE EVENTUALLY BE LIKE,
"DAMN IT, MAN,
"I WOULD'VE MADE $5,000
YESTERDAY
"IF I DIDN'T HATE
KOREAN PEOPLE!
"THIS IS SO STUPID!
"KOREAN-AMERICANS AREN'T
TRYING TO DESTROY AMERICA,
THEY CAN'T EVEN
FIND THEIR KEYS!"
BUT THEN, WEIRDLY,
THAT STEREOTYPE WOULD GET
INTEGRATED INTO HIS RACISM.
LIKE, HE WOULD SEE KOREAN
PEOPLE, AND HE'D BE LIKE,
"PSSH, LET ME GUESS.
CAN'T FIND YOUR KEYS?
CHING-CHONG, BING-BONG,
WHERE'S MY KEYS?"
HE SEES A KOREAN DUDE
OPENING A DOOR, HE'S LIKE,
"HA! THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU DON'T SEE EVERY DAY!
"KOREAN DUDE ACTUALLY
HAD HIS KEYS FOR ONCE.
"[hums Oriental Riff]
♪ WHERE'S MY KEYS? ♪
[Oriental Riff]
♪ THEY'RE IN YOUR HOUSE ♪"
NOW, OBVIOUSLY, I DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN PEOPLE ARE RACIST,
BUT I AM WEIRDLY FASCINATED
BY RACIAL SLURS.
LIKE "CHING-CHONG, BING-BONG."
HOW DID WE ALL KNOW THAT?
AS SOON AS I SAID,
"CHING-CHONG, BING-BONG,"
EVERYONE'S LIKE, "YUP,
RACIST TERM FOR ASIAN PEOPLE.
I'M ONBOARD."
NO ONE WAS LOST.
HOW ARE RACIST THINGS LIKE THAT
SO UBIQUITOUS?
AT ONE POINT,
DO OUR PARENTS SIT US DOWN?
"HEY, BY THE WAY, THE RACIST
THING FOR ASIAN PEOPLE
"IS 'CHING-CHONG,
BING-BONG.'
"DON'T EVER SAY IT TO 'EM.
"WELL, IF THEY SAY
SOMETHING RACIST TO YOU,
"I DON'T KNOW,
I GOTTA GET OUTTA HERE.
DON'T TOUCH
THAT MACARONI."
ONE DAY, I DECIDED
TO DO SOME RESEARCH
ON RACIAL SLURS, AND SEE
IF I COULD LEARN ANYTHING.
AND I FOUND A VERY
INTERESTING ARTICLE.
IT WAS TITLED,
"LIST OF EVERY ETHNIC SLUR."
AND IT WAS 21 PAGES LONG.
AND I READ ALL OF 'EM.
AND IF IT'S COOL
WITH YOU GUYS,
I'D NOW LIKE TO SHARE
A FEW OF MY FAVORITES.
[cheers and applause]
NOW, THESE ARE RACIAL SLURS,
ETHNIC SLURS, OKAY?
SO, THEY'RE OFFENSIVE.
THEY'RE OFFENSIVE
BY THEIR VERY NATURE.
SO, IF I SAY ONE,
OR I DESCRIBE ONE,
AND YOU'RE OFFENDED,
THERE'S NO REASON TO BE LIKE,
"OH..."
[trails off]
'CAUSE WE ALL KNOW
THEY'RE OFFENSIVE.
SO INSTEAD, YOU CAN
SHUT YOUR FUCKING MOUTH.
AT THE SAME TIME,
THOUGH, AT THE SAME TIME,
I DON'T WANNA
DO THIS BIT,
AND LOOK AT THE AUDIENCE
AND SEE SOME GUY JUST LIKE,
"YEAH!
[excited laughter]
YEAH!"
[grunting]
'CAUSE THAT WOULD BE
TERRIFYING
ON THE OTHER END
OF THE SPECTRUM.
SO, HERE WE GO.
MY FAVORITE RACIAL SLURS, OKAY?
THE FIRST ONE--
IT'S DEFINED AS,
"A DEROGATORY DESCRIPTIVE PHRASE
"FOR A PERSON OF PREDOMINANTLY
CAUCASIAN ANCESTRY
"WITH REAL
OR SUSPECTED
DISTANT ASIAN
OR AFRICAN ANCESTRY."
NOW, THIS IS A PRETTY
SPECIFIC SITUATION
TO NEED TO BUST OUT
A RACIAL SLUR,
BUT, UH, IF YOU'RE EVER
CAUGHT IN A JAM,
ALL YOU GOTTA SAY IS,
"YOU KNOW WHAT, MAN?
"YOU GOT A TOUCH
OF THE TAR BRUSH!
"YEAH, YOU HEARD ME. YOU GOT
A TOUCH OF THE TAR BRUSH.
"THIS IS A TAR BRUSH,
THIS IS YOU. BOOP!
"YOU DON'T THINK I SEE
THAT DISTANT ASIAN ANCESTRY
IN YOUR PREDOMINANTLY
CAUCASIAN FACE?"
SOME OF
THE RACIAL SLURS, UH,
CONTAINED OTHER RACIAL SLURS
WITHIN THEMSELVES.
THEY WERE COMBINATIONS,
WHICH SEEMED
VERY INCONVENIENT TO ME.
FOR EXAMPLE, THERE WAS ONE
FOR NATIVE AMERICAN PEOPLE--
"PRAIRIE N-WORD."
"PRAIRIE N-WORD"?
WHENEVER I HEAR THAT,
I IMAGINE THIS SCENARIO:
SOME GUY'S TALKING
TO A NATIVE-AMERICAN DUDE.
"GET OUTTA HERE,
PRAIRIE N-WORD."
SOME BLACK GUY'S LIKE,
"WHAT'D YOU SAY?"
"DUDE, I SAID, 'PRAIRIE.'
THIS DOESN'T CONCERN YOU.
STEP OFF."
BUT A LOT OF TIMES,
YOU READ THE RACIAL SLUR,
AND IT'S LIKE, WHAT?
WHAT ETHNICITY IS THAT FOR?
WHO WOULD YOU SAY THAT TO?
SEE IF YOU CAN GUESS ONE.
SEE IF YOU CAN GUESS THIS ONE.
"DOGAN."
IT'S IRISH CATHOLIC. SEE?
NO ONE COULD GUESS IT.
SEE IF YOU CAN
GUESS THIS ONE.
"CHRIST KILLER."
ANYONE HAVE A GUESS
ON THAT ONE?
"CHRIST KILLER."
WHO WOULD YOU SAY THAT TO?
CHRIST KILLER.
KILLER OF CHRIST.
DID SOMEONE SAY,
"JEWISH PEOPLE"? NO.
IT'S ACTUALLY
FOR ASIAN PEOPLE.
IT'S USED BY PEOPLE
THAT HATE ASIANS SO MUCH
THEY BLAME 'EM
FOR THE DEATH OF CHRIST.
"CHRIST KILLER!"
"BUT I'M ASIAN!"
"I KNOW. WHY YOU THINK
GOD CREATED LOCKS?
CHING-CHONG, BING-BONG,
YOU KILLED CHRIST."
BUT WHAT I LEARNED
READING THAT LIST, THOUGH,
WAS I THINK YOU CAN MAKE
ANYTHING SOUND
RACIST OR HATEFUL.
WITH THE RIGHT TONE IN YOUR
VOICE, THE RIGHT INFLECTION,
YOU CAN MAKE ANYTHING
SOUND HATEFUL.
LET ME SEE IF I CAN CREATE
A RACIAL SLUR RIGHT NOW.
LIKE, UH, SIR,
YOU SITTING RIGHT THERE.
UH, WHAT IS YOUR ETHNICITY?
WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
SHUT UP, KIT-KAT!
QUIT LAUGHING, KIT-KAT!
SEE? THAT STARTED TO SOUND
REAL RACIST.
'CAUSE YOU'RE THINKING,
"WHOA, WHOA.
"THAT GUY'S NOT A KIT-KAT.
HE'S A PERSON.
"AZIZ MUST BE IMPLYING
HE'S BROWN ON THE OUTSIDE,
WAFER-LIKE ON THE INSIDE."
I'VE BEEN HAVING FUN
DOING THIS TOUR.
WHEN I STARTED THE TOUR,
I WAS READING THIS
MOTLEY CRUE AUTOBIOGRAPHY.
AND IT WAS
REALLY INTERESTING.
I QUICKLY LEARNED
THAT MOTLEY CRUE TOURS--
WAY CRAZIER
THAN AN AZIZ TOUR.
IT'S FASCINATING BECAUSE
THESE GUYS WERE AT ONE POINT
THE BIGGEST BAND IN THE WORLD,
PERFORMING AT ARENAS AND STUFF,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME
THEY WERE DOING MASSIVE AMOUNTS
OF COCAINE AND HEROIN
ALL THE TIME,
AND MY BODY JUST COULD NOT
TAKE ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
EVEN IF JUST TONIGHT,
I WAS LIKE, "LET'S DO HEROIN!"
THE NEXT DAY, IT'D BE LIKE,
"AZIZ IS DEAD!
YEAH, HE DID HEROIN ONCE,
AND HE DIED."
"HOW MUCH HEROIN
DID HE DO?"
"NONE, HE JUST
HAD A NEEDLE IN HIS ARM,
AND FELT WOOZY
AND FELL OF A BUILDING."
THEY HAVE ALL THESE
INSANE STORIES ABOUT GIRLS.
LIKE, AT ONE POINT,
THEY'RE HAVING SEX
WITH ALL THESE GROUPIES, RIGHT?
BUT THEY HAD
GIRLFRIENDS AT HOME.
SO AT THE END OF THE NIGHT,
TO COVER THEIR TRACKS,
THEY WOULD PUT THEIR PENISES
INSIDE BURRITOS.
HOW DID THAT
BECOME THE PLAN?
WAS A MOTLEY CRUE GUY
JUST RUNNING AROUND?
"OH, MY GOD, MY DICK SMELLS LIKE
ALL THESE OTHER VAGINAS!
"MY GIRLFRIEND'S GONNA FIND OUT
I'M CHEATING ON HER!
"WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
WHAT I'MA DO? WHAT I'MA DO?
"CAN I WASH MY DICK
WITH SOAP AND WATER?
"NO! THAT WON'T WORK!
WHY? I DON'T KNOW!
"QUICK, GIMME THAT BURRITO.
"IT'S PERFECT.
THE SCENT OF PICO DE GALLO
WILL TOTALLY THROW OFF
MY GIRLFRIEND."
THAT STORY'S
A QUINTESSENTIAL DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A COMEDY TOUR
AND A ROCK TOUR.
A ROCK TOUR, SOME DUDE'S
FUCKING A BURRITO, IT'S LIKE,
"YEAH, MAN,
GOTTA GET THE SMELL
OF ALL THESE OTHER VAGINAS
OFF MY DICK."
COMEDY TOUR, IT'S LIKE...
[cries] "I'M SO ALONE!"
I LIKE TOURING.
THE ONLY THING I DON'T LIKE
IS THE ACTUAL TRAVEL ITSELF.
'CAUSE PEOPLE CAN BE SO RUDE
WHEN YOU'RE TRAVELING.
THE RUDEST PERSON I'VE EVER MET
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE
IS THE EASTERN EUROPEAN CUSTOMS
LADY AT THE TORONTO AIRPORT.
WHAT'S THAT LADY'S PROBLEM?
WHY SHE GOTTA BE SO RUDE?
CUSTOMS PEOPLE
ARE THE FIRST PEOPLE YOU MEET
WHEN YOU GO
TO A NEW COUNTRY.
THEY SHOULD BE NICE,
WELCOMING.
THIS LADY, AS SOON AS YOU
WALK UP, SHE JUST GOES,
"WHAT YOU ARE
DOING HERE?"
AND I WAS LIKE,
"UH, I'M SHOOTING A MOVIE."
SHE GOES, "WHAT IT MEAN,
'SHOOTING MOVIE'?"
LIKE, "YOU KNOW,
LIKE FILMING A MOVIE."
SHE GOES, "I KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS FILMING MOVIE.
"I MEAN ARE YOU DOING
THE LIGHTS? ARE YOU ACTING?
ARE YOU DIRECTING? I COULD DO
WITHOUT YOUR SARCASM."
I WAS LIKE,
"WHY ARE YOU BEING SO MEAN?
"I SAID SOMETHING,
AND YOU WENT,
"'WHAT IT MEAN,
"SHOOTING MOVIE"?'
"SO I JUST ASSUMED
YOU'RE KIND OF DUMB,
"AND I'M TRYING
TO EXPLAIN THINGS TO YOU.
"I'M STUNNED YOU KNOW
WHAT THE WORD 'SARCASM' MEANS.
"YOUR ENGLISH
IS SLIGHTLY BETTER
"THAN ANIMAL
FROM THE MUPPET BABIES.
AND YOU'RE YELLING AT ME
LIKE A PSYCHOPATH."
AND I GOT MY STAMP,
AND I WALKED ON.
BUT I KIND OF WISH
AFTER I'D GOTTEN THE STAMP,
I TURNED AROUND, AND I WAS LIKE,
"GUESS WHAT. I LIED."
AND THEN PULLED OUT A DVD
OF JURASSIC PARK AND A HANDGUN,
WAS LIKE, "THIS IS WHAT IT MEANS
'SHOOTING MOVIE.'"
BANG, BANG,
BANG, BANG, BANG!
PASSENGERS CAN ALSO
BE RUDE TO YOU ALSO.
I WAS FLYING HOME ONCE, AND I
WAS SITTING NEXT TO THIS COUPLE.
THEY HAD THESE TWO PUPPIES
THAT THEY PUT UNDER THE SEATS
IN FRONT OF US.
AND THERE WAS AN OLDER COUPLE
SITTING THERE, AND THEY SAID,
"HEY, UH, YOU GUYS MIND MOVING
THE PUPPIES OVER A LITTLE BIT
SO WE'LL PUT
OUR JACKETS UNDER THERE?"
AND THE LADY
WITH THE PUPPIES IS LIKE,
"UH, NO. WE HAVE TWO PUPPIES,
THEY NEED ALL THE ROOM.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH."
AND I WAS LIKE,
"WHOA, WHY'D SHE NEED TO BE
SO RUDE ABOUT THAT?"
AND THEN SHE STARTED TALKING
TO HER HUSBAND.
SHE'S LIKE, "UGH, CAN YOU
BELIEVE THOSE PEOPLE,
"ASKING US TO MOVE THE PUPPIES
FOR THEIR JACKETS?
WHAT KIND OF NERVE DO THEY HAVE?
WHO DO THEY THINK THEY ARE?"
AND I WAS LIKE...
[whispers]
"I FUCKIN' HATE THIS LADY."
SO I STARTED CHIMING IN.
I WAS LIKE, "YEAH, I HEARD THAT.
"I COULDN'T BELIEVE THEY'D
ASK SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
"THOSE PEOPLE ARE AWFUL.
THOSE PEOPLE ARE TERRIBLE.
THOSE PEOPLE
DESERVE TO BE MURDERED."
AND I DIDN'T SAY ANOTHER WORD
THE WHOLE FLIGHT.
AND THEN THE FLIGHT LANDS.
AND THE OLD COUPLE GETS UP,
THEY LEAVE THE PLANE.
NOW THE YOUNG COUPLE'S
ABOUT TO GET UP,
BUT I HOLD 'EM DOWN, AND I GO,
"NO, NO. I GOT THIS."
AND I STEP OVER 'EM,
AND I START FOLLOWING
THE OLD PEOPLE, RIGHT?
YOUNG COUPLE'S BEHIND ME,
WE GET OUTSIDE THE AIRPORT,
I PULL OUT THE GUN THAT I HAD
FROM THE PREVIOUS JOKE,
LOAD IN TWO BULLETS.
I AIM IT AT THE OLD PEOPLE,
BUT THEN I SPIN AROUND
AND I AIM IT AT THE PUPPIES.
BANG, BANG!
I SHOOT BOTH THOSE PUPPIES
IN THE FACE.
AND I GO, "NEVER BE RUDE
TO THE ELDERLY AGAIN.
HAVE FUN BURYING
YOUR DEAD PUPPIES."
I KNOW WHAT SOME OF YOU
ARE THINKING.
"OH, NO!
WHY'D THE PUPPIES GET SHOT?
THE PUPPIES DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING!"
I DIDN'T REALLY SHOOT
ANY PUPPIES.
YOU'RE BEING STUPID.
I HAVE MET SOME REALLY
INTERESTING PEOPLE ON TOUR.
ONE OF MY FAVORITE PEOPLE
THAT I MET
WAS THIS GENTLEMAN WHO ONCE
PICKED ME UP FROM THE AIRPORT
AND DROVE ME
TO THE VENUE.
AND I WAS TALKING TO THIS GUY,
AND I WAS LIKE,
"WHAT DID YOU DO
BEFORE YOU WERE A DRIVER?"
AND HE GOES, "I USED TO BE
A CELEBRITY BODYGUARD."
I WAS LIKE, "WHOA.
WHO'D YOU BODYGUARD FOR?"
HE'S LIKE, "YOU NAME IT.
BRUCE WILLIS, MILEY CYRUS,
JONAS BROTHERS."
LIKE, "WHOA. OUT OF ALL
THE PEOPLE YOU BODYGUARDED FOR,
"WHO WAS THE TOUGHEST PERSON
TO DO SECURITY FOR?
WHO HAD
THE CRAZIEST FANS?"
HE GOES, "TOUGHEST PERSON
TO DO SECURITY FOR? CHER.
CRAZIEST FANS?
PAULY SHORE."
AND I WAS LIKE, "WHAT?
THOSE ARE BOTH WRONG ANSWERS."
I CAN DO SECURITY
FOR PAULY SHORE.
"HEY, MAN, CAN YOU LEAVE
PAULY SHORE ALONE? THANKS.
ALL RIGHT, PAULY, LET'S GO.
THOSE TWO GUYS ARE GONE."
AND THEN I ASKED HIM--
I SAID, "WHAT'D YOU DO
BEFORE YOU WERE
A CELEBRITY BODYGUARD?"
HE GOES, "USED TO DRIVE
MADONNA'S TOUR BUS."
I SAID, "HOW WAS THAT?"
"NOT FUN."
I SAID, "WHY?"
HE GOES, "'CAUSE EVERY TIME
I DROVE THE BUS,
ONE OF HER DANCERS
PUT HIS DICK ON MY SHOULDER."
THAT WAS NOT WHAT
I WAS EXPECTING HIM TO SAY.
SO I SAID, "SIR, YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO ELABORATE."
AND HE TOLD ME THE STORY,
AND BASICALLY,
ANY TIME HE WAS DRIVING THE BUS,
AT ONE POINT,
ONE OF MADONNA'S DANCERS
WOULD JUST COME UP AND...
[thumps mic]
THROW A DICK
ON HIS SHOULDER.
AND THIS HAPPENED SO MANY TIMES
HE HAD TO QUIT HIS JOB
AND GET INTO
A NEW PROFESSION.
BUT I GUESS THAT WOULD
MAKE YOU QUIT ANY JOB.
YOU COULD BE A LAWYER.
PEOPLE WOULD GO, "HEY, MAN,
WEREN'T YOU A LAWYER?"
"YEAH, I WAS. TILL THIS NEW
PARTNER JOINED THE FIRM.
"AND EVERY TIME
I PRESENTED A CASE,
"HE PUT HIS DICK
ON MY SHOULDER.
SO NOW I WORK AT QUIZNOS."
EVEN IF YOUR JOB
WAS JUST STARING AT A DICK
ON YOUR LEFT SHOULDER
FOR THREE HOURS A DAY,
IF AT SOME POINT,
ANOTHER GUY CAME
AND PUT HIS DICK
ON YOUR RIGHT SHOULDER,
YOU'D BE LIKE, "WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS?
"I NEVER
SIGNED UP FOR THAT.
"I SAID ONE DICK ON THE LEFT
SHOULDER FOR THREE HOURS A DAY.
"LOOK AT THE DICK-SHOULDER
CONTRACT WE SIGNED, MAN.
"THE LANGUAGE
IS VERY SPECIFIC.
"DICKS CAN'T
JUST START POPPING UP
"ON MY KNEES, ELBOWS,
AND TOES NOW. WE HAVE A DEAL.
"YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S FINE.
"IF THIS IS HOW YOU GUYS
RUN THINGS, I QUIT.
[thumps mic]
I'M PAULY SHORE!
I DON'T NEED THIS SHIT!"
RIGHT NOW, I WANTED TO TAKE
A COUPLE OF MINUTES
TO UPDATE YOU ON ONE OF MY
FAVORITE PEOPLE IN THE WORLD,
AND THAT'S MY CHUBBY
LITTLE COUSIN HARRIS.
[cheers and applause]
[chuckles]
HARRIS IS A LITTLE COUSIN
OF MINE THAT LIVES IN GEORGIA
AND, YOU KNOW, I DON'T HAVE
ANY KIDS OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT,
SO I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD UPDATE
YOU ON WHAT HE'S BEEN UP TO.
UH, HARRIS IS A WEIRD KID.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T GET TO SPEND
A TON OF TIME WITH HIM.
BUT I DO CHECK UP ON HIM
REGULARLY ON HIS FACEBOOK PAGE,
AND READ HIS
STATUS UPDATES.
HE RECENTLY
HAD A QUOTE UP THERE.
AND THE QUOTE SAID,
"LIFE'S A DIRTY GAME.
YOU GOTTA PLAY DIRTY TO WIN IT."
DASH, "HARRIS."
HE'S QUOTING HIMSELF
ON THIS ONE.
YUP, THAT'S
A HARRIS ORIGINAL.
THAT'S NOT
FROM SEASON FOUR OF THE WIRE.
THAT'S FROM A CHUBBY KID
NAMED HARRIS
WHO ONCE TOLD ME HIS
FAVORITE FOOD IS HOT POCKETS.
WHAT A DARK THING TO SAY.
"LIFE'S A DIRTY GAME.
YOU GOTTA PLAY DIRTY TO WIN IT."
WHEN HAS HARRIS
PLAYED DIRTY IN LIFE?
I CAN ONLY THINK
OF ONE INSTANCE.
IT'S WHEN
HE'S PLAYING HALO.
'CAUSE AS SOON AS
THE BOARD STARTS,
HE ALWAYS KNOWS WHERE
THE ROCKET LAUNCHERS ARE,
AND HE GRABS 'EM AND STARTS
BLOWING EVERYBODY UP.
IT'S FUCKED UP,
HE DOES THIS SHIT EVERY TIME,
THAT'S WHY I DON'T
PLAY HALO WITH HIM ANYMORE.
NOW, I'M SURE THERE'S
SOME PEOPLE HERE
THAT HAVE NEVER PLAYED HALO,
AND THAT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE,
SO I WILL GIVE YOU
AN ANALOGY, OKAY?
IT WOULD BE AS IF YOU'RE
PLAYING MONOPOLY, RIGHT?
AND, UM, SOMEONE ROLLED A 10
AND LANDED ON PARK PLACE,
AND THEN HARRIS CAME IN
WITH A ROCKET LAUNCHER
AND BLEW EVERYBODY UP.
LAST TIME
I SPOKE WITH HARRIS,
I SAID, "WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON?"
AND HE SAID,
"I'M APPLYING FOR COLLEGE.
IS THERE ANY WAY YOU CAN HELP ME
WITH MY COLLEGE ESSAYS?"
AND I WAS LIKE, "YES.
"'CAUSE YOU'RE A WEIRDO,
AND WHATEVER YOU'RE GONNA WRITE
"IS GONNA BE INSANE, SO I COULD
READ IT TO PEOPLE IN PUBLIC,
AND IT'LL HELP ME
WITH MY JOB."
[cheers and applause]
SO I BROUGHT ALONG...
A COPY OF HIS ESSAY.
AND THIS IS 100% REAL.
THE ESSAY IS TITLED,
"ALL THE SMALL THINGS."
"TAKE THE THUMB.
"EVEN THOUGH IT IS
JUST ANOTHER FINGER,
"IT IS THE MOST ESSENTIAL.
"IT CONTROLS EVERYTHING
"FROM EATING AND DRINKING
TO WRITING.
"INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH,
I HAVE FOUND MANY THINGS
IN LIFE TO BE THE SAME WAY."
ALREADY, THE ESSAY
MAKES NO SENSE.
WHEN'S THE LAST TIME
SOMETHING INTERESTING
IN YOUR LIFE HAPPENED,
YOU THOUGHT,
"THIS REMINDS ME OF MY THUMB"?
NEVER.
HE GOES ON.
"IT'S ALWAYS THE SIMPLE THINGS
THAT HAVE THE GREATEST IMPACT.
"THE SPLITTING OF AN ATOM
"CAUSED THE DEATH
OF OVER 200,000 PEOPLE.
"REDBOX TURNED THE MOVIE
INDUSTRY UPSIDE-DOWN
"WITH THE SIMPLE NOTION
OF CREATING
VENDING MACHINES
THAT SOLD MOVIES."
YEAH, THOSE TWO THINGS
ARE COMPARABLE.
200,000 PEOPLE ARE DEAD.
AND YOU CAN RENT
MRS. DOUBTFIRE FOR A DOLLAR
AT THE GROCERY STORE NOW.
HE GOES ON TO DESCRIBE
A PARTICULARLY
INTERESTING SUMMER
WHERE HE VOLUNTEERED
AT A LOCAL HOSPITAL.
THIS IS HOW HE DESCRIBED
THAT EXPERIENCE.
"I WAS A HUMAN
WHEELBARROW.
AND LET ME TELL YOU,
IT SUCKED."
YOU CAN'T SAY "IT SUCKED"
IN A COLLEGE ESSAY.
WHEN YOU USE LANGUAGE
LIKE THAT,
YOU KNOW WHAT
"IT SUCKS" MEANS?
YOU'RE REFERRING
TO SUCKING DICK.
SO WHAT HARRIS JUST SAID
IS LIKE, UH,
"HEY, UNIVERSITY,
YOU KNOW WHAT VOLUNTEERING
"AND HELPING PEOPLE
REMINDED ME OF?
"PUTTING A PENIS IN MY MOUTH,
AND SUCKING IT
TILL IT COMES IN MY CHUBBY,
LITTLE CHEEKS."
LATER ON,
HE TALKS ABOUT A PARTICULARLY
CRAZY DAY AT THE HOSPITAL.
"A WEEK AFTER I STARTED,
THE INCIDENT OCCURRED.
"WHEN I SET FOOT
IN THE HOSPITAL THAT DAY,
"IT WAS MORE
CROWDED THAN EVER.
THERE WEREN'T ANY NURSES
ASKING ME IF I WANTED COOKIES."
THAT'S HIS GAUGE OF HOW CRAZY
THINGS ARE AT THE HOSPITAL?
"WHY ISN'T ANYONE ASKING ME
IF I WANT COOKIES?
[scoffs] A LOT OF PEOPLE
MUST HAVE CANCER."
BUT WHAT HAPPENED THAT DAY
WAS HARRIS ENDED UP
MEETING A GENTLEMEN
WHO WAS ILLITERATE.
AND HE'D NEVER MET ANYONE
ILLITERATE BEFORE.
AND THIS REALLY
AFFECTED HIM.
HE DESCRIBED HOW HE FELT
WHEN HE DROVE HOME THAT DAY.
"I REMEMBERED THINKING
HOW BIZARRE IT WAS
"THAT SOMEONE
COULD NOT READ.
"WHAT IF I COULDN'T READ?
"I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO TEXT
MY FRIENDS MOVIE TIMES,
OR EVEN ORDER CHEESE BISCUITS
FROM RED LOBSTER."
THESE ARE THE THINGS
THAT COME TO HARRIS'S MIND
WHEN HE IMAGINES A WORLD
WHERE HE CAN'T READ.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU COULD EASILY
DO BOTH THOSE THINGS
IF YOU COULDN'T READ.
I DON'T THINK
ILLITERATE PEOPLE
SEE MOVIE POSTERS
AND NUMBERS
AND ARE LIKE,
"NO CLUE WHAT THAT MEANS.
CAN'T PIECE THAT
TOGETHER."
NOW, THE RED LOBSTER THING
IS WEIRD ALSO,
'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW
HOW MANY OF YOU ALL
HAVE BEEN
TO RED LOBSTER,
BUT IF YOU'VE BEEN THERE,
YOU KNOW
NO ONE ORDERS
THE CHEESE BISCUITS.
THOSE ARE COMPLIMENTARY.
THEY JUST SIT 'EM DOWN AT YOUR
TABLE AS SOON AS YOU GET THERE.
SO WHAT'S HARRIS
TALKING ABOUT?
I'M GUESSING
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS.
HE FINISHES HIS BISCUITS,
AND HE SEES ON THE MENU IT SAYS,
"IF YOU FINISH YOUR BISCUITS,
FEEL FREE TO ORDER MORE."
HE'S LIKE, "WHEW!
THANK GOD I CAN READ.
MORE BISCUITS, PLEASE!"
SO I TOLD HIM, I SAID, "HARRIS,
YOU CAN'T SEND THIS ESSAY.
IT'S TOO CRAZY.
LET ME DO A REWRITE."
I DID A REWRITE,
WHICH HE REJECTED,
BUT I WILL
SHARE WITH YOU NOW.
"I ONCE VOLUNTEERED
AT A HOSPITAL.
"IT SUCKED DICK, BUT I DID
GET TO EAT FREE COOKIES.
"AND LET ME TELL YOU,
I WILL SUCK DICK FOR COOKIES.
"ONE DAY, I MET A MAN
WHO WAS ILLITERATE.
"IT REALLY AFFECTED ME.
"IT MADE ME REALIZE THE WORLD
IS FULL OF GREAT TRAGEDIES.
"9/11, THE TIME I OVERCOOKED
THAT HOT POCKET,
"AND HERE, THIS MAN.
HE COULDN'T READ.
"HOW WOULD HE FIND
A BOX OF BAGEL BITES
"AT THE GROCERY STORE?
"EVEN IF HE FOUND
THE BOX OF BAGEL BITES,
"HOW WOULD HE
READ THE DIRECTIONS
"TO COOK THE BAGEL BITES?
"HAVE YOU EVER EATEN
FROZEN BAGEL BITES?
"I ATE SIX OF 'EM ONE DAY,
AND IT WAS DISGUSTING.
"MY NAME IS HARRIS.
"I HOPE YOU CONSIDER ACCEPTING
ME INTO YOUR UNIVERSITY.
"BY THE WAY,
DURING REGISTRATION,
"WILL THERE BE
FREE COOKIES,
"OR WILL I NEED
TO SUCK SOMEONE'S DICK?
LIFE'S A DIRTY GAME.
YOU GOTTA PLAY DIRTY TO WIN IT."
[cheers and applause]
I USED TO, UH--
I USED TO KID HARRIS
FOR BEING CHUBBY,
BUT HE'S ACTUALLY
NOT CHUBBY ANYMORE.
HE HAD A GROWTH SPURT,
AND HE STRETCHED OUT.
HE'S FINE.
BUT A FEW MONTHS AGO,
I WAS ACTUALLY WORRIED
THAT I WAS GETTING CHUBBY.
I SAW A PHOTO OF ME
ON THE INTERNET,
AND IN THE COMMENTS,
SOMEONE WROTE,
"WHOA!
WHO ATE AZIZ ANSARI?"
WHICH--HOLD ON--
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
IF SOMEONE ATE ME,
THEY WOULDN'T ASSUME MY FORM
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
"WHY DO YOU LOOK
LIKE THAT G--"
"I JUST ATE HIM!"
BUT THE PERSON WAS RIGHT.
I GAINED 12 POUNDS.
SO I STARTED
EXERCISING AT THE GYM,
LOST THE WEIGHT RIGHT AWAY.
BUT I DIDN'T ALWAYS
LIKE THE STUFF
THE PEOPLE AT THE GYM
WOULD TELL ME.
THEY WOULD SAY THINGS LIKE,
"HEY, AZIZ, YOU SEE
THIS NEW STUDY ON YAHOO NEWS?
"IT SAYS ANY FOOD
YOU EAT AFTER 11:00
"GOES STRAIGHT
TO YOUR BELLY.
YOU SHOULD CUT OUT
THOSE LATE-NIGHT SNACKS."
AND I WOULD ALWAYS
WANT TO SAY,
"OH, REALLY?
"THERE'S THIS OTHER STUDY
I HEARD ABOUT
"THAT SAYS, UH, IF YOU HAVE
A LOT OF ALCOHOL IN YOUR SYSTEM,
"AND YOU EAT A QUESADILLA
AT 3:00 IN THE MORNING,
"IT'S DELICIOUS.
"YEAH. I DID THAT STUDY
LAST NIGHT.
TWICE."
[cheers and applause]
BUT I LOVE FOOD.
I LOVE GOING OUT TO EAT
AT RESTAURANTS AND STUFF.
IT'S REALLY SOMETHING
I LIKE A LOT.
I WAS EATING AT ONE OF
MY FAVORITE RESTAURANTS
IN NEW YORK
NOT TOO LONG AGO,
AND I WAS HAVING DINNER
WITH A FRIEND,
AND HE'S LIKE,
"AZIZ, WHAT YOU BEEN UP TO?"
AND I SAID, "SHUT UP.
"50 CENT IS SITTING
OVER THERE,
AND I NEED TO HEAR
EVERYTHING HE SAYS."
AND 50 CENT
DID NOT DISAPPOINT.
50 CENT THE RAPPER
ORDERED A GRAPEFRUIT SODA.
THE WAITER BRINGS HIM
A GRAPEFRUIT SODA.
AND THEN 50 CENT
SAID THE GREATEST THING
ANYONE COULD EVER SAY
WHEN THEY SEE A GRAPEFRUIT SODA.
HE LOOKS AT THE WAITER,
AND HE GOES,
"WHY ISN'T THIS PURPLE?"
AND IT TOOK ME
A FEW SECONDS,
AND THEN I REALIZED,
"OH, MY GOD.
"50 CENT HAS NO IDEA
WHAT A GRAPEFRUIT IS.
"EXCUSE ME, EVERYBODY
IN THE RESTAURANT, SHUT UP.
"A WAITER'S ABOUT TO
EXPLAIN TO A GROWN MAN
WHAT A GRAPEFRUIT IS."
YOU REALIZE
HOW AMAZING THIS IS?
THERE ARE PARENTS
THAT AREN'T THERE
WHEN THEIR CHILDREN LEARNS
WHAT A GRAPEFRUIT IS.
I AM THERE FOR THAT MOMENT
IN RAPPER 50 CENT'S LIFE.
THIS GUY LEAVES
THE RESTAURANT,
HE'S GONNA KNOW
ABOUT A NEW FRUIT.
AND THE EXCHANGE
WAS JUST GLORIOUS.
THE WAITER STRUGGLING
TO EXPLAIN THE CONCEPT
OF A GRAPEFRUIT TO A MAN
WHO JUST DIDN'T GET IT.
HE WAS LIKE,
"NO, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
"THEY'RE TWO DIFFERENT THINGS.
GRAPE, GRAPEFRUIT.
GRAPE, GRAPEFRUIT."
"I KNOW GRAPES ARE FRUITS.
WHY DO YOU KEEP
SAYING IT LIKE THAT?"
"NO, IT'S JUST ONE WORD.
'GRAPEFRUIT.'
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST ONE--
IT'S A DIFFERENT--"
"I GET IT.
GRAPEFRUIT, APPLEFRUIT,
ORANGEFRUIT, CARROTVEGETABLE."
"NO. THAT'S NOT IT AT ALL."
AND IT JUST BLEW MY MIND.
HOW DOES 50 CENT NOT KNOW
WHAT A GRAPEFRUIT IS?
THIS GUY'S BEEN RICH
FOR SO LONG.
HE HAS TO RUN INTO A GRAPEFRUIT
EVERY NOW AND THEN.
I DO OKAY.
I SEE GRAPEFRUITS
EVERY FUCKIN' DAY.
WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN HE SEES A GRAPEFRUIT?
IS HE JUST LIKE...
"WHAT'S UP
WITH THOSE ORANGES?
"THEY'RE
ALL RED AND SHIT.
"AND THEY'RE BIG AS FUCK!
THEY'RE LOOKING AT ME WEIRD!
SHOOT THOSE THINGS!"
[imitates gunfire]
WHEN YOU DO THIS
KIND OF WORK,
A LOT OF PEOPLE WRITE STUFF
ABOUT YOU ON THE INTERNET,
AND SOMETIMES
PEOPLE WRITE MEAN THINGS.
AND THE SMART THING TO DO
IS JUST IGNORE THAT.
BUT SOMETIMES I WOULD
ARGUE WITH PEOPLE,
BECAUSE I LIKE ARGUING.
AND I WOULD DO THAT
EVERY NOW AND THEN,
BUT I RECENTLY PUT AN END
TO ALL OF IT.
AND I WANTED TO SHARE WITH YOU
GUYS WHAT HAPPENED
THE LAST TIME I GOT
INTO AN ARGUMENT ONLINE.
IT STARTED WHEN MY EMAIL
WASN'T WORKING.
SO I WENT ON MY WEBSITE
AND I WROTE,
"IF GMAIL EVEN MESSES UP
A LITTLE BIT,
"I GET UPSET.
IT'S A LITTLE UNREASONABLE,
BUT SERIOUSLY,
SEND MY EMAIL, GMAIL."
AND THEN A GUY
WRITES BACK AND SAYS,
"DUDE, YOU'RE COMPLAINING
ABOUT A FREE EMAIL SERVICE?
"MAYBE YOU SHOULD USE
SOME OF YOUR HOLLYWOOD MONEY
TO BUY A REAL
EMAIL ACCOUNT, TURD!"
WHICH SEEMED
A LITTLE AGGRESSIVE.
SO, I WROTE HIM BACK, AND SAID,
"HEY, MAN, I WAS JOKING,
"AND EVEN SAID
IT'S UNREASONABLE,
SO GO FUCK A BUCKET
OF DOG SHIT."
THEN HE GOES, "OH, SORRY,
DIDN'T MEAN TO SUGGEST
"YOU SHOULD USE A LITTLE
OF THAT MONEY YOU HAVE
INSTEAD OF CRYING
LIKE A BITCH."
AT THIS POINT, I DECIDED
TO TAKE THINGS UP A NOTCH.
I SAID, "I HOPE FOUR
HIPPOPOTAMUSES
"FORCE YOU TO BLOW THEM,
"AND THEY ALL COME ON YOUR FACE
SIMULTANEOUSLY,
AND YOU CHOKE
ON HIPPO COME AND DIE."
'CAUSE THAT WOULD PROBABLY BE
A PRETTY ROUGH WAY TO GO.
UM...
IMAGINE YOU'RE JUST
AT YOUR HOUSE,
LIKE, MAKING EGGS
OR SOMETHING.
[imitates doorbell]
"OH.
"A HIPPO IS HERE.
FOUR HIPPOS?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU GUYS NEED?"
AND THE HIPPOS
ARE JUST LIKE,
"SUCK OUR DICKS!"
EVEN LOGISTICALLY,
THIS IS GONNA BE ROUGH.
I MEAN, YOU GOT FOUR HIPPOS
LINED UP AT YOUR HOUSE,
YOU GOTTA BLOW 'EM
AT THE SAME TIME.
[excited murmering]
AND EVENTUALLY,
THE HIPPOS ARE LIKE,
"WE'RE ABOUT TO COME!"
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT TALKING
HIPPOS DO IN THAT SITUATION.
AND THEN IT STARTS.
[imitates shots]
"AAH, OH, NO! OH, NO!
OH, NO, I'M CHOKING!
"I'M NOT GONNA MAKE IT!
I'M GONNA DIE! I'M GONNA DIE!
"I NEED TO EMAIL MY FAMILY
AND TELL 'EM I LOVE 'EM!
FUCK! GMAIL'S DOWN!
THAT GUY WAS RIGHT."
SO, I WROTE THAT UP THERE,
AND THEN HE RESPONDED AND SAID,
"HERE'S A TIP.
DON'T USE THE WORD 'SERIOUSLY'
"WHEN YOU'RE JOKING.
"WANNA COME DOWN TO S.D.
AND TALK THAT BIG-BOY TALK
FACE TO FACE?"
I'M ASSUMING "S.D."
STANDS FOR SOUTH DAKOTA,
WHICH DOESN'T
INTIMIDATE ME AT ALL.
I WILL GO TO SOUTH DAKOTA
AND FUCK SOMEBODY UP.
NOT FOR REAL,
'CAUSE I'M SMALL,
BUT I'LL SAY SHIT LIKE THAT
WHEN I'M ONLINE.
SO, I KIND OF WANT
TO END THIS ARGUMENT,
SO I TELL HIM, "LOOK, YOU'RE
THE ONLY ONE OF THOUSANDS
"WHO HAVE THIS
IMPRESSION OF ME.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST LOOK UP
'SARCASM' IN THE DICTIONARY."
AND HE GOES, "YOU CAN'T TELL
SARCASM THROUGH TEXT, AKBAR.
BUT NICE TRY."
AND I SAID,
"WELL, THAT'S STRANGE,
"BECAUSE EVERYONE WHO DIDN'T
HAVE THE VEINY SHAFT
"OF A HUGE HIPPO COCK DEEP
IN THEIR THROAT COULD, KEITH.
"YEAH, I CALLED YOU 'KEITH,'
A RANDOM WHITE GUY NAME.
"JUST LIKE YOU CLEVERLY DID
TO ME WITH 'AKBAR'.
"BY THE WAY, THE PREVIOUS USE
OF THE WORD 'CLEVERLY'
"WAS SARCASTIC.
COULD YOU TELL IT BY READING IT,
YOU DUMB PIECE OF SHIT?"
AND THEN HE WROTE BACK
AND SAID,
"WHATEVER, YOU JAWA."
AND I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANT.
I HAD TO LOOK IT UP.
THAT'S A SIGN OF TERRIBLY
INEFFECTIVE RACISM.
YOU CAN'T SAY SOMETHING RACIST
TO SOMEONE AND THEY'LL GO,
"HEY, WHAT'D YOU SAY?
"SPELL THAT FOR ME.
I NEED TO LOOK THAT UP."
IT'S GOTTA BE IMMEDIATE.
BUT I LOOKED IT UP,
AND APPARENTLY "JAWA"
IS SOME STAR WARS CHARACTER
THAT'S, LIKE, SMALL,
AND WEARS A HOOD,
AND IS BROWN,
YELLOW EYES.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT DOESN'T OFFEND ME.
BUT I LOVE THE IDEA
OF A GUY
THAT'S REALLY RACIST
AND REALLY INTO STAR WARS.
THAT IS
AN AMAZING COMBINATION.
I WOULD LOVE TO HANG OUT
WITH THAT DUDE FOR A WHILE.
I WOULD GO TO THE MOVIES
WITH HIM WHENEVER I COULD,
BECAUSE AT ONE POINT,
I FEEL LIKE HE WOULD STAND UP
AND HE'D SAY
SOMETHING LIKE,
"DAMN IT,
I CAN'T HEAR THE MOVIE
CAUSE ALL THESE DARTH VADERS
WON'T SHUT THE FUCK UP!"
SO...AT THIS POINT,
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THIS GUY.
I'M A BUSY GUY.
I'VE GOT JOE PESCI RESEARCH
PILING UP, AND...
I TELL HIM, "LOOK,
I DON'T HAVE TIME
"TO ARGUE WITH A GUY
WHO'S INTEGRATING RACISM
AND STAR WARS TRIVIA."
AND HE GOES, "THIS CEASED
TO BE AN ARGUMENT
"FOUR HOURS AGO.
"I JUST WANTED TO SEE
SOME D-LIST IDIOT
GET ALL WORKED UP
OVER HIS TINY PECKER."
AND I SAID, "WELL, EVERY
PECKER MUST SEEM TINY
"AFTER ALL THE HUGE
HIPPO COCKS
"YOU'VE HAD IN YOUR MOUTH.
"GO SUCK MORE OF THEM.
YOU GOT A TOUCH
OF THE TAR BRUSH."
[cheers and laughter]
I'VE HAD A REALLY FUN YEAR
THIS YEAR.
I HAD A REALLY FUN
NEW YEAR'S,
BUT IT WAS ALSO ONE OF
THE MOST EMBARRASSING,
HUMILIATING, TERRIFYING
MOMENTS OF MY RECENT LIFE.
I WENT TO A JAY-Z CONCERT
IN LAS VEGAS FOR NEW YEAR'S.
[scattered cheers]
WHICH WAS--YES.
HE'S A LOT OF FUN.
AND, UH, AFTER THE SHOW
THEY HAD AN AFTER PARTY
FOR EVERYONE THAT WENT
TO THE CONCERT,
AND IT WAS A LOT OF FUN,
EVERYONE'S HANGING OUT.
THEN AT ONE POINT,
JAY-Z CAME OUT
BEHIND THE DJ BOOTH
AND WAS RAPPING ALONG
WITH ALL HIS SONGS,
AND EVERYONE WAS GOING CRAZY
AND HAVING A GOOD TIME.
AND JAY-Z BROUGHT
THE MUSIC DOWN,
AND HE STARTED TALKING
TO THE CROWD.
AND HE WAS LIKE,
"HEY, EVERYBODY,
"JUST WANTED TO WISH EVERYBODY
A HAPPY NEW YEAR.
"IT'S A REALLY SPECIAL
NIGHT TONIGHT.
"WE'VE GOT A LOT OF GREAT
PEOPLE IN THE BUILDING TONIGHT.
"WE GOT ME, JAY-Z,
IN BUILDING.
"WE GOT BEYONCE
IN THE BUILDING.
WE GOT RIHANNA
IN THE BUILDING."
AND I LOOKED AT MY FRIEND
ALAN, AND I WAS LIKE,
"WE GOT AZIZ
IN THE BUILDING."
AND THEN JAY-Z GOES, "WE GOT
AZIZ IN THE BUILDING."
AND I WAS LIKE, "OH, SHIT!
I'M IN THE BUILDING.
I HAD NO IDEA I WAS
IN THE BUILDING."
I'VE NEVER BEEN A PART
OF BUILDING
ANNOUNCEMENTS BEFORE.
NO ONE'S EVER EXCITED ABOUT
ME BEING IN THE BUILDING.
IT'S NEVER LIKE,
"AZIZ IS IN THE BUILDING!"
IT'S ALWAYS LIKE,
"AZIZ IS IN THE BUILDING?
"LET'S GO
TO ANOTHER BUILDING.
THIS BUILDING'S GOT
REALLY LOW STANDARDS."
SO HE SAID THAT,
AND I WAS LIKE,
"OH, THAT WAS NICE OF HIM
TO GIVE ME
A LITTLE SHOUT OUT
OR WHATEVER."
BUT THAT'S WHEN THINGS
GOT TERRIBLE.
'CAUSE RIGHT AFTER
HE SAID THAT, HE GOES,
"YO, AZIZ, COME UP HERE
AND TELL EVERYBODY A JOKE."
AND I WAS LIKE,
"AAH, NO!"
IT'S 4:00 A.M. ON NEW YEAR'S.
I'M OUT OF MY HEAD.
I'M NOT IN THE CONDITION
TO TELL JOKES.
BUT HE KEEPS PUSHING IT.
HE'S LIKE, "NO, MAN,
COME UP HERE
AND TELL EVERYBODY
A NEW YEAR'S DAY JOKE."
A NEW YEAR'S DAY JOKE?
THAT'S A REALLY
SPECIFIC REQUEST.
WHAT WOULD THAT
EVEN BE?
WHAT DID ONE BIRD SAY
TO THE OTHER BIRD?
"WOW, THIS YEAR
REALLY FLEW BY."
BACK TO JAY-Z, EVERYONE!
[laughter and applause]
BUT HE KEPT PUSHING THIS,
AND HE WOULD NOT STOP.
AND EVENTUALLY,
I JUST HAD TO GO UP THERE.
AND I'M GONNA DO MY BEST
TO RECREATE WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN I TOOK THE STAGE.
HE PASSES ME
THE MICROPHONE.
"UM...
"HELLO.
"OKAY, UH, ONE TIME,
"UM, THIS RESTAURANT--
I WENT TO MY HOUSE--
[forced laughter]
"THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
THAT'S NOT--
"THAT'S NOT HOW THAT ONE GOES.
[chuckles]
[yawns]
"I'M SLEEPY.
HAPPY NEW YEAR."
AND I GAVE THE MIC
BACK TO JAY-Z,
AND THE JIGGA MAN
WAS NOT PLEASED.
HE GRABBED THE MIC.
HE MADE THIS WEIRD FACE.
HE WAS LIKE...
AND I WAS LIKE, "OH, NO,
I LET HIM DOWN.
I GOTTA, LIKE, THINK
OF SOMETHING FUNNY."
SO I THOUGHT
OF SOMETHING FUNNY TO SAY.
AND I REACH BACK
FOR THE MIC,
AND HE WAS LIKE, "NO!
"YOU HAD YOUR CHANCE
TO BE FUNNY
AND YOU MISSED IT."
AND I WAS LIKE, "OH, NO!"
BUT I GET IT.
'CAUSE JAY-Z IS
THE SMOOTHEST MAN OF ALL TIME.
HIS LIFE OPERATES
IN A DIFFERENT WAY THAN MINE.
HE CAN'T COMPREHEND
THE LEVELS OF UNSMOOTHNESS
THAT GO ON WITH ME.
LIKE, IF JAY-Z SLIPPED
ON A BANANA PEEL,
HE WOULD JUST PUT HIS OTHER
FOOT ON THE BANANA PEEL
AND SLIDE TO WHEREVER
HE WAS GOING.
"MAN, I GOT HERE EVEN FASTER
THAN I ANTICIPATED.
HA HA!
THANKS, BANANA PEEL."
MY LIFE IS THE OPPOSITE.
MY LIFE IS ME SPILLING MUSTARD
ON MY SHIRT ALL THE TIME.
JAY-Z IS NEVER GONNA SPILL
MUSTARD ON HIS SHIRT.
EVEN IF MUSTARD WAS ABOUT
TO LAND ON HIS SHIRT,
SOMEONE ELSE WOULD
COINCIDENTALLY BE PASSING HIM
A HOT DOG, AND THE MUSTARD
WOULD JUST GO,
"BUMP BUMP BUMP BUMP BUMP."
AND HE'D GRAB THE HOT DOG
AND BE LIKE,
"YO, MAN, CAN I GET
SOME MUST--HA HA!
YOU ABOUT TO TAKE A BITE
OF THE WORLD'S GREATEST."
[humming and chewing]
[cheers and applause]
BEFORE I LEAVE, I WANTED
TO TALK ABOUT R. KELLY
FOR A SECOND.
[cheers and applause]
UM, WHEN I WAS
PUTTING TOGETHER
THE MATERIAL FOR THIS SPECIAL,
I WAS THINKING LIKE,
YOU KNOW, I DON'T NEED
TO TALK ABOUT R. KELLY.
I'VE DISCUSSED HIM
IN THE PAST.
NO REASON TO TALK ABOUT HIM
ANYMORE.
AND I WASN'T GONNA DO IT.
BUT HERE'S THE PROBLEM.
R. KELLY KEEPS DOING
AMAZING THINGS.
SO I'M VERY CONFLICTED
ABOUT THIS, BUT...
THIS IS WHAT R. KELLY'S
BEEN UP TO.
HE PUT OUT A SONG
LAST YEAR CALLED ECHO,
AND IN THE SONG, HE'S TALKING
ABOUT HOOKING UP WITH A GIRL
AND TRYING
TO MAKE HER ECHO.
THAT'S WEIRD.
UM, I HAVE NEVER BEEN
HOOKING UP WITH A WOMAN,
AND HER BEEN LIKE,
"AZIZ! AZIZ!
[trailing off]
AZIZ! AZIZ! AZIZ! AZIZ!"
'CAUSE I WOULD THINK,
"OH, NO!
I'M HOOKING UP
WITH A GHOST."
BUT HE PUT THIS SONG OUT,
AND I GUESS WHAT HAPPENED IS
THERE WERE SOME R. KELLY FANS
THAT DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT AN ECHO IS.
SO WHAT DO YOU DO IF YOU'RE
R. KELLY IN THAT SITUATION?
WHAT, ARE YOU GONNA POST
A VIDEO ONLINE
DEFINING THE WORD "ECHO"?
YES! THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT HE DID.
AND THE VIDEO WENT LIKE THIS.
HE COMES ON THE SCREEN,
HE'S LIKE,
"ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL,
SOME OF Y'ALL DON'T KNOW
"WHAT AN ECHO IS.
"NOW AN ECHO IS JUST
BASICALLY,
"LIKE, YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU STAND
ON TOP OF A MOUNTAIN
"AND YOU GO, 'HELLO!'
"AND YOU HEAR,
'HELLO, HELLO, HELLO, HELLO'?
THAT'S AN ECHO."
END OF VIDEO.
AND I SAID, "UH,
THAT'S THE MOST AMAZING THING
"I'VE SEEN IN QUITE A WHILE.
"HOW DO WE GET R. KELLY
IN TOUCH
"WITH THE MERRIAM-WEBSTER
PEOPLE IN ORDER
"TO START FUNDING
FOR THE ONLINE R. KELLY
VIDEO DICTIONARY?"
THAT'S GOTTA HAPPEN
AT SOME POINT
IN OUR LIFETIME.
WOULDN'T THAT BE AMAZING?
TYPE IN ANY WORD.
"CHEESEBURGER."
"ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL,
SOME OF Y'ALL
"DON'T KNOW
WHAT A CHEESEBURGER IS.
"YOU KNOW WHEN YOU GO
TO MCDONALD'S
"AND YOU ORDER
A CHEESEBURGER?
THAT'S A CHEESEBURGER."
"SEE ALSO RELATED WORDS:
'VEGGIE BURGER.'"
"YOU KNOW WHEN YOU GET
A CHEESEBURGER
"AND IT TASTES FUNNY?
THAT'S A VEGGIE BURGER."
OR, UH, "JUICE BOX."
"ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL,
SOME OF Y'ALL
"DON'T KNOW
WHAT A JUICE BOX IS.
"YOU KNOW WHEN YOU
MAKING LOVE TO A WOMAN
"AND YOU'RE HOLDING ON
TO HER BOOTY,
"AND YOU'RE LIKE,
'OH, MY GOD,
"'THIS IS THE MOST
AMAZING BOOTY
"'I'VE EVER HELD ON TO
IN MY LIFE.
"'I CANNOT LET GO
OF THIS BOOTY.
"FOR WHATEVER REASON,
I CANNOT LET GO.'
"BUT YOU GET REALLY
THIRSTY?
THAT'S WHEN YOU CAN REACH
FOR YOUR JUICE BOX."
[imitating liquid slurping]
OR "ATM MACHINE."
"ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL,
SOME OF Y'ALL
"DON'T KNOW WHAT AN ATM IS.
"YOU KNOW, AN ATM MACHINE
IS A MACHINE
"WHERE YOU CAN PUT A CARD IN,
YOU GET MONEY OUT,
"YOU CAN GET YOUR MONEY OUT
AND YOU CAN LEAVE.
"OR IF YOU GOT A GIRL
WITH YOU,
"YOU CAN PUT HER AGAINST
THE ATM MACHINE AND JUST...
"♪ GRI-I-I-I-IND ♪
"♪ SHE'S GOT HER HANDS
ON YOUR THING ♪
"♪ YOU GOT YOUR HANDS
ON HER TITTIES ♪
"♪ YOU ABOUT TO MAKE LOVE
TO THIS NICE ITTY-BITTY ♪
"♪ Y'ALL ARE FUCKIN'
BY THE ATM ♪
"♪ FUCKIN' BY THE ATM,
FUCKIN' BY THE ATM ♪
[cheers and applause]
"♪ WITHDRAW, DEPOSIT,
WITHDRAW, DEPOSIT ♪
"♪ DAMN, GIRL, I NEED
ADDITIONAL FUNDS ♪
AND THAT'S 'ATM.'"
THANK YOU, GUYS,
SO MUCH!
THANK YOU VERY,
VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING OUT.
YOU'RE A FANTASTIC AUDIENCE.
GOOD NIGHT.
THANK YOU!
[cheers and applause]