♫ I could see you ten
or twelve times a day
♫ I think it's best we do
it your therapist's way
♫ I grow my hair long
and wear big coats, yeah
♫ I get so lovesick my sad thoughts float
♫ The time you've got me running
♫ News broke today so we're not talking
♫ I think it's best we do
a little bit of stopping
♫ I want a house on a
beach and you in my dreams
♫ I need water, yeah,
and a love love love love
♫ The time you've got me running
♫ The time
♫ You've got me tired
♫ Well I've got more
for the world than this
♫ I've got more
♫ And I've got love that I need to give
♫ And I've got more
for the world than this
♫ I've got more
♫ And I've got love that I need to give
♫ ah
- I'm gonna make some snack.
- I think I'm getting a
rash from these boxes.
Are you ready for your
epic journey to New York?
Yes!
- I'm not eating bread.
Since when?
- Since I want a flat belly for auditions.
New York's not gonna put
up with Midwest butt.
- You look great, don't freak out.
Are you sure you don't want any?
It's your favorite, it's Trader Toe Jam.
- Can't do it.
Hey, who am I?
- I don't know.
How about now?
- Oh god no, don't, don't,
don't hug-massage me.
You're Carl, okay, you're Creepy Carl!
Got it.
- Those are yours, that's your pile.
- Hm, I have doubles.
I actually went to a
drugstore and had copies made.
- Wow, I,
I have a whole bunch you
know, on my computer,
but I never think to print them.
- I know.
I'm gonna put a bunch of 'em on my fridge,
in my new apartment.
Speaking of which,
my new job called, and they
want me there in 2 weeks,
or they have to give it to someone else.
- I'll still take care
of the bills this month.
I'll even clean the oven.
- I'm going to work, I'm late.
Doors closing.
Last before doors close.
You look like shit.
- Thank you.
- It's Jamie, she's
leaving in two weeks now.
- I don't really see a point,
she doesn't like me like that.
- Okay, first of all,
you don't even know that
because my last girlfriend
said she had a crush on me
for like, months, before
we even hooked up.
- Renee.
- Jody, Renee was before
Jody and after Lisa.
- I liked Lisa, Lisa was funny.
- Yeah, she still is.
I'm gonna have to hook you
up with some cool ladies.
Yeah, you
can try, I don't know.
- No I get it, I get it.
I fall in love with every girl I fuck too.
Cheer up!
What up dog?
Always with the down low, dang!
Seriously, you're gonna have
to stop hanging out with Jamie.
It's all right, I'm gonna
hook you up with some hotties!
♫ Too much time to think
♫ My future prospects stink
♫ Feels like I'm standing still
♫ You got it bad for the wrong girl
♫ All these lousy beans
♫ What will it ever mean
♫ They smell better than they taste
♫ Your love life's a total waste
♫ Let me say this is not okay
♫ You bring joy to us every day
♫ She can't hear you, she's in a trance
♫ I wouldn't mind getting in her pants
♫ If you want this girl then let her know
♫ Tell her now or let her go
♫ A body like yours is made for cooking
♫ I'm climbing up and
down but she's not looking
♫ Climbing up and down
but she's not looking
♫ I'm climbing up and
down but she's not looking
- Large soy chocolate steamer, for Chuck.
- Thanks.
Hey.
- Hi.
So Dawn said you used to do
stained glass in Madison?
- Yeah, that was a great gig.
I still do it, but most
of the studio I use now,
for my leather business.
- Leather jackets, custom chaps.
But uh, accessories are the big seller.
I sell like a dozen a week,
even more in July and August.
- Yeah, yeah I went there
last summer but umm,
a bee stung me on my lip
like the very first day,
so I was in my tent on
Benadryl like the whole time.
But I remember there
was a lot of good music
and um, corn bread.
- Your lips look just fine right now.
- Um, you're a smoker.
Yeah.
- I don't think this is gonna work out.
- Yeah, sure, I could eat.
I don't care what you did,
Sasha, it doesn't matter now.
- Line.
Sorry, Jess.
Let's just
break, reset scene, take ten.
- Hey.
Sounds good.
- Thanks, I wish you
could be here to see it.
Do you, really?
- No, I don't wish you
could be here to see it.
Yeah, 'cause you look like
you're totally checking out.
- Look at me.
Look at me.
- You look like a tapestry
that fell off the wall.
Looks terrible.
- I like this a little--
- Hey Jamie, thought you were in New York.
Brooklyn.
Ten days.
- Uh, oh.
- Can't believe you're
not off book yet, man.
- What do you mean, we're
not up for a few weeks.
- I was kidding.
- Oh, so what neighborhood
you gonna move to?
Uh, Ditmas Park.
- It's out past Park Slope.
- You're gonna love it.
I got a cousin there in
Williamsburg, she loves it.
She's a painter, she loves it.
- She's married.
- I have to pee.
- Yeah, I'll meet you
at the beach in an hour.
Okay.
- Um yeah, so don't forget
about me when you're all famous.
Send me a postcard from Broadway.
But don't worry, you don't
have to go to Broadway Street.
A regular postal service will be okay.
- Okay.
Ah, okay.
I'll see you around Carl.
- Okay.
♫ They think I got it made
♫ You think I got it all
♫ But it's not what you think
♫ Feeling pretty small
♫ Don't know what happens next
♫ I may not pass the test
♫ They say I got the stuff
♫ But what if it's not enough
♫ What if you're not enough
♫ I can't wait to get out of here
♫ I'm ready to explode here
♫ Can't shoot my load here
♫ Chicago ain't my kind of town
♫ Don't explode
♫ That'll get messy
♫ She's moving on
♫ But what about Jessie
♫ You're a big fish in a little pond
♫ There you're just another prawn
♫ New York is the place for me
♫ You all just, just wait and see
♫ I will be a big star
♫ I can go far
♫ And you won't need a car
♫ New York will put me to the test
♫ But I am different than the rest
♫ New York will put her to the test
♫ She thinks she's better than the rest
♫ New York will put me to the test
♫ I think I'm better than the rest
♫ New York will put her to the test
♫ She thinks she's better than the rest
♫ New York will put me to the test
♫ I know I'm better than the rest
♫ New York will put her to the test
♫ She thinks she's better than the rest
- Thought you didn't
have time for me anymore.
I have ten minutes.
Take it off.
- Okay, you missed it.
I don't know why I wait for you.
Um, if you're not here in ten
minutes, I'm gonna take off.
- Oh god, don't, don't get sand on me.
You were supposed to be here
at sunset, I called you.
- I'm sorry, my phone died.
Didn't think you'd still be here.
Sorry Jess.
Hey.
Who am I?
Blah, blah blah blah blah.
Blah, blah, blah blah blah blah blah.
Blah, blah, blah blah blah, blah.
Blah, blah
- Close-talker.
- Yes, my name is Sean.
You will know what I had for lunch
whether you want to or not, blah.
- I can tell what you had
for dinner, that's for sure.
- Uh-huh.
- Let's go skinny-dipping.
- It's not warm enough.
- Come on, just come in up to here.
- The last time I went in
there I got a yeast infection.
- That's not why you
got a yeast infection.
Come on, pretty soon I
won't be here to swim with.
- It's too cold.
- Pussy.
- Yeah, that's right.
♫ And if I say hello again
let it be for the last time
You know I think
this may be the only table
that will fit in my apartment.
- Sounds about right.
- Thanks.
Crap!
What?
- It broke off in there.
Screw it, I owe you a foot rub.
This is your last chance to claim it.
Let's go.
(light acoustic guitar
music in background)
♫ And if I say I love again
let it be for the last time
♫ And if break my bones again
- I still need to sort
through the bathroom stuff.
- Yeah, I can help you with that.
- Need to rent the truck,
do laundry, wrap dishes.
I'm kind of afraid of New York.
♫ Let's be happy
♫ All day and night
♫ I don't, know I won't, pretend it
♫ Let's be happy
- Hey.
Heyo.
- I don't really think they
were looking for girls like me.
It was a bunch of models there.
- That's a shame.
Foxy Oxy works too, got the
blood out of my frisbee shorts.
- Yeah, I was the one who rubbed that
on your frisbee shorts.
- Hey, I did your MichFest towels.
- Yeah, you probably should
have burned those.
- Your show's gonna come on.
Glenn Dreck.
- Scary.
- No, thank god, I need
a night to be depressed.
Hey, you wanna make frames for these?
- Okay.
Okay, no more.
Business
values or labor values,
they're American values.
- Let's go to Homo Depot, for the frames.
We'll get wood.
- Yeah.
- So shoes.
- Okay.
- And jacket.
- Hey Jamie.
Um-hm.
What?
- Chicken butt.
Nerd.
- Ow!
♫ I cannot breathe I cannot sleep
♫ I meditate while counting sheep
♫ Every now and then I think of you
♫ You are the eye inside my storm
♫ If I were cold, you'd be my warm
♫ Every now and then I think of you
♫ If you could see me
the way that I see you
♫ Then everything would
be just how I want it to
♫ Until you do, I will think of you
- You know mom is already
planning her holiday in Manhattan.
She wants me to come with.
It's gonna be a girls weekend.
- Um-hm.
You know mom and dad came here twice
in the last three years?
It's New York she wants to see.
- Come on.
So, who's Jessie's new roommate?
- This guy from school, gay guy, musician.
- Well he better be cool,
because I'm not giving up
my Thursday nights away from my kids.
- Well, yeah, I mean if that's okay.
I love Jess, she's--
- It's, it's fine.
- This has got to be really hard for you.
I mean you guys talk like every day.
- It's not like we're not gonna talk.
When is she
planning on coming to see you?
- I don't know.
We haven't worked that out yet.
Hey, I have something for you.
I bought you this two years
ago in a thrift store.
- Hm, it's gorgeous, I love it.
Although I don't know if
I've really been a size six
since before the baby.
- Don't say that until you try it on.
- Ohh, my little sister!
- Ow, ow, all right, geez.
- I'm really proud of you, you know.
What?
- Just, don't be too
disappointed when I flop.
- That's the thing, babe,
even when you do flop
you still keep going anyways.
I know.
- Oh by the way, if you
don't sell everything
in the yard sale, dad's planning
on giving you some money
so don't worry about it.
Hey, when's this from?
- That's last summer.
It's a great
picture of you two.
It's a copy, we have the originals.
- Sure, I'll put it on my fridge.
Oh shit, the spaghetti!
Oh fuck, it's all mushy now.
Lemme see.
- I guess it's just been one
of those really lucky years
for me, you know?
You ever have one of those?
- Well now that Mercury
is out of retrograde
and Jupiter's aligned
with Mars, I mean come on.
Let's go for it, right?
- Right.
- And then when Dawn said
that she had somebody
she wanted me to meet that,
I might really like, , I um,
pulled out the calendar
and whoa, it was Flag Day.
It's about being proud of who you are.
- Proud of your country,
sure, but, you know,
standing up for yourself and saying yes.
I want love, I want freedom, you know?
- Just noticed your tattoo.
It's pretty awesome.
Miss Pac Man, I've never seen that before.
No, it's not Miss Pac Man.
- Oh.
- Um, it's an ancient symbol of a fish.
- Mm-hm, it uh means time before time.
Love before hate.
Something like that.
- Sounds about right.
- I should probably just tell you now
what eventually is gonna come up later.
- Um, well, we're not allowed
to talk about it in my family.
But,
my Grandpa was in the Nazi youth.
- Uh, oh, okay.
- He wasn't in it for very
long, only a couple years,
and then he moved to France.
- I, I don't really know what to say, um.
I'm feeling kind of nauseous
and my stomach is just like--
Something else we'd have in common.
I just didn't want any
secrets between us, you know?
- I have to go home.
Um.
- Okay.
- I need uh, I need to make
some watermelon slices.
- Oh, okay, take your time, I mean,
I really do think we could
have some fun though.
- See you later.
- Um-hm, it'll be a lot of
fun just to spend the day
out in nature.
- Right.
- Hey.
- Jessica!
- Hi!
- Uh.
- There's extra pasta if you want some.
- Oh no thanks, I'm not hungry.
- Hey Jess, Jamie said it's still cool
for me to come over after she moves.
- Awesome, Spaghetti Thursdays.
Mm-hm.
Did you kiss her?
- I've already tried to blank it out.
Oh, I didn't realize you were
dating other people already Jess.
- I'm really super tired, I'm gonna.
- Hey Jess, I'm planning
on coming to see your play.
Can you tell me when is it again?
- It's next month.
- I will, uh, have a good night, bye.
- Night.
What's going on?
- She had a bad day,
she wants to go to bed.
- I don't get it.
♫ Far away I lie to myself
♫ For a change I lie to myself
- Okay, what's the first
thing you're gonna do
when you move to New York?
- Hm, buy tampons, I start
my period on the 15th.
- Mm, so do I.
- I know.
- Um, I'm gonna buy a
slice of sausage pizza
and walk everywhere.
- Do you have to start
your job right away?
- Mm-hm.
- Mm.
- She's got two auditions
lined up already.
Really, for plays?
- One is for Candyland, the play.
- Um-hm, I'd play Princess Lolly.
- Mm, you were born to
play Princess Lolly.
- Yeah, I'd want to play her too.
- She's moving after
this last year of school.
- Which is a long way away.
- Two semesters.
Hey, let's split another beer.
- Ah, if you insist.
So how was your date with
the dental hygienist?
- Kind of like getting your teeth pulled
but without the nitrous.
- Thank God I'm with Sarah.
I don't even know what
it's like to date anymore.
- Yeah, I don't know if I've
ever really dated anyone.
It's just hard to find the
kind of girl I like in Chicago.
- Yeah, especially since she's going to be
in New York in a minute.
Only have to
get me another drink.
Hey!
Hey, how's it goin'?
- Hey, glad you made it.
I already got your drinks.
- Oh, thanks.
- Thank you, awesome.
That's why I love you.
- Good turn out tonight.
- Think you'll have time to squeeze in
another one
- Here, I've got to go to the potty.
- I swear she has a bladder infection.
- She drinks too much
water, not enough wine.
- Is that why she has anxiety
attacks every other week?
- Oh my god, this person, I'm knocking.
Hey, is this the end of the--
- Yeah.
God I hope they play some
decent music this time.
- Yeah, it was really
shitty last week, wasn't it?
- I wish they'd play
something, you know, funky.
- Yeah, 'cause I uh, like it funky.
- Cool.
- And I like your T-shirt.
- Thanks, I have trouble with real ties.
- Yeah.
Ah, go ahead, you can take mine.
Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- If you dance with me.
- Yeah, all right.
- To Jamie, and her Big Apples.
- I do love big apples.
♫ I'm captivated,
mesmerized by your eyes, I
♫ Saw you glance at me
and kinda look shy, I
♫ I think you're sexy and
you got a nice swagger
♫ We could complement each other
♫ But make it after
♫ We kiss 'cause I like
love being adventurous
♫ So place my two fingers
across your sexy lips
♫ Sh, don't speak, let's exchange vibes
♫ We don't need to talk,
we could talk with our eyes
♫ Yeah, I know, that's what your eyes said
♫ You'd like to come
over and see my big bed
♫ I got satin sheets would
you like to touch 'em
♫ They're white and they're soft
♫ I'm sure that you'd love 'em
♫ You wanna take a test drive in my ride
♫ The passenger seat, I'll
give you a glass of wine
♫ The engine all revvin'
up, it's time to go
♫ My love machine has pickup
but it starts out slow
♫ Hey sexy baby, wanna make you mine
♫ If it's not good forever
then at least tonight
♫ I'm a sucker for your
energy, come over to my house
♫ And be awhile
♫ I said, hey sexy baby
wanna make you mine
♫ And if it's not good
forever, then at least tonight
♫ I'm sucker for your
energy, come over to my house
♫ And feel my
♫ It's been around the
world, never runs out of gas
♫ When you push it to the
limit, it can go really fast
♫ Would you like to come
along, and drive my
Jessica?
- Um, do you mind if we
move over to the rocks?
I'm allergic to grass.
- Sure.
That must be a drag.
- A friend of mine is
allergic to wheat and corn,
plus he can't drink wine.
- That'd be horrible.
- You get used to it.
- Okay.
- I'm a little nervous.
- That's okay, you're my first blind date.
You too.
- It's nice out here.
- Yeah, I like to come
and watch the boats.
- I'm not over my ex.
- I'm kind of in love with my roommate.
- Right.
♫ I can't wait to tell her
♫ Can't wait to tell her
♫ I should've told her long ago
♫ She has to feel it, she must know
♫ Definitely positively know
♫ This is love
Hey James, Jamie?
What?
- Can't wear that.
- Crap, I can't wear my lucky shirt then.
Yeah.
Well, you can't wear that one,
they'll smell you a mile anyway.
- I know.
Ow!
- Oh!
I'm really nervous.
- You're gonna be great, come on.
You've run it a million
times, you know your lines.
The play's about being in
love, you've been in love.
So, just connect with that.
Go in, say your lines right,
you'll knock 'em out of the park.
- It won't take long, I, I uh,
it'll just help me focus,
run lines, you know?
- Mmm.
- Fine.
Only if we get to go skinny-dipping after.
- Yeah sure cool, whatever,
let's just go I'm late.
Whoo!
And then
the sun started to sink
just like the coward it was.
You were the last one to see it,
but I was the last one who cared.
And, scene.
Thanks again.
Next?
- Hello.
- Hey, just do what you
do, I'll be over here.
- Oh, Jamie!
- Oh!
Hey Hi!
Are you auditioning for this?
- No, I'm just waitin' for Jess.
- Oh, she'd be wonderful in this, I think.
Hey, anything lined up in New York?
You know, it's always good
to get a few auditions
in your calendar before you get there.
- Yeah, I'm working on it.
- Well, keep me informed.
I know some people you should meet.
- I will, thank you.
- You know, you should
just audition for this,
now that you're already here.
I mean, it's good practice.
- I-I'm not gonna be
in town for it though.
- So much the better, it
won't matter that much.
I'll get ya in next.
- I, I don't want to cut in line.
- Hey, come on.
- Oh, hey, I'll be out in 10 minutes.
Jess, she pushed,
she pushed me in there.
Whatever.
Helen said to
audition for practice.
It's not like I'm gonna,
I don't even want the role.
Okay, it's harmless.
- I don't really feel like swimming.
- Hello, this is Jamie.
Hi, yeah.
Oh, thank you, but um, I
don't think I can take it.
Yeah, Helen told you right?
Yeah, huh, I really can't take it.
I've got some stuff lined
up in New York already,
but umm, thank you.
Yeah, you too.
Bye.
- Hello.
Oh hi.
Really?
Yes, yeah, I,
yes, I, I, I, I really love this role,
I really want, love this play I,
Okay.
Okay, okay, well, thank you so much.
Okay, uh, bye.
- Yeah, I got it.
- That's awesome, Jess.
You knew how much
this meant to me, Jamie.
Yeah, that's
why I didn't take it.
- So what, now I know
I'm their second choice.
Why did you even try out?
- Helen pushed me in there.
- Don't blame Helen!
You are so fucking selfish!
- I'm sorry,
what do you want me to do?
- You just do this all the time.
- You wouldn't even have been
there if I hadn't asked you
to come and support me.
You just, everything just
comes so fucking easy for you.
Jess, Jess.
Go, go hump a camel!
Damn it.
Hey, do you need help?
- Yeah, someone took my wheel.
People suck, who does that?
It's raining.
Sorry,  do you need help?
- No, I walked today.
Can you leave it here and
then just come back for it?
- I don't want them to
take the rest of it.
I'm going about two miles that way.
- Well, I'll go with you.
I was going to Andersonville
anyway, we'll take turns.
- Yeah, come on.
My god.
What?
Bad day.
It's kind of like a wheelbarrow--
- I know.
- you have to angle it.
There, okay, got it.
- That must be kind of great,
getting to be on the stage,
you know, to be someone else.
Yeah, but I'm
always me, you know?
Like no matter who I play.
Sometimes I wish I could just
totally become someone else,
you know, and have their voice.
Oh yeah, like Meryl Streep.
- No, no, no, no, no, I
mean, I could never be her.
Like, like scientific stuff, you know?
Like, instead of having lines from,
from Mamet or Wasserstein, I
could be thinking about like,
microbes and protons.
Do you want me to switch?
- Well, yeah, here I'm gonna put it down.
Go for it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, here, done.
- Oh god, here, thank you.
Well, you know, you don't have
to be good at just one thing.
- You're right, I could
fail equally at many things.
- Seriously, I couldn't do what you do.
- Yeah, you kind of keep us sane.
You're basically a mental health worker.
- Um, well, I, believe it or not,
I used to want to write mystery novels.
And then I went into my
family's snack business.
Come on.
- Little Bobbie.
Oh my god are you for
serious, I love Little Bobbie!
With the, the, let me get that.
With the, with the, with
the, with the swirly thingies
and the the caramel star, um, cake things?
- Yep.
- That's hot.
- Yeah, well I hated it.
And then I didn't really
like being around my family,
so I went into computer engineering.
- Aa-ah.
Do you have a lot of bad lighting there?
Is that the
one with the talking dog
and the old guy baby?
Yeah.
It's like there's all these shows with
old fat dads, you know?
- Well, that's why they
need the talking dog
and the old guy baby.
- Well maybe you can
explain it to me sometime.
- This is me.
Thanks again for helping
me take that home.
- Yeah, sure.
You know, I have a little sailboat
I'm taking out this weekend.
Do you maybe want to join me?
- Yeah.
- Um, I don't know, my, my
roommate is moving and I'm help--
- Well, here, give me your hand.
Why don't you, let me know.
- Okay.
What's up?
- Someone stole my wheel.
- Bummer, I'm Jamie.
- Hi, I'm Elizabeth.
It's nice to meet you.
It's really nice to meet you too, Jessie.
Bye.
Oh, sorry.
- Oh, thanks.
- Bye.
- She's hot.
She live around here?
Dunno, have to work.
- Well call in sick, I'll
pay your wages for the day.
For the week how bout?
- Don't be weird.
What're you doin'?
- I was gonna send you this,
but you may as well have it now.
I feel like a hooker.
- You're my friend, moving
to an expensive city.
Come on, this is easy for me.
- That's like a month's rent.
- It's what I make in a day, just take it.
You're gonna miss me.
- Don't rub it in.
- That's not what you said a minute ago.
- I wish I could take you with me.
And Jessie, and Katrina, George,
my sister, and the lake.
- And your women.
You've got the best of both worlds.
What worlds?
- Well, you have booty
calls whenever you want them
and you have the wife at home,
cooking, cleaning, and doing your laundry.
- We share the laundry.
- So you're the only
one who hasn't noticed?
- How Jess looks at you.
Like what?
- Like so.
Ohh.
- Oh, that looks good on you.
- Whatever, it's good you're leaving.
I don't know how much
more of this I could take.
- You're not exactly single.
I'm sorry, I guess I'm just jealous.
- You didn't get jealous you said.
- Everybody gets jealous.
It's just a matter of time.
Now get outta here.
♫ Hurry up and leave my love
♫ Hurry up and go
♫ The first time that I touched you
♫ I didn't even know your name
♫ Now I can hardly stand it
♫ Got beat at my own game
♫ Hurry up and leave my love
♫ It's time for you to go
♫ Hurry up and go
♫ I thought that I was
♫ Tough and strong
♫ Would never wear a ring
♫ Our one night stand
♫ Went on too long
♫ It became a three month fling
♫ And now the die is cast
♫ I'm just a story in your past
♫ I'm already wondering
♫ Which kiss will be our last
Hey.
- You should press
through your hands more,
straighten your back.
I don't need your advice, thanks.
- Actually, um, could
you just leave me alone
for a few minutes, I'm trying to relax.
- Yeah.
Oh, just real quick, 'cause
you never called me back.
Um, are we still doing something tomorrow?
- Um, I can't, I, I have
a date with Elizabeth.
We're going sailing, she has a, a boat.
- Cool.
We always said we needed
friends with boats.
You're still helping me
with the yard sale, right?
- Yeah, I said that I would.
- And um, we need to go
grocery shopping for the party.
- Yeah, okay, can we just
talk about this later?
♫ Why don't you tell her
♫ You waited all your life to tell her
♫ Come on you know you wanna
tell her what she means to you
♫ It's a cynical life and
you're not a simple girl
♫ You drink a bottle of wine every night
♫ And you prefer to
keep a mask on your face
♫ You're playin' it safe under the covers
♫ You're losin' your faith
in the mantra that you live
♫ It's sayin' that you gotta
love the one you're with
♫ If you can't be with the one you love
- No thanks.
- Five days.
Jessica going too I assume?
- Nah, she's got a year left of school.
- Uh no, actually we're not
together, we're just friends.
Oh, oh.
How much is this?
- Um, I don't know,
actually, that's Jessie's.
She made it?
- Yeah.
- It's great.
- Yeah, she should have
been here by now, actually.
I'll give
her five bucks for it.
- How about I set it aside for you,
and when she gets here I'll
let her know you want it.
That sound good?
Yeah.
- Good.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Uh--
- Come on in, come on in, you
don't have to stand out there.
- Thanks, sorry.
Ah, Jamie said that she left
a hoodie of mine over here?
It's a black, it's kinda long, have you?
- Oh, I haven't seen it but
you're welcome to come in
and look around if you want.
- Cool, cool yeah, thank you.
Oh.
Wow.
- You have a lot of cameras.
- Oh, yeah, well I started
collecting them when I was a kid.
- Cool.
- This one's my favorite.
Why?
- It was one my dad gave me.
You know why they call it Kodak?
- 'Cause when you press the
button it makes that sound.
Kodak, Kodak.
- Yeah, yeah, it sounds
like when you say it.
My Mom had a camera when
I was, when I was little,
and it would like talk at
you and it would say like,
too dark, too dark, when it was too dark.
But it wasn't clicking
it was an automated,
you know, accented, yeah.
- You're a lot funnier than Jamie is.
- Thanks.
I'm, I'm sorry, am I
interrupting something?
- No, no no, I was just having
a drink, do you want one?
- Sure.
- All right.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah that's, whiskey's fantastic.
Awesome.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Oh, you don't need to chug
it, you can just sip it.
- Oh, okay.
- Cheers.
- Cheers, sorry.
- Uh huh, I think I need a little more.
- Yeah, I'm, I'm fine, I just--
- I just kinda wanna get
my hoodie back, you know?
- Yeah.
- Jamie is always taking my stuff and--
- Yeah, it's okay, I got it.
Cool.
- Sorry, I'm just weird
about the sweatshirt.
It's probably not even here.
You know, you just lend something to Jamie
and then you think you're
gonna get it back maybe
at some point, but then she
gives it to someone else
and then you see them wearing it
and that's just, it's strange.
- Yeah, I have the same
problem with my jewelry.
She like takes it, doesn't
ask, never get it back.
- You still have some on.
- Oh this, well, I never take this off,
so she'd basically have to like,
take it off while I was sleeping.
Which would be creepy.
- Yeah, oh yeah that
would be pretty creepy.
This is good.
- Yeah, I uh, I didn't make it
so I can't take credit for
it but I, I poured it--
- I have, yeah.
In the wintertime.
- That's intense.
- Yeah, it's fun.
Tastes better when you
work for it, ya know?
- Is that like the liquor
version of hunting or something?
I never
thought about it that way.
You're so weird.
- Okay.
I feel like I should tell you something,
but I don't want this to
come off the wrong way she,
Jamie's not really good at
keeping in touch with people.
You know?
Why are you telling me that?
- I mean, I don't know, just,
thought you should know.
- Are you talking about like
when she goes to New York?
Like whether she's gonna call me or not?
- I mean, I don't know
what she's gonna do,
I'm not saying that.
- I mean it doesn't
really matter, we don't,
it's not like we've made any promises
to each other or anything.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
You worried about that?
- Mm-Uh.
Yes you are.
- No, I'm not.
You like her don't you?
- No.
- Yeah you do, you like her a lot.
- You need to shut up.
- You definitely don't
like me very much, do you?
- I'm done.
It's a camera.
See, Kodak, Kodak.
- You are so weird.
- Um, the glasses.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Oh, we don't have to stop.
This is awkward.
♫ I could come down
♫ To your love
♫ And I could live longer than you thought
♫ And then you'd never have to leave me
♫ And you would never have to deceive me
♫ Oh I could come down
♫ I went to your show
♫ To see the actors
♫ Though I'll never know
♫ How much they suffer
♫ 'Cause it's only shining stars
♫ On stage with bleeding hearts
- All right,
here you go, have a good one.
- I just put Judith Butler
in the kids' section.
I am freaking out.
- Oh it's like
Jess is acting weird.
- Well, she blew me off at my yard sale,
now she won't answer calls.
- It sounds like she's sad, not
mad, for you abandoning her.
- I'm not abandoning her,
she's not my girlfriend.
- Ah, coulda fooled me.
She acts like she's in love with you.
- You know you're not the first person
to tell me that this week?
- Oh, here she comes.
Hey.
- Thank you.
Oh my god, falafel.
Thank you, I am so hungry right now.
Hey Jess, I need to talk to you.
- Um, I wanna talk to you
too, but I have to go to work.
I'll see you at the party?
Bye Katrina.
- Bye.
She looks good walking away.
- It's really sweet of you
throwing this party for Jamie, George.
- Going away parties are
so more important than
birthdays or weddings, that's what I say.
- You know, I'm going to
be leaving too one day.
- No, it's all right.
Here, cheese nib, aw, pop.
- Mm, those things are good.
- I know, it's right there, it's good.
Who's that sexy thing?
I haven't seen her before.
Hey, you might get lucky tonight.
Hey.
Hey, how you doin'?
Ah, this is my sister.
- Hi, I'm Monica.
- Hi, Rhonda, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Rhonda's a good friend.
- Yeah.
- Good.
I'm gonna go get a drink.
Hey.
- I didn't know you were gonna be here.
- Clock's ticking.
- Have a cheese nib.
- Everyone, everyone.
A toast.
- Yes, okay, even though
you are my younger sister,
and a complete pain in the ass.
And you narcked on me every
chance you could to dad,
I couldn't have asked for a better sister.
I'm proud of you, Jamie.
- Here, here.
- Oh, okay,
okay, okay, okay.
The bookstore is gonna miss her,
and I'm gonna miss you
especially even more
because I'm not gonna
be able to play D and D
all the time on the computer!
But seriously, enjoy New
York, I'm gonna miss you.
- Cheers.
To Jamie!
- My darling roommate, a
fabulously talented actress
and an even better fuck, huh?
What?
I know you know.
You know Jamie, Chicago
is going to miss you, but
I'll survive.
- Jess, you're drunk.
Did you eat anything?
You care?
- God, don't be so mean.
I'm the nice one, Jamie.
Who got you into that Improv
for Pinter class, huh?
And who helped you with
all your algebra tests,
negative plus negative
equals positive, Jamie.
- Yeah, that was you, Jess but--
- Yeah, and when you
had to sell your eggs,
who put all the hormone
shots in your butt?
And who got you lime popsicles every night
because you were feeling really shitty?
Those were made out of real limes.
- Thanks a lot, I'm leaving.
- No, no, no, no, Jamie!
This is your party, hm?
Hm, go, have fun.
I'm gonna go home, to my house.
And I'm gonna watch a show.
Whatever.
- Jess come on, we love you too.
- Yeah, okay.
Jamie, we're gonna have a good time.
A good time, you know, with your friends.
Jamie, Jamie.
- Jamie.
- It's your party.
Fortunately, there is still alcohol.
So drink, drink, drink,
drink, drink, drink,
drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink.
All right, cups up.
Whoo!
- To Jamie and Jessie.
To Jamie and Jessie!
♫ We don't want to take no sides
♫ It's gettin' sticky with you guys
♫ Come back out and have a drink
♫ For you we'll mix up something pink
♫ For you I'll muddle something pink
♫ Your appetite for the ladies
♫ Gets you in such trouble
♫ But we find you entertaining
♫ So get out here on the double
♫ No matter what we'll still be here
♫ In fact I'll have another beer
- Hey!
Yeah, come on!
I'll have another one too.
Or two.
I had about four too many.
Come on, out.
No.
Oh, but you
borrowed the purple shirt.
- I'll mow anything you want.
- Come on, Jamie.
We're not leaving.
- You're super-selfish.
- But we like you.
♫ It'll all work out
♫ Sweet Jamie dear
♫ And when you wake up
♫ You'll still be queer
♫ Don't let my eyes tell lies
♫ Its been harder--
- That really sucked you told everybody
I sold my eggs for money.
That was horrifying.
♫ I've been afraid to walk
- That really sucked Jess!
♫ To feel it--
- Oh my god, honey.
Let me get you a washcloth.
Will you turn that off, oh god.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Jessie,
you're one of the coolest girls I know.
But you know me.
No one compares to you, Jess.
Think you can go lay down?
Yeah.
Oh, nope.
This way.
I'll turn on your fan, get you some water.
Let's go.
Hey.
- Hey.
How you feeling'?
- Better-ish.
- Yeah.
Mm, this is good.
Want some?
- Mmm.
I don't make it as good as you though.
- Got to put the peanut butter on first,
then the butter then the jam.
- So much for low carb.
- It's a cougar.
- Stripes and spots.
- Yeah.
- Then answer it.
- Hi.
Hey.
No, I'm not doing anything, I just got up.
♫ Hands pressed hard against the window
♫ Looking out like a puppy
♫ Waiting for its master
♫ Your mattress, the biscuit's quenched
♫ And you think a little too much
♫ About her
♫ Be all that
♫ You see I'm trouble for you
- Don't forget that one.
I got ya.
It's all right.
Good?
Yeah, that was awesome.
Swimming right off the boat,
I've never done that before.
God, it was beautiful today.
- Yeah it was.
- You got some sun.
- It's worth it.
- Your hair's all wet.
- That happens when you go swimming.
- Yeah.
Come here.
You make me feel like
John Cougar Mellencamp.
- Like what, Jack and Diane or,
or Little Pink Houses or something?
- I don't know.
Um, I've, I've got to home.
I gotta wake up early.
Is that okay?
- Yeah, yeah, it's fine.
Here I'll, I'll take these two, okay?
- Okay.
- It's hemp milk, it's good.
- I wish you wouldn't do that.
- That tastes like sidewalk chalk.
- Yum.
- Spider, spider!
- Oh, shit.
- Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
- Go, go, go, go.
- My hero.
Is this my underwear?
Yeah.
Ah-ah.
♫ Come on baby just light my fire
♫ Come on baby tonight
♫ Come on baby just light
♫ Come on baby just light my fire
♫ Come on baby tonight
♫ Come on baby just light
♫ Come on baby just light my fire
♫ Come on baby tonight
♫ Come on baby
- Hi.
That's true.
- Yeah.
- I can't, I'm going sailing.
♫ Hearts beat, eyes roll
♫ Lips meet drum roll
♫ Built up to this moment with you
♫ Build up to this feeling so true
♫ But you
♫ Can't stay, can't stay
♫ Can't stay any longer so you
♫ Move your feet
♫ So you move your feet
♫ As far as you can go
♫ Move your feet
♫ As far as they can--
- I'm a little worried about you.
Come on.
Step into my office.
So what's going on with Jamie?
- I messed up.
We slept together
a few days ago.
Oh my god.
- Yeah.
- No way, are you like--
- Well, and then I slept with her lover.
How did that even happen?
- I know.
I-I-I-I-I went over there
and I said that I lo,
that Jamie had taken my hoodie,
that she had left over at Rhonda's.
- Oh that's not good.
- I know that.
- Okay, I can't believe
that Rhonda did that either.
- Yeah, afterwards she said that we um,
were probably just doing it
so that we could get closer to Jamie.
- Yeah.
- Yikes.
- Thanks.
Which is so funny because she's
not even my type, you know?
- Whatever that means.
Oh my god, does Jamie know?
- Oh god, I don't know, I
mean I haven't told her.
Um, I don't know if Rhonda has.
I was gonna tell her right away, you know,
to just kind of like get back at her
and stuff like that--
- This is really good.
- Come on, for that audition
thing, are you kidding?
- Well I-I-I-I didn't really have
fully think this all out, okay?
- Okay.
- I felt better for like
48 minutes afterwards.
Because she's leaving in like three days.
I mean, are you still gonna still tell her
that you're in love with her, or?
- I don't know.
I'm all smooshed up, Dawn.
- Okay, let me ask you a question.
Do you dream about Jamie?
Sometimes.
- Okay, in these dreams
what are you guys doing?
- Stupid stuff, like you know,
doing laundry or watching TV or--
- Okay, okay, and this
new girl, Elizabeth.
How do you feel when you're with her?
- Kind of shy.
You know, nervous, excited.
Yeah, but
without the goopy eye things.
- I mean, do you feel like, eager to
touch her and just to be near her?
- Yeah.
- Do you like, feel your shit
drawn to her like a magnet?
Geez Dawn, yeah, yeah.
- Talking's good.
You know, she, she, she gets my jokes.
Time goes by quickly.
- Do you think about Elizabeth
when you pull espresso?
Like, her eyes and her mouth?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
One last question.
Okay, pretend Jamie asks you
to be with her, as a lover.
And asks you to go to New York with her.
What would you do?
Take your time.
- I wouldn't go.
Why not?
- 'Cause I don't want to
follow her around anymore.
'Cause I'm not in love with her.
I mean, I think I was,
but I'm not anymore.
Are you sure?
- I mean,
she knows me better than anybody.
And, and I would do anything
for her and I love her
and, and I don't ever want
her to forget about me but,
I'm not in love with her.
Holy shit,
Dawn, I am like, I'm,
I-I-I, okay, I kinda have bad self esteem
and I'm kinda this neurotic mess, but,
I am not in love with Jamie.
Yeah, okay cool, I'm, I'm gonna go.
Okay, I have--
- Okay.
I mean I have to
talk to her about, stuff.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
- Yeah, you are welcome.
- I'm not in love.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Streetcar Named Desire just came on.
- That's interesting, how
bout something a little,
I don't know, less depressing?
- Sure.
- It uh, it makes me sad
that we haven't been getting along lately.
- Yeah.
- And um, I was talking to Rhonda.
- Well I mean, she's not
my Rhonda but you know.
You know Rhonda.
- I know two Rhondas.
There's a Rhonda that
lives down the street
and then there's your Rhonda.
- Well, the Rhonda that we both know.
- Your Rhonda, so you're
talking about your Rhonda.
Okay, yeah?
So, what?
- Well, I was just um,
I was talking to her
and she said,
I was telling her I'm gonna miss you.
- I'm, I'm gonna miss you too.
- An, and uh,
I mean--
- Well, you know how important
you are to me, right?
I'm gonna call you like ten times a day.
- Of course, and I'll
probably do that too, but?
And um--
- Well, hopefully Elizabeth
knows how to handle you.
- I think she does.
- Well then.
- Well I...
- Can we just watch
animals eat each other?
I'll rub your feet.
Yay, yay, yeah?
- Yeah, yes, yes.
- Give me your feet please, thank you.
Oopsies.
Look at his head.
It's huge.
I mean, I think it's a he.
- In two days I'm gonna be in Brooklyn,
eating a real bagel.
- Yeah, you won't have
sky like this though.
- I'll have stars though.
Madonna lives there.
- Yeah, I heard that Michelle
Williams lives in Brooklyn.
- She's lovely.
Madonna.
I'd go for Michelle.
Yeah you would.
- I'm goin' in.
Hey Jamie?
- Yeah.
That's all Jessie!
♫ You don't have to ask
♫ When the going gets rough
♫ I may not know what to say
♫ But being here is enough
♫ I got a good feeling
♫ I'll know you for a long, long time
♫ Let me lean on you
♫ Any time that I fail
♫ You get me laughing so hard
♫ On you I would never bail
♫ I got a good feeling
♫ I'll know you for a long, long time
♫ Picking up where we left off
♫ Here we are together again
♫ Doing nothing but everything
♫ Hand in hand with you
♫ I got a good feeling
♫ I'll know you for a real time
♫ I'll love you for a real long time
♫ I got a good feeling
♫ Ba-bah-ba-ba-bah
♫ Ba-bah-bah-bah-bah
♫ Ba-ba-ba-bah-bah-da-bah
♫ Ba-bah-bah-bah-bah-ah-ah-ah
♫ Things are looking alright today
♫ Sun is shining I'm feeling okay
♫ My chin is up and my spirits high
♫ I'm pretty sure that I could fly
♫ So I'll sing
♫ La, ti da, ti da
♫ And I say
♫ Things are finally right for me
♫ Sun is shining, I'm feeling free
♫ My heart is whole, I can finally breathe
♫ The horizon I can see
♫ So I sing
♫ La, ti da, ti da
♫ And I sing
♫ Things are finally going swell
♫ Sun is shining I'm feeling well
♫ My mind is clear finally
♫ I feel the happy coming back to me
♫ So I sing
♫ La, ti da, ti da
♫ And I sing