I may take the liberty
of beginning by saying something
about myself...
and my role...
in talking to you
about philosophical matters...
because I wanted to be
understood perfectly clearly
that I am not a guru.
In other words...
I talk about what we call these things...
and that comprises a multitude of interests...
concerning oriental philosophy...
psychotherapy...
religion, mysticism, etcetera.
I talk about talk about these things
because I'm interested in them...
and because I enjoy talking about them.
In every sense of the person...
who makes his living by doing
what he enjoys doing.
And that is fading.
Now in stating that
although I am not a guru...
that means also...
that I am not trying to help you,
or include you.
I accept you as you are.
I'm not out there for the same world.
Of course when a stream...
a bubbling spring...
flows out from the mountains,
it's doing it's thing.
And if a thirsty traveler helps himself,
well that's fine.
When a bird sings...
it doesn't sing
for the advancement of music.
But if somebody starts to listen
and is delighted, that's fine.
And so I talk in the same spirit.
I don't have...
a group of followers.
I'm not trying to make disciples.
Because I work on the principle
of a physician...
not as a surgeon.
A physician is always trying
to get rid of his patients
and send them away healthy
to stand on their own feet.
But as a clergyman,
is trying to get the numbers...
of the religious organization...
Hold on one second.
It's behind the pillow.
Fuck.
Wait. One second, I can...
Hold on.
Okay.
Okay wait.
Dr. T.
Hold on.
I found it.
So, hold on.
Just... I'm gonna...
No, Dr. T, let me just... okay.
My niece is coming tomorrow,
she's 25, she's an actress...
we have a lot of similarities.
But you know, my brother has
totally dropped the ball.
He's not showing up as her dad...
No, 'cause he's in still in rehab.
No, for three more months.
I think probably the reason she's an actress
is because of that I'm an actress.
Well, she didn't really have
a lot of role models, did she?
No, it's just I always seem
to step in and I'll try to...
you know...
cheer her up because...
you know, what am I gonna say?
Hi, your dad's in rehab for,
what, the 10th time and...
you know, I'm sorry
he stole all your stuff?
Dreamworks.
- Hey, Shawn. Is Peg there? It's Marie.
Hey Marie, hold on. Let me see
if I can get her for you. Hold on.
Okay, thanks.
Hello.
- Hey, hey, what's up?
I lost you up the road,
so I'm just calling you back.
So did you hear?
- Well...
yeah, I did. I mean, unfortunately,
on the fox movie, it's not gonna happen.
They made an offer to somebody else.
Who was it?
I think it's Kristen Wigg.
I'm trying to find out.
Oh right. No, no, that makes sense.
That makes sense.
No, it's okay.
Yeah, no, no.
I mean, it would have been great
because at least you would have made
a little bit of money on that but...
Yeah, unfortunately.
And my guess is she's gonna do it, so.
Yeah, no, no.
- Onward, I guess.
Right.
No, so, okay and...
is the other thing...
what's happening with that?
Oh yeah. I mean,
the good news is on the indie...
they have a start date, so...
that's looking more real at least.
Okay.
Yeah. That looks like it might be happening.
And I did find a solar engineer
that you can talk to.
You know, you wanted to do
some research, you said yesterday.
Right, right, but wait.
They have a start date?
Did they have money?
Well, it's not clear
if they have their money.
They're claiming they have a start date
when they're gonna go.
I mean, it's a sag
ultra low budget film...
so how much money could they need?
I don't know.
Ultra? Is ultra low?
No, it's fine, it's fine.
It's a good script.
Okay.
- Okay, have a good day.
- Okay.
You too, bye Maria.
- Bye bye.
Where is he?
Where is he now?
Carol!
Did you just get here?
- I did.
I didn't hear you.
How about if you say:
I now...
- Yeah.
You gonna hate me for this, but it's really good.
- No, I'm gonna love it.
Okay, I have 45 years...
to draw upon every incident that I'm in.
It's not like wow, oh God,
I'm 45, can I still do this?
It's like, I have 45 years
worth of experience to meet...
this brand new experience.
This moment right now.
- And I have all 45 years worth...
of colors, and range, you know...
everything to be in this moment.
You know? Whether it's like
doing the most boring thing...
or the greatest adventure you're on,
right?
Why don't people think of that?
I now own 45... I have in here.
Instead they're like: I'm 45.
I can't do that anymore.
That's fun.
That is fucking fun, right?
Will you try it?
Can we have an experiment?
- Yes.
Can we be like the...
what could it be called?
I have, I have...
- We could just start a...
a cult. Like when people are
gonna look in the mirror and go:
I'm just joking, I have...
I'll come to that workshop.
You have shooters.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Well, maybe so...
- I think, I think that...
I'm content that that is just over.
That's just... that era of...
The fertility era?
- No, the seduction...
the attraction, seduction...
You know, oh, I'm gonna wear these...
heels with this outfit.
- I don't believe it.
I don't believe it.
- No, believe it.
Believe it.
- When did it end?
Just...
- Years ago!
a couple of minutes ago?
- No, years ago.
Well, you still... doll up pretty nice.
You referring to my coif?
I like it.
Sort of the ocean look.
The sea breeze look, it's good.
It's good.
You don't need to make an effort.
You're so Au natural.
You look good.
Hey it's me, it's Faye.
I'm just letting you know
that my flight lands tomorrow at 11...
so I should be at your place around noon.
I can't wait to see you. Okay. Bye.
Between western psychologists,
psychiatry, and psychotherapy...
and the so-called religions of Asia
there is common ground...
because those are interested
in changing states of human consciousness.
Whereas, institutional western religion...
Christianity, Judaism and even Islam...
are relatively less interested
in this matter.
Western religions...
are more concerned with behavior,
doctrine...
See, he has a colossal advantage.
Take off your cross and follow me.
Hey, but wait a minute.
I don't know I'm gonna be resurrected
two days later.
I can't perform miracles.
Wait. Put this down, put it down.
Wait. Just take off your shoes.
I know, it's a pain in the ass
but it's just sandy.
Oh my God, your hair is so nice.
Come, okay.
- Oh my god.
This is so pretty.
Are you gonna take a picture?
- I'm gonna do a video.
Look at this.
It's like on top of the ocean.
See?
It's just ocean.
It's like a boat practically.
- What?
It's like living in a boat practically.
It's so good to see you.
You know?
How is your mom?
She's good.
I think she's pretty good.
She's working a lot.
Do you still have that same boyfriend?
Yeah?
What's that like?
- It's the best.
I wouldn't know.
No, things are going really
well right now with him, so.
You think you guys are gonna
get married and all that?
Maybe?
Really?
You talk about it?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd like to stay with him.
So I'm going to West Hollywood...
and I should be back by five.
- Cool.
And we're gonna have a quick...
I'm just meeting him
and then I'll come back.
Okay, cool... Have fun.
- I'll see you.
Thanks. And...
You know, anything in the fridge
that you want, it's yours.
There's water on top of the fridge.
Where is my purse?
Hold for a second.
I can never find my fucking purse.
I just applied to one school.
Which one?
- Columbia.
And you got in... the school of engineering.
- I got in.
Yeah.
And I got in, I got there in '68
after that whole... you know.
Isn't that kind of funny that
that's how you become something?
Well, as it turns out...
- I got into Juilliard...
so I became...
I saw that.
You googled me.
- I did, I did.
And I actually read something
but I didn't...
It's all lies.
- Well, I don't know if it's lies...
but I didn't read...
I didn't see anything, unfortunately.
No images? You didn't...
- I saw the images, yeah.
So I know who I'm looking at.
- I see what you mean.
You did not see me...
- I didn't get to look, I didn't like it...
pretend to be other people.
- Yes.
Right, I didn't see that.
That's okay.
- But I saw that people liked your work.
Oh, that's nice.
- Yeah. They do!
All right. So...
- This is a pyronometer.
This is, we use this for...
What is it?
- Well...
Do I need to put this in context
before we start...
or you wanna talk about the instruments?
I mean, I know you're researching
something here, but...
But what is it?
- It measures sunlight.
You see this little black thing
inside the two plastic domes...
in the glass domes?
That's a thermopile.
This thing.
- No, no.
That.
- That.
Inside the black, the little black...
thing in the middle, the black disk.
- The black circle is a thermopile.
Thermopile.
- Pile.
Yes. It might love sun,
temperature too...
but it's a thermopile.
- Okay.
And what happens
is when the sun shines on it...
it's black and absorbs the heat.
And it absorbs broad-spectrum radiation...
and it... it's really what it is,
is a bunch of little thermocouples...
which are bi-metal devices that...
when tempera... when heat flows
from hot to cold...
generate a small current.
We're, you know,
looking for bankable data...
which is what they call it.
The data you can take to the bank...
convince investors that there's a...
a viable solar or wind facility...
and go ahead and get people
to put up money...
and then we're talking
serious money, you know?
And are they putting up money for...
solar panels and windmills?
- They're putting, yeah...
solar panels, wind turbines...
- And you measure with things like this.
Things like this.
- How much energy is hitting the ground.
What is this thing?
This one measures the beam...
the direct beam of the sun
into the, you know, the...
what you see when you stare at the sun.
Right.
- Yeah, that beam.
So this measures the overall
illumination of the sky...
and this measures the beam.
This includes the beam,
but this measures only the beam.
It seemed like everybody else
was already really successful...
and I was this broke, like,
girl from New York with...
you know, ripped jeans
and my dad's overcoat.
And I would go for meetings
and these women were already...
they had, they were, you know,
they were 25 years old...
and they were making so much money...
and so they would show up
looking like that.
And I would arrive
in my rental car, like...
And I would get feedback too, like:
She's not pretty enough.
But really what it meant is, like...
I wasn't in the right,
I didn't have the Gucci shoes...
and the pencil skirt.
- Right, sounds terrible.
Well, I also think I wasn't,
I think I was self-conscious.
I wasn't... I mean, it's my... thing.
I just wanted to be around
people who were all working.
That seemed exciting to me, like...
- Yeah.
comparing notes.
I didn't, it didn't...
I mean, I would be really sad...
if I didn't get a part that I wanted.
And I remember I would,
you know, I had all...
I would... if there was a sidewalk...
I wouldn't step on the crack, you know.
I still pick up pennies.
Do you do that?
I see a penny, I pick it up.
Oh, that's awesome.
I mean, waiting...
If a director was
trying to decide whether...
you know, I would hear from someone:
Oh, it's between you and so-and-so...
and he just can't decide.
So, you know, there's three...
She's blonde and you're not,
so if they cast so-and-so...
There's also, like, maybe...
So they're just waiting to find out.
And I would spend two months...
you know, not stepping on cracks
and picking up pennies.
Get lost.
You said it yourself.
Like children love to play
hide and seek...
Get lost, like we all like to go to a play.
It's all glass windows...
so like, you just look out from the
kitchen and all you can see is the ocean.
It's the coolest thing.
You just don't see anything else.
Honey, I'm sure it's lovely.
- It's so great.
You know what? Send me a picture.
Post a picture on Facebook, tomorrow...
Okay.
- and I'll see.
I will.
- Okay.
I'll give you a video tour.
I really miss you.
- I miss you too, I love you.
I love you too.
You think... you think I could see,
you think you could...
I don't know how to put this
delicately...
Okay.
- I'd really like to see your breasts.
Right now?
- Yeah. Yeah!
I'm kind of just in the middle
of the living room, right.
Is she asleep?
- Yeah, but I'm scared.
I think it's okay.
You don't have to do a whole show.
I just wanna see, you know,
can you show me a little bit?
Yeah.
Can you see? Those are my boobs.
- Yeah. Oh yeah.
Do you like them?
- Yeah. Yes!
Oh my gosh.
- You can't talk that loud.
Sorry.
It's okay.
What's happened, what's going on?
- I'm so sorry.
I'm just... we're just looking at photos.
No, that's Marie.
Oh my god.
I'm sorry. I didn't know
this is video chat, okay?
Yeah, I'm live, the live feed.
It's nice to meet you.
It's really nice to meet you.
- Yeah.
Can you see?
- I thought you were just working...
Were we disturbing you?
No, no, I just don't sleep at night.
I have insomnia.
I was just gonna get a glass of water.
Oh, you're so cute. He's so cute.
I know.
- Well done.
And well done, sir.
Okay, enjoy yourselves.
I'm gonna go back to...
Okay, do you need us to be quiet?
- No, no...
you didn't wake me up,
I'm listening to my audio books.
Okay.
That's why I didn't wanna do that.
Nice meeting you.
I've never worn a wetsuit before.
It's great. You're gonna like the...
I like it.
I wish...
I sort of like the wetsuit feeling.
No, like, I wish I had this kind of...
other layer of protection all the time,
you know?
Okay.
Actually, can you do me a favor?
You wanna zip me up and I'll zip you up?
Yeah.
They're finished.
They do make it so...
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Oh my god!
Okay... so just hang 'em...
You can hang 'em
on the back of the chair.
Okay.
- I'll grab the towels.
It's stuck on my feet.
- I'm gonna help you.
Sit down.
No one can see.
Okay.
- Thanks.
Just hold... actually take your towel
and hold it in front of you.
Like, over your boobies.
They're great boobs.
- You have great boobs.
No, I had great boobs.
- No, you have...
You know, my boobs used to be
up here somewhere.
They're gorgeous.
- And then they go down.
No.
- Yes. No, they do.
You have to enjoy these
while they're... while they're up.
Let's do it, wait, hold on.
We're gonna preserve them for posterity.
Hold!
I'm not looking forward to taking
my clothes off the way I used to.
It used to be great, I couldn't wait.
- Yeah?
Like, can we just get through all this...
stuff that makes me nervous,
like the dinner,
and the talking, and everything,
and to the I'll just...
take my pants off, my shirt
and you'll be really happy.
So what do you...
how do you navigate that, though?
It's awkward.
I'm sure they probably feel
self-conscious too.
Like it's, like they're looking at images
of all these women...
but they're not the same
like they used to be either.
I guess it's different for boys.
I don't know why but I think it's dif...
I, I... maybe they feel...
Well, they... they might feel insecure, but...
it seems more...
it's...
I felt more pressure in my life
to be the object of...
you know?
- Right.
The thing that ma...
the engine for why it's...
hot.
- Right.
The image that starts
the ball rolling or something.
I'm worried that we're squishing them.
You think we're squishing them?
- Probably.
Wait, I should stay up here
'cause the... this light's amazing.
Then this light?
Awful?
- Yeah, well, it's very artsy.
That's what I was thinking.
- This looks like an album cover.
Medicine in Jefferson and Lincoln.
Is it to do with facial hair?
- No.
Is it to do with their appearance at all?
Is it to do with their policies?
- No.
Is it to do with their personalities?
Is it to do with their sexual orientation?
- No.
Yes, they're all transgendered.
Didn't you know that?
- Those four...
Does it have to do with the fact
that they're all on Mount Everest?
No, I'm not gonna say.
Why?
- 'Cause then you'll...
Maybe you'll steal it.
I don't know you very well.
Hi guys.
- Did you see that lightening?
Yes.
Hi, my love.
Did you have a good day, monkey, monkey?
Yes, and you?
- Little monkey.
All right, sorry,
I don't wanna interrupt.
These are my friends.
This is Suzanne.
Oh, hello.
- Hi, I'm Marie, nice to meet you.
Hi, Dan.
- Hi Dan.
Marie.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm really glad you guys are here.
Yeah, it's a great place.
- Enjoying it?
It's beautiful.
Yeah, we've definitely been enjoying
this deck.
I'm really sorry.
I think I broke your toilet seat.
No, no, it's not broken.
I promise you.
- No, I think I broke it just now.
You didn't.
I know it seems like you might...
That you broke it to you,
but it's bin, it's an old toilet seat.
It was already broken?
It was already broken.
- Oh, okay.
Yeah, no. It was here, you know,
it's a cheap rental toilet seat.
I thought I... I lifted it up,
I'm really high, I'm sorry.
Are you gonna...
- It's okay.
Are you gonna blend that?
Yeah. Do you want some?
Yeah.
- That's good.
Wait, can I smoke before you...?
Oh, of course.
Yeah, no.
Go ahead.
I thought I broke your toilet seat.
- But you didn't.
I was so worried.
I was like... alright, you have to go
in her kitchen now, you know?
'Cause now...
'Cause now, first you're not hanging out...
with other people because
you're so busy staring at a screen...
but now we're not hanging out with each other
'cause we're so busy...
staring at ourselves on screen.
Is that what kale tastes like?
That's what kale tastes like.
- Okay.
Just drink it down.
You're going to feel good.
What else is in there?
- Just drink that down.
You're supposed to drink it all at once?
Great.
You know, I sit on it and I slip, right?
This is bad.
I don't think you can fix it.
It's just a cheap rental.
No, I can... look.
See?
- Wait, I didn't know that...
See that bolt, yeah.
It's like a little secret hatch
and then under here is the...
Wait.
Put your hand under there.
See, that's where the bolt
comes out through there?
I never would have known that.
Yeah.
And that just pops back in.
That's...
No more spectacle...
- Here, try it out.
I can actually like, It doesn't...
It didn't move.
Yeah, that's the way
you could have been...
For a year.
- For a year...
you could have been doing it like that.
See, this is good.
- Nice.
I'm thinking right here.
Does that seem...
- Yeah. Yeah.
That's where you want it?
- Well, does it seem high?
Does it seem right to you...
if it was your house?
Hold on. Let me go...
Oh yeah.
Hey, how's it going?
- Come on in.
Okay. Can I...
Just hang your coat right there.
Did that seem right?
That felt good.
- Okay.
Oh, this is so great.
- Yeah?
What I really liked about
your last movie was...
sort of the combination
between horror and comedy.
So it seems like that's something
you're continuing with?
Yeah, I think I have
a morbid sense of humor...
so I think there will
always be some of that...
you know, on display.
But I wouldn't consider it
say horror-comedy per Se.
I think it's a genuine story
about it's loneliness...
and about the isolation
that being a vampire is.
And at the same time...
just being a single person
in the modern ages.
So I think that it's just...
they're good parallels.
Yeah, totally.
What... do you know what the movie's about?
- I have no idea.
I think it's something to do
with a private detective.
I don't know much about it.
I'm here because I missed
his last movie and...
I just have to make up for it now...
so it doesn't seem
like I'm a terrible friend.
But we're not real friends actually.
So, just be like looking at me
and then...
Yes.
I was... I loved...
All right, I really like this place.
- Yes.
It's got a nice...
Oh gosh.
I'm good. How are you?
Good.
I'm... I just wanted to say good night.
I'm actually out with a bunch of people
and I think we're gonna stay out
pretty late, so...
I wanted to say good night now.
I love you too.
I miss you a lot.
I... How do you do iPhone...
if you're gonna... if you stay...
- I do it like this.
So, can I ask you?
Are you...
If you're talking to people
and you say like...
'well, I'm gonna...'
Do you do that?
Yeah, sometimes.
- Like, you mime it?
Yeah, or when I, like I'm like,
and I wrote a...
Oh god.
I'm just...
Okay.
I'm sorry, you can talk.
- No, no, I don't wanna say anything.
I mean...
Oh, a really nice hot tub.
That's the way it should be. It's yours.
It's my hot tub.
I shouldn't be saying that.
Is it conceded to say 'you have
a nice hot tub', is the question?
How long are your parents out of town?
My parents...
I actually don't know.
I just sent them an email asking them...
if I could use the hot tub
and they said yeah.
You drink this water out of a bowl?
You want some water?
- No.
I have a boyfriend so I feel
like I shouldn't do that.
Okay.
I understand.
You gonna come back outside?
Okay, I think this is gonna be
really good for you.
And you might not want it...
but I think you're gonna like it.
I'm sorry.
- Oh no, don't.
Don't worry. You know, I understand.
I had way too many mornings like that.
Here's two acetaminophen that you're
gonna drink when this is done.
Now, okay, I have something
that you're really gonna love.
It's a very loud noise
so I want you to brace yourself.
Just hold on to me tight.
We're together in this.
You ready?
Oh, oh, the poor.
Little monkey.
Little monkey overdid it.
Oh god.
Here, I'll finish it.
Are you gonna throw up?
Oh, are you? Are you?
Forgive me.
Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
It's really okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Do you think that's it?
- I think so.
Okay, let's get out of here.
This is a global station
in which we're measuring...
you know, the whole dome of the sky.
Okay.
There are no beam measurements.
If you notice, they got
the little domed instruments out on the...
south side of this thing
on these little wings over there.
Oh, the things...
Yeah, the little...
- Yeah, exactly...
Is this thing under it that beam thing?
No, that's there is no beam
measurement here.
That's just, we call that a cross arm.
Cross arm.
Just a support.
- Okay.
And we're also measuring
relative humidity, in that.
What's the name of the dome?
- Pyronometer.
The pyronometer.
So there's two pyronometers.
For redundancy.
This is a John installation.
He always puts the fencepost
on top of that and...
and tapes up all the excess cable...
like a mummy.
You know, this is...
you know, you can see where all the wires,
all the colored wires are?
Those are the...
sensors, all landed on little terminals
in the logger.
So this is coming...
No, this, that's just battery...
and solar panel stuff
on the right hand side.
Okay, where's
the pyronometer measurement?
Those are all in there.
Into this.
- Into that, that's correct.
All of these things are
sort of tuned and calibrated.
They're well established.
You know, it doesn't take very...
you know, you don't have to
start from scratch.
You're not baking a cake from...
you know, basic... ferm... mix...
from ingredients.
You're basic baking it
from mix, you know.
You're basically...
A lot of this is sort of set.
- So you're saying this is like...
an instant cake.
It is like an instant cake.
It... you know, it's like
inexpensive ice cream.
And when we put these things in,
we have to...
you know, we have to document
this thing thoroughly.
You know, this is all bankable data,
so everybody wants to know...
the serial number of every
instrument that's out there.
They wanna know how it's calibrated.
- Right.
You take, you know,
exhaustive photographs...
of how each thing is mounted.
We... every photograph is like...
you know, with the iPhone with the GPS...
pin in every photograph,
so you know exactly...
where you were, you know where the...
what serial number the instrument is.
It's all very, very rigorously established...
so that anybody sending their auditor...
from a bank for a loan for half
a billion dollars is gonna...
They have proof.
They have proof...
of how that we,
at least we went through this...
process in a rigorous and thorough manner.
Documented everything...
So what happened?
Did you wanna get divorced?
Or... was it a mutual?
- No, I didn't.
No?
No, it was a big disappointment.
I'm sorry.
- Yeah, I know.
My wife just...
you know, suddenly...
suddenly kind of flaked. I don't know.
She...
just...
had a better idea and left.
And actually had an
alternative to me in mind...
you know, back east.
- Okay.
That happens.
Apparently.
But you were together how many years?
At the time of the divorce
it was 32 years.
Wow.
- Yeah.
It was really pretty awful.
Do you think you would
wanna get married again?
Not soon. Not today.
I'm not asking.
- No, okay. Well, you know...
what's happened in the course of my...
so-called recovery is that I have...
started to look at women...
and then say, do I wanna,
is that something I wanna...
you know, very nice,
very attractive, do I wanna...
interrupt my current... solitude!
- Yeah.
My lovely...
how is this gonna fit into my lovely life?
Exactly, which I'm now creating.
Which I'm really enjoying.
- Right. Exactly.
I know... I know.
Do I have to come, have to...
come, have to hang out
with this person all the time?
She's really pregnant.
- Yeah.
Was this a while ago?
And so did she have this baby?
Yeah, she's actually had
another baby since then.
But I didn't take a picture
of that pregnancy.
Have you ever been pregnant?
- Never.
Not once?
- Not that I know of, no.
Have you?
No.
What...
What?
When I was playing a doctor once,
I went and watched...
babies being born... for real.
Like... and I've thought the women, I think...
because they gave me scrubs...
and I think the women just thought
I was an intern or a doctor.
Really?
Who let you in, like, the hospital?
The hospital let me in.
Because, you know, you say
blah, blah, blah...
the studio, whatever, was blah, blah.
And they're like:
Oh, okay, sure, you can go.
Go, you know, the fourth floor.
Here's the pass.
You know, you sign something or whatever.
I remember one of the doctors
was delivering a baby...
and he had his hand inside this woman...
and he was watching a baseball,
like, a basketball game.
While he was...
- Yeah, it's that...
you know, he just does it all the time
so he's sort of like, okay.
Was she like conscious?
- Yeah, giving birth.
Yeah, she was conscious.
And she wasn't like: Turn off the TV
while I'm giving birth.
No.
What?
Oh, I thought we were gonna kiss.
Do you... you should do it then.
- Oh, really?
'Cause you kinda,
I thought we were too...
but then I thought, he doesn't want to.
No, It was mentally, you said 'what'
and I went...
Should I just be very still and quiet?
Okay, what if I just, I'm gonna sit here.
- Yeah.
And then you just do what you wanna do.
- Okay.
'Cause then I'll know
it's what you wanna do.
'Cause I can't stand it.
I'm so tired of the guessing.
Oh, okay.
You're tired of the guessing?
I can't... yeah,
I can't tell what you want?
Really?
- I really can't.
Okay, yeah, I said I wasn't gonna do
anything but that's really nice.
No, they're just too tight.
I'm not taking them off.
That's like whoop.
Oh really?
Yeah, a speed bump.
What?
I feel like I'm on a ride
at a theme park;
this is like a seat belt.
Unintelligible mumble.
Yeah. No, I'm the camera.
- Yeah.
Sorry, I can't find my car key.
It must be just right...
Right around here maybe.
You know, I think it's in the bedroom.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Sorry.
Oh my God. I looked through this entire bag.
I'm so sorry.
Okay.
You all right?
Do you put the ice in first, then?
Not yet. I'm gonna start it
and then get it going.
All right.
Folks, it's show time.
You gonna put in the ice?
Not yet. I'm gonna do it... later.
Or that's later?
Alright. Ready?
- So this is you...
So you liked him?
- You thought he was okay.
I really like him.
- He's fun.
Yeah, he's really nice.
He seems tender.
I don't know.
Seems like he really cares about you.
Until he tried it.
Are you trying to set us up?
- No.
He's really...
He's just a friend.
He dates lots of young women...
like your age.
- Really?
I think that's lame.
- No.
Oh, I don't know.
It's just... it's biology.
He's still got a...
I don't know, I almost...
he's still got a sack full of nuts.
But that makes no sense.
That he's got...
That he... he's...
- A sack of nuts.
Still.
Right?
- I guess. Cute.
And so then...
you know, we'll be together and a...
young woman will walk through the room and...
he... you know, you just see,
just biologically, he's like...
His brain's going wha-a-a.
I could pollinate that.
And I can't, you know,
I can't get upset about that.
I get upset about that stuff.
Really?
- It really scares me.
Yeah, it scares me to think...
about being in a position where, like...
I'm not the young one anymore.
'Cause I feel like my whole life,
I've always been...
like, the young person, like the young
person who was precocious...
and part of... but I think...
- Yeah.
You were the young person who was advanced.
Right.
Hanging out with...
Yeah, older people.
- older people.
Right.
- And then suddenly you're...
Yeah, now like everyone's
sort of caught up to me...
I feel completely like, a duh.
I'm just so afraid for like,
and also I feel like I used...
being young and as like
a way of getting things.
It's power.
- Right.
It's power, right?
- People will do anything.
So then you feel your power...
kind of being drained away.
- Yeah.
When I started to realize that...
if I walked into a room
men weren't looking at me...
that they were looking at younger women...
you know, that something had passed me by.
I became really depressed about it
and then that's when I started...
I was just stoned all the time.
I would just... I thought
I could escape it somehow.
But really, it just narrowed
my options really.
So that's why I'm interested, you know...
because you have all of these,
you can do anything you want.
And it's very powerful. You can do...
- Yeah.
I mean, I think... that, you know,
there're all those different roles.
Like, if you get married
and you become a mother,
then you're... that's your role.
Yeah, I've talked to a lot of people...
men, whose wives were actresses
who stopped...
acting completely once they had kids.
They were just like: 'I don't wanna
deal with this bullshit anymore.
Right, I'm done.
This is now my new life.'
Right.
Which, if it's so easy
to just stop doing it...
I mean, why am I even getting...
Right. But do you think
it would be easy for you?
Don't, don't, it doesn't matter
what other people do.
I just wonder what...
If it would be easy for me...
- Yeah.
What you think it would be easy for...
if you do think it would be easy
for you to stop acting...
and stay home with a baby all the time?
I think it would because if...
I don't know, realistically, but...
part of me thinks it would because
so much of...
it is about attention,
getting attention...
and if you have a kid, that kid is just...
paying attention...
- And it needs you.
And it needs you so much more
than like...
the movie business needs me.
- Right.
I don't know.
- I always feel, like...
what was a little bit weird for me,
a little...
a sort of tragedy, is that I always
wanted to...
you know, you knew.
I always was way into...
being with the kids
and playing with the kids.
I always thought I would have kids.
Didn't you think that I would?
- Yeah.
Right?
So, I always thought that
that was just gonna happen.
I just never met a man I thought
would be a good father.
That I could really rely on.
- Right.
But that might have been
my skewed perception because of...
you know, grandpa and your grandfather
and all of that, like...
It's a little different than Brooklyn, right?
- Sorry?
It's a little different from Brooklyn.
- Yeah, it's pretty different.
Yeah.
It's something... it's great.
And then one day all these houses
are gonna be gone.
I mean, the...
sea level here is...
it's getting higher every year.
All these...
you know, we talk about
castles right in the sand.
Yeah, I can't imagine, I mean,
I can't imagine living here.
I'd be scared that I'd fall
into the water or something.
Yeah, it's great for the moment
but... it's just...
it's funny to think these people
bought their dream houses.
They thought they were, you know,
putting their nugget away.
Yeah.
- And, I mean, look at these pylons.
This is all gonna erode.
It's just part of the folly of it all.
But you know, I got my place...
five years ago.
And the tide was just...
- Do you regret it?
No. No, every day is...
fucking awesome.
But if you were thinking
you were cashing in...
you gonna have to think it again.
All this...
will be gone in, I don't know, 10 years.
That doesn't scare you?
No, I'll just move somewhere else.
I'm already, you know,
I'm done with... fretting over it.
I've spent a lot of time...
trying to change people's minds
and it just doesn't work.
So now I'm just gonna enjoy the ride...
from each beautiful place
and watch it crumble away.
But look at this, you know.
You just live in the moment.
It's spectacular.
Well, I'm gonna take a cab home, okay?
No, I want to come get you.
I'm gonna come get you.
I know, but last time you did that
you were really grouchy...
and you said you resented me
for making you... pick me up.
Well...
that was a weird... that was...
that was a weird night.
Now, this one's gonna be
a very normal one.
I'm just gonna come get you
and be really happy...
and we're gonna make out in the car,
etcetera.
Cool. I can't wait. I really miss you.
I miss you too.
- I really love you.
I love you.
- I can't wait to hold you.
I'm gonna kiss you as soon as possible.
Yeah, it'll be really soon.
All right, love you.
- I love you too.
Bye.
Thank you so much.
No, thank you.
I'm so glad you came.
Me too.
- All right.
Come on. I don't want you to be late.
Alright, now, I want you to be really...
really careful going out of here.
Okay.
Say a little prayer.
Really. Just start...
say a little prayer.
Okay.
- I love you.
I love you too, give me a kiss.
Thank you again.
- I'll see you.
Call in and text me
when you get to the other side.
Okay.
- Okay, just to let me know you're okay.
Be very careful.
All right?
Look at those waves.
We should offer this as a service.
We could go down like Venice Beach.
- Leave it... it's off.
Under there.
- Did I get it?
You, you, all right. Now, when I'm up here,
you go under.
Okay.
Good. We're gonna go through the center.
My God, I almost...
Okay.
- Okay.
Good, good.
It's done.
Awesome.
And the cord. I get the cord, alright?
And then it does this thing.
It's better.
- Sweet.
It's much better.
There's a green bean by your foot.
Just... just dropped it.
Good stuff.
You got anything else?
I'm all done.
Oh yeah.
What a night.
What's going on up there?
I don't know.
I mean, there's...
for the longest...
I don't know...
I lived here almost a whole year
and no sound, no parties.
No, I've never heard, I never heard.
But, it's just like...
They're kids. I think they
just graduated from something.
They're young.
To youths.
Can you do Jack?
Please.
Jack finishing dinner?
Yeah.
Just ask me about the kids again,
as Jack.
How about those goddamn
kids upstairs, huh?
It's enough to drive you crazy.
You know what I mean?
Again.
No, that's enough.
No, I can never have enough Jack.
Oh, Rusty, come on.
Do some Jack for me.
Come on.
So Jack...
did you think the fish was underdone?
No, I thought the fish was perfect.
Stop worrying about it.
Know what I mean?
The fish was perfect.
All righty, Ann?
All right, Rusty.
Did you just pat me?
- I did, I like this.
I like your shawl.
He's patting me.
- Look at you in your shawl.
Your little granny shawl.
It's cute.
All right.
You know what you just did?
You patted me,
then you called me a granny...
and then you called me cute.
- That's not so bad.
What?
Don't look, why...
And then you look at me like that.
Fuck you.
Really.
Em, chill.
You're too...
You know, you've been on this...
Just...
- tear!
You've been on a tear.
A what?
A tear?
You're on a tear.
A pity party tear.
Come on.
- You don't understand nothing.
Oh, maybe not.
I just think you're
spending a lot of time...
I mean, tell me what it is.
Wha... are you... are you...
having a crisis?
Am I having a crisis?
I think you're projecting.
I'm doing fine.
So am I.
- Okay.
Well, you're just being sensitive.
That's the only way I'm bringing it up.
I'm not trying to...
come at you. You're just being so sensitive.
With the granny stuff.
This is... This is a...
what should I say about this...
a beautiful lace thing?
What do you wanna say?
I think it's pretty.
It's nice.
That's nice.
- Okay.
What else do you like?
I like being here with you.
You know that.
Yeah, you're comf... I'm comfortable.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I don't think
we should fuck with that.
I agree.
I only hope you didn't think
I thought we should...
I hope just comfortable.
- Yeah.
We had a nice dinner.
You know, I like it when we,
you know, I can...
laugh with you and... yeah.
So, when I say you're cute,
that's not that I'm...
You shouldn't feel threatened, like...
- I know, but it was...
like I'm saying...
- No it's, I wasn't threatened...
I was insulted. It's just the patting,
and the granny, and the cute.
It's just a little much.
That was a little...
Don't you think?
Come on?
- I mean, really.
What do you want?
- Like, we're great friends.
I don't want anything.
I like, I was enjoying...
What do you want? Petting? Not petting?
Are you flirting with me now?
No, I'm just trying to make things right.
They're right, they're fine.
- Good.
I think we have a good...
Don't you think we have a good arrangement?
- I do.
We can do that too.
Doesn't have to be a big deal, right?
Come on, Em.
Just a little.
- Rusty, I don't wanna...
See, I don't even know if I can pet you.
I just don't want you to feel bad.
You're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I think you're very drunk.
No, I'm just...
just feeling good.
No, do Jack.
Tell me that you're feeling good.
Come on.
Tell me.
Will you have sex with me if I'm Jack?
I said, tell me that you're feeling good.
I'm feeling good.
Good.
- All right.
All right. So we...
okay.
- All right.
- So, not tomorrow? We're not going out?
No.
I'm going by myself.
Okay.
- But maybe later in the week?
Sure.
Just text me and I'll meet you out there.
- Okay.
Let's clean this up.
Okay. No, you clean.
- I've been cleaning up.
You clean it up because
I did most of the cooking.
You stay there.
- No, you know what?
Granny's just gonna curl up.
'Cause grannies get to just...
Look, old granny need another drinkie?
- Doctor I ain't sick...
Granny's cold.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Grandpa Jack.
There's a sense in which...
psychiatry and psychotherapy are becoming...
the religion of the west.
Psychoanalysis has much in common...
with the forms and procedures
of institutional religion.
There is, for example, apostolic succession...
the passing down of one of...
So, what's going on with the sun?
If somebody asks me that?
It's...
there. It's, you know, for, for...
for the foreseeable, useful...
future.
Ultimately, it goes away.
Not everything goes away.
But in the meantime, it's sitting there.
It's a...
a middle-aged star. And...
you know it's there and...
you know, available in various forms
for us to harvest...
energy we use from it.
Okay.
Wind is ultimately solar.
Wave power would be solar
because it's generated by winds.
You know, direct solar energy,
you know, photovoltaic or...
concentrated forms of solar energy,
those are all...
just...
energy harvested as it's produced.
Even ethanol, you know.
You grow plants.
You create a fuel, an alcohol, and...
that's also renewable, solar base, fuel.
The fossil fuels are also solar based.
They took, you know...
I don't know,
70-100 million years to make...
and they were stored...
you know, in the form of plant life.
And...
there's a lot of that stuff and we've been...
taking that large accumulation,
all that we had in the back...
and we've been...
burning it in a 100 years time.
So, what the earth was busy doing for...
a long, long, long, long time...
was going up very rapidly... in smoke.
So that seems to be something...
that you would think would
throw things out of balance.
So the whole renewable idea is one
of living within your means.
Using things as they come...
in a sustainable matter.
Until, of course, the sun goes away.
Is that what you meant?
I think so.
I forget.
I was gonna ask you something else
but I forgot what it was.
Well...