Hey! (LAUGHS)
Hey! Ha ha ha!
Yeah!
Wa-hey!
Yeah! (LAUGHS)
(QUIET, EERIE MUSIC)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(EERIE MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(CICADAS CHIRP NOISILY)
- (SPEAKS JAPANESE)
- We are not lost!
We are somewhere around here.
(SPEAKS JAPANESE)
I told you, we're lost!
We should've brought a compass.
I don't need a compass!
(SPEAKS JAPANESE)
No, that's east! We've been
walking north since we set off.
But... we turned west
at the river.
(SPEAKS JAPANESE)
It's that way!
It's getting dark soon.
You play with your GPS.
I'm going this way.
(GPS BEEPS)
Akito?
Akito!
- (AKITO SCREAMS)
- Akito?!
Akito?!
(YELPS)
(SCREAMS)
(SOBS)
Akito?!
(SOBS, PANTS)
(WATER SPLASHES)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(SCREAMS)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS
IN BACKGROUND)
Jen, you seen the headlamps?
Hey, Jen?
Y-yeah, I'm in the bathroom.
You know where
the headlamps are?
Oh, yeah, um... they're in
the kitchen. I'm charging them.
Oh, have you seen my phone?
No. Uh, but I'll have a look
when I get out.
Well, better hurry.
They're here.
What time do you call this?
(CHUCKLES)
Ah, you said 10am.
Yeah, on the road at 10am.
It's already 10:05.
Oh. How do you live
with this guy?
I just let him think
he's in charge.
- Hi.
- Mwah.
Oh, yours.
Ah. Thanks. Where was it?
It was just on the sofa inside.
You two - smile.
- (SHUTTER CLICKS)
- Aw!
I got that torch
you told me to get.
Oh, God.
Tell him about the torch.
Took out a second mortgage
to get that thing.
120 hours of full charge.
Worth every cent.
Guys, get in. Group shot.
(SHUTTER CLICKS)
- Alright, let's hit the road.
- Nice.
ERIC: So, uh,
I read your latest article.
10 best bars in Bucharest.
Tough assignment.
Worst hangover I ever had.
You've got the cushiest job.
This might be a little tricky,
though. But it'll be worth it.
How'd you find out about it?
Oh, my mate Cash.
He runs tours out of Cairns.
Cash?
You'll see.
CASH: So, anyway, we're over
in Puerto Escondido.
I look across
and I see this crazy bastard.
He paddles into
this monster wave.
This thing was huge.
It was near vertical, right?
He gets completely wiped out.
Fucking boom!
Like, this thing explodes
on this head, right?
So I race over on the ski and I
had to haul his sorry arse out.
Oh, get off!
- I see what you mean.
- Mm-hm.
So, this cave?
Mmm.
What I can tell you is
this thing is unexplored.
Right? You won't find this
on any of your caving websites.
Yeah, see, that part doesn't
really excite me very much.
It's all good, mate.
(SIGHS) I cannot believe
I let Eric talk me into this.
You say that every time.
What is that, water?
Not pregnant, are you?
Wait. You're not?
Oh, wow! Really?
That is amazing!
Yes, but please
don't say anything, OK?
I haven't even told Viktor.
Why? He's gonna be
so excited when you tell him.
Yeah.
It's just... not something
we've ever spoken about.
- Well, surely...
- And what about you?
(CHUCKLES)
No, Eric would freak out.
You know, things have been
kind of... bad for us. Um...
Sometimes I get the feeling
he's keeping his options open.
(LAUGHS) Well, remember Simmo?
Remember that time
when he was like...
..he's coming off
the bloody pier
and he's straight into
the water?
- Simmo's bloody mad, that guy.
- (LAUGHS)
You want to dance?
Yeah? (CHUCKLES)
(LAID-BACK MUSIC PLAYS)
(INHALER PUFFS)
What?
Nothing.
Let's not do this.
Let's just go somewhere
by ourselves, huh?
Like an island.
We can sit on a beach, get
massages, order room service...
I thought you said
going into remission
meant you want to
live life to the full.
(CHUCKLES)
I do. It's just...
I mean, don't you want to
experience something new?
Eric can send me the photos
and I'll make
the experience part up.
I write most of my stuff
from the hotel anyway.
I think it's time
you experience the real thing.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
- Morning, Prince Charming.
- Morning.
Hey, don't forget,
I found this cave.
I'm going in first, alright?
Thought we were gonna
toss for it.
Toss this.
ERIC: So, how did you
find this cave?
CASH: I was in
a search party last week
looking for those missing
Japanese bushwalkers.
I was searching
through the forest
and I stumbled across
this shaft.
I shine my torch in.
This thing goes way down.
Any luck, she'll lead
to a bigger system
and, uh... we can start
making some money.
And what if it doesn't?
Well, then we'll be
back in town
in time for another party,
then, won't we?
Eric's shout.
(SHUTTER CLICKS)
Did you see that?
JEN: Oh, yeah.
Hey, are there many crocs
around here?
Yeah, a few,
now that we can't cull 'em.
Relax.
If some nasty croc thinks
he's got an easy lunch...
- Jesus!
- Whoa! What the fuck?!
What? It's not loaded!
The clip's in the glove box.
Did you ever find
those missing tourists?
(SHUTTER CLICKS)
Nah, not yet.
Yeah, this is it.
(CICADAS CHIRP NOISILY)
- So, where is it?
- It's up through there.
What do you reckon?
Yeah, it's moving south.
We'll be fine.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Welcome to Cash's Cave.
Well? What do you think?
Let's go find out.
(ERIC WHISTLES)
Looking good.
You ready, big fella?
Yeah, it's all good.
You can go first.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
You've never done this before,
have you?
Yes, course I have.
Wrong way round, mate.
Huh?
- Ready?
- Mm-hm.
So, when you're on,
it's one hand on the brake
all the way down.
Mm.
- JEN: Right, be careful.
- See you at the bottom.
Yeew!
(SIGHS)
Ready?
(SIGHS) Ready as I'll ever be.
Whew!
- You right?
- Yeah, totally.
(JEN CHUCKLES)
Whew!
(GROANS)
ERIC: That's it. Nice work,
guys. Almost there.
- (CASH GRUNTS)
- (SHUTTER CLICKS)
ERIC: Keep coming.
Nice!
Attaboy.
Nice.
Look. Over here.
What do you reckon?
Uh... what if there are
snakes in there?
Eric will get bitten first,
then, won't he?
Go.
After you.
Oh, God.
Alright.
Here we go.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(JEN GRUNTS)
Hope no-one's claustrophobic.
Probably should've asked that
before we came down here.
Mmm.
- (CLUNK!)
- Oh!
- You right?
- Yep.
Everyone OK?
Yeah.
This looks promising.
YOLANDA: I wonder
how far it goes.
What if we get lost down here?
I mean, no-one knows
we're down here, right?
I don't know.
We won't get lost.
We should keep moving.
Yep.
Come on. I've got
a good feeling about this.
(SIGHS)
Lead the way.
CASH: Oi, check this out.
- JEN: Oh!
- VIKTOR: Oh, what is that?
It looks like a...
a goat or something.
VIKTOR: So, we're not
the first ones down here, then.
How did it get down here?
(WATER TRICKLES)
Where do you reckon
that's coming from?
Just seepage.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(THUNDER CRACKS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC BUILDS)
Careful, guys.
Gets a bit tighter up here.
Whoa. You feel that?
What?
Space.
ERIC: Careful.
It's low right here, guys.
Watch your step, guys.
(GRUNTS)
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo! Yeah!
(ALL LAUGH, EXCLAIM)
ERIC: This is
what it's all about.
This makes it
a cave worth exploring.
Holy shit, man.
We are in business!
- What did I tell you?
- VIKTOR: Yep.
Well done.
- Let's check it out.
- Yeah.
Let's have a look over there.
You guys coming?
- After you.
- Come on.
Watch out for this.
- You good?
- (LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES) Cold?
Little bit.
Nah, it's not too bad.
You right? (CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Don't need me
to hold your hand?
(WATER TRICKLES)
It's just seepage, mate.
Maybe.
It's running pretty fast,
though.
Yeah. Probably
a natural waterway.
Cave river tours.
(CHUCKLES)
Oop.
Oh, shit. Thought I checked
those batteries.
YOLANDA: What happened
to the light?
VIKTOR: Oh, shit.
(WATER TRICKLES)
I don't like the look of this.
I think we should head back.
Are you serious?
Mate, this cave's
just getting started.
(CHUCKLES) A little bit of
water's not gonna hurt you.
Oi!
Inspired?
This is incredible, huh?
(WATER GURGLES)
(WATER SWISHES)
(MOVEMENT IN WATER)
Hey?
Hey! I think there's something
in the water.
What the hell is that?
- (DISTANT RUMBLING)
- CASH: I don't know.
(RUMBLING GROWS LOUDER)
(WATER ROARS)
(ALL SHRIEK, EXCLAIM)
(GASPS FOR AIR)
Jen!
JEN: Help! Help!
CASH: Grab my hand!
Grab my hand!
Jen!
YOLANDA: Viktor! Viktor!
Help!
Jen! Faster, Jen!
This way. Come on.
Are you OK?
(ERIC COUGHS)
(GROANS)
(ALL COUGH, GASP)
You're OK. You're alright.
You're alright, darling.
(GROANS)
I lost my bag.
OK. We'll find it.
(PANTS) We'd better.
Had my keys in it.
Where in the fuck did
that water come from?
It was the rain, wasn't it?
Didn't you say that we were
on the edge of the storm?
No, that's got to be
more than that.
That river must have
burst its banks.
VIKTOR: So, how are we gonna
get out of here, then?
Oh. Here.
- What? Hold on.
- Fuck!
Hold on. Hold on.
Fuck!
Does anyone have service?
There's not gonna be a signal
down here, guys.
We're gonna have to go back
the way we came in.
VIKTOR: It's gonna be
underwater.
I'm not going underwater
in this cave. I'm just not. OK?
Look. It's only
a short passage.
Once we clear that low rock,
I reckon we'll be
above the waterline.
Well, we could just wait
for the water to go down
and... and then we'll...
..we'll just swim back out
the way we came in.
- No, we can't wait.
- Why?
The cave's filling up. Look.
The water's still rising.
We're gonna be in the water
whether we like it or not.
JEN: Fuck. (WHIMPERS)
Wait. I saw something.
Before the water hit.
What?
It was over there.
I don't know.
I'm not going. I'm not going
back in the water in this cave.
Hey. Look at me.
It's only a short swim.
I'll go first
and check it out, OK?
It's gonna be fine.
Let's just stick together
and stay calm.
You right?
We need to find that backpack.
Alright? We're not going
anywhere without those keys.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What's that?
It's Cash's bag.
ERIC: This is it.
I'll go down and make sure
we can get through.
10, 15 seconds max, I reckon.
Be careful.
(VIKTOR YELPS, WATER SPLASHES)
What was that?
- Viktor?
- Where did he go?
- Viktor!
- Viktor?
Viktor!
- Viktor!
- Viktor, where are you?!
- Viktor?!
- Viktor!
(WATER THRASHES)
- Stop! Wait!
Get out of the water!
- Viktor!
- Get out of the water!
(ALL SCREAM)
- Viktor!
- (VIKTOR SCREAMS)
Viktor!
Viktor! Oh!
Get her out!
Arggh! Viktor!
Viktor!
Eric, get out of the water!
Come on! Come on!
Viktor! Viktor!
Get up! Get up!
Oh, shit! The bag!
Oh, fuck!
It's not Viktor!
VIKTOR: Fucking hell!
Viktor!
- (SCREAMS)
- Viktor!
Viktor! Get out of there!
- Get out!
- Get out of it!
- (VIKTOR SCREAMS)
- Viktor!
Viktor!
Oh! Oh, it's coming!
- It's coming!
- (ALL YELL)
Get him out of
the fucking water!
Viktor!
It's coming!
Oh!
Get up! Get up!
Run!
No, no, no!
Get up! Get up, get up, get up!
Oh! Viktor!
(ALL GASP FOR AIR)
- (GRUNTS)
- Viktor. Hey, hey.
Look at me. Look at me.
Can you talk?
- Yeah.
- OK.
Oh, God. Alright.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, shit!
Oh, God.
YOLANDA: Is he OK?!
Is he OK?!
Oh, fuck!
VIKTOR: He kept
trying to roll me.
Move back in close.
Step back.
Hey, buddy. This is gonna
really hurt, alright?
One, two, three.
- Arggh!
- Sorry. Sorry.
(JEN WHIMPERS)
You've got to sit him up.
Up you get. OK.
- I'm gonna come up the back.
- Yep.
Good thing
he spat you out, huh?
(CHUCKLES) Must've not liked
the taste of me, huh?
Good work. Good work.
VIKTOR: Thanks.
We need to get him
to a hospital.
CASH: This is one of our
missing bushwalkers.
(VIKTOR GROANS SOFTLY)
JEN: Those painkillers
should kick in soon, alright?
Cash and I will go.
What?
Cash!
We've got to swim
out of here, mate.
Did you miss something?
There's a massive fucking
crocodile in this water!
Yeah. Is your phone
still waterproof?
Yes!
OK.
So we get back to the entrance,
get a signal, call for help.
While we're at it,
we grab your gun,
come back here
and kill the bastard.
(LAUGHS)
Look, we just need
to get through there
and we'll be fine.
Oh, we'll be fine, will be?
Yeah... No!
I've got my knife.
That fucking croc comes for us,
he's gonna get it in the head.
Great.
It's bloody Crocodile Dundee.
You can't be serious.
- He needs a hospital.
- Eric.
- Jen.
- Don't be stupid.
We're all gonna be
in the water soon.
Crocs are territorial.
He's not gonna be happy
till we're all gone.
We have to try something.
CASH: Mate, this is madness!
I'm not doing it.
Nup. Nuh. Fuck you.
What?!
Eric, you cannot get
in that water.
What choice do I have?
W-wait! Wait!
Just wait a minute!
(CASH SPEAKS INAUDIBLY)
What's he saying?
Cash!
Alright!
Yeah?
Alright, this is what
we're gonna do.
We're gonna push that
out there,
and when the croc grabs it,
we go.
You got it?
That might just work.
Let's do it.
(YOLANDA GROANS)
Aaah!
(LOUD SPLASH)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Go. Whatever you do, right,
don't splash.
Careful.
They're attracted to
vibrations, OK?
Slowly! Slow!
Attaboy.
OK.
CASH: Jesus.
Oh, shit.
(TAKES SHALLOW, SHARP BREATHS)
Stick together.
(GASPS AND PANTS)
(BOTH PANT)
- You good?
- Yeah. Yeah.
(COUGHS)
Shit.
(BUBBLING)
What's that?
Just keep moving.
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC)
- Fuck!
(CASH PANTS)
- What?
- I felt something.
You sure?
Yes!
Hang on.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Let's keep moving.
(VIKTOR GROANS SOFTLY)
(VIKTOR GASPS AND GROANS)
JEN: Hey.
Here you go.
(VIKTOR STRUGGLES TO BREATHE)
- Yolanda?
- Yep?
Uh... have you got, uh,
Viktor's puffer?
- He said it's in your pack.
- Yep.
Take some deep breaths,
alright? OK?
Oh...
(SOBS) Yep.
- (VIKTOR WHEEZES)
- It's OK, buddy.
JEN: Throw it over!
Come on, Yolanda,
throw it over!
- He's suffocating!
- Yes!
(VIKTOR WHEEZES)
(SPLASH)
Fuck!
(WHEEZES)
Uh... Do you have
another one of those?
- No!
- JEN: Slow down.
- (WHEEZES)
- Hey. It's OK. It's OK.
Look at me. Look at me.
It's coming. OK?
You're gonna be just fine.
It's OK.
Hey, hey, hey... It's OK.
It's OK. It's OK.
- It's OK. It's OK.
- (VIKTOR WHEEZES)
Calm down. Calm breaths.
Calm breaths.
It's OK.
Calm down.
(GENTLE SPLASHING)
Yolanda, no!
Slowly!
Gently.
Don't splash, OK?
YOLANDA: Fuck. (PANTS)
Fuck.
Yes!
(VIKTOR WHEEZES)
(SPLASHING NEARBY)
YOLANDA: Aah!
(SIGHS)
(LOUD SPLASHING)
(YOLANDA AND JENNIFER
PANT FRANTICALLY)
Do not move.
Do not move a muscle.
(YOLANDA GASPS)
- (CRUNCHING)
- Aah!
Go!
Go. Go, go, go, go, go!
Come on.
- Come on.
- (YOLANDA GRUNTS)
Come on.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Here.
Breathe. Breathe.
- (PUFFER HISSES)
- Again.
Breathe.
(VIKTOR GASPS)
Hi. It's OK.
I'm here. I'm here.
(CRIES)
(SIGHS)
(LIGHT SPLASHING)
(BOTH PANT AND GROAN)
That hole we dropped into,
it should be
on the other side of this.
It's a bit of a swim.
Give me your phone.
Hey?
No point both of us
drowning in that crack.
If you think I'm letting you
have all the glory...
(BOTH LAUGH)
I'll see you on the other side.
- Righto.
- Yeah?
(YELLS AND GASPS)
Aah! (GASPS)
- No way through.
- How? It's...
The water... must have
moved the rocks.
(GASPS)
We've got to try to move 'em.
- Let's do it.
- OK.
(MUFFLED GROANING)
(GASPS)
Fuck!
We gotta... we gotta
go back down.
Mate, those rocks
aren't going anywhere.
We have to go back.
Come on.
Just give me a sec.
(MUFFLED THUD)
(GRUNTS REPEATEDLY)
(TRIES TO SCREAM)
(GASPS AND PANTS)
Eric?!
Fuck. Fuck...
(SOFT SPLASHING)
Eric?
(BUBBLING)
(GASPS)
(BUBBLING CONTINUES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(PANTS FRANTICALLY)
(BREATHES SLOWLY)
Aaagh!
(CRIES OUT)
Aaagh! Aaaagh!
(SCREAMS REPEATEDLY)
(SCREAMING ECHOES)
(GASPS AND PANTS)
Cash?!
Cash!
Fuck.
JEN: Water's still rising.
There's a breeze.
Hey.
It's OK. It's OK.
We're gonna get out of here.
- OK?
- (WEAKLY) Yeah.
We have to.
- Yes, boss.
- (LAUGHS)
Viktor, I'm pregnant.
- You're gonna be a dad.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna be a dad?
- I was gonna tell you... Yeah.
- I was gonna tell you.
- Yeah.
I've just been waiting
for the right time.
- I'm gonna be a daddy.
- Yeah.
(SOBS) Hey?
Hey, I found a passage.
(ERIC GASPS FOR AIR)
Look.
Here.
Oh, baby.
Where's Cash?
He, um...
What?
Oh, God.
Oh!
(SOBS) Oh. Oh, fuck.
Well, did you find a way
out of here?
No, it's blocked.
We can't get out that way.
(WATER GURGLES)
Hey, I think I found a passage.
- What?
- It's up there.
(VIKTOR COUGHS)
Hey, Jen. Where's the Ventolin?
Careful.
Hey.
It's pretty tight, but I think
I might be able to squeeze in.
- Eric?
- Hey, it's alright. I'll go.
We need to find a way
out of here.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
ERIC: This whole place is
gonna be flooded soon.
We need to get Viktor out.
We will. We will.
Eric, I'm pregnant.
Have you told Viktor?
Yeah. Just now.
Here.
That should help take
the temperature down.
(WATER GUSHES)
Oh, God.
The water's really rising.
Hey.
Do you think you can
make it up there?
(GROANS)
We've gotta move, OK?
Or we're gonna go under.
Yeah.
I think so.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
OK.
(WATER SPLASHES)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(BOTH GROAN)
OK. I got you.
JEN: Hang on.
OK, we're there.
It's OK.
(VIKTOR GROANS)
(WATER SLOSHES)
(SCREAMS)
Aarggh!
OK, that's it!
- (BOTH GRUNT)
- Come on, buddy.
Gotta get up here.
- Come on.
- (YELPS)
You have to get up here.
You can do this.
Get up!
Get up here!
Oh!
Come on.
Get up! Come on!
Come on! Arggh!
(BOTH PANT)
- (PUFFER HISSES)
- (COUGHS)
Here.
Yolanda's pregnant.
I know.
It's amazing.
I'm so happy for you guys.
We never thought
we could have kids.
After all the chemo,
I thought I was sterile.
It's incredible.
Fuck!
We're never gonna get
out of here, are we?
We will.
Of course we will.
(VIKTOR WHEEZES)
(CAMERA BEEPS, WHIRRS)
(FLICKS THROUGH PHOTOS)
(CONTINUES FLICKING
THROUGH PHOTOS)
(SIGHS)
VIKTOR: What?
What?
JEN: You're OK.
- You're OK.
- Are they back?
No.
Yolanda's so sure
of herself, isn't she?
It's funny, um...
Those two have always been
the adventurous ones
and... (CHUCKLES)
..you and I, we always just
wanted to sit by the pool.
I used to joke
with Eric that...
..maybe we should
switch partners.
He'd laugh.
Look.
The keys.
Cash's pack.
Here. Hold this.
Hey. Wait.
- Jen...
- We need them to get back.
Hey, wait. Wait.
Jen.
(GASPS)
VIKTOR: Hey.
(GRUNTS)
OK. OK. OK.
Fuck!
(WATER SPLASHES)
Jen! Jen, I think it's coming!
Jen, get out of the water!
Jen!
(YELPS)
Jen?
Jen.
Jen, can you hear me?
Oh, shit.
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
Shit. Jen.
Aarggh!
Jen.
Wake up.
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
- (JEN GROANS)
- Come on!
(WATER SLOSHES)
(JEN GROANS)
(YELLS)
(WHIMPERS)
Viktor?
Viktor! Viktor!
Come on, Viktor!
(WATER GUSHES)
(VIKTOR SCREAMS)
- (VIKTOR CONTINUES SCREAMING)
- Oh!
(SOBS)
(GRUNTS)
ERIC: Jen.
Huh?
ERIC: Jen!
JEN: I'm over here.
Shit. OK.
Um... we're gonna have to swim.
It's not far.
We'll stick together, OK?
ERIC: Hey. Are you alright?
Where's Viktor?
ERIC: Jen?
What?
He, um...
(SOBS)
Uh... you OK?
- You OK?
- (JEN SOBS)
Wait, did you... (SOBS)
Did you find a way out?
Did you get out?
No, we can't get out that way.
(JEN WHIMPERS)
JEN: Fuck!
Why did you bring us down here?
Why did you bring us here?!
Jen, just calm down.
We're gonna fucking die
down here!
Fuck, Jen, you wanted to come.
- No, I didn't!
- OK, I get it! It's my fault!
(YOLANDA WAILS)
When were you gonna tell me?
About the two of you?
- Jen, come on. What the fuck?
- I know, Eric.
Just tell me the truth.
Please just tell me the truth.
(SCOFFS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY, SOBS)
(YOLANDA SOBS)
It wasn't an affair.
Then what was it?
It was a mistake.
A mistake?
Is the baby yours?
(JEN SOBS)
(SOBS) Oh, God.
(SOBS)
Look.
Sunlight.
There must be a shaft. The
light's coming in through it.
It's a down current.
See the way the water eddies
near the wall?
So?
So... it means
the water must be
getting sucked out there
somewhere.
Like a plughole.
It could be a way out.
We don't know it's a way out.
We could get sucked down there
and drown.
Well, it's that
or wait here to get eaten.
We could get eaten
swimming over there.
JEN: Yeah?
Well, I'd rather
take my chances.
Jen...
What, Eric?
You want to stay here too
and wait to die?
(SIGHS) Oh, fuck!
(PANTS NERVOUSLY)
(WATER SLOSHES GENTLY)
(GASPS)
(YOLANDA HYPERVENTILATES)
(BREATHES NERVOUSLY)
Hey. You're OK.
You're OK. Just keep swimming.
Keep swimming.
Nice and slow. You're OK.
YOLANDA: (SIGHS) Oh, shit.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
BUILDS SLOWLY)
It's coming!
Swim! Swim!
(WHIMPERS)
ERIC: Go!
(YOLANDA YELPS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Help me!
Ah! Ah!
Come on, you bastard! Come on!
Eric!
- Go!
- (SCREAMS) Eric!
- No!
Eric! Come back here! Eric!
Eric, come back here!
Eric? (WHIMPERS)
Arggh!
(CROCODILE GROWLS)
Eric!
- Arggh!
- (GROWLING)
JEN: Eric? (WHIMPERS)
Oh!
(CROCODILE SNARLS)
(YELPS)
(BOTH COUGH, GASP)
You're OK.
(COUGHS)
(JEN COUGHS)
Eric?
Oh, fuck.
Come on. Come on.
What the fuck is this place?
(DARK MUSIC)
Ohhh!
We have to get out of here.
Which way?!
(YOLANDA WHIMPERS)
(BOTH PANT, EXCLAIM)
Look!
Is that a way out?
Go! Go!
That's it.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC SWELLS)
(YOLANDA GASPS)
(STIRRING MUSIC)
Come on!
- OK.
- Quick, quick, quick!
(GRUNTS)
Oh, God. Oh, God.
(EXCLAIMS WITH RELIEF)
Oh, God.
This is the road
we came in on, isn't it?
I think so.
(BOTH SIGH)
Jen.
I'm so sorry.
(STARTS ENGINE) Not now.
Look out!
(YOLANDA SQUEALS)
(SIGHS)
Oh, God. Fuck.
Yolanda, are you OK?
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
- We have to get out of here.
- Oh, shit!
- Come on.
- Oh! Oh, my God!
Come on. Oh, come on!
- Can you open your door?
- I can't!
Come on. (ROARS)
(GROANS)
This is where
we just came out of.
Oh, my God. (GROANS)
Oh, shit!
YOLANDA: Oh, shit!
Oh, my God! (WHIMPERS)
The gun! The gun!
Oh, my God! Get the gun!
Quick, quick, quick! Get it!
Did you find it?
We need the clip.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC SWELLS)
- Come on!
- Here you go.
- OK. It's OK.
- OK.
Where is it?
(BOTH SCREAM)
(BOTH WHIMPER)
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, shit! Oh, my God!
No! No!
(SPLUTTERS)
Yolanda!
Yolanda! Yolanda!
(SOBS) Oh, God!
(GASPS)
- Are you OK?
- (GROANS) My ankle!
Can you swim?
We gotta swim down there.
Come on!
(BOTH GRUNT)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Nearly there. (SPLUTTERS)
(GROANS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC SWELLS)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOT)
Jen!
(SCREAMS)
Jen! (PANTS)
(SOBS) Jen!
(SCREAMS)
(GUNSHOT)
YOLANDA: Jen! (SOBS)
Jen!
Jen! (SOBS)
(SPLUTTERS)
Jen!
- Jen!
- (SPLUTTERS)
YOLANDA: (PANTS) Jen!
(GASPS)
YOLANDA: (SOBS) Jen!
(BOTH SOB)
Are you OK?
Yeah.
Come on, then.
I'm sorry. I love you.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(WATER BUBBLES)