(distant phone ringing)
You do things
for your friends,
you got their backs
when they're in trouble,
or else what's
the friggin' point?
Excuse my language,
but you know what I mean.
'Cause Kevin and I,
we've been tight,
like forever.
He's like a brother
to me, you know,
it's just these boys now,
they don't grow up.
So he calls me,
and he's all like,
"I'm gonna kill myself,
and boohoo,
Shelley dumped me,
I'm no good,"
and I'm like,
take a friggin' valium.
But there's only so much
you can do over the phone,
so I can kinda tell by his voice
that he's fucked up again,
and trust me you don't want this
guy gettin' behind the wheel
drivin' over to my place.
So I'm tellin' him,
don't do anything drastic
until I get there,
and then I go over.
What this punk didn't tell me
is that he was calling me
from the balcony
of his apartment
while this party's going on.
And I walk through the door,
it's like these
friggin' characters.
I mean, the second
I walk through that door,
I'm like, "Katrina,
this is no good."
But then they tell me that
he's holed up in the bathroom,
so I go in, you know?
I know the rules,
I didn't see nothin'.
Like out on the table, no
paraphernalia that I recognized.
There was loud music
and low-lives layin' around
all over the place.
And trust me, Kevin
didn't tell me the part
where Shelley dumped him because
he's dealing crank again.
She can't take it.
If I would've gotten there
five minutes earlier,
I would've said my piece,
and I would've been gone.
And if I would've gotten there
five minutes later,
I would've seen the squad cars,
and I woulda kept on drivin'.
You know?
You're not gonna really write me
up for five minutes, are you?
You violated your parole.
-I know, but I wasn't...
-On the premises
with a convicted felon,
controlled substances.
I wasn't doing anything.
Your hearing will be
at 11 o'clock on Wednesday.
Don't be late.
I've been clean,
I've been sober.
I've been
like a friggin' nun.
Well, you let them know that
at your hearing.
Ugh.
You will hear about
five or six of those a day.
She reminds me
of this girl
who moved into
my mother's neighborhood.
Like, right off
there's this parade
of nasty-looking
boyfriends.
(phone ringing)
'Scuse me.
Hello.
Yeah, just for a minute.
Was he there?
What about the truck?
Okay, let's keep trying.
Excuse me.
Now my mother is afraid
to leave her apartment.
There's a balance
you have to find.
Guiding your clients
towards rehabilitation,
but always keeping in mind
the welfare of the public.
The non-criminals.
Yeah, I'll take
the next one.
Re-assignment,
Fontayne Scott.
Scott!
They told me
Delmarco's gone.
Your supervisor retired,
I'll be taking over your case.
You have a drip.
You are Fontayne Scott.
Maiden name Gamble.
Well, that's all I got.
(toilet flushing)
Come with me.
Cindy, take this
sample downstairs,
then go to Caplan's
and get us some lunch.
We're eating in?
Um, ham and cheese on sourdough,
Russian dressing, no pickle.
I'll eat your pickle.
Yeah, okay fine,
and Dr. Brown's Cream soda.
Got it.
Take a seat.
-So, Bernice.
-Past acquaintance
between officer and client
is prohibited,
so after today,
you'll have to be re-assigned.
But for now,
you violated your parole.
Marvela come into the diner,
I hadn't seen her
in some time,
we gots to talkin', she offered
to carry me home on the ride,
that's all.
Marvela who has two
warrants for her arrest.
-I didn't know that.
-Marvela who was driving
without a valid
driver's license.
A friend offer you a ride, you
don't ask to see no picture I.D.
If I was in danger
of returning to prison,
I wouldn't want
to take any chances.
I didn't know.
You went to two bars
before you were picked up.
I had club soda.
Both bars are known to be venues
for narcotics transactions.
You see where I live,
there ain't nothin' but that.
So how you been, Bernice?
All right, I guess.
Got this job.
Yeah.
Married?
Was.
Kids?
I had a son, he's a--
he was a soldier in
Operation Enduring Freedom.
Wow, grown up that much, huh?
Mm-hm.
How you been?
You can read my jacket.
It's too long.
Look,
I fucked up.
Marvela, I know she ain't who
I'm supposed to be hangin' with,
but...
...where I live everybody
got some kind of record,
everybody likely to be carryin'
something they shouldn't be.
I got to feel alive sometimes,
otherwise what's the point
in being out?
I can't do no more time,
damn it.
I already let enough
of my life slip by.
Must be fun, huh?
Sitting here,
play God on people.
This sorry girl ain't
got her shit together,
we're gonna have to lock
her ass up some more.
You can go.
I'm not recommending
a hearing.
My record?
I'll write it up
so it won't be a problem.
Is your sample okay?
Nothin' in it
but orange juice.
They squeeze their own
at the diner.
Just be more careful
in the future.
For old time's sake, huh?
(phone ringing)
If you ever need anything...
If I can ever do anything
for you, anything...
Right, like I got anything
to do with your world.
Thank you, Bernice,
for real.
Parole Agent Stokes.
You kept your married name?
Look, it would be better
in here if you just--
Parole Agent Stokes then.
Hey.
Any news on Rodney?
You did?
What's his?
Fuzzy.
That's his real name?
Address?
♪
Sorry that took so long.
No problem.
Really tricky case.
You're a public defender,
what could be tricky?
This kid might be innocent.
At least of the thing
he's been accused of.
Like I said, innocent.
You are a soft touch.
Sure.
Where do you wanna eat?
It doesn't matter,
or we could go to your place,
and I could throw
something together.
Listen, Bernice.
What?
Who is she?
Whoa. how'd we get from
where do you wanna eat
to who is she?
I listen to people sugarcoat
their bullshit all day,
Dez, so.
-So do I.
-Then we both know
where this is going,
so.
Who is she?
My wife.
I don't know if that makes me
feel better or worse.
I never heard one good
thing about the woman.
-From me.
-From you!
We got kids.
You can see 'em
whenever you want to.
-We started this--
-Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
you read me the warnings.
It's not an easy
decision to make.
It better
goddamn not be.
Your wife?
The things
you've told me.
The idea is that
it'd be different.
You okay?
No!
(laughing)
That's exactly what
she would be doing.
(laughing)
That's what I'm talkin' bout.
Nah, nah, nah, nah.
Yo yo, Fontayne, Fontayne,
what's up, Mama?
Look at you walkin' around
on two legs out in the world.
C'mon over here, girl.
-Hey, Wiley.
-Hey, what's up, baby?
Come here, hey, you know
I got what you need, right?
Come on over here.
No, no, not tonight.
Come on over here, baby.
Let me talk to you,
let me talk to you a sec.
Rodney,
it's your mother.
♪
You there, Rodney?
I'm worried about you.
♪
Just call, you know,
I don't--I don't care what...
♪
Just call me, okay?
Love you.
♪
Back up.
(police dispatch)
Move back, folks.
That's it,
back up.
Back up.
On this side of the tape.
Hey, Vick.
-Hey, Bernice.
-What's up?
Oh, the usual, somebody
got in over their head
and they got it
blown off.
I.D.?
The late Fuzzy Niles.
The only victim?
They killed his pitbull, too.
(laughs)
What are you doin' here?
Oh, a client
in the neighborhood.
At this hour?
Get a life, girl.
So, um, what
was he into, Fuzzy?
Nothing good.
♪
(indistinct chatter)
Here ya go, babe.
Where'd you
learn to cook?
In County, first visit.
I could scramble
50 eggs at a time.
You comin'
to check up on me?
When you get off of work?
Four.
Somethin's come up.
I'll be back then.
Oh,
it's you.
You haven't been to work
since last Friday.
I've been sick.
Oh, symptoms?
I have a fever.
Hm, well, let's see
about that.
What's minimum
wage nowadays?
Eight dollars an hour
or some shit like that?
You ain't makin' no tips
scrapin' that grill.
You want somethin'?
No, just to see
an old friend.
I was never friends
with with you, Wiley.
Customer, associate?
It hurts me, it hurts me
to see a woman like you
in here slavin' away
for nothin' like this.
You'll survive.
You ain't feelin' so good,
I can tell.
I've felt worse.
Yeah, but you've felt a whole
lot better before, haven't you?
Whole lot better.
I'm done with that.
Really?
Ain't much to look forward to
when you get up in the mornin',
then, is there?
Every day I wake up,
I look forward to a day
where I don't see you.
Now you just
hurt my feelings, girl.
And I was just gonna ask you
to come partner with me again.
Same deal we had
before, you know,
you help me move my product,
you get a discount.
If you ain't
gonna order no food,
then you need to move your
narrow ass up off a that stool.
You ain't feelin'
well at all.
Snappish.
Hey, you know
where to find me.
She know where
to find me.
How's that burger?
Bernice.
Bernice!
Detective Mueller.
Right, you were
the arresting officer--
Naomi Prosser,
both times.
Is she in trouble?
I've moved over
to robbery/homicide.
Oh.
You know a character
named Fuzzy Niles?
I walked into
his wake last night.
He's a friend
of your son, Rodney.
He is?
And we'd like to
talk to Rodney,
but, um, we don't
have an address.
Well, when you get one,
you let me know.
My own son is, like,
in witness protection.
Really?
No address, no number
that works anymore.
You know, Rodney, he's--
he's got his own life now,
and apparently I'm not
a part of it.
He's a suspect.
In the murder?
You let us know
if you hear from him.
You know it's
the right thing to do.
♪
So?
I'll do what I can,
but some of the people
I gotta talk to,
that's in violation
of my parole.
Not--not if you inform
your parole officer,
and get approval.
I'm your parole officer.
I thought you was
gonna re-assign me.
I'm your parole officer.
Right.
♪
I don't think that landlord
believed I'm anybody's aunt.
Yeah, well, at least
he gave us the key.
You ever been in here?
He never invited me.
Nope.
Still doesn't
clean his room.
You know, that
was the big battle.
He claimed there was a
constitutional right to privacy,
and I'd threaten to call
the sanitation department.
My room don't look much neater.
I mean, he got nicer
stuff than me, but...
He used to love the Clippers
when he was little,
you know,
the basketball team?
Had all their posters
all over the wall.
Kinda loser team
most years.
At least the tickets
were easy to get.
You sure you wanna
be doing this?
Well, if I'm gonna find him,
I gotta know him.
Better than I do
lately, anyway.
You know, there
used to be a time
where I could tell
how his day had been
by the way he opened up
the refrigerator door
when he came home
from school.
It's just a little hash,
no big deal.
Yes it is.
Man, he got all the toys.
Yeah, when he was little
he had me get him Roadblock.
Who that?
G.I. Joe's black buddy.
And all the machine guns,
and whatnot.
Did he read comic books
back then?
I never bought 'em for him,
but he had 'em around.
All right,
let's see if I can
get into his messages.
I bet this is one of them
that can turn everything
in the house on.
Change the channel,
change the temperature.
You know, inside the joint
they got, like,
everybody's old throw-away
computers and shit,
and no walk-around telephones.
When you get out,
you're like years behind.
(loud computer alarm)
Turn it off,
Turn it off!
Leave the area immediately.
Okay.
So much for reading his mail.
You know, we can't
leave this place like this.
I ain't doin' no dishes.
I mean, in case the police,
you know, if it goes that far.
Oh, damn, he's growin'
some shit in here.
(grinding)
He ain't gonna
thank you for that.
Well, that's just too bad.
You know, find a bag,
and put the computer in it.
I'm gonna go upstairs and check
the pockets of his clothes.
You know his
mail hutch outside?
It was all crammed full.
I'll find something
to jack it open with.
Coulda had a life
in crime, Bernice.
♪
Ain't none of this what
I'm supposed to be doing.
My parole agreement.
It's all right
if you're with me.
Yeah, that's how I used to
figure it back in school, too.
Can't be doing nothin' wrong,
Bernice is here.
Hi, can I speak
to detective Mueller?
Tell him it's Bernice Stokes.
You ain't supposed
to talk on the phone
while you drive either.
Hi, Detective Mueller?
Yeah, I, um, I found
Rodney's address for you.
Yes, I--I stopped by there
with a friend, but he wasn't in.
Of course I didn't
take anything.
What would I want
of Rodney's?
♪
This a new bitch?
Hello, Dixon.
Look at you,
all dyked out and shit.
(laughing)
You like pussy, Dixon?
You know I do.
Well, that's one thing
we got in common.
-Vernell in?
-Vernell don't wanna see you.
Well, he gonna have to,
sooner or later.
All this nice shit
going to waste.
Damn.
It ain't a crime.
I'm not saying anything.
-When did you?
-I started comin' to jail.
'Cause at school that just...
Yeah, I was cuttin' up
with them boys.
-So?
-So,
boys turn
into men, sorta.
And men ain't never
done me no good.
What's the problem,
Fontayne?
No problem,
just need to talk.
Oh.
This is Bernice.
So talk.
I'm lookin' for Fuzzy Niles.
That boy got popped
last night.
You ain't into
that shit, are you?
What shit?
The shit that
Fuzzy was up to.
Who he been hangin' with?
So why you wanna know?
Cause the mothafucka'
owes me money,
and not no little bit
of it either,
so if he's not here,
then I mean
to get it from his boys.
A little Mexican cat
by the name of Juan Calles,
and some black boy
they called the Rod,
used to be in the Marines
and some shit.
Where they hang?
Last I heard, they went
down to the border.
Damn.
Yeah.
Is Juan your Mexican, Mexican?
He's from Oxnard.
Fuzzy die natural?
What you think?
Do you know
who did him?
I don't know, somebody that
got tired of his bullshit,
like I'm getting
tired of yours.
Could've been one of those
two buddies of his.
The border, huh?
Unless they took a million
dollars of your money,
and you got an army
to get it back,
I would forget
about those boys.
Nice meeting you, Bernice.
You were married
to that guy for three years?
It's on my sheet.
So what's up with that?
Yo wanna keep
up with this?
Of course!
You know what
your son been up to?
Not really.
-He was a marine?
-No, no, just infantry.
You know, transport unit.
He got out, he bought
a truck a year ago,
and he just started
hauling stuff.
Stuff.
He doesn't talk to me so much
once he got out of the service.
I--I don't really know
what he's been doin'.
You really wanna
find out?
I want him back.
Okay, they've been hangin'
down on the border,
I maybe know somebody
in San Diego.
I'm gonna need you to sign off
if I leave the county.
Don't worry about it.
-It's almost seven.
-What's at seven?
I see some familiar faces
here today, welcome.
Some new faces, welcome.
Um, Fontayne, haven't heard
from you in a while,
why don't you
get us started?
I'm Fontayne Gamble,
and I'm a drug addict.
-Hello, Fontayne.
Fontayne,
who's your friend?
Um, hi,
I'm Bernice Stokes,
I'm not an alcoholic
or a drug addict or anything,
a parole officer.
I had her once,
she's a real ball-buster.
(laughter)
The more you do,
the longer you do it,
the less "you"
there is left,
and maybe that's what
you want at first.
You know, get rid of that person
you don't like so much,
you just become a habit,
a hole that needs fillin',
and you desperate, but
you wanna be desperate, right?
'Cause that excuses
everything, you know,
everything you about to do,
everything you ever done.
When I was in County this
last time, waitin' for trial,
I couldn't score
but once or twice a week,
that low-quality shit.
Then you just
stuck with yourself.
Stuck.
I don't know, um...
I guess I'm not
ready to die yet.
I've had lots of clients
go through the program,
and for some of them
it really worked.
Clients.
It's a term
they encourage us to use.
Hollywood agents have clients.
They get 10 percent.
Maybe I'm underpaid.
Bernice, you don't want
no part of my life.
Yo.
Yo!
We're lookin' for Juan Calles.
We look anything like cops?
That's been nailed shut.
Well, you can't beat the rent,
right?
(dog barking)
Look, I don't care
if I am with you,
I ain't breakin' in here.
I'm gonna check around back
and call you if it's open.
Whatever--
playin' Buffy the fuckin'
Vampire Slayer here.
Fontayne!
It's open!
(door creaking)
♪
(bottles rattling)
(light switch clicking)
♪
Doubtin' anybody live here.
(screams)
(bottles rattling)
What the fuck you doin' here?
-Juan Calles?
-What about him?
Nothin', I'm looking for him,
and my son.
-What about your son?
-Rodney.
-Rodney Stokes.
-Freeze, little man.
I'm Detective Gamble
of the L.A.P.D.,
and I will blow
that mess you got for brains
right across this room.
Now drop it.
Very slowly now,
you gon' get up off the lady,
and bend yourself
over this stove here.
Spread your legs wide--
I don't know what you need
a razor for,
you don't even shave yet.
-I ain't done nothin'.
-You didn't visit
Fuzzy Niles last night?
-I don't even know who that is.
-Why're you in here?
Lookin' for Juan Calles,
just like you.
Why?
I want a lawyer.
What's in this?
♪
You're gonna tell me
what this is.
I'm gonna blow your head off,
right now.
I'm as serious as cancer,
little man, tell me.
All I know is Calles
and the other two
fucked up
down at the border--
I was supposed to give 'em this,
that's all.
Who, where they at?
T.J., maybe, Mexicali.
-How we find him?
-You don't, they find you.
Some Chinese guy
gave me this envelope
and sent me here
to deliver it.
-A Chinese guy?
-From the old country.
Look, I swear I'd tell you more
if I knew it.
(distant siren wailing)
All right, little man,
I'mma cut you a break.
If you can disappear
before my backup gets here,
I won't run you in.
Think you can do dat?
I'm gone.
Stay that way.
Where'd you get a gun?
I always carry a .45.
(distant siren wailing)
You goin' to the police
with this?
And once Willis made detective,
I thought, you know,
he'd relax a bit.
But he put even more hours
on the job,
came home tight,
like if you'd touch him,
he'd explode.
He okay with your boy?
He was kinda like,
"Yes, sir, no, sir."
But Rodney,
he lived to please that man.
And you split up.
No, he died.
Oh.
Cerebral hemorrhage.
His partner found him
sitting behind the wheel
in the lot
of Rampart Station.
His coffee was still warm.
So you raised him up yourself,
Rodney.
I guess.
I mean, I wanted him
to go to college,
but he got that army idea
in his head.
Yeah, the uniform.
You know, he wanted me to sign
for him when he turned 17,
said he wanted to be
a part of something
bigger than himself.
Of course, I wouldn't.
He had to wait six months.
Barely got two civil words
out of him all that time.
He was never in trouble before?
With the law?
God, no.
I'd go 10 miles
over the speed limit,
he'd be all over me.
Hm.
I'm trying to remember
why we fell out.
In high school.
Carlos Washington.
Nah.
You stole my boyfriend.
I didn't steal him.
He came after me.
But you didn't walk away,
did you?
I was jealous of you.
Oh, yeah, right.
You had both your parents.
When I came over,
they'd be so nice,
nobody screamin'.
I just wanted
to stay there forever.
We were so tight.
People always said
we could go for sisters.
Your boy ever been married?
Engaged.
Then he went over
and they talked on the computer.
She sent him cookies.
They broke up
a week after he got back.
He wasn't angry like his dad,
but moody.
And I just wanted him
to go back to school,
you know,
get his degree.
And he bought that truck.
(engine revving)
That's the husband.
I don't want
to step on her thing here.
Okay.
Chula!
Chula.
Can we talk?
In the park up ahead,
can't miss it.
How'd you get to be friends?
Not friends,
we were together inside.
It's, you know,
its own world in there.
Now she got a baby.
Who's this?
Orfeo.
It's Spanish for "Orpheus."
Damn.
It was Ricky's
grandfather's name.
Some kind of superhero
in Ancient Greece.
He went down to Hell
after his wife.
And before that,
saved all the sailors
from the sirens.
Which is like mermaids?
They were beautiful women
who would sing.
And make you smash up
on the rocks.
He doesn't know, Ricky.
Anything?
He knows I was in the Locos.
But he doesn't know I did time.
You gonna tell him?
Maybe.
This is Bernice.
Her son's gotten into some mess
on the other side.
We could use some help.
That's not my world.
It's over the line.
You know anybody who could help?
I'll have to leave Orfeo
with my cousin.
Detective Suarez?
This looks like trouble.
I don't need any trouble.
These people need
to talk to you.
Not at my house, they don't.
(speaking in Spanish)
Gracias, Leslie.
Gotta watch my cholesterol.
So.
I want him back.
And if there's any way,
I don't want him to go to jail.
This is Juan Calles.
Now, you must still have friends
on the local force.
No.
There was a federal sting.
My voice is on the tapes.
I didn't take any money, but...
you gotta be careful
who you do favors for.
Charges?
I had to resign,
lost my pension.
I have money.
The first one
is to look into it,
should take me
a day or two to find out
if there's anything I can do.
The second one is a bonus,
if I find him.
Dead or alive.
Look, I don't have that much.
You know, maybe I could
put together half,
and then pay you
the rest over time.
Two thousand up front then,
cash.
We used to call him
"The Terminator."
Like the movie.
How you been, pequeña?
That's my baby.
Huh.
Your man got a job?
Husband.
He's a plumber.
He need an assistant?
Jesus.
Not here.
I'm supposed to be retired.
♪
Chula.
You're doin' good.
Yeah.
Makes our life in prison
seem like a dream.
More like a nightmare.
Like a dream for me.
A nice one.
Take care of yourself, Fontayne.
150, 250,
350, 450, 550,
650, 750, 850.
Two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten,
eleven, twelve.
Get a money order
for this tomorrow.
Go to the office
and pay the property taxes.
This isn't dangerous, is it?
Of course not.
Well, if it's not dangerous,
why did they pay you
so much money?
Because of my years
of expertise.
It's not illegal?
It's no big deal, really.
It's just a missing person
kind of thing.
Do you have your pills?
I do all the leg work,
you'll do all the driving.
What, they took away
your license, too?
I flunked the eye exam.
I got macular degeneration.
I'm like a blur to you?
I do all right.
At the corner make a right.
(engine revving)
(door buzzing)
Hey, Freddy.
I like your posse.
Who is that guy, Tony Orlando?
You still got my package?
Gettin' back in the saddle?
Somethin' like that.
My sister been married
to a police, 40 years.
She had to have a screw loose.
I ain't a cop no more.
Oh, yes, you are.
You look like one.
You smell like one.
Juan Calles.
I better tell Ynez
to get started
on the funeral arrangements.
Has he been around?
Not lately.
Since when, not lately?
About two weeks.
Might have passed over
into T.J.
He stay there?
If he came back,
I didn't see him.
I need to fill this.
Shame Ynez won't qualify
for the widow's benefits.
I understand this has been
compromising for you,
and I appreciate it.
I'll put you on the bus
in the morning.
What do you mean?
You done what I needed.
Hooked me up, so--
This ain't over.
What can you do down here?
What can you do?
You ever been a cop
on the street?
No, I went straight
to corrections
from youth counseling.
Then I ain't leavin' you alone
down here.
I'm not alone,
I'm with Suarez.
Blind old cop,
been tossed off the force.
If you don't go back,
you'll lose your job.
My parole officer will give me
another one.
One where I don't smell
like bacon all the time.
Jobs are hard to come by.
Tell me about it.
What would you do,
if you could do
anything you wanted?
-You remember.
-What?
We were gonna be stewardesses.
Right.
In Hawaii.
You're down from Oakland,
you're Rubin James Zoletti.
Rubin James.
Who's in San Quentin.
Got it.
I don't like her taking chances.
She's a big girl.
I'm the one in law enforcement.
You ever buy drugs
on the street?
No.
Turn here.
She's gonna do fine.
Pull over.
We'll wait.
So you did somebody a favor?
Another cop.
He was my best friend.
He was doing something
that he shouldn't have,
and I looked the other way.
If you'd done the other thing,
you'd have turned him in,
how you think
you'd feel about it?
I'll never know, will I?
I got a date with Tenoch.
You Tenoch?
Wassup?
Your boy Fito put me onto you.
Pull your shirt up.
Now the arms.
Those look old.
This ain't for me.
Whatever, how much you want?
A finger of the black eagle.
Two grand.
You're dreamin'.
Dreamin'?
You know,
my regular customers get it
for a little over half of that.
But you're no regular customer,
are you?
Well, nice knowin' you.
Hold on, hold on.
What's your hurry?
I ain't got time to fuck around.
Sit down.
You know, it's nice to have
somebody from the old school
drop by.
These days,
these days, you gotta have
a fuckin' graduate degree
to stay in business.
You know, flunitrazepam,
hydroxybutyrate, M.D.M.A.
-College boy drugs.
-Yeah.
Yeah, but heroin?
Shit, that's vintage, sister.
All right.
I'll hook you up.
A finger for a grand and a half.
1,200.
See, now you're just
pissin' me off.
What the fuck.
Let's do it.
All right, follow me.
Scoot over.
Oh, get the fuck outta here,
man.
Move it.
You know, I ain't got shit--
I ain't got shit.
I'm Agent Suarez,
Drug Enforcement Agency.
This is Detective Gamble,
San Diego P.D.
And the lady holding the latest
in surveillance technology
is my colleague,
Agent Parmoli.
All you got is talk.
Officer Gamble,
did you receive anything
from the suspect?
He gave me this.
This looks like exhibit A to me,
Tenoch.
Y'all can't do this shit, man.
You can't do this,
this ain't fuckin' Mexico.
You have three law enforcement
officers as witnesses.
We have a recorded conversation.
And after we have this substance
analyzed back at the--
Motherfuckers, man.
You motherfuckers.
There is another way
to handle this.
Nah, no, no, no.
Nah, I ain't no snitch.
What?
Juan Calles.
What about him?
He's gone.
Make him come back.
What is this thing, really?
Guitar tuner.
It hooks onto the neck.
♪
You play?
My father crossed illegally
in 1950s.
He followed the crops.
He sold melons
on the side of the road.
He saved till he had enough
to bring us all up here.
And he would say to me,
"You're an American now.
Act like one."
So I started
a rock and roll band.
♪
Freddy and the Debonairs.
(cell phone vibrating)
Suarez.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll meet you there.
Juan Calles.
He wants to surrender to me.
♪
So we've been runnin'
yellow fish,
mainly Fujian.
The Snakeheads get them
into Belize.
They get 'em over the Rio
and on to Mexico and then--
then all the way over
to Sonora
on the Arizona border.
The Coyotes walk 'em over,
and then we load 'em in a truck
and haul 'em up to Tucson
or Phoenix
or L.A.,
and then they're on their own.
Lucrative?
Some of these people pay 50
grand to get into the country.
Yeah, we get a piece of that.
You get a truckload
of 30-40 Chinese,
that's a lot of feria.
But somebody stuffed up.
Pinche Fuzzy
was doing some side business
when we were partying in T.J.,
and he gets busted
by the Federales.
You know those Mexican jails,
man.
So he told the story.
Yeah, and they let him walk.
But he didn't let
me and the Rod in on it.
There was big bust in Nogales,
and the Snakeheads
get hauled in,
the paying customers.
And Rodney's still in T.J.
with this new girlfriend.
So that's who gets snatched
by the Chinos.
You hear from them?
They sent me his ear, man.
Oh, Jesus.
And then they came back up
and they got Fuzzy.
How much they want?
A hundred grand.
They think all Americans
are rich,
even Morenos,
no offense.
Underground,
that's crazy.
So you're gonna put me
in protective custody, right?
You know anybody in Albuquerque?
No.
One, two, three,
four, five,
six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, good.
Here's 500 cash.
Tomorrow you buy a ticket
to Albuquerque.
Why's that?
Not too many Chinos.
Fuck, dude.
500?
Cutbacks, homes.
The fat times are over.
I gotta get a drink.
Be careful crossing the highway.
You'll cover expenses.
I don't have any 100,000.
That's only the opening figure.
They like to haggle
a little
to see
if you're really serious.
What's next?
We go to T.J.
You're leavin' the U.S.A.?
Look, I'll write you up
some paperwork, just in case.
That won't be a problem,
will it?
Me crossing with you two.
We gotta take some pictures.
♪
From this point on,
they got cameras on you,
looking for
suspicious characters.
That'd be us.
We gotta look relaxed.
Like we're on a holiday.
Sing something.
Fontayne sings.
Throw it down, girl,
and smile.
What?
Sing.
♪ Just a closer walk with thee ♪
Louder.
♪ Grant us, Jesus,
if you please ♪
Tempo, bring it up.
♪ Really walking close to thee ♪
♪ Next to thee, dear lord,
next to thee ♪
That's it, tempo.
♪ I am weak,
but thou are strong ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ As I walked down the river ♪
(laughing)
Morning.
Good morning.
Identification, please.
How long do you plan
on staying in Mexico?
Two days.
Purpose of your trip?
We're playing a party
for a friend's wedding.
Freddy Suarez, Ocean.
These two are Ocean.
Señora,
can you please open the case?
A Rickenbacker 360.
Single-coil pickups.
Original.
Have a nice wedding.
Thank you.
♪
I ain't never been
out the country before.
I went to Puerto Rico once.
With your husband?
Before Rodney.
You like it?
Layin' on the beach next
to a good-lookin' man, shoot.
Know the place, huh?
I was supposed to come down here
and lay low for a while,
but I got my ass incarcerated.
Did you find
what you was lookin' for?
I got a good idea
where to start.
Make that two.
So you got connections
with the local police?
Maybe.
But the police
don't run this town.
Put your purse under the table
and open it.
I'm gonna place my pistol in it.
You want me to hold it?
For the moment, yeah.
I got a feelin'.
Border towns.
Really good people here.
But you also get
the worst of both sides.
Have relatives here?
T.J.?
No.
I'm a pocho down
for holiday.
It's too hot.
I need something here.
I barely speak the language.
Mexican different down here?
This isn't Mexico.
This is like a theme park...
for bad behavior.
Gracias.
Gracias, señor.
Here you go.
You should get one of these.
What is it?
Juan Soldado.
Patron saint
of illegal border crossers,
soldiers who have been
betrayed by their superiors.
Just give her five bucks.
Can I say prayers to it?
You can.
To really do it,
just light a candle
and make a wish.
What do we do now?
All right.
You go back to the hotel.
I'm gonna go around town and
spread the word a little bit.
That's all?
Should be enough.
Hasta luego,
señoras.
You talk Spanish?
I took a course for the job,
but I'm lousy at it.
Now which way's
the damn hotel?
(whistling)
(door creaking)
(crowd chattering)
(speaking Chinese)
Mother Han.
Among other languages.
Yes.
What is it you want to buy?
A young black man.
You're the wrong century
and the wrong country,
my friend.
Buy is not the right word.
More like an exchange.
I saw images of the dead.
I saw articles
of veneration,
and to those who believe,
I saw miracles.
But I do not deal
in human beings.
Not even to move them
from one place to another?
You have me mistaken
for somebody else.
Well, then...
if somebody were
in Tijuana,
wanted to find a person
being held up for trade,
where would he go?
Some of my customers
have prayed to El Santo
and reported wonderful results.
You know all the vendors.
Any of them want to unload
an African American male
by the name
of Rodney Stokes,
I'm at the Estrella
de Bajo Hotel.
Rodney started playing
football.
I wanted him to...
to try soccer,
but he said it was
for pussies.
The very first game
I went to,
you know, the play
where they...
they--they run at each other?
Kickoff?
He ran snap
into this other kid
and got knocked unconscious.
And he just...
flat.
And I ran out,
and they had...
got his helmet off,
but there was only
the guy that, you know,
wraps the tape
around their ankles.
So I...
I got down on my knees,
and I--I...
pulled that, um...
that plastic thing
that protects the teeth out,
and I...
started mouth to mouth.
He wasn't breathing?
He was cold.
And there was steam
coming out of the mouths
of all the other players.
And there was nothing
from Rodney.
You saved his life.
I don't know,
maybe.
I mean, he was just...
He took a lot of shit later...
from his friends,
you know?
French kissing his mama.
Sounds right.
At the time,
you know, I thought he'd
rather die
than be embarrassed like that.
You can't protect him
forever, Bernice.
You can try.
You hook up with somebody else,
after your husband passed?
Not for long.
I mean, when you get older,
you just--you get...
Standards?
(laughing)
Yeah.
Not highest, maybe,
but, you know...
take all that mess
you did when you were
in your 20s.
You?
I don't know.
I don't think
I'm even a dyke.
Not a real one.
Now when you're inside...
locked up...
you're in a situation, right?
That Chula?
Man, I ain't never been
more in love than I was
with that girl.
Nice pair of cheerleaders.
(laughing)
Uh-oh.
You're up, you're up,
and when you're down,
you're down.
And when you're up
against Fremont...
(laughing)
...you're up!
Pivot, side, down.
(laughing)
The red and the green.
I'll go back and live
in that world again
in a heartbeat.
You know, he probably out
buyin' rounds
for his amigos
on your money.
What if he don't come back?
Maybe your friend
overestimated Freddy.
He hasn't been
on the force for a while.
That blind detective shit
ain't too bad, either.
I don't think he handin'
out any refunds.
I'mma try somethin'.
What's that?
This is Rodney's phone bill.
There's a long distance number
he calls almost every day.
Talks at least 15 minutes.
And it's the same
area code
from this area.
You got a story ready?
(ringing)
Hola.
...Rodney Stokes.
Oh, you speak English.
Who?
Okay.
Zeidy, listen.
I am Rodney's mother.
And I am here
in Tijuana.
Where are you?
Club Macondo.
Calle...
"Pi-ya Wella."
Right, okay.
Okay, listen,
so, I'm--I'm on my way,
and you won't have
any problem recognizing me.
No.
Sweetie, you and I
have to talk.
So, I'm on my way.
Okay.
Rodney got himself a girl.
Yeah.
Club Macondo.
Let's go.
Well, what about Freddy?
You know what?
He can wait for us
for once.
I'll bring the map.
♪
(yelling)
Ms. Stokes?
Yeah, that's me.
This is Rodney's aunt.
Hello.
So, what goes on in there?
A little bit of everything.
I only serve drinks
to the men.
Is that where
you met Rodney?
Yes.
Maybe...
six month ago.
And when was the last
time you saw him?
Last week.
He stays with me
for the night.
You know what he been doin'?
How he been makin' money?
He helps people
to go north.
He helps?
They pay money.
Well, do you know how
we can contact these people
he's been workin' for?
Los Chinos?
The Chinese.
No.
You don't wanna
talk to them.
You don't want to meet them.
Oh no, yes we do!
You know, they have him.
Have him?
Kidnapped,
holdin' him for ransom.
Do you know
if he's still alive?
Is he alive?
As far as we can tell.
He's alive.
I don't--I don't
like what he's been doing
with this--this thing.
He's--but he's a man,
you know?
He has his ways
and his ideas.
So long hombre.
So these people that
he works for,
do you think that--
Maybe, mi--mi primo.
Maybe we can ask my primo.
Your cousin?
My cousin, yes.
Nestor from Mexicali.
I'll write it down for you.
Does your cousin
know these people?
Yes.
He knows the...
he has chicken
for the battle.
Cock fighting.
Yes.
The Chinese, they all come
and bet their money
to the fight,
to the battle.
It's Mexicali,
it's not very far from here.
It's another city.
(speaking Spanish)
Un momento.
I was gonna meet with him
after work.
We was gonna go
to Ensenada.
But he never comes.
Do you know his friends?
His American friends?
Juan Calles,
and this other people,
cómo se llama,
Fuzzy.
Fuzzy Niles.
I don't like him.
He's not good.
He have Mexican friends?
Not really.
But a guy he makes
business with.
What's the name?
But that one is
very peligroso.
He's muy dangerous.
What's the name?
Who is he?
Rufo.
He lives over there.
Sometimes he stays there.
Rodney make you any promises?
Uh...
you have a good son.
He's a very good son,
your son.
Would you tell me
if you find him?
(laughing)
(beeping)
Which one of you is Rufo?
Yo.
You speak English?
It's my second language.
Can I speak with you
alone for a minute?
(speaking Spanish)
What you want with me?
You know Rodney Stokes?
Oh, Rod?
That's what I call him, yeah.
What are you,
his mommy?
That's right.
(laughing)
He's been a naughty boy.
You know where he is?
That depends.
Depends on what?
How bad you want
to find out.
So, we're talking money.
That is my first language.
Hey, lady.
You like what you see?
You mean you two,
or the titty books?
You got a card?
A card?
A money card.
Cómo se dice?
ATM.
ATM card.
I ain't got nothin' like that.
All Americans
got a card.
Not the ones that can't
get credit.
Maybe we take you
to a machine,
and you show me how
to use that card.
Dream on.
Maybe you got
it in a pocket.
Back off--
Hey, don't you push
me, moronita.
Hey!
Move away from her.
You don't come here
and be telling us what to do.
I said to move the fuck
away from her!
Whoa, Bernice.
Now, you really fucked
up, lady.
Do you know who I am?
Policía municipal.
I don't see a uniform.
Now you're gonna
hand me that pistol.
(shot firing)
Oh, shit!
(grunting)
You wanna piece of this?
Don't shoot!
Move.
I coulda handled them.
Let's go.
(grunting)
Juan Gabriel.
So...
ex-detective Suarez.
What can I do for you?
Chinese that are crossing
from here.
Not my people.
But you know them.
They pay a little mordida.
Permission to do
business in my territory.
Of course,
they lie.
Pinche Chinos.
They always make more
than twice what they admit to.
They have an American.
So?
They're cutting pieces
off of him every day.
Pretty soon,
there'll be nothing left.
I need you to tell them
to give him back.
Do you know the name,
Rocio Duenez?
The DEA agent
you people tortured
to death.
Yes, so here's
what I'm going to do for you.
I'm not going
to torture you.
But you will disappear
south of the border.
I said,
I need your help.
Excuse me, do I...
owe you a favor,
ex-detective Suarez?
No favor.
Okay, let's do business.
What do you have
that I want?
Something that's worth
more than the gringo.
You remember the drug bust
in '07 in Kern County?
The one where you people
said you got 50 kilos?
Which is bullshit.
You people always exaggerate.
We only sent up 20.
We only found five.
Five?
The mule, who was stabbed full
of holes in Delano,
he never made the phone call.
Then who?
Ask your compinche up there.
What's his name?
Ask him what happened
to your 15 keys.
And you know this?
That was on the bust.
No kidding.
They say he has
a avocado farm
up in Santa Paula.
Fifteen keys.
What's that worth
on the street today?
One gringo negro?
I've done a lot
of funky business,
but I ain't never shot nobody.
Look, I have had training.
That don't mean you
shoot no cop!
Well, he got what
he deserved!
How hard is it gonna be
for them to spot
two black women
in this town?
He's gonna be too embarrassed
to take you to court.
I mean, lettin' a woman
shoot him.
Please.
This ain't goin'
to no court.
These people,
they don't play that shit.
Okay.
Come on!
Are we lost?
No!
That Rufo say anything?
He said to take
my money and blow me off.
I should've shot
his ass.
You're dangerous, girl.
Gettin' all Dirty Harry
and shit.
You know what?
I'm sorry.
I will get you out
of this clean.
I promise.
Why you hang with me?
Shit, girl,
I need your help.
Nah, I mean,
back in school.
Back in school?
You were loyal...
till Carlos Washington.
You were...
a good person.
I was a good person.
You are.
You are a good person.
When I'm not dopin',
yeah.
Well then,
I guess you got a choice then,
don't you?
Go on, go on,
go on, go on.
I'm sorry.
I sound like a teacher.
It's all right.
You ain't the one
that gotta get her pee pee
evaluated
every week.
We wanna be
on Constitution.
I haven't seen
a street name in quite a while.
Well, we see
the 18th in November.
Oh, what, what?
We just passed Freddy.
Freddy!
Freddy, Freddy!
Yo, we gotta go.
The car's just up here.
Why aren't you
at the hotel?
Bernice shot somebody.
Shot somebody?
With my gun?
You gave it to her, bro.
Woman's cold.
All right,
let's go.
I gave you people
a simple instruction.
Which way to the hotel?
I told you
just to stay in the room
and keep your heads down.
Make a right.
Cop car up ahead.
Just be cool.
Did you kill the guy?
If I wanted to kill him,
he would be dead.
I just put him down
with one in a leg.
That's all?
Well, they'll hold
a parade for us.
Just go straight.
You're gonna give me
your room key,
and then you're gonna
drop me off, slow down.
Then you're gonna go
past the hotel,
drive into the parking lot,
and wait with your engine
turned off in the back
where it's dark.
That's all, okay?
And then what?
We gotta make it
to Mexicali.
If your son's still alive,
that's where he is.
How'd you get
that information?
I made a deal
with the devil.
Who's this?
Oh, shit!
(brakes squealing)
God!
(shots firing)
Oh, my God.
♪
(shots firing)
They're gone.
You okay?
Yeah.
Fontayne?
You hit him?
Couldn't even see them.
Shot up into the air.
Put holes in the car.
Get me to the hotel.
The bullet must've
passed right between us
and gone out past
the back window.
Maybe they're still out there.
Maybe.
He showed his friends
he don't take no shit.
That may be enough.
One way or another,
we gotta get the hell
out of Dodge.
You were right.
It's still open.
Oh, man, T.J.
never sleeps.
Won't that attract
a lot of attention?
Not as much as these.
♪
Navajas will be sending
word to the Chinese
to release your son,
but he doesn't control them.
They're smugglers,
not professional kidnappers.
What does that mean?
That your son might be
dead already.
Man, you got us out here
in the middle of nowhere.
I mean,
we can't contact him?
He'll contact us.
We're gonna split up,
move around town.
Ask questions.
Be visible.
And stay out of trouble.
And if they find us?
You call me immediately.
We'll play it from there.
Where do we start?
You two,
La Chinesca, Chinatown.
♪
Señor, buenas días.
Sí, I am learning this...
Kelly's in the red house,
Caroli's in the yellow house.
Actually...
what we're trying
to find is who...
if--if you wanted to bring
people from down here to like...
Houston or Los Angeles,
who would we--
But this is what
I am doing.
Ramiro Chow.
(speaking Spanish)
I'm opening.
Sit yourselves, please.
(speaking Spanish)
Please, sit, sit.
You really are
a travel agent?
Where do you wish
to be seen?
There is many places in Baja,
or in other areas
of my country.
We're more interested
in other kind of travel.
Other?
Like crossin' the border
illegally?
Ah.
The colorful history
of Mexicali, eh?
My own abuelo,
my grandfather,
once upon a time,
has a cantina
where he smuggles el alcohol,
the alcohol.
There was a [Spanish word]
under the border
where they would pass
the liquor.
And the people--
Chinese people?
Como yo, sí.
At this time, eh,
Mexicalis has
more Chinos than
Mexicanos ves.
These tunnels
still down there?
Well I don't have
a tour, pero...
We're looking for the people
that smuggled Chinese
illegally into the States.
De estranjeros, cómo?
Foreigners.
No, no, no, no,
I no have nothing
to do with it, no.
Okay, well,
thank you for your time.
But, no, no,
espere.
Esperes un momentito.
I show you something.
Some of these things
are still left
from the day mi abuelo.
This goes all the way
to the other side?
Do you wanna look?
♪
-You good?
-Yeah.
♪
You'd have to crawl
from here on.
Not me.
Spiders and shit in there.
What, you never tried to dig
your way out of prison?
(laughing)
Somebody been
watchin' the movies.
Man, you got to be
some awful kinda desperate
to be crawling underground
like an insect.
People doin' it
every day.
It's mostly instinct.
Gallos wanna
fight each other
to be the last one
standing
and screw the gallinas.
You gotta keep
their blood up.
This one won't fight.
Look, your cousin Zeidy,
she--
La puta.
She's a waitress.
For her family,
working in that place?
She's a puta.
She said you could
help us.
I heard she was tied up
with one of yours.
That a problem?
Depends on the guy.
The last one she was
with, Mexicano,
a hotel stealer.
Thief.
And this one?
He's being held,
we think,
here in Mexicali,
by the Chinese.
They've been told
to let him go,
but we need
to make contact.
And Zeidy wants this
cabrón back?
We all do.
Wait here.
Hey, look,
his name is Rodney.
Wait here.
I knew this guy
used to raise dogs,
fight each other.
Barbaric.
I know people pay
to see boxers
knock the hell
out of each other.
Well, at least
they got a choice.
Maybe.
The choices you make,
that's who you are, Fontayne.
I know people inside
get comfortable with it.
The bars, the buzzers,
the rules.
Day starts and there's
not so many possibilities,
you know,
good or bad.
They say to go
to the other side
and follow the truck.
That's all you're
gonna get.
So, they--they
still have him?
Follow the truck.
♪
Siga el camion.
They were watching you,
watching all of us.
Why wouldn't they
let us know where it is?
They have their own
way of doing things, los Chinos.
They told us to cross
over to the other side.
It won't be far
from the border crossing.
Got a feeling the truck
is in use.
They get the people
across somehow.
Load 'em up
over here.
Through the tunnels?
Tunnels are rumors.
We went down in one.
We didn't go far,
but--
So, you think
they took Rodney's truck
and they're using it?
Something like that.
There's a possibility
we haven't considered.
Your son might
be part of all this.
Why would he do that?
Because he needs money.
Because he knows
you can put it together.
Look, there's a lot
of kidnappings down here.
We have to think
about all the variations.
Rodney wouldn't
do that.
-Is that it?
-Where?
We just passed it
on the right.
Make a turn here,
nice and easy.
It's on the side street?
Yeah.
♪
Take a left here.
Pull over.
♪
You guys wait here.
(indistinct talking)
♪
Drive.
Where to?
Some place where
we can park
and not catch
too much attention.
Not too far.
(beeping)
I put a tracer on it.
Anywhere it goes,
we can follow.
Turn here.
(beeping)
And now?
If the truck
is turned on
or starts to move,
this device here will
buzz like a banshee.
Pass me my jacket.
I need to take a nap.
♪
Yeah, I can remember stuff
from when we were
back in school,
but I can't remember
how I felt,
you know, how it
felt to be me.
Like that was
another person.
Long time ago.
Not just that,
jail, all the doping,
was like there's
a big wall
that separates me
from what come before.
You ever wanna have kids?
I almost did, once.
We got pretty far along, too.
I was so fucked up,
my health.
You lost it?
Maybe it sensed
where it was headed,
had the good sense
not to be born.
I almost lost
Rodney, too.
And he came
a month early.
You know, his lungs
weren't getting enough oxygen
so they had to do, you know,
a procedure where
they couldn't say
whether he was
gonna survive or not.
Little thing.
Yeah, he had asthma really bad
when he was little, you know?
Still gets an attack
now and then.
He had this idea
in his head
that the army somehow
found out and that's why
they stuck him
in transport.
The way he used
to fight to breathe.
Now he got all them muscles,
and a truck,
and a girlfriend who
works in a titty bar.
(fast beeping)
They're leaving.
Yeah, they're goin'
somewhere.
Now the dial hands here
show the relation to us.
At twelve o'clock
we're following them.
If it goes to the right,
you turn right.
The higher pitch
the beeps,
the stronger the signal,
the closer we are.
Signal's good
for five miles.
They're going.
No hurry, okay.
We don't want
to get pulled over.
Doesn't matter
if we can't see them,
we've got the signal.
We don't wanna catch up?
We follow them
until they stop
and then we'll figure
it out from there.
Right now,
we just hope
that they don't
go back into Mexico.
♪
Border Patrol spot checks
this highway.
Sometimes the smugglers
sense there's a cop car ahead,
call back if the coast
is clear.
Damn, we almost to Yuma.
Might be a pick up
there, but,
could be going all the way
through to Phoenix.
Well, how far is Phoenix?
We've got half
a tank of gas left.
Chinga,
I didn't think of that.
And if we stop?
They'll be
out of driving range.
What did that
last sign say?
Next exit 33 miles.
Hit the gas,
we gotta go past them,
pick up a couple of minutes,
get gas
wherever we can.
What if they pull off
after we pass?
We'll turn back and go
looking for them, now gun it.
And if we get stopped
for speeding by the police,
do we tell them
to stop the truck?
That's up to you,
Bernice.
Smuggling people is still
a Federal [unintelligible].
There they are.
(beeping)
♪
Yeah, I can't see
who's driving.
Keep the speed up.
What does the dial say?
It's six o'clock now.
Don't go too far ahead
that you lose the signal.
♪
Getting closer.
There he goes,
moving pretty good.
I--I got this.
He just went by.
Damn.
Come on.
(siren wailing)
Hang it up,
let's go!
♪
If they've stopped it,
we'll go past them
and then pull over,
and I'll walk back
and do the concerned
citizen routine,
and we'll find out what's up.
Needle's at nine now.
(sirens wailing)
They've gone off-road.
Slow down.
Find us a place to turn off.
♪
(faint beeping)
Put your low beams on,
and follow the signal.
You're gonna have
to do some dodging.
Nice and easy,
we don't need to lose a tire.
♪
That's it,
stop the car.
You lost them?
Probably found a farm road
or some dry wash to run on.
They left us in the dust.
Fontayne,
get the county map.
You see the highway
we were on?
Yeah, I got it.
Go north of it,
see any roads?
There's just some
little bitty ones,
I think they're on
an Indian reservation.
Hey, I need the light.
Shhh.
♪
Border patrol's
got to have sensors out here.
Cut the headlights.
(helicopter overhead)
♪
Got a story
if they find us?
Not one they'll believe.
Okay.
I'm gonna walk ahead,
find a good path.
You guys'll follow me,
but no lights.
We'd better be
on a road by sun up.
And then what?
They're probably
heading into Phoenix,
we can use
the tracker there.
Sorry, baby.
♪
We gonna find him,
don't you worry about that.
♪
I have an old friend
down here in the INS,
he'll probably be
at work by ten.
I'll have him check
to see if anything notable
got picked up last night.
Which way is Phoenix?
Maybe 50 miles.
Let's go.
♪
The sentencing
usually goes
by how many people
have been transported,
and if they were
put in any danger.
He'd get two years
inside at the minimum,
two years
supervised release.
Unless of course
he wants to cooperate
with some kind of a sting
against those people,
which case,
he could cut a deal.
You ever done time?
No, I haven't.
And you know the kind
of jobs a man done time
is likely to get,
if he can get a job.
I'm just saying,
it's not the end of the world.
That is if they're
not just playing with us,
and getting us out
of their hair.
If they haven't
already killed him.
I didn't say
anything like that.
If they'd already
killed him,
when your man
in Tijuana made the call,
what would they do?
Lead us on some chase,
then get us out of Mexico
and give them time
to clean things up.
Look, there are plenty
of possibilities, okay?
(beeping)
Where's the dial?
It's at ten o'clock.
There's a road
to the left.
Take it.
♪
Twelve o'clock.
Okay, that's
dead ahead of us.
By the beeps,
they're not movin'.
♪
Rodney?
(banging)
♪
Get the other side.
I got water in the car.
Not enough.
(speaking foreign language)
♪
Rodney.
Oh, no, no, no.
Baby.
Mama?
♪
Oh, it's okay, shhh.
It's okay.
(sobbing)
♪
We gave your friend
Juan some money.
He's in hiding.
What about Fuzzy?
They killed him.
It's all over, Rodney.
You are free and clear.
Just breathe, honey.
Just breathe.
Yeah, we're just driving
on Camino del Diablo,
right by, ah,
Coyote Wash,
and there's a whole
bunch of men
running around out there.
No, we didn't stop.
They looked--
this is kind of funny,
they looked Chinese.
Yeah.
We just thought
you should know.
They'll get sent back.
They didn't reach
their destination
that they paid for.
They'll get a full refund
and get another crack at it.
Chinese are expensive
but they're thorough.
I didn't think there
was a chance in hell,
but I just hung
to be with Bernice
when she got
the bad news.
You must have
been some hot shit
behind that badge, Freddy.
Callin' me The Terminator.
♪
Hey.
Checkin' up on me?
I--I wanted to come
by in person,
I had them take
me off your case.
You'll have Betty Nakamura,
she--she's okay.
Good.
Last one I had
was a bitch on wheels.
No matter,
she'd like to shoot ya.
How's Rodney?
Oh, he's doing better.
He got a--a prosthetic ear,
it doesn't look bad.
He sold that truck.
So you're off my case.
Too weird for ya, huh?
No, I don't know.
I don't have that many...
that many friends.
♪
You don't want
to complicate things.
♪
So, ah, what time
does your shift end?
Five.
You--you wanna
do something?
Like what?
Whatever.
Sure.
♪
Yeah, that'd be cool.
You--you better
hold your ears.
(crushing)
♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Cinderella
dressed in yella ♪
♪ Went downstairs
to kiss her fella ♪
♪ Made a mistake
and kissed a snake ♪
♪ How many doctors
did it take ♪
♪ Cinderella
couldn't be trusted ♪
♪ Went downtown
to buy some mustard ♪
♪ On the way
her girdle busted ♪
♪ How many people
were disgusted ♪
♪ Jump in, jump in,
jump in, Fontayne ♪
jump in ♪
♪ We all jump in,
jump in, jump in ♪
♪
♪ Down by the river
down by the sea ♪
♪ Johnny broke a bottle
and blamed it on me ♪
♪ I told Ma,
Ma told Pa ♪
♪ Johnny got spanked
so ha ha ha ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Had a little puppy,
his name was Tiny Tim ♪
♪ I put him in the bathroom
to see if he could swim ♪
♪ He drank all the water,
he ate a bar of soap ♪
♪ Next thing you know
he had a bubble in his throat ♪
♪ In came the doctor,
in came the nurse ♪
♪ In came the lady
with the alligator purse ♪
♪ Doctor said measles,
nurse said flu ♪
♪ Pay me, said the lady
who's around the zoo ♪
♪ Out went the doctor,
out went the nurse ♪
♪ Out went the lady
with the alligator purse ♪
♪
♪ Bernice, jump back,
jump back, jump back ♪
♪ Fontayne, jump back,
♪ We all jump back,
jump back, jump back ♪
♪
♪ Alligator, alligator,
I can't swim ♪
♪ Time to call
Loretta in ♪
♪ Here comes the teacher
with a bamboo stick ♪
♪ I wonder what I got
in arithmetic ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Eaper weeper,
chimney sweeper ♪
♪ Had a wife
but couldn't keep her ♪
♪ Had another,
never loved her ♪
♪ Up the chimney pipe
he shoved her ♪
♪ Bernice, jump up,
jump up, jump up ♪
♪ Fontayne, jump up,
♪ We all jump up,
jump up, jump up ♪
♪
♪ Cowboy, cowboy,
how about a date ♪
♪ Meet me at the corner
at half past eight ♪
♪ Bring along your horse,
bring along your mule ♪
♪ Don't bring your teacher
'cause I hate school ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ My mama and your mama
hanging out the clothes ♪
♪ My mama gave your mama
a punch right in the nose ♪
♪ My mama and your mama
live right across the way ♪
♪ Every night
they have a fight ♪
♪ And this is
what they say ♪
♪ Icky bicky soda cracker
icky bicky boo ♪
do you love me true ♪
♪ Icky bicky soda cracker
icky bicky boo ♪
out goes you ♪
♪
♪ Bernice, fall down,
fall down, fall down ♪
♪ Fontayne, fall down,
♪ We all fall down,
fall down, fall down ♪
♪
♪ Not last night
but the night before ♪
♪ Twenty-four robbers
knockin' at my door ♪
♪ As I ran out
they ran in ♪
♪ And I hit 'em on the head
with a rolling pin ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Gee gee ga ga
go go go gee ♪
♪ Gee ga ga go ♪
♪ Old Mother Mason
broke her basin ♪
♪ Traveling down
to the railroad station ♪
♪ Old Mother Kelly
had a pimple on her belly ♪
♪ Doctor cut it off
and made it into jelly ♪
♪ Old Mother Cole
had no soul ♪
♪ Tried to get to Heaven
on a telephone pole ♪
♪ Jump in, jump in,
jump in, Fontayne ♪
jump in ♪
♪ We all jump in,
jump in, jump in ♪