[Music]
[Overlapping chatter]
[Announcer] ...To change the way
this ball club is playing. This was a good time out.
Kingston state just can't seem to get things going.
They're playing listlessly.
Have no emotion on the floor.
Seem to have nothing on the ball at all.
Preston university playing out of their minds
while Kingston is sleeping.
Are we gonna be okay?
[Announcer] ...Gonna change the look
of the club on the floor now.
The only clue is--
[toby] Five baskets.
Ten points.
$100,000.
Is this gonna be okay?
Who the hell knows?
This time, we were beyond shit's creek.
And if I had a question right now,
it would be, "where's the map?"
How did I get to this place?
[Rock music]
♪♪
[Whistles]
[Stammers]
Uh, Tammy.
I've got a family thing
I really need
to take care of.
Can you cover
the rest of my shift?
Eat me.
I'll take your
Friday morning shift.
Please.
And next Saturday.
Fine.
Fuck.
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Hey.
Afternoon, lady.
You wanna meet up later?
No?
I'm working.
Hey. What's up?
What's up? What's up?
I really prefer
not to watch.
Come on,
you fuckin' piece of shit.
Okay.
Here we go.
Have some lunch,
case.
[Jude] Come on.
Here we go. We can do this.
It's a big game,
boys.
What did we get in at?
Spread is six and a half.
A half point?
This is stupid.
Why don't they
just say seven?
Seven has to win by eight.
Is there even
an eight in football?
Go. Go. Go.
Drink.
Asshole.
Don't fuckin' jinx us.
It's a beer and a bag
of funyuns before kickoff.
[Announcer] ...Power behind their 4-1 start.
Tampa set to kick off. Their kicker,
second-year man Scott channing.
Here's the kick.
And receiving...
[Jude]
All right. Perfect.
And they're off.
Here we go.
[Toby] We were always serious
about our bets.
But this one was special.
A thousand bucks.
We each pitched in enough for the pot.
The winnings were going straight
to a blowout trip to Vegas.
Fuck.
[Announcer] Actually made at about
the 42-yard-line.
An amazing pickup--
[toby] Jude Petra.
My roommate and best friend since the 7th grade.
We rushed every frat. They snubbed us cold.
Jude thanked them by pissing
in their Ferrari gas tanks.
I can't
watch this.
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
[Toby] Casey young.
Smart as fuck.
We found him lost in the dorm
on the first day of school,
so jude adopted him
as our social science project.
[Announcer] Now, buffalo needs to get
the running game going--
with a wobbly blevins on third down.
Come on.
[Toby] And me.
I had a 4.0 coming out of high school.
Back then, I didn't know anything
other than studying hard.
But college ain't high school.
Come on,
baby.
[Announcer] What is setting up to be
the last play of the game--
[jude]
Come on.
Stop 'em here,
and it's payday.
[Toby]
Stop 'em.
[Jude]
Get him. Get him.
Somebody nail him.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
That's what
I'm talking about.
Yeah.
[Toby] Life is so sweet.
[Toby] Or maybe not.
[Announcer] The official has now
called a touchdown.
That's not
a fucking touchdown.
[Announcer] Clearly, the running back
was not in the end zone--
that is not
a fucking touchdown.
[Announcer] Half a yard short of the goal line,
but they give them the touchdown anyway.
That's like 333 each.
Mm.
Plus 33 on the vig.
Right.
That's like--
like, two semesters
worth of books.
I knew we shouldn't
have done that.
So stupid.
What were we thinking?
Jesus Christ.
Casey.
When you lose a big bet,
the best thing to do
is just handle it
in a mature fashion.
[Jude]
Aw, fuck the bears!
And fuck their
fuckin' fuck defense!
[Laughs]
Hey.
What time is it?
[Jude]
We gotta get to the drop.
Grab the money.
Come on.
Jesus, Casey.
Will you punch it already?
I don't wanna
get pulled over.
I'll pay
the fucking ticket.
[Jude] Casey,
why are you stopping?
[Casey]
The light's red, man.
Oh.
Is that him?
[Jude]
The big guy?
[Toby] No.
The guy in the car.
[Jude] The buick's
the pickup guy.
[Toby]
Mm-hmm.
Can we go?
Can we drive the car?
It's red.
I mean...
[Toby] He's leaving.
What are we doing?
[Jude]
Follow the buick.
I will.
If we're late,
they double the vig.
Blow the light, man.
Come on.
[Jude]
Just 'cause you're sober
doesn't mean you have
to drive like a dentist.
[Toby] Yeah.
Come on, Casey.
Right, right, right,
right, right.
[Toby] Yeah, yeah.
He's turning into that gate.
This must be the place.
[Jude] Good.
I'll go. I'll go.
Do you have the money?
Casey, stop the car.
[Casey]
Okay.
Let me out.
Give me the money.
[Toby]
Be careful.
I got it.
Gate's closing.
Hurry.
Hello?
Hey. No, no, no.
Just makin' a drop.
Makin' a drop.
Are you fuckin' crazy?
Oh,
Jesus.
You don't come here.
That's why we have
a drop point,
you little fuck.
Sorry, sorry,
sorry.
Left jacket pocket.
Don't look at me.
I didn't wanna be late.
Get outta here.
[Screams]
College kid
followed me here.
He didn't want to be late.
I gathered.
Get inside.
[Toby]
God, what a shitty day.
[Jude]
Even shittier night.
[Casey] Well, at least
we didn't pay the double vig.
So, let's at least
salvage our buzz.
Go to the bar.
Dollar drafts.
Potential ladies.
I'm declaring
this night done.
Yeah.
Me too.
No, no.
Come on. Come on.
I can't go out
without my boys.
All right. All right.
I'll make you a deal.
We'll-- we'll,
uh, flip for it.
[Toby] It's amazing how there
are moments in life when things could go one way...
Come on.
Be bold.
...or they could go another.
[Jude]
There you go.
...to be such a bastard.
[Laughs]
All right. All right.
All right.
Here's the deal--
heads, we go back
to our shitty, shitty rooms,
and our pathetic lives.
But tails...
The bar.
[Laughs]
Both options exist as completely separate
and viable futures for just
the smallest, unmeasurable nanosecond.
But once you step into one future,
you never know what the other could have been.
Nice.
Good.
Bet you a round that
the next beer
ordered is German.
I'm down to a dollar.
Casey, cover me.
[Man]
Hey.
Give me a Heineken.
Yes.
No, jude.
Heineken's German.
No,
nut sack,
it's from Holland.
We won.
Hey.
What's the haps
on the craps,
little white bitches?
Hey, what's up,
Duane?
Duane Harrison. Power forward.
If I hadn't tutored him in stats,
he would've been kicked off the team.
What y'all doin' here?
[Toby]
Chillin'.
[Duane]
Oh, okay.
This is my man,
Toby.
He's the reason I'm not
failing statistics
this semester.
Hey, man.
What's up?
Hi.
All right.
Later.
Later, Duane.
Hey. They're takin'
the conference this year.
I'm gonna take a piss.
Me too.
[Arcade sound]
[Overlapping chatter]
Hunter mcguire. All-around jock.
Known on campus to be cool like a dude.
Little one-on-one?
I never would've thought
she'd look at me twice.
Yeah.
[Arcade voice] Let's go.
Ah.
[Buzzer]
Bet a buck.
Wow.
I kind of destroyed you.
It looks like it.
You're a really
good loser, though.
Oh,
thank you.
It means a lot.
I'm Toby.
You can call me "loser,"
if you want.
Nice to meet you.
I think my turn's over.
Yes.
Pay up, chump.
[Jude] Toby. You didn't
even have the balls
to get that girl's number.
Cost me my last dollar.
Here, Casey.
Take it.
Congratulations.
Go have a party.
[Casey]
You owe me ten more cents.
[Jude]
What?
It's $1.10 with the vig.
Out of the mouths of babes.
It's clear the only
people making any money
out of this stuff
is bookies,
and they make it with
their fucking vig.
I want my fucking vig.
Well, you can collect
your fucking vig
when you become
a fucking bookie.
Until then,
fuck off.
[Casey]
Fine. Okay.
[Jude]
Can you believe this, Toby?
He thinks
he's a bookie now.
And then, sometimes, you open your own mouth.
I read this article,
a couple weeks ago,
about sports betting.
It said the biggest growth
market was college students,
aged 18 to 24.
And destiny speaks.
[Jude]
This is the best idea
in the history of mankind.
[Toby]
I wasn't serious, man.
I was kidding.
[Jude] Can it possibly
be this easy?
[Casey]
What are you guys thinking?
[Jude] Think about it.
What does a bookie need?
[Toby]
What about the risk?
[Casey]
Isn't this, like, a felony?
Jesus,
ladies.
This isn't the sports
book at Caesar's.
Yeah.
But felony...
There's gotta be some way
to do this anonymously.
Felony.
How are we gonna
get bettors?
Economics 233--
marketing
in the new millennium.
If-- if demand exists,
in a specialized market,
merely make your
presence known,
and word of mouth
works wonders. So...
That's it. Where do we make
our presence known?
At the frats.
[Laughs]
Yes. Exactly.
The-- the money thing.
We have to have...
$2-3,000.
I mean...
How about
an emergency student loan
from financial aid?
But I mean,
it's a really,
really bad idea.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Casey.
I love this idea.
Uncle Sam will fund
the whole fucking thing.
Come on.
We all know
we're only going
to school to make money.
Puritan work ethic.
Delayed gratification.
We work our asses raw now,
and pray to God that we get
a six-figure job
in the future. So...
What's the harm in gettin'
a little ahead now?
Uh-- fine.
Fuck it.
Fuck the money.
Let's just do it for
the fun of it.
The action.
Pure and simple.
I'm not--
we all have to agree.
Three or none.
[Laughs]
What is that?
Is that a smile?
That smile
looks like a yes.
Yes.
Yes?
Yeah.
C-dog.
Um,
I have to think about it.
What?
Uh...
Casey.
Casey,
come on.
Come on.
[Laughs]
Fine.
[Laughter]
We were immortal.
Kings of our world.
Masters of the future.
Old enough to be brilliant.
Young enough to be stupid.
[Toby] Hey, Duane.
I need a little favor, man.
Can I meet you at practice?
Duane.
What's up,
man?
How you doin'?
New arena's tight.
Yeah. But it's not
enough to play well.
I gotta fill
up the seats too.
Well,
there she is.
Better men have
died trying.
What did you do to this?
God, why didn't--
hey.
Loser.
I don't remember you
being on the team.
Yeah.
Actually, Duane asked
for a little help.
Listen.
Do you want to go out
with me on Friday?
What do you got for me?
There's this lambda
party I heard about.
It's gonna go off.
Are you a lambda guy?
No.
I'm not.
Oh.
Well, then how did you
figure we would get in?
Oh--
can you get in?
I thought maybe...
You could...
Let me get this straight.
You want to take me
to a lambda party
that you need
me to get us into?
[Laughs]
No. I-- that's--
that's not what I mean.
I'll see you around.
Hey.
Stop.
Listen.
Listen to me. Please.
I was not straight up
with you before.
Here's the deal--
my friend and I,
we're starting this--
this sports
betting business.
Okay?
And...
We need clients.
We thought that lambda would
be perfect hunting ground
for suckers,
you know?
That's cool.
It's--
it's cool?
Pretty balls-out.
I didn't expect
that from you.
[Man]
Catch you later, hunter.
Why is that?
You're kinda white bread.
Hey,
if you do this,
then I'll take you
on a real date.
Why don't we see how
the party goes, first, huh?
Can you get three of us in?
All right.
Check list.
Uh...
Cell phone's a go.
The guy who
cloned it said
it's pretty much
untraceable.
Nice.
The big board is a go.
Whenever you
guys get bets,
you write
'em on these cards,
and then you put
'em up on that board.
And then, I get a shitty
Internet connection
to get the odds,
and then I do the math
on my shitty computer--
how many times
to I have to--
we're not spending $1,000
on a new fucking computer.
I'm just saying,
it would be so much easier--
I heard you
the first million times.
[Toby]
Come on.
This is a fucking
business meeting.
Is it judgment day,
bitch?
Is that what you're
trying to say?
[Toby]
Yeah. It's judgment day.
Here.
Two grand.
Emergency student loans.
Nice.
Bankroll is a go.
What are you doing?
What--
it's all there.
I need 500
to make an impression
with the frat guys.
You gotta come out big
to establish
some credibility.
As long as we get it back,
man.
Yeah.
Some of it.
[Toby]
All right.
Business cards.
Here.
Remember.
When we pass these out,
we are not the bookies.
We're just
a satisfied customer,
doing our favorite
bookie a solid
by passing along the word.
Obviously,
do not tell them to ask
for jude, Casey,
or Toby when the call.
We gotta have code names.
Well, I don't really
wanna take any calls.
Doesn't matter, man.
You gotta have a code name.
Why?
Because it's cool.
It's cool.
I'm Frankie.
I'll give you $500
for that name.
Of our money?
All right.
Fuck you, then.
Dean got more pussy
than Sinatra anyway.
I'm dino.
Casey, you're Sammy.
Why?
I'm not black--
[both]
Sammy.
[Laughs]
[Jude]
What else?
Rules?
Yeah.
Rules. All right.
Yeah. Rule--
rule number one--
uh...
No matter what happens,
we share everything.
Three ways.
Nothing comes between us.
That's right.
You didn't tell
this hunter chick
what we're doing,
did you?
No, man.
I'm not a chump.
I wouldn't do that.
All right.
Good.
So,
rule number two.
[Toby]
No bets over $500.
People bet too much,
they get into debt.
And we get ratted out.
[Toby]
Any bet over 500,
we refer to our
old bookies.
Agreed.
I have a rule.
Nobody touches
my shitty laptop.
[Toby]
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Come on.
All right.
Let's do this.
All right?
How's it going?
Good.
Plus three?
Hey. For you?
Have a great time.
Hey.
Right hand.
Right hand,
please.
Other right hand.
Right hand.
[Jude]
Casey. This way.
There. Tobe.
Game room.
Let's go reel
these suckers in.
Hey,
I think I should
hang back with hunter,
you know?
Guy's pussy-whipped
already.
All right.
Yeah. Fine.
Casey.
Let's do this.
Excuse me.
I wanna go watch.
Oh.
[Laughs]
Hey, guys.
I'm really sorry.
Come back when you
got more money, huh?
Okay.
What's the buy-in here?
Oh, I think it's a bit rich
for you kids. It's 100 each.
[Jude]
What do you think?
Bling. Bling. Bling.
[Toby] Julius Garrett.
The richest fuck in the forest.
If we got Garrett's business,
we'd have a business.
What's up?
Hey.
You got a light?
Listen.
I didn't mention
this before,
but could you
pretend not to know
what's going on here?
I wasn't supposed
to tell you.
Sure.
My lips are sealed.
Don't worry about it.
Thanks.
Let's start on ten.
I'm in.
So, what made
you guys decide
to do this
bookmaking thing?
Oh, it's just to scrape up
some extra cash, you know?
I'm on academic
scholarship, so--
what's the real reason?
Just the action.
Action?
Yeah. The action.
I mean...
Either you know it,
or you don't.
I know it.
I don't know if you do.
Well, maybe you'll have
to show me sometime.
[Laughs]
I'll think about it.
Hey.
How about dinner next week?
I can't.
I, uh...
I got three midterms,
a monster paper past due,
and two away games
with the soccer team
the week after that.
Yeah. It's really
busy for me too.
All those midterms
and stuff.
How 'bout three
weeks from now?
How 'bout four?
How 'bout five?
How 'bout three?
That's what I thought.
Smart guy.
Don't Welch.
Two pairs.
Queens and eights.
Three deuces.
Whoo.
Whoo-hoo.
[Garrett]
Come to papa.
Makes me up only
1150 for the week.
[Casey]
Mm.
[Laughs]
How's that?
Uh, I-- I won big
on that bears game.
[Laughs]
Sweet.
[Jude] See,
if you boys are serious,
you should hook up
with my bookie.
He's solid.
Do you have some
of those cards?
[Jude] It's an on-campus
drop-off, pick-up.
And they're off.
Let's go dance.
What's up?
Let's go.
I'm in.
[Jude]
Oh. What is that?
What is that?
Oh. Oh. What's up?
Now, see,
that's...
That's gotta
be disappointing.
That's can't feel good
for you right now.
[Jude]
Sorry. [Laughs]
There you go.
[Jude]
Oh. Oh. Oh. What is that?
What is that, case?
Oh. Oh.
That's in your face.
[Casey] ...You keep
using the same offense.
[Jude] Well, why don't you
learn how to defend my...
[Casey] Why don't you
do something different?
Why don't you fucking
cradle my balls
real gentle?
You know how--
[phone ringing]
[Phone ringing]
Oh, fuck.
Take it.
Yeah?
Uh-huh.
Uh, this is,
uh, dino.
Buck fifty on Philly.
Yeah. Let me get you
the latest on that.
Casey.
What do you got there?
My name's Sammy.
Right.
Fuck off.
[Casey]
And it's at, uh...
Minus 15 and a half.
[Jude]
Right.
Hello? Sir.
Yeah. Uh...
[Stammers] Philly's
givin' 15 and a half.
Okay. You're--
you're-- you're-- uh,
a new client,
I assume?
Okay. I-- I need your--
your name,
and your,
uh, phone number,
and, uh, we'll call
you back with the--
the drop-off
and pick-up info.
[Jude]
Okay. Okay. Um...
Is that it?
Yeah.
That's it.
Cool.
All right.
Holy shit.
[Applause]
Ah.
[Jude]
Go.
[Laughs]
Oh. Nice.
There he is.
Our cherry.
This is our first bettor,
boys.
Oh. An occasion like
this calls for--
[phone ringing]
This is Frankie.
Okay. Yeah.
San Fran.
[Beeping]
Uh, can--
can you hold one one second?
Hello?
This is Frankie.
Uh, let me put
you on hold.
One-- one--
one second.
Yeah. Hello.
Yeah.
Can I-- can I take
down your information?
Yeah. Just give me your
name and-- and, uh,
and address,
please.
No. No. I've got 'em comin'
in at plus six and a half.
The over's 45 and a half.
That's-- that's
direct from Vegas.
Hey. Can you read this?
What is this?
Is that a nine or a four?
I can't read any of these.
Sorry.
Here. Here.
Can I int--
sir?
Can you turn
down the music?
Can I interest you
in a parlay or a teaser?
Hold on.
What's--
what is that number?
That's a--
that's a-- a four.
Or, um, uh...
Maybe it's a seven.
I can feel the fucking
tumor growing.
We gotta get headsets,
man.
[Beeps and whirring]
It's fucking jamming,
dude.
Good luck, sir.
Here. Go, go, go.
Go.
Fuck, man.
I tried to take
all--
[Casey] Dude, I can't
read any of these.
I'm sorry, sir.
We're--
we've been swamped today.
[Casey] Are you practicing
to be a doctor or something?
Okay.
We'll keep that in mind.
What can I help you with?
[Sighs]
[Casey] We can't
do it like this anymore.
We need a new system.
36, 37, 38, 39, 40.
That's it.
$4,340.
Can't we start
upgrading now?
[Laughs]
Yeah.
Let's go shopping, boys.
So, assuming
a maximum bet of $500,
I'm using
a probability-based formula
to calculate the risk
between straight bets
and over-unders with
teasers and parlays.
So, if we have too much
money on one team,
the computer tells us.
If we have enough
teasers and parlays
to statistically
balance it out,
the computer tells us.
If we want to know
how much money
we could make or lose
on any given day,
the computer tells us.
And if Toby's mom gives
me another blowjob?
The computer tells us.
I'll take that.
Give me two on Detroit.
[Man]
Two on Detroit. Got it.
50 on 'zona.
[Man]
Got you for 50 on Arizona.
[Toby] You had to love the frats.
In no time, we had over a hundred clients
lined up for the kill.
Soon, word of the bookies
spread across the entire campus.
Monday was collection.
Clients left payments in specific books
we assigned them and dropped them
in the night slot.
They had to be in by 6:00 A.M.,
or a double vig kicked in.
Jude worked the ass-early shift every Monday
to make sure no one else touched our books.
[Jude] Can this be this fucking easy?
What's the harm in getting a little ahead now?
[Toby] Friday was payout.
This time, each client had a different book
they were to check at a pre-determined time.
Jude made sure to use books that have never
been checked out in the history of the school.
Philosophy,
the unabridged works of Plato,
or anything in a foreign language.
It didn't start slowly and grow
like a plant you nurture.
It blew up like a fucking atom bomb.
And I mean immediately.
The future just happened.
We paid off the loans right away.
Pretty soon, we were making enough
to start blowing some serious paper.
I'm talking eight big on our best weeks.
Two on our worst.
We had to open a safe deposit box
at the bank to keep it all.
At this rate, we'd split 150k
by spring break.
We top out at a nickel.
Call that other number
for the other
bookies I gave you.
Hey. I got it right here
in front of me, man.
I can't believe you of all
people are complaining.
We're small time, man.
We can't take that.
Call that other
number I gave you.
Okay.
You're all set then...
You're all set.
Sammy.
Dino.
Frankie.
[Man 1]
The one pushing the cart.
[Man 2] How do you
know that's the guy?
[Man 1]
I saw him with the books.
[Man 3]
Okay. Let's do it.
Fuckers.
Toby.
Tobe.
Case.
Is Toby with you?
[Ringing]
Oh, pick up the
fuckin' phone.
Come on. Come on.
[Phone ringing]
Hey.
Toby.
Be at the fountain
in 15 minutes.
I'll meet you there.
What?
I got-- I got jumped for
three big on the way home.
But I know the guys who
did it. We'll get it back.
Hey. Hey.
Jude. Hold on.
Okay? Just don't-- don't do anything stupid.
No, no, no. No.
Listen to me.
If we let one guy
get away this...
Then it's gonna get
around that we're soft.
Dude.
Hold on, okay?
Okay. Listen. Just let me think.
All right?
I don't know.
Get a couple big guys from the bar
to go with you to work on mondays.
Follow you home, or something.
Yeah. Maybe.
What about those
fuckers that jumped me?
Let's forget about them.
Just-- I don't know.
Chalk it up as an
operational loss.
We need to keep a low profile.
Let it go.
Oh,
fuck that.
Jude.
Just hold on, all right?
Trust me on this.
Okay? Don't-- don't do anything.
I gotta take a shower
before I go anywhere.
Hey, you did--
you did really good.
It was great.
Hey.
Are we cool?
Is everything all right?
Yeah.
I got it.
I'll be good.
Okay. Later.
Sorry.
So,
what's the plan?
Today...
You and me are gonna
get serious.
Ah.
I'm sorry.
A bet's a bet.
Can we get another round,
please?
I'll lose all day
if it gets you drunk.
[Laughs]
You wish.
All right.
How about this time...
I will play...
One-handed.
Okay. Just to humiliate
me even more.
Or we could
do something else.
No.
Let's play.
Let's just raise
the stakes a little bit.
Raise the stakes?
Getting beat
seven times in a row
isn't enough
punishment for you?
I'm not the one
afraid of losing here.
Oh,
I'm not afraid of losing.
Okay.
So then,
let's make the game
a little more exciting.
You're not gonna
get me naked.
Oh, well.
See ya later.
Oh,
come on.
What do you wanna bet?
Well,
it's...
It's gotta
be something risky.
You know?
Make your palms sweat.
I mean, if you're not
nervous about losing,
then why play at all?
Hmm.
We're not talking
about money, are we?
No.
Not this time.
If you lose...
I do get to see you naked.
And what are you
willing to risk?
I'll do whatever.
Okay.
If you lose...
I get to see your little,
secret betting operation
in action.
No.
No. No.
I-- that's--
that's off limits.
Sounds like it's on then.
All right.
One-handed.
Holding you to that.
[Man 1]
Dude. Roundhouse. Roundhouse.
Sweet.
How'd you do that?
[Man 1]
Oh, yeah. [Laughs]
[Man 2]
Damn.
Oh.
[Ball clattering]
Oh, yeah.
Getting kinda easy.
[Toby] It's gotta be something risky.
Make your palms sweat.
Go, man.
Come on.
[Shouting]
You're dead.
Get that guy.
[Car honking]
Over there.
Come on.
[Grunting]
Come here.
It's a little different
one-on-one, huh?
If you even call us again,
we'll fuckin' kill you.
Bitch.
Hey.
You okay?
Never better.
What did you do today?
Nothin'.
Did you do your 131 paper?
[Laughs]
No.
It's due tomorrow,
man.
Mom? Is that--
is that you?
I'm just sayin', man.
It's due.
Dad? When--
when-- when--
when did you two fly in?
[Sighs]
[Larry]
Trevor Shannon?
What kind of name is that
for a black fighter?
Sounds like an Irish name.
He should be named
more like, uh...
Tyrik.
Or, uh, Calvin.
[Phone ringing]
Yeah.
This is Larry.
Vincent.
Huh?
Take this call.
It's another college kid.
[Sighs]
This is gonna suck.
Whatever.
You told her a date.
The more the merrier,
right? [Laughs]
This is a bad idea.
I think a bad idea
is keeping a $500 limit,
when we can handle
much more than that.
Hey. Hey.
Lower your voice
in the hall, man.
I told you.
We can't do that.
It's way too risky.
It's how clients
get in deep shit.
Cops get called.
You worry like
a school girl.
Case.
I'm not ready yet.
Gimme a second.
We can't take that
kind of trouble.
Come on, Casey.
We're late.
[Jude laughs]
[Toby]
Don't embarrass me, jude.
[Jude]
Oh, what? Me?
Excuse me,
do I know you?
I'm the man of your dreams.
Yes.
May I help you?
Uh, reservation for six.
"Winter."
[Vincent]
Got another call today
from some college kid
I ain't never heard of.
Somebody's layin' off.
Like we need this bullshit.
Relax. Relax.
Next time you talk
to one of his clients,
you get some info.
Nice fuckin' room.
Jesus.
Who the fuck is this?
[Thud]
Mm.
Sorry.
It's kids.
Cheers.
I'm fuckin' starving.
Do you eat at all?
[Waiter]
Madame.
50 bucks says that's
a fuckin' toupee on that guy.
[Jude laughs]
How's it goin'?
It's goin'.
This loud kid with
the crazy hair...
I know him from somewhere.
[Hunter]
Osso buco, penne arrabiata.
Prosciutto with melon
to start.
Same.
What the fuck is happening
in this goddamn country?
Don't let it ruin
your enjoyment
of, uh, chardonnay
with veal. Huh?
So, hunter.
That's a nice dress.
[Jude]
It's very mature.
Thanks.
I put down 20 bucks
you were gonna show up
in a Jersey and cleats.
Yeah.
That's funny.
I should've put down 50
you'd show up
in nothing at all.
All right.
A fuckin' ball Buster.
Here we go.
Okay, you two.
This round is over.
Let's take a little trip
to the bathroom, buddy,
before we get
kicked outta here.
[Toilet flushes]
I, uh... I-- I--
I think it's going well.
You're such an asshole.
Just stop,
all right?
Yeah.
Fine.
That's all you had to say.
[Imitates whip]
[Sniffs]
Hey.
Were you lookin' at me?
No.
You know me?
Do I know you?
No.
You sure?
No-- yes.
Yes. Yeah.
I think I know you.
Oh, yeah.
You eat here before?
No.
What?
No. I--
you gonna eat here again?
[Larry]
Huh?
No.
[Sighs]
[Laughs]
Wipe your nose.
Time to go.
Let's go right now.
What?
Just fucking trust me.
It's time to go. Come on.
Come on.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
I was ready to leave anyway.
I'm really sorry
about tonight.
Right.
I swear he can
be a good guy
if you get to know him.
I'm sure.
Let me make it up to you.
Please.
Let me take you out.
Just...
Have some fun.
Look.
Next time,
we go alone.
And I'll make the plans.
All right?
[Professor]
All right, everybody.
Turn in your exams.
All right.
Time's up.
[Jude]
Toby. Tobe.
Wait up, man.
Toby,
hold on a second.
Hold up, man.
Hey.
Hey. We're cool,
pal, right?
Yeah.
We're cool.
I haven't seen
you all day.
Hey,
listen though...
You would tell me
if something was wrong,
right?
[Laughs]
Do you need a hug, jude?
Listen.
I'm serious, man.
Yes. I know.
Things are good.
Okay?
What are you guys doing?
Just talkin' about you.
Why?
He's kidding.
Shut up.
Come here.
Nobody fucks with this.
My boys here.
Hey, guys.
I have a test at 9:00.
Keep it down
or I'll call security.
Get outta here.
This is our house.
Nice.
[Laughter]
Come on.
Come have a drink.
Hey hunter.
It's Toby here.
I'm just callin' to,
uh...
Maybe set
up a little rematch
with you or something.
So,
um...
Just call me back.
Okay. Bye.
[Knocking on door]
What's going down,
dawgs?
You mind if I come in?
Uh...
No.
I got a noise complaint.
You dawgs been havin'
a little party here?
Uh...
No. We--
we were...
It's over now.
Good.
That's fair enough.
Goddamn.
This is so thin,
it's flat, huh?
Toby.
You gotta lock this shit--
come in.
Come in.
Is this your room?
Hey.
Don't look at him when
I'm talkin' to you.
If I talk to you,
you look at me.
Mm.
You understand that?
Yeah.
Is this your room?
Yes.
Yeah,
if you can call it that.
What?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
It's my room.
You guys know the,
uh,
dorm policy
on alcohol here?
Yes.
We do.
Sir.
Do you?
Yes.
I know it well.
Good.
So, let's just keep it down
after 10:00, all right?
Yeah.
This might be your--
your "crib."
But this is my house.
You understand?
I hear ya,
homes.
You--
you hear me what?
I hear ya.
What did you say?
No, that's...
What?
I understand,
sir.
Good.
We're understood.
What's wrong with this guy?
Son,
are you all right?
I'm fine,
mom.
Mm.
He's cute,
right?
Yeah.
Adorable.
Fuckin' miserable
police academy reject.
Holy shit.
You were a big help.
[Laughs]
[Phone rings]
Yeah.
Hold on a minute.
Hey.
Larry.
[Vincent]
You want 25,000 on Michigan?
[Laughs]
That's a lot
for a college kid.
What's your name?
"Julius Garrett."
You've called here before.
Yeah.
What's your reference?
Of course I know them.
Do you?
[Vincent] What's their
fuckin' number then?
[Casey]
This is yours?
It's good,
right?
Come on.
Let's go for a ride.
Do some shoppin'.
I've gotta study.
Fine.
It's you and me,
Casey.
Here.
You drive.
See?
[Laughs]
I think you should really
take it down a notch.
No, man.
On the contrary,
I think you need
to take it up a notch.
[Sighs]
[Engine rumbles]
[Tires screeching]
It's a totally
student-run operation.
I heard it's huge.
No shit?
I swear to God.
They make
a shitload of money.
It's a totally
awesome idea.
Hey.
Do you guys know what
we're doing in there?
Yeah.
Everybody does.
What are we doing in there?
Um...
Studying.
Yeah.
See you later.
Bet you get a 4.0,
man.
[Laughter]
Oh, dude.
I'm so stoned.
[Laughter]
Jesus.
You're late.
Colleen says these
have to be done by noon.
Don't touch these.
Ever.
Asshole.
[Phone ringing]
What?
How's it hanging, kid?
Who's this?
You guys are, uh, operating
in territory that's,
uh,
already spoken for.
We need to discuss some arrangements.
Yeah. Yeah. We're doin'
fine on our own.
Thank you.
I don't think you exactly
understand what I'm sayin'.
No. I think
I understand you exactly.
[Sniffs]
You wanna fuck us.
And we don't
wanna bend over.
End of story.
No.
I can find you.
Yeah?
What's my name?
Now I'm mad.
Hey.
Dude, I still got
papers in there.
Idiot.
[Beep]
This is Frankie.
Tampa bay's at,
uh, six and a half.
Toby.
Guess what.
Guess what I did
with that girl Hanna
from art history class.
Whoa.
Hi.
[Toby]
Oakland's at nine.
It's really hot right now.
Hey.
Where's jude?
Hold on.
He's still at the library.
Does he know about her?
Uh-- [Sighs]
Don't worry about it.
Just tally these, man.
We're way behind.
We'll hit a parlay instead.
And go with an even dollar
on t.B. And Miami.
All right.
Even 50 on Tampa giving seven.
Done.
[Ding]
[Beep]
[Toby]
Frankie. What's up?
Did you check
your book on time?
[Door opens]
Hey.
[Toby] I can't
do anything for you.
We can't pay you twice
because you
call up and say so.
It doesn't work that way.
I'm gonna go.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
I was invited.
Casey, what's go--
does she know?
Jude--
Jesus Christ, Toby.
You fucking told her?
[Hunter]
Will you calm down?
All right?
I'm leaving.
Fuck you.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's fine. Stay.
Make yourself at home.
You already fucked
everything up.
[Toby]
Jude--
Jesus, Toby.
What the hell
are you thinking?
[Toby]
Calm down.
Casey,
fuckin' help.
Lock the door
and hit the blinds.
It's no big deal,
all right?
Ah.
Fuck.
Cheap ass shit.
[Toby]
Dude. She's cool, okay?
You know what this is?
This is what happens...
When you only think
with your dick.
[Toby]
Come on, man.
Don't be a fucking asshole.
I'm--
I'm the asshole?
You fucked us.
You fucked everything.
Fuck, man.
Motherfucker.
[Grunting]
I'm good. I'm good.
Get the fuck off me.
Not till you promise
to calm down.
Calm down.
Get off of me.
Do you want
me to get someone?
It's okay.
Just go.
Yeah. You go ahead.
He's got it under control.
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
Fuck you.
Hey.
I'll see you later,
girl.
I thought I might
find you here.
That got a little
out of control.
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
I'm fine.
Let's just-- let's go get
some food or something.
This doesn't piss you
off even a little bit?
I mean,
he took a swing at you.
If one of my friends
came at me that way,
I would either
write him off,
or try to help him out,
maybe--
look. Listen.
This is my problem, okay?
Why don't you
let me handle it?
All right?
All right.
Hey.
Listen, man. I'm sorry
that I brought hunter here.
[Sniffs]
Did you catch up with her?
Yeah.
I saw her.
I was out of it, man.
I was...
I was really
fuckin' out of it.
I'm sorry.
I'm just worried about you.
You know?
All right.
Um...
I've been thinking
about this a lot,
and um...
You know, we always
do everything together.
And so,
I have a proposition for you.
I will stop using
right now...
If you agree to expansion.
Kill the limit?
Yeah.
And you'll quit right now?
Just-- just like that?
Cold Turkey?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
[Laughs]
You always gotta have
things your way, don't you?
[Laughs]
Yeah.
What, are you new?
Okay.
Yes.
It's-- it's done.
I'll kill the limit.
All right.
Deal.
Is it all gone?
Yup.
Flushed all of it.
Which, uh,
which toilet did you use?
[Laughs]
I'm not telling you.
I'm joking.
Not that it would
matter anyway.
I'm not looking
forward to tomorrow.
Yeah.
It'll be all right,
man.
Yeah.
I'm glad we're friends,
Toby.
Yeah.
Me too.
[Snoring]
Get up.
Police.
Right there.
Come on.
Let me see your hands.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Geez.
Can someone
toss me my pants?
What?
Do you think I'm stupid?
You think I'm stupid, huh?
Is that it?
You think nobody noticed
all the expensive
shit you got here?
That big, wide-ass
screen t.V. With the, uh...
High-definition receiver,
plus the thx DVD?
This looks like a fuckin'
best buy commercial.
How 'bout that $50,000
car parked downstairs?
What? Did you just found
it in the street, or...
Are we doing a little
low-grade drug dealing here?
Maybe some x, or some,
uh, some grass?
Maybe some coke,
or some little--
nothing.
How 'bout the dog?
[Officer]
The place is clean.
We can't find anything.
[Jude] Hey, mark.
How's it goin'?
[Dog yelps]
Is there some sort
of official apology
we should be expecting?
What happened,
you guys?
They fuckin' kicked
the door in, dude.
They thought
it was a drug bust.
Fuck 'em.
We're free and clear now.
They're not gonna
raid us twice.
We'll sue
their ass.
[Phone ringing]
[Beep]
Hello.
[Toby]
Oh, hey. What's going on?
Okay.
What do you need?
Oh, yeah?
Fuckin' asshole.
What was that?
It's Julius fuckin' around.
Says he wants
a hundred grand
on next week's
Preston game.
It's Julius Garrett.
He's fuckin' loaded.
He can totally
cover that bet.
$100,000?
Guys, the spread
is ten points to Kingston.
That's five easy baskets.
Preston's a bunch
of honky white boys.
We're leading the league.
We'll beat 'em by 20, easy.
We cannot take that bet,
jude.
There's no way.
Gimme the phone.
Wh-- what about the limit?
We killed the limit,
Casey.
[Toby]
Yeah. If you stay clean.
That was the deal.
Look at me.
I'm--
I'm keepin'
my side of the deal.
Gimme the phone.
[Beeping]
Yeah. Hello. Can I speak
to, uh, Julius, please?
[Professor felix]
Your early exams
are showing you at a 3.68.
You know that's not a 3.7.
Fortunately,
your scholarship allows
for one
probationary semester.
Now,
my office is here to help.
So, let's see
what we can do
to get you back on track.
Sir.
[Announcer] Dobson pressured by boucher...
[Casey] I hope Kingston
has an off night.
Stop worrying,
Casey.
Preston sucks.
It won't even be close.
Nice.
[Knocking on door]
Hey.
You guys are so fucked.
What?
Rumor has it jude
fixed the Preston game.
He paid off some
of our starters
to make sure
the game is a blowout.
Oh, Jesus.
It was a gift.
Who cares if they play
a little harder than usual?
Who cares?
Don't you understand that
if anyone gets wind of this,
it's not just
the ncaa investigating,
it's the FBI.
The entire athletics
department of this school
will go up in flames.
This goes beyond
taking a couple bets.
Hey.
Hold on.
Jude, did--
did you do this?
What?
Holy fuck,
jude.
That's fucked up.
You stay away
from the athletes.
[Toby] You should've
talked to us first.
Hey, d.
What up,
h?
So,
we're gonna win today?
Shit...
We'll see.
Listen, uh, can I talk
to you for a second?
Yeah.
What's up?
I know you like Toby.
He's cool.
Why?
All right.
Here it is. Um...
He and some of his friends
are running
a bookmaking operation.
Jude paid off some
of your teammates
to make sure you guys
take it by ten.
You know I got nothing
to do with that shit.
I know.
Then let me tell
you something.
Do what you want with it.
We ain't coverin'
that spread.
[Vincent]
College players sell cheap.
I give 'em just ten
each to take a dive.
But this kid...
He tried to buy 'em off
for a nickel a pop.
Not in my town.
They're in pocket now.
Julius did well.
Fuckin' children.
Should I erase
Garrett's debt?
Yeah.
Mm.
Ouch.
[Vincent] Oh, yeah.
I finally got this kid's name.
[Phone ringing]
[Video game sounds]
Jude.
Turn that shit down.
[Phone ringing]
Hello.
[Hunter] Listen to me.
I'm giving you the heads up.
You're gonna get screwed.
Someone outbid jude.
The team's gonna shave.
No way they can win by ten.
Call it off.
Hey.
That was hunter.
She said
somebody outbid you.
The team is gonna
shave points.
Oh,
whatever, man.
She's trying to fuck
with your head.
Yeah, well,
I'm gonna find out.
Duane.
Hey. Hey.
Come here.
Two minutes.
Please.
What?
Are you in on it?
Fuck y'all.
Duane.
I had nothing
to do with this, man.
Swear to God.
I had nothing to do with it.
Whatever, man.
Yo, I can't
be talkin' to you.
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
Hey. Duane.
Listen.
I'm fucked here.
Okay?
My ass is on the line.
You gotta help me out.
Just cover
the spread for me.
Ten points.
This ain't no playstation,
bitch.
You think I can just go out
there and do it by myself?
Hey. Hey. Hey.
I'm begging you.
What do you need?
What is it gonna take?
Because I can help your
family out with bills,
and groceries...
Ya know?
I can do that stuff.
So,
that's how it works?
I'm your nigga now?
Fuck.
[Phone ringing]
Yeah.
It's true.
We are in serious shit.
Have Casey call Julius to cancel the bet,
and you start laying it off now
to cover that hundred grand.
It's way too late
to lay that much off, man.
Those players are
not gonna fuck me.
Relax, come back,
and watch the game.
Son of a fucking bitch.
[Beeping]
[Phone ringing]
I'll be right back.
[Beeping]
[Phone ringing]
Speak.
Yeah. I wanna put
a hundred grand on Preston.
You wanna put how
much on Preston?
100 grand.
Or anything close.
I'm willing to put down
40 cash in collateral.
Ah.
This must be jude.
It's-- it's a friend of jude's.
Oh,
I see.
So, you help him with his operation, and so forth.
Did you get a lot
of action today?
I hear you decided to take real bets.
You're big shots now, huh?
Fuck.
[Car honking]
Tell you what,
friend of jude.
I hope you can cover for
our young friend Julius.
Because we're
gonna be serving
as his collection agency.
Oh, shit.
[Laughs]
Fuck me.
[Crowd cheering]
Ugh.
[Announcer] Blocked by o'shea.
Ortega wanted a foul, but clearly that was clean.
We come back the other direction--
oh, through the middle.
That's a layup. Right there.
He just let him drive right to the basket.
Where is the defense from Kingston?
And Kingston state really can't get anything going.
Layup, no good.
They've missed yet another one,
and we come back the other way.
Preston looking inside. They've got it.
Puts it up and off the glass good.
This is unbelievable.
I have never seen Kingston play so poorly.
...signaling for a timeout.
He wants to slow things down,
and get Kingston back on track.
[Toby] Five baskets.
Ten points.
$100,000.
Is this gonna be okay?
Who the hell knows?
It's too late to pull over now.
[Announcer] Underneath...
Up and good.
Harrison with the layup.
What a beautiful layup.
He drove right down to the basket untouched.
And Harrison now looking again from the outside
drives inside...
Two-handed slam.
And again with a beautiful dunk.
Now, that's a first team all American for you.
He turned things around and all the kids are playin'...
Stolen by friarson.
Back to Harrison.
Alley-oop. It's gonna be--
good.
That was beautiful.
We've got another team that's shown up out here.
There's Harrison again.
And they take the lead.
A beautiful three-pointer.
Keep it up.
Running the other direction.
Kingston state a whole new ball club
since substitutions early in the first half.
And another jam--
oh, yeah.
[Laughs]
Harrison, now with nine assists...
Ten rebounds-- and there's a three...
It's good.
Look at the leadership of Duane Harrison.
[Whistle]
Oh.
It's a fuckin' foul.
Harrison fouled there with no time left.
Just one second remains.
And who would've thought it?
Come on. Come on.
Two more points.
Please, God.
...of Harrison, with a beautiful comeback.
He hits the first one.
Holy shit.
Oh, God.
One more point.
Please, God, please.
[Toby]
One basket.
Come on.
Come on...
[Shouting]
Duane.
Motherfucker yes.
[Cheering]
Yeah.
I love you.
[Laughs and shouts]
Hey. Hey.
[Laughs]
I'm just so glad we're
not getting killed.
Oh.
[Phone ringing]
Yeah.
Hold on a minute.
It's the fucking kid.
He wants to know
if we're gonna cover
for Julius' debt.
Let me make this clear.
You are lucky to walk
away dead even from this.
So do that. Walk away.
If I hear you take
any more action...
There'll be consequences.
Find this kid.
[Toby]
Let it go, jude.
It's over.
We're getting that money.
I'll guarantee you
those guys are holding
at least a hundred big after
collection, before payout.
So, we go and get
our hard-earned share.
You've lost your mind.
No,
I haven't.
You need a nap,
or something.
Oh, fuck you
and your nap.
You need to stop
being such a pussy.
Oh,
I'm a pussy?
We go and we take
what we deserve.
You should be thankful.
There's no way that
this is gonna happen.
You need help.
Listen to yourself.
Take your help
and shove it up your ass.
I've kept my side
of the deal.
Please stop this
crazy fuckin' talk--
you're either with me,
or you're not.
You're in or you're out.
I'm out.
[Phone ringing]
What?
Dino.
Yeah.
What am I?
Fuckin' t.V. Guide?
I don't know what
channel it's on.
Hey.
I just came by to tell
you it was the mob.
They were trying to get
us under their thumb.
I guess it's a good
thing you won, then.
Yeah.
Yes,
it was.
I'm sorry.
I'm--
I'm done...
With this whole thing.
I'm out of it.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Can I just come in?
And we can talk
about it maybe?
Hunter, I don't see what
the problem is, you know?
The problem?
You're taking risks...
That involve more people
than just you.
You're taking chances
with other people's lives.
Toby...
You need to learn
when to walk away.
Go home.
[Beep]
You have one new message. [Beep]
[Jude] Hey. Listen.
Your Christmas present's in your desk drawer.
You can go ahead and open it.
It doesn't seem possible,
but if you have any balls left,
meet your two best friends
at our old bookie's place at 12:00.
[Beep]
Thanks for drivin',
man.
I'm fuckin' hammered.
Why are we picking
this money up so late?
I guess they didn't wanna
sit on such a big payout.
Mm. It's right here.
It's right around the corner.
[Mumbles]
[Sniffs]
Ah.
Here do a quick bump.
No.
No?
What are you doin',
man?
I'm just--
I'm tired, man.
I need a little...
Celebratory pick-me-up.
All right.
Ah.
Wait here for me.
Seriously. What the fuck are
you doing with that, man?
Relax, man.
It's just in case.
In case of what?
You don't remember
what happened
to me the last
time I was here?
Dude, you should
give me the gun.
No.
Fuck you.
They don't even know that
we're coming, do they?
I'm not doing this.
All right.
Listen.
That's-- that's our
money in there, man.
That's ours.
I'm not leaving
until we get it.
Well, I'm not gonna
be a part of this.
Yeah?
Well, then fine.
Fuck you.
You're not driving my car.
Fine.
Then I'm just gonna walk.
Yeah--
you're gonna--
Casey. Case.
No, no.
Dude. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Look at me. Stop.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry.
It's me.
It's just you
and me here now.
I can--
I can do this shit myself.
I just--
it would--
it would mean a whole lot
to me if you had my back.
Casey.
Are you gonna
help me or not?
[Car honking]
[Tires screeching]
I'll be in and out, case.
No problem.
Hey.
Toby,
what the fuck?
No. It's off.
Get out of here.
Oh,
fuck you.
Jude.
Come on, man.
Hey.
[Grunting]
Give me the gun.
I figured
a way around this
so no one has to get killed.
Give me the damn gun.
Ugh.
[Grunting]
Guys.
I've got a way around this.
Jude.
You gotta trust me.
I got a plan.
Okay?
Let's go.
Let's just go.
Jude,
do it my way.
This one time.
Trust me.
[Toby] Sometimes you dig yourself
into such a deep hole...
The only way out is to keep on digging.
Whoa.
Nice face.
I should see the other guy,
right? Huh?
So,
uh...
Tell me I came
here for a reason.
You owe me and
my associates $100,000.
Now, we're assuming
that's a loss,
but we want you
off our backs.
You're right.
It is a loss,
and things are only
gonna get worse.
The thing is...
I think that I have a way
we can work this out.
Go ahead.
I'm listening.
One last bet.
You pick the game.
You pick the team.
If you win,
we pay you $100,000.
And we won't take
any more bets.
If we win...
You leave us alone
and we forget that
any of this shit
ever happened.
What are you,
stupid?
No.
We're gamblers.
Like you.
I'll call you about
the game tomorrow.
We're not the same.
You and your friends
are gamblers.
I'm a businessman.
[Boxing bell]
[Announcer] Trevor Shannon,
the defending champ,
comes out in the white trunks.
Rodriguez, the number three contender,
comes out in the white trunks with red stripes.
[Toby] A boxing match.
Fuckin' mafia. What do you expect?
The guy Larry gave us was Trevor Shannon--
defending middleweight champion.
Larry's guy was umberto Rodriguez.
Our guy Shannon was favored four to one.
But Larry made it clear
it was an even-money bet between us.
No odds and no vig.
Sweet of him.
[Announcer] It's an overhand right.
Shannon's hands down by his sides,
and he is out.
I don't even think we need a count for this one.
Referee walks over and takes a look,
and Trevor Shannon is out cold.
I have no idea what he was doing with his hands.
He looked so good defensively
up to that point in the fight.
[Toby] It all went as planned.
We knew the match had to be fixed.
So, we bet like mad dogs
against the guy Larry gave us.
What is that?
Is that a smile?
[Toby] We bet everything.
You're a fucking genius.
[Toby] I mean, total liquidation of assets.
Jude gave up his car,
we sold our t.V., our stereo,
our satellite dish, our furniture.
Everything but the ass God blessed us with.
We bet all of our earnings from the operation.
We even bet our credit card limits on the Internet.
[Phone ringing]
Yeah.
Hey.
No kiddin'.
Oh,
that hurts.
Ouch.
Oh, that's too bad.
I'm sorry.
Ah.
No.
We hit nothin'.
I'll talk to you later.
That was sal.
He just told
me some college kid
took him big on this fight.
[Vincent] He's cryin'
his ass off right now.
He's such a fat moron.
He never knows the call.
Fuck me.
Good job,
kid.
[Toby] 100 went to Larry, as promised.
300 went to Frankie, dino and Sammy.
It was the big score...
And we came out on top.
[Laughter]
[Toby] And with that, it was over.
Jude wasn't the first genius to flunk out of college.
All right,
man.
You take care.
Yeah.
You too.
Later,
man.
[Toby] We stay in touch, but...
It's not the same.
What is?
I lost my scholarship,
but with the hundred grand,
I'm covered into grad school.
Casey--
he switched majors. Made Dean's list.
It's a big campus.
I see him, but not often.
I wonder all the time...
Is there any significance
to the people we meet in our lives?
Does our life follow fate?
Or chance?
I saw hunter the other day on campus.
I asked her if there was any way
she would give me a second chance.
She looked me right in the eye,
and said she'd play me for it.
Best two out of three.
Ugh.
[Grunting]
Maybe we should
get a wheel barrel.
[Muffled screams]
Wheel "barrow."
Right. "Wheel barrel."
That's what I said.
Should I get one?
[Muffled protests]
No.
Oh,
I know that look.
[Muffled protests]
You hungry?
Huh?
[Muffled screams]
I think eating would,
uh...
Make you happy again.
Give me that.
Last time,
you almost cut your toes off.
It was raining.
Remember?
My hands were wet.
It slipped.
Give me that.
[Muffled screams]
Yeah.
You're moody.
Maybe we should
go to Charlie's,
and get some of that
chicken piccata you like.
[Trunk closes]
That's with the red sauce,
right?
[Chainsaw starts]