[♪♪♪]
[choking]
The magic Luz's abuela did...
I spoke to Jirou.
I touched him.
He was real.
Give her the baby in this
picture?
The magic only works if the
person in the image is dead.
[crying]
[screams softly]
[baby crying]
Oh. Oh, God.
[humming]
[wind blowing]
[♪♪♪]
[speaking in Japanese]
[laughing in delight]
[♪♪♪]
[distant screaming]
[gasping in fright]
[fireworks crackling outside]
[screaming and cheering outside]
Is it Fourth of July?
No, it's August.
I go look.
No, don't
go out alone.
Wait!
Oh...
Yamato-san...
Yamato-san,
slow down.
[crowds scream and cheer]
[crowds cheer and celebrate]
Hey! Hey, son!
Sonny!
What's going on?
We did it!
What?
We got 'em!
We bombed the Japs!
Whoo!
We hit Hiroshima!
[♪♪♪]
They'll have
to surrender!
[crowd cheering]
[♪♪♪]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[singing a lullaby]
[baby cooing]
[singing]
[truck approaching]
[truck honking]
Señora, do you
need help?
[with Japanese accent]
Aguayo?
We can take you there.
[baby fussing]
This is our daughter,
Esperanza.
[Chester]: Get her inside!
What happened?
Yuko found us.
She's taken Luz
and the baby.
- What?
- Let's get her to bed.
- We'll find her.
- Let's go bring her inside.
Hector,
can we borrow your truck?
Yes, yes, of course.
Why don't I
come with you?
Stay with
your grandmother.
Chester, watch out
for military tonight.
It's no place
for Japanese folks
so close to Los Alamos.
Did something happen tonight?
In the war?
Do you know
where Hiroshima is?
[speaking in Japanese]
[radio broadcast]:
8:15 a.m. local time,
the United States
detonated a bomb
over the Japanese port city
of Hiroshima.
This is reportedly
the largest bomb
ever detonated
in human history.
[tuning the radio
to another station]
♪ ...be just dandy ♪
♪ The day I take my Candy ♪
♪ And make her mine, all mine ♪
[♪♪♪]
[Chester]: Luz...
Luz!
Yuko-san?
[speaking in Japanese]
Oh, my god...
Luz...
The yurei.
She's taken him.
Where did she take him?
In the car.
[speaking in Japanese]
[Asako gasps]
[soft humming]
[humming]
[baby cooing]
[passersby laughing]
The whole world's
falling apart,
and people
are celebrating.
As though a child
in Hiroshima
had anything to do
with this war.
I wanted
revenge once.
It consumed me.
I thought getting it
would ease things,
but I didn't feel
any better.
Major Bowen
want to kill you.
It was either him or you.
You did only
thing you can.
But I didn't...
How did you...
Shh!
Only our own people know.
It's all right.
If WRA not find out by now,
they never will.
You see...
it easy to want vengeance.
Natural as death.
What about you?
I cry more tear
come back from camp
than at camp.
All we had...
gone.
Gone.
Give him to me.
Give me my baby!
We will stay
with her.
Don't worry.
Go find the baby.
I'm going now.
I'll get him back.
I'm coming.
I'm coming with you!
Lie back.
Chester will get him.
You haven't called
the police?
About the couple
in the car?
No, no.
Good.
I need you to
take me back there.
Was there anyone else
in the car?
Just them.
[girl sobbing nearby]
[sobbing]
I didn't do it...
I didn't do it.
It was the woman,
with... with the baby.
We'll take you
to a doctor, okay?
Can you please
tell me what happened first?
[baby cooing]
[speaking in Japanese]
[clock ticking]
[♪♪♪]
It was a good day,
wasn't it?
Yes.
It was.
It's nice to keep your mind
on other things.
Asako-san...
I would like
some more broth.
Yes, of course.
Right away.
What are you
doing?
[speaking in Japanese]
[photographer
clearing throat]
[flashbulb pops]
[crickets chirping]
[brakes squeak]
[engine stops]
Stay back.
I'll go in
myself.
Then what?
She'll just give you the baby?
My baby isn't Taizo.
The baby she wants
is from 25 years ago.
Do you still have
the picture on you?
I haven't forgotten it.
I just need you to do it.
She must have
hidden here
for months.
Preparing.
[Chester]: Carving stones,
waiting for the baby to come.
Sutras on the walls...
No.
Not sutras.
Names.
Her ancestors.
Your ancestors.
Dozens of them.
She's preparing for a burial.
I have to go. Now.
Go where?
The limestone quarry.
The stones are from
the other side of the woods.
I know the path from here.
No, listen, boy.
There's a better way.
We just need some time.
There is no time.
She's taken my child.
Now, please,
promise me you'll give
the picture to Luz's abuela.
God damn you.
[door shuts firmly]
[footsteps running away]
[Luz]: The trees
in the photo of you in Japan.
[Asako]:
They're the same as here.
[Luz]: She's here, I know it.
[Asako]: How much farther?
[baby cooing]
[singing a lullaby]
[speaking in Japanese]
[distant singing]
Yuko-san.
[baby cooing]
[speaking in Japanese]
[Henry speaking in Japanese]
[putting shotgun down]
Pop, no!
Find Ma! We need
another picture.
[cocking shotgun]
[firing]
[baby crying]
[groaning]
Hold this.
Do not let go.
A sutra?
Why?
Pop, no, she'll possess you.
[baby cooing]
We tried that
at camp.
It didn't work.
It did work.
[wheezing]
It trapped her.
Until we burnt it off.
Now, go!
Get out of here.
[wheezing]
[Henry screams]
[gasping]
Aah!
[Henry]: Chester!
Run!
[cocking shotgun]
[firing]
[baby crying]
[cocking shotgun]
[firing]
[gasping]
[Chester crying out]
[groaning]
[straining]
[crying out]
[baby crying]
[Chester groaning in pain]
[Chester screams in protest]
[speaking in Japanese]
No!
[birds singing]
[Chester groaning in pain]
[Luz]: Chester!
[Chester]: The grave.
She went in the grave!
Oh, my god...
Henry.
Henry!
[sobbing]
Hen...
Henry!
[speaking in Japanese]
[sobbing]
Come on.
[Chester]:
Get the baby!
Go. Go.
Asako-san.
Asako-san, come on.
Come on.
The sutras...
[Chester]: My father
brought them.
They trap the spirit.
[baby crying]
[crying]
Luz, stay back!
[baby crying]
[crying]
[unsheathing knife]
[Chester]:
Stop, Ma! Stop!
[stabbing]
Stop!
Ma, stop!
She can't be killed!
[Asako sobbing]
We can't
destroy her.
Her spirit will never rest.
She'll find a way somehow.
[gurgling]
Chester...
Maybe there is a way.
[Luz praying in Spanish]
[speaking in Japanese]
[Luz continues to pray]
[♪♪♪]
[speaking in Spanish]
[Luz continues to pray]
[♪♪♪]
[speaking in Japanese]
[birds singing]
[♪♪♪]
[gasping]
[speaking in Japanese]
[baby cooing]
[gasping]
[laughing in relief]
[baby cooing]
[♪♪♪]
[Henry]:
Chester!
Son?
Stop dreaming.
Are you taking
the photo or not?
[shutter clicks]
Okay. Good.
[popping can tabs]
I never told anyone
this before.
Do you know why
I became a fisherman?
I thought
that's all there was.
No.
I became a fisherman
because in the water,
there's none of the cares
of the world over there.
I was a bachelor here
for so long,
I named my boat "Taro."
"First-born son."
But when your mother
came over,
and we adopted you,
the most miraculous
thing happened.
I felt the same calmness.
When I held my boy
in my hands,
all the cares of the world
vanished.
My taro.
I think today,
I'm going to sail out
into the ocean...
far, far away from the world
and all its troubles.
Come on.
Let's go together.
I can't, Pop.
I've got too much to do.
I understand.
How about taking
one more picture?
Something to remember
this day?
Yeah.
Sure.
[advancing film]
[sighing]
[shutter clicks]
You got it?
Yeah.
I got it.
[baby cooing]
[♪♪♪]
[baby fussing]
Shh.
[baby crying]
[baby settles]
Hey...
it's time to say goodbye
to your ojichan.
I wish he could've been with us
a little longer,
see the war end,
maybe even see
your mom and I settle down.
You know
what his name is, son?
Henry.
Yeah. Just like yours.
[♪♪♪]
[wind gusting]
[speaking in Japanese]
[♪♪♪]
[shutter clicks]
Yamato-san!
It's Genzo.
Ah, little Genzo.
Look at you.
Where were you?
Manzanar.
My whole family.
You?
Colinas de Oro,
but now I am in Hawaii,
with my great nephew.
Everybody there Japanese.
We went to Indiana.
No one there is Japanese,
but that's where
a farm took us in.
Hey, Mama.
Save some for the
others, Yamato-san.
I can barely
keep up.
You make these?
Yeah.
Oh my.
Enjoy.
Hey.
No appetite?
Bad memories.
I hate that
every time
I come back to
see my people,
it gives me
nightmares.
But your babies
are beautiful.
I want to adopt more.
I'd take them all
from the hospital
if I could.
Chester would
probably like that,
and little Henry too.
[♪♪♪]
[Chester]: This is why
we have Obon, son,
to remember,
not just the people we knew,
but the places we've been.
We have to make sure
we keep remembering, okay?
Or else we forget who we are.
[♪♪♪]
♪ I wish I knew how ♪
♪ It would feel to be free ♪
♪ I wish I could break ♪
♪ All the chains holdin' me ♪
♪ I wish I could say ♪
♪ All the things
that I should say ♪
♪ Say 'em loud
Say 'em clear ♪
♪ For the whole round world
to hear ♪
♪ Well, I wish I could be ♪
♪ Like a bird in the sky ♪
♪ How sweet it would be ♪
♪ If I found I could fly ♪
♪ Oh, I'd soar to the sun ♪
♪ And look down at the sea ♪
♪ And I'd sing 'cause I know ♪
♪ Yeah, and I'd sing
'cause I know, yeah ♪
♪ And I'd sing 'cause I know ♪
♪ I know how it feels ♪
♪ Oh, I know how it feels
to be free ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, I know
how it feels ♪
♪ Yes, I know, I know ♪
♪ How it feels, how it feels ♪
♪ To be free
Lord, Lord, Lord... ♪
[♪♪♪]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org