-=Sync&Corrected by Misiek666=-
-=Podnapisi.net=-
Do you understand now?
Do you forgive me?
- What's happening?
Let's go, let's go!
You okay?
Be careful.
Step aside.
Turn around.
On the table.
Have a seat.
Identification.
- William Freeman?
- Yeah.
- You're from D.C.?
- Uh, no.
There's no William
on the lease records.
- Oh, it was, um...
- Face forward.
It was, um,
my girlfriend's place,
Carolyn Hartley.
She didn't make it.
And Eva Balsora?
The other name on the lease.
Eva.
Yeah, she was, uh,
visiting her parents in England
when everything happened.
I haven't heard from her
or spoken to her.
Don't move.
Stay right where I can see you.
What is all of this?
It's quarantine.
I built it to keep her safe.
You sure went to
a lot of trouble.
Yeah.
Didn't work though.
And these?
Wanna explain these?
They're mine.
We're carriers, right?
Sarge?
Get up.
Lead the way.
What is this?
Just a few that I knew.
That's all.
All right, boys.
Apartment's clear. Let's move.
You know, I'm impressed.
You guys have lasted a while.
Don't worry.
I'm not taking the sick one.
I know what we do
with the sick ones.
Sick one?
Enjoy the next
few days with her.
Come on.
Need to pack.
I know.
It's time to go.
-Okay.
I need this jacket.
- Is it okay
if I take these, too?
Sure.
May I have your
attention please?
May I have
your attention please?
This is a state of emergency.
Tonight's curfew is in effect
for all citizens.
Stay indoors with windows
and exits closed.
In order to avoid
any exposure to the ash.
Report all females
to the nearest accord.
Stay close.
Don't say anything.
You look ridiculous, by the way.
Come on, come on, come on.
How many MREs
do we have right now?
Let's go.
We'll need, uh, coffee.
Hey!
Get on the ground.
Get down on the ground.
All the way!
Face down. Eyes down.
Are you all right?
Who else is working today
in the store?
Just me. I'm the owner.
Don't you lie to me.
- I'm not.
- And what did you see?
- What?
What did you see?
Nothing. Nobody came in.
This is what we're gonna do.
Take out $40.
We will pay you
for these groceries.
And we are leaving this store.
You lay there and you count.
Backwards from 500.
And don't you move.
Eva, let's go.
But before
we get to all of that,
we wanted to
kick off today's show
with a bit of cosmic news.
NASA just announced
that we should all be
in for quite a show
over the weekend.
Cavino's Comet will be taking
its rare journey
close to Earth...
Carolyn, I'm out of here.
I'll see you later.
- Hey, girl.
- Hey.
Did you get my text
about the yoga class?
Are you coming with me?
You know what,
I'm not really sure
if I wanna roast myself
at 100 degrees,
- so you're on your own.
I'm going out
with the girls tonight,
so you guys have
a bit of privacy.
You don't have to do that.
You know that, right?
No, no, no,
the place is all yours.
So, uh, you guys
can do it everywhere.
On the couch, in the kitchen.
Just not on that table
'cause my granny bought me that.
- What, this table?
- Yeah, that table.
It seems pretty strong to me.
Don't touch it.
I'm not playing.
- Yeah, no, close them.
Not on the table.
I did buy you
a bottle of champagne.
It's in the fridge.
- Your favorite bottle.
- I love you.
I love you, too.
- I'm so excited for you.
- Oh, my God!
I sleep so much better
when I sleep next to you.
Can we plan a trip?
Where you wanna go?
Uh, a waterfall.
You know, we haven't
been there in years.
I'd love that.
I love you.
I love you, too.
- Hey.
You're cooking.
Well, what's cooking?
- Want some?
- Mmm-hmm.
Mmm.
Okay, just a little bit.
Just a little bit more.
- Okay.
Okay.
Because of your fantastic
moving abilities,
I want you to sit right here
for a second.
Okay.
Why?
I have a surprise for you.
Close your eyes, please.
- Close your eyes.
- Okay, okay, okay.
I like surprises.
How did you do it?
- What is it?
What is it?
Ready? Can I open my eyes?
Right now?
Now.
Okay.
Who are these cute little guys?
- That's us.
- That's us?
Okay, you remember
the road trip?
We stopped
at the weird rest stop.
Oh, my God.
-We'll drive there,
we'll drive there again.
-Yeah, we tried on,
- um, those plushie hats.
- Oh, my God, yeah.
And I was the bison...
- I was the owl.
- Right.
Oh. You remembered.
That was the trip
we decided to move in together.
♪ Lay your trust
♪ Lay it all on me
What's that?
I don't know.
What's this? Is this...
You think it's snowing?
No, it doesn't look like snow.
Carolyn, is that you?
- Yeah.
- Are you seeing this?
What?
Outside.
You're covered in it.
You okay?
Hey.
We'll stay here for the night.
Just in case.
- Hey.
- Yo, buddy.
Hey there, sugar.
How about a little bit
of sugar tonight, huh?
Oh.
Soft-spoken.
I can be gentle, you know.
Okay. Oh.
Not everybody's ready.
I get it.
But in case
you change your mind,
I'm in 181.
Just, um,
come on by.
Hello, boys.
Interested in some sugar?
Ah. Yoo-hoo!
- Hello, boys.
- Get your bag. Let's go.
Oh, looks like
we got ourselves a first-timer.
- Hey! Get inside.
- What's your name?
Fuck off, tranny.
Fuck you.
You okay?
Classy.
Yeah.
- Okay.
Looks pretty empty.
Two?
I don't know.
Seems like a dumb risk.
Pancakes.
Mmm. Bacon.
Shall we order to go?
You want my last cooked meal
to be to go?
Hmm.
It was not he who disobeyed,
it was she.
And now we see
that the Lord taketh.
He brought the ash from heavens
to punish us and remind us
that you cannot
keep living in sin,
this sin.
We cannot keep living
without His words
to guide us and remind us
who God made in His image.
Need a minute?
Nah, I'll take
two specials, thanks.
We ain't got any eggs.
We know.
Now you see
what I've been
trying to tell you.
There was a tiny glimmer of hope
that came out
of Washington today.
Scientists at the U.S. Center
for Rebirth and Repopulation
called a press conference
with some promising news.
This experiment,
dubbed The Embryo Project,
reached a historical milestone.
Latest trials saw
the fetus survive
to the second trimester,
a first in
artificial womb technology.
Many world leaders
publicly praised
their achievement
as this has widely been seen
as a possible method
of repopulation
once the cure to HNV21
has been found.
It appears that the ads
being run from
the past few weeks
may be nothing, but...
Here you go.
Looks great, thanks.
Mmm.
Now, isn't it better than
your gourmet canned ravioli?
Yeah.
Sit anywhere you like.
What's he saying?
Bobby, turn it up, won't you?
Can't hear a damn thing.
Doctors' plea,
the Department of Health
and Human Services
was quick to
announce an increase
in the federal reward
for the successful reporting
or locating
of live American females.
The House and Senate
unanimously approved
an increase in reward
- from one million
to two million dollars...
- in their hopes that...
- Two million bucks. Bullshit!
Whoa!
You don't reckon
they don't pay?
You tell me you'd
turn in your wife and daughter
for two million bucks.
Not my daughter.
You know what
they do to 'em, don't you?
Eh, they're like staying safe.
Don't tell me
you ordered two eggs here.
They're doing
a damn science experiment,
a human-chick combine.
You guys doing okay?
Yeah. Thanks.
-Want me to
top those off for you?
-Sure. Yeah.
Get you guys anything else?
We'll take
two slices of pie to go
and the check, please.
You got it.
Let's get out of here now.
Eva.
Son of a bitch!
Hey, I'll take the check.
You know those boys?
No.
I don't know those boys at all.
Finish up. Time to go.
Are you all right?
Hey.
- It's fine. I'm fine.
- It's not fine.
You and I
both know how this goes.
Day one is hemorrhaging.
Day two is dizziness
and loss of motor control.
- Just pull the car over.
- Day four is seizures
-and convulsions
if you make it that far.
-Just pull over.
- Day six.
- Just pull the car over!
Eva, wait a se...
Eva!
Give me the keys.
Hey.
What?
Glad we're finally
doing this, but...
- I just don't understand...
- Stop.
It's done.
Let's try and enjoy this. Okay?
Come on.
Let's go find our waterfall.
She fell and bumped her head.
Got her?
I'll fill the forms, yeah.
Hey.
Let's go.
What... What do you...
What's happening?
- Would you just talk to me?
- We've got to get you home.
There's got to be
a covered path
to the garage.
Hey.
Just talk to me.
Tell me what's happening, Will.
We'll talk in the car.
Will, I'm not leaving till we
hear about Carolyn, okay?
We've done all we can
for Carolyn.
-Right now,
I'm thinking about you.
-I'm fine.
It's only women.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
I've been calling you.
What is going on?
We don't know yet.
We've never seen
anything like this before.
And Mom, how is she?
Mother is fine.
I got her to quarantine
as soon as it started.
The quarantine?
I've been trying
to reach a friend at the CDC
but so far, I can't control...
So where do we go?
What do we do?
You have to
follow my instructions exactly.
Are you still doing that?
Doing what?
That. Who's gonna see them?
You don't think there is
any other woman
in this entire world?
I don't know.
I'm not that special.
Will?
Yeah?
Can you please
help me with this?
Yeah, of course.
Tell me.
Um, help me...
Be careful.
Okay.
How long have I been out for?
Gotta start
boiling the water now.
They say it's entered
the water supply, so...
Did you even go to bed?
It looks like canned
and pre-packaged foods
for a while,
but I like ravioli, so...
When did you go to the store?
Soon as it opened.
What's with these lights?
UV lights, baby.
They kill pathogens and germs
within a couple feet.
This will be over
in a few weeks,
but till then,
I'm gonna keep you safe.
Got it?
Where's the phone?
- Where's the phone?
- Um, it's on the coffee table.
Leave it in the bag though.
Don't take it out.
It's safer.
Hello?
Mmm-hmm.
This is she.
Yes. Yes, yes.
That's correct.
I'm sorry, could you
please slow down?
I can't understand
what you're saying.
What do you mean?
Babe, what happened?
What?
It's been 48 hours
since the mysterious ash
began to fall
throughout parts of the world
and little is still known
about the pathogen HNV 21
present in the debris
that has now killed
thousands of females
and infected millions more.
International flights
have been grounded
in every major airport
as authorities struggle
to contain the spread
of this disease.
Doctors have now verified
trace amounts of the virus
in at least a dozen
human males in hospitals
around the country.
While none of the male patients
displayed symptoms,
authorities are now cautioning
all males to avoid
any physical contact
with uninfected females.
Will, take care of her, okay?
- Good to talk to you.
- We love you.
- Bye. Love you.
Love you, Mom.
Please be safe.
- Want some ravioli?
- Sure.
Move! Move!
Shh! Shh! Shh!
- Got it.
- You got it?
The pulley is here
but the vent is to the right?
Yeah.
The President
appears to be visiting women
held in official
government captivity.
The women are shown to be
happy and healthy,
as they urge other women
to come forward and ensure
the future of America.
You shouldn't be
taking pictures like that.
You're in front of the window,
it's not safe.
Eva, come on.
Give me the camera.
Do you smell that?
That's like just
Lysol everywhere.
Do you smell that?
No.
- No, but you keep going out.
I'm sorry, I know
it's not your fault.
Is this really
what I think it is?
Got it.
No personal information.
Riots and looting
continue in the streets
of London, Paris,
Barcelona and Rome
as the general
surviving population
seems to be turning to anarchy.
- What are you looking for?
- Where's the phone?
-We're not using
the phone anymore.
-Why?
I read some of the messages,
and all I'm saying is that...
-Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
What did you do?
-Listen,
- all I'm saying is that...
- What did you do?
-Why are you going
through my phone?
-There's information
that you are
giving out there, Eva,
that you should not...
Why are you
going through my phone?
At least
a dozen explosive devices
rocked the offices
and labs of the Embryo Project
late last night in Washington.
Terrorist group Via Natura
quickly claimed responsibility
justifying their action as
defending God's work.
Honestly,
the hardest part
is feeling helpless.
I don't want to be
the policeman.
I don't want to have to
tell you what you have
to do anymore.
You know what you have to do.
So you do it.
Your dad was very clear with us.
He told us the things
that we had to do
every single morning,
which we have to do
every single day,
when I come back from the store,
when I come back from my site,
We don't know
what I'm bringing in.
We don't know.
I'm not sure
how else to report this.
The death toll has clipped
ten million females
today worldwide.
This officially makes HNV 21
the fastest
and deadliest epidemic
in modern history.
But we're definitely
not the last ones.
My mother is still
safe in England.
Hang in there, ladies.
How hard is it?
When you come out,
you zip the thing up,
you wash your hands.
How difficult is that, really?
I know he is
doing this all for me,
but he is different now.
We're different now.
Do I just sound
like an ungrateful bitch?
-You don't see...
-Give me the rules again.
Just give me the rules!
Just give me the rules, okay?
Just give me the rules.
No calls, no contact
with the outside world...
I don't want
to control you,
I'm trying to protect you.
Don't you
fucking touch me.
What have you done?
Don't lag so far behind.
I won't be able to
save you from the bear.
Bear, huh?
You need help?
You want me
to carry you?
Got something for you.
What?
What is it?
Oh, yeah!
Mmm! That's good.
You wanna shoot somethin'?
Are you sure this
is what the map says?
I'm sure.
Ah!
I told your mother
we should have sold
this piece of junk.
She was a better driver
than you.
You know what you're doing?
How hard could it be?
Oh. Okay.
- Back far enough? Okay.
- Oh! Don't worry.
One...
Two...
Safety's on.
- Oh, boy.
Okay. One...
Two...
Going again.
My stance was...
Gotta relax
my shoulders. Okay!
Damn.
All right, you wanna try?
You try. Come on.
Okay.
Is that it?
Yeah, that's the one.
Put it back here.
Safety's on.
Hold it like this... Okay.
Here we go.
Oh!
Did you see that?
- No way!
- Be careful with that thing.
- Okay. Okay.
I know you did it but try again.
- Yeah, yeah. Try again.
- Okay.
Hey! Go girl!
Uh!
Ay!
Ahhh!
We're like what cavemen
did back in the day.
I grab her, and drag her.
Don't joke.
- You had such good aim.
- And you suck!
- You had such good aim,
earlier tonight.
Where is it all gone?
I'll see you in a bit.
Mmm. Feels so good.
Eva. Eva!
I got you, baby.
Come on.
You'll be okay.
A little late
to the party, ain't you, son?
Sold my last 320 Swift
about a week ago.
Let's see what we got here.
So, you wanna
be accurate but not lethal?
You hit 'em in the ovaries,
you ain't getting
nothing for 'em.
How about this?
No, I'm looking
for something smaller.
A hand gun
or something like that.
You know, you don't have
to play coy with me, son.
There's a tool for every job,
you just gotta make sure
you got the right one.
- This one.
- Hmm.
You ain't ever
hunted before, have you?
Looking for self-defense.
Yeah, well, I'll say
whatever you want.
You realize
I'm still alive, right?
I'm gonna take it.
I'm tired of this too.
I can't even touch you.
Take the test.
If I'm not a carrier,
then maybe we can...
Thought it was worth a try.
"Open the medically sealed swabs
"and remove one swab
from the sealed packaging."
Mmm?
"If the solution
remains clear,
you are negative.
"If the solution turns indigo,
"you must seek
immediate medical attention."
Okay, so...
Clear-good,
indigo-bad.
At least you're safe.
Yeah, but you're sick.
Will, you have it.
I'm a carrier but I'm not sick.
I feel fine.
See...
We're together...
What's so bad?
And that's enough for you?
Eva.
- Ah!
Eva!
You close?
Good morning.
Who's Eva?
All right.
Get out of there.
Step out.
Stand right out here.
Right there. Right there.
Where is she?
- Don't come back!
- Don't yell.
Over there, see the big tree?
Over there!
Sit down.
Don't get too close, buddy.
Hold your right hand up.
Just like that.
Like that.
Put your hands together.
Where is she?
Is there any sign of her?
She can't be far.
She's sick, man.
Day four...
She won't make it.
We need to split up.
Start looking for her.
- Run, Eva!
- Hey!
I told you...
No yelling.
Double back down the trail.
Make sure we didn't pass her.
I'll head towards the river.
Be careful.
Hey!
She's not coming back.
You hear me talkin' to you.
Keep your voice down.
The boy's asleep.
To hell with your boy!
How did you keep
her safe for so long?
Where have you been hiding?
I tried to do the same
for my wife and...
The basement in our house...
I thought I sealed it,
sterilized it,
but she died after
only a few weeks.
Something my stepson
will never forget.
I'm not a monster.
I want you to know that.
But we have to rebuild.
We have to...
re-populate.
I want my son to have some hope.
Maybe a family
of his own someday.
I promised his mother this much.
She's sick.
That's why we need
to find her soon.
'Cause the eggs,
they don't last more than
six or seven hours after death.
What is...
What is this about?
The money?
I'm a little disappointed
in your gal
for not turning herself in.
Would you have
turned our wife in?
No, you're right.
I wouldn't have.
Cathy,
she would have
gladly turned herself in
it would help.
Hey, buddy.
It's time to wake up.
Shift change.
Oh!
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Okay, okay.
Let's get this off.
Hey! Let's go.
Hey, Case.
Case, you still awake?
Casey!
Go, go, go, go!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Casey! Casey!
He called a couple
of times on the cell,
but, um...
Five minutes.
We'll set up a secure VPN,
and we'll call him back.
Why, why did he call the phone?
I don't know.
But the VPN's secure.
We'll call him right back.
You guys planned this
whole thing out, right?
To not call the phone,
and he called the phone.
What if it's an emergency,
and what if he's not
by his computer?
Let me just call him, please?
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Don't say anything.
I know.
Eva?
Eva? Are you there?
Is that...
Is that you, Eva?
The screen's black.
I haven't heard from you.
I just want to know,
are you okay?
Are you alive?
Shh.
I... I don't know
what to think anymore.
I don't know what to do.
I thought...
I thought your mother was safe.
There was no need
to take a woman
of her age.
Oh, God!
Eva, I...
I tried my best to stop them.
I, I really tried my best.
But...
They had guns.
I don't know where
they took her.
I don't know.
And I...
Now I want to see you.
I want to see you, beta.
Meri jaan, say something.
Dad, I'm okay!
- What are you doing?
- Eva, no!
- Give me the phone! No!
- You can't... Eva!
Are you fucking kidding me?
Stop this!
-Eva...
-They took my mom!
They took my mom!
- I heard what he said.
- Please give me the phone.
You can't talk on
an unsecured line.
You know that.
Give me the fucking phone!
Give me the phone!
I'm not giving you the phone.
-Give me the fucking phone!
-I'm not giving you
the fucking phone!
Okay?
If you talk on
an unsecured line,
they will be here in 15 minutes,
and they will take you
just like they took your mom.
Is that what you want?
I can't let you do it.
I'm not letting that happen.
You're not gonna let me?
You said you're not
gonna let me?
What does that mean?
Huh?
Eva, I'm not trying
to control you.
Okay?
I'm trying to protect you.
Did you even ask me?
After all this happened,
you just... You just did it.
The... The quarantine,
the fucking protocol.
- This fucking...
- Hey, hey, hey!
Come on, come on, come on.
I fell asleep and
you just put me
in a fucking prison!
Will! This is
a fucking prison!
It's the way it is now.
You are not with me.
I am alone.
I'm...
What the fuck are we
waiting for?
Some kind of cure or miracle?
I wanna go out there!
I wanna see the sun!
-I wanna talk to my dad.
-Lower your voice.
Lower your voice!
-I wanna talk to my dad.
My dad...
-Lower your voice.
Please let me talk to my dad.
What's happened to us, Will?
What are we even doing this for?
Do you even love me?
Hmm?
I don't know what
to fucking say.
But what I do know
is that we can survive this.
Okay?
We made it this far, you and me.
What if I don't want
any of this, huh?
any of this?
I'm waiting for you
to wake up and realize
that this is life now.
Eva, put the gun down.
Okay?
I want you to leave.
I'm not gonna leave.
Just go.
I need you to leave.
This is not you.
You're emotional, and now...
Just fucking leave!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Don't worry about me.
Hey.
- We're close.
- Yeah?
We're close. Come on.
- Baby steps.
- Mmm.
Come on.
Baby steps.
♪ There's nowhere to go
♪ Now that you know
♪ There's no turning around
♪ To buy those tickets
♪ To that same old show
♪ And you try to insist
♪ That you could resist
♪ But what is the point?
♪ Your name is on the list
♪ So if it's all right with you
♪ If it's okay
♪ I will keep on loving you
♪ This way
♪ If it's all right with you
♪ If it's okay
♪ I will keep on loving you
♪ But I can't stay
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ Ooh
♪ I wanted to see you
♪ I wanted to sing
♪ I wanted
♪ Everything
♪ But there's nothing
to take here
♪ There's nothing to own
♪ There's only this feeling
♪ Of finding home
♪ So if it's all right with you
♪ If it's okay
♪ I will keep on loving you
♪ This way
♪ If it's all right with you
♪ If it's okay
♪ I will keep on loving you
♪ But I can't stay
♪ If it's all right with you
♪ So if it's okay
♪ I will keep on loving you
♪ This way
♪ If it's all right with you
♪ Darling, if it's okay
♪ I will keep on loving you
♪ But I can't stay
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ Ooh