[ominous music]
[beeping]
JANITOR: Don't you ever go home?
Oh, I got to finish
this report by Tuesday.
Have a happy Fourth.
Right.
GROUND CONTROL: Flight 1055,you're clear for final approach
into Denver.
Come on down to
1,500 feet, cowpoke.
Denver approach,
Flight 1055 descending
through 1,500 [inaudible].
GROUND CONTROL:
Thank you, partner.
Folks, we've turn onthe fasten seat belt sign,
and we started our
descent into Denver.
We'll have you in the MileHigh City around 8:15.
That should be plenty
of time for you
to rest up for tomorrow'shot dogs and fireworks.
The current temperature inDenver's about 75 degrees.
But it's going to zoom all theway up to 95 degrees tomorrow.
It's going to a hot,
sticky Independence Day.
On behalf of the
entire flight crew,
we want to wish you a safeand happy 4th of July.
PILOT: Unfortunately,
this low cloud cover
is going to keep us fromshowing you a beautiful view
of the Mile High City skyline.
And we're going to
be in this thick soup
until we touch
down on the runway.
We're going to be
putting on the fasten
your seat belt sign
in just a few minutes.
So if you want to
stretch your legs,
this is a good time to it.
What the hell?
Where's the runway?
I got it.
Full throttle.
Go around.
Flaps up.
Trim for climb.
Not responding.
PILOT: Turn off the autopilot.
Shut down the computer.
Shutting down.
Still not responding.
We're too low!
The plane's going down!
We're gonna crash!
[indistinct yelling]
COPILOT: Switching to manual.
Adjust the trim.
The rudder's frozen.
Still no control.
FLIGHT ATTENDANT:
Take your seats.
[inaudible] seat belt.
COPILOT: Mayday, [inaudible].Mayday.
The controls are dead.
Nothing's responding.
Oh, god.
[explosions]
[elevator dings]
Neil.
Neil, what happened?
Well, they crashed.
Keller says we've got peoplefrom Washington coming.
Where is he?
Hey, boss.
My presentation.
- I'm just finishing it.
- Move it.
And just remember the
operative phrase for you
two is seen and not heard.
Got it?
Right.
Put on some pants, Neil.
And for god's sake,
lose the earring.
OK.
Gentlemen, thank
you for coming.
Two hours ago, Flight 1055crashed into the largest
skyscraper in Denver.
Half of downtown isstill engulfed in flames.
Based upon the rising toll
of dead and injured, not
to mention the property damage,this is hands down the worst
disaster in aviation history.
Jesus Christ.
That's three major
crashes in three weeks.
Doesn't anybody here have aclue as to what's going on?
General Roberts from
the NSA has an idea.
He'll be joining us shortly.
But now here's
what the FAA knows.
Flight 1055 stopped
responding to air
traffic controllers
approximately one hour
before it crashed.
DIA went nuts trying
to raise them,
and they could not
get a response.
Any read on those black boxes?
Our first look at the
flight data recorder
reads like they were rightwhere they were supposed to be.
The cockpit voice recorderwas empty, nothing.
Obviously they've bothbeen tampered with somehow.
What about those
first two crashes?
Any similar mechanical failures?
Actually there are.
Neil, that's good
of you to join us.
Rudy, let's run the demos.
You're looking at three
spectacular crashes.
In each case, the crewswere unaware of any problems
prior to the lost communication
between the aircraft
and the ground.
First, Flight 232
from Honolulu to LAX--
new engine shut downhalfway through the flight.
It plunged into the Pacific.
Flight 90, JFK to
Seattle, this one
veered 200 miles from
the original flight path
and crashed into a mountain.
Again, controllerspowerless to get through.
Gentlemen, the news
is getting worse.
A half hour ago, the
Pakistan terror group
Red Dawn claimedresponsibility for the crash
of flight 1-0-5-5.
They've also
claimed responsibility
Jimmy Hoffa and El Nino.
Shut up.
What was that?
Sir, I was just saying doesn'tthe Red Dawn seem a little,
well, organized for
something of this scope?
[chuckles] Just howextensive is your knowledge
of terrorist groups?
My right-hand man spent
two years with Red Dawn.
But maybe, just maybe, youknow more than he does.
I'm not suggesting that, sir.
I'm suggesting that we'rethinking inside the box.
I think we're dealing
with a whole new breed
of terrorist here,
a computer hacker.
The FBI's Computer CrimeUnit doesn't think so.
Move on, Neil.
No, hear me out, Sam.
Listen, each plane that wentdown was the same model jet.
And each one had a flightcomputer retrofitted
with the new Oxcilis
chip, which drains
an unprecedented
amount of control
from the pilot to the computer.
It's the same chip thatprevented 23332 from ditching
last year, that rerouted
hundreds of planes
this year alone around
dangerous weather.
And which was manufacturedby a company with the most
lax security imaginable.
I mean, I'm talking a12-year-old could hack in--
Son, I don't know what
you've been smoking.
Because what I'm smelling hereis a whole lot of horse shit.
You know, even a
redneck old fart
like me knows that
a plane's computer's
not connected to the ground.
They're self-contained so thata hacker can't gain access
unless he's on the plane.
Let me explain.
This guy hacks into the
mainframe of the company
that makes the chip, OK?
Then alters the
programming on the chip
itself, telling it to link upto him once it's in the air.
What the FBI needs fromthe is technical analysis
not these conspiracy theoriesand intellectual bullshit.
And that's exactly
what you will get, sir.
Neil will have the break down onthe on-board computer sequences
done by noon.
We will be pursuing
this investigation
per the instructions
of General Roberts.
Anything else?
Man, all I'm saying is thatthe Red Dawn couldn't have had
the technological know how--
Son--
I think we're done here.
Let's go.
I want you to do the computermodels and break down the data,
and that's all I want you to do.
I can do that with
my eyes closed, Sam.
- Then do it!
- I'm sorry.
If I see something important,I'm gonna point it out.
There are lives at
stake here, Sam.
You listen to me.
You are not one of
the investigators.
You are on this task
force to crunch numbers.
The FBI has computercrime specialists to bring
in if that's what they need.
Sam, just hear me out.
No.
Hear me out, hotshot.
Don't you ever run roughshodlike that over me in a meeting.
I was expressing an opinion.
You were out of line!
If you do it again, I willdrop you like a bad habit.
Whoever's doing thisisn't going to stop, Sam.
They're going to strike anotherplane and strike it soon.
One more flight to go.
You know, from now on
July 4th isn't just
America's Day of Independence.
It's also Josie Wallus's--
free from the sky and
running my own business.
Hold on there, girl.
You're sounding like you'vegot short-timer's disease.
What?
Mm-him, using the
last flight to take
revenge on all the ghostsof bad passengers past.
[laughing] You know
what I'm talking about.
Wait.
You're under the impression thatI'm actually working tonight.
I mean, I thought you weregoing to let me take it easy.
Oh, don't even try.
[laughing] Besides,
it's a holiday red eye.
It's a piece of cake.
Exactly what I planned--
hardly any passengers
and most of them asleep.
Hey, did I tell you
I signed the lease?
Only about 10 times.
[laughing] I'm gonna
miss you, Josie.
Aw, well, you're not
done with me until dawn.
Oh, I'm sorry we're gonnabe done with you at all.
Oh, thanks, Paul.
That's nice to hear.
So, um, tell me, those,um, hippety-hoppity clothes
you're going to be selling--
[laughter]
It's hip hop.
Ah.
Oh, right.
Um, those are those
ridiculous clothes
that my nieces and nephewslove and I hate, right?
Right.
That's why I'm gonnagive them a big discount.
[laughter]
It's one route awayfrom a life on the ground
and coincidentally
one route away
from your last chance with me.
[laughing] Now that's
got to break her heart.
[laughing].
Flight check.
Aye-aye, Captain.
Think about what you're missing.
Never.
That's it.
My god, makes perfect sense.
Each plane that crashed hadthe Oxcilis chip, right?
Yeah, but there arehundreds of planes that have
the chip that haven't crashed.
Yeah, I know.
But look at this.
Sam, how you doing?
You're going to have
that analysis done soon?
You know it.
Just finishing it now, boss.
OK, we narrowed it downto the models [inaudible]..
Then eliminate the planes
that aren't flying.
Cut out the commuter planesand international flights
because this guy likes big,spectacular US crashes.
Neil, you're not
a secret agent.
That narrows it
down to these three--
Austin to Omaha, Providenceto Atlanta, Seattle to Salt
Lake City.
Neil--
And he's escalating.
It's going to be morespectacular than the last one.
More specular than
annihilating Denver?
I'm dead serious, Rudy.
I think we got the
power to stop this guy.
Look, this flight's beenrerouted, 2:00 AM departure.
It's going from Milwaukee to--
--Washington, DC.
It's going to DC
on the 4th of July.
If you want spectacular,
that's the one.
Wait, what are you--
what are you doing?
You-- you can't just
go to Milwaukee, Neil.
Neil!
Look, if I'm wrong,
I get disciplined.
Maybe I get fired.
But if I'm right, people die.
I couldn't live with that.
I really think you're
making a mistake, Neil.
Look, [scoffs] if
you're so convinced
the plane's in trouble,
why don't you just call?
Rudy, I got to do it myself.
I call Keller.
He starts screaming.
Maybe he sends some no-brainerdown to check out the computer.
I still think you're
making a mistake, man.
We live in a
binary world, right?
It all comes down
to ones and zeros,
black or white, yes and no.
Come on.
That's self-indulgent
programmer crap.
In the real world, wedeal with shades of gray.
Stay or go, do or die.
Tell Keller I went out
to get some coffee.
[energetic music playing]
Getting back to our topstory, "Disaster "in Denver,
grizzly recovery after--
WOMAN [OVER LOUD SPEAKER]:[inaudible] pick up
the white courtesy phone.
Laura Ward, please pick upthe the white courtesy phone.
TV REPORTER [ON TV]:
15 passengers and 6
crew member are confirmed dead.
I want it monitored 24-7.
Yep.
Are we going to see
the White House, Mom?
That's right, Tobaz.
And a big museum with dinosaurs.
CHILD: Cool.
You know, call me
if there's any change.
Look, of course that's OK.
Got it.
Bye.
You know, maybe this isn't theright time to go on holiday.
New residents are
coming in next week,
and I need to be
at the hospital.
Philip, we are
on family vacation.
And this is the only time youget to spend with your son.
Of course.
[phone rings]
Dr. Philip here.
Hey, I'm so glad you called.
You know, go to the hospital,check their blood pressure.
Hey, don't I know you?
DR. PHILIP: --vitals
every four hours.
Make sure somebody
stays with him 24-7.
Nope, I don't think so.
I know this
sounds like a line,
but you look very
familiar to me.
Mm-hm.
But then again, if
I don't know you well,
that can be fixed
right here today.
I'm Ray-- Ray Macklin.
AIRLINE EMPLOYEE
[OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
Because of security
measures, this will take
a little longer than usual.
We are now seating firstclass passengers and rows 40
through 45.
We do appreciate your patience.
And thank you for
choosing Domaine
Airline for your travel needs.
[energetic music]
MAN: Thank you.
Is there a chance I
could [inaudible] seats?
The boss told me with
the DC trip and my job,
it's the only reason I'm here.
I hate to fly.
Yeah, I love airports--plastic food, plastic people.
[energetic music]
Listen, all I'm saying isit would take a lot longer
to get on this damn
plane than it's
going to take to get to DC.
It's for your safety
and security, sir.
Well, I'll feel
a lot more secure
once I make it to my damnsales meeting on time.
Enjoy your flight.
Yeah, right.
Ray?
Ray Macklin?
Oh, Jesus.
It's been a long time.
Sure has, Max,
since high school.
And you know my tooth is stillchipped where you hit me.
- You deserved it.
- That's debatable.
Would you like a
pre-flight beverage?
No.
I'm fine.
Thanks.
- Good.
Excuse me.
Jesus.
Here we go.
Is there a problem?
Yes.
You.
[energetic music]
Ah!
Uh, man.
JITTERY MAN: Sorry.
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Let me help.
FEMALE PASSENGER: It's OK.
Here you are, honey.
Thanks.
[energetic music]
Hey!
No parking!
OFFICER: Hey!
- Watch that for me.
Hey!
Stop!
Airport Security.
Hey!
Stop!
FAA emergency.
Stop him!
Hey, stop the plane!
I need you to bring
back that plane.
Stop that plane!
Hey, buddy.
You don't who you're
dealing with here.
- Son--
- I'm with the FAA.
You better show me some ID.
My chest bottom pocket.
[jet engine running]
Sorry.
Get the pilot of that
plane on the phone.
I'm so--
Get it done.
Patch me through to 617.
Thank you.
Captain O'Kelly, I have
a representative here
from the FAA, and you
need to talk to him.
Thank you.
Captain?
Listen, I think someone'sfucked with your computer.
I need to run some checkson it before you take off.
Ground control, we're
staying put until this
is straightened out, over.
Roger, 672.
Hold your current position.
We're gonna roll
out the red carpet
and open up the front hatch.
Thank you.
We need to get
out to that plane.
This way.
Let's go.
[beeping]
Yes?
CAPTAIN O'KELLY: Josie, prepareto open the front hatch.
Yes, sir.
Why are we moving?
CAPTAIN O'KELLY: I
don't have a clue.
Disengage autopilot?
Never turned it on.
COPILOT: I'll hit
the override anyway.
CAPTAIN O'KELLY: Do it.
Paul, what the hell?
You didn't get the clear.
Hey.
What the hell was that?
We just started moving, sir.
Everything is fine.
No, but why did it--why did it jerk like that?
There's nothing
to worry about.
FAA emergency.
We need your truck.
Go ahead.
Great.
OFFICER: You in?
I'm good.
Go!
GROUND CONTROL: 672, whatthe hell are you doing?
The plane's moving on its own.
Hey.
Deeper breaths are better.
[breathing deeply]
Goddamn it.
He's moved it.
OFFICER: Hang on!
GROUND CONTROL: 672, 672,you have not been authorized
to proceed to the taxiway.
CAPTAIN O'KELLY: Thisaircraft is moving on its own.
COPILOT: We're
gonna clip his tail!
Cut the computer.
Shut it down.
- I'm trying.
I can't.
No!
[shrieks]
WOMAN: I think we just hitsomething on the runway.
Oh, my god, we're
off the runway.
GROUND CONTROL: Return
to the gate immediately.
CAPTAIN O'KELLY: I'd
like nothing better,
but I can't
[inaudible] autopilot.
Well, what can we do?
[sighs] Strap
yourself in and pray.
We've got no control.
Go!
I'm calling in backup.
Get me to the plane first!
There's no time.
CAPTAIN O'KELLY: Ground control,we are moving on to the runway.
Oh, god.
COPILOT: Holy shit!
Rudder hard to starboard!
I can't do anything.
We're gonna ram him.
No.
Keep going!
GROUND CONTROL: 672, youare crossing into the path
of an incoming flight.
If you maintain your presentcourse, you will collide.
I repeat, you will collide.
We have no control
over the aircraft.
Divert them.
GROUND CONTROL: They'rehalfway through their descent.
I can't divert them.
And be aware of a ground
vehicle under your tail.
That must be that FAA
guy trying to get on.
Josie, go back and
open the rear hatch.
- OK.
If anything goes wrong,
you slam it shut.
We'll talk to him from the air.
Closer!
Get me the rear hatch.
We're following
behind those engines.
The jet blast will kill us!
Do it!
You got one chance here.
GROUND CONTROL: 672,
abort your takeoff.
Abort!
Prepare for collision.
COPILOT: We're dead.
[indistinct shouting]
Great.
Made it.
What the hell's going
on with this airplane?
Take me to the cockpit
and I'll show you.
CAPTAIN O'KELLY:
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the captain speaking.
As I'm sure you noticed, we hada bit of a scare on takeoff.
Rest assured that
everything is fine now.
Fine?
We've got a navigational systemthat's setting its own course.
Yeah, can you bypass
the flight computers?
I don't know.
I've never seen anything
like this before.
I have no idea what's happening.
Like I said, somebody's beenfucking with your computer.
You're from the FAA?
Yeah-- Neil McCabe.
You know something aboutwhat's happening here?
Plane was refitted withthe Oxcilis system, right?
Right.
So were all the
planes that went down.
Someone's altered thechip's programming to give
them control of this plane.
That's impossible.
Is this plane respondingto anything that you do?
No.
Do you have a screwdriver?
What are you going to do?
Yank the problem
out by its roots.
MAN [OVER SPEAKER]:
No, no, no, I
wouldn't do that if I were you.
You extrude that chip andmy fail safe mechanism's
launched--
Immediate engine
failure followed
by a nice muzak medley.
What the hell?
Jesus, who is that?
MAN [OVER SPEAKER]:
How rude of me.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Cain.
I'll be your guide for todayas we ride into darkness,
a ride you won't soon forget.
Then again, it will be thelast ride you ever take.
So sit back, relax, do notattempt to adjust the controls.
I control the horizontal.
[screaming]
I control the vertical.
He's trying to kill us.
[inaudible]
[screaming]
Nothing's responding.
Goddamn it!
[beeping]
CAIN: I'm in control.
I control your lives.
How can he hear us?
Must have bugged the cockpit.
No.
In the other crashes, the tapesin the black box were blank.
That must be what's happeningto the cockpit voice recorder.
Get ground control now.
The radio's dead.
He's cut us off completely.- Man.
How are the gauges?
Everything's steady.
Fuel OK?
Full capacity.
Paul, what are you doing?
No nut job does that to myplane and scares my passengers.
Try and retry the
emergency channels.
Stay here and stay fastened in.
What the hell are you
guys doing up there?
Captain, excuse me.
Everybody all
right back there?
No injuries, no damage,
but the passengers
are freaking out.
WOMAN: You can say that again.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my name is Paul O'Kelly,
and I'm the captain
of this plane.
What's going on?
VARIOUS PASSENGERS: Yeah!
Needless to say,
we're in a crisis.
But I want to assure you thatI and the rest of this flight
crew are going to do
everything we can to get
you down quickly and safely.
He did that.
He controlled the plane!
No, he doesn't.
I may have to rewire andrun off the backup system,
but that moron controls nothing.
[screaming]
Do not make me repeat myself.
This plane is mine.
Once again, enjoy your flight.
WOMAN: We need a doctor!
[distressed yelling]
[crying]
My god, he's gonna kill us!
No!
Please, calm down.
It's OK.
Thank god, he's alive.
We need to move
to a safer place.
I-- I can move thepeople out of first class
to the empty seats in the back.
Perfect.
And see if you can
find neck brace.
What can I do?
Get me some men
to move him, please.
I'm gonna need to ask all ofyou to move to the rear cabin.
Oh, hell no.
I'm not moving.
Please, sir.
This is an emergency.
We'd really appreciateyour cooperation Thank you.
How could you people letsomething like this happen?
I'm not moving
unless she's moving.
I'm moving.
You do the same.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I paid for a
first class ticket.
Yo, Doc, fix him up
so he can do his job
and fly this damn plane.
My husband will
do his best, OK?
Ray, stop complainingand make yourself useful.
Help them get him
into first class.
Fine.
Thanks for helping.
RAY: All right.
Excuse me.
Who is that on TV?
Tell us what's going on!
As soon as we know
what the situation is--
We have a doctor on boardwho's taking care of the--
There's a doctor?
I need a doctor.
Let me help you with
some of these people.
Lean your head back.
That's-- that's it.
Oh.
[grunting]
All right, I helped.
Now you be sure and fix him up.
Yeah.
Thank you, sir.
We appreciate your help.
Yeah.
Yeah, you, captain junior overthere, no waiting for him,
all right?
Get in that damn cockpit
and fly this plane.
Thank you, sir.
Yeah.
All right.
[indistinct angry chatter]
Definite cerebral concussion--although I don't think
he is permanently paralyzed.
We've got no pilot
in that cockpit.
It's him.
[distressed chatter]
No, no, no.
I can't believe this shit.
Why don't you shut up!
Ray, just sit your ass down.
Fasten your seat belt
and shut your trap.
But we need to get
him to a hospital.
Christ.
I'm not able to get anythingon the emergency channels.
Can you keep him stabilized?
Only for a while.
All right.
I'll let the passengers
know what's happened.
Thanks.
OK, and Doc, you
take care of him.
Can-- can I have
your attention please?
[distressed shouting]
Listen.
Who the fuck are you?
VARIOUS PASSENGERS: Yeah!
My name's Neil McCabe.
I'm with the FAA-FBI task forceworking on the recent crashes.
We're gonna crash!
Goddamn it!
Everyone, please, it's OK.
Just please, calm down.
Calm down.
We ain't got no
goddamned pilot.
Not true.
The captain is injured,
but the copilot is fine.
I know we're gonna crashlike they did in Denver.
[inaudible]
Listen!
Listen, we don't know
what we're gonna crash.
Now, what we do know isthat someone on the ground
has found a way to take overthe plane's autopilot system.
So you're saying
the guy on the TV
has control of this plane.
Yes.
PASSENGER: Oh, no!
Listen.
Listen, these are not goingto stay that way for long.
Now, what I need to ask allof you is to remain calm.
The worst thing we
can do is panic.
I promise you, we will find away to land this plane safely.
[indistinct shouting]
Where's my husband?
He's fine.
He's tending to Captain O'Kelly.
How do we know he's
from the FAA, huh?
For all we know, he couldbe working with him.
He could be the onebringing this plane down.
Enough.
That guy risked his life
getting on this plane.
He's definitely here to help us.
Oh, Jesus.
How's Paul?
He'll be OK, right?
If we can get him to
the hospital, and that
means getting down.
Is that a wireless phone?
Yeah.
You can't use that.
Why not?
It'll disrupt the
navigational system.
Right.
OK.
[phone ringing]
Keller.
NEIL: It's Neil.
I'm on the--
Where the fuck are you?
We're in crisis mode here.
- I'm on Flight 672.
- Oh, my god.
That was you?
Turn on your com cam.
I was right, Sam.
I know you were.
How are you doing up there?
The passengers
are scared to death.
The captain has been
seriously injured too.
We've got to land thisthing as soon as possible.
All the avionics arebeing controlled by a guy
who calls himself Cain.
All air-to-groundcommunications are knocked out.
We're talking
radios, you name it.
The guy's wired the
cockpit for sound.
He can overhear
everything we say.
And plus, if we yank thechip, the engines shut down.
Does he have the
auxiliary systems too?
I think so.
But I'm not sure.
What does he want?
I don't know yet.
But as far as I know, this guy'scrashed three planes already
without asking for anything.
Well, he's got
to want something!
Unless he's a
total psychopath.
This guy's-- he's got
to have a background
in aviation computers.
You check and you see who'sworked on the entire systems,
and especially Oxcilis.
Can you access the
computer flight path?
We're trying to keep
the air clear for you.
But it would help if we knewwhere he was taking you.
I'll see what I can do.
Josie?
Can you find me a blankpiece of paper and something
to write with?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
And Neil, you broke
every rule in the book,
but I'm really glad
you're up there.
Marston?
MARSTON: Yes, sir?
Look at the
computer personnel,
starting with the
Oxcilis project.
Contact Quantico.
Get them cracking
on a psych profile.
What can we conclude about a guynamed Cain, first murdered, uh,
killed his brother.
Go, guys.
Let's go!We haven't that much time!
Perfect.
I'm sending the
coordinates to you now.
I don't recognize them.
But the longitude's
definitely East Coast.
That's not good, Neil.
The whole Eastern Seaboardis reporting severe wind
sheer and clear air turbulence.- Rock steady.
We'll get right back to you.
Just help us get down, OK?
How's he doing?
He's unconscious.
But he's OK.
How are you doing?
Me, I'm-- I'mconscious, but I'm not OK.
Doesn't seem that way to me.
I just--
I don't know how much longerI can keep it together.
You can.
You're doing a great job.
Thanks.
Today's supposed to
my last day at work.
Thought it'd be an easy flight.
[indistinct yelling]
WOMAN: Oh.
RAY: Let's go.
Get up.
Got to move.
WOMAN: Hey, quit
trying to take my seat.
RAY: No, you [inaudible].
[indistinct yelling]
See what I mean, easy.
I was the first class.
I should have the row back here.
Would you be quiet, please?
My son is trying to sleep.
What?
You are being an ass.
VARIOUS PASSENGERS: Yeah.WOMAN: Yeah, that's for sure.
Please be calm.
Just please be calm.
These seats are
way too small .
You got to do something.
I know we're in
a scary situation.
No, I'm in an
uncomfortable situation.
That's different.
I'm going back to first
class, where it's safer.
Ray, this is
not the "Titanic."
There aren't any lifeboats.
You want a row?
There's a private
row in the back.
[clapping and cheering]
So happy.
Hey, what's up, baby?
Don't I know you?
No.
My name's Ray.
Coordinates line up toCalvert Cliffs, Maryland.
What the hell is
in Calvert Cliffs?
Oh, my god.
You track it?
Neil Ferris McCabe,
Social Security, 343-4--
You know.
I know everything.
As a matter of fact, I justfinished draining your 401[k]
and registered you
as a sex offender
with your local law
enforcement agency.
Fuck you.
No, don't worry about it.
You're not gonna be aroundlong enough for any of this
to bother you.
Oh, and by the way, I wouldhave given you the coordinates.
All you had to do was ask.
[phone ringing]
What?
Hang up the
speakerphone, Neil, now.
What's going on?
He's taking you toCalvert Cliffs, Maryland.
Oh, Jesus.
Tell me you guys got aplan for this because, uh,
I'm drawing a blank right now.
You've got to find
a way to reroute it.
[inaudible]---- he's
wired the cockpit.
He's monitoring everything I do.
Did you find
out what he wants?
He still hasn't
made any demands?
Nothing.
You got to get manual
control or reroute it.
It's up to you.
Shit.
Listen, if I cut the connectionbetween the hydraulics
and the chip, can
you land manually?
Are you kidding?
That's insane.
Listen, this is a crisis.
I realize that, all right?
The autopilot is essential, OK?
We've to cut it.
Listen to me.
The autopilot is not
a luxury, all right?
It's wired directly
to the hydraulics.
If you cut it, youalmost guarantee a crash.
All right.
We've got to alter
the land coordinates
without him knowing.
Well, where we are headed?
Baltimore area.
OK.
There's only one
option I can think of.
This is a particularly
nasty virus.
Now, if I can load this onto his computer, occupy him,
maybe it'll act
as a distraction.
And while he's
scrubbing his system,
you reset for Baltimore
International.
OK.
There's a jack you can useunderneath the cockpit.
JOSIE: I can take you there.
Great.
I need schematics.
Of course.
We're gonna make
this work, right?
Right.
The schematics.
[inaudible], thank you.
Good luck.
Come on.
How's he doing?
Still unconscious
but holding steady.
Cain might not
notice if we can go
in through an auxiliary jack.
There, it should beright behind the fuse box.
OK, ready?
Yep.
You got it?
You got it.
Should be up here.
OK.
[inaudible].
Is that it?
Yeah.
NEIL: Which one?
What do you mean which one?
There are two.
Which is the main?- Well, how should I know?
I'm not an engineer!
It's OK.
Just tell me what it says.
You know, I made plans
to start a business,
have a nice, stable life.
I mean, this was my
last day at work.
You told me.
Now just--
I don't like having thiskind of responsibility, OK?
I make the wrong
decision and people die.
Sh.
Take a deep breath.
Just tell me what is says.
OK.
Um, um, left is auxiliary one,and right says auxiliary two.
You decide.
Right-- use the
one on the right!
Got it.
Is it working?
Told you.
Stand by.
Roger.
Now.
It's working.
We're reset for
Baltimore International.
We got it.
[whistling] Neil,
I give you an inch,
and you, you take a mile.
Do not, I repeat, do
not underestimate me.
I wrote the goddamn
Brethren virus
when you were still in diapers!
I'm disappointed in you.
And you know, Neil,
you're gonna have to do
a little better than that.
You have no idea who
you're fucking with!
you are fucking with.
Campers, attention, campers,it appears that some people
are incapable of followingsimple instructions
and are trying to ruin
the fun for everyone.
So I'm gonna have to
teach you all a lesson.
I'm sorry.
Neil!
Hold on.
Brace yourself.
[screaming]
[inaudible]!
I got you.
[indistinct yelling]
It's too many Gs.
The plane can't take it.
[distant screaming]
It's amazing the limitsone can push [inaudible]..
[sobbing and crying]
Ah!
[screaming]
[inaudible]
Stop crying, stop.
Sh.
Simmer.
Stop crying.
Stop.
Shh.
[inaudible]
Stop crying!
Because I have a very specialsurprise for all of you.
Now, don't tell anyone this.
But you're my favorites.
I mean, Honolulu,
you know, I just
dropped them into the Pacificwithout introducing myself.
And, yeah, I worked out
my kinks with Seattle.
And Denver is something I--
I always wanted to do.
What's with this
crazy motherfuck?
The brilliance of flight672 will be the inspiration
of miles of empty canvas.
Songs will be written.
And moves will be made.
You're going down in ablazing, blast of history.
What's he talking about?
But I'm sure yourwhite knight from the FAA
has already told
you all about that.
Happy trails, campers.
Where are we going?
Believe me, you
don't want to know.
No.
No, I do want to know.
Where are we going?
Calvert Cliffs, Maryland.
Well, what's there?
Largest nuclear reactor
on the East Coast.
Gonna kills us all.
Are you OK?
Stay calm.
I'm here.
I'm right here.
I got to get out.
I have to get out of here.
He's gonna kill us!
I swear to god.
[inaudible]
He's gonna kill us.
Hey!
[inaudible].
He's gonna kill us.
Hey, you OK?
[indistinct shouting]
Please get out of here!
Whoa.
- [inaudible] you.
[inaudible]
Let me go.
Come on [inaudible].
What are you doing?
[inaudible]
Let me go.
What the fuck are you doing?
We don't want you
to hurt yourself.
[grunting and groaning]
PANICKING MAN:
What are you doing?
NEIL: Whoa.
Whoa.
What are you doing?
Ah!
Excuse me.
Excuse me, where
is he taking us?
We're going to
land this plane.
If you know something,I think it is your duty--
[inaudible] should havecaught this in the last check.
Hey!
Where are you going?
Check?
What you talking about?
FEMALE PASSENGER:
Where are you going?
Excuse me!
That Cain guy is
just crazy, understand?
He's-- he's just sayingthings to make us all scared.
Philip!
WOMAN: What if it's
true what he's doing--
BOY: Dad!
You guys OK?
Stay with us now, Dad, OK?
Philip, what's happening?
Who's that man?
What are you talking about?
We go into the Oxcilis systemevery six months for software
upgrades and fine tuning,I guess-- some glitch
specific to this type of plane.
Shit.
Do you know when this
plane last went in?
Yeah.
About a month ago.
Ah, a little nervous
here, but I'm not
gonna let you bleed to death.- Ah.
Ow.
I think my arm's broken.
It hurts.
Ow!
Owie.
[inaudible]
You're not becoming
a good person, are you?
Please, you know
me better than that.
All right, you'll be OK.
WOMAN PASSENGER: Doctor?
Doctor, we need
your help back here.
Do you have to go, Dad?
Do you?
Go, Philip.
It's what you do.
Duty calls.
I'll just go, hm?
I think it's broken.
- Let me have a look.
- Ow!
Owie!
- Let me see.
Let me see.
- Ow.
Like I said, nice
fucking security.
What are you getting at?
I'll show you.
Here's a list of
last month's checks.
Now, this ID's the numberfor your plane, right?
Right.
I told you we were there.Wait a second.
Hold on.
AV29367, that's the flightfrom Honolulu that crashed.
Here's Denver.
And there's Seattle.
Holy shit.
Doc.
Hey, doc, she's, uh--
she hit her head back there.
Do you think you could
come take a look?
OK.
You keep an eye on
the nervous breakdown.
I'll take care of this.
- OK.
[computer sounds]
Sam, I'm sending you--
What the hell was
going on up there?
You people were
all over the radar.
That's putting it mildly.
Listen, I'm emailing
you list now
of planes that have been
in the Oxcilis group
recently for fixes.
You ground them all.
What are you talking about?
Oxcilis brings in these planesevery six months for checks.
The three planes that
crashed, and this one,
were all in the
plant a month ago.
Now--
Neil, I got him,
Wilson Rundle.
Way to go, Rudy.
Worked writing code
in the Oxcilis project.
Send him this info.
OK, Neil, the consensus
is that this guy's
a brilliant coder but crazy.
He was badly burned in
a fire at the plant.
Oxcilis gave him a big pay outprobably to keep him quiet.
So he quietly
went away, knowing
just when the planeswould be back in the plant
and vulnerable.
Looks that way.
SAM: We'll get
right back to you.
Paul.
I'm right here, Paul.
I can't feel my arms.
It's a temporary paralysis.
I'm sorry you won't beable to move for a while.
Who's got control
of the plane?
He still does.
So I haven't seen my
dad for like two years.
And, um-- and I
finally found him.
And he had been in thehospital for a couple of weeks.
And I-- and I justreally wanted to see him.
[crying] I really wanted to--
BOY: Dad, come back.
You'll see him, [inaudible].
You'll see him.
I want my dad.
It's OK.
Dad!
Mama's here.
Will you be OK?
Dad, come back.
Come back.
It's OK.
BOY: Dad!
Dad!
Oh, ma'am, I'm sorry.
You really can't be up here.
Nonsense.
Go be with your family.
I'll take over
from here, Doctor.
BOY: Dad!
Ma'am, this man is
seriously injured.
I need to be here.
Your wife and son needs you.
We don't have much time left.
Go now.
Go be with them.
BOY: Dad!
DR. PHILIP: Thank you.
How are you feeling, Captain?
I know you.
You're a nurse.
Not really.
I just play one on TV.
Ah.
Right.
You're Bernadette DeCoer.
You're on "Love
in the Afternoon."
15 years, until theydecided I was too old to play
the sexy love interest.
Ah.
I don't think you're
too old for all that.
You will do just
fine, Captain.
Papa's going to
stay right here, OK?
BOY: I'm so glad
you're back Dad.
Last known address was
right here in Chicago.
I'm setting Rudy out witha SWAT team right now.
Rock steady, Neil.
We're coming down
the homestretch.
Once we find Cain's
system, I'll link up
you and Rudy to go do thatvoodoo that you do so well.
Are you ready to
rumble, kemosabe?
You better believe
it, chief, After all,
it's a binary world, right?
Yes or no, black or white.
Yeah.
Now you're talking.
Let's do this.
[guns clicking]
[beeping]
We've got company.
I [inaudible].
[ding] Ladies and gentlemen,it's time to begin
our in-flight entertainment.
Now, it is R and has not beenedited for content, but--
BOY: It's that guy, Dad.
CAIN: --I think we're allmature enough to handle it.
Now, please close
your window shades.
And if you--
Everyone, fasten
your seat belt.
--headphones
purchase head phone
from one of our
lovely attendants,
don't worry about it.
This one's on me.
MAXINE: Fasten your seat belt.
CAIN: The particulars may be--
Oh, my god.
CAIN: --obscure, so I'll
provide a play by play.
Fucking Boneheads International,or whatever FBI stands for,
are knock, knock,
knocking at my door.
They're he-re.
But I'm not.
The number you dialed
has been disconnected.
Sit tight.
Sit tight, yeah.
Sit tight's what I do best.
CAIN: [inaudible] hot and stickyin night in downtown Chicago,
as the FBI--
[sighs] nowhere to
run, nowhere to hide--
in full riot gear [inaudible].
And there they are.
Yeah.
Hey, guys.
Hey there.
Peek-a-boo.
What the hell do you want?
What do I want?
I want my genius to berealized and for the world
to regret throwing away andnot cherishing that genius.
I want my place in history.
But most of all, I
want to watch it burn.
You don't have to do this!
[sputtering] Shit.
You know, you're gonna
miss the best part, OK?
Come in.
Welcome to my
world, motherfucker!
[indistinct exclamations]
Oh shit!
[gunfire]
[inaudible], up, please.
Thank you.
Oh, that's got to smart.
[gunfire]
[laughing]
Jesus!
That's your buddy Rudy!
FBI AGENT: The whole
place is booby trapped.
Get me the hell out of here!
Come on.
[inaudible]
[laughing]
[gasping]
Access Road West should
get you out of here.
Move it [inaudible], kemosabe.
That's kemo.
Come on, buddy, move it.
Get your ass out of there.
What the hell do you want?
[sputtering]
Oh.
Let's go.
Maybe they'll find his teeth.
You piece of shit.
Ah, temper, temper.
Neil, Rudy was a moron.
I mean, really, I
did him a favor.
You know the pain
you're causing.
Pain?
What do you know about pain?
[indistinct exclamations]
Are you afraid?
Because you damn well better be.
[grunting]
WOMAN: Hey!
No!
MAN: Stop him!
Don't!
Let me go!
Get out of my way!
Let go of the door!
[rush of air]
[yelling]
[screaming]
Ah!
Looks like someone
lost their [inaudible]..
[screaming]
Grab a strap.
No!
Get it off!
This is supposed to
be my last night of work
not my last night
on planet Earth.
WOMAN: Help!
We need help back here.
BOY: No!
No!
No.
Don't touch me!
Stop it!
Get off!
Please, Tobaz,
keep this on, please.
Keep it on.
- Yours first.
Yours first.
He won't [inaudible]
if you don't.
Here you go.
[inaudible] OK.
It's all right.
There you go.
DR: PHILIP: Breathe.
Help him.
He was hit in the head.
Breathe.
[gasping] Wh-- what happened?
What are you talking about?
This always happens in coach.
[laughter turned to coughing]
You can't-- that's
murdering US citizens.
So is allowing that planeto crash into that plant.
Look, Keller, I do not wantto shoot that plane down.
Then give them more time.
Call off the jets.
All of my training, my
entire career and life
have been devoted to protectingthis country and government.
If I allow them to continue,I fail that mission.
Give Neil a chance
to regain control.
If what our special weaponsteam saw has any indication,
Cain has everything covered.
We don't know that for sure!
Well, I know my
hands are tied!
Once they reach
77-degrees longitude,
I've got to take them down.
We have to get to
a lower altitude,
at least to 15,000
feet for the masks off.
None of the controls respond.
We don't have
enough oxygen. We
burn through it
at this altitude,
people are going to start dying!
There's only one
thing I can think of.
JOSIE: What?
If I cut the connectionsbetween the chip
and the major systems, wecontrol the plane manually.
But if you cut
the connections,
the engines
automatically shut off.
We could restart themonce we have manual control.
Manual control?
Flying on of these thingsmanual is hard enough.
Landing is next to impossible.
If everything's perfect,10 to 1 you'd still crash,
even with an experienced crew.
And I can't handle it!
You could still get usdown, guide us through it.
Is there any other option?
There must be something.
There's not another option.
Let's do it.
He's bringing us down.
We're beginning our descent.
Friends, countrymen,
lend me your ears.
Our journey is
drawing to a close.
I'm sorry.
I'm not very good at goodbyes.
Don't worry.
We'll-- we'll see
other soon-- in hell.
It's Independence Day.
You'll have just enough fuel toensure the greatest fireworks
the world has ever seen.
He's dumping fuel.
He's dumping fuel!
[inaudible]
Why didn't you
tell us about this?
We have a right to know.
- Would it have helped?
BERNADETTE: We deserve
an explanation.
I deal with what's
in front of me.
And what's in front of
me is a way out of this.
Neil, you have to go downto the wiring compartment.
Josie, move the
captain to the cockpit
so he can see the readings.
Now, tell me exactly whatI have to do down there.
We need to keep contact
to a minimum in case
Cain overhears us.
OK, there are
three main components
hooked into the
autopilot, the ailerons,
the elevator, and the rudder.
Once you cut out all three,the engines will cut off.
If we can restart,
we'll be in control.
You all need to be readyto take over the second I
disconnect the wires.
All right.
Josie, Neil, there aretwo F-16s flying with us.
Is that good or bad?
They could be here
to help us, right?
I don't think so.
OK, Neil, you need
to cut the red wire,
then the black, then
the green, got it?
Red, black, green.
OK, you guys.
Sam, you can't do this!
I'm trying to buy you
as much time as I can.
Trying isn't
gonna cut it, Sam!
You patch me through
to the pilots.
Jesus, Neil, you
know I can't do that.
77 degrees is the cut off.
You got that?
At your speed, you've
got about five minutes.
You patch me through
to the pilots, Sam.
There may be another
way out of this.
Let me see what I can do.
I'm in.
Great.
FIGHTER JET PILOT:
1672, delta one-niner,
do you read me, over?
Delta one-niner, this is 672.
Listen, you need to
give us some time.
We're about to regainmanual control of the plane.
I need more time.
FIGHTER JET PILOT: On whoseauthority are you speaking?
This isn't about authority!
This isn't about what's right.
You're about to shoot down aplaneload of American citizens.
Sorry, 672, I have my orders.
No.
Wait.
Listen, there's a chance
you can get out of this
without blood on your hands.
I'm gonna disconnect everythingand restart the engines.
CAIN: Hey, Neil.
And just a few more minutesis all I'm asking for.
FIGHTER JET PILOT: 672, youare 80 miles from kill zone.
Neil, answer me.
Neil, I need to talk to you!
I'm right here, Cain.
I'm feeling a little strange.
We're feeling a
little strange too.
You know the cabin's
depressurized.
FIGHTER JET PILOT: 672,
70 miles from cut off.
Two more minutes.Two more minutes, please.
Hos did you lose a door, huh?
You know, so I hope
you know I didn't
have anything do with that.
I wouldn't do
something like that.
It's beneath me.
People got scared.
You got us all scared, Cain.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
That's what I've
been thinking about.
FIGHTER JET PILOT: 672, you'reat 50 miles and counting.
Delta one-niner, I haveto end communication now.
But I'm about to regain
control of the plane.
Two more minutes,
and these people
have a real chance tosurvive this, over and out.
I'm feeling something
[inaudible],, Neil.
What's that?
Out.
I don't know, man.
I don't know if, uh,
what I'm doing is, uh--
I don't know if what
I'm doing is right.
I can't-- I can't stop seeingthe screaming faces melting.
It's not too late to stop.
Trust me, Neil, it's not fun.
I swear to god it was
gonna change the world.
Look what they
fucking did to me.
So you know what?
Screw 'em.
I'll change the
world however I want.
Neil?
Hey, Neil?
Neil, listen to me.
Hey, Neil, I'm just
fucking with you.
[mad laughter]
FIGHTER JET PILOT:
672, what's going on?
672, [inaudible].
[screaming]
[inaudible]
[mad laughter]
FIGHTER JET PILOT: 30
miles from kill zone.
[inaudible]
[laughter] Oh,
and I must say--
I must say, Neil, nice jobwith the fighter pilots.
I mean, really, you
are [inaudible]..
I mean, really, it
was-- it was touching.
It was touching.
I mean, really, it
got my heart strings.
FIGHTER JET PILOT: Requestpermission to lock our target,
sir.
I mean, [inaudible] going--
you're all-- you're all twomore minutes-- two more minutes,
and these people
got to meet Jesus.
FIGHTER JET PILOT:
Razor, lock on target.
RAZOR: Arming missile.
I thought you
were going to start
talking about moms and flagsand apple pie and all that shit.
Hey, Neil, you're
a fucking genius.
[laughs]
Hey, Cain.
Yeah?
I'm just fucking with you.
It's done.
Everything's cut.
Get ready.
[inaudible]
[screaming]
Oh, come on.
FIGHTER JET PILOT: 672,
what is your status?
Delta one-niner, we haveregained control of the plane.
It's all up to you now.
God help us.
No!
No-o-o!
That's it.
The engines are cut.
Ah!
Two buttons below
the throttles.
You see them, one and two?
But do it sequentially.
We'll get a hot start.
You are going to end up a pileof twisted metal, burnt bodies.
No matter what you
do, you're gonna be--
you're going down.
You are not going
to make this, Neil.
FIGHTER JET PILOT:
672, we are locked on.
What is your status?
[inaudible] are on.
Pull back on the
control sticks--
control sticks, it's there toyour right-- to your right.
What?
NEIL: Hold on.
Hold on!
FIGHTER JET PILOT:
[inaudible] orders.
Pull back!
Ah!
Neil, you need
to get up here now.
We need your help.
10 seconds.
I will be there in 10 seconds.
[inaudible]
throttle, more power.
More power!
CAIN: You're gonna end up a pileof twisted metal, burnt bodies.
Don't listen to him!
He can't touch us now.
FIGHTER JET PILOT:Standby to launch missile.
We need more power.
Push forward on the throttle.
More power!
Come on!
I'm trying!
CAIN: Fireworks.
Oh, my god.Is that what I think it is?
[screaming]
CAIN: [inaudible]
Calvert Cliffs.
[grunting]
I can see you.
And I'm telling you,you're not gonna make it.
You're not.
You're gonna [inaudible].
NEIL: We got it!
[screaming]
FIGHTER JET PILOT: Launch hermy command, Razor, in 10--
You're not gonna make it.FIGHTER JET PILOT: --9, 8--
NEIL: Come on!
FIGHTER JET PILOT: --7--
CAIN: [inaudible]
FIGHTER JET PILOT: --5,
4, 3, 2, [inaudible]..
[screaming in the cabin]
Did we do it?
FIGHTER JET PILOT:
Nice work, 672.
Delta one-niner
returning to base.
That wasn't as spectacularas I would have liked.
But let me assure you ofone thing, the demise of--
Hey, Cain, shut the fuck up!
Man, that felt good.
OK, all right,
what do we do now?
We've got to find some
place to set her down.
Where?
Wherever we can.
What's going on?
Cain no longer has
control of this plane.
[cheering]
NEIL: Sam.
Neil!
We've been trying
to get through.
We did it, Sam.
We disconnected him.
We're flying the plane manually.
[cheering]
We'll clear every
runway at Baltimore
International for you.
It's only 20 miles away.
The navigational systemsare completely knocked out.
When I say we're landing
manually, I mean it.
Jesus.
You got enough fuel to
hold out till daylight?
Cain dumped most of it.
And the fuel that we
do have is going fast.
We had to restart the engines,which knocked down about 20%
of what was left.
I'm unable to
operate the controls.
So I'm gonna have to
walk Neil through it.
We're gonna do everythingwe can up here, Sam.
Just make it as easy
in us as you can.
You got it.
Neil, there's a couple ofthings you need to know.
First, we've grounded everyairplane equipped with Oxcilis.
Good.
I got some bad news.
I know about Rudy, Sam.
I'm sorry.
Sam, [inaudible] best.
OK, you heard the man, people.
Let's make it easy on him.
Saddle up!
DISPATCHER: All units
to runway three.
Mobilize full resting
units to runway three.
GROUND CONTROL:
All inbound traffic
to Baltimore International beadvised the airport is closed.
MAN: Move it!
GROUND CONTROL [MALE
SPEAKER]: 1846,
you are not clear for takeoff.
Return to gate 17.
GROUND CONTROL [FEMALE
SPEAKER0: Flight 733,
reduce air speed
to do 2-5-0 knots.
Cut right 0-1-5 and
divert to Dulles, over.
GROUND CONTROL [MALE
SPEAKER]: All air
traffic has been diverted.
The runways are clear.
All right, Neil.
You are go for landing.
Runways are clear?
We've done everythingbut tear down the terminal.
OK, just want to remind
you boys, we that land
using the ILS system
or radio beacons.
It's visual all the way.
OK, here's the plan.
Circle around and beginyour descent toward runway
two over the terminal.
Over the terminal?
Are you crazy?
We've evacuated it.
Land in the opposite
direction, and you
should have enough room.
Doesn't that send us
directly into the Bay?
There's an empty
field beyond runway two.
OK.
You make sureeverybody's out of there.
Because we run out of fuel,we're gonna be coasting in.
Roger that.
You're gonna make it, though.
Ease back on the throttle.
Start taking us down.
[bing]
OK, folks, we're
gonna try to land.
Now, I know we've
been through some hair
stuff here to put it mild.
While I can't promise youthat the worst is over,
I can promise you thatthose of us in this cockpit
will do everything we can
to get you through this.
See you on the ground.
[sigh]
One of you needs to
extend the flaps to slow
us down for final approach.
You got it?
CAPTAIN O'KELLY: It's a blackswitch over on your right.
Yeah.
Flaps extending .
Got it.
[beeping]
Christ, the flaps
didn't go down.
CAPTAIN O'KELLY: Pull
on that [inaudible] now!
Ah!
GROUND CONTROL: 672
is losing altitude.
[screaming]
Hold on!
GROUND CONTROL: 672
is going to tank.
They're going to crash.
Get the flaps back up now!
Ah!
Look at that!
672 is back in the air!
[crying]
We're burning through fuel!
Goddamn it.
Talk to me, Neil.
What's happening up there?
One of our flaps is stuck.
We can use one on each wing,but it's still not gonna get
us down at an acceptable speed.
And any second now we'regonna be running on fumes.
We're not gonna
pull this off, are we?
Keep it sturdy as you can.
Need to be lined up.
There should be rows of
white lights down there.
Can you see them?
- Yes.
We're right in line.
We're lined up.
Are you ready for us?
That's affirmative.
God speed.
Stead now.
I got it.
Can't get enough leverage.
For Christ's sake
you're not gonna
get any leverage if
you're splattered
all over the windshield.
Control the levers
as best you can.
Are we lowering
some of the flaps?
CAPTAIN O'KELLY:
Yeah, one on each wing
should slow us down some.
Use the rudder to line
us up with the runways.
You swerve, and we're history.
Stay focused.
We're out of fuel!
Aw, let go of the throttle.
It doesn't matter anymore!
Just use the rudder.
And for God's sake,
keep us level!
OK, lower the wheels.
Got it.
They wheels are stuck!
- Can we land?
- Should I pull up?
Ah, it's too late goddamn it.
But we can do it!
It won't be pretty,
but we can do it.
GROUND CONTROL: 672,
land clear [inaudible]..
Come on!
Hold on!
Oh, god.
[screaming]
Hold it steady, Neil!
Hold what steady?
[screaming]
[sirens]
[crying and murmuring]
MAXINE: Everyone,
unfasten your seat belt
and slowly and calmly follow me.
[cheering]
That's just great.
We did it.
GROUND CONTROL: 672 has landedand is safe on the ground!
[cheering]
We made it.
Josie!
Talk to me.
[sirens]
Thank you, Captain.
[grunting]
- Oh, my side.
Oh, you just
hang in there, OK?
Help's gonna be on the way.
We did.
We made it through
the hard part.
Everything's gonna be fine, OK?
[sirens]
We did it.
Never again-- I am
never flying again.
Amen to that one.
Listen, I've been
meaning to, you know,
apologize about that stuffway back in school, you know?
I want to start fresh.
Maybe, like, take you to alittle dinner or something,
you know.
But I promise, this timeI'll keep my hands to myself.
[laughing] Maybe this
time you don't have to.
What?
[inaudible]
Watch the hands.
Still hard to get.
Come here.
[laughter]
Neil?
[inaudible]
I-- I--
[crying]
It's OK.
We made it.
Yeah.
I told you.
Now, you're gonna be OK.
Yeah.
You're gonna see your daddy?
OK.
Hm?
MAN: Can we get
some help over here?
Keep him steady.
Don't worry.
I'll ride with him
to the hospital.
She's got me covered, Doc.
Don't worry about [inaudible].
It's time you go and be
with your family now.
You've done all you can.
Besides, I'm beginning
to like this role.
Is there [inaudible], Captain?
CAPTAIN O'KELLY:
That's just great.
Take care of your husband.
[sirens]
Dad.
Dad!
Let's go!
Yes, son, we're going
to the White House, hm?
Yeah?
MAN: Zoe Michaels?
Zoe Michaels?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm Zoe.
Miss Michaels, your father--
Oh, God, what is it?
No, he's doing much better.
If you want, you
can come with me.
And I'll take you to see him.
He's been asking about you.- He has?
Yeah.
Come on.
OK.
It's over.
[inaudible]
Ah.
Said he wanted
to see things burn.
He was on a suicide mission.
Wherever he is, it's close.
We need to get this arm set.
Looks like you may
have a fractured rib.
I'm taking you to
County General.
I'll be right there.
I'd like that.
[ambulance starts]
Be careful.
Go.
How was your flight?
JOSIE: No!
Adios, kemosabe.
[inaudible]!
It's Cain.
He's here!
Woo!
[laughing] [whistling]
NEIL: It's him!
Come on!
Ooh.
It's Cain!
[laughing]
Shit.
Hey!
Get back here!
Welcome to Baltimore
International Airport,
where your life on on
Earth shall be nasty,
[inaudible], and brutish.
Ah!
You better-- you reallybetter fasten your seat belt.
[laughter] Come on.
Ooh-hoo.
[laughter]
[grunting]
What a rush.
[zapping]
Oh.
Nice to meet you, kemosabe.
But you know what?
You're a little too late.
That [inaudible] second string.
But in 10 minutes, we're
all gonna be toast.
It's going to CalvertCliffs with no one aboard!
[inaudible]
[grunting and groaning]
Bitch!
She is so beautiful.
You want to know what
my pain is all about?
[sounds of fighting]
Ah!
Go.
Go!
No!
[screaming]
[explosions]
Yes or no.
Do or die.
Ow.
You're hurt.
Yeah.
Let's get you to a hospital.
That's a good idea.
Yeah.
You got any plans
for the Fourth?
No, why?
Well, I was thinking maybewe could take the train,
watch the fireworks overthe capital [inaudible]??
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Train's are good.
NEIL: Yeah, trains are good.
[music playing]