(panting)
Jim Till.
October 27th.
I feel I better start recording
what's been going on around here
because I fear I'm losing my
mind
but I'm not crazy.
There are orbs here.
I seen like, three of 'em.
They're like those transparent
balls you see on TV
and in photographs.
I'm not going crazy, but like
on the precipice.
Something's going on in my
head.
January 27th.
It's three AM.
I followed a little girl into
the warehouse here.
Where is she?
I need to talk to her.
Little girl?
Where are you?
Where are you...
Little girl!
They make you see things that
you don't wanna see.
They make you do things that
you don't wanna do.
They like to make you afraid.
Whatever scares you the
most...
they know what it is.
I think I pissed them off.
June seventh.
Something's up.
They're coming back.
They're coming again.
They're, like, inside my head.
I gotta get into this tank.
I'll be safe in this tank.
(panting)
Ah!
(Banging)
No!
Ah!
(Otherworldly sounds)
(grunting)
Ah, aah!
(Screaming)
(banging)
Come on, come on, come on!
My name is Jim Till.
I'm an assistant professor
of theoretical physics at
Stanford
and I've encountered a
phenomenon
that I can't explain.
I came through this door and I
looked to my left
and sitting right around there,
by those boxes at the very end,
was aa woman dressed in black.
Babe, we gotta go.
Come on, pack it up.
See this guy.
- He's Ashen's brother. -Wow?
- Ashen has an older brother.
- Okay?
- Ashen, from the winery? -I
know who Ashen is.
Why are you treating it like
it's some conspiracy
that he has an older brother?
Dax, he talked to us
for an hour about his family
and not once did he mention he
had a brother,
let alone one that's a
theoretical physicist.
I mean, don't you think that's
a little strange?
No, I don't.
Self-centered little rich
pricks
don't like to gloat about
their more accomplished
siblings.
You're right. I'm sorry. I'm
just so excited about this.
This is an amazing, amazing
opportunity.
Out of all the paranormal
investigators,
we were the first to be chosen
to investigate one of the most
haunted places
in the United States. Do you
know why?
Because Ashen has a hard on
for you.
Yes, and because I'm a kick
ass producer.
And you're very humble.
Drink this. I don't think you
need it but
This is coffee.
Yes, it is.
Very good coffee.
I can't have coffee. It's not
good for the baby.
Shit. I'm sorry. I know. I
keep forgetting.
You keep forgetting? Wow.
That makes me feel all fuzzy
inside.
Stop. Can you have tea?
- Can I get you tea? -Yes, I
can have tea.
Decaf? Organic?
Baby friendly? Anything else?
Come on. Let's go!
Little bit of eye candy for
the network execs,
because they tend to like that
kinda thing.
Yeah. Actually, I think this
is
Mike's first and last day with
us, right?
All right, and that's my
loving girlfriend.
- Okay. -Mike.
- I got you a coffee. -Oh,
nice.
Thank you, brother.
And you are...
Hi, I'm Jason Meeks
and this is a digital voice
recorder
for capturing EVPs.
Or...
recording ghosty ghosts.
And have you ever recorded
one?
I believe I have.
On several occasions.
With all the cell phones
polluting our airwaves,
you're still convinced
that what you're hearing are
ghosts?
Sarah's a little bit of a
skeptic
and also a little bit of a
ho-bag.
Jason still believes in the
tooth fairy.
For the record, I stopped
believing in the tooth fairy
months ago.
And what do you do here?
I'm Maya Peterson.
I'm the sound dude.
Mike.
Mike?
Could you not do that, please?
Use the fish eye lens.
(Laughing)
Mike!
Stop!
Tilt/shift that ass!
Theresa!
Hi, I'm Sarah Hall and I'm
standing
in front of the King's Ransom
Winery,
located in Guerneville,
California.
King's Ransom is widely
considered
as one of the most haunted
places in the United States,
and not until now has any
paranormal investigations been
allowed. No.
You know what? Since we're
stopped,
I need to check the white
balance.
Maya?
Awesome. Thanks, baby.
Should I take from the top, or
just where I stopped?
- Keep going. We're gonna cut
in. -No, no, no.
Take it from the top, you're
doing great.
We're gonna take it from the
top.
(Blows raspberry)
Okay, ow.
Hi, I'm Sarah Hall and I'm
standing
in front of the King's Ransom
Winery,
located in Guerneville,
California.
King's Ransom is widely
considered
as one of the most haunted
places in the United States.
This is the only weekend out
of the entire year
that the winery is closed
down,
and the owner, Ashen Till, has
given us full access.
So for the next 48 hours,
we have this entire place to
ourselves.
It actually used to be a
logging company
before it became a winery.
That's my great-grandfather.
And this was his wife, Rachel.
So that's the famous Rachel
Till.
She's beautiful.
She was the first suicide.
When was that?
1932.
They said that she heard
voices.
She stabbed herself to
death...
Thirteen times.
How does somebody stab
themselves 13 times?
You think after the first one,
they'd be like "ow," you know,
and stop.
You'd think.
And who else committed
suicide?
Rory Devink, my grandfather's
second wife.
And how did she kill herself?
She also stabbed herself to
death.
The same way.
Thirteen times?
I'm not sure how many.
And what about the third girl?
Beatrice Blaine.
But she was murdered.
Tell me about that.
It was 1972.
Her father Joe Blaine, he was
a machinist working here.
They say that he raped her.
And evidently he got her
pregnant,
and to cover it up, he killed
her.
How?
(Screaming)
He threw her down on these
blades.
Pretty gruesome.
You think there may be a
demonic presence here?
I mean, that's a really evil
thing to do.
I don't know about that.
I mean, I definitely think
Joe Blaine was a disturbed
individual.
And what's the auger for?
It's how we crush the grapes.
Okay, so, so far we have the
two suicides and a murder,
so we're missing the third
suicide.
Supposedly after Joe murdered
his daughter,
he went into his office and
shot himself in the head...
13 times.
It was a joke.
So the house was built in the
1800s.
The late 1800s.
When we were kids, my brother
Jim dared us
to spend the night here.
That's a beautiful piano over
there.
What year is that?
It's 1870s.
Square grand.
Made out of rosewood.
I wouldn't touch it.
And this, uh...
this was Rory Devink's
bedroom.
Your grandfather's...
- ...second wife. -Second wife.
Yeah.
But she hardly stayed here.
She was paranoid that the
world was coming to an end
and she built a bomb shelter
and literally lived in it.
I guess she went a little nuts
because she started dining on
rats.
Ew...
And where is this bomb
shelter?
The entrance is in the garden
behind the house.
So this is the room that you
and Rebi stayed in?
I did, but Rebi,
sheshe stayed in a room across
the hall.
(Beeping)
Rachel Till's old room.
It was the middle of the
night.
I heard her screaming and I
got up
and I ran through here...
...and I saw her standing on
the bed
looking at me like she was
possessed.
Maybe she was messing with
you?
No.
Did you ever ask her what that
was about?
She died not long after the
incident.
I'm so sorry.
Can I ask how?
Car crash.
Maya, rig a light.
What are you guys doing?
You unscrew the flashlight
just enough
for a ghost to be able to turn
it on.
Yeah, so if the flashlight
comes on
it means that you're probably
going to die.
Hey!
Upstairs is off limits.
What?
My sister's stuff's up there
and my dad would freak.
Besides it's locked and I
don't have a key.
We're paranormal investigators
that can't go into the attic...
Yeah. Sorry.
Dax, we don't need to get up
there.
Yes, we do. We specifically
asked to go into the attic
and now all of a sudden we
can't.
Sorry.
Thank you.
So how many acres is it?
Three thousand,
three hundred sixty of it
vineyard land.
About eight square miles, with
two miles surrounding us.
So Ashen, when are we getting
married?
Sarah's a little bit of a gold
digger, I should warn you.
So how long have you two been
friends?
- Since we were kids. -We grew
up on the same street.
So, in this stomach is a baby
boy or a baby girl.
You really don't know?
I want it to be a surprise.
What are you hoping for?
A lesbian.
- Just like her mom. -Yeah, you
know, thanks to you,
I'm seriously considering
going there.
Wouldn't be the first time.
Well, I think Theresa is gonna
make a rockin' mom.
Thank you.
So what is Dax's problem?
We've just been having a
stupid argument.
We've been having it ever
since I became pregnant.
Dax thinks that the baby was
conceived in LA,
and Theresa thinks that the
baby was conceived here.
- At this winery? -Yep.
We came up here a few of months ago just to scout locations
and get permission to ghost
hunt.
Grabbed a couple of bottles of
wine.
Went for a hike along the
property line.
Got totally drunk.
Don't remember making love
but we were completely
trashed, so...
Got it.
This place is awesome, right?
Compared to that ratted out
asylum we investigated?
- That asylum was gross. -And
dormant.
How many investigations have
you guys done so far?
This'll be our fourth but the
other three were lame.
- Very lame. -How does it work?
I mean, do you sell it to a
network or something?
Well, right now just the
internet
but we're stepping up our
game.
We invested some more money in
gear
and we just hired Mike,
our newest ghost hunter.
You're awesome by the way.
I like to think so.
(Giggling)
(door creaking)
If you need to make a call,
you're better off
using a land line.
Yeah, the service here sucks.
I told my old man to put in
his own cell tower,
but he thinks that the
microwaves
contaminate the grapes.
- Boo! -There you are.
Just wanted to see how these
new EMFs were working.
Any spikes?
Ah, no. Nothing.
Maybe I'll sneak around by
myself
and try to get some footage
away from the...
Do what you gotta do. Just be
discreet, okay?
I promised Ashen we wouldn't
run amok.
Got it.
One of our employees thought
the place was demon possessed.
Tried to burn it down when I
was a kid.
Barely got out of here with my
life.
My dad drank himself to sleep
with a cigarette in his mouth.
Ran out of the house, forgot
about me.
Solid year in the hospital on
a morphine diet
getting skin grafts.
Pain was so much fun I left my
body.
Is that why you ghost hunt?
I've seen the other side.
I know it's real.
You ready? You can put your
gear in the museum.
Just don't scratch anything.
What the hell is this?
What do you think it is?
You know how I feel about
guns.
Mike.
We're up here all by
ourselves.
You don't want a little bit of
protection?
Okay, but you can't shoot a
ghost
and there's nobody here.
Yeah, that's a perfect time
to rob the place.
Maya.
Mike...
So we've just finished the
tour
and everyone's getting prepped
for our first investigation.
We're gonna start with the
original winery,
the part that's over a hundred
years old.
If there's something here,
we're gonna find it.
I've been looking through
these videos.
They're uploaded by Jim Till,
Ashen Till's older brother.
He talks about these balls of
light.
Now, they're pretty common in
photographs.
They're usually just specks of
dust on the lens.
But if he's seen these in
person...
Gotta make a note to ask Ashen
about his brother.
Maybe I can get an interview.
Maybe he can help us.
I've got a really, really good
feeling about this place.
I mean, there is so much dark
history here.
There's an abundance of
violent deaths
and all sorts of unexplainable
phenomena.
Why are these candles lit?
Uh, Theresa?
Was someone else down here?
'Cause these candles are lit.
Maybe Jason.
I'll check with him.
Jason, did you light any
candles?
Why would I light candles?
Copy that.
That's a negative from Jason.
Great.
Yeah, I just walked into a
cold spot right here.
Okay. Well, check your TG.
Fifty-nine...
Fifty-four...
Forty-nine...
Are you joking?
Yeah.
Ha ha.
We're not gonna find anything
down here.
What makes you so sure about
that?
They all killed themselves.
Suicide's a straight shot to
hell.
It's pretty black and white in
your Catholic world, huh?
Uh huh.
Unfinished business is
unfinished business.
Rachel, I hope we're not
intruding.
We just want to understand
you.
- What's on the EVP? -Huh?
Are you running an EVP?
Oh, that's probably
a good idea.
I just hate hearing my voice
recorded.
Rachel, why did you stab
yourself 13 times?
And why in the stomach?
Why such a painful
and slow death?
Were you trying to get
someone's attention?
Sweetheart, you have our
attention,
so go ahead and tell us.
I like to flirt with my
ghosts.
If you're here, give us a
sign.
Come on, ya crazy bitch.
Run an EVP.
Rachel, if you have anything
to say,
I can hear you with this
device.
Tell us why you killed
yourself.
We want to know. We want to
know your story.
(faint ghostly whispers)
That sounded like something,
right?
Uh, guys?
I'm getting, um...
EMF readings in this dining
room.
He's in the old boardroom.
On the basement floor.
Jason? You're in the old
boardroom.
What kind of readings are you
getting?
Pretty consistent at 2.5
with...
spikes all the way up to 7.
Seven?
Yeah.
(Creaking)
All right, is somebody fucking
with me?
No, no. What's going on?
The door just moved.
And it just got really fucking
cold in here.
Okay, 68...
65...
62...
50...
That's like a 10 degree drop.
That, that's for real.
(Scratching)
Are you guys picking that up?
Do you hear that?
No. What are you hearing?
(Scratching)
I hear scratching.
(beeping)
Hold on a second.
Play that back.
(Beeping)
So how long have you and Dax
been together?
Um, three to three and a half
years, I guess.
He's kind of a short fuse.
Yeah, I guess.
Maya.
To the left of you?
That's where they found
Rachel's corpse.
Hey, what's goin' on?
Shh.
We got a positive EVP.
(zapping)
Theresa, is anybody else in
the winery?
Is there anyone else here?
I'm gonna go check it out.
I saw somebody walk past here.
Are you sure it couldn't have
been something else?
No, I saw it too.
If you've got a message for
me, tell me what it is.
(Beeping)
(rewinding)
...message for me, tell me
what it is.
(Faint ghostly whispers)
Okay, I got something.
Are you sure?
Fuck yeah. I'm gonna listen to
it again.
(Rewinding)
...message for me, tell me
what it is.
(Faint ghostly whispers)
(beeping)
(creaking)
Jesus!
What's going on?
A lot of shit, man.
Oh God.
Hey.
Sorry.
Oh God.
What'd you see?
Right through here.
We saw a shadow of somebody
walk past, Mike.
- You scared? -Well, if it's a
ghost, then no,
but if it's an intruder with a
knife that's gonna
tie me up and murder me, then
yes.
I don't think it was an
intruder.
This place is the real deal,
isn't it?
(static filled ghostly
whispers)
Sounds like "fuck you."
Yeah, I was gonna say the same
thing.
That's what I heard.
(Static filled ghostly
whispers)
No, I'm hearing "they."
"They fuck you."
That's lovely.
Play my EVP.
(static filled ghostly
whispers)
I hear "go" and "idge."
Play it again.
(Static filled ghostly
whispers)
Grids?
Go to the ridge?
Go to the fridge?
Fridge? She's hungry?
Maybe we should go make her a
sandwich.
So what do you think?
I think we might sell our
first show to a network.
I just felt a kick.
- Let me feel! -I just felt a
kick!
That's so exciting!
Yeah.
Hey. You got another one of
those?
I thought you quit.
Live dangerously.
You all right?
I'm not cut out for this shit,
man.
I'm...
I don't know how to deal with
it.
It's "like father, like son,"
no matter how much I resist.
You and Maya are good though,
huh?
Yeah, she thinks so.
You don't?
It's perfect, like, we don't
argue.
No problems.
That's the problem.
We don't fight.
We don't laugh.
You don't fuck.
Yeah, man, I've been in that
relationship.
You guys are more like brother
and sister.
Exactly.
Brother and sister?
Hi...
Prick.
Ask and you shall receive.
Go get her, man.
This is video surveillance
footage
from inside the bottle
factory.
Oh shit, that's spooky.
Pay attention to the courtyard
shot.
Wait. Can you pause it a
second?
What year was this taken?
'93.
And that's not your sister?
She died a year before.
It could have been a visitor,
right?
You said the winery does
tours?
I think that girl is Beatrice
Blaine.
The girl from the auger?
Yeah.
Creepy.
Have you posted any of this on
the net?
Jim might have.
All he does is tweak out
and post videos on YouTube.
He's a tweaker?
He's a total loser.
My dad, he lets him park his
trailer on our land.
I don't know why.
He should cut him off,
but now that he's sick, he
won't.
He thinks he's gonna run this
place with me.
It's not gonna happen.
Would you like to join us,
Dax?
What are you doing back there?
I'm just watching the footage.
What is your problem?
Why do I have to have a
problem?
We have 48 hours to do this,
right?
Whoa.
Definite overanalyzing. I'm
just sitting back.
I don't like to sit close to
the screen.
- I'm sorry. -Should we do this
another time?
- No, please. -No, please give
us a second.
- Let's just watch. No. -You
don't direct everything,
Theresa, thank you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
(otherworldly vibration)
You wanna see something
disgusting?
I think that's a
three-week-old cookie.
- Want some? -No.
No? You're full?
How long have those cookies
even been in there?
I don't know.
A really long time.
Do you think that, um, Ashen
likes me?
(exhales)
I don't think that you want to
know what I think about that.
Why don't you try dating
someone that gets you?
Someone that gets me?
You know, instead of these
jerks
that just use you
and then spit you out?
Come on, we have been friends
for so long.
I don't wanna ruin that.
Yeah...
(slams)
Look me in the eyes and tell
me right now
that you've not been with
anybody else.
I never cheated on you, Dax,
all right?
- I didn't. -Why? Because we
were broken up?
I swear on this baby's life
that you're the father.
- Here we go again. -What do
you want?
You want a relationship like
Dax and Theresa?
You're venting to somebody
about our problems.
Because you don't talk to me.
Is it so wrong
that I don't wanna fight?
You respond to fights.
We don't have to fight.
(Meter vibrating)
You just keep on dating your
rich father,
who abused you.
Excuse me?
Do you remember that night
when you were walking down the
street
with this crazed look on your
face?
How dare you bring that up?
How dare you?
Do you remember what we said
to each other that night?
You can't just talk about that
shit.
You can't just bring that shit
up.
You're always looking to
someone else.
(Overlapping arguing)
You want that negative attention,
and I'm catching you.
That's what this is about? You
catching me?
(Overlapping arguing)
Things would be a little more
cut and dry...
Tell me the truth. You don't
know how I would react.
Dax, we came up here to
location scout.
That's the only time it
could've happened.
- Stop. -Don't fucking ask me
that.
Stop it right now.
I'm not trying to fucking hurt
you.
I'm not the one tr
Don't you ever talk about that
again.
You promised you would never.
Out of the seven people that
are here
out of the seven people that
are here,
who have you told about your
cousin
blowing his head off with your
gun?
Because I guarantee you told
someone.
No! (Gunshot)
But the fact that we don't
fight
and the fact that we don't
talk
about our messed up past
bothers you.
I tried, I said I'd come to
you, I say,
but "No, I'm too busy, I have
to focus on work."
Dax, I know, I know I tend to
get consumed with my job
and with my goals and the things I want to accomplish in life
but I'm not gonna stop doing
the things I want to do in life
because you feel threatened.
(Overlapping arguing)
Fuck you, Jason, you know?
Fuck you.
Why the fuck are you even
talking to me?
Don't fucking talk to me.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Maya.
Maya!
Get your ass back here!
The baby is yours Dax, okay?
We need to calm down.
(grunting)
I'm sorry.
And I'm going to do everything
in my power
to make sure you stay calm
this weekend.
Just breathe.
Wine, wine, everywhere, nor
any drop to drink.
Ah. Not bad.
Don't get us in trouble, okay?
I doubt they're gonna miss one
little bottle of wine.
I'm gonna go check out the
bomb shelter.
You go back to the old Till
house.
Okay?
You read my mind.
(Panting)
(panting)
(clattering)
(pulling light switch)
Rory Devink.
"This much time
underground..."
Oh my God.
(Glass shattering)
Who's there?
"Rachel knows how to make..."
(panting)
"They know..."
"Go away..."
"Rachel knows how to make them
go away."
So I just found something
really, really cool.
I had a good feeling about
this place
and King's Ransom does not
disappoint.
We've had positive EVPs,
dramatic temperature swings,
EMFs that are all over the
place...
There is something here.
I looked around in Rory Devink's bomb shelter and I found this.
It's her diary.
It's mostly just incoherent,
but look at this.
"Rachel...
knows how to make them go
away."
What does that mean? Who are
"they," you know?
Maybe there's something that
Ashen isn't telling us.
Maybe there's something else
hidden in these videos.
(Creaking)
So this is the old Till house.
It's off-limits to the family
for whatever reason.
It's my belief that ghosts are
shy.
And they like it when it's
dark.
And they like it when you're
alone.
scared.
We definitely have all three
of those things
happening right now.
(Exhales)
This place definitely...
gives me the creeps.
There's the old piano.
Rachel?
If you're here, play something
on the piano.
I'll start you off.
(Hits piano keys)
(rustling)
Okay, what was that?
Okay, I definitely heard a
noise.
Could have been a pinecone
coming off the roof...
(clattering)
Or not.
(Clattering)
Okay, something just rolled
down the stairs.
(Panting)
What is that?
What's...
Oh my God, it's an eye.
Okay, that's fucked up.
That fucking door is unlocked.
Hello?
You all right?
Yeah.
Is it me, or do you get the
sense that there's
something up with Ashen?
- Like what? -I dunno.
It's like every time he talks
about his dead sister
or his brother, he gets this
this weird look on his face.
- I haven't really noticed it.
- I mean, think about it.
What's this winery worth?
I can't count that high.
With his sister dead, his
brother is the only thing
standing in the way of him
inheriting this whole place.
I mean, he hates his brother.
You can hear it all over him.
Well his brother's a drug
addict.
Yeah, he's probably hoping he
ODs.
You don't know that.
He said his sister died in a
car accident.
I wonder who was driving.
These fucking dolls.
Who makes this shit?
There's writing all over this
wall.
Not nice things.
(Exhales)
It's definitely not...
a good feeling in here.
What is this here?
Not a bad artist.
Vineyards...
the Till house...
Don't like that one.
Whoa, what is this?
This is your notebook?
(clicking)
(otherworldly sounds)
What the hell was that?
(Panting)
Rebi?
(panting)
You've got to be kidding me.
Looks like someone decapitated
a bunch of dolls
and put them in a bathtub.
Let's check out this room.
It's so cold in here.
There's dust everywhere.
What the fuck...
Okay, that's a leg.
What is this?
Peek-a-boo...
(door slams)
Okay.
The door just moved.
Did you do that?
(Panting)
Okay, who's screwing with me?
(Running footsteps)
Oh shit.
(Shrieking)
Oh, shit!
What happened?
(Screaming)
Stop it!
(Muffled screaming)
Oh, shit!
It's out there in the woods.
It's an entity.
I can't really explain.
It picked me up,
literally picked me up off the
ground.
It's strong, it's like
Do you really think I killed
my sister?
You know the next time you want to have a private conversation,
try turning your headset off.
I'm sorry, Ashen.
I can get paranoid
I didn't kill Rebi.
I loved my sister.
I love my brother, too.
I have nightmares to this day
about that crash.
That's the truth.
Do you know why you're here,
Theresa?
To hunt for ghosts.
To prove their existence.
Not to me.
So please...
stay focused on what's
important.
Okay.
(Grunting)
Maybe we can fight a little.
(Panting)
Whoa. You all right?
You okay?
What happened?
- Baby? -No, I'm good.
I'm just tired, I guess.
(Beeping)
Whoa.
That's substantial.
Check this out.
Check the meter. See where it
is?
- Mm-hm. -Watch this.
(Beeping)
It's weird. It's like this
room
just, like, feels creepy.
Somebody's becoming a
believer.
No, I'm not saying that.
It just feels weird.
Look at these pictures.
They're of the Till family.
People always look funny from
these times.
(Door creaking)
You two look rosy.
- We went for a walk. -A walk?
I don't want to see you after
a run then.
What do you got?
We got fluctuations up to
five.
It's spiking.
Dax.
Go back for a second to that
other picture.
Which one?
This one?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, the other one.
The one of the room?
Look at this.
This is the room we're in,
right?
- Yeah. -Look.
There's a door
where that armoire is.
No, that's the door we just
walked through.
No, no, no. Look.
If you look at the layout of
the furniture,
it would put this door...
right here.
This is where I'm getting the
strongest reading.
Is it okay if we move this?
Let's do it.
Wonder why it was covered up.
I have no idea.
It's been like that since I
was a kid.
I know that.
That's super creepy.
(Creaking)
Oh wow.
Oh my God.
Mike, do you have enough light
to get this?
Careful what you touch.
I'm not sure you should be
touching things.
Smells like dead rats in here.
Guys, this paint is still wet.
Look at these paintings, you
guys.
Check out all this writing.
It comes all the way over here
too.
Bridge...
"Now I go
to the summer bridge..."
to meet the devil?
God.
Shit.
(Phone ringing)
Hello? Dad?
Dad, I'm gonna call you later
from a land line, okay?
Summer bridge...
Are you getting service?
Yeah, like one bar.
Guys. You guys, you guys.
The bridge.
That's what the EVP was
saying.
"Now I go to the bridge."
He shouldn't just be wandering
around,
especially now with us not
having any cell service.
- I'm sure he's close by. -I'm
sure he's close,
but we don't have time for
this.
We've got a tight schedule.
Speak of the devil.
Hey.
Hey!
Where the hell you been?
I went for a little walk
to clear my head.
What's goin' on?
Okay, well, nice of you to
join us.
Come on, we got a big lead.
Let's go.
This way.
Why doesn't Ashen ever have
to carry anything?
(soft conversations)
So what's the deal with this
bridge?
Rebi and I used to play here
when we were kids.
And this is where she died.
Careful, guys.
Can I ask you what exactly
happened?
When I found Rebi, she was
convulsing
and speaking in a language
that I didn't understand,
and...
I couldn't find anyone to help
me.
So I tried to drive her to the
hospital
but she forced us to crash.
She wasn't belted in and she
went face first
through the windshield.
You were driving?
Yeah.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. -Don't do
that.
- That's not funny. -Chill out.
I was joking.
Jason's scared of the water.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, guys, look down
there.
There's someone down there.
There's a woman down there.
All right, guys, stay here.
Mike, come on.
Let's go, let's go.
- Hello? -Getting anything,
Mike?
I can't see anything down
here.
Where did she see her?
Somewhere around here.
This is the spot right here.
Anyone there?
(Slow beeping)
Anything?
(Screaming)
Maya?
Maya!
Sarah?
Sarah!
(Screaming)
- Hey hey, what do we got?
- Sarah's down there?
- How? -He pushed her.
He pushed her in!
What the hell is wrong with
you, man?
She was gonna jump. I tried to
grab her.
Bullshit. I saw you.
I did not! She was gonna jump!
You're such a fucking liar.
You pushed her in.
The current is strong.
We've got to get down there.
Let's go.
(all shouting for Sarah)
She should be here. It seems
shallow.
Somebody needs to go back to
the winery
and call the fucking police.
I'll go.
Take the girls.
Grab the equipment.
Let's keep looking.
Come on, come on, come on!
(Engine starting)
What?
I can't get an outside line.
All right, we'll go to town.
Come on.
Fuck.
Go inside.
I'll fix it.
Wait, why?
Go inside.
I really think that tire was
slashed.
No!
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
All this stress isn't good for
the baby, that's all.
(Creaking)
I don't like this. I'm
checking on Mike.
(Panting)
Mike?
Mike!
Nobody gets out of here. Pull
the trigger.
- We're all gonna die. -Pull
Do it!
(Gunshot)
- Mike! -Oh my God.
Mike, Mike!
(Choking)
I get reception in the cellar.
We can go down there.
Mike, look at me.
Mike. Mike.
(Panting)
(phone ringing)
(gurgling)
(hyperventilating)
Maya?
(phone ringing)
(phone ringing louder)
Maya?
(Phone ringing)
(otherworldly sounds)
(gasps)
(shrieking)
(grunting)
(screaming)
(stabbing continues)
Maya?
They genetically bred out
fear.
Who are you talking to?
Theresa.
I'm talking to you.
(creaking)
(crickets chirping)
(panting)
Sarah?
This is impossible.
Sarah!
I didn't push her in.
Why would I fucking push her
in?
- Why would I do that? -Why
would she jump?
I don't know, man.
- Why would she jump? -I don't
know!
Let's not lose our heads,
okay?
I swear to God, man.
I swear to fucking God I
didn't push her in.
Let's find Sarah.
We'll ask her what happened.
Can anyone hear me?
You getting that?
Sarah.
Can you hear me?
Hello?
Is anyone there?
I can hear you.
Can you hear me?
Barely.
I'm at this road and I see
wooden shacks.
Wooden shacks? She must be
back at the winery.
Sarah, listen. Stay where you
are.
We're coming for you.
Sarah, can you hear me?
Why aren't we getting
reception?
Because her radio's wet.
We're lucky we're getting
anything at all.
I'm gonna go look for her.
Go. I'm coming with you.
Listen, you stay here in case
she comes around, all right?
You stay in contact.
Do you understand me?
Yeah.
There's definitely something
evil here.
The phone lines were cut
and our tires were slashed.
Maya's missing...
Mike...
There's only one person who
knows what's going on here.
I'm gonna find Jim Till.
Hello?
Is anybody here?
(Knocking)
Hello?
Jim?
(Sighs)
Oh my God.
That's disgusting.
Orbs...
They bred out fear.
Man's been enslaved by these
demonic forces.
They're able to navigate
between
the physical and the astral
plane.
They're technologically
and physically superior to us.
Religion calls them demons.
Ufologists call them
multidimensional beings.
What's relevant is they're
trying to assimilate us
into their fascist empire run!
And parasitically deplete us
of our physical
and biological resources.
They've been exploiting
mankind for thousands of years
you listen to me! Carefully
manifesting
this abduction hybrid breeding
program.
And they want to be portrayed
as saviors
while mankind goes mad...
Listen to me!
Listen. To. Me.
You're not fucking listening
to me.
Listen to me!
(Video continues to play)
(video continues to play)
(radio static)
Hey Dax?
Mike?
Can you guys hear me?
I can't stay here by myself.
I'm going insane.
I'm gonna go back to the
winery and look for her.
Sarah?
Oh my God.
Oh my God. Are you okay?
Where have you been?
Here. Put this on.
Put this on.
You're freezing.
What happened?
What happened? Look at me.
- Sarah. -They're beautiful.
Sarah, look at me. Look at me.
Okay, we gotta go this way,
all right?
- We're gonna go this way. -No.
Come with me. Sarah?
- Come. -No!
Sarah, come on!
Sarah!
Sarah.
Sarah, we're at the shack.
Come outside.
Sarah, do you read me?
Where is she?
Is there any other place she
could be?
I don't know.
- These the only wooden shacks?
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
What?
Did you just hear that?
Sarah?
Now what?
Where?
(Rustling)
It's nothing. Let's go.
All right.
Sarah?
Sarah.
We've been looking all over
for you.
Sarah.
You pushed me.
Sarah. No.
You pushed me off the bridge.
You fell. I tried to save you.
No, you tried to kill me!
You tried to kill me!
Sarah, I would never hurt you.
Sarah, I...
Why would I ever want to hurt
you?
I'm in love with you.
(Screaming)
Jason?
(sobbing)
Hello?
(Faint ghostly voices)
Who's there?
- Beatrice? -They are too real.
Hello?
Fine.
Don't believe me.
They make you see things you
don't wanna see.
(Loud clattering)
They make you do things that
you don't wanna do.
Beatrice? What'd I say about
your imaginary friend?
She's real.
What the hell did you do?
What I had to.
What the hell did you do?!
Talk to Rachel.
She knows how to make them go
away.
Jesus Christ!
Daddy!
(Screaming)
(shouting)
(screaming)
(slam)
(gasps)
(creaking)
(otherworldly sounds)
(grunting)
Beatrice?
Ashen!
Yeah, yeah?
We gotta get her to the
hospital right now.
We gotta go right now.
Get the door.
Stay calm, Theresa. Just be
careful.
I want you to stay calm and
relax
and focus on the baby right
now.
I need you to be quiet because
she needs to stay calm.
Just stay calm.
Just breathe.
Stay warm.
All right, go, go, go.
- I need you to breathe. -We
need to find Rachel.
- Are you having contractions?
- We have to go find Rachel.
There's something else here.
Okay, just relax, all right?
It's okay.
Hey.
Kill her.
How far are we from the
hospital?
No, no, no, no.
(Panting)
- Dax. -Yeah?
- In the glove box. -Yeah?
I need you to get me
something.
Look at me. You're gonna be
fine.
I'm here, okay?
I love you.
Hang on!
(Screaming)
Dax.
Dax!
Come on, come on, come on.
Please, Dax.
Come on. Oh my God.
Ah, my legs!
Come on!
Come on.
Go!
No!
Don't let me burn.
(Screaming)
Please!
(screaming)
(grunting)
(laughing)
(panting)
Get up!
(Gunshots)
Get on your fucking feet!
(grunting)
(gunshots)
Get out of my head.
Please let me go.
Kill her.
I'm sorry.
(Grunting)
(gunshot)
(weeping)
(panting)
(sobbing)
911. What's the nature of your
emergency?
I need help.
Miss, what is your emergency?
My best friend is dead.
Dead? Are you sure?
What is your location?
Miss, I need you to remain
calm.
What is your location?
I'm at the King's Ransom
Winery.
I don't know what happened.
Are you sure your friend is
dead?
Can you tell me what happened?
Hello?
I think I killed him.
You think you killed him?
Miss, did I hear you
correctly?
Miss?
Hello?
Can you hear me, miss?
Are you there?
Miss?
I'm dispatching emergency
crews right away.
I need you to stay on the
line, okay?
(otherworldly sounds)
(zapping)
Hello?
Are you there?
Miss?
(banging)
I can help you.
Come this way.
Theresa.
Theresa, come over here.
(pained cry)
(screams)
Step in there.
It's safe in there.
They like to make you afraid.
Whatever scares you the most,
they know what it is.
What do they want?
Rachel can tell you.
You have to talk to her.
It's the only way.
Yeah.
Have you seen them?
No.
What do they look like?
They're beautiful.
Are you afraid?
That's what they like.
I'm scared too.
But they can't hurt you, can
they?
Yeah.
But in a different way.
I'm gonna go see where they
are.
You stay.
Okay?
(panting)
(otherworldly sounds)
Run!
(Alarm blaring)
(rumbling)
(eerie sounds)
Ma'am, were you are you taking
something?
What's going on? Calm down.
We need an 11-41.
What are you doing? What are
you doing?
Don't go in there! Don't let
him go in there.
It's okay. He'll be okay.
He'll be okay.
I'll be right back.
(Sobbing)
(engine struggling to start)
(siren blaring)
(police dispatch)
In case I don't make it out
alive,
I want everyone to know what's
going on.
There's something here.
It's not human.
It's not a ghost.
It's a beautiful light
but there's something sinister
at its core.
And there's only one person that knows how to make it go away.
That's Rachel Till.
And I'm gonna find her.
(Woman singing in foreign
language)
Rachel?
Rachel?!
I'm here.
Why are they trying to kill
me?
I used to be beautiful like
you.
If they wanted me dead, I'd be
dead by now, wouldn't I?
What do they want?
They bred out fear,
which is the foundation of all
emotion.
Without emotion there's no
desire to breed,
to explore, no will to live.
They are dying.
So they come here on occasion
to study it and...
extract it.
Extract it...
how?
What is living inside you is
not human,
and if it is born...
God help us.
They're gonna take my baby.
Aren't they?
I stopped them.
Rory and Beatrice stopped
them.
Now you must...
stop them.
(Grunting)
(sobbing)
(coughing)
(grunting)
(weeping)
(otherworldly sounds)
Take it.
(gasping)
(screaming)
(high-pitched whistle and
boom)
(grunting)
(otherworldly sounds)
(clicking)
(zapping)
(otherworldly sounds)
Theresa!
Theresa?
Are you here?
I don't think she's here.
Help.
Help me.
Please.
Is that her?
I dunno.
Why'd you stab yourself?
What?
I need a doctor.
Please.
Help me.
What happened to your friends?
They're all fucking dead.
Holy shit. Did you hear that?
Yeah.
That's crazy.
No, wait.
Wait, please.
Hey, what the fuck was that?
I dunno. And I don't wanna
find out.
Let's get out of here.