(dramatic music)
(clock ticking) (upbeat music)
♪ I'm tied to the tracks
of an oncoming train ♪
♪ I'm lightning's rod in
the cold, pouring rain ♪
♪ In the beat of the
barrel of a loaded gun ♪
♪ I've run ♪
♪ Out of places to run ♪
♪ Nobody sleeps ♪
♪ Not in my neighborhood ♪
♪ The good old days ♪
♪ They were never that good ♪
♪ Dreams burn away in the godless sun ♪
♪ I've run ♪
♪ Out of places to run ♪
(clock ticking) (upbeat music)
(bell ringing)
(clock ticking)
(people moaning)
(heavy breathing)
- That was great, honey.
- Think that'll hold ya 'til I get back?
(heavy breathing)
- Do you really have to stay overnight?
- Well I promised Anne.
I haven't seen her in almost two years.
Rachel.
She's my only child.
All right?
All right, that's a good girl.
I'll be back tomorrow evening.
(camera shutter clicking)
(gentle music)
♪ Why do I want you to call ♪
♪ Why do I want you to do ♪
♪ Telephone rings and I just ♪
♪ I'm telling myself that
it's love but it's work ♪
♪ Are you the lock for the key ♪
- [Carla] What?
- Hi.
It's me.
- [Carla] Did he leave yet?
- No, not yet.
He's just in the shower.
- So are we on for tonight or what?
- I don't know.
I was thinking maybe we should wait.
- Wait for what?
If you back out on me again,
just rip up my phone number
because I don't want to hear it anymore.
- Carla, don't be like that.
- I'm serious, Rachel.
I've had it.
Now, are we on for tonight or not?
- Thank you.
So what're your plans for the weekend?
- Hangin' out with Carla.
- Hanging.
Hanging out with Carla.
How many times do I have to tell you
when you slur your speech,
you sound illiterate?
- I know.
I know.
Sorry.
- When are you gonna
realize that hanging out
with Carla is one of the reasons
your self-improvement's been so difficult.
- She's my best friend.
- I know.
But do me a favor, leave
your wallet at home.
I don't want you lending
her anymore money.
And whatever you do, don't
wear that lace outfit.
- Oh, but it's so pretty.
- It's tacky.
It's cheap-looking.
- Cost near $800.
- Expensive doesn't mean discerning.
Remember?
- You're gonna.
You're going to miss your plane.
- See ya tomorrow evening.
(bright music)
♪ Tick, tick, tick ♪
♪ Tick, tick ♪
♪ Let's go solo ♪
♪ Watch your pocket ♪
♪ Rider come by, this boy rocks ♪
♪ Get me away from ties and suits ♪
♪ I wanna find a blonde
with brunette roots ♪
♪ 911 I need a savior ♪
- There you are.
I thought you were
gonna chicken out again.
(bright music)
♪ Tick, tick, tick ♪
♪ Tick bears coming ♪
♪ Tick, tick ♪
- I'll get us some more drinks.
- Do you think that's a good idea?
- I wouldn't do it if
it wasn't a good idea.
Would you sit down and
let me worry about things
and try and act like you're having fun?
- All right.
What do we do first?
- Just relax and look cute.
I'll do everything else.
Hey, can I get two Stoly kamikazes
for that table right there?
- I kinda have my hands full right now.
- The quicker they get
there, the bigger your tip.
♪ Bad behavior ♪
♪ Getting time ♪
♪ Getting time off ♪
- Do me a favor, huh?
Those drinks that lady ordered,
put on my tab, all right?
♪ Oh when things went out the way ♪
♪ Of what we have to show ♪
♪ If you know ♪
- Oh, the drinks have already
been taken care of, ma'am,
by the gentleman at the bar.
(bright music)
- I can't...
- [Carla] Sh.
- Howdy.
I'm Travis.
- Hi Travis.
I'm Carla and this is Rachel.
- It's a pleasure.
Hey, y'all mind if I join ya?
♪ What if we looked up to the
things we don't remember ♪
- So, tell me Travis,
are you a real cowboy
or do you wear that hat
just 'cause you think
it looks good on you?
- It does look good on me.
Doesn't it?
- Yeah, I think so.
- So you wanna dance?
- No, I couldn't.
- It's just a dance, Rachel.
♪ Oh they're telling me ♪
♪ They're telling me that I don't know ♪
(patrons clapping)
- What the hell?
(gentle music)
- It's your first time here, right?
- How can you tell?
- Well your dress for one thing.
I mean it obviously cost
about a month's wages
for most everybody in here.
- [Rachel] My husband bought it for me.
- See that's another thing.
I'll wager you're not the only
woman in here who's married,
but you are the only
one who hasn't bothered
to remove her wedding band.
- Hey, why should I?
I'm just here to have a couple of drinks
with my friend, nothing more.
- So he does all right,
this husband of yours?
- [Rachel] He's a potato broker.
- What?
- He travels between here and Idaho Falls,
buyin' and sellin' potatoes,
decidin' which ones will go to
restaurants or supermarkets,
or become potato chips, or
frozen like in TV dinners.
- And he got rich doin' that?
- His family's worth millions.
- Because of potatoes?
(gentle music)
♪ Solid ground ♪
- So I come up from Texas
for that rodeo last April
and then I met a girl and I
decided to stay for awhile.
- So where is she?
- We split up.
Anyway, I've been punchin'
cows up to Gentry Ranch
'til I can get me a grubstake.
You know, get back on the road.
♪ Solid ground ♪
- I'm takin' off.
- Oh, so soon?
- It's one o'clock in the morning
and I've got a long drive ahead of me.
Here's your purse.
- You know, maybe I should go, too.
- Rachel (whispers).
Well, don't do anything I wouldn't do.
- Is there anything you wouldn't do?
- I reckon not.
- Well, what now?
- What do you mean?
- You didn't leave with your friend.
- And I'm not leavin' with you either.
Bakersfield's a small town.
We've already given everyone here
more than enough to talk about.
- All right, fair enough, but...
- What?
- Just because we don't leave together,
doesn't mean we can't
end up being together.
♪ I was stunned ♪
- I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to offend you.
- Do you know where Pioneer Village is?
- Yeah.
- You leave first.
If I'm not there in 20
minutes, I'm not coming.
♪ Solid ground ♪
(soft music)
- [Travis] I was afraid
you weren't gon' come.
- I almost didn't.
- So this is Pioneer Village, huh?
- Our one and only true tourist trap.
Don't tell me you've
never been here before?
- Well I've passed by it a few times.
- Well come on then.
- Is it open?
- It is for us.
Come on.
(gentle music)
Oh I used to love coming out here
at night like this when no one was around.
And this is my favorite spot.
Beale Clock Tower.
It used to sit smack-dab in
the middle of town square,
but it got damaged in the quake of '52.
So they dragged it out here
with all the other landmarks and relics.
Whenever things got too tough at home,
I'd come out here and hide for awhile.
- If I had your money,
I don't think things
ever'd get too tough for me.
- I wasn't born rich.
I married it.
At least that's what his daughter says.
- What're you doin' out here with me, huh?
I mean you were gonna
leave with your friend
and she whispered somethin' in your ear
and you decided to stay.
- She double dared me.
- What?
- It's how she used to get me
to do all kinds of crazy
things when I was a kid.
Now it's just sort of a runnin' joke.
- I double dare you.
(gentle music)
(dog barking)
(engine roaring)
She's gone.
You get what you wanted?
- Yeah and then some.
- I still can't believe I
let you talk me into this.
- Didn't look like you
were suffering too much.
- Nope.
I reckon not.
(clock ticking) (ominous music)
(bell ringing)
- [Carla] I'm serious Rachel, I've had it.
Now, are we on for tonight or not?
♪ You really know your way in the dark ♪
- Okay, great.
I'll see you there at eight o'clock.
♪ I'm tired of the game ♪
♪ Crying shame ♪
♪ I don't love ♪
- [Carla] I missed you.
Mm.
- [Travis] God, I missed you, too.
Now we got the whole weekend together.
♪ I don't love ♪
- Not this weekend.
That was Rachel on the phone.
Her hubby's going out of town,
so back to Bakersfield for us.
- I don't know about this, Carla.
I mean, I know we talked
about it and all but...
- But what?
- Look, I'm already a two-time loser.
This thing backfires,
I could spend the rest
of my life in prison.
- It's not gonna backfire.
It's not one of your stupid
liquor store hold-ups.
You know I've been plannin'
this thing for two years.
What's the matter?
Don't love me anymore?
- [Travis] You know I love you but.
(gentle music)
- But?
I'm the best you ever had.
Say it.
- Carla.
- Say it.
- You're the best I ever had but.
(gentle music)
Since I am the one takin' all the risk.
- Mm-hm?
- 50 50 don't seem hardly fair.
- Okay.
How 'bout 60 40?
- I was thinkin' 70 30.
- Hey, can I get two Stoly kamikazes
for the table right there?
- I kinda have my hands full right now.
- Well the quicker they get
there, the bigger your tip.
Well, don't do anything I wouldn't do.
- [Rachel] Is there
anything you wouldn't do?
- I reckon not.
Don't bother, I got it.
Thanks.
♪ Piece of solid ground ♪
(tires screeching)
(ominous music)
- What are you doing here?
How'd you find me?
- What?
No, you were great last night?
Nothing?
- You were great last night.
Now what do you want?
(suspenseful music)
- I realize that this
is an awkward moment.
So I'll just go 'head and start.
You don't want your husband
to see those pictures.
Gonna cost you $100,000.
- What?
I don't have that kind of money.
- Come on, Rachel.
Don't bullshit a bullshitter.
Look, this thing right here.
I bet it's worth $100,000 all by itself.
- Didn't last night mean anything to you?
- Yeah.
$100,000.
I'm right about this, ain't I?
- It don't matter whether
you're right or not.
It's not mine.
None of it is.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
It's my husband who has the money, not me.
- Well, then how 'bout I just take this,
call it my grubstake?
- No, don't.
Holden will notice it's missin'.
My jewelry.
- What about it?
- I'll hock some of my jewelry.
I don't wear it that often.
Maybe Holden won't notice.
- There.
Now that wasn't so tough, was it?
Now you see what you can accomplish
when you put your mind to it?
Well, I don't wanna overstay my welcome.
Besides, you better get dressed.
Get on down to the pawn shop.
- You expect me to do it now?
- This ain't layaway, darlin'.
I want my money by tonight.
Oh and you can go ahead
and keep those pictures.
I got plenty of copies.
(dramatic music)
- So how'd it go?
- Well she said she couldn't pay.
So then I threatened to take
that stupid tusk of hers
and started to walk off
with the damn thing,
just like you told me to.
- And?
- And.
She's gonna hock her jewelry.
- See, I told ya she'd cave
if you took that thing.
It's Holden's favorite piece.
- Oh yeah?
- Yes.
- Speakin' of favorite pieces.
- Are you sure you
didn't enjoy it with her?
- No, no, no.
Pure torture.
I was in agony the whole time.
- Well, I think I better check
it just to be sure it's okay.
- Well if you think you ought to.
(ominous music)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- So, how'd it go at the pawn shop?
- I got your money.
- Great.
I can pick it up in about an hour.
- No.
I gotta go out.
I can't meet you 'til tonight.
- All right, fine, tonight then.
- And I don't want you
comin' by here anymore.
I wanna meet you someplace
else where no one will see us.
- Like where?
- The Gottchalk's parking
lot at 10 o'clock.
The north end where no one ever parks.
- What you got up your
sleeve there, Rachel?
She wants me to meet her in
a parking lot tonight at 10.
- That's fine.
What's she gonna do?
(gentle music)
- All right.
I'll meet you.
But I'm telling you right
now, you try anything...
- You just be sure and
bring the negatives.
(gentle music)
- She's up to somethin'.
- She's just playin' it safe.
- No, no, no, no, it's more than that.
- Well if it is, I'm sure she's
left me 20 messages already.
- I hope you're right.
- Look, I've known Rachel
since the fifth grade.
We're best friends.
She tells me everything.
She's up to something, I'll
know as soon as I call her back.
- Reminds me of that ol' sayin'.
- Which one?
- With friends like
you, who needs enemies.
- Oh, you know, stop
you're breakin' my heart.
She always lands on her feet.
She was head cheerleader,
homecoming queen.
She went out with the star quarterback.
- Damn, I bet you were a
wild-ass in high school.
- (sighs) Well Rachel's daddy
didn't like me much (laughs).
Thought I was a bad influence.
- Yeah and were ya?
- Every chance I got.
- Uh huh.
- That's why she hung out with me.
She could do any crazy thing
she wanted and blame me for it.
You know I used to go
out with her husband.
That's right.
I was Holden Avery's girl until
I introduced him to Rachel.
- Tough break.
- Yeah.
- So as far as I'm concerned, she owes me.
(bright music)
- [Rachel] Thank you.
- I checked the odometer.
Hey, take it easy, will ya?
I just fixed that thing.
(bright music)
♪ Where I'm standing ♪
♪ As far as I can see ♪
(clock ticking)
(bell ringing)
- I'll be back tomorrow evening.
(man humming) (water spraying)
(gentle music)
- Hi, it's me.
No, not yet.
He's just in the shower.
I don't know.
I was thinkin' maybe we should wait.
(gentle music) (water spraying)
(phone ringing) (gentle music)
- Fairfield Investigations.
- This is Holden Avery.
She's on the phone with him right now.
- Mr. Avery, I've been tracking your wife
for almost a year now
and if she's got some stud in her corral,
she's keepin' him well hid
because I haven't caught her with no one.
So far.
- Well maybe she's just
a little more devious
than you give her credit for.
- Well maybe, but my motto is,
if it ain't broke,
don't fix it.
- Quaint.
She'll be dropping me off at the airport
in less than an hour.
Pick her up there.
- [Clay] You're the boss.
- Good.
I want you to keep her
under constant surveillance
'til I get back.
Now my appointment calendar's downstairs.
What time we meeting tomorrow night?
- 10:30, your place.
- Fine.
I want a detailed report.
(gentle music)
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] The white zone is
for immediate loading and
unloading of passengers only.
(dramatic music)
The white zone is for immediate loading
and unloading of passengers only.
No parking.
(gentle music)
(bright music)
♪ Tick tick tick ♪
♪ Tick time is coming ♪
♪ Tick tick let's go solo ♪
♪ Set your watch on ♪
♪ Watch your clock ♪
♪ Trying to come by before it rocks ♪
♪ Get me away from the ties and suits ♪
♪ I wanna find a blonde
with brunette roots ♪
♪ 911 I need a savior ♪
♪ Getting time off for bad behavior ♪
(clock ticking) (bright music)
(clock ticking)
(suspenseful music)
(patrons clapping)
- [Host] We'd like to
thank all you guest riders
and stragglers for hanging
out with us tonight.
Have a good night and drive home safe.
(gentle music)
(water splashing)
(ominous music)
(upbeat music)
♪ Well I was lying on the floor ♪
♪ I was busted up and bleeding ♪
♪ When a vision came to me ♪
♪ Where's the garden of Eden ♪
(clock ticking)
- Thank you.
No, no, no, keep the change.
Rachel?
Where are ya?
I don't believe this.
She knew I was comin' home tonight.
(phone dialing)
(phone ringing)
- [Carla] Hey, it's Carla.
Obviously I'm very busy,
so leave me a message.
(phone beeping)
- Carla, this is Holden.
I assume Rachel's with you.
Have her give me a call as
soon as you get this message.
(gentle music)
Oh my god.
Carla.
(suspenseful music)
(upbeat music)
♪ I was sitting right
there sad all the time ♪
♪ I got the right taste of the heartache ♪
♪ I gave her all the things to find out ♪
(clock ticking)
♪ Being a good thing in a bad way ♪
♪ You gave the good life ♪
♪ I was in bad shape ♪
♪ I should've said goodbye to new ♪
- You're late.
Where were you?
- Where do you think?
- Then he's dead?
- And Travis' fingerprints
are on the photos
and the murder weapon.
- He's out in the middle of
nowhere without an alibi.
- How 'bout you?
- He was still here,
scribblin' on his notepad
when you showed up.
- Perfect.
Perfect.
He should be finding the body any minute.
When the police get there
and see the photographs,
they're gonna think that Travis
tried to blackmail Holden,
and when Holden refused, he killed him.
- Are you sure they won't suspect me?
I mean after all I'm the one
inheritin' all the money.
- Holden hired the detective, not you.
He's gonna say that you
were sittin' at the bar
having a drink at the time of the murder.
- Did you really do it naked?
- Well bloody clothes
are hard to get rid of.
It took me two minutes to hose off
the evidence and get dressed.
- That's what Holden gets
for not trustin' me, huh?
- Yeah, he was even obliging enough
to leave a message on my machine.
You have the perfect alibi.
- We're really gonna get
away with it, aren't we?
- It's too bad about Travis, though.
He's a great lay, isn't he?
- Yeah.
You were right about that.
- But not as good as me.
Right?
(gentle music)
Say it.
- Not as good as you.
No one's ever been as good as you.
(gentle music)
(clock ticking)
- [Waitress] Oh, the drinks have already
been taken care of, ma'am,
by the gentleman at the bar.
♪ You know what they do so tell me ♪
♪ Tell me 'cause I don't know ♪
- Carla, I don't think I
can go through with this.
- You can and you will.
I'm the one who has to do the hard part.
All you have to do is sleep with him.
- No, I can't.
I can't, Carla.
I can't. - Sh sh sh.
- Howdy.
I'm Travis.
- [Carla] Here's your purse.
- Maybe I should go, too.
- Rachel.
You're doin' great.
Don't let me down now, okay?
Besides, he's a great lay.
(gentle music)
♪ You're my solid rock ♪
(ominous music)
- [Waitress] Can I get
you another round, ladies?
It's last call.
- No thanks.
I think we're gonna call it a night.
(gentle music)
Okay, let's go get the tragic news.
- Well, where is everybody?
(ominous music)
- I don't know.
This place should be swarming with cops.
Unless the detective didn't find the body.
- You remembered to leave
the door unlocked, right?
(ominous music)
It's locked, Car.
It's locked.
- It was open when I left.
(ominous music)
Don't touch anything.
We have to come back in the morning.
Let the maid find the body.
(ominous music)
- Where is he?
- I don't know.
He was right here.
- Well maybe he wasn't dead.
Maybe after you left, he
managed to call an ambulance.
- Oh right, and they tidied up
before they took him to the hospital?
There was blood everywhere and
that thing was right there.
- Well what happened?
- I don't know.
Just let me think, okay?
- Carla, I got a real
bad feelin' about this.
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Carla] Travis?
- Carla, where the fuck are you?
- I got restless and I went for a drink.
Why?
How did it go?
- I told you that bitch
was up to something.
- What do you mean?
- She didn't show, Carla.
So I went out to her house.
(engine roaring)
Son of a bitch, I knew
we couldn't trust her.
(ominous music)
(tires screeching)
(suspenseful music)
Rachel?
Come out, come out wherever you are.
(suspenseful music)
(doorbell ringing)
(gentle music)
(car horn beeping)
(suspenseful music)
I think I pretty much got
the blood out of everything
except I couldn't get it
out of this oriental rug
and a couple of files.
Then I dumped his body out by the lake
where we go skinny-dipping.
Made it look like a mugging.
I took the rug and the files
and I burned them in my barbecue pit.
- Nobody saw you?
- No, no, I don't think so.
But some guy saw my
truck in their driveway.
- What guy?
- I don't know what guy.
Some guy.
I think he saw my license plate.
Oh man.
I am so screwed.
- Don't panic, okay?
I'll figure out something.
Just sit tight 'til I get there, okay?
- Just hurry, all right.
Hey.
- Hm?
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
- What did he say?
- We gotta get out to the lake.
(ominous music)
Come on and grab his legs.
- Oh my god, look at his head.
- Don't be such a priss.
You knew I was gonna bash him.
- I know, but how many times?
- I wasn't exactly keeping count.
Now will you get down here and help me?
(ominous music)
- Ugh.
- Oh come on.
- [Rachel] I just take it?
- Yeah.
Go.
- [Rachel] Ah.
- [Carla] Don't worry about your pants.
Just go.
Come on.
- God.
- Okay.
(ominous music)
What's going on?
Why won't it close?
- Okay, wait, wait.
Oh.
His finger's stuck in the lock.
I think we broke it.
- What, the lock or his finger?
- This ain't funny, Carla.
What're we doin' here, Carla?
What the hell are we doin'?
- Would you keep your eyes on the road?
You're swerving all over hell's half-acre.
- You said that nothing could go wrong.
You said absolutely
nothing could go wrong.
- Nothing has yet.
Okay, you still have an air-tight alibi
at the time of the murder.
All we have to do is
get Holden's body back
to where it was so that the
maid can find it in the morning.
It's even better than we planned.
- (scoffs) Better?
Better?
How could this possibly be better?
- That detective saw Travis'
car in your driveway,
which puts him smack-dab
at the scene of the crime.
Okay?
He's gonna fry for the murder.
Not you.
- You really think it's gonna work?
- Yes, Rachel.
Trust me, okay?
I've got everything under control.
- Okay.
(sirens blaring)
(gentle music) (sirens blaring)
- Don't panic.
Just don't.
Don't panic.
Just pull over to the side of the road
and we'll just see what they want.
(gentle music)
- Evenin', Deputy.
- Ma'am.
May I see your driver's
license and registration?
- Here's my license.
And here's my registration.
- Thank you, ma'am.
Mrs. Avery?
- Mm-hm.
- Now the reason I pulled you over
is you were weaving
quite a bit back there.
Have you ladies been drinkin' tonight?
- Well...
- We had a drink at a bar,
but it was a long time ago.
- All the same, I'm afraid I'm gonna have
to ask you to step out of the car, ma'am.
Back here, ma'am, away from the road.
(ominous music)
- She's not drunk, if
that's what you're thinking.
- Ma'am, I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to ask you to be quiet.
Now Mrs. Avery, I want you
to put your feet together
and stand with your arms
outstretched like this.
- [Rachel] Like this?
- That's fine.
Now I want you to lean your
head back and close your eyes.
Now, I want you to bend your right arm
and touch the tip of your
nose with your index finger.
(ominous music)
Okay, now your left arm.
(gentle music)
- She did it.
She passed, right?
- Mrs. Avery, I'd like for you
to do one more thing for me.
I'd like for you to let your
friend drive just to be safe.
- Of course.
- Whatever you say, officer.
(ominous music)
- Whoa.
Whoa.
Hold on a minute.
- Yes sir?
- There's somethin'
stickin' out of your trunk.
(ominous music)
- Oh yeah.
That's a.
It's just an old shower curtain.
It's nothing.
- Well maybe so, but it's
hanging over this one taillight.
That could be a hazard.
You best pop it back inside.
- I have to get the key.
(ominous music)
God.
There ya go.
Have a good night.
- Ma'am.
(ominous music)
Can I give ya a hand with that, ma'am?
- No, no.
It's no problem.
We don't wanna be any more trouble.
- It's no trouble really.
(ominous music)
Looks like you got it.
- Yeah.
Yeah, looks like it.
Have a goodnight.
(engine roaring)
How ya doin', you okay?
- I think I peed my pants.
- I know I peed my pants.
(gentle music)
Here we go.
Okay.
Okay, you get the door.
I'll get the trunk.
- [Anne] Daddy?
- Anne.
What are you doing here?
- Is my dad with you?
(clock ticking)
- [Announcer] Flight 501 from Bakersfield
is now arriving at gate two.
- Hey Daddy.
- Anne.
You didn't have to meet me here.
I told you, we're having lunch tomorrow.
- I know.
I just thought that since we haven't
seen each other in so long,
we'd have dinner tonight too.
- I have an appointment with an attorney
in less than an hour.
- All night?
- Then I have another appointment.
- With who?
- With whom.
- Whom.
- Look, I'm registered at the Regent.
So come by tomorrow around one o'clock.
- Dad...
- Anne, please.
Do as I ask.
Please.
(ominous music)
I already know it's bad.
Just need to know how bad.
- [Doctor] We're making new
breakthroughs every day,
discovering new treatments...
- Doctor, I don't need
the inspirational speech.
I just need to know how long I have.
- [Doctor] Three to six months.
- At least get a second opinion.
Have you talked to Dr. Medina back home?
- No.
I don't want Rachel to know about this.
- Why not?
- Because I intend to
divorce her before I die.
- What?
- It's the only way I can
leave everything to you
without her being able to contest it.
- Daddy, I don't care about your money.
- Yeah, but I do.
She's been having an affair.
- With whom?
- I don't know yet.
But I think it's been going on
since before we were married.
- Are you sure?
- I've suspected it for a long time.
And just as soon as I can prove it,
the prenuptial allows me to dump her
without giving her one red cent.
- Daddy, this is crazy.
Why can't you just stay and
visit for just a couple of days?
- I have an important meeting,
one I cannot afford to miss.
I'll call you in a few days,
when everything's settled.
- Daddy?
I love you.
- Believe it or not.
I love you, too.
(gentle music)
- Hi.
When's your next flight to Bakersfield?
(clock ticking)
(phone ringing) (clock ticking)
Still no answer.
That's it, I'm calling the police.
(dish clanking)
- They won't do anything until
he's missing for 24 hours.
I'm sure he's fine.
- Then why doesn't he answer the phone?
- Well maybe he's just really busy
or maybe the meeting's
not even in his office.
If it'll make you feel better,
we'll take a drive down to
his office and check on him.
- That's a good idea.
That's a good idea.
- Actually, I think that
somebody should stay here
in case he calls or comes by.
(clock ticking)
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Come on, Rachel.
- Now what're we doin'?
- I've got an idea.
It's even better than we planned.
Oh just shut up and drive.
I'll tell ya on the way.
(ominous music)
- [Rachel] So what's the plan?
- First we have to go back
to the bar and get my car.
Then, you can follow me
out to Travis' cabin,
but turn off your headlights and stay back
so he doesn't see you.
He's probably been drinking and
he's bound to be freaked out
'cause I've been gone so long.
He'll wanna know where the
hell have you been, Carla?
And I'll tell him my
battery died or something
and it took me forever to get a jump.
And then I'll say something like.
It's freezing.
Come on, let's go inside.
(gentle music)
Once we're inside, you pull
up and park out of sight
over by the generator shed.
(ominous music)
And then sneak up to the
front of the cabin on foot.
There you'll see a
wheelbarrow and a shovel.
You can use the wheelbarrow
to move Holden's body
from your trunk to the
back of Travis' jeep.
And don't worry, it won't be locked.
It never is.
But first, use the shovel
to scrap up his fender
and side panel and be sure
you don't make too much noise.
Then go find a phone booth.
Make an anonymous 911 call.
Give them Travis' license plate number
and say you saw him hit a
parked car and take off.
I'll get Travis into
bed and then get myself
out of there before the cops show up.
How much of that have you had?
- [Travis] About this much.
- Well maybe you should lie
down and try and get some sleep.
- What are you stupid?
I'm about this close to
the gas chamber right now.
- Well you dumped the body
and you wiped up all the evidence, right?
Then you've got nothing to worry about.
If the cops go after anybody,
they're gonna go after Rachel.
She's the one with motive.
I mean you've never even met the man.
- What about the guy who saw my truck?
- What about him?
You're not the only guy in
Bakersfield who drives a jeep.
- Hey genius, he saw my license plate.
- He made a mistake.
You were here with me all night.
It's his word against ours.
- Yeah right.
You got all the answers, don't you?
- Sometimes.
- Oh you should've seen him, baby.
The way his skull was all caved in.
It was a god-awful sight.
- [Carla] It's okay.
It's over now, okay?
It's gonna be fine.
- The man is dead, Carla.
It's not gonna be fine.
- Yes it is.
I'll take care of it, I promise.
Okay?
(gentle music) (people groaning)
- [Travis] Carla.
- Wait.
What the hell are you doing?
What are you trying to ruin everything?
- [Rachel] Is he dead?
- No.
No thanks to you.
- You had to screw him
one last time, didn't you?
- Don't be stupid.
I was just trying to wear him
out so he'd pass out quicker.
- Don't give me that shit.
You may get away with
treating your men like this,
but I won't stand for it.
Do you hear me?
- Yeah, I hear you.
You sound like a jealous old harping wife.
- You just remember who's
inheriting all the money.
- You just remember who
set this whole thing up,
who went to every stinkin'
tractor pull and rodeo
looking for just the right guy.
Do you know how many assholes I had
to let slobber all over me
until I finally found Travis?
- Yeah and I'm sure it
was a real sacrifice
for someone with your
high moral upbringing.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You put out for every
boy in high school,
including your own brothers.
- I don't need this shit.
- Carla.
Carla, I'm sorry.
Okay?
I didn't mean it.
You know that I didn't.
The money doesn't mean anything to me.
I'm sorry.
- Well let's go get Holden.
(ominous music)
Jesus Christ.
- Now what?
(ominous music)
- Good enough.
Okay.
You check the road from here to the cabin
and I'm gonna backtrack to your house.
Holden's gotta be someplace in between.
- Carla, I don't think I can keep this up.
- Rachel.
Don't fold on me now.
We're almost home.
We're almost home, okay?
Please?
(gentle music)
(soft music)
- Carla?
(gentle music)
(soft music)
(dramatic music)
(gentle music)
- Oh god.
(suspenseful music)
(clock ticking)
(gentle music)
(phone ringing) (gentle music)
- [Clay] You've reached
Fairfield Investigations.
You know what to do.
Wait for it.
(phone beeping)
- [Anne] Mr. Fairfield,
my name is Anne Avery.
My father is missing and...
- Hello, Miss Avery?
- Mr. Fairfield.
- Yes ma'am.
What's this about your father missing?
- That's right.
For quite some time now.
And it says here he had
a 10:30 meeting with you?
- He missed it.
- I knew it.
I knew it.
Something's happened to him.
- Well now, don't go
jumpin' to conclusions.
Where are ya?
- [Anne] My father's house.
- All right, give me some
time to get myself together
and I'll be out there
in less than an hour.
- Thanks.
Bye.
(ominous music)
- Little bit late for
a ride in the country,
isn't it Mrs. Avery?
Your husband there looks dead on his feet.
Hands, please.
(gentle music)
(phone dialing)
(phone ringing)
Hello, Sheriff's Office?
Hello?
Damn piece of shit.
I just fixed this the other day.
Ah, here we go.
Yeah, hello?
Yeah, I thought I lost
you there for a second.
My name's Clay Fairfield.
I used to be on the force.
Now I'm a P.I.
I just uncovered a.
(woman screaming)
(tires screeching)
- Carla, is that you?
- Who'd you think it would be, Rachel?
The goddamned auto club?
- Is he dead?
- Well I damn-near hit
him at 50 miles an hour.
- What're you doing?
Let's get out of here.
- Oh, you can drive like that?
With your hands behind your back?
Come on.
- Oh my god.
He was my alibi, Carla.
You just ran over my alibi.
- I already thought of that.
He wrote everything down
in this stupid little book.
See look, it says he
watched you at the bar
until he went to meet Holden at 10:30.
Oh my god.
This is even better than we planned.
- You keep saying that but I don't see it.
- It says that Anne called
and said Holden was missing.
He suspects Travis.
So when the cops find him,
they'll think that Travis
killed him and Holden both.
We just have to make
sure the cops find this.
Ready?
Okay, ready?
One.
Two, three.
(dramatic music)
- You stinkin' bitch.
You just been settin'
me up this whole time.
Well now I got myself a little
bit of a dilemma, don't I?
Should I kill you first?
Or maybe you, huh?
- Oh, way to go, Rachel.
My grandmother could've knocked him out
for longer than that.
- This is my fault?
- Well it's not my fault.
- I cannot believe.
- Oh, don't even start whining.
- I let you talk me into this.
- You know something?
You are the biggest whiny spoiled brat.
- Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
- Don't, don't.
(ominous music)
Take his gun.
Take his gun, Rachel.
(ominous music)
- Now what?
- I don't know.
Let me think.
- Well make it fast.
The sun's gonna be up any minute.
- Okay, I got it.
We'll take him deep into the woods
and bury him where the
cops will never find him.
And then they'll just
think that he got away.
- Hey, come on, Carla.
Look, you don't have
to do that, all right?
You don't have to do that.
You just let me go, you'll
never see me again, I promise.
- Okay, just shut up.
Just shut up.
Do you think it'll work?
- Yeah.
Your alibi's still perfect
and with him out of the way,
the frame-up's even stronger.
(laughs) It's almost better
than we planned (laughs).
- Yeah.
It is.
- I know you're not gonna
believe this but I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- Don't do this, Carla.
Please don't do this.
(gun firing)
(ominous music)
- You never would've changed.
Not even for me.
Once a whore, always a whore.
Don't touch her.
I'm the one she loved, not you.
- All right then.
What about me, huh?
- Put these on.
Do it.
No, behind you.
(ominous music)
Just so you don't get any bright ideas.
Evidence.
(ominous music)
Let's go.
- Where?
- Oh, you're gonna escape.
After killing my husband, your partner,
the private investigator
who almost caught you.
- Listen to me, Rachel.
This is never gonna work, okay?
You're never gonna get away with this.
- Would you just shut up?
This has been the worst night of my life
and it's all your fault.
Keep moving.
(ominous music)
Keep walking.
That's right.
Up the hill.
(clock ticking)
Okay.
That's far enough.
- Look don't do this, Rachel.
Come on.
All right, look, I'm beggin' ya.
- Will you just shut up
and take it like a man?
- Fuck you.
(ominous music)
(suspenseful music)
Goddammit.
(gentle music)
(phone dialing) (gentle music)
(phone ringing)
- [Operator] 911, state your emergency.
(gentle music)
- There you are.
You lookin' for me, huh?
(suspenseful music)
You fuckin' point a
gun at me, huh, Rachel?
Take it like a man, huh.
Take it like a man.
God.
Goddammit.
(suspenseful music)
(ominous music)
(upbeat music)
♪ She's a beautiful woman ♪
♪ They're the dangerous kind ♪
♪ She's got pretty this and that ♪
♪ Heaven ever designed ♪
♪ You never see it coming ♪
♪ There's not a next time ♪
♪ She's a beautiful woman ♪
♪ They're the dangerous kind ♪
♪ Better loosen your collar ♪
♪ You see I know a way ♪
- Here in Bakersfield,
police are stepping up
the search for a kidnapping
suspect, Travis Brewer,
who now potato heiress Rachel Avery
may be a victim of that kidnapping.
♪ You got the local Delilah ♪
♪ Running through your mind ♪
♪ She's a beautiful woman ♪
♪ They're the dangerous kind ♪
♪ Beautiful woman ♪
(dramatic music)
♪ There are certain things in life ♪
♪ That I've taken as a given ♪
♪ Little things that we accept ♪
♪ Everyday that we're living ♪
♪ One thing that don't make sense ♪
♪ I just don't understand ♪
♪ Who the hell ever said
the devil was a man ♪
♪ A man ♪
♪ Well I was lying on the floor ♪
♪ I was busted up and bleeding ♪
♪ When I vision came to me ♪
♪ Was the garden of Eden ♪
♪ I had to take notice ♪
♪ I had to sit and stare ♪
♪ A snake bit the apple ♪
♪ Had curlers in her hair ♪
♪ One thing that don't make sense ♪
♪ No, I just don't understand ♪
♪ Who the hell ever said
the devil was a man ♪
♪ The devil comes in high heels ♪
♪ Devil tells you lies ♪
♪ Devil sings so sweetly
with the fire in her thighs ♪
♪ The devil's got some stockings ♪
♪ Devil's got long legs ♪
♪ The devil comes in closing
time and teaches you to beg ♪
♪ Busted down the room
below just steal guitar ♪
♪ Can't drive it up so sweet ♪
♪ Just looking for a star ♪
♪ Told me I was pretty ♪
♪ Told me I was good ♪
♪ She said she liked the engine
that was underneath my hood ♪
♪ Two years later as she's
leaving me for dead ♪
♪ She always wore a hat to
hide the horns on her head ♪
♪ Yeah the devil comes in high heels ♪
♪ The devil tells you lies ♪
♪ Devil sings so sweetly
with the fire in her thighs ♪
♪ Devil's got silk stockings ♪
♪ The devil's got long legs ♪
♪ The devil comes at closing
time and teaches you to beg ♪
♪ I never really understood ♪
♪ It's just like a disease ♪
♪ Where's the wicked women
are a mystery woman ♪
♪ Thunder and lightening ♪
♪ Fire up on high ♪
♪ Six inch heels turn my head
and I can't tell you why ♪
♪ One thing that don't make sense ♪
♪ No, I just don't understand ♪
♪ Who the hell ever said
the devil was a man ♪
♪ One thing that don't make sense ♪
♪ No, I just don't understand ♪
♪ Who the hell ever said
the devil was a man ♪
♪ One thing that don't make sense ♪
♪ No, I just don't understand ♪
♪ Who the hell ever said
the devil was a man ♪
♪ Who the hell ever said ♪
♪ That the devil was a man ♪
(dramatic music)
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org