- Truman, Truman, wake up.
There's someone in the house.
- Wake up, wake up.
- Oh, party's over, huh?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
Thanks, great party.
By the way, where exactly am I?
- Belle, just a second,
I wanna put these out for the mailman.
- Good morning, Mr. Weston.
- Thank you, Belle.
- Weston residence.
Yes, just a moment.
It's for you, Mr. Weston.
- Oh, thanks, Belle.
Yeah, yeah, what is it, Mike?
I've got exactly seven minutes.
Belle, Belle, can you get him
to hold it down out there, please?
- Yes sir, it's fine, Mr. Weston.
Hey, hey, can you hold
it down out there.
- Belle, listen, I'm gonna late tonight.
I've got a meeting
downtown with the buyers.
Oh, will you get this refilled for me?
- Oh sure, Mrs. Weston,
I'll keep dinner for you.
- Thank you.
- Mike, Mike, if
I could off the phone.
Yes, yes.
- Pasta stuffed for dinner.
- Yes, Mrs. Weston.
- All right, Mike, I'll be there.
Okay, I'm on my way, bye.
Belle, I want you to go
to the cleaners today,
pick up my gray suit.
I've got a big meeting tomorrow.
It's my lucky suit.
- You better pick out a lucky tie too.
That suit don't work
too good the last time.
- You know something, she's right.
Better make it the blue one.
- Hold it.
Have you both forgot that
today's Robey's birthday?
- Aw.
- Oh no.
- I'll just have to pick
up something at lunch.
I'm really late.
- Okay.
Belle, tell him that I
said happy birthday
and that I'll see him tonight.
Maybe you can pick him
up a cake or something.
Traffic's gonna be murder.
See you later, Belle.
- Bye, Mrs. Weston.
Hey, hold it, where do
you think you're going?
Get in the kitchen and
get some breakfast.
- No, I'm not hungry right now, okay?
- Go and don't you give
me no trouble, huh?
- Blow out the candles and make a wish.
Now, open your present.
- Thanks, Belle.
- You find a girlfriend
to give it to, okay?
- Okay.
- Good, now go.
Go or you're gonna be late for school.
- Hey, I'm goin'.
Bye.
- Bye.
- I'm bringing Mason Wainwright
home for dinner tonight.
- I can't do this every night, Truman.
- No, no, no, no, just
Wainwright, that's all.
I just need tonight,
I'll close the deal.
- That's what you said last night.
- Look, this is my business.
You know how may guys are out there
just waiting for me to slip
up this much, and I'm out.
I'm back to designing strip malls
for some two-bit developer in Ohio.
- That's not gonna happen.
- Baby, we are so close.
We're so close.
Wainwright is the biggest client
that I've ever brought into the office.
He's got 60 lots of prime
L.A. real estate to develop.
The partnership's mine.
Kramer's about to retire.
He's practically dropping it in my lap.
- Truman, what have you done?
- Come here.
Now, don't peek.
- Truman, what are you doing?
- Do not peek.
Okay.
Peek.
- What is that?
- It's leased.
Gotta look like we can
play with the big boys.
- Truman, we can't afford a new car.
We're up to our ears in debt.
You never needed an expensive
car to do your job before.
- It's not just my job.
It's my career, it's my life.
You know what they say, if you
wait till you can afford it,
you're never gonna have it.
- Truman, I can go back to
work, at least part time.
- Christ, Patty, don't bring me down.
Can't you just believe in me?
Haven't I given you everything?
- What I want is a home
and a family, Truman,
not a car payment or a mortgage.
- You let me worry about that.
I'm gonna take care of you.
But we're so close,
baby, we're so close.
Dinner's at eight.
Wear somethin' pretty, okay?
- Can you believe this guy's called
three times in one morning?
- Good morning!
- Thanks, Patty.
Am I ever glad you're here.
Everyone in this office is
acting incredibly strange today.
Even my computer is on the fritz.
I can't get the functions to work.
Look at that one.
Call back Brad, he's called three times
in less than an hour.
Please, just call him.
- Did Wainwright call?
- No, not this morning.
- Well, give him an hour or
so to sleep off last night,
and confirm dinner with him tonight,
okay, call him.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's this?
- What's goin' on in there?
- I have a great respect
for your talent.
- Beats me, Green and Kramer
have been hiding in there for two hours.
Something's up.
- You're my eyes and ears
around here, darling,
keep 'em open.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Hey, Cheryl.
- Hi, Robey, why aren't you in class?
- Uh, well, I was
actually waiting for you.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
- Sure, what is it?
- Well, today's kinda my birthday,
and uh, I was just hopin' that maybe
you'd like to come over
later, maybe do something.
- Oh, I'm really sorry, I can't.
I'm kinda seein' somebody right now.
- Oh.
Well, that's okay.
- I'm really sorry,
happy birthday, though.
- Yeah.
Sure.
- Oh, Mr. Kramer, I just wanted to--
- What's goin' on?
- All right, here's all I know.
His name is Alex West,
and he's some hot shot over
with Platt and Associates.
Kramer's been on the phone with him
for the past couple of weeks.
- What for?
- I don't know, nobody's talking.
- Nothing to worry about there.
- It's big.
- Oh no, definitely--
- Keep on, okay?
- Remind me, none of my lawyers--
- All right.
- All the way.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Tough day, Mr. Weston.
- Just long, Belle.
- Well, your lucky suit
is up in the closet,
but I'm pushing for the blue one.
So, you want the good
news or the bad news.
- Uh, surprise me.
- Okay, here goes.
The gardener busted out the
window in the guest house.
I told him that if he doesn't
replace it before it rains,
he'd find a scorpion in his bed.
- Okay, so what's the good news?
- That is the good news.
The bad news is the school called.
Robey didn't show up today.
- Robey!
- Excuse me, Mr. Weston.
- Yeah, dad?
- Robey, come down here.
- Traitor.
- So, it was a nice day today.
You have the top down, yeah?
Good, good.
We got just a few weeks left
till the end of the school year.
And the Brookview Academy agreed
to take you as part of
their summer session,
providing you brought up your
academic standing a notch.
So, do you think now is the
time for you to fuck up?
- I don't understand why
I can't just finish high school here.
- Robey, the Brookview Academy's
one of the finest college
prep schools in the country.
Your mother and
I are trying to give you
an opportunity that few
young men could hope for,
your freedom to choose a
college, to choose your life,
rather than the other way around.
- And if I choose something different.
- Well, I guess until you're capable
of making those decisions
with some sort of clarity,
I'll just have to make 'em for you.
Give me the keys.
- What?
- Give me the car keys.
- Dad, come on.
- The keys, Robey,
just call it business.
When you can hold up
your end of the bargain,
then you can have 'em back.
It's the way life works.
- Yeah, well, it sucks.
- What'd you say?
- I said, yes, sir.
- Wait, watch out for that step.
Come on, here.
Uh, sorry we're late.
We just, we stopped for a drink.
Time just slipped away.
Are we forgiven?
- I would personally feel very hurt
if I wasn't forgiven by
such a beautiful woman.
- Dinner's been ready for over an hour.
I can't guarantee the outcome.
- Well, if tastes a fraction
as delicious as you are,
my dear, I'm sure it'll
be a veritable feast.
- Come on, let me get ya a drink.
- And yes!
Very nice.
You are too kind.
- Pat,
babe.
You can save that for later.
Mason thinks you don't like him.
- Truman, I'd like to get
this food off the table.
- Come on, have some wine.
- I'm really tired.
- I got him hooked.
Help me reel him in.
Be nice to him, party a little bit.
Hey, buddy
- Yeah.
- A little freshener.
- Uh, yeah, thanks.
- And Patty, as glass--
- No, please, no.
- Oh, please, have one.
- Excuse me.
Hello.
Who?
- Your husband's a very lucky man.
- My man.
- He's gonna make
a lot of money with me.
- Well, good.
- The party's canceled.
No, there's no party tonight.
- To big business?
- Just the guy I'm--
- Okay.
- Tell them tomorrow.
- You're a very beautiful woman.
- Yes, I'll call you tomorrow.
- I beg your pardon.
- All right.
Talk to you later, bye, bye.
- Sorry.
Just tryin' to be a little friendly.
- Yeah, right.
- Hey, what's goin' on?
- You finish your business
and you tell that creep
to get out of here.
- Well, what's the matter?
- He had his hands all over
me, that's what's the matter.
- He wouldn't be here if
this wasn't so important.
- Did you hear what I said to you?
- I'm just being cordial to him.
- He had his hand up my dress.
- Look, I need this deal.
Please, be nice to him!
- What are you saying?
- Just do this for us.
- Damn it!
- Mason.
- Hm?
- Have some more wine.
- Very impressive, Truman.
As a matter of fact, you've,
you impress the hell.
- We have a deal, then?
- Well, I was kind of
looking for something
a little bit extra, something,
how shall I say, to,
uh, sweeten the pot.
- Mason, I've done my homework on you.
You're in good hands.
- That's what I've been
waitin' to hear, Truman.
That is what I have been
waiting to hear all night long.
You forgot your wine.
- Truman, I didn't
expect you this early.
- I just closed the Wainwright deal,
thought I'd get started
on the paperwork.
- Now Truman, I'd like
you to meet Alex Weston.
- How do you do?
- Alex, this is Truman Langley.
Alex will be joining us.
- Uh, I'm gonna grab a cup of coffee.
- Good idea.
- It was nice meeting you, Truman.
- What's up, Mike?
- Weston's a good man,
top executive at Platt and Associates.
He comes in with two major
international developers
and a luxury hotel chain.
Now, I don't have to tell you
what clients like that
are gonna do for us.
- That's great, that's great, Mike.
- And I'm thinking about retiring--
- Mike, please, why
don't you just tell me
what's going on around here?
- Partnership's going to Weston.
- Jesus Mike, it's my partnership,
I worked my ass off for that.
- It was the only way we
could get him to come in.
And now, we need a strong administrator,
and we're gonna have to
ask you to step down,
take an office downstairs--
- Wait, wait, what are you gonna do?
Just put me in shipping and receiving
until you can get rid
of me all together?
- I'm sorry, Truman.
- Yeah, yeah, I'm sorry too.
- Rina.
- Mm?
- Can you take this off?
- Mm, honey, what time is it?
It's, uh, it's 11:30.
- A.m or p.m.?
- A.m.
- Oh, god.
Mm.
Alex, if you didn't know me,
would you wanna have sex with me?
- Sweetheart, I do know you,
and I am trying desperately to
have sex with you right now.
- No, honey.
I mean, I if was just some stranger
that you saw standing across
the street, would you want me?
- Rina, I don't
know what you want me to say.
- God Alex, just
answer the damn question.
- Yes, I would wanna make love to you.
I wanna make love to you right now,
but you kinda have to be here for it.
- I thought that we agreed to
use some sort of protection.
I think I may be ovulating.
- Well, that did it.
- Here.
I think that we should pretend
that we're adrift in the
middle of the ocean all day.
- Don't mind if I swim to shore
for coffee and a Sunday paper, do ya?
- Black, lots of sugar.
- Aye aye, captain.
- Oh Alex, could you check on Robey.
I didn't hear him come in last night.
- Sure.
- Tru.
Truman?
Whatcha doin', honey?
- I'm goin' to the office.
- It's Sunday, you never
work on Sunday, honey.
- Partnership went to someone else.
- Workin' on Sunday, huh, Mr. Langley?
I guess that's why you
make the big bucks, huh?
Mr. Langley, Mr. Langley?
Mr. Langley?
- Belle.
Belle!
- Excuse me, Mr. Weston.
You scared me half to death.
- I'm sorry, Belle, I just
wanted to let you know
I'm gonna be doing some
work at home this afternoon.
- In all the years
that I worked for you,
I can't remember you worked at home.
Something wrong, Mr. Weston?
- Yeah, well, I can't move into
my new office until tomorrow
because maintenance has to repaint,
then patch a bullet hole first.
I'll be in the den if anyone calls.
Oh, and Belle, I want you to go upstairs
and find my lucky suit and burn it.
Robey.
Robey!
I'm trying to get some work done here.
- Yeah.
- Robey, are you smoking?
- We'll catch ya later here, man.
Nice to see you, Mr. Weston.
- Good morning, Kramer,
Weston, Green, and Associates,
how may I direct your call?
One moment please.
Good morning, Kramer, Weston,
Green, and Associates,
how may I direct your call?
Good morning, Mr. Green.
Yes, she is, let me transfer you.
Hi, I'll be with you in one second.
- Good morning, Kramer,
Weston, Green, and Associates,
how may I direct your call?
Can I take a message?
Thank you.
Mr. Kramer's expecting
you, go right ahead.
- Good morning, Kramer,
Weston, Green, and Associates,
how may I direct your call?
- Mr. Kramer, Patricia
Langley is here to see you.
- Oh, bring her in.
Ah, Patty.
- Hi Mike.
- Here, sit down, come.
Can I get you something, coffee, tea?
- No, thank you, I'm fine.
- We're all so very sorry.
- Mike, about the company's
life insurance plan,
isn't there something you can do?
- It's completely out
of my hands, Patty.
Since Truman's death was self-inflicted,
the policy is worthless.
Now surely, Truman had
a personal policy.
- He borrowed against it.
- What about other assets?
Stocks, savings?
- I haven't really gotten
into that yet, Mike.
- Aw, give yourself some time,
and when you're ready,
I'll be here to help you.
Oh.
Well, let me get you some water.
- Good, I'll get someone to
work on these right away.
- Right.
- Uh, Karen, can you file these please.
- Sure, have a nice lunch.
- Good tastes, Weston.
- Thanks.
- I don't know if you're
up to this, Patty,
but some of Truman's things
are still in Alex Weston's office.
I thought you might
wanna go through them.
I'll leave you alone for a little while.
- You son of a bitch.
Who did you have to fuck, Alex Weston?
- I need this deal!
Please!
Be nice to him!
- I was just tryin' to
be a little friendly.
- Just do this.
- Well, nice to see you again.
What?
- I say we cut out at
third period, don't you?
- I can't cut
out at third period, man.
- I've got 35
kids in my gym class.
35, got that?
I don't know, they wanna play
two-on-two basketball with 35 kids.
- Good morning, may I help you?
- I hope so.
My husband and I just moved
here from the east coast,
and we were hoping to enroll
our daughter Stephanie
in El Camino next semester.
- Well, this is a lovely school.
- Our concern is that Stephanie
would have difficulty
with the new curriculum,
and I was hoping you
could recommend a tutor
who could bring her up to
speed during the summer.
- Oh, we have several wonderful teachers
who work during the summer.
I have them on file.
Let me get them for you.
- Thank you.
- Well, it's a 12th grade course
to prepare them for college.
- Let me get, I have
to get back to my gym course.
I got them playing volleyball.
- Volleyball?
- Here's a list of teachers
who do private tutoring,
and here's an application for admission,
and we're looking forward to
seeing Stephanie in the fall.
- Thank you.
Goodbye.
I'm gonna destroy you Alex Weston,
you and your family, one by one.
- Robey!
- What's wrong, Mr. Weston?
- Aw, nothing, now, where's Robey?
- Oh, he went out.
- What about Mrs. Weston?
- Upstairs, I think.
Rina, Marina!
- I'm on an island in the
middle of the Caribbean.
Unless you come bearing
pineapples and trinkets,
there's no one home in
this little grass hut.
- How 'bout if I scrub your back?
- Mm, only if I can call you boy.
- There's a letter from Robey's school.
- Aw, what now?
- Uh, I don't know.
They're afraid they can't recommend him
for the Brookview Academy
unless he can bring his
overall grade point up
before the end of the semester.
- Alex, he studies, we
stay on him all the time.
I mean, what else can we do?
- I don't know.
Maybe he's not focused.
They suggested a tutor.
They sent a list of three names.
- You're looking at me like I
have time to deal with this.
- I'm overwhelmed at the office.
I had to take over all of
Truman Langley's clients--
- Enough, boy, I'll call these people,
but you have to be the one to tell him
that he has to spend the
rest of his free time
with his nose in a book.
- Why not?
I'm his least favorite
person right now anyway.
- Hm, Belle, can you find
my other shoe for me,
please, sweetie, I'm gonna be late?
- Oh sure, Mrs. Weston.
- Thank you.
Yes hi, I'm trying to
reach Amanda Cressfield.
- Yes, this is Amanda Cressfield.
Yes, I am available.
I'd be glad to.
When would you like to start?
- Could you come by this evening?
I'm sorry I'm in such a rush.
- That'll be fine.
Yes, I have a pencil right here, mm-hmm.
Say, 5:30 then.
Look forward to meeting you, Mrs.
Weston.
- Robey, could you come in here please?
There's someone I'd
like for you to meet.
Sweetheart, please don't
bounce that in the house,
I've asked you not to.
Robey, this is Amanda Cressfield.
She's gonna be your new tutor.
- Nice to meet you.
It'll be painless, I promise.
Have a seat.
- He hasn't been very focused lately.
He has the potential,
but he just hasn't
been applying himself.
- I'd like to hear what you have to say.
- Alex, sweetheart,
could you come in here for a minute?
There's someone I'd
like for you to meet.
Amanda, this is my husband, Alex.
- Well, it's nice to meet you.
- Alex, this is Amanda Cressfield.
She's gonna be tutoring Robey.
- Pleasure.
- Oh, sweetheart, you found someone.
- Yeah.
- We really appreciate your help.
So, when can you start.
- Well, there may be a slight problem.
The owners of the building I live in
are having some contractors come over
to do renovations on Tuesday,
and I know this morning I
said I could start earlier,
but I'm gonna need about a week
to find a new place to live.
- Well, Robey's finals
are in just a few weeks.
- I know.
- I'll understand if you
wanna find someone else,
and I'll help you.
- We have a guest house.
- The guest house?
It needs so much work.
Alex, what do you think?
- I don't know, it's
empty, if you don't mind.
Well, I think if it helps our
son get in Brookview Academy,
then I'm all for it.
Thanks, Belle.
- Belle, do you think that you
could work some magic
with the guest house?
- If that's what you want, Mrs. Weston.
- I can't thank you enough.
That's just terrific.
- What do you mean, you gotta go?
You gotta go where?
- I gotta go study with a tutor.
- Oh man, come on.
You are turnin' into a drag.
We're not gonna be able
to get a game goin'.
You know, Weston, if you get
a plastic pocket protector
and some glasses, you
could be a real nerd.
- Hi, Robey.
Want a ride?
- Dude!
- Thought we could get started early.
Wanna drive?
- Whoa.
- Who was that?
- I don't know, man, but she is awesome.
- You're doing good work, Robey.
Trust me, we'll have your
grades lined up in no time.
- You should have something to eat.
You'll get a headache if you
work your brain too hard
on an empty stomach.
- Thanks, Belle.
- Yeah, thanks, Belle.
Now, if you don't mind, we're busy.
- Yeah, sure, I just wanted to make sure
he doesn't strain his brain or his eyes.
- Quite a shopping spree.
- I am so glad to be home.
I have been to at least
a 100 different stores.
My feet hurt and my back is killing me.
- Well, 30 minutes of yoga
and a massage works wonders.
- Well, if I start right now,
I might just be lucky enough
to be presentable by seven o'clock.
- Okay, um, hot bath, stiff drink.
Less therapeutic, same results.
- You know what the really
irritating thing is?
Alex will come in here at 6:15,
he will shave, shower, dress,
and be standing downstairs harping at me
that we're gonna be late by 6:45.
- Where do you want these?
- Um, upstairs, actually,
I was hoping Belle would
be here to help me.
Belle!
- She must be out shopping
or something, let me help.
- Oh no, I couldn't ask.
- Please, I'm dying to
see what you've bought.
- Okay, okay.
- Running one very hot bubble
bath with essence of gardenia.
- Oh, I can't thank you enough.
I wanted to thank you for all
of your hard work with Robey.
He's been very dedicated
for the last few days.
He feels very comfortable with you.
I just don't get to
spend much time with him.
- That's a devastating gown.
Party?
- Fundraiser at the country club,
all of Alex's design cronies.
Do you really think it's me?
You don't think that
it's too much for me?
- Are you kidding?
You'll be stunning.
- Huh, you know, sometimes
I forget how old I am.
I find myself having to mark my age
by how many years we've
lived in this house
or when we bought our second
car or the year Robey was born.
- Time slips away quickly, doesn't it?
- Sometimes, I feel like I
haven't paid enough attention,
you know, or, I don't know, I just,
somehow things just slipped
by me when I wasn't looking.
- It's easy to let that happen.
- Yeah, most of the time,
I just see a stranger in the mirror.
When did I get to be a grownup?
- About the time you
joined the country club.
I think they only
take grownups, don't they?
- Oh my god, you're right.
I have become a country club matron.
- Trust me, not in that dress.
Oh, your bath!
I'll get it.
Hello, Weston residence.
- Is Alex home, please?
- No, I'm sorry, he's not.
Can I take a message?
- Oh no, it's not important.
- Want me to tell him who called.
- It's uh, Mike
Kramer, I'll call back.
- Who was that?
- Oh, some woman,
wanted to talk to Alex.
Wouldn't leave a message and
refused to give her name.
You know what they say, if
a woman answers, hang up.
Hot bath and wine as promised.
- Oh thanks, you're very sweet.
Mm.
- More wine?
- Mm, I'm Cleopatra
floating down the Nile
alone on my barge.
- Well, Your Highness,
you're getting pruny.
No one likes a pruny potentate.
Especially in a low-cut gown.
- Mm.
- You know, I used to model a little
when I was much younger, and
I worked with a designer once,
and he said to me, the
key to how a woman feels
when she wears my clothes
is how she puts them on,
and he said, everything
that touches a woman's body
should feel good because
when she feels good,
she looks good.
And now, a little scent
on all the pulse points.
And you never know.
Look how beautiful you are.
- I feel beautiful.
- Marina, honey, I'm home!
Marina!
Marina, let's go, we're gonna be late!
- I'm gonna finish up
my work now, Mr. Weston.
I'll see you on Monday.
- Aw, that's great, Belle.
Be sure to lock up, and
have a nice weekend.
- Thank you.
- Alex, I'm ready.
- Rina?
I love it.
- Oh, Mrs. Weston, you
look so beautiful.
- It was worth the wait, sweetheart.
- Ow, Belle, come on.
I was just lookin' for my basketball.
- Sure, and pigs fly.
So, young Mr. Weston
is now a peeping Tom.
- I am not, I didn't do anything.
- You are not so big
that I still can't put you over my knee.
If I catch you again, I am
going to tell your father.
Now, go to your room,
and if you look for that dirty
magazine under your mattress,
you won't find it no more.
- How does it feel?
- How does what feel?
Why are you in here?
- I wanted to see your room.
- It's kinda messy.
- You were lookin' in my
window tonight, weren't you?
- Ow!
- Don't lie.
It doesn't feel very good
havin' someone spy on you, does it?
When you do bad things,
you have to be punished.
Have you ever been punished?
- Yes.
- It's Friday night.
Why aren't you out with your
friends having a good time?
- I don't know.
- Are you a virgin?
Next time you wanna see something,
knock on my door and ask me.
- Oh shit.
Shit!
- I'm gonna teach you everything I know.
Pay attention.
You'll be tested on
all the material later.
I expect your grades to go up.
I may even give you a pop quiz.
Take off your clothes.
Do it.
All of them.
Mm.
You have to go.
- I wanna stay here.
- You can't, if your father
catches you here at this hour,
it's over for us, do you understand?
- All right.
- Robey.
- Yes, sir.
- Robey, it's four
o'clock in the morning.
Where have you been?
- Out.
- Out?
Well, for the next week,
you can just stay in.
You come straight home after
school and hit the books.
- Yes, sir.
- Oh god.
- So, how much did you
have to drink last night?
- I don't know, I didn't
think I had that much.
I was very tired.
- You were very drunk.
- Alex please, if I made
a fool out of myself,
I don't wanna hear about it, not now.
- Okay.
- Mind if I join you?
- No, of course not, sit down.
I've been wanting to talk to
you for several days anyway.
How's the guest house?
- It's wonderful.
Can't thank you enough for that.
- Well, it will be thanks enough
if you tell me my son's
grades are improving.
- He's doing great.
- Really?
- He seems very eager to please.
- That's a relief.
You know, he's got finals
in less than a week.
- He'll be fine.
I notice you have a
pool table in the house.
Do you play?
- Why, do you?
- Oh, I can hold my own.
- Is that a challenge?
I'm warning you, I play for keeps.
- So do I.
What are you doing?
- Just giving you some privacy.
- I'll be home in time
for dinner, Belle.
- Belle, I want you to go to my room
and take those damn birds out of there.
I also want you to strip
all the beds upstairs today.
- But Mrs. Weston, I just--
- Belle, just do it, and don't
give me such a hard time!
Jesus, just once I would like to ask
that something be done
and see that happened.
I just wanna know that I'm
sleeping on clean sheets.
I don't think that I'm
asking for too much, do you?
Thank you.
- Oy vey.
- Now, we're
going to do a figure eight
only we're not gonna
do it with our finger.
We're going to do it
with our hips, like this.
Okay, let's start with
a twist to the left.
- Weston residence.
- Push your right hip--
Right, left, and center, please.
Push to the right and here,
push the left hip back.
Back, center.
Hips, like this.
Okay?
But to start, we'll twist
to the left, bend the knees,
two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
Back and center.
Hips, like this.
Okay?
But to start, we'll twist, and left.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Chest, two, three, four.
Push your chest one and then in one.
Back and forth, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Push your chest, front, and
slide you chest to the left.
Then touch right back,
rolling the shoulders forward.
Then relax.
Ready, and five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- And then there were three.
- One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven.
- Belle!
I'm home!
Belle!
Hey.
I'm gonna go do my homework.
Amanda?
- I'm in here.
Wait, wait, whoa, whoa!
Wait, how did you do on your math quiz?
- Got a 94.
- Oh, let me see.
- What, you don't trust me?
- No ticket, no laundry, let me see.
Oh, very good boy.
What's this?
What is this?
- I hate French.
I don't get it.
- Yesterday when I asked
you about French,
you said you were doing fine.
48 isn't fine!
A 48 isn't acceptable.
A 48 isn't even passing.
- It's my worst subject.
- You lied to me.
You know how I feel about lying.
- I'm sorry, I--
- Turn around, turn
around, face the table.
- What are you gonna do,
spank me or something?
Ow!
- You're gonna learn French.
- What?
My name is--
- In French and quickly.
- Ow!
You're hungry.
You want something hard.
- Raise your arms.
Do you now what this is?
- No.
- Well, you're gonna find out.
Don't move, uh huh.
Uh huh, in an hour, I promise,
you'll be able to beg in two languages.
- Belle!
Belle!
This is all my fault.
I was in a bad mood and
I took it out on her.
- It's not your fault.
It was an accident, just an accident.
- No, I'll never believe that.
- It was just an accident, mom.
- I'm gonna make you some tea.
- Rina!
- Alex.
Oh, Alex.
- I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Help me get your mother upstairs.
- Nice shot.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Oh, I'm sorry, I hate that too.
Couldn't sleep, huh?
- No.
No, I couldn't.
- I'm sorry about Belle.
How's Marina?
- She's upstairs, she's a mess.
She blames herself.
- Well, that's ridiculous.
- Marina hasn't been too clear lately
on exactly what's
ridiculous and what isn't.
- Oh, tranquilizers will
have that effect on you.
- Is it that obvious?
She's been under a lot of stress.
- Moodiness, depression, denial,
loss of appetite, loss of sex drive.
15 in the corner.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid of me.
- It's been a hell of a day.
Belle was with us for 12 years.
She was part of the family.
My wife is upstairs passed
out on Valium again.
My son hates me.
I'm down here feelin' sorry for myself.
And yes, I am afraid of you,
afraid of looking at you too long,
afraid of standing too close to you,
afraid that right now I could
justify almost anything.
- I can help you, Alex.
I know what you're going through.
Hurt me, Alex.
Harder, come on.
- Robey?
- So Alex, that was one
hell of a game of pool.
You know, I've been thinkin',
maybe goin' off to school
might not be such a bad idea after all.
We can just call it business.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, I made you some coffee.
- Amanda, you don't have to do that.
- I know, I want to.
- Marina's not feeling
well this morning.
- I'll stay with her.
You need me.
- Chapman Pharmacy, good day.
- Hello, this is Marina Weston.
- Yes.
- I'd like to get a prescription
refilled and delivered, please.
- All right,
that shouldn't be a problem.
Do you happen to have
the prescription number
handy, Mrs. Weston.
- Yes, number 1276977.
- Just a moment please.
- Marina?
Are you awake?
I brought you something.
- Amanda?
I didn't know you were here.
- I'm gonna stay and
help out for a while.
- Oh, god.
- Don't cry, everything'll be okay.
Here, camomile, guaranteed
to chase the blues away.
I promise.
Come on, sit up.
- Amanda, I just feel so terrible.
I just feel so terrible
about Belle, about,
I haven't paid any
attention to my house,
my husband, my son, myself.
What on earth is happening to me?
- You've been through
something terrible.
Give yourself a little time.
- No, I've wasted too much
time, and I want it all back.
Amanda,
I'm really glad that you're here.
I don't have anybody else to talk to.
- Oh, there, just lay down, come on.
Everything's gonna be okay, shh.
- Robey isn't in school?
- Hello!
Anyone home?
- Robey?
- Mom, didn't know you were home.
- Why aren't you at school?
- I have to study for finals.
- Robey, don't ignore me.
- I'm not in school
'cause I don't wanna be.
- Sweetheart listen, I know
that you're upset about Belle,
but please don't take this out on me.
- You have no idea what I'm upset about.
You never do.
You wanna know why I'm not in school?
Why don't you ask me
where I was last night
or why I didn't bother to come home?
You didn't even know I wasn't here.
Take another fucking pill, mother.
- Robey!
Robey, please, I'm sorry!
God!
- You go and apologize
to your mother right now.
- No.
I won't.
- I know you're angry, but
you're not angry with her.
You're angry at what you saw
in the pool room last night.
Oh Robey, I wish you hadn't been there.
I wish you hadn't seen what
your father did to me, but.
- He forced you.
- He was angry, hurt.
He didn't know what he was doing.
I know he never would
have done it to me if--
- Did he hurt you?
Did my father hurt you?
Did he hurt you?
- No, I'm all right.
I was just a little scared.
- That son of a bitch.
That son of a bitch!
- Robey, no, wait.
You'll only be making things
worse and hurting your mother.
- I just wanna get the hell outta here.
- I know, baby.
We're almost there.
We're almost there, we're almost there.
Just a few more days, okay?
And you can pack your bags and go.
Marina I brought you some tea.
I'm gonna make some soup or something.
- Um, I'm not hungry.
Tea will be fine.
- You know, you really should eat.
Oh, I found this in the laundry.
It's an antique earing.
I hope you have a mate to
it, it's really beautiful.
- Marina?
Marina, if you're
sick, go to a doctor.
- Oh, Alex, leave me alone, I
don't wanna see you right now.
- Marina, don't shut me out.
- Alex, leave me alone.
- Where are they?
- What?
- These, these, goddamn it!
- I haven't taken anything.
- No!
- Alex, stop it!
- I said, get up, Marina!
- Stop it!
God, stop it, Alex!
- Look at yourself, look at you!
You can't even stand up.
- Alex, stop, no, Alex!
- Don't fight me!
- Stop!
- Damn it, Marina!
Alex, you're hurting me.
Alex, stop!
Alex!
Alex, please!
Alex, you're hurting me.
Alex, stop!
Alex, what are you doing?
- Amanda told me you'd deny it.
I didn't believe her.
Let me tell you something, Robey.
This is my house, and
as long as you're in it,
you're gonna treat me and
your mother with some respect.
You got that?
I don't care what your problem is.
Oh, what, you mad at me, huh?
You wanna take a swing at me?
You wanna challenge me?
Well, come on, you little shit.
Huh?
Come on, tough guy.
- Oh sorry, I just came
to get my sweatshirt.
Marina?
You look like you could use some.
- I guess I was just
feeling a little dizzy.
- Maybe the sun isn't
a good place for you.
- Hm.
I was just trying to stay busy.
Actually, I was, I was
trying to help Robey pack,
but I think I was just more in his way.
I just have to remember
that he's not my little baby anymore.
- No.
I know you'll miss him.
- I already do.
- My apartment will be
ready in a few days.
- So, you're gonna be leaving too?
Amanda, you've been a
really good friend.
- That won't change.
- Oh!
Uh.
Oh!
- Are you all packed?
- Yeah, I guess.
- When do you leave?
- Tomorrow afternoon.
Ryan's pickin' me up,
takin' me to the airport.
- I guess this is our last
chance to say goodbye.
- I'll be home late tonight.
- Alex.
Aren't you even gonna
say goodbye to Robey?
- We've said our goodbyes.
I just think it's better this way.
- Okay.
I love you.
- I love you too, mom.
- I love you so much.
Okay, get outta here.
- All right.
- Now listen, you guys be careful.
- See ya later, Mrs. Weston.
- And please make
sure that you call me, okay?
- And then there were two.
- All right, I'll call
you as soon as we get there.
- Hello.
Hello.
Hello?
Hello!
Whoever this is, I'm
gonna call the police.
- Rina?
Jesus Christ, Rina, what
the hell's wrong with you?
Put down the damn knife.
Rina, it's a blown fuse, that's it.
You stay here, we've just blown a fuse.
- Alex, no,
please don't go downstairs!
- Damn it, Marina, you coulda killed me.
Unless that's what you
were trying to do.
- Alex, there was someone in the house.
Someone kept calling and then
the phone lines went dead.
Then I heard someone on the stairs.
You gotta believe me.
- Rina, Rina listen, the
phone's are fine, Rina.
Everything's all right.
There's no one here.
- Alex, Alex, listen to me.
I think she's trying to kill me.
- Who?
- Amanda, I really think
she's trying to kill me.
- For god's sake, Rina,
Amanda is not here.
Will you listen to me, Rina?
She's not here, you're fine.
- You don't understand.
You gotta believe me.
- For Christ's sake,
Rina, let's go upstairs.
- Alex, don't patronize
me, I am not crazy!
- Rina look at me.
Look at what the tranquilizers
are doing to you.
- God damn you, Alex,
I'm not taking anything.
- Alex.
Alex!
- Yeah?
- I've been talking to
you for two minutes.
Did you hear anything I said?
- Sorry, I'm just a little tired today.
- The design department's looking
for all the research
on Reich Development.
Alex?
Alex, what is wrong with you?
What happened to your hand?
- Uh, it's nothin', i just
had a little accident.
So, where are the files?
- Uh, probably still in
the boxes over there.
- Thanks, Karen, what
would I do without you?
- Mm-hmm, too little, too late, Weston.
Too little, too late.
- I will not be afraid in my own house.
My babies.
Oh, I'll feed my babies.
Angels?
Angels, good morning.
- Hello, Marina.
- What are you doing here?
- I brought you some tea.
- I don't want any tea.
I know that that's
what's making me sick.
- Drink it.
- I don't want it!
- Get up.
Get up.
Don't make this any harder on yourself.
Move!
- What are you gonna do to me?
- Alex is gonna understand
what it's like to have nothing left.
- Please, don't do this.
- He's gonna come home and find
that you slashed your wrists
and bled to death.
- No, no, he knows I could
never do such a thing.
- You've been irrational
and depressed for weeks.
You've taken Seconal every
day with your vitamins,
and yours will be the only
prints left on the knife.
Take it, it won't hurt as
much if you take the pill.
Take the pill, Marina.
That's it.
- Aw, Alex, I'm sorry you're having
to play cleanup behind Langley.
- Ah, it's no problem, Mike.
- Listen, I'd like you to
go over this file with me.
- Excuse me, I have
to make a phone call.
- Alex, is there a problem?
- The woman in this
picture next to Langley,
who is she?
- That's Patricia
Langley, Truman's widow.
- That's it.
- Weston, Weston!
- Excuse me.
- Good afternoon.
Kramer, Weston, and Green Associates,
how may I direct your call?
- I think I have to pay a fine
and uh, hey Alex, how ya doin'?
- Alex!
- The aftermath's a
sign that you really gotta--
- Could you duplicate
these blueprints, please,
and send them over--
- I gotta go over.
- I need you to make an
emergency call for me.
I said a fucking emergency!
Call the police, give 'em my address.
Tell 'em my wife is in danger.
- Is he all right?
You know, if you keep struggling,
the pills won't work very quickly.
I don't have to wait, you know?
You were right, Marina.
You should've paid more attention.
You had it all, you had everything
and you let it slip away.
So did Alex.
And his job is more
important than his wife.
- Marina!
Oh my god!
I know who you are.
Everybody knows.
- I don't give a damn who knows.
You deserve this, you son of a bitch.
- I love my wife very, very much.
Now please, put down the knife.
- Is that why you fucked me, Alex?
'Cause you love your wife so much?
You're pathetic.
Your son's a better
lover than you anyway,
so was your wife for that matter.
- You bitch.
- I'm sorry, Mr. Weston, we've
searched the entire property.
There's no sign of her anywhere.
Obviously, she wasn't hurt
as badly as you thought.
There's nothin' much
left in the guest house,
except a few personal items.
- What do we do if she comes back?
- I strongly doubt if she'll be back.
She knows everyone's lookin' for her.
After you get this arm taken care of,
I'm gonna need you both to
come down to the station,
give us a statement.
Where's your son?
- He's away at school, thanks god.
- Honey, I don't want
him to know about this.
- I'm gonna need that
statement as soon as possible.
Office Young'll wrap up here.
- No, no, no!
- All right, shh.
Shh.
Honey, honey, it's okay,
it's okay, sweetheart.
I just brought you some tea.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
- Alex, it's not that.
I just need some time.
Hello.
- Hello, mom.
- Robey, hi honey, I'm
so glad you called.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Is everything all right?
- Yes, mom, I feel fine.
- I miss you so much, baby.
- Yeah, I miss you too.
- Your father's right here,
would you like to talk to him?
- No, I don't wanna
talk to dad, not now.
- Okay, um, listen, you stay
in touch with us, all right.
I love you.
- I love you.
- Bye.
Mommy and daddy send their love.