(MultiCom Jingle)
(tense music)
(phone beeps)
- [Sanders] Get me the Senator.
- The Colonel.
- The situation under control?
Jesus Christ.
Some fucking mess
you've created.
You call me when it's done.
(slow suspenseful music)
- [Sanders] There
she is, right there.
Come on, step on it.
(tires screeching)
(woman panting)
(gun fires)
(sullen music)
(woman gurgling)
(gun fires)
(eerie music)
- So, anyone else
give me some examples?
Tyler?
- Um, stem cell research.
- Ah.
Stem cell research.
Yet another moralistically
ambiguous topic.
Is it ever ethical to sacrifice
one embryo to save 10,
20, a hundred or a
thousand individuals?
Who would like to speak to that?
Caleb.
- Yeah, I think so.
I mean, it's all about
the greater good, right?
- I don't know
Caleb, you tell me.
Mr. Anderson.
- Well, define the greater good.
- Ah, (chuckles) define
the greater good.
Ava, why don't you
do that for us?
- I don't think
it's right at all.
Who's to say one life is
more important than another.
I mean, where do
we draw the line?
- So, we have four
very different opinions
to one question.
A four-sided, complex
moral question.
Now, who's to say
that either side
will be able to see the
other's perspective.
Right?
Ms. Donovan.
- I'm not sure.
- Indecisiveness will
get you only so far
in my class young lady.
- Well, then, I'd have to
say it's highly unlikely.
I mean, it's hard
enough to get two people
to agree on a movie,
let alone the value of one
life versus the collective.
- Very well put, Ms. Lacie.
All right, good people,
that takes us to the end.
It is indeed semester break,
and contrary to what
Mr. Caleb believes,
I am not an unreasonable man.
So, I've only assigned
chapter seven and eight
to be completed over break.
And yes, Mr. Anderson,
there will be an exam over
this material when you return.
- Can't wait.
- All right, good
people, that's it.
Enjoy your break.
Get some rest.
We'll see you in
a couple of weeks.
Ms. Donovan, can I
speak to you a moment?
- What's up, Professor?
- Well, I'll be frank,
you're missing work.
Two research projects,
two essay papers,
plus you've got a 62
on that last exam.
Now, I'm telling you this
because you're a good student.
Use the break to
get it together.
Come back, finish out
the semester strong.
- I do want to.
I just, I had to work the
night before the exam,
and I did give you the
Roe versus Wade paper.
- Ms. Donovan, I am
not your life coach.
I'm your professor.
You've got time to
make up the work.
Let's make sure that you do.
Okay?
- Okay.
(phone ringing)
Hey.
Whats' up?
(Lacie sighs)
I can't.
Okay.
Yeah, thanks.
(Lacie laughing)
Yeah, good.
Have a good time.
(slow suspenseful music)
Yeah, yeah, I'm here.
Okay, bye.
(dramatic music)
(microwave beeping)
(light knocking)
- [Killian] Lacie.
- Hey, Killian.
- Good, you are up.
Listen, Joe is having
a party tonight,
and you are coming with me.
- Yeah, I don't know.
- Okay, well you do know that
it is officially break, right?
Come on, everyone's doing it.
- Is this peer
pressure I'm detecting?
(Killian laughs)
- No, no, but you
want to fit in, right?
(both laughing)
- Yeah, no, I would
love to go, but um,
I just, I have a ridiculous
amount of studying to do,
and plus I have to get
up early tomorrow, so.
- How is the job going?
- Uh, it sucks.
Overworked, underpaid,
typical stuff.
- [Killian] Bummer.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, since it
is a work night,
what if I promise to
have you home at 11?
(Lacie laughing)
- You know, I am not some
naive freshman anymore.
That stuff doesn't work on me.
- Okay, well, what if I
told you that we bought
a foam machine and we are
about to break it out.
Not gonna lie, it's
gonna get wild.
(Lacie laughs)
- Um, foam machine, wow.
I would have to say,
good luck with that.
- Hey, did you sign up for this?
- No, I wasn't
sure it was for me.
Why?
- Because I signed up
for it earlier this week.
You should totally do it.
A buddy of mine did a
research study like this
a few year ago,
I guess they just had
him play video games
for like five straight days,
and he earned two grand.
Easy money.
- Oh, sounds excruciating.
(Killian chuckles)
- I don't know about that.
He was also saying
that when he was there,
like 90% of the time they
just, you know, read books or--
- Played video games?
- Or played video games.
(both chuckling)
So technically, you could
get some studying done,
and you could earn a few bucks.
- Yeah, that doesn't sound bad.
- No, not at all.
- But uh, but what
are they testing?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, it doesn't say
what we're signing up for.
- Yeah, I asked
Clint about that too,
and I guess it's
not supposed to.
Something about
knowing what it is
would attract a
certain personality.
This way it keeps it
completely random.
- Completely unbiased.
That makes sense I guess.
- Makes sense, yeah.
(light knocking)
- [Friend] Hey bro,
hit or quit it.
We're out of tequila and the
ladies are getting restless.
Let's go.
- Wow, I am sorry about that.
My friend is kind
of, well, an ass.
- It's okay, go, go,
go, have sex with girls.
(Killian laughs)
- No, that's not,
okay, I do have to go.
Am I gonna see you later?
- No, I can't.
But um, but you put
up a good fight.
- Thank you.
Well, if you change your
mind, you know where we'll be.
And you should seriously
think about doing that.
It would be nice to see you
outside of the
dorms for a change.
- Okay, goodnight.
- [Killian] Good night.
- [Lacie] Have fun.
- [Killian] Bye.
(eerie music)
(phone beeping)
(phone ringing)
- [Operator] Thank you for
calling Systems of Science.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
(phone beeps)
- Hi, this is Lacie Donovan.
I found your flyer on my campus,
and I have a few
questions for you.
So, if you could call me
back at your convenience,
my number is 555-7178.
Thanks so much, bye.
(phone rings)
Hello?
- [Brian] Lacie Donovan.
- May I ask who's calling?
- [Brian] Yes, my
name is Brian Nelson.
I work for Systems of Science.
You just left us a message.
- Oh yeah, yeah,
yeah, that was me.
- [Brian] Okay, good.
I know this is last minute,
but we're holding evaluations
tomorrow at 4:00 p.m.
Are you interested?
- Yeah, absolutely.
I'm off at work by
then, so that's great.
- [Brian] Excellent.
If you give me
your email address,
we can send you all the
information you're looking for.
- [Lacie] Sure, it's
LacieDonovan@yahoo.com.
- [Brian] Okay, Ms. Donovan,
the email has been sent.
Good luck tomorrow.
- [Lacie] Thank you.
(tense music)
- Right here.
Right.
Good.
Open.
Say ah.
- Ah.
Good.
Uh-huh.
- [Lacie] Ah, it's cold.
- Breathe deeply.
Again.
One more time.
We, uh, need to draw some blood.
We'll use this to test your
red and white blood cell count,
cholesterol, liver function,
blood glucose levels, et cetera.
We'll also know if
you've taken any drugs,
legal or otherwise.
- Well, then it's a good thing
I kicked my heroine addiction
a few weeks ago. (giggles)
- Drugs are not a laughing
matter, Ms. Donovan.
- Oh, no, I know.
- Normally an assistant
would do this,
but she went home sick.
Hold that.
- Mm-hmm.
- We're done here.
We'll be evaluating your,
your results over
the next few days.
No need to contact us
with any questions.
We'll call you if
you're accepted.
- Okay.
- Uh-huh, good.
Oh.
Thank you, Ms. Donovan.
- Thank you.
(light knocking)
- I think we're good.
(slow suspenseful music)
(phone rings)
- I believe we've
got our next group.
- Good.
Very good.
Let's see to it that you don't
fuck it up this time, okay?
- You got it.
Asshole.
(Dr. Detrick laughing)
- [Dr. Detrick] Asshole.
(tense music)
(phone ringing)
- [Lacie] Hello.
- [Brian] Lacie Donovan?
- [Lacie] May I
ask who's calling?
- [Brian] This is Brian Nelson
from Systems of Science.
We spoke on the
phone the other day.
- [Lacie] Oh yeah.
- [Brain] Congratulations,
you've been accepted.
We've emailed you the directions
and everything you need to know.
Please be there no later
than 6:00 p.m. tomorrow.
- [Lacie] Okay, thanks.
- Hello.
- [Lacie] Hi, um, I'm
here for the test.
I have this confirmation email.
- Great.
Yes, yes.
How are you today?
Did you have any
trouble finding us?
- Yeah, actually,
I got really lost.
I'm, I don't really come
out this far normally.
- Out here in the
middle of nowhere.
Why would you?
- (chuckles) Good point.
- Okay, let's see here now.
There you are, Ms. Donovan
I'm sure you already
read this in the email,
but I am required to tell you
that there are no cell phones,
laptops, or anything
electronic on the premises.
They tend to interfere
with our equipment.
- Oh yeah, that's okay.
I didn't bring anything anyway.
- [Receptionist] Great.
Lacie, this is nurse Daphne.
She's gonna go ahead and
take you to your room.
- Is she ready to go?
- She's all yours.
All right.
Have a great time, Lacie.
- Thank you so much.
- All right, thank you.
Bye bye.
(scanner beeps)
- Okay, what's with the smile?
- It's nothing.
- [Daphne] Not-uh, you can't
be smiling like
that about nothing.
- Okay, well this is stupid,
but um, when I was a little kid,
I had this pet white
mouse named Daphne.
- Oh!
- You know, from Scooby-Doo.
We would just sit outside
and talk for hours.
- Aw, that's cute.
- Yeah, but then she kind
of sort of died tragically
in an eighth grade
science fair experiment.
- [Daphne] Ew.
- It's just that, I
hadn't heard that name
in a really, really long time.
- Well, everything
has to go sometime.
However God sees fit,
that's how I see it.
- I guess.
Is this it?
- Mm-hmm, this is
where you'll be staying
for the next several days.
- Looks just like home.
(Daphne chuckles)
- I'm sorry to have to do this,
but I need to
check your backpack
for any electronic devices.
It's company policy.
- Oh yeah, that's fine.
- [Daphne] All right.
Pockets.
- Uh, I.
(Lacie chuckles)
- All right, well,
thanks for understanding.
Go ahead and get settled in.
There are scrubs on your bed.
You should get changed and
then head down to the cafeteria
for a meet and greet.
I believe most everyone
is there already.
It's around the
corner on the left.
- Okay, great,
thank you so much.
- All right.
(slow suspenseful music)
- Hey.
- [Lacie] Oh hey.
- How's it going?
Are we supposed to wait here?
- Oh no.
No, I'm just standing here
watching that bald, funny guy.
But how's it going?
- Awesome, I'm Carter.
- [Lacie] Hey, Lacie.
- Nice to meet you.
This beautiful creature right
here is my fiance, Amanda.
- I want you right here, baby.
- Ah, god, he's
so inappropriate.
It's really nice to meet you.
- Hey, nice to meet you.
- So, let's go man.
- Yeah, let's go,
yeah, let's go.
- Let's go. (chuckles)
- [Jake] Oh, I know this guy.
- What's going on buddy?
- Dude, what was it?
Erectile dysfunction.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Yes, it's uh, it's Carter.
- Got it.
- Yeah, dude, what's up man?
- Jake, right?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Cool, man.
- What's going on?
- Not much dude.
I'm glad to see you're still
coming to these things, man.
This is um, this is Amanda.
Jake, Amanda.
- Hello.
- This is my fiance.
- Hi.
- Oh, pleasure to meet you.
- It works.
- Oh my god.
Look at you, dude, last
time I saw this guy,
they gave us one of
those limp dick pills
that had us hard for
like a month straight.
We were like just
clanging swords.
- Not a month.
- Fiance.
- Come on.
- He's got Excalibur down there.
- Okay.
- Congrats.
- Thanks.
- Let's sit down.
- Come on, come on.
- Yeah, that was awesome.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- [Killian] Hey, it's
about time you showed up.
- How's it going?
- How you doing?
- Good.
How are you?
- Good, good.
- [Lacie] Okay.
- Well, look who
decided to show up.
- Hi, Killian, what's up?
- Not much.
So, now you telling me
that you will drive to
some god-forsaken facility
in the middle of
nowhere to see me,
but you won't walk 50
feet down the hall?
Now, what is up with that?
- Well, I'm here now, right.
- Yes, you are, and
I'm glad you are.
Did you get a chance to
meet my buddy, Ty over here?
- No.
- [Killian] Ty, Lacie.
- Hey, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
You guys know each other
from school or something?
- Yeah, we live in
the dorms together.
- [Ty] That's cute.
- I'm telling you, she's
always hitting on me,
trying to take me to
the bars and stuff,
and I'm like Lacie,
it's 10 in the morning.
Let it go.
- He's a liar.
- Anyway, Lacie, I'd
like you to meet Keisha.
Keisha, Lacie.
- What's up?
- Nice to meet you.
So, you guys came together?
- What do you mean by that?
Seriously, what do
you mean by that?
Did we come together?
What, because we're black,
we just automatically
just come and go together?
- What?
- You, you speechless right now?
I don't understand,
what's going on?
- [Lacie] You're serious.
- Yeah, seriously, like yeah.
That's what happened.
Harriet Tubman just
led us on the fucking
Underground Railroad here,
to this place right here.
I don't understand
what you mean by that?
Why would you even ask us that?
Seriously.
I'm here to make a
buck, just like you.
No, no, don't.
What the fuck is this shit.
Lacie, seriously.
Lacie.
I'm completely fucking with you.
(everyone laughing)
- Oh my god.
- Shit, fuck.
- Oh my god, she's sweating.
Do I look like that type?
Now, I'm really
offended, seriously.
- [Lacie] Fuck you.
- [Ty] You're killing
me sweetheart.
- I'm a really
racist person too.
- No, actually,
Keisha and I just met
like a minute before
you walked in.
- Oh, I'm an idiot,
nice to meet you guys.
- [Ty] No, no, I feel terrible.
- No you don't.
- Hey, hello lady.
Why don't you come
join us, come on.
Come on.
There you go.
- See?
- Hey!
- [Jake] Yay!
- Thanks.
- So, so,
what's your name?
No, no, wait, let me guess.
Sarah?
- Noah.
(all laughing)
- You look like a
Kelly kinda, yeah?
- My name's Riley.
- Riley.
She's Korean.
So, Riley, do you come
to these things often?
- So, did they give
you those stupid pills
at the last experiment?
- Oh!
- Ow.
- Those pills.
- Listen, listen.
I'm just trying to impress
her with my witty personality
and my rugged good looks.
(all chuckling)
- It's fine, it's fine.
As a attracted as I am to you,
I found the flyer on my campus,
and I thought it looked
interesting, so I came.
- Uh, where do you go to school?
- I'm studying art at
the Westlake branch.
- Oh, cool, yeah, I'm
at the main campus.
- Do you like it?
- Uh, it's okay, it's okay.
I mean, it's, it's
really expensive,
so that's, that's
kind of why I'm here.
- I thought I was
why you are here.
(Lacie chuckling)
- No, I'm not.
Um, yeah.
(all laughing)
No, my mom, my mom is
having a hard time,
so just trying to help her out.
So yeah, do you know
that they're raising
tuition next semester?
- Actually, I didn't.
My parents pay for school and
pretty much everything else.
So, I just come to these
things to really piss them off.
- Does it work?
- Fucking yes.
(all laughing)
- Gentlemen, ladies.
I hope everyone is well.
My name is Sanders.
- Dude,
it's fucking Colonel Sanders.
- Before we get started.
- Shut up.
- You're here because we're
developing a new medicine
for the military that
will aid our soldiers
in coping with anxiety
on the battlefield.
Now, it's very safe.
At most you may feel euphoric,
more anxious, nothing more.
I just want you to
know that you're doing
your country a great
service here today.
- Listen, that is so cool
about the soldiers and all.
I mean, I feel you.
But I'm here for the
thousand bucks, man.
(all chuckling)
- Well, don't worry about that.
You'll all be taken
care of in good time.
- Uh, what about dinner?
- Will there be a secret
blend of 11 herbs and spices?
- Salads or like
sides of any sort?
- I understand you're all
hungry from fasting today,
and I apologize for that.
We will be feeding you shortly,
since it's important that you
eat prior to the procedure.
- Could have used a better word
than procedure, don't you think?
- Yeah, right.
- In fact, a nurse should
be in here any minute
with your food.
You can eat in here
or in the rec room,
which is just down the hall.
Remember, what's most important
is everyone relax, have fun.
Before you know it,
you'll all be out of here
a thousand bucks richer.
(all cheering)
I, uh, almost forgot.
The procedure starts
tonight at 8:00 p.m. sharp.
We'll call for you
when we're ready.
Be sure to drink lots of water.
Have a good night.
- Thank you.
- All right, let's eat, yeah.
- [Ty] Let's go.
- You know, this isn't bad.
No, it's not bad at all.
- Are you serious?
This makes me look forward
to my diet of ramen noodles.
- Mm, just be glad that they
didn't serve the ravioli.
My man Carter can
back me up on that.
- Yeah.
You guys have no idea.
It was like a piece of cardboard
with snot wrapped on it
and then tomato paste on top.
- That's gross.
- [Amanda] Oh my god.
- No, he's right.
He's exactly right.
- Do you know what
snot tastes like?
(all snickering)
- This actually tastes
like my grandma's chicken.
- [Jake] Really?
- Well, that's not saying
too much, she's um,
she's starting to lose it,
if you know what I mean.
And she swears she's fine,
but she recently invited
my whole family over
for Easter dinner in
October, mind you.
And she served us cat
food and potato chips.
Now, none of us had the
heart to say anything,
we just kept finding
excuses to get up
and throw the food
in the garbage.
- [Amanda] Oh, that's sad.
- The worst part about it was
that cat's been dead for
years, so it's anybody's guess
how long that food had
been sitting around.
I guess that's why
I'm doing this.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna take the
money that I make from this
and use it to fly her
back to Ireland before,
well before she--
- Before she invites everyone
over for Christmas dinner?
(all laughing)
- What about everybody else?
I mean, what are you guys
gonna do with the money?
- I think I'm gonna
fly home to see my mom.
She's been really lonely
since my dad left, so.
I don't know, I found that
as I get farther and
farther along in school,
I have less time
and less money, so.
Hey Jake, can you
hand me the blanket?
It's kind of cold.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I mean,
dude, I don't know.
I mean, my rent's due,
but I don't know how
I'm gonna pay for it,
considering I'm gonna blow
this money on a giant TV.
- Awesome.
- Nice.
- I cannot wait to
play my Xbox 360
in glorious high definition.
- I'm glad you got your
priorities straight.
- Oh hell yeah.
Shit, I mean, even
if I get evicted,
I can still snuggle
up with that TV.
- I like that my fiance
finds this amusing.
- Yeah, odd couple.
- Straight priorities too,
apparently.
- What are you guys
gonna be spending,
spending your cash on?
- Well, we're saving up for
the wedding and the honeymoon.
- Yeah, we're gonna go to Vegas.
We've never been to Vegas.
Never done the
whole casino thing.
So you know, kind
of a one shot deal.
Maybe get Elvis up in there.
- Come on, hey
guys, guys, come on.
There's children around here.
- So, Keisha, what are
your plans with the money?
- No disrespect, but you guys
are really willing to risk
your health and
wellbeing for what?
A television or a flight home?
To me, that's ridiculous.
I don't know.
- All right, well, what
makes you different?
- Well, four months ago, I got
laid off because of cutbacks
and unemployment ran
out and reality sank in.
This for you guys is a choice.
But me, it's my only option.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Well, look on the bright
side, at least the food's good.
(all laughing)
- Amen girl.
Amen.
- So, um, Ty, I'm sure you
got somewhere else to be
besides this lame hospital.
- Well, it's funny
you should ask.
- [Woman] Attention,
attention, it is now 7:50.
Test subjects need to report.
Please get there immediately.
Thank you.
- First procedure, and
then test subjects.
What have you gotten me into?
- (chuckles) A weekend with me.
- Yeah, and six strangers
in a creepy hospital.
How romantic.
- We'll probably be great.
- Test subjects, let's go.
- [Carter] I guess.
- Good, 'cause I
don't want to pick up.
(Carter chuckles)
- Hey, I'll meet up with
you guys in a sec, okay.
(eerie music)
(heavy breathing)
- [Man] Hey, get the
fuck out of here.
(Lacie gasps)
(tense music)
- You're not
supposed to be here.
- Nice.
- [Lacie] Thank you.
- What did you do out there?
Nurse Ratchet looked mean.
- She has that effect on people.
(Jake laughing)
- I feel embarrassed.
- How dare you.
Naughty.
- This is kind of a shady place.
- Yeah.
- I like it though.
- Yeah, it's weird.
- You would like it.
- So, what's up with
like the one nail?
- Oh, you know, just a
fashion statement, you know.
- Oh.
- What's up
with the head though?
- Well, that's, a total
fashion statement.
- All right.
- Yeah.
Shiny.
- It's kind of cute.
- And beautiful.
- Shave that thing.
- Aerodynamic.
- Yeah.
- Like that?
Like that?
(tense music)
- [Daphne] Amanda,
please come with me.
- Um, do I really
have to be first?
- [Daphne] Amanda, you
need to come with me now.
(Amanda sighs)
- Everything will be okay, baby.
It'll be over
before you know it.
- Are you sure?
- [Carter] Yeah.
- Do you promise?
- Say it.
- I promise, baby.
- Okay.
- [Carter] You good?
- Yeah.
I love you.
- I love you too, baby.
And I'll see you
real soon, okay?
- Okay.
(Carter sighs)
- So, a priest and a lawyer
are walking down the street,
they come across
this playground.
The priest turns to the lawyer,
says, hey, you want
to fuck some kids?
The lawyer says sure,
but out of what?
(all chuckle)
Ba dum cha.
- You know, you really should
stop doing these tests.
They're starting to effect
your intelligence and tact.
- Come on, come
on, that was funny.
- No.
- That was funny.
- [Keisha] No, it wasn't.
- All right, all
right, try this one.
So, a guy walks out
of a bathroom naked.
He's got, he's got a
poodle under one arm,
he's got 50 feet of duct
tape under the other.
- [Daphne] Ty, come with me.
- Let's get this shit over with.
(somber music)
(clock ticking)
- [Daphne] Jake.
Riley.
Keisha.
Carter.
- Where is everyone?
Shouldn't they be done by now?
- Well, they're probably
just waiting for us
back in the rec room.
Right?
- I don't know, maybe.
But there's something really
weird about this place.
I saw Sanders wearing
one of those masks.
- What kind of masks?
- The masks you
see in the movies
when something really
bad is about to happen.
- [Daphne] Killian,
please come with me.
(Killian sighs)
- [Killian] Hang in there, okay?
You're gonna be all right.
- [Daphne] Lacie,
please come with me.
(suspenseful music)
After you.
- Hey, hey.
Hey.
Let me out.
Hey!
Let me out!
Please let me out.
Please!
Please.
(Lacie whimpering)
- Release the gas.
(gas hissing)
(Lacie panting)
(Lacie coughing)
(Lacie screams)
(Lacie sobbing)
(Lacie panting)
(Lacie screaming)
All right, call in a crew,
let's get outta here.
- All right then,
come and get her.
(slow suspenseful music)
Are you recording?
- Standby.
- Everything's set up correctly?
- Everything is good.
- Senator, are you
getting our feed?
- Everything looks
good on my end.
I want updates with
each new development.
- All right, we are recording.
(camera whirring)
(Amanda gasping)
- Carter?
Carter?
(Amanda groans)
(Amanda sighs)
(door creaks)
(eerie music)
(Carter groaning)
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
How are you?
- I'm good.
Mm, you smell good.
- I always smell good.
- Yeah.
(Carter sighs)
- [Amanda] I want you inside me.
- Now?
- Yeah, now.
Take off my shirt.
Come on.
(slow suspenseful music)
Take yours off.
- Oh, baby.
- Take off my pants.
- You take off my pants.
(both laughing)
(Carter moaning)
(Amanda panting)
- Mm.
(both moaning)
Pull my fucking hair.
Mm.
Pull it harder.
(Carter panting)
Oh!
- Oh fuck.
- [Amanda] What's the matter?
- [Carter] Baby.
- Is that my hair?
What the fuck?
What's going on?
- Baby, what is going on?
(Amanda panting)
(tense music)
(Amanda groans)
Baby.
Fuck.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
Amanda.
Baby.
Whats' going on?
(suspenseful music)
- What's happening to me?
Oh.
Oh, Carter.
My hair.
Carter.
(Amanda sobbing)
Carter!
- [Carter] Whoa.
(water trickling)
(tense music)
- [Amanda] You did this to me.
- What?
(Amanda screams)
(Carter screaming)
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
(Lacie gasps)
(Lacie panting)
- Hello?
Hello?
(clock ticking)
Is anyone there?
Hello?
Seriously guys,
this isn't funny.
- Lacie.
- Hey.
- What's with all the yelling?
- No one is here,
Killian, everyone is gone.
- [Killian] Wait, what do
you mean no one's here?
- I, I can't find any of
the doctors or nurses,
and every single door
I checked is locked.
I just--
- Well, it's still early.
- No, that's the thing.
There's one clock that
says it's like 11:15
and another one that
says it's like four.
- Okay, okay, okay, calm down.
There's got to be a good
explanation for this.
Let's um, let's just look around
and see if we can find anyone
else who's awake, okay?
- Okay.
- [Killian] Okay.
- What time is it?
- I'm sorry to wake you.
- [Lacie] Hey Riley, I'm
sorry to wake you up, but.
- Just bear with us.
Lacie seems to think that
there's something wrong.
- We can't find anyone.
Kind of weird, so, do you
want to just meet me outside?
- Now?
- Yeah, now.
- Like right now?
- Would you mind?
- Sure, just give
me a minute, okay.
- Okay, thanks.
- I'll be right out.
- [Killian] Okay.
- See you outside.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Anything?
- No.
- [Lacie] Told you.
- Jesus Christ, I'm so
freaking tired right now.
- Me too.
- So, what's going
on, why are we here?
Why we up so early?
- There's no one here.
Everybody is gone.
- What's she talking about?
- Well, what Lacie
is trying to say
is that none of us
can seem to find
any of the doctors or nurses
and she's, well, we're
all a little concerned.
That's all.
- No, no, no, no.
What I'm saying is that
something is very wrong here.
- Seriously?
That's what you woke us up for?
I'm going back to bed.
- [Killian] Ty, just hang on.
- No, you don't get it.
There is nobody here.
There is no way out.
Everyone is gone.
All the doors are locked.
- So then, where's
the honeymooners?
- I checked their rooms.
We don't know where they are.
- Probably just fucking
on some gurney somewhere.
(Ty groans)
I'm sorry, they're
probably making love
on some gurney somewhere.
- Or they're probably
having breakfast
with the doctors and nurses.
- No, no, you guys,
I'm telling you--
- But since we're all up,
we might as well go
look for them, okay?
So, you three go that way,
and we'll go this way,
and we're bound to run into 'em.
Good?
- Okay.
- Sounds good.
(tense music)
Carter.
Amanda.
It is awfully quiet.
I mean, someone
should be here, right?
- See, I told you.
- You know, this reminds me.
I was doing one of these
a couple of years ago.
Couldn't find this
guy for like two days.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, yeah.
It ended up, he was
underneath his bed,
like just paralyzed,
locked with fear.
Essentially, the guy
was having nightmares,
but he was like fully awake.
- What the fuck were
you guys testing?
- Let's just say it's a drink
that gives you a lot of energy.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Which one?
- A very popular one.
- What is that?
(slow suspenseful music)
What the?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, dude, dude,
you don't, you don't
want to go in there.
- Well, what if they're hurt?
All right, what if
they need our help?
- After you.
Whoa, whoa, Lacie,
Lacie, whoa, don't.
Shit.
- Oh.
Carter.
Amanda, is anyone in here?
- Oh god!
- [Killian] Lacie.
(Carter gasping)
(Carter screaming)
(Jake retching)
- Carter.
(Carter growling)
(Jake panting)
Dude, we gotta go.
- What is it?
- We gotta go.
- We gotta fucking go, dude.
- What is it?
What did you see?
- It's Carter!
It's fucking Carter in
there, man, but, but it's,
but it's, it's not him.
It's no, no, no.
Don't, don't go in there.
Okay, okay.
Trust me on this, okay?
Let's just find everyone,
we'll just get out.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay, okay.
Come on, come on!
- Come on.
- [Jake] Go, go, go.
Go, go, go!
No time to explain, we gotta
get the hell out of here.
Let's go, let's go.
Go, go.
(suspenseful music)
- Damn it, damn it.
You need the security
card to get in.
- [Killian] Okay, let me try.
(Killian groaning)
Shit.
- Okay, um, well,
what about the stairs.
- We tried them all,
they're all locked.
- Will someone care to tell me
why the hell are we running?
And what exactly is going on?
- Carter's dead, man.
- [Keisha] What about Amanda?
- He's fucking, Carter is
fucking dead, did you hear me?
Fucking, someone tore him
apart and left him for dead.
I don't know, he was,
he was still alive.
I saw him, but I don't
know exactly what I saw.
- What about Amanda?
- We don't know.
Look, there's got to be a
phone or something, right?
- We tried them all.
They're all dead.
(Jake panting)
- This is just fucking great.
This is great, we're trapped
in here with no way out.
Everyone's gone except for us.
None of the phones work.
And Carter's dead.
You know what this is?
This is fucked, man, this
is completely fucked!
- Calm down, all right?
There's gotta be
another way out of here.
- Really?
- I got a phone.
- You mean like a cellphone?
- Yeah, I snuck
it in when I came.
- Why didn't you say so?
- Can we go?
- Go, go, go!
- Go!
- Go, go!
- Don't stop!
- You guys hungry at all?
'Cause I am starving.
I'm thinking pizza,
maybe some peperoni.
Or we could do vegetarian
if that's your thing.
- Bring up camera
12, and 17 over here.
- Fine.
Just, I've got a very high
metabol, you know what, fuck it.
You don't give a shit.
- Hold on, I'm gonna go get it.
(Riley panting)
(Ty and Lacie panting)
(tense music)
- Guys.
Is that Amanda?
- Amanda, is that you?
I got a bad feeling about this.
- What is she
standing there for?
- I got it.
- [Ty] Keisha, Keisha, run.
Run, Run!
(Keisha screams)
(dramatic music)
- [Ty] Hey, hey, don't,
what are you doing, man?
We gotta get her.
- It's too late, man.
- No, no!
- It's too late,
there's no time!
- What the fuck are you doing?
- This shit ain't over, man.
- Come on.
- It's locked.
It's too late, it's too late.
- [Thank you] Are you kidding
me, man, listen to her.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Come on.
(tense music)
- [Killian] Oh shit.
(all panting)
Oh shit.
- What the fuck, man,
we could have saved her.
- Ty, it was too
great a risk, man.
There's nothing we
could have done.
- You mean there's nothing
you could have done.
- Ty, you need to
calm down, right.
This isn't gonna help anything.
This isn't gonna
change anything.
- Let me tell you something.
This thing between you
and me, it ain't over.
(dramatic music)
- Shouldn't have brought
your cell phone, huh?
(phone ringing)
Guys.
- Pick it up.
- Here it is.
- Progress report, gentlemen.
Are we ready to execute or not?
- No sir, but we have made
quite a bit of progress.
The subjects are still
exhibiting various symptoms
such as trouble
breathing, hair loss,
and bleeding from
various orifices.
But the good news is
that the chemical is taking
effect much more rapidly.
We also believe
that we do in fact
have a fully functional
counter agent.
- How so?
- We inoculated
two of the subjects
prior to being
exposed to the gas.
So far, both subjects
are symptom free.
- And they're both still alive?
- Not exactly.
One of them has unfortunately
expired sooner than we hoped.
- If you had kept them
isolated like I suggested,
we wouldn't be talking about
this issue right now, would we?
- Sir.
- It's, it's important
that the subjects
remained together.
Physical interaction and
conversion are important
and necessary,
keeping the mind busy.
If we separate them, we
risk the possibility--
- Dr. Detrick, yes.
Yes, how long
before you're ready
to start manufacturing
the agent?
- We're certainly close, sir.
Could be ready within
a matter of weeks.
- I beg your pardon,
did you say could?
- Will, (chuckles) will.
It will be ready, sir.
- Good.
(slow suspenseful music)
- Christ sake.
- I don't know if
that thing was Amanda,
but whatever it is
might come back.
- The barricade's solid.
Nothing's getting in.
- I don't suppose that
gate opens, does it?
- No, I already checked.
You need a key.
How are you holding up, baby?
- Why are they doing this to us?
(suspenseful music)
- Uh-huh.
No, no, there's no way, man.
That thing was
moving way too fast.
I mean, this must be something
completely different.
- Brilliant insight, Jake.
Okay, now that we're clear
on what actually constitutes
as a zombie, we need to--
- Do you guys think that we're
gonna turn into those things?
I mean, seriously you
guys, what was in that gas?
- Look, I think we need
to stop hypothesizing
and actually start to
think of some kind of plan.
- Hey, check out those cameras.
They, mm-mm, they
weren't here before,
which means someone's
watching us.
Hello.
We need some help please.
Hello?
- Will you please
turn that off.
- We need help, someone.
(suspenseful music)
Fuck it.
(static buzzing)
- Uh-oh.
- I thought you said
they were shatter proof.
- Hopefully, it's
still under warranty
because I'm pretty sure
we don't have the
extended service plan.
- This isn't the time.
I don't know how, but fix it.
Do we have another
camera in that room?
- Of course, it's coming
up right now, Jesus.
And there it is.
(Sanders sighs)
- [Killian] What are you doing?
- You know what,
if they want us,
they can come and get us.
I don't know about you, but
I am not going to die here.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You all right, you all right?
- Yeah.
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
It must have been
the chicken, right?
(Ty coughing)
- Should one of us
go check on him?
- He's fine.
- Listen, I think Ty's gone
off the reservation, man.
- I can hear you, asshole.
Okay hotshot, you got
us locked in this room.
What next?
Huh?
Tell me there's something
more to all this.
Tell us all what the
fuck you plan to do
if that thing comes back.
- I don't know.
- What?
- [Killian] I said I don't know.
- Hey, I don't see you
coming up with a better idea.
Okay, so while you sit
over there in the corner,
at least he is doing something.
Killian's gotten us this far,
so if you don't have
anything constructive to say,
then why don't
you just back off.
(Jake snickers)
- You got something you
want to say, funny man?
- No, no.
- That's what I thought.
- Check out the balls on Lacie.
- Shut up, Jake.
- Guys, guys, seriously,
we need a legitimate plan.
- Sooner or later,
someone's gonna come
looking for us, right?
As long as that
thing's out there
and we're in here, we're safe.
All right, so let's
just sit tight,
relax, wait this thing out.
- No way.
What about food?
Or going to the bathroom?
I mean, you guys, it feels
like I haven't eaten in days.
- Yeah, I mean, for all we
know it could have been days.
- Maybe we should try to
get Keisha's cellphone.
- That's a good idea.
Yeah.
Yeah, we'll just go out
in the hallway there.
We'll hang out with
whatever that thing is.
You know, it's
probably just waiting
around the corner for us.
- It was just an idea.
- No, I think it's worth a shot.
I mean, we can't
stay here forever.
- You know what, my ass
is staying right here.
- That's very
noble of you, Jake.
- You know, chivalry died
with women's lib, all right?
I'm all for equal
rights, ladies.
- I can do it.
Seriously, I'm the
smallest one here.
You guys can move the vending
machine a couple of inches.
I'll squeeze through, I'll
get the phone, and we're done.
- You're serious?
- Yeah.
- You sure you want to do this?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Let's go.
Come on.
- Okay, okay.
Let's do this.
Ready?
On the count of three,
one, two, three.
(slow suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
(Riley screaming)
(Riley panting)
- [Riley] I got it.
- Does it work?
- Yeah.
Oh shit.
- What?
- There's no signal.
(phone beeping)
Hey.
- Fucking
bullshit.
Excellent idea.
- Get it off my hands,
get it off my hands.
Get this shit off my
hands, get it off my hands.
Get it, no, no, I need to
get this off right now.
You don't understand, no,
no, get this off of me!
- Calm down, calm down,
breathe, breathe, breathe.
Just breathe, just
breathe, all right.
Just breathe, breathe,
breathe, breathe, okay?
- We need to face reality
and assume that no
one is coming for us.
- You don't know that.
- Jake.
Jake, think about the people
who are operating this, okay?
They kidnapped us.
They held us against our will.
Okay, they pumped us
full of god knows what.
They have everything to loose,
so they're going to do whatever
it takes to keep us here.
We can't just wait around here.
We need to find a way out.
- What do you propose we do?
Huh?
Walk out the front door?
- Okay, we're on the top floor.
We can't go down,
so we need to find a
way to the roof, okay?
And then from there, we
can see if we get a signal.
- Or use the fire escape.
- If there is one.
- [Killian] Right,
if there is one.
- The roof is our best bet.
Do, do you agree?
- Yeah, I think
that's our best option
given the circumstances.
Riley?
- Yeah, I agree.
- All right, and how do you
propose we get to the roof?
(tense music)
- What about the air ducts?
- [Jake] What?
- You know what, she's right.
In buildings like this,
the air conditioning units
usually are located on the roof.
- Okay, okay.
Okay, so we find a
way to the air ducts
and then, and then
we get to the roof.
Right?
- You think it'll work?
- The air ducts
should be big enough.
- There's an air
duct in the rec room.
- [Killian] Okay, are
you sure about that?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- All right.
Then we make our
way to the rec room.
We use the air duct,
and we should be golden.
- Listen, I,
I hate to be Debbie
Downer on this, all right,
but you guys remember that
thing's still out there.
- [Ty] Even if we make it
to the roof, what then?
- You know what Ty,
you contributed exactly
two things today.
Jack and shit.
So, here's your chance pal.
We're all listening,
we're all here.
Enlighten us.
(Ty retching)
- Fuck.
It's throwing me.
- Dude, I don't
think that's normal.
- Ty.
- Run.
- Shit!
- Ty!
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Run!
(Lacie screaming)
- [Killian] Go, go, go, go, go!
(Killian and Ty grunting)
(dramatic music)
(glass clattering)
(Killian groaning)
- God.
- No.
- No!
- I have to go back.
- He's gone, he's gone.
(Ty pants)
(Riley screams)
(Ty panting)
(Ty grunts)
(dramatic music)
(Jake screaming)
- [Ty] Where are you?
Huh?
(all panting)
- Okay.
I think we're good, come on.
- Guys, guys, guys, guys.
Look where we're at.
- It's the waiting room.
- Jake, no.
- Yeah.
Yeah, we gotta at least look.
- No, no, that's
a horrible idea.
- What?
- No, no, no, come on.
Come on.
- Jake.
- [Jake] Come on.
- [Lacie] Goddammit.
- [Riley] I don't understand
what's going on you guys.
- I hope I didn't
miss anything tasty.
Now, this is interesting.
(slow suspenseful music)
(glass clattering)
- So, they were watching
us this whole time.
How did you know that
they would be watching?
- Well, I've been doing
enough of these things
to know that there is
always someone watching.
Maybe now I can
get some answers.
Come on.
(slow suspenseful music)
Okay.
There's not a goddamned thing.
I thought we'd find
something, anything.
It's nothing.
- It's okay, it's
not a big deal.
We just start it--
- No, no, no, it's not okay.
We may be turning into one
of those things out there
that's chasing us.
I say we're anything but okay.
- Jake, calm down.
- I'm sorry.
- It's fine, it's just
you're not the only one
who's dealing with this.
We all are, so let's
stick together.
- You're right.
You're right.
- Okay.
Okay, the important
thing is we keep moving,
so let's, let's
get to the rec room
and just get the fuck
out of here, okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
(dramatic music)
(Ty panting)
- Should I call
in a cleanup crew?
- Put 'em on standby.
Let 'em know we'll
need 'em soon.
You take care of their cars yet?
- All good.
- How we doing otherwise,
anything else to report?
- You missed it, they
broke into the lab.
- Really?
- See for yourself.
- It's over there.
- Uh, I'll find something
to block the door.
Get this vent off.
(grate clanging)
(slow suspenseful music)
I think we're okay.
Okay, all right?
All right, you ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
(Lacie grunting)
(Lacie panting)
(Lacie coughing)
Okay, come on.
- Wait, what about you?
- Don't worry, I'll
be right behind you,
don't worry about me.
Go, go.
(Riley screams)
(dramatic music)
(Ty panting)
Shit.
(Ty screaming)
- Not so funny now, are you?
(Ty grunting)
- Where?
- Right there.
(tense music)
- As I was saying Colonel,
I expect a full report on my
desk at the end of the week.
Anything else?
- Cleanup crew will
be here shortly.
We're about ready to wrap it up.
- Perfect.
I'll handle the local press.
Our cover story runs
day after tomorrow.
- We'll be long gone by then.
- Excellent, gentlemen,
you've done your country
a great service today.
- [Sanders] Thank you, sir.
(dramatic music)
(Jake panting)
(Ty grunts)
(Jake groaning)
(Jake panting)
(Ty grunting)
(Jake groans)
(Riley screams)
(Ty groaning)
(suspenseful music)
(Jake coughing)
(Riley coughing)
- Hey, you okay?
(dramatic music)
(Riley groans)
- Jake?
Riley?
Where are you?
(suspenseful music)
Help.
Help!
Damn it.
(engine rumbling)
- [Soldier] Go!
- Help!
Help!
Jake.
(gun fires)
- Do you understand
that time is an issue?
That we're under contract
to deliver this weapon
and that, and that the results
are far from what
the Senator wants?
- Would you stop worrying?
We have plenty of time,
despite what he thinks.
Now, don't give me that look.
This is a small price
to pay for progress.
- Really?
- We're doing a good thing,
and when we're done here,
an American casualty will
be a thing of the past.
No more taking an enemy head on.
We'll release this gas
on whomever we want
and simply let them
kill themselves.
No virus, no hole in the ground,
no connection to the U.S.
- Do you really believe that?
- [Sanders] I sleep quite
well at night, my friend.
- Well, I don't.
- Tough.
'Cause we're not done
till we have a weapon
that leaves no visible symptoms.
(Lacie grunts)
(soldier screaming)
(gun firing)
What the fuck is
going on out there?
- [Soldier] We have
a man down, man down.
(gun firing)
(gun fires)
- We need to be more careful.
Things are getting
out of control.
- Are you kidding?
This was nothing.
You're lucky you weren't around
when we were developing AIDS.
Our initial results were
ungodly to say the least.
(soldier groaning)
(gun firing)
(tense music)
- South wing clear,
moving forward.
(somber music)
(fire crackling)
(tense music)
- [Sanders] You about done?
- Just finished.
- [Sanders] Good, the truck's
loaded and ready to go.
(slow suspenseful music)
- Mr. Vice President,
everything went as planned.
Yes, sir.
We are almost ready to
launch a live field test.
Yes, sir.
No, no, no, thank you, sir.
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
(somber music)
(tense music)
(MultiCom Jingle)