Captioning made possible by
lions gate entertainment
i've got to quit smoking.
So much for
new year's resolutions.
You really
fucked everything up,
didn't you, m.j.?
Amanda,
quit attacking me.
You have no idea
what i've been going through.
Fighting isn't getting us
anywhere, you guys.
Don't you think maybe
we should go look for her?
Maybe. I don't know.
What time is it anyway?
Just after 2:00.
And it looks like we're
gonna be here for a while.
Does anybody want
more coffee?
You certainly know how
to clear out a party.
Give it a rest, amanda.
Let's face it.
This isn't
the first time
you've ruined one of
our little soirées.
Oh, yeah?
For instance...
for instance,
your birthday.
Come on, everybody.
Let's surprise her.
1, 2, 3!
Surprise!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, m.j.
uh, henry,
meet my roommates.
My best friend
frankie...
hello, henry.
And her boyfriend
taylor.
And this is banks
and amanda.
Hi, henry.
How you doing?
Uh... i'm late.
I've got to get ready
for work.
Hey,
good morning, los angeles!
It's 7 a.m., september 1,
and a cloudy 68 degrees.
And here's the new one
from rain on fire...
called here we are. Yeah.
What?!
Amanda, it's dan.
Willie has
disappeared again.
I'm damn sure he's not
on his way to school.
I found all of his books
under his bed.
If he shows up, will you
please redirect him,
and try to stress the importance
of an education to him?
That brother of yours
won't make it out of the
eleventh grade at this rate.
Good morning!
I can't go back there.
I just left
that place...
oh, 6 hours ago.
Hey...
let's both
call in sick today.
Come on.
We can go sailing,
and we can do it
all day long.
Please.
You know i can't,
and neither can you.
Why?
Because mario
starts the mural today.
It's a big day.
He needs me.
I need you, too.
Come on back to bed.
Taylor, get up.
I refuse to move
until you come back here
and kiss me now.
Oh!
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Mmm.
Morning.
Mm.
Who the fuck finished off
my captain crunch?
Amanda, please.
Hey, baby,
what's for breakfast?
Oh! Willie!
Nice going.
Good morning.
Hey, banks.
Morning.
I've got a big
audition today.
Oh, hey.
You may be looking at
the future...
mr. Cat chow.
Right on, brother.
Everybody owes me
rent money.
The shower's
fucked up again.
Then somebody has to
call the landlord.
Not it.
Has anybody seen
my white silk shirt?
Now what?
Ah, henry!
Um, i'm late.
I--i'll call you.
So, you guys,
what time is this
birthday dinner tonight?
About 8:30.
Sounds a little early
for m.j.
bye.
See ya.
Oh, amanda, you're gonna
make the cake, right?
One of your special
4-layers
with pretty roses
and stuff?
Taylor, toast.
Don't get on me tonight.
Aw, it would mean a lot
to m.j. if you were there.
Oh...
i'll see what i can do.
Well, bye.
So who's the guy?
Just a guy.
Well, i hope
you're being careful.
Yes. Thank you.
I'm using condoms.
I hate them,
but i'm using them.
I'll see you tonight,
mother.
See you tonight, dear.
And try not to be
too late.
You are going to school.
Forget school.
Look at it outside!
Come on,
let's go to the beach
and eat cheeseburgers.
Will, dad called
this morning, ok?
He's pissed.
Yeah, well, fuck him.
I mean, school's whack.
Really, minx.
You wouldn't believe what
they had us doing yesterday.
We spent
the entire health class
putting rubbers
on bananas.
It's totally bogus.
I mean, besides,
my band is kickin' ass.
I want to be famous
like my big sister.
Yeah, well,
i'm hardly famous.
Yet.
Hey, boss, it's me.
Yeah, i'm sorry i'm late.
I had a little
problem this morning
that i couldn't get rid of.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, i did hear about
that takeover bid.
What's the reaction
in the market?
Really?
Uh-huh.
Well, i spoke to
my infamous c.p.a. friend,
and i'm gonna see him
at 4:00 for drinks,
then i'm on to my stinky rich
gold and oil friends, yeah.
Yeah, i think they're ready
to close the deal.
Oh, and david?
I'm sorry, but this will
never happen again.
Ok? Right.
Right. Bye.
Now 30-year
treasuries are eight...
oh, shit.
Fuck.
Hey, you got
another hole in your ear.
Yeah,
stacey made me do it.
Stacey? Who's stacey?
My woman.
Wait a minute.
I thought jocelyn
was your girlfriend.
That ended weeks ago.
Hi, mr. Solomon.
Hiya!
What is this,
mr. Rogers' neighborhood?
Who the hell knows their
neighbors in los angeles?
Hey, can i come to
the birthday party tonight?
In the car.
You are late for school.
Please?
Oh, stuart,
this is all my fault,
but let's not get the insurance
company involved, ok?
I mean, they can be
such a hassle.
Let me level with you.
Today's my 25th birthday,
and if i don't get to work
in 5 minutes,
i'm gonna lose my job.
Ok, ok.
Calm down.
You look like
a smart man.
Yeah.
What do you do?
No, let me guess--
hollywood.
You make great movies.
No, actually,
real estate.
That was my second guess.
Commercial, definitely.
How'd you know?
Your style.
The armani suite.
A man who enjoys
the finer things in life.
You're good
at what you do.
And so am i.
And what is it
that you're so good at?
Making intelligent people
terrifyingly rich.
You know, we should
get together and talk business.
And then we can clear up
this matter about the car.
Eh, it's...
actually not that bad.
I know a mechanic
who owes me a favor.
Perfect.
Let me give you
my number.
My business cards
are being reprinted,
so i'll give you
my home number.
Call me, stuart.
Ok... linda.
Hey, linda.
Yes, stuart?
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Jesus, hallelujah.
Oh, mario.
I thought
we'd use the whole wall,
and we'd have, like,
this vibrant blue color
and these huge eyes
that are just, like,
piercing down at you.
Mm-hmm.
And then, um,
it'd be kind of like
an abstract thing
with this aztec style.
You know, like,
with the little, um, shapes,
and then they make up
the whole picture.
And then, of course,
we'd sign my name
at the bottom,
like that, in big letters.
6-foot letters.
So typical of m.j.
to miss her own party.
You guys,
this is ridiculous.
Why don't we just
go home?
Oh, come on.
I'm sure she just got
caught up with work.
You know how she tries
to do everything at once.
Ooh, sounds
seamy to me.
I'm sure she's got
a perfectly fine reason
for not being here.
Now, can we just relax?
Probably some guy.
Named jose cuervo?
Who's that?
Great idea!
Shots for everybody.
All right, then.
Yo, bartender!
Why didn't you
tell us earlier
it was your birthday?
Oh, because
it's no big deal.
You know, i should
probably be going.
Nonsense.
Aren't you guys exhausted?
What year were you born,
young lady?
My mother taught me
never to reveal my age.
Well, how does
1969 sound?
Close enough.
All right, one more.
I'll drink to that.
They kept me sitting there
for 3 1/2 hours
with these screaming felines
crawling all over my body
just to see
if i was a cat person.
I've got fleas and scratches
all over me.
I hate cats.
Hey, waiter?
Well, guys,
i just called the house,
and she's not there.
Ah, a sucker is born
every minute.
Wait till you see
mario's sketch for the mural.
It's so beautiful.
Really?
Oh, that's great.
That's really cool.
I can't wait
to see it.
Yeah, me, too.
That would be--
ok, ok, ok. Chill out.
Oh, this is
bullshit.
You know something?
You guys can sit here
and wait all night long
if you want to,
but i'm gonna go
play some pool.
Great idea, minx.
What exactly
is in cat chow?
I don't exactly know,
but it tastes mostly
like cardboard...
with this touch
of gross fish guts.
Mmm.
So the director says,
"i like what you do
with the acting,
but i don't feel the connection
between the cat."
I was like, no, i love cats.
I--i've had cats
all my life. I--
well,
look who showed up.
Hi, guys.
I'm really sorry.
By the time
i got to the restaurant,
you guys had already left.
She's bombed.
I totally lost track
of time.
You know, m.j.,
you're one lucky bitch
you got friends like us,
'cause nobody else would
put up with your shit.
I know.
I'm really sorry,
you guys.
But i brought ice cream--
toffee heath bar crunch,
new york super fudge chunk,
chocolate burnt almonds...
aw, come on, you guys.
I'm gonna
take everybody out big time
when i collect my commission
on these clients.
You should've seen the money
that was flying.
We had 3 $500 bottles
of champagne.
So?
We were
drinking longnecks
for, what,
2.50 a bottle?
Had to be,
at least.
Oh.
Anybody want anything?
I'm getting a beer.
No, i'm fine.
I'll have a beer.
Yeah, me, too.
Listen, willie.
16-year-olds who
drink too much to be cool
end up on the bathroom floor
throwing up.
She speaks
from experience.
No way, minx.
I'm not drunk.
I am not.
I'm just happy.
I mean it.
Happy birthday.
Oh, thanks, banks.
I'll get it.
Not here.
I am not here.
Hello?
Yeah, hi, this is henry.
Is m.j. there?
Oh, hang on a minute.
M.j., it's henry.
I'm not here.
Oh, silly me!
M.j.'s still out.
Yeah, all right,
i'll have--
i've called
2 times before--
fine. Bye.
Well, make sure--
that's the third time
he's called today.
Tell me about it.
Fuck 'em once,
they want to put a goddamn
leash around your neck.
Did you by chance grow up
in a truck stop, amanda?
Banks,
why are you a fag?
Willie!
Why?
Uh...
it's a long
and complicated story
that i--
oh, brother.
Anybody want to help me
put this little
nightmare to bed?
Let's take him out back
and shoot him first.
Little shit.
I'm gonna go to bed, too.
You coming?
Uh, in a minute.
Ready?
Happy birthday, m.j.
really just a pleasure
spending the evening with you.
Ok.
♪ Oh, we have
something for you ♪
oh!
Happy birthday.
Oh, god.
It's really
from everyone, so...
oh, my god.
Oh, frankie,
this is so beautiful.
It's from indonesia.
Watch his head.
Yeah, i like this.
Frankie...
i'm sorry about tonight.
It's ok. I understand.
Happy birthday, girlfriend.
I love you, frankie.
Mmm.
Well, i'm going to bed.
Hey, m.j., um...
i thought henry
was kinda cute.
Why didn't you
want to talk to him?
Because there are
200,000 henrys in l.a.,
and i just
haven't found one
that i want to spend
the rest of my life with.
Hmm.
Well, don't give up.
It happened to me.
All right,
well, good night.
Good night, frankie.
Taylor.
You know when i realized
i was turning into an adult?
I was driving
really fast one day,
and i could visualize
being in a car accident--
the crunching metal,
being pinned against
the steering wheel.
Maybe that was just
a message to slow down?
You know, like
cracking the mercedes.
Oh, please.
I got out of that one,
no problem.
Besides, you've gotta move
really quick
to get what you need
in this lifetime.
Even if that means
hurting people?
Come on, banks.
You both want it
just as badly as i do.
Miss metropolitan museum,
and you, the aspiring actor.
Yeah, well, at least
we're not self destructive.
I mean, come on, m.j.,
where's your sense
of self worth?
I mean, you are always
taking advantage of people
and you know it.
I really don't need
a lecture on morals.
You know,
sometimes i wonder
if you even have any.
Want to try it on?
I didn't hear you come in.
It's gettin' too crazy.
What are you talking about?
Things are becoming
serious with frankie.
Oh, i'm so happy for you.
I just have
one question, though.
Why are you still
sleeping with me?
It can't happen anymore.
I just wanted
to tell you that.
So these women really
put on gorilla masks
and protest sexism
in the arts?
Yeah.
Somehow i can see you
slinking through
the streets
in a fake black fur.
Yeah, well,
at least they're making
a statement
about the white male domination
in the art world.
I mean, you walk into
any art gallery
and you look at the ratio...
i mean, it's pitiful!
It's the same
white male artists
over and over
and over again.
You know, i swear,
i am going to start
the l.a. chapter
of the guerilla girls.
Watch me, i will.
I know.
It's like every time
i turn on the tv,
it's the same faces
getting the same
bad tv roles.
You know, sometimes
i really wonder
what the hell i'm doing.
Like today,
i have this audition.
The casting director's
all smiles,
"that was
a perfect delivery,
banks, that was
wonderful!"
And then
she shuffles me out
and shuffles in
6 other guys
who look just like me.
I just feel like
i'm wasting my time.
No, you are not.
Hey, you've got
2 national commercials.
I mean, that is great.
Any horse's ass
can drink a soft drink
and sell ketchup.
Nuh-uh.
I'm thinking of getting
back into the theater.
Yeah?
Back east somewhere.
My agent
keeps telling me
that a movie
will happen soon,
but yada, yada, yada.
It's like i keep waiting
for something out there
to make me feel whole
and complete, but...
but maybe
that's my problem.
Come on, banks.
Ok, you--
you have to have
those dreams,
you know?
And those
goals, too.
I don't know.
I think the future's
overrated, anyway.
I mean, whatever happened
to living in the present?
You know, being happy
day by day.
How often do you
find yourself thinking
"as soon as i get
that job,
"or meet that person
or sell that painting,
then i'm gonna be happy."
You know, i think
there's something
inherently wrong
with that way of thinking.
I think we constantly
set ourselves up
for dissatisfaction. I--
hey, hey.
I'm sorry.
I'm just in
a piss of a mood.
I had a lousy audition,
i don't have enough money
for rent.
Hey, listen,
you know i sold
a painting last week
so it's no problem
if you need the money.
Ok?
Thanks.
You're welcome.
I might have
to take you up on that.
We'll do it.
I really like that one.
I think it's gonna be great.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Well, maybe someday
it'll hang in the museum
of contemporary art.
You hang onto
those dreams, girlfriend.
That's why we stay
in this smog-infested city.
Come on, i gotta change
for an appointment,
and then i'm gonna
buy you some breakfast.
Come on, joey,
hurry up, man!
Hey, frankie?
Yeah?
Did you hear about
george's brother?
No.
E.s.g. got him.
His first night
out of jail,
they shot him.
Oh, my god.
You're staying out of it,
aren't you?
Mario?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not stupid.
Give it to me,
give it to me!
Give it back! Come on!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey! Hey! All right,
you, sit down.
You, sit down.
Now you just sit here
until you're ready
to behave, ok?
I got plenty of other kids
that want to paint.
I'm really sick of you
picking on people, george!
Why don't you mind
your own business?
Because it is my business.
You could have called
to tell me this,
but you didn't.
You came here.
I know why you're here,
and so do you.
M.j., it's
over with now.
I just wanted
to see you
face to face
and be done with it.
Now, taylor, wouldn't you miss
our little rendezvous'?
Stop it.
I know you want me.
How can you go on
doing this?
You know, i thought
she was your friend.
Same way you can.
I know how
you feel about me.
I can see it
in your eyes.
I don't feel
that way anymore.
Touch me, taylor.
I want you
to touch me.
Touch me.
Please?
Taylor, your heart's
beating fast.
So is mine.
So fast.
Don't stop, don't stop,
don't stop, don't stop,
don't stop.
Well, you see, in this
painting here,
she's holding his head
out of the window
because she's deciding
whether or not to keep him,
and the monkey
around her neck
symbolizes the relationship
which--which doesn't
go beyond the physical.
Hmm. That's,
uh, interesting.
What size is that?
Uh, this one's 6 by 8.
Do you have
anything smaller?
No.
Yeah, to be honest.
I'm not sure i have any
openings for some time,
but, uh,
maybe over dinner
you could
convince me
to rearrange
my schedule.
What do you say?
Um...
thanks...
but no thanks.
Oh! Oh, god, what if
somebody comes home?
Nobody's coming home
for hours.
Hello!
Is anybody home?
Oh, shit, somebody's here!
Grab my jacket,
get my jacket!
Ahh.
Mm-mmm.
Nectar.
Hey, will.
Hey.
Are you coming
to my boss' party today?
Absolutely.
Where is it?
Malibu.
Free beer?
All you can drink.
I suppose i can
check it out.
Amanda, on answering machine:
speak!
The car
has been stolen.
Before i call the police,
i thought your brother
might have an idea about--
hi, dad. Hi, dad.
Yeah, amanda,
willie wouldn't be there
by any chance,
would he?
Yeah, yeah,
he's here.
Did you know he's supposed
to be grounded?
No, no, that was
my fault.
I asked him
to come over
and help me
hang some stuff.
Well, it would have been nice
if he'd let me know he was--
no, no, no,
you're right.
He should have
left a note.
All right, well, make sure
he doesn't drink anything.
No, i promise.
And be sure he gets home ok,
would you?
Ok.
All right, bye, honey.
Speak to you soon.
Ok. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
You're busted!
Will, you gotta stop
stealing dad's car!
Come on, i can't face
all those gonads on the bus!
And besides, the car's
just sitting there.
He's never around anyway.
What's with all the beer?
Oh, god.
Thanks for
covering for me.
Yeah.
So, uh, what time's
that party today?
You are not going
to the party.
You are going home.
But m.j. invited me!
No!
Besides, you owe banks
an apology,
and until he gets one,
this house is off-limits, ok?
Banks?
I meant it!
Anybody home?
Oh. Hi, guys.
Banks, dude, look.
I'm sorry about asking
why you're a butt pirate.
Oh, my god. Willie!
Ok, no hard feelings,
all right, man?
What?!
What?
M.j.
m.j., your boss has
a nice little beach house.
This is just for weekends.
It's the biggest place
in town.
Oh, my god.
Divine.
Wow.
Nervous, frankie?
Mm-hmm.
All right, let's go.
Thank you.
Hey. Thanks.
Oh, my god.
David!
I'm going to the bar.
Excuse me.
Oh, champagne.
Cheers.
M.j., it's about time.
And of course
you know julia.
Julia.
Nice to see you, m.j.
you look so--so skinny.
The house is great.
Everything looks--
it's nice of you
to say so.
Would you excuse me
for a minute?
I need to have a word
with the caterer.
All right.
Bye--bye, honey.
Oof, your wife hates me.
Well, of course.
But for all
the right reasons.
I'd take it
as a compliment.
It's good
to see you again.
Sorry, but...
i don't know you.
Yes, you do.
But you might not
remember.
It wasn't
in this lifetime.
But i'm sure it's you.
Apparently,
you're mistaking me
for somebody who just might
buy into this shit.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
I want to talk to you.
Every thought,
every feeling,
every action of my life,
my pasts...
has led me to this moment.
You are the other half.
Spare me, ok?
The more you know,
the less you'll understand.
Alexander.
Alexander midnight.
When did you
make that one up?
I come from a long lineage
of midnights.
Let me guess.
When you're not,
um, you know,
passing out
the cocktails,
i bet...
that you are an actor.
And if i said yes,
what does that mean?
Do you so easily
define people
by their--
by their occupations?
Don't we measure
a person's strength
on what we call
"distinction"?
True individuality?
Everyone wants
to make their mark,
but the buddhists say,
"that is only the pursuit
of a phantom."
You're not one of those
chanting buddhists,
are you?
But this--this identity,
this label,
it's merely a thought,
it's a picture
of who we are,
what we can be.
It's an illusion.
Do you want
to take a walk?
Well, i thought you were
working this party.
Not anymore.
Whoa! Windy!
Heh. How are you?
Fine.
Vic. Vic montana.
Hello.
Pleasure's all yours.
Excuse me, i have to...
get a--my--
excuse me.
You know, you remind me
of someone.
So, is there anything
you want to confess?
You seem like
the type of person
who has a lot of secrets.
Why would i tell you?
Because you like me.
No, i don't.
Yes, you do.
I do not!
You're lying!
How can you tell?
'Cause your nostrils
are flaring.
No, they're not.
Yes, they are.
They're not!
They are.
They're not.
You're very cute.
Hey!
Hi, honey.
Hello.
I just met the fruit
of the loom grape.
He's actually a hell
of a nice guy.
Hey...
that guy,
he's really cute.
Very cute.
You're not shopping.
Oh, yeah.
Where is taylor anyway?
I don't know.
Probably working.
Everything ok
with you guys?
Yeah.
You know what, banks?
I think i'm gonna
marry him.
Really?
Someday.
Well, i'm happy for ya.
Thank you.
That's great.
So why are you so quiet
all the time?
Why do you ask so many
questions all the time?
I want to know
everything about you.
Well, maybe i'm resting
my brain.
You have this
goddess thing
about you,
you know that?
Really?
You remind me
of aphrodite.
Well, maybe
i should have been
a statue
in somebody's garden.
What are you
so angry about?
I admire you social workers
for doing something
so selfless in this town
full of egomaniacs.
And i'm no exception.
Banks, yes, you are.
Listen, honey, you're wasting
your time with tinkerbelle here.
Call me.
Hey, loved your shampoo spot.
It worked.
Yeah.
Don't ask.
Having fun
at your party?
No. You?
I love your parties.
Yeah, well,
you have to say that.
You work for me.
No.
I mean, look at all these
dreadful people
i'm forced to entertain,
pretending to like each other.
At least in new york,
people hate each other openly.
Although, there is one person
i'd like you to meet, mm-hmm.
Over there, see him?
Paul knowles.
Major venture capitalist,
recently divorced.
Aphrodite.
You want to take a dip?
What, you think i'm gonna
get in this thing with you?
Why not?
Well, what if somebody
comes in?
I mean, i usually
don't make a habit
of getting into hot tubs
with people
i just met at a party.
But we didn't
just meet.
Ok, the other life,
i completely forgot,
i'm sorry.
Hey, it's just a tub.
Plus, look what i found.
♪ Bum bum bum ♪
ok, ok, but, um...
just leave your underwear on.
Oh. I wouldn't have it
any other way.
Here, you can wear
my t-shirt.
I'll just, uh,
i'll wait under here...
until you've
changed.
All right.
Ahh.
Hey, come on,
hurry up, all right?
And don't look.
Actually,
i just got back
from spending a month
in kenya.
Ooh. How wonderful.
Yeah, it was.
People there say
it's the soul
of the universe.
I think so.
Good place to get away,
clear your mind.
Ah.
But enough
about that stuff.
David tells me
you're the new fireball
down at the brokerage.
I love my job.
Maybe we should
get together and, uh--
talk money?
Well, i had thought about
a little dinner first.
That would be great.
Let me give you my card.
Great.
My home number's on it.
Call me.
Perfect.
Thanks.
My brother and i used
to pretend we were in seahunt
and stay under water
for 45 minutes
and really
freak our mother out.
How amusing.
Stop it.
Hey, how come
you're so worried
about being miss perfect
all the time, huh?
Stop it!
Don't you realize
that is it precisely
our imperfections
that makes each human
individually loveable?
Do you ever
take some time
and actually listen
to the shit
that you say?
Do you?
I am a firm believer
in love at first sight.
And few people are fortunate
enough to experience it.
So why are you
telling me this?
When i saw you earlier,
i knew that we had
been together before.
That's what love
at first sight is.
It's a reconnection
of 2 old, intertwined souls.
It's snowing.
Hey man, thanks a lot
for the party.
Oh, yes.
We'll really have to
have you over next time.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, betty.
Hey, wait a second!
Wasn't that guy
working for us?
I know,
i should have called.
Are you mad?
No, i was
just worried
when you never
showed up.
I know, i'm sorry.
But i...
i'm just not in the mood
to be at a party tonight.
Taylor, what's
going on?
I woke up this morning
wondering...
how much of my life
am i going to spend
working on cases that...
i don't care about?
So i quit.
Do you think i'm crazy?
No.
I mean...
i don't know
what i'm gonna do,
but somehow that just
doesn't seem...
very important right now.
Boy, i knew
you were unhappy.
I had no idea
it was this extreme.
Yeah.
Well, i kinda wish
you had talked to me
about it.
Well, uh--
it's just something
i needed to work out alone.
But why don't you
let me help you?
I love you, taylor.
I just want us
to be happy.
Pphttt.
I gotta go to bed,
you guys.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Ok, honey.
It was fun.
Good night.
Bye.
Mmm.
I think i'm gonna
turn in, too.
Amanda?
Yeah?
Who was that guy
that you disappeared with?
Oh, he's just
another lunatic
who's convinced
we were lovers
in a past life.
Oh, dear.
It's very
frightening.
Good night, honey.
Good night.
Henry, on answering machine:
hi, this is henry's machine.
I'm not home right now--
hello, i'm here!
Don't hang up! Hello!
Like, one minute
you can't stand the guy,
and then you're
picking up the phone
and you're calling him.
Oh, you're one to talk.
Hopping into hot tubs
with total strangers.
M.j., nothing happened.
Of course, i understand
why that's so difficult
for you to believe,
because you probably
would have fucked him.
Just because
some of us enjoy sex
doesn't imply
that i'm a slut.
Henry wasn't
your type anyway.
Neither were
half the other guys
i've ever dated.
Do you guys know that
i lost my virginity
to a kleptomaniac?
His name was bobby rose.
Seriously, after he took
my virginity,
he stole my father's watch.
A total klepto.
Well, at least
you remember his name.
I lost my virginity
to doris becker,
and i've never been
the same since.
Boris becker?
Boris becker, my god!
So, uh, banks,
have you ever thought
that, i don't know,
maybe you just
haven't been
with the right
woman yet?
Well, that's definitely
not the issue here,
but thank you
for the offer.
Oh, you're welcome.
Look, i haven't lost
my virginity yet,
but i'll be sure
to share it with you all
in great detail when i do.
Oh, jeez, isn't anybody
tired in this house?
It's 4 a.m.!
You know what's
the really weird thing?
Is that the only thing
i can remember
is that it was in
my parents' house
behind the couch.
It's so scary how our brains
let us remember
only isolated memories.
I think it's all
still in there,
but as we get older,
our brain, you know,
sorts through
all those ideas
and memories
and feelings
and philosophies.
And it's like
it's all compacting
and compressing down.
But you know, like,
a diamond is formed?
Ok, so we're forming
a diamond in our minds
of who are we are
and what we need to know.
Sometimes i think
it's best just to forget
certain things that have
happened to us.
So, where
are we going tonight?
He's making me dinner.
Oh, how nineties.
Oh, honey,
you can't wear that.
So, what--who's
making you dinner?
The man i met
at david's house.
The older one?
Uh-huh.
Oh!
Ugh, i do look fat.
Yeah, you--
she's really fat.
She's huge.
At least 10 pounds overweight
on the hips.
I haven't seen much
of you or taylor lately.
Taylor quit his job,
you guys.
Really?
Wow.
He didn't want me
to say anything.
Been in a really
weird mood lately.
What an idiot.
He was making
so much money.
So what is he
gonna do now?
I don't know.
Tonight's our
one year anniversary.
Oh, god,
i hope he remembers.
Doubtful.
I'm just kidding!
Amanda, mr. Midnight's
been calling
an awful lot lately.
Not interested.
I mean, as friends.
You know, he's helping me
put together
a show and stuff.
I think
he's good looking
and i think you guys
make a fabulous couple.
Listen, you can't
wear underwear with that.
You have major v.p.l.
then i'm not gonna go.
Christ, will you just
put anything on?!
You'll take it off,
anyway.
It's different
with paul.
He's older,
sophisticated.
Besides, he's
a potential client,
and i have never
slept with a client.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
The opera man!
Taylor...
i'm really glad
you remembered.
I thought for sure
you'd forget.
You don't know what
i'm talking about.
Of course i do.
What, then?
Jesus, taylor.
Hi.
- Hi.
Wow, you look great.
Thanks.
Come on in.
Thank you.
Hello?
Hey,
is amanda there?
She's not here
at the moment.
Can i take a message
and ask who's
calling, please?
This is alexander midnight.
Hi, alex,
how you doing?
Is there something wrong
with your voice?
No, there's nothing
wrong with my voice.
What are you doing tonight?
Tonight?
Yeah.
I'm painting.
Well, can you go out?
I want to show you something.
I don't think so.
Oh, come on, why not?
Because.
Your nostrils are flaring.
No, my nostrils
are not flaring, ok?
Yes, they are.
I'm gonna come over, ok?
Ok. Ok, fine.
Ok, but just
for an hour.
No problem, no problem,
just an hour.
Ok. Bye.
What a piece of work
is man?
How noble in reason?
Of infinite and faculties,
in form and moving.
How express and admirable.
In action,
how like an angel...
in apprehension.
How like a god.
The beauty of the world,
the paragon of animals.
♪ My kitty, your kitty,
everybody's little kitty ♪
♪ likes to eat its chow ♪
meow!
♪ My kitty, your kitty-- ♪
oh, man. Forget it.
Thanks, i'm glad
you like it.
I find it attractive
when a woman appreciates
a good wine.
My ex-wife always
used to complain
that it gave her a headache.
Well...
so what happened?
If you don't mind
my asking.
No, that's all right.
I found out that she'd been
having an affair.
For quite a long time.
How awful.
Yeah, it broke my heart.
I'm just glad we didn't
have any kids.
But it's been a while now.
Since then i've been having
love affairs
with french burgundies
from the seventies.
Cheers.
All right,
hold on.
I know what
this place is.
I didn't come up here
to fuck you,
so don't even think
about it, all right?
Whoa.
Who hurt you so bad?
I'd never fuck you, ok?
I just wanted to show you
one of my favorite places.
Look...
i really need you
right now...
to be patient with me.
It's not that i don't care,
because...
i do.
I--i--
i'm sorry.
God, you smell great.
Where did you take
this photo?
Oh.
Well, i spent
a lot of time
exploring
the serengeti,
and i took this shot
from the taita hills
at about, uh,
7,000 feet.
You can see for hundreds
of miles from this spot,
and at night,
there'd be these
incredible
lightning storms
that just ignite
the entire plane.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
You know, heh,
we've talked about food.
Why don't we
talk about money?
What are you
thinking about?
About the different ways
looking up at the stars
can make me feel.
Like how?
Well...
when you read things like...
we're just one galaxy
of some hundred thousand
million galaxies,
and each galaxy itself
contains some hundred thousand
million stars.
I mean...
how are you supposed
to get out of bed
in the morning?
You know?
It wasn't until...
last week that i realized...
i'd been afraid to look up
at the night sky.
You know, instead of being
in awe of it all
or amazed...
at the mystery
and the beauty.
That was terrifying.
Everything felt
unbearably huge.
But then last night...
i stayed up all night
just sittin' right here
thinkin'...
and i was overcome
by the sense that...
everything was gonna be ok.
Even if i didn't really
understand why.
And despite how fucked up
or chaotic things may seem,
it...
well, maybe there is
some order to it all.
I mean, it can't
just be coincidence.
There are the smallest
of perfections
in the most...
unlikely places.
Like...
the swell of your lips.
Or the curve of your breast.
I want you to come, frankie.
I want to watch you come.
You know, i really should
get going.
Why?
Because i just don't think
we should be doing this.
Why not?
Well, um, ow. Wait.
Wait a second.
You know, i don't--
wait, paul! No!
No, wait, please,
i don't want this.
Why don't you
want this?
Because!
No, no!
No, paul, stop it!
No! No!
No!
Aah!
I want to travel.
Hmm, where to?
I don't know.
It just seems like
the only thing
holding me to this down
are these dock lines and you.
How the hell is that
supposed
to make me feel?
What--
it means that i love you.
I want to go.
Will you
take me home?
I'm sorry.
Tonight was such
a disaster.
Do you want me
to come inside?
No, it's late.
I have to get up
really early.
So...
tell me 3 images
from your childhood.
Quick.
Don't even think about it.
Cats,
lime jell-o, and...
baseball games.
Good.
And you?
Me?
Mm-hmm.
Kneeling, snow,
and my twin brother.
You have a twin brother?
Mm-hmm.
Charlie.
Charlie midnight.
He's excellent.
Oh, god.
Not another one of you.
I gotta go.
So you'll remember me.
See you around, kid.
Are you mad at me?
No, i'm not mad at you.
I'm just tired.
I'll see you tomorrow, ok?
H-hey--
oh, my god.
M.j.
w-wait--what--
what happened
to you?
Hey. What
happened to you?
My god.
It makes you wonder
what the word "no"
means to some
people, doesn't it?
God.
I wonder how many
other women
this has happened to.
Tons.
I offer no excuse
for those of my sex.
I mean, half the male ego
problem stems from the fact
that we can't have children.
Women are--are--
are so much more grounded
because they can give
a child life.
Whereas men, they're in
this constant battle,
whether blatant or subtle,
to make their mark
in the world.
Well, he certainly
made his mark.
So why didn't you
nail his ass?
M.j., it was like
you just let him
get away with it.
Amanda, i really wish
you would stop
throwing this in my face.
Do you know
what i went through?
Do you have any idea?
Have you ever been raped?
Well, if you're not gonna
deal with it legally,
you know,
like pressing charges,
i think maybe you should
work it out emotionally.
What are you talking about--
emotionally?
Get in touch
with my feelings?
You're the ice princess
of the world
and you're telling me to get
in touch with my feelings.
I am talking about using it
as a fucking excuse
for treating the other
people in your life
like shit.
Ohh...
you know...
whew. I thought
you understood.
What...
what time is it?
It's early.
It's very early
and i'm sorry.
It's ok.
I've been up all night
fighting a panic attack.
Sometimes i just feel like
i'm--i'm so dried up inside
and that there's
something...
sucking the life
out of me and...
i don't know what--
i try to fight it,
but...
come here.
Honey...
i'm sorry.
Just think of what
you've been through.
You know, i really think
that you should press charges
against this bastard.
No. No, i just want to
put it all behind me.
M.j., this fucker
raped you.
You can't expect those
feelings just to disappear
3 weeks later.
Yeah, but, you know...
maybe--maybe i--
maybe i brought it on
myself.
Don't you dare say that.
It's your body.
He had no business forcing you
into doing something
that you did not want to do.
Yeah,
and then david said
that paul totally
lied to me,
that--that
it was his wife
that caught him in bed
with another woman.
I am such an idiot.
I can't believe
i fell for his crap.
He's a pig.
But, hey,
how are you
supposed to know?
God, i...
i just can't get it
out of my head.
I'm sorry.
How you doin'?
Who's bones?
Frankie? Why her?
'Cause she's
so damn skinny.
That's a good call.
I heard there was
a shooting last night.
What happened?
I don't know.
Mario, what happened?
A few of the boys
from the hood
did a drive-by
and wasted
some of the e.s.g.
were you there?
No.
Mario.
No way.
I can't believe
2 kids are dead over graffiti.
Yeah, well,
people get shot down here
for all sorts of reasons.
That's just the way it is.
Hey! What's you doin'?
Cut it out.
I got you.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're a menace.
Come over and help us paint.
I don't give a fuck
about your stupid mural.
You lied. You said you were
gonna take us to the beach.
Hey, hey, hey.
Come on, man,
chill, ok?
You be cool.
Look. She's down
with us, homeboy,
so why don't you stop
causing scenes like this
or we're not getting
any more paint,
do you understand?
Huh?
Ok, go on.
Go finish your work.
By the way, i lined up
the next space.
They're gonna pay you.
Cool.
Um...
who's your friend
with the hair?
That's my housemate.
Amanda?
Yeah?
Mario.
Mario, amanda.
How you doin'?
Hi.
I really like your work.
Uh, thank you.
You're welcome.
Can i help you paint?
Yeah. Yeah,
that'd be great.
It'd be an honor.
Cool.
You can start over here
and, uh...
i'm famished.
I'm always starving
before a show.
I need more fuel
for maximum energy.
Oh, by the way,
did i mention
that i made a manikin
of you out of papier-mache?
She sits in my bathtub
sipping a martini.
I tell her all my secrets,
and she just smiles.
Who is this guy?
Radical board, dude.
You been half-pipin' it
lately?
Alex,
this is willie.
Willie, the little bro.
What's happenin'?
How's it hangin', slim?
Pretty good.
Cool.
I got baseball cards, minx.
Thanks, little bro.
Where you guys goin'
with this thing? Whoa.
We're gonna go hang these
at the club where alex
is doing his performance
art piece tonight.
You gonna come, dude?
Well, if it's ok
with minx.
Sure it is.
Yeah, you can get
a ride with m.j.
bye.
Sexy.
Whoo!
Oh, i gotta show you
my place.
I hear you've been having
some sort of existential
meltdown.
May i recommend
a bottle of wild turkey,
a copy of sartre's
la nausee,
and a double-barreled
shotgun
to cure this affliction.
Come on, it's a joke.
Yeah.
I'm--i'm glad
you're here.
I've been wanting
to talk to you.
About?
About what happened to me
a couple weeks ago.
I want to say thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
No. It really meant a lot,
you being there like that,
and i just wanted to say...
thank you.
You just tell me
where he lives,
i swear i'll kick
the shit out of him.
Oh, no. I'm just trying
to put it behind me.
I'm just sorry
that it happened to you.
Friends?
You know what
the really sad part is?
For a minute there,
it felt like somebody
was out there for me.
Yeah, right.
Sometimes i wonder
if there's any hope
for romance.
This is it.
Oh, wow.
This is great.
Yes, i'm into
organized chaos.
I can see that.
Oh, wait.
What?
I have something
for you.
I'll get it.
So, um, finish telling me
about this--this crazy
theory of yours.
What did you call it--
accessible...
happiness. My theory
of accessible happiness.
And it's not crazy.
See, if you can think
of 3 accessible things,
little things
that make you happy,
that you can
always count on,
because they are
immediately attainable.
It works.
Like for me.
I have my motorcycle,
led zeppelin,
and my third thing is--
oh, god.
Big sandwiches.
All right.
Good as mine.
Ohh!
Oh!
Oh, god!
Ohh!
Damn.
You broke my nose,
you creep!
Good.
So, in the 12th century
there was this radical
mutation in human feelings
and consciousness.
It was then that the origins
of romantic love can be found.
People finally
began saying fuck you
to prearranged marriages,
going against
the church's will,
willing to risk
burning in hell for love.
It was the time of those
crazy troubadours
who wore tight velvet pants
and sang songs of love
to ladies who tested
and tortured them
and made them wait.
But they waited...
because it was for true love.
Do you ever stop talking?
So, after fighting
many silly battles--
whoo--
and standing around
and guarding
unnecessary bridges
and waiting in the rain
reciting endless poetry...
the ladies
would either refuse
the troubadours
or accept them as lovers,
by saying...
merci.
Merci beaucoup, mon amour.
Isn't that incredible?
You have to read this book.
All of these books.
Do you know what
they all have in common?
I have no idea.
They all have something
interesting to say
on page 36.
Page 36.
Yes.
It's a 9 number.
The number 9 represents
contact with the inner soul,
greater self-expression,
the order of the angels.
Ok.
It's a little trick
i picked up
from granny midnight.
You'd be surprised.
She also gave me black panthie.
And my pet
emperor scorpion sufi.
Would you like to meet him?
No.
Sufi.
Come here. Su--
no, stop it.
Wait a minute.
Oh! Don't do that.
This looks like fun.
Yeah, it looks
flea-infested to me.
Yeah.
Am i nervous?
Well, no, now that
your paintings are here,
i think everything's
gonna work out fine.
It's gonna be great.
Yeah?
Amanda.
Hey.
Hi.
It looks great.
Hi, m.j.
it looks fantastic.
Oh, my god,
you're gonna be so famous.
I'm so proud of you.
Willie's stuck at the door.
The bouncer won't let him in.
Bubba won't let him in?
No.
Ok, i'm gonna
take care of it.
Hi, ladies.
Forrest walrath.
I'm 24 years old.
I'm a virgo.
Uh... i was born
in 19...
i come here--
i come here a lot.
Uh... i do.
I really--
bubba. Bubba,
uh, listen,
this guy's
a special visitor...
ok, thanks.
Thanks, big, uh...
uh, bubba.
Where's frankie?
That's a good question.
I'm starting to get
worried about her.
I don't like the idea
of her downtown this late.
It's not really safe.
Yeah, i know.
But she knows
what she's doing.
She's been doing it
for a long time.
Look, if you're
really worried,
you can take my car.
Ah--
yeah, i mi--
yeah, i will.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I'll see you later.
You gotta stay,
because all the guys
will be coming down
and we'll be going down--
i gotta go.
No, come on, please?
It'll be live.
We'll be jamming.
I don't know.
Boom box.
Noise.
Dancing.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, man,
what's up, homes?
The mural looks great, ese.
Doesn't it look nice?
You like the colors?
Man, all that work...
work, you know?
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's give a big
round of applause
to mr. Alexander midnight!
When i think about my life,
it seems to be composed
of random images,
all stored in my brain
like pictures
in a photo album.
Often, for no reason at all,
i'll think of some lost part
of my childhood.
The smell
of my mother's hair.
My dad's big hands,
coarse and callused.
Lime jell-o
in the afternoon.
Waah!
Lightning bugs
in thick glass jars.
Aaaahhh...
sometimes,
if i think hard enough,
i can see myself
a child again.
Aaaahhhh!
Aaaahhhhh!
When i was about 12,
i remember
lying awake in my bed
on a quiet, dark night,
feeling my heart pulse,
pulse, pulse,
throughout my whole body.
For the first time,
i understood that someday
it would be still.
I became petrified,
and i stayed awake
all night sweating,
with my eyes wide,
for i knew
if i fell asleep,
i would die!
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo.
Yeah!
Whoo, yeah!
I have since
come to terms
with the fact
that i will die.
I tell myself that death
is just a part of life,
and many people
have done it before me.
Still i wonder,
where do we go?
From here to there
and back again.
An entrance
into infinite
possibilities...
ssssss!
There are times
when i wake up early,
perhaps on
a saturday morning,
with sunlight
pouring through the window.
And i blink a few times,
maybe rub my eyes,
and i put my feet
on the cool...
wood... floor.
And i look outside,
and i see a slow blur
of color and motion,
which discriminates
into cars and bicycles,
young couples with strollers
and shopping bags,
sea gulls--awk! Awk! Awk!
Old men on benches.
I drink a cup
of cuban coffee
and make a list
entitled "today."
On these mornings,
everything is clear
and sharp,
and i often marvel
at how beautifully
everything is put together.
The laws of physics
and chemistry
that have somehow interacted
to maintain this world.
What is your contribution,
i ask myself in the mirror?
Whoo!
I am alone, floating,
seeking the rapture
of being alive,
my mind
fragrant with memories.
I do not try to figure out
where i am going.
I simply live my life
from day to day
and let the strange
forces of destiny
take me where they may!
Look out!
I am a happy man.
Yeah!
All right!
Whoo!
Hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Boy, did you miss
a hell of a show, man.
Hey there, buddy,
what are you doing
sitting in the dark?
She's still not back.
No call, no message,
nothin'.
I'm, like, ready
to call the police.
Relax. They're probably
celebrating
because they just
finished the mural.
I wouldn't alert the lapd.
That's a long time
to celebrate.
Well, i wish
frankie was here
because i have something
kind of important
to tell everybody.
Um...
i've been accepted
into steppenwolf.
Hey, congratulations!
Oh, that is so cool.
What the hell
does that mean?
It means i'm moving
to chicago january 1st
to get back
into the theater!
Score! Then i can move
into your room, bro.
Congratulations, honey.
Thank you so much.
I'm really proud of you.
We're gonna miss you.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
Well, here's to
the windy city
and to getting the fuck
out of los angeles.
You know, there's
a few things about l.a.
you're gonna miss.
Yeah, like, uh,
not getting a seat
at a restaurant
unless you've been
in the arts and entertainment
section recently, like, uh--
trapped on the 405
on friday.
Yeah. Like, uh--
meeting new
and interesting people
who have something
to talk about
other than film
and who's fucking who.
Exactly my point.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Let's go party.
Let's party.
To chicago.
No, i don't drink,
thank you.
That's cool.
Great job, alex.
I'll be in in a second. Ok?
Oh.
Hey, minx. Want a cheese
and pickle sandwich?
Cool it with the beer.
Here.
Unh.
So this is great.
I get to move
into banks' room.
Finally!
Willie, you can't
move in here.
Willie.
Sure i can.
You are 16 years old.
You have to go
to high school,
and you have to live
with dad.
Well, maybe i don't
want to live with dad.
And if you don't
want me here,
i'll just find
someplace else.
Sweetie,
listen to me, all right?
It's not that
we don't want you here. Ok?
You just gotta slow down
a little bit.
Besides, dad and sharon
want you with them, so--
yeah, right.
I think they'd be thrilled
if i wasn't there.
I mean, you don't--you don't
know what it's like.
You haven't lived at home
for years.
Maybe you're right.
But you know something,
willie?
Mama's been dead
a long time.
And dad, i don't know,
he's...
he's just trying
to live his life.
And i understand completely
why you are angry at him,
but trust me,
in time, you will learn
to forgive him.
I doubt that.
I know you're gonna think
i'm a queer for saying this.
But i love you.
And i would absolutely do
anything in the world for you.
But you can't move in here.
Mmm...
want some potato chips
with your sandwich?
No.
Ok.
There's some pillows
and blankets on the couch.
You can sleep there tonight.
All right?
Ok.
♪ China ♪
♪ gets broken ♪
♪ it will never be the same ♪
♪ boats on the ocean ♪
♪ find their way back again ♪
♪ i am weaving ♪
♪ like a drunkard ♪
♪ like a balloon
up in the air ♪
♪ i am needing a puncture ♪
♪ and someone to point me
somewhere ♪
♪ i'm gonna keep
my head on straight ♪
♪ steady on ♪
♪ i just hope
it's not too late... ♪
m.j., i am totally
in love with you
and would very much like
to have sex with you right now.
I was told to find
an older woman
to groom me sexually
so that i can
drive the chicks crazy.
So i choose you.
I mean, think of it
as performing
a greatly needed service
to a sex-crazed 16-year-old
virgin seeking knowledge.
Oh, will...
so what do you say?
So what do i say?
I'd say you're probably
one of those guys
that girls are gonna be
back-stabbing
each other for.
Parents are gonna be
waiting up late at night,
worried
about their daughters.
You know?
Will?
And you'll probably be
one of those guys
who passes out after sex.
Good night, will.
♪ I was feeling imploded ♪
♪ a wooden smile,
a wooden heart ♪
♪ then things exploded ♪
♪ like rockets in the dark ♪
♪ now i'm pulling
out splinters ♪
♪ and i'm off
to hibernate somewhere ♪
♪ for the nuclear winter
of another love affair ♪
♪ 'cause he seemed
like a miracle ♪
♪ steady on ♪
♪ i ate it up like cereal ♪
♪ but it was something
like shrapnel ♪
♪ steady on, steady on ♪
♪ steady ♪
♪ gotta steady on ♪
where the hell
have you been?
Do you have any idea how--
what happened to you?
♪ Steady on ♪
♪ steady on... ♪
♪ steady on ♪
good night.
♪ I'm gonna keep
my head on straight ♪
♪ i'm gonna keep
♪ i'm gonna keep my head on... ♪
♪ straight ♪
♪ just steady on... ♪
i am so...
sorry.
I don't know
what to say.
You just gotta
keep in mind, frankie...
you can't save
the whole world.
♪ Just steady on... ♪
maybe not.
Mario's dead,
and, um... mm...
i really would have liked
to have saved him.
Ohh...
ohh...
oh, god.
The one day
i get to sleep in.
Oh, god--
oh.
Goddamn it.
Great.
There's no ginger ale.
Is it my imagination
or do these guys
just blow leaves
from one pile to another?
What is willie doing
in your bed?
I really can't believe
that a 16-year-old is--
amanda, i didn't sleep
with your brother.
Bet you can't catch me!
I bet i can! I bet i can!
Banks, i need you
to make sure
all the christmas lights
are plugged in.
Already done.
This is my last cigarette
of the year.
Good new year's
resolution,
but according to the paper,
out of the last 365 days,
the air in l.a.
was found unfit to breathe
189 days.
That's ridiculous.
189 days?
Why would anybody
live here?
Tell me about it.
I think we should all
move to bali.
That's totally screwed up.
Willie, keys.
All right, guys,
we gotta concentrate,
just gotta breathe,
just gotta concentrate.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
These guys gotta cool out
with this party anxiety.
Oh!
Right here?
You want to know the key
to my sister's heart?
Mm-hmm.
Orange marshmallow
peanuts.
If 75 people don't show up,
my reputation's ruined!
Trust me,
she loves these.
I could owe you big
on this one, bud.
Yes, you could.
Ha ha.
How we doin', sweetie?
Well, i think
this party's a smash
as long as more of
the hollywood elite show.
And you wonder why nobody
entertains in l.a.
one lousy party
and your life can be shattered.
Lots of chicks.
Oh, you saw backlash.
Thanks.
Barbara eden really went
the distance on that one.
Hey, how are you?
Alex.
Why are you always
grinning?
Copious amounts
of wild sex
and fine hallucinogens.
So help me god!
Having a little
trouble, amanda?
Come on! Come on!
Oh!
I didn't invite him.
Hey, guys,
can i come in?
Close the door,
already!
Oh!
My face is crooked.
Oh, ok.
You worry way too much.
I can't believe
either one of you told me
i have this thing
in my teeth.
Everyone having fun?
Yeah, except
the one guy i like.
He's more interested
in banks.
Henry keeps following me
around.
I'm sorry,
henry bugs me.
What about you?
What about your boyfriend alex?
He's not my boyfriend.
Nuh-uh.
So, frankie,
how was the funeral?
It was pretty depressing.
Uch. It must have
been a nightmare.
Was it really sad
being down there?
You know,
mario was a real good guy.
Yeah, he was.
There's so much
going on, you guys.
I got offered a job,
with the van horne
foundation in san francisco.
San francisco?
Frankie, that's great.
I don't know.
I love my life here, you know?
Why should i
give this all up?
Because
it's a career move,
an opportunity.
Money.
Taylor talked you
out of it, didn't he?
He doesn't even know yet.
Come on!
Keep your pants on!
God! Oh, henry.
Hi, henry.
Hello, henry.
What the hell you suppose
they've been doing in there?
Women--they have this thing
about pissing in packs.
Smoking is for the weak.
Um, excuse me.
I need to borrow them
for a minute.
We're doing a group
photo thing, so...
what--
what are you doing?
Group photo!
Hey, you guys, where's--
m.j.!
Aah!
M.j.!
I'm coming,
i'm coming!
Whoo! Yes!
1... 2... 3...
smile.
Thank you!
Hey.
Want something to drink?
I'll have a little bubbly.
Whoo...
it's wonderful news
about frankie.
What are you
talking about?
Her job offer
in san francisco.
I think she should
take it.
Could you excuse us
for a second? Thanks.
Could i talk to you?
So what's this
about san francisco?
You heard.
Yeah. I--
i can't believe you haven't
said anything to me.
I mean, that's--
i was planning on
telling you tomorrow
when we had time
to discuss it.
I don't understand.
Frankie, are you...
do you love me?
Yes.
I really do.
Good, good. That's good.
I--i mean...
it's good because
i've been thinking
about all these plans
for us.
I... i mean,
i kind of thought that
we would get married.
Do you want to marry me?
I mean...
will you marry me?
Yeah?
Ohh...
look at you.
You can open up
your eyes now.
I made this for you.
It's called ride 'em, cowboy.
Amanda, i love it.
Oh, god.
Oh...
i'm gonna miss you.
I'll come visit you.
Hey...
hey.
I like alex.
He's great.
Yeah?
Yeah.
He is pretty cool.
It's like the two long-lost
brothers over here.
At least i'm leaving you
in good hands.
Oh, please.
This guy is so cool.
He says he's gonna get me
a tattoo.
No tattoos.
I can't wait.
First of all,
straighten up.
Straighten up.
Look, like there's--
like there's a string
coming from the ceiling.
From the sky.
That's right.
Straighten up.
Come on, will, ok?
You're very tense.
I want to dance
at your wedding.
Can you believe
he asked me to marry him?
M.j., i'm so happy.
You want to dance, baby,
or what?
Eew.
Later. Ok.
I've been doing
a lot of thinking lately.
Do you think it's possible
to find someone to love?
You're drunk,
and i don't want
to hear it.
No, it seems that
everybody's either
getting divorced
or fucking around these days.
Most of the couples
i know, they're miserable,
trapped.
No. I think marriage
is doomed. I really do.
You know, you are
truly unbelievable.
I just asked frankie
to marry me
and now
you're out here
talking about
divorce.
I'm not in the mood
for one of your
games tonight, m.j.
no, taylor.
I'm not playing any games.
I'm just confused.
I don't think i'll ever
find anyone to love.
I know
a hundred guys
that are in love
with you.
Soon as you decide
you want someone...
yeah, look what happened
the last time
i thought i found someone.
And even if i did
find someone,
how do i make it work?
How do i make it last?
Do you really think
it's possible
to be with one person
your whole life?
Do you?
Yeah.
What has it been,
2 months?
Let's give this guy
a medal!
Shut up!
And what happens
after you're married?
You go to a party,
and there,
sitting right there,
is the woman of your dreams.
Imagine never having sex
with anybody else,
never exploring a new body.
What do you do?
Do you suppress
those feelings?
I think you come
to realize
that such...
momentary satisfaction
doesn't outweigh
the pain you cause
in someone else.
Or your own guilt.
You can't suppress
those feelings, taylor.
You just don't
get it, do you?
There has been
nothing between
you and i
for months now.
At one point i thought
maybe i could love you
because behind
all of your bullshit,
there really is this
warm, loveable woman.
And maybe it's possible
to love 2 people
at the same time...
i don't know,
but i made a decision.
And in the process,
i've fallen in love
with frankie,
and i'm gonna
marry her.
Oh.
Oh...
we had some good times,
didn't we, taylor?
No.
Yeah.
But it was
just sex, m.j.
i mean, i always
got the feeling
that you thought
being with me
meant mediocrity.
Why am i even
talking about this?
I'm going back
inside.
Everything's all fucked up!
God, why can't you just
be happy for us, huh?!
Is that so goddamn
hard for you?
It--
it really
doesn't matter.
It's all
over with now.
You know, the only times
i've ever felt safe
is when i'm having sex.
I felt that way
with you, you know.
Like i could block out
all the other shit,
and then he took
even that away from me!
You know how terrible
everyone felt
when that happened
to you.
Deep down inside,
i know how you guys felt,
that i brought
everything on me.
M.j., that's not true.
Sometimes i think...
that i really did
love you,
and that i still do.
What are you doin', huh?
I'm not gonna fall for this.
You don't really
want me, m.j.
you just want to know
you can have me.
Then why do i want
to kiss you so badly?
Ugh.
You think we should go
pry my brother
off that poor girl's face?
Ah! Where'd you get these?
Mmm.
I can't believe
you actually
eat these things.
Mmm, tasty.
Right?
Do you know many
muscles there are
in the trunk
of an elephant?
No.
100,000.
Liar!
On my mother's eye.
Oh.
Merci, beaucoup.
I love the way
you look
right before
i kiss you.
Happy new year.
Ah!
M.j.! God!
Why are you here?
I know you want it.
What does it take
to get through to you, huh?
Come on!
M.j., don't do this.
Please don't do this.
Excuse me.
Has anyone seen taylor?
It's almost
midnight, right?
Yeah, no. No, i haven't
seen him lately.
Oh.
Ok, everybody,
it's almost midnight!
Ready?!
10, 9, 8,
7, 6,
5, 4,
3, 2--
come on.
One!
Oh, my god!
Oh, shit!
Frankie, wait, wait!
Frankie, please!
What's going on here?
Frankie!
You know what, amanda,
i'm really sick of you!
Well, fine! Be sick!
I don't give a shit!
You guys, you guys,
i'm sick of both of you.
Please? My plane leaves
in 4 hours.
Can't we just...
pretend to get along
for a little while?
Taylor, what happened?
Did you guys find her?
Talk to me! Hello!
Taylor!
No, we didn't
find her anywhere.
This is really
not good.
No, this is
really fucked up.
But, you know,
you really
can't blame the girl
for not wanting to be here.
Boy, that really
helps, amanda.
That really helps,
especially
coming from you
sitting on your ass.
Oh, fuck you!
She's out there
all alone!
She is all alone!
Frankie, frankie
will be here
when she'll be here.
Now, i think
we should all
just take a look
at the anxiety
flying around
this room.
Darling?
Yes?
I'm gonna
go upstairs
and have a relax.
You wanna come?
No.
Frankie...
frankie, let me explain.
There's nothing
to say.
No, just listen to me.
Get your hands
off of me.
No.
Get your hands
off of me!
No! Not until you--
get your fuckin'
hands off of me!
Ow! You're
hurting me!
All right, i just want
to explain to you what--
aah!
Have you ever thought
about anyone else
beside yourself?
God, for all
these years,
i have put up with
so much bullshit!
I'm such an idiot.
Ok, m.j., now you're gonna
tell her what happened.
God damn it, you tell her
what i said to you
in that room now!
He, um...
he told me that--
that he didn't love me.
That he loved you.
I was the one
that climbed
into bed with him.
I wasn't invited.
And it--it never
happened before?
Oh, god!
Oh, god, you both
are so fucked up!
You really
deserve each other.
I--i need help!
Please!
I need you.
I used to think
that was important,
that people needed me.
And look what i have
to show for it.
I'm moving out
of this house.
You can't go
to san francisco.
Come on, we can
work this out.
Please.
I'm not leaving l.a.
i belong here.
But you are getting
the fuck out of this house
right now.
I have to go.
Ok.
Well, anybody hungry?
Definitely, dude.
Let's get out of here!
I mean, everybody's acting
like somebody died.
This is new years day.
That means cheesy parades,
bloody marys,
football.
Breakfast is on me.
Oh, where'd
you get this?
Um, minx, now that you
have 2 rooms open,
you're definitely
gonna need a roommate.
Willie's there's not
going to be
anybody living here
after a while.
I love you.
I'm gonna
miss you.
Who's gonna take me
to the airport?
Mmm.
Here, let me get that.
My keys.
Thanks.
Bye.
♪ Strange to see you, babe ♪
♪ ain't nothing
down here free ♪
♪ did you
lose your ticket? ♪
♪ Hope you weren't
looking for me ♪
♪ now i'm still wearing
the scars i got ♪
♪ from being your fool ♪
♪ you messed me up
pretty good, babe ♪
♪ i didn't mean
to rule you ♪
♪ remember when
i first saw you, babe ♪
♪ you were looking
pretty good ♪
♪ said you were
looking for love ♪
♪ well, then
why didn't you? ♪
♪ You just sat there ♪
♪ taking everything
that you could get ♪
♪ never thought one day ♪
♪ you might have
to pay for it... ♪
i'm gonna
miss this place.
♪ Well, did you ever
dream, baby ♪
♪ one day you might fall... ♪
let's go.
It'll miss you.
I ought to know.
Come on, banks.
All right.
♪ Did you ever dream, baby,
one day you might crawl? ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ did you ever dream ♪
♪ now when you're putting
on your face ♪
♪ i guess that you feel
kinda low ♪
♪ knowing that you
passed your best ♪
♪ and you got
nothing to show ♪
♪ well, baby, you know
just as well as i ♪
♪ some fool is gonna
fall your way ♪
♪ only this time around ♪
♪ you might have
to pay for it ♪
♪ did you ever dream, baby
one day you might fall? ♪
♪ And feel your back
against the wall? ♪
♪ Did you ever dream, baby
one day you might crawl? ♪
♪ That's what i said ♪
♪ did you ever dream ♪
♪ baby ♪
♪ when you had no need ♪
♪ did you ever dream ♪
♪ that you might
have to pay for it? ♪
♪ I do believe ♪
♪ that you might
have to pay now ♪
♪ did you ever dream, baby,
one day you might fall? ♪
♪ Yeah, and feel your back
against the wall? ♪
♪ Well, did you
ever dream, baby ♪
♪ one day you might crawl? ♪
Amanda, on answering machine:
what?!
It's dad.
Has anybody seen
my gold card?
♪ Strange to see you, baby ♪
♪ mmm, it's strange ♪
♪ very strange ♪
♪ 'cause you messed me up good ♪
♪ yes, you messed me ♪
♪ messed me up
really good ♪
♪ now didn't you, baby? ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ took me a long time ♪
♪ to get back here ♪
♪ and i swear i didn't mean
to rule you ♪
♪ i swear i didn't mean
♪ how do you mend what
you didn't mean to do? ♪
♪ 'Cause i swear
i didn't mean ♪
♪ i swear i didn't mean ♪
♪ i swear i didn't,
i swear i didn't mean to ♪
♪ swear i didn't mean
to rule you ♪
♪ i swear ♪
♪ but you messed me up ♪
♪ you know that you
messed me up good ♪
♪ you know ♪
♪ you messed me up good ♪
♪ yes, you did ♪
♪ yes, you did now, baby ♪
♪ 'cause i'm looking
at you now ♪
♪ and you are paying now ♪
♪ yes, you are now ♪
♪ i swear ♪
♪ and you never dreamed that ♪
♪ you never dreamed that ♪
♪ no, you never
dreamed that ♪
♪ but you're paying now ♪
♪ ooh ♪
♪ mm-hmm ♪
♪ you never dreamed that ♪
♪ i'm looking
right at you now ♪
captioning made possible by
lions gate entertainment
captioned by the national captioning institute --www.ncicap.org--