♪ Opening Song
So, what's this one called?
You know, I'm not sure.
Any suggestions?
Wow, this one actually
smells really good.
Gee, thanks.
Well, you did have the one
that smelled like fish.
There wasn't even any
fish in it.
You guys trying out lotions?
Mmm hmm.
Don't make Margarett
throw up again.
No, this one actually
smells really good.
Mmm, that's actually better than the pineapple one you had a while ago.
See, I'm improving.
Did you take your
medicine today?
- Yes.
I already have one mom.
Girls, your father's here
with the cake.
[All] CAKE!
I can't believe I
finally finished.
I know it's about time.
Hey we can't all graduate
in four years.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Oh, John's here!
Elinor?
Yeah?
I heard the Porter account
came through.
Yes, just yesterday.
Good job. That's a
huge client for us.
Thank you. I know.
- John, welcome
- Hi.
So what do you think?
You're in the presence of a remarkable woman.
Poised to take on the
world of... um?
English.
After all those semesters
that's what you ended up with.
Dad!
[LAUGHTER]
Just kidding.
That's not funny.
Well, I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
Mmhm. Thank you.
John when do you leave
for Switzerland?
Uh, in a few months. The
beginning of next fall.
Thanks again for opening the
door for me with that company.
Happy to.
So far away, though.
What are you going to do without Marianne?
Well, we won't be
apart for very long.
Um, this sounds like this is
getting really serious.
It is. Apparently the job that dad got him
is going to put him ahead like 10 years.
Wow!
I mean I'm gonna miss him but...
You never know what may happen before he leaves.
Well, take it slowly. I mean,
you don't know him that well.
Trust your heart. That's
what I always say.
Oh right 'cause the heart
is never wrong.
When did you get so practical?
Is it because you haven't had a boyfriend in two years?
Okay. I know for you that would
be like a biblical drought.
How many boyfriends have you
had in the last two years?
It's not about quantity,
it's about quality.
Well, at least we agree on that.
Mmm hmm
[doorbell rings]
Oh, I'll get it.
Hi. Can I help you?
Special Agent Wayne.
Is Henry Dashwood here?
Uh, is there a problem?
Elinor.
Henry Dashwood we have a
warrant for your arrest.
What?
You have to come with us now.
Daddy.
It will be okay.
Daddy. What's happening?
Call our attorney!
Henry?
Dad?
You have the right
to remain silent.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Your husband is accused of fraud.
What's commonly known as a ponzi scheme.
What does that mean?
Well, basically it's when a person takes an investor's money,
promises a big return
and is paid with other
investors' money,
but in reality most of the
money is pocketed illegally
by whoever is running
the scheme.
My husband would never do that.
Well, I will defend the best I can but the government's case...
If they win Mr. Dashwood would
owe a lot of money.
The authorities have a list of
a couple hundred investors.
So, what comes next?
Well, they have a search warrant to search your
home and they'll take any evidence with them.
The government will also seize
any valuables such as cars,
art, jewelry, any and all
assets in Henry's name.
His accounts have already been frozen,
so there will be no access to any of his money.
But what about the house?
What about my home?
Well, remember he hasn't
been convicted.
If Henry is found guilty they'll
most likely auction it off,
but for the time being
they'll put a lien on it.
Do you think he's guilty?
Well, what I think is irrelevant,
but the authorities seem to be building a good case.
I'll do everything I can.
So, what's the worst
case scenario?
If convicted, major prison time.
[REPORTERS AND CROWDS
TALKING]
The family seems subdued today for the sentencing of Henry Dashwood.
Convicted of securities fraud, money laundering,
and several other federal charges,
Dashwood was sentenced to a
maximum 75 years in prison.
Mom.. Please turn that off. We
have enough to worry about.
But your father, we have
to appeal this.
We don't have any money.
If dad hadn't prepaid our rent then
Marianne and I would be out in the street.
I cannot believe he did this.
I know, but there's
evidence that he did.
Guess what? We made the front
page of the tabloids.
Oh as if that's something
to be proud of.
Uh, I look pale.
Oh please, we're famous.
No, stop it. You guys throw that out.
You know those papers exaggerate.
What are we going to do?
Marianne and I are going to get jobs
and we're going to pay our own way.
We are?
Yes.
Well, what about Margarett?
Her medicine is more than $3000 a month.
Plus doctor visits. Before that
was nothing, but now?
Okay but don't we have
health insurance?
That's with health insurance.
We've lost everything. I am not
going to lose Margarett too.
No, mom, we will get her
enough of the medicine.
I mean, do you think we
can make enough?
Well, your aunt Charlotte has offered a place for me to stay,
and so if I work in her shop,
I may be able to bring in a
third of what we need.
Okay. Alright.
Well, Marianne and I will just make up the rest.
I mean all we need are jobs.
Yeah, this looks promising.
Hi, I am calling about
the job listing.
Okay, thank you.
It's already been filled.
Ohhh.
♪♪♪
Yes, I will see you in Paris.
Thank you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No problem.
Name is Dashwood, correct?
Oh please, call me Elinor.
Dashwood, where have I heard
that name before?
I'm concerned your work experience is
insufficient for the required qualifications.
Um, but I have worked
extensively with-
Good luck to you.
Hi! I'm calling about the
executive assistant position.
Okay, thanks.
Elinor...
I'm sorry to waste your time but we have decided to hire from within.
Yeah, hi. Is the clerical job
still available?
Work experience?
Um, none. [Chuckle]
Dashwood.
Hmm, I, I don't know if you're
the best suited for this job.
But you haven't asked me
a single question.
I just,
I don't think you fit into the culture we have here at the office.
Sorry.
Hey.
Uhh... You calling about a job?
[Phone voice] If you're calling about the file clerk job,
it has been filled.
For all other inquiries
please press 0.
Uhh, and the ones that aren't filled,
you need more work experience.
This is way harder
than I thought.
If it makes you feel any better,
having work experience doesn't help either.
Everybody takes one look at Dashwood
Investments and promptly kicks me out the door.
I'm sorry.
I mean there are jobs out there.
They're just not quite as
glamorous as I'd hoped.
Okay, this is a job. This is a job.
This is a job. I am getting paid for this job.
I'm dancing with my banana.
Helloo.
[From Car] Hey nice coconuts.
Oh, thank you sir, thank you.
Oh my goodness.
Hello, it's my money time.
Hello.
AAAHHH! AAAHHH! OHHHH NOOOOO!
Ugh, who knew this
would be so hard?
That costume stunk, too.
I can't believe you got fired.
I know.
How was I supposed to know that the sprinklers were going to go off
and that the suit couldn't get
wet. I didn't know.
Well that's why it smelled.
It's never been washed.
[Sigh] Can it get any worse?
I don't think so.
I just got fired from a job where I wore a gigantic gorilla costume
and waved a banana at
cars passing by.
I... [laughing]
Just wait here a moment
Okay.
I don't think she's for us.
Why not?
Recognize her?
Uh, so. She's cleaning. How
hard is that?
I don't want the customers to be uncomfortable
thinking that she might steal from them.
She'll be out of sight and she's got to be pretty desperate.
Alright. We'll give her a chance,
but you keep your eye on her.
Hi.
Hi. Any luck?
I don't know if you call it
luck but I got a job.
I am now the new custodial technician at the spa on Main Street.
Custodial Technician?
[Clears throat] Janitor.
Sounds lovely.
Yeah, but I think it's going to be enough to cover our expenses.
I'm just worried about
Margarett's medicine.
Well, my options were fast food, which pays nothing,
or a grocery bagger that pays even less.
I was really starting to give up,
but I checked the internet one more time
and you are now looking at the new copy assistant to a marketing firm.
You're kidding! That's
amazing. How did you do that?
Well, I think you'd
do great here.
Can you start Monday, Ms. Webb?
I think he thought I was cute.
Wait, so are there any other
jobs available?
No, but um, I should be
bringing in enough to cover us.
Okay, well, we still
need to be frugal.
Yeah, how am I going
to get to work?
Ugh, the bus is stinky and always running late.
We need a car.
Well, I could actually walk to the spa from here,
but a car would come in handy.
I'll start looking for
something cheap.
Something nice.
Of course.
Alright, well, I gotta get ready
I'm going to dinner with John.
John? I haven't heard
about him in a while.
I think he was worried about
the job that dad got him,
but he sounded happy so it must
still be going through.
Good. Have fun.
Thanks!
Ai yie yie. How are we going to
be able to afford a car?
Have you heard from
your dad recently?
Um, my mom's talked to him.
She fills us in.
Hmm.
It's been really hard
on everybody.
I mean my poor mom she just
didn't see that coming at all.
She could really use some good
news right about now.
Well, I have some.
Really?
The Switzerland job.
I thought they were going to dump me after your dad was arrested,
but they're flying me out
to start the job.
That's great!
Yeah, I'm going out there to get trained,
start workin', and I will get to explore Switzerland.
So, when do you leave?
This week.
Ohh, and any idea on when
you're going to return?
I don't know. I mean, no exact dates yet,
but the plan is to get started,
and then transfer me to one
of the offices here in the US.
Oh, good.
Hey, I'll miss you.
I'll miss you, too.
I'll call you every day.
[Sigh]
Guess what? I got us a car,
actually it's a truck.
What happened to our TV?
Yes, I had to pay for the
truck, somehow.
Listen, it's not what we're used to, but,
it's going to get us from a to b.
Come look, come. You're gonna
love this. Come on.
Well, it can get us from point a to point b,
but can it get us back to point a?
My friend gave me a great deal 'cause her dad doesn't need it anymore.
[Sigh] I already miss
the flat screen.
No, need. I got us a
replacement.
This keeps getting
better and better.
Doesn't it? So what happened on
your date last night?
Nothing. Well, something. The
job came through in Switzerland.
Oh good.
He leaves right away.
Oh bad.
Well, do you wanna take
it for a spin?
Honestly, no.
Yeah.
All right so here's where we
keep all of the fresh linens.
We have sheets here, towels here.
Everything's organized by size
so it's face, hand, and body.
Got it.
Um so, each customer's going to get a set in
their locker when they come in and so you
need to refill the lockers
as each customer leaves.
Also, put extra towels
in each treatment room.
Okay, I think I can handle that.
Okay good, ummm and
your uniform.
Uniform?
Yeah.
Great.
How's the work going?
Oh, it's fine.
Uh, the bathrooms need a deep cleaning so you
can stay late one night this week and do that.
No problem.
I'm Hannah the office manager.
I'm not going to sugar coat it.
You've got a lot of work ahead
of you.
We come up with marketing campaigns for tons of accounts.
People will come to you throughout the day with presentations, contracts,
whatever to copy. And this will
be your domain.
Good luck with the machines,
but don't sweat it if you go through a few reams of paper
trying to figure it out.
Just be sure to log in the copy job with what client it goes for.
That way we can bill them.
Okay.
Big talker aren't ya?
Well, I was just wondering...
I'm at extension 377 if
you get in a panic.
Hi!
Oh, you're new here aren't you?
Yes.
I hope you can do this. I need 50 copies collated,
3 whole punched and bound.
Okay, don't use those coil things.
Brads or brackets will be fine. I will be back in a half an hour.
Okay.
Brads, brackets.
[Sigh]
This goes there.
Uh, yeah, well that was easy.
Ugh, Come on. What did I do?
What is with you?
Don't stress. It's just a jam.
Thank you.
I'm Brandon. You must be the
new copy girl.
Yes, Marianne Da--,
Marianne um Webb.
I just need a copy
Okay, um.
I got it.
Wow, that was... easy.
I think the user manual's
on that shelf.
Really? Thank you!
Good luck.
Hey.
My hands are killing me.
Mmm, I'm sorry.
Mmm hmm.
Oh, you wanna use some of my
lotion?
Yeah, thanks.
Mmmm, I forgot how good this
one smells.
Hey I've come a long way.
Remember when I used to make those concoctions out of clovers?
[Laughing] Oh yeah, how could I
forget that?
Wow this already makes my hands
feel better.
Really?
Yeah, I'm not even just sayin'
that to be nice.
Can I keep this bottle?
Yeah, go for it.
How was your day?
It was stressful.
I mean who would have thought making copies could be so difficult?
What are you watching?
I have no idea. The reception
on this thing is terrible.
Well with all that tinfoil on the antenna I bet
you we could pick up a talk show from Mars.
[LAUGHTER]
We good? Okay.
Hey. I was just looking for you.
Oh.
Um, can you put together five packets from the file on this drive?
Oh. Uh, okay, when do you
need it by?
Um, after lunch. Is that
enough time?
Sure.
Great.
Be careful dear.
My arthritis is acting up so my feet are awfully tender.
Oh, ok.
Uh, excuse me. Sorry I couldn't
help but overhear. Try this.
What is it?
It's a lotion my sister makes.
Okay.
Ohhh that scent. What
is that ambrosia?
Uh, I don't know. It's fruit,
flowers, I'm not sure.
Mmm. Very refreshing. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay. Let's see.
Alright. Okay.
Print to copier. Huh.
Uh, I T apostrophe S.
It's a contraction.
[PHONE RINGS]
Yeah, no, that is the amount.
Okay, bye.
Hey, Hannah, um, I noticed a
type-o on one of the copies.
Print it anyway.
Are you sure? It's
pretty obvious.
Our people know what they are doing.
It might be a play on words.
Yeah, I'm just going to ask
Brandon. Double check.
It's for Brandon? Definitely.
Just print it. He's senior management.
I'm just trying to help.
I know you think you are but
your job is simple:
copy, staple, hole punch.
Don't overstep.
Ooohhh, my feet.
Was there something wrong
with your pedicure?
Oh no. I feel like
I'm 20 again.
This dear girl gave me some lotion.
It's really easing the pain.
Oh? Well, that's good.
Do you know where I could find her?
The girl who was gathering the towels.
That girl?
Oh miss, miss.
Oh hi. How are your feet?
Oh, they feel better then
they have in years.
I'm wondering if you have any
more of that magic lotion?
Oh and Betty,
she has terrible backaches because of her mattress
and her husband's too
cheap to replace it.
He always says what's not broke don't fix it,
but he's just a tight wad.
I think this lotion is just
what she needs.
But I, I don't make it my
sister does but-
Oh honey to feel like this,
I am willing to pay for her time and ingredients.
You talk to your sister and let
me know next week.
Okay, I will. Thank you.
Okay.
Sorry.
Just don't let it interfere
with your work.
Got it.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Saving money.
Are you washing those?
Hey, whatever cuts costs.
Alright, alright.
So, mom called.
Oh, how is she doing?
She's been better. She is gonna
send Margarett to visit us.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I think so.
I think she's just having a hard time at school, just kids.
Poor thing. Like she doesn't
have enough to worry about.
Yeah.
Where you goin'?
Oh, I'm gonna go back to the spa.
I'm gonna pick up some extra hours, so don't wait up.
I won't.
Oh hey, uh, can I get a couple
more bottles of that lotion?
I just gave you a full bottle.
I know but there's this customer there who loves it.
She wants to buy some.
Really? Okay.
Okay.
Bye.
Yeah, I'm here.
Yes, I'll get it. Okay.
[Singing] I've been workin' in
the bathroom all the...
[light distant singing]
...bathroom just to make the tiles shine white,
ba boom ba boom ba boom.
Can't you hear my alarm clock goin' off.
It's gonna go off so early in the morn..
Wuh wuh wuh. Can't you hear Fran sayin',
please Elinor scrub the floor!
Elinor clean the floor. What?
Elinor clean the floor. Who? Elinor clean the floor.
Please clean. OH MY GOSH!
Uh, it's okay. I'm a lawyer.
How, how does the fact that you are a lawyer make me feel better?
I just stopped by to pick up
some stuff from Fran's office.
Oh.
And you are?
Yeah, I'm the uh new custodian.
I didn't think there was anyone here.
It's okay. It's not everyday I
get a live concert.
Yes, yes well you know I was just trying to prepare for my,
my career in reality television.
Mmm hmm.
Yeah, I thought I would start with uh
singing and then I would move onto dance
and then you know the survival
one I wanted to try and and
maybe the one where I can choose
my own husband would be good.
I'd vote for ya. Elinor?
Uh yeah.
Um I should go back to work here.
I'm trying to impress my boss.
I could put in a good
word for ya.
Oh no no that's okay.
I'm, I need to earn my reputation.
Um, hey maybe we could keep the
singing thing between just you and me.
Yeah, of course.
Um but only until you're on TV 'cause after that I make no promises.
Ooohhh that was awesome.
Fran?
In here.
My sister cooking.
I took a look at everything.
What do you think?
I think you have to make
some decisions.
The spa can only bring in so
much. You owe a lot of money.
Yes, thank you for stating
the obvious.
I don't suppose anybody
owes you money?
I did loan Lucy a twenty.
How did you get into
so much debt?
Oh you know start up costs,
bills, blaahh.
Maybe it's time to give it up.
Shut down the spa? No.
You could move. Maybe some place cheaper.
Change your lifestyle.
Not an option.
Fran! I'm just trying to help.
You're losing more money
every month.
Getting second, third,
fourth notices of default on your loans.
What if I got another loan to
float the others?
That's just gonna
make it worse.
I mean how long before they threaten to take everything away?
[Sigh] Have they already
threatened that?
I'll figure something out.
Fine.
Oh, hey I was surprised to find someone working so late at the spa.
She was cleaning the
locker room.
Oh, that's Elinor. She didn't
give you any trouble did she?
No, not at all. She been
working for you long?
No, our janitor just quit. Why
all the interest?
Not interest, curiosity.
Her father is that fraud,
Dashwood.
Ugh, I mean she's just a janitor so I
agreed to let her work for me but, woo.
How gracious of you.
Go go get on the left I got the guy on the right.
Shoot, shoot. Oh yeah!
[Cell phone rings]
Guys, hold on a second.
[Clears throat] Hi.
Hi. I didn't wake you, did I?
What time is it there?
Uh, it's it's ten.
Ten? I thought you guys were
nine hours ahead.
Yeah, uh, I must have set
my watch wrong.
[Sigh] You poor thing.
So, how's it going?
Good. It's good.
Everything's very Swiss.
How so?
Uh, there's holey cheese
everywhere and, uh, yeah
it tastes a lot better than
the stuff we have here, there.
And, um, how's work going?
It's great.
It's great but it uh would be a lot better if we were together.
Well, you better hurry up and impress them so you can come home.
I'll do my best. Uh look I
gotta go can I call you later?
All right. I miss you.
All right, you too.
All right guys I'm back.
Ah, come on.
[Sigh]
You completely embarrassed me.
What?
There's an error in this.
I presented this last night to our CEO
and a client that would have been worth
five million dollars to this company.
I was just told to copy it.
Typical. Just do the bare minimum, right?
Just enough to get by. Never thinking.
I saw the mistake. I took it to my boss and she
told me that you would know what you're doing.
Wait, you saw this and
you let it go?
Well, why didn't you see it.
Had I seen it, I would
have fixed it!
Don't blame me because you
don't take pride in your work.
You know this is what I get.
This is what I get for expecting a copy girl to understand.
[Sigh]
Just go ahead and have a seat,
your pedicurist will be right with you.
Oh thank you.
Oh Elinor, uh, wash the bowl
first and then the step.
Thank you.
Anything to make you go faster.
Excuse me.
Yes, ma'am?
No, I meant her. Are you the one
that makes that special lotion?
Oh yeah, that's me. Well, it's
actually my sister.
Oh, Mrs. Jennings could not
stop talking about it.
She's the biggest gossip,
but when I heard I figured I need to try some.
Do you have a bottle I can buy?
I do. I do, you know it's
actually for Mrs. Jennings,
but I don't think she comes in
until the end of this week.
Oh, I'd love it.
Okay, I'll go get you one.
Thank you.
Anything wrong?
Elinor's selling lotion.
Yeah, a customer came in
earlier asking about that today.
Let me know if any other
people are looking for it?
Are you going to stop
her from selling it?
No. Not yet.
Well if it isn't
the midnight idol.
Oh yes, just one of my
many secret identities.
Mind if I sit?
No, please.
You on a break from work?
Yeah, the brownies
here are amazing.
[Laugh] I've never tried 'em.
We weren't properly introduced
the other night, Edward Farris.
Elinor Dashwood. Farris? You're
not by any chance related to-
Yeah, Fran is my sister.
Oohh.
Yeah, don't fault me for that.
Well, I won't hold your relatives against
you if you don't hold mine against me.
Oh, that's right. The
investment guy.
Yeah.
So, what're you doing?
I'm, um, I'm actually trying to
make ends meet.
Looks intense.
Yeah, it's amazing the things
you just can't do without.
Like that brownie.
And groceries, and medicine.
Medicine?
Um, not for me, for
my little sister.
Oh, what's wrong with her?
Um, she has a type of leukemia.
It's treatable but the medicine is really expensive.
Yeah, money's heartless that
way. You know take us lawyers.
Without a good one your life
could be destroyed.
Lawyers and doctors. What kind
of law do you practice?
Patent law, mostly with
corporations and stuff.
Ahh.
Yeah, that doesn't make me any
more likeable does it?
Well, I'll see if I can maybe
overlook it.
Good.
Hey.
Hey, dinner's almost ready.
Macaroni and cheese?
It's a budget meal.
Elinor, you and your
budget meals.
Are you okay?
Yeah I just, uh, I had a bad
day at work.
Already?
Mmm hmm. I don't really want to
talk about it though.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I just left John this whole long voicemail about it so.
Okay, so I've been going over
our budget...
Ugh.
No, it's good news and bad news,
but the good news is we have enough to cover our expenses.
The bad news is we're way short
on Margarett's.
Do we really need to talk about
this right now?
I have an idea.
[Sigh] Okay what?
Your lotion.
What about it?
It does something to people and
the smell is amazing.
So, I don't know if it's the scent that just
makes people feel better or if there's
actually something in the lotion,
but those bottles you gave me the other day,
they're gone and not to the
people they were intended for.
Really?
Do you think we can make more?
Yeah, sure. I, um, just gonna
need some extra ingredients.
Let's see calendula, and
passion flowers, cream, fruit.
You should buy it in bulk.
Are you feeling okay?
Yes.
[Laugh] Okay, are you sure that
we can make this back?
I mean, I'm gonna raise the
price so yeah.
I get to go shopping!
Just for the ingredients.
Okay, all right. I'm on it.
Kay!
You can have the mac and
cheese without me.
Thanks.
Hi.
Um, I came by to apologize.
I was upset yesterday,
obviously,
but even without the typo my proposal wasn't what the client wanted.
But, what you said about me not taking pride in my work,
you're wrong.
I do take pride in my work, I
take too much actually.
That's why, uh,
that's why this is a little hard for me to swallow.
Okay.
Hmm. Thanks for your
understanding.
[Sigh]
Here you go.
Ooh, I can't tell you how
excited I am about this.
Well, good. I hope you enjoy it.
Oh I will and I've been telling
everybody about it.
I'd buy them all a bottle but
nobody ever pays me back.
Oohh.
Uh, it's wonderful. Have you
smelled this?
That is good. What is that?
Lilac?
Uh, I don't know flowers, and
this and that.
Well, I am off ladies. Goodbye.
Goodnight.
I have never seen
her that happy.
Good. So listen I am taking off.
There's a bunch of towels in the dryer.
They're going to be done in like 45 minutes
and I'm gonna fold them tomorrow morning.
Okay, great.
Edward!
Hey.
How are you?
Starving. Have you eaten?
No.
Of course not you just got off
work. Do you want to join me?
Yeah, that'd be great.
Awesome.
Thanks.
Of course.
I am not ignoring the letters.
I understand that you can take everything.
[Creditor on phone] That's what will happen if you
don't make a payment by the end of the month.
I-
Thank you.
Edward didn't come inside?
Apparently not. He just
picked up Elinor.
I need you to get something
out of Elinor's locker.
What?
A bottle of that lotion.
You want me to break
into her locker?
Yes, is that a problem?
No, [sigh] she just sold some today, though,
so I don't think she has any left.
Well, then you wait until
she brings some more in
and then she won't notice
there's any missing.
Okay, but you have to set
me up with Edward.
Done.
Yeah, this probably isn't what you had in mind when I mentioned dinner.
No, this is perfect. Thank you.
My pleasure.
I didn't think a place like
this was your style.
Well, I wasn't always a lawyer. This is, uh,
kind of reminds me of growing up.
Growing up I went to garden
parties and golf tournaments,
but this feels more real.
I like it.
Good, 'cause ladies first.
Uh-oh.
Yeah.
I don't think this is going
to go very well.
Well, we'll see.
Kay, uh uh uh.
Mmm hmm., interesting.
Oohh, that wasn't-
All right.
- Great was it?
Um, no no.
All right let me show you a
better way okay?
Yep.
Okay, step up to the line.
Okay.
Hold the ball about here.
Yes.
And then as you let the ball come back step forward and then release.
I mean isn't that what I did
basically?
Uh no.
[Laughing]
So aside from being new to
bowling, tell me about yourself.
Oh, you don't really want to hear about
the investment manager turned custodian.
No, no. Skip the
dirty laundry.
I don't know if it's that easy.
You know we get a lot of letters from
investors, angry, distraught, letters.
It was a lot of money.
Sometimes I hate my dad for
what he did but I love him.
Sounds confusing.
[Laughing] Yeah, sometimes I wish I could go back in time.
My life was nearly perfect.
Nearly?
You had garden parties.
[Laughing]
Woo! That was amazing.
Yeah, that was okay.
Then again, you know, if
nothing every changed I'd still
unknowingly be helping my dad
steal from people,
and I would never have
learned how to bowl.
Speaking of, your turn.
Look out.
I'll be watching.
'Kay.
All right.
Oh oh oh.
Good form, good.
Thank you.
Mmm hmm.
Don't talk, you'll mess me up.
Okay. Huh.
Ugh.
Ohhhh.
[Laughs].
All right.
Yeah.
Um, can I help?
Yes.
'Kay.
All right hold this.
Put your fingers in there.
Done.
Good. Okay step up to
the line here.
This line?
Yes, very good. So you want to
center up on that. Good.
'Kay, and then hold the ball up
to about where your chin is
and then step forward as you
bring the ball back.
I'm scared.
Good. Now you're all right just
don't drop it on my foot.
Aaahhh!
[Laughing]
Oh, you did it!
OH!
Wow.
Thank you for your help.
Anytime.
[Phone rings]
Oh.
Um, it's my phone
Mmm.
Hello. Right now?
No that's fine. Totally, of
course. Okay bye.
You okay?
Yeah, um, my sister is
visiting. Tonight.
Oh, uh, I'll take you home.
Is that okay?
Yeah, yeah.
This was really fun though.
Yeah, no, um, I'll
tell you what.
Promise me a re-match to show off what
you've learned and we'll call it even.
It's a deal.
Hi!
Hey.
Margarett is going
to sleep over.
Fun!
Yeah, we are hard at work making
some more Soothing Scents.
Ooh, I wanna scrub in.
Okay, water's boiling so we cannot skip this very important step.
So, why do you have to boil it?
Oh trust me you want to,
otherwise, your skin itches.
So, what are you guys making?
We're trying something new.
It's called 'Elinor's Love Potion Lotion'.
Designed to do what?
Oh, get you a date.
Okay. I was just on a date, I
think, when you called.
[At same time] Seriously? You
think?
Well, details.
There aren't any details yet.
Maybe on the next date.
I said I would take the couch.
She had so much fun tonight.
You wanna know what she asked
me while you were gone?
What?
She wanted to know if dad stole all that money
to help pay for the medical bills and medicine.
Dad siphoned away more money then we
could ever need for medicine or anything else.
I know. That's what I told her.
[Sigh] We're gonna make it
through this. Marianne we are.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Uhh, it's John.
Okay.
Hi.
Hey, it's me.
I know.
I just wanted to call you and
wish you goodnight.
Oh, that's really sweet.
Hey, where are you? It
sounds kind of loud.
Uh, about to go in a meeting.
The conference room here overlooks these beautiful snowy mountains.
That sounds amazing. So, you
can't talk for too long?
No, I'm afraid not but I was just thinking about you
and had to talk to you before you went to sleep.
Well, I'm really glad you did.
Sweet dreams.
Sweet dreams whenever it's
night time in Switzerland.
Bye.
John, how are you man?
Starving.
Her name's Patrice.
Her father owns five restaurant chains across the country
and she's the one that
inherits them all.
I can't wait to meet her.
Hey, did you need something?
What? No.
Okay.
I was gonna go grab
an early lunch.
Good.
Do you wanna come?
Uh, sure.
Great.
You wanted to see me?
Yes, the toilet is backed up in the men's
locker room and I need you to deal with that
and quickly before any
clients notice.
Okay.
Also, the tub in the couple's
room needs to be scrubbed.
Check that drain for any clogs.
We have a client booked for treatment room 5
and she's allergic to all sorts of laundry soaps
so what you're going to have to do is take a set
of sheets and hand wash them with baking soda.
Use the scrub brush.
Be very thorough.
Okay.
Oh and our client scheduled for room 2 has requested satin sheets,
she'll be here at noon.
Okay.
♪
OH! Ugh
Uh.
Oh. OH OH! Whoo.
Oh no, did uh Fran say room 2
it's room 4.
Uh, if you hurry you can just make it before the client gets here though
and be sure to put the regular
sheets back on that bed.
[Sigh]
Excuse me.
Yeah. Can I help you?
Uh, I'm looking for a certain
lotion to buy.
Oh.
My aunt has been
talking about it.
Oh yeah, yeah. I'll get ya one.
Just one second.
Thank you.
Hey Big Al, the special please.
Um, I'll have one too.
I got it.
Oh, thank you.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Mmm. It's better than I thought.
So, do you come out here a lot?
To the park?
Mmm hmm.
A lot more relaxing than a
break room.
Mmm. Well it's all the flowers.
Do you know that there are 35 different kinds of flowers in this park?
Is that a lot?
Yeah, can you name even ten
different types of flowers?
Red roses.
Okay.
White roses.
Mmm hmm.
Yeah, I can't.
No you can't.
I can't.
Exactly. It's hard.
How did you know that?
Flowers are my thing.
So, what brought you to the
copy room and not a greenhouse?
I mean a girl like you seems like she could get a job anywhere.
I tried, but I don't really
have much work experience.
Now my sister, she could run
circles around me.
What does she do?
Um, she recently got downsized
so she works at a spa.
Well, if you like I could, you know, ask around HR,
see if there's any positions opened up.
That's okay. I think she's
warming up to it.
Edward, wow, um, what
brings you here?
Just visiting Elinor.
Really?
Yeah.
She's working.
Didn't you guys just close?
She does all the behind
the scenes things.
Besides, I think you could
do a lot better...
Edward?
Hey! Are you done working?
Yes.
Excellent. How does
Indian food sound?
Indian food how delicious. I'm
getting hungry myself. Lucy?
That sounds delicious. Yes.
'Kay, well I should probably get
going. It's been a long day.
Do, do you wanna ride?
No, I'm okay thanks.
Well, shall we?
Yeah.
What happened?
I don't know. It just died. It
barely made it home.
Now it won't start.
Okay, pop the hood.
Let me take a look.
Okay.
Is that it?
Yeah. I think so.
So, how was your day?
Ugh.
I don't know how much longer I can stay working at the spa.
Any jobs opened up at
your office?
No, not really. Hey I had lunch
with a coworker today.
Guy or girl?
Guy.
Oh, naturally my next
question is, is he cute?
Uh, I don't know I
mean, I guess.
Is he like John cute?
Huh, I don't know. Besides it
doesn't matter.
John and I are together and Brandon he's just like way too serious.
Oh, and the mature thing isn't
really for you.
Hey!
Ha ha ha [laughing] Okay try it
again. Let's see.
All right.
[CAR WON'T START]
Yep, no. I'm officially calling
it, time of death 6:13 p.m.
No, no. You know what, it just
needs maintenance.
We don't know the first thing
about repair.
Well then we're gonna learn...
and tomorrow we're gonna walk.
Mmm [groaning]
Ahh, isn't this cool crisp air
invigorating?
Yeah, it feels like a
glacial lake.
You know we wouldn't have to walk if you would've gotten a better car.
Hey, you know what?
Cars break down.
Yeah but sometimes when you spend less
money upfront it costs you more in the long run.
Wow, that's like the smartest
thing you've ever said.
Rude. So, uh how much lotion
have you sold?
Shhhh.
What?
You got a place...
In the Hamptons.
Yeah.
Oh, oh.
Is that John?
I didn't tell you but you look
beautiful today.
He's back?
I can't believe he did that to
you. He lied.
You know there was always something about him that bothered me.
Okay, Elinor I really don't want to talk about this right now.
Let's just go to our work.
He lied about Switzerland.
We don't know that.
Are you kidding?
It could be a misunderstanding.
That could be his cousin or something.
They looked really chummy
to be cousins.
You know this never would have happened if dad hadn't stolen money.
Please, don't make
this about dad.
It made John very uncomfortable.
It's been hard on him.
This has been really hard
on all of us.
When times get tough you see people's
true colors and now we've seen his.
You don't know that.
Stop defending him.
Are my copies ready?
Oh, yep. There you go.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah, tough morning.
Um, I wanted to show you
something. Maybe after work?
What is it?
I can't tell you. I want to but I can't.
It's sort of a surprise.
Uh, okay.
Yeah?
Sure.
Done.
Good.
I will have this analyzed.
Figure out what's in it.
Why?
Mmm. I know somebody who would
be interested in buying this.
Something that heals would be worth tons and you keep quiet about it.
This could save you your job,
could save the spa.
You ready?
Still not gonna tell me where
we're going?
Nope.
So, um, how long have you been
with the company?
Five years? Yeah, five years.
Hmm, and family?
Out of state.
Pets?
None, but I did have a
goldfish when I was a kid.
[Giggle]
Girlfriend?
Uh, no. I was engaged
once years ago.
We were probably too young,
but it felt right.
What happened?
Her family really wasn't into it.
Mine either come to think about it.
They sort of persuaded us
to, uh, call it off.
Oh.
I think she went on to marry
some oil tycoon or something.
And what about you?
Did you move on?
Took me a while, but yes.
And here we are.
Wow, this is amazing.
So, can you tell me how many
flowers are in this park?
[Laughing] No.
Come on.
I'll show you my favorite and you can tell me what it actually is.
Hey!
Hi. Looks like you're in
a good mood?
Yeah, I had a really
good day today.
What about John?
Oh well I have found someone to
distract me, Brandon.
Oh, man I just bought all this ice cream thinking
you would be wallowing tonight over John.
He took me to the most
amazing garden.
Oh, a garden. Good thing I got
a flavor I like.
I mean he must like me right?
And John?
Jerk.
Huh.
Marianne.
Hey.
Thank you so much for taking me to the garden.
I had a really good time.
So did I. I was actually looking for you.
Do you wanna get some, uh, lunch?
I'm actually gonna get lunch
with my sister.
Hey, I thought we were
meeting at the cafe.
I was early, so, I thought
I'd come by.
Hi. Brandon Hurst.
Elinor Dashwood.
Dashwood? I thought your last
name was Webb?
Um. It's my uh mother's
maiden name.
No jobs open, either, huh?
Elinor! [Sigh]
Hey.
Must be so nice. Having a good job with people
around you who don't care what your name is.
I didn't want all the questions.
Uh, I probably wouldn't have
gotten the job if I hadn't-
Lied to them. To Brandon,
to me.
I just, I just had no idea how
selfish you are.
Selfish?
I have been doing pretty well considering we don't have,
I don't know, a TV, a car.
I haven't complained once!
All you do is complain and while you've
been wallowing in your own self pity
I have been trying to
make this work!
Do you think it was easy going around from interview to interview
with each person judging me and
laughing me out the door?
Okay so that's why I did what I did so
the same thing wouldn't happen to me.
No, what you did was worse.
You told me there were no jobs available at your office.
I have been scrubbing toilets
and cleaning out clogged drains
with Fran watching over my
shoulder.
Do you know how much more money we
could have made if I had a better job?
You're assuming they'd even
hire you.
Uh, yeah I am.
Then again I also assumed that
you cared about Margarett.
[Doorbell rings]
Hey.
You okay?
Dashwood?
Yep.
It fits you better.
So you're not upset?
I know you. Your name doesn't
change anything.
Well it does to a lot of
people.
Well not me.
Are you and Elinor going to be
okay?
I hope so.
Gotta make you feel better.
Sweet, thank you.
All right, I have to ask.
What is all this?
Well, you know my obsession
with flowers?
Mmhm.
This is what I do with them.
You destroy them?
No, I make scented lotion.
Here do you want to try?
Sure.
Put some petals right there and just go
ahead and start mixing them around.
One more for you. But in a
circular motion.
Really?
And you'll start to see some oils and then you
just keep on going until all the pieces are gone.
Smells planty.
You need to mix some more
things in it.
Ow!
Oh.
Ow.
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Oohh.
I'm fine. I'm fine. Yeah.
Well, that is not going to
help, here.
Let's try this.
Right there?
Yeah.
How's that feel?
Better.
What do you mean it doesn't
work? I tried the lotion myself.
[From Phone] It causes an itchy
rash
An itchy rash? Well then, you got the ingredients wrong.
Did you double check the analysis?
[From Phone] Yes we did. We
triple checked it.
Well then, then there's got to be something in the process.
Uh, uh try some variations.
[From Phone] Okay extra costs
will be incurred.
I am paying you plenty for
this.
[From Phone] The time and
resources cost money.
Okay, okay.
[From Phone] Good.
Fine
Fine!
It's Fran Farris.
Well, that wasn't a very nice
thing to say John.
I need you to do
something for me.
I don't care what you're
in the middle of.
You do this for me and I will conveniently forget about Eliza Williams.
Rumor has it that if your family were to find
out about her that you would be disinherited.
You understand?
Good.
You need any help?
[Sigh]
I'm really sorry. I shouldn't
have lied.
You hand me that pan?
All right.
Okay, just put it under the
engine.
Do you want me to climb under
there? Okay, okay!
I've been through worse things
at the spa.
I'm going.
Okay.
All right, pan's in place.
All right, here we go.
Aahh!
What happened?
Oohh. Oh no. Oh no.
Don't laugh.
[Laughing] Oh no!
It's not funny.
Yes, it's very funny.
Hand me that towel
A clean towel.
Okay a clean towel. [Laughing]
Ughhhh.
Everything okay?
Yeah, it's peachy.
What's wrong with the truck?
Um, I don't know.
It won't start so I tried changing the oil but it didn't work.
Do you mind if I take a look?
No, oh please yes.
So, how's work going
by the way.
Work is fine, most days.
I did have to scrub a pair of
sheets by hand the other day.
Ew, you're kidding me.
I wish.
And, uh, my sister?
Your sister's good. She's fine.
Huh, you're holding back.
Um, I uh,
I get the feeling that she doesn't approve of me or something.
I don't know how much longer
I'm gonna be working there.
Yeah my sister can be a little
judgmental sometimes.
Sometimes?
Okay, give it a shot.
Okay.
[Car Starts]
How'd you do that?
Hm, it wasn't the oil.
I watch a lot of car shows.
Trust me Dillan, once we get the bugs worked out
this is going to be very lucrative for both of us.
I think your company's going to
be blown away by the potential.
[From Phone] You realize that going to bat for this puts me at risk, Fran.
You mess this up my reputation
suffers.
Oh, you won't be disappointed.
Neither will your company.
[From Phone] When can I expect this to be fixed?
My people are asking about it.
I have my entire team working
on it as we speak.
Surprise, I'm back! What are
you not excited to see me?
Oh oh are you talking to me or the blonde
girl you were holding hands with in the park
while you were supposed to be
in Switzerland?
Uh, look it's not what you
think. She's just a friend.
Oh, that looked like more than a friendship and that
still doesn't explain what you're even doing here.
I know it looks bad,
but after your dad was arrested I was tainted.
The job in Switzerland fell
through.
You said it was still going.
I know. I didn't know what
else to do.
Maybe not lie.
And I was afraid that being with you would make it even harder for me.
Because I'm a Dashwood?
Stupid, I know.
Who is she?
Crystal? It's just someone to talk to.
It meant nothing, honestly.
Look I made a mistake. Can't we
just start over?
I don't think I'm every going
to be able to trust you again.
Let me make it up to you.
By the way, how's the uh hobby
going?
It's good.
Well you should show me how you do it.
I love to watch you work.
You've never cared before.
I do now.
Maybe some other time, not
tonight.
Later then.
Just the two of us cooking up
flowers.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hey John. Yes, I got them.
They're beautiful.
Yeah, I miss you too.
That was a fun date.
Tonight?
Um, hmm, well what time?
You know I'm actually still at work so do
do you mind if I just call you when I leave?
Okay, bye.
Hey Lucy, um, listen I just noticed that there was
a little bit of damage to the lock on my locker.
I was wondering if you knew
what happened?
Why would I know that?
Oh no, I don't know.
I mean I...
You know what I wouldn't worry about it it's just that, um,
I think I'm missing something.
You think?
I'm pretty sure.
It's nothing huge I just I thought I should mention it.
Well, if it's nothing huge
don't bother me with it then.
You shouldn't even be selling
those bottles anyway.
I didn't tell you that that's
what's missing.
Oh.
Lucy did you have something to
do with this?
Uh okay, it wasn't even for
me.
It was for, it was for Edward.
Edward asked me to take it.
Why would he do that?
Um, he wanted it to sell to
some cosmetics company.
A cosmetics company?
Yeah, he says it's worth a
fortune. Men, huh?
Uh!
Oh! Sorry.
Watch it.
Sorry.
Elinor you really need to maintain a much more professional appearance.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Um, Lucy was just telling me about she and Edward, um...
Elinor.
You didn't really think that Edward was hanging
around you for your personality did you?
[Sad sigh]
Brandon, hey. How was your day?
I've had better.
I'm sorry. Hey you wanna, uh, come over?
Elinor's making chicken cordon bleu.
Thank you, but um,
I think it's best if we just kept this professional.
[MARIANNE'S PHONE RINGS]
Hey. I was just calling you.
What's up?
The lotion. Edward stole a bottle,
actually he got Lucy to do it.
What? Why?
To sell it to some big company.
But that's my lotion. How do we
stop them?
Well I don't think we can.
It's not protected by a patent or anything.
Uh, a patent?
Yeah, Edward's a patent attorney.
I can't believe I didn't see this coming.
We were just getting started.
Well, can't we get our own
lawyer?
Well what lawyer can we
possibly afford?
Brandon blew me off today.
Yeah John lies, Edward steals,
and Brandon blows you off.
I thought he really liked me.
We're doomed.
Excuse me.
My romantic sensibilities refuse to accept that.
Mmm staunch denial. I like it.
What are we doing with our
lives?
I don't know.
I don't want to keep working at the spa but we need the money.
Just quit.
Yeah, I should get like a temporary job at the mall or something.
I'm just tired of us having to fight so hard to
get what we need only to be disappointed.
Things used to be so much
easier.
[From Computer] Taser smoke,
woo! Don't breathe this?
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Fran, yeah I'm working on it.
I just need a little more time.
We don't have more time.
I keep calling her. She's not
ready.
Everyone is just waiting on how to make this healing lotion work.
You have 24 hours or our deal
is off.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hey John.
Oh, uh, tonight, let's see um.
..
Yeah that sounds great.
Elinor, hey. I tried calling
you.
Yeah, I've been really busy.
Can I give you a lift home?
No, I'm good.
How can you trust John?
He called and apologized.
I think it's worth another chance.
He lied to you and pretended to
leave the country.
It's not like I have very many options now that Brandon's blown me off.
You know you could go a week
without a boyfriend.
[Doorbell rings]
Come in!
I was just taking off.
Hi.
Thanks for letting me come
over. I missed you.
So, are we going to cook up
your little hobby?
I thought we were going to
dinner?
Sure, after this Okay?
Okay.
Here it is.
How was dinner?
Fine. So we're good now right?
You're not gonna say anything.
Yes, if the information on here is accurate then your secret is safe.
Edward? How are you?
Uh good. Is Elinor here?
Uh no I haven't seen her. You
free Friday?
Uh I'm busy. Thanks, though.
Fran.
Shhhh....
Yes? [Giggle]
You seem awfully excited.
New business deal coming
through.
Oh?
Um did you need something?
Yeah where's Elinor?
I don't know. She didn't show
up today.
It's unacceptable really but what can you expect from people like that?
Can I buy you a brownie?
Think a brownie can undo what
you've done?
Okay, you have to help me out
here.
Your scheme.
Stealing the formula for the lotion to sell off.
I haven't stolen anything.
Okay a technicality counselor,
you got Lucy to do it for you.
Lucy?
Oh, you can't even admit it.
Admit what?
You really don't know what I am
talking about?
No.
You didn't ask Lucy to steal a bottle of lotion from my locker?
She said you did.
Who did?
Lucy.
Okay you trusted Lucy?
And then Fran said that... I
don't know who to trust.
You can trust me.
Elinor, I would never do something to hurt you or your family.
You have to believe me.
I'm so sorry. I thought it was
you.
Don't be. I understand why
you'd be upset.
So wait. Did, did Lucy steal
it?
I don't know.
And if not for you then who?
Wait, what was this formula
to, a lotion?
Yeah it's that lotion that Marianne makes with the flowers.
Flowers? Fran.
Fran?
Yeah Fran.
She had something in her office instructions, ingredients.
Instructions? What was she
have..?
Wait a second.
Marianne was going to teach
John Willoughby.
I have to call Marianne.
Hi I...
How could you?
Calm down.
You stole it!
Don't be so naive. It's worth
a fortune.
It's wrong!
You're such an idealist. Don't you see?
This solves everything for me.
You actually think you're
right?
Well, it's not that black and
white Edward.
Give it back.
The formula? It's too late.
Fran.
I sold it. I'm just waiting
for payment to come in.
Don't you see? I took care of
everything.
Hey I got your message.
Ooh whoa.
Did you really think that I
wouldn't find out?
Look, look it's not what you
think.
Oh, okay so you didn't steal my lotion and sell it to Fran Farris?
Okay that part's right but I
had a reason.
Oh a reason. Wow, what a
relief.
Look Fran's been blackmailing
me. It's a tough situation.
Try me.
All right. I had a friend and
she got pregnant.
If my family found out it would
be a disaster for me.
For you? I cannot believe I
ever loved you.
You only care about yourself.
Hey now that's pretty hypocritical coming from you Marianne.
Well at least I am ashamed of
it.
It's not my fault. Fran made
me do it!
Oh please. Don't tell me you
didn't have a choice.
I didn't.
Look if your father hadn't been arrested everything would have been fine.
Until I found out that you lied
to us all.
Why didn't you just break up
with me?
Because, I love you.
[Laughs]
Let go! Get off of me!
Hey hey hey hey!
Stay out of this!
Just let her go man.
Fine.
Let's go Brandon.
Wait you know this guy? Who's
cheating now you little skank?
John and Fran tried to steal
the formula.
Tried.
They did steal it.
Fran's been drowning in debt.
She must have seen this as her way out.
So, what are you going to do?
I mean you can't let them get away with it.
Can't you call the police.
No, that won't amount to
anything.
This is a nightmare.
There is one thing we can do.
What?
We can beat Fran to it.
All right this pitch has to be perfect.
It's a long shot, but I'm hoping they'll listen to me.
And how do you know them?
They're one of our biggest
accounts.
Here you go.
Elinor?
Hmm?
Can you make a smaller version of that so I can give everyone a sample?
Yeah.
Great, and can you proof this?
Yes, definitely.
Your honor, yes,
I wanted to check and make sure a courier delivered a filing for my firm.
Great, well thank you very
much.
Sign here and here.
We ready?
Yeah.
Are we sure this is gonna work?
It will.
And what about Fran?
I'll take care of Fran.
This is a great deal for you.
Yes, you've mentioned that
once or twice.
Excuse us.
Uh, this is a private meeting.
Edward?
Sorry to interrupt but you should have
all the facts for your company's sake.
Facts?
This man is obviously in the
wrong room.
The formula Ms. Farris is
trying to sell you is stolen.
Which we can prove quite easily with Ms.
Dashwood's documentation.
How do we know this is
legitimate?
The proof is all there but in the meantime we've filed an injunction
against Ms. Farris that
prohibits this sale.
Edward are you sure this is
the right time to be...
Yes.
Definitely.
We'll need our team to get to
the bottom of this.
That's understandable.
We wouldn't want you to become victims of Ms. Farris' actions as well.
However we've presented this
lotion to another company
that has agreed to purchase the
formula.
But from us. It's rightful
owners.
I don't know where these people came from,
but there's clearly been some sort of mistake.
Edward?
I'm your sister.
And you should know better.
You completely swindled me you
know that?
But Dallin it's not my fault.
Our biggest competitor just applied for a patent on the lotion.
Our company lawyers are breathing
down my neck because of an injunction
they received about stolen
property!
It's not like that.
Our lawyers are going to sink their teeth so deep into your scheming hide
that not even your little
lotions will help heal you.
In case you haven't heard,
the lotion deal was finalized today.
You know the irony with this is that you were so mean
to Elinor thinking she was going to steal from you,
then you stole from her.
I guess I have to be careful now,
I don't want everyone to know that my sister's a thief.
Edward I...
By the way, Elinor quits.
I'm doing this all
wrong aren't I?
No you're, actually you are. Yeah wait,
let me show you. You have to move your wrist.
Um, you're actually still doing
it wrong.
Legally were not supposed to be making this
up anymore now that you sold the formula.
This is a new product.
Yeah. Brandon thinks we need to
develop more to sell off.
[Phone beeps÷}
Oh... Margarett says they got
the check.
Mom must be ecstatic.
You should be too. Margarett's
gonna be okay. You did it.
We all did it.
Hey will you hand me that
flower over there?
Yeah.
Oh no, not that one.
The other one.
Really?
Wait.
[CHEERS FROM PEOPLE]
Are you okay?
Yes, yes.
I was just thinking about how I'm going to miss her.
You're not wishing you could go back and change things are you?
No, no. Everything worked out
perfectly for her.
Not just for her.
For us.
♪