- Yes?
- Ready?
Let me talk to Michael.
- Let me know he's okay.
- Trust me, he's all right.
But your little boy's dead
if you're not ready.
If you really kidnapped my son
then let me hear his voice.
I've done everything you've said.
I haven't left the house,
I haven't made any calls.
We know...
Read the paper?
The paper?
No, I haven't read the paper.
Let me fix that.
Oh, God!
You sick prick!
What have you done!?
Relax, he's got nine left.
Now, are you ready or does he die?
I'm ready.
Good.
Got a pen?
Yes.
Good. First stop is the
antique shop on Highway Nine.
Red truck in the lot will have
a gun on the rack. You take it.
A gun, why do I need a gun?
Just in case...
Kill or be killed.
Like the Fleming novel.
Read any Fleming?
No, I don't read any Fleming and
I don't know how to use a gun.
We will teach you. Stop number 2 is
a payphone at Brice and Arroyo.
Now, bring your duffle bag for
the gun and don't even think about
talking to the copsl
Ma'am?
Nice truck.
Clean your windshield?
Oh, no. Uh, let me just,
get you uh...
Heyl
Hey, what the hell you doin'?
Just wanted to
clean her window.
He wasn't bothering you,
was he, Ma'am?
He's my uncle and normally
I don't leave him alone, but...
Oh, don't worry, no I was just,
trying to give him some change.
Oh, never mind.
Can I help you into your truck?
Have a nice day, Ma'am.
Hello?
Hello!?
Shit!
- Hello?
- You're late.
This isn't easy, damn it.
What's with the Deputy?
You didn't call the cops, did you?
No, I didn't call the cops.
They just... showed up.
I'm doin' everything...
Shut itl Now, the finger
was for openers.
If you fail us, we'll send you
his head. Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Tell me what's next.
Learn to use the gun.
1512 Arnez Street. Ask for Peter.
Take the weapon out and say,
"Show me how to use this.
My husband's a two-timing
son of a bitch."
Let me talk to...
Hello?
I'm looking for Peter.
Why?
I need him to show me
how to use this,
my husband's a two-timing
son of a bitch.
Where do I find Peter?
You're looking at her.
You want to put a bullet
in your husband's head...
You got my vote.
That's what I did to mine.
Come on.
Clip holds five rounds,
six in the chamber.
The barrel kicks so aim low
till you get used to it.
Come on.
Now remember, aim low.
All right now, grip it tight with
your left hand, ease up on the right.
Good... Now think of
your husband.
Think of him bangin'
all those little chippies.
What do you know
about my husband?
Oh, come on. They're all
the same model, aren't they?
Just with different serial numbers.
Now, go ahead.
Put his face over
the one on the target.
And aim low.
Hey, Peter, I'm locked
in here! Peter!?
- Hello?
- Nice shootin', Love.
Gets you all warm inside,
doesn't it, Sweet Cakes?
Now, get to your office,
log onto your computer,
download a file simply
entitled: "ORBS TAR."
Where do I deliver it?
Wait behind the tree by the dumpster,
someone will be there to meet you.
Then we'll arrange to
get you back to your son.
Little early,
aren't you, Jane?
Uh, just tryin'
to catch up.
You're workin' too
hard for too little.
Why you sellin'?
Oh, just need the money.
I got pink slipped.
Oh, Jesus.
Not you, too?
Goddamn corporations
are like tanks.
They don't feel nothin', they just
roll over the top of things.
Well... if you need some
help gettin' placed,
you know where to find me.
Thanks.
Yeah, I got that.
Yeah. I tried that.
Hang on.
Damn it.
Hello?
Sorry, our mistake.
It's been rectified.
Yes?
I didn't say view it.
I said download it.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Shut upl Hurry, or
your son loses a hand.
Yes?
Get to the drop point,
you've got the gun incase
someone tries to stop you.
If there's trouble, remember,
- leave the bag in the dumpster.
- When do I get Michael?
Just wait here,
I should be...
What happened?
He got shotl Over therel
Right over therel
- Hello?
- Tell me what happenedl
I don't know. Uh, I was sitting there
and someone behind me just fired.
How do I know you didn't do it?
You had the rifle.
I didn't do it!
Are you insane?
What possible reason
would I have?
Where's the disc?
In a bag, in the dumpster.
Look, I don't know what
the hell happened back there but
I have done everything you asked me...
Please, just give me
back my son.
You're sure you left the gun
and the disc in the dumpster.
Yes! That's what I said!
Now, where's Michael!?
- Right behind you.
- What?
Mom!
Michael!
Oh, I'm coming!
- What'd you do?
- What?
What'd you do that
made them take me?
I didn't do anything, nothing.
How can you ask me that?
How can I ask you that, Mom?
Because first...
Your fingers?
It wasn't your finger...
What the hell are
you talkin' about?
Come on...
Get in the car.
I can walk myself.
Just get in the car!
I don't believe you. Aren't you
even curious what they did?
They locked me in box in some yard,
like a stupid hamster in a cage!
Michael, I know what you
must have gone through.
No, how could you know?
You weren't even there.
Look, you're okay now.
So just calm down.
Something's going on I can't
figure out until I get home.
Till I stop for a second,
I just can't talk.
You can't talk?
Some jerk-offs grab me outside of
physics class,
wrap tape around my mouth and
lock me in a box all night,
and you can't talk?
What the fuck, Mom?
Quit your goddamn swearing,
Michael, I'm warning you!
Mom!
They're gonna ram
us from behind!
Just hold on!
Oh God, are you all right?
Yeah.
Mom, look out!
Bitch!
Anything you want to
tell me?
Look, I just want to get home,
regroup and then I'll call the police.
Looks like somebody's
already done that for us.
Mom, don't run
from the cops!
Turn on the radio.
- The radio? Why?
- Just turn it on.
...another update on the CY-KOR
assassination after a word
from our sponsor.
Hil This is Billy Bob Parker
down at Downtown Dodge...
Just turn on the goddamn news!
You betchal
We're back with news radio 620.
In case you haven't heard,
Carl Churnings, the 55 year old
Chairman of CY-KOR was assassinated
this morning. Authorities have
started a state wide manhunt,
or should we say, "woman hunt"
for the suspect.
She's apparently a disgruntled
CY-KOR employee recently laid off
from the accounting department.
Her name is, and mind you, this is
not an alias, her name is "Jane Doe."
If you have any information as to
her whereabouts, please...
The whole thing was a set-up.
Mom, did you do it?
No, I didn't do it.
How the hell can you
even ask me that?
Don't you get it?
They set it up and now they're
trying to kill us and
pin the murder on me.
Well, Sheriff...
What you got?
Truck load of bad press for
your alma matter.
Looks like one of your employees got
a little pissed at her layoff notice.
We found this in a dumpster next
to the sniper sight.
A rifle inside was fired
three times...
Erick says he saw Ms. Doe
enter the building with it.
May I?
The janitor saw her download
somethin' off the work station.
Any idea what's on it?
Not yet. We're waitin' for
a criminalist.
We don't want to compromise
the evidence.
Of course.
Meanwhile, Mr. Avery, uh,
how do you want me to handle
the press? It looks like you've
got a bit of an image problem here.
I mean, this'll pretty much
make CY-KOR a household name.
You think you can keep
things contained?
At least until we can
determine her motives.
Well, I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Well, I better be headin' back.
I'm sure you got a lot to sort out.
Were you close to him?
Who?
The victim?
Churnings?
I mean, he was your boss in
Washington, wasn't he?
Yes, he was. I became CEO after
transferring from the London
office a year ago.
So we hardly knew each other, really.
But I had the utmost respect for him.
...I think it's time you quit
lying to me and tell me what you did.
I don't lie to you, Michael.
I told you-nothing.
Churnings was murdered in the
parking lot and they pinned it on you.
- They must've had a reason.
- How did you know his name?
I heard his name on the radio.
Look, it doesn't matter what his
name was, it...
what did you do?
Nothing. I don't know! God,
I sent Mr. Churnings a memo.
A memo?
Yeah, I sent him a memo.
A confidential memo to
Washington last week.
What was in it?
I... why? Why are you so
interested in this?
God, no wonder Dad split on us,
you're so dense sometimes.
You know, people kidnapped me.
Forgive me for being "interested."
- What was in the memo?
- Level 9 codes.
Which are?
Back door passwords.
They have access to
everything inside CY-KOR'S
data banks.
So...
So, someone was using them
without clearance.
I notified Mr. Churnings,
I guess he was...
Coming here to deal with it.
You should have just
stayed out of it.
Stayed out of it?
Stayed out of it.
Michael, it's my job.
That's what I do.
I administrate passwords.
You know, I assign them,
I monitor them, and I file memos
when someone uses them improperly.
Yeah, well, it looks you
filed one too many memos.
These appear to be wire transfers
into Churnings personal accounts.
There should be an authorization
code next to each amount.
Yeah, there is. The same in
each case, 2A11.
2A11, give me an ident on that.
2A11 is assigned to Jane Doe.
It's her password audit trigger.
Would it give her access to
cash transfer approvals?
Not directly, but with
a little innovation.
What's the bottom line total
on those wire transfers?
Uh... four million and change.
Four million buys a lot of innovation.
I guess that settles it, gentlemen.
It's clearly a case of collusion.
Churnings was extorting CY-KOR funds
with her acquiescence and
cutting her in on it.
We're still missing
a motive for murder.
How about blackmail?
Churnings secretary just
faxed this from Washington.
It's a letter she found
hidden in his desk.
"Carl, I have reassessed my value
in your corporate game-plan and
wish to adjust my compensation
accordingly.
This is not open to negotiation.
Any reluctance on your part will
have its consequences."
Any bets on who signed it?
Eddy, paint it and ship it.
...right, it's the truck stop
off of I-17. Hey, I gotta go.
Who did you call?
No one. I just tried checkin'
the messages.
Oh, you are so lying, Michael.
Who did you call, your father?
Well, good. Because don't think for
one second he would lift a finger to
help you.
Just chill, okay. I didn't
call him. How much did you get?
Eighty-two hundred.
Geez, Blue Book had to
be at least thirteen grand.
I know, Michael. I took what
he offered, okay.
I'm sure they I.D.'d the car
and he don't have any money.
- There's someone following us.
- What?
Don't, don't look.
Come on.
We have more information now in
the shooting in Bolton, Montana.
CY-KOR sources have revealed
shocking details of a conspiracy
involving Carl Churnings,
the assassination victim and
the suspect, Jane Doe.
The two were apparently involved in
an extortion scheme that lead to
blackmail and Churning's
eventual murder.
Yeah, it's Tony down here at
Tony's Used Cars on I-17.
Yeah, you know that
Jane Doe on the TV?
Yeah. She was just here.
I just bought her car off her.
Yeah, she's right
outside the lot.
Freeze!
You twitch, I fire.
You breathe, I fire.
You don't slip me that gun
in five-milliseconds... I fire.
Who are you?
My name's Lucky.
I'm not gonna touch that.
Why are you following us?
All shucks, love, I'd really
like to tell you, but uh...
- it's just not ethical, is it?
- You sonovabitch!
Sticks and stones may break
my bones but I'm just doing me
freaking job!
Read any Fleming?
What? You mickin' all
my good lines?
Didn't he write:
"Stick your face in the bowl before
I unload this clip into your skull?"
No... I don't think
he wrote that.
Well, I think he did.
Stick your face in the bowl.
Can I flush it first?
You don't have that kinda time, Lucky.
Stick your face in the bowl!
Hey, Mom. I really
think we should go.
In the bowl with the
rest of the shit!
Lower!
Hell, no sense partin'
with this kinda cash.
I'd a given you
a ride for free.
Well, we're in a big hurry.
Can we just go?
You betcha.
Climb right in.
Yeah, I got 'em.
A black freight liner,
Montana plates...
Mary, Apple, 4-4-6-6.
Look out!
Now, gol Gol Gol
Let's gol Step out of
the cab immediately.
Step out of the cabl
Step out of the cab now with
your hands above your head, let's gol
Not you, idiotl
The other two. Get in therel
Step out of the cab nowl
Just do what they say.
Hands up! Put 'em on
your head!
Come on. Get 'em in there!
Let's go!
Come on! Let's move it!
Move it! Move, move into the van!
Into the van! Let's go!
Move! Come on!
Who are you guys,
state police?
No, Mom, they're not
the state police.
Then who? FBI?
They're not the FBI.
Well, we're innocent.
We have rights, you can't just...
Mom...
Just shut up.
Hey, Dad!
Jane...
It's been awhile.
Get off me!
Back off her!
- Just get your hands off me!
- Put her down!
- Mom, it's okay.
- Don't touch me!
- Just let me...
- I said... don'touch-me.
Jane... if you calm down
I can explain everything.
- You hungry?
- Starving.
I got all your favorites.
Turkey... Pastrami on rye.
Thanks.
What about you,
have you eaten anything?
Have I eaten?
No, I haven't eaten, David.
Food has not been
a huge priority lately.
But would you mind just taking
a second to tell me where the
hell we are and why everybody's
been trying to kill us
and what are you doing in
the middle of this.
And why are you just
so goddamn calm!?
- I told you she'd be pissed.
- No, I am way beyond pissed.
I am way beyond pissed.
I am su-a-fuckin'-cidal!
And beyond that,
I had the fabulous good
fortune to get one of
my migraines this morning...
...you know, but in my haste,
to keep the little schedule that
my son's kidnappers devised for me,
you know, gun theft,
target practice,
short-range assassination,
that kind of thing.
I just mistakenly skipped out of
the house without my Motrin.
I could really use some Motrin,
David. About a pound of it.
Can you get that for me?
Can you get that!?
Simmons...
Could you get me some Motrin?
- Motrin?
- That's right. I said Motrin.
How long have you been talking
into your collar, David?
In nine years of marriage and
five years of divorce,
I've never seen you do that.
You said you were
in sales, David.
"Military salvage"
I think was the term.
At least that was the excuse that
kept you on the road 350 out of
365 days a year.
Business must be good, huh?
Got yourself your own little ranch?
Your own little goon squad.
Military Salvage salesman?
I don't think so.
So who the hell
do you work for?
The D. I.A.
The Drug Enforcement Agency?
That's D.E. A... D. I.A.
Defense Intelligence Agency.
Oh, your dad's a spook, Michael.
But you obviously knew.
We'll get to that later.
So what is it that you uh,
you guys do anyway?
I don't' think I've heard
that acronym on CNN lately?
We coordinate intelligence
operations for weapons procurement
and disposal for the
United States Government.
How long?
The Agency was conditioned in 1975.
No, how long have you been
lying to me, David?
Since before we were married.
Jane...
It's the way things are done.
Here, just stay over there!
Just stay over there!
Don't patronize me!
Tell me the rest.
You were set up.
In a word: Duh!
By who?
- Avery.
He kidnapped Michael in order to
get you in place for the murder.
Then he staged an elaborate
cover-up to give you a motive.
I'm listening.
The disc you downloaded?
Had phony files on it linking you to
an extortion attempt with Churnings.
Avery's saying you tried to
blackmail him and when he wouldn't
play ball you had
Churnings killed.
Well, that's nonsense.
I sent Churning's a memo
telling him someone was
using unauthorized passwords.
That someone was Avery.
Well, why would he need...
Information.
You work there...
You know CY-KOR collates more of it
than any institution in the country.
He's been using the passwords to
access it to sell it.
Sell it?
He's got a deal to sell it off in
one big down load to a foreign broker.
Well, why is this stuff
so valuable?
Think about it.
Any foreign Intelligence Agency
would love to know who's in
financial trouble.
Who's vulnerable to recruitment.
Foreign pharmaceutical
companies would pay...
You... are a lousy
spin doctor, David.
It's the weapon's CY-KOR is
building, isn't it?
Reconnaissance satellites,
missiles.
You could probably give
a rat's ass about the rest of it,
am I right?
You were always
a fast read, Jane.
Just illiterate when it
comes to husbands.
So, arrest Avery.
Stop the data transfer.
No, we want him to sell it.
Why?
Because we doctored it.
We spent over a year with
my contact inside CY-KOR...
The data's poisoned with enough
disinformation on weapon's systems
to set a hostile government
back twenty years.
Why couldn't you just come to me?
Tell me what you were doing?
Frankly, we didn't need you.
Oh, that's right. You said you had
your little contact inside CY-KOR.
And so what poor dumb
sap were you able to turn?
That would be me.
Jesus, your own son.
You were a goddamn mole for him?
Is that what you are, a pathetic
little mole for the D.E.A.?
It's D. I. A! And I'm not a mole.
I'm an operative.
Oh, I'm sorry.
An operative.
Well, I should have
figured you wouldn't understand.
- I mean, you're just a mom.
- Jane!
Got your Motrin.
Now then, I'm Kurt Simmons,
David's partner.
Can I get you anything else?
Yeah, a gun like that. I'd like to
unload it into my ex-husband.
She's funny.
I like her.
On behalf of the agency, I'd like to
apologize for all you've been through.
From here on out things will
run a lot more smoothly if you
just follow me.
Wait a minute.
Phelps wants 'em taken to
a safe house.
A safe house? Where?
Why wasn't I notified about this?
Well, David, your ability to
deal with the situation is
seriously hampered by your
relationship to the parties involved...
We decided this was best.
Please, we haven't much time.
Wait a minute, hang on.
Look, call Phelps.
I got my orders.
What should I do?
Go with him.
I'll make sure you're safe.
Jane...
Avery didn't know
I recruited Michael.
It wasn't supposed to
turn out like this.
Yeah. That's what you said when you
got me pregnant at eighteen.
How long have you
worked for them?
Fourteen months.
How'd you do it?
I didn't.
You did.
What?
You know how you'd take home
those password backups at
night to analyze their activity?
Three times a week they'd
send me compressed files.
I copied them onto your discs
after you went to bed.
When you went to download those
files into the system the next day...
Dad's files went along with them.
You little shit.
Look, it wasn't supposed to
hurt you, okay.
It was meant to be a way to
spread bogus information,
that was it.
It was no big deal.
Just tell me why.
Did he promise you something?
Money, tax free dead presidents.
Oh, you disgust me.
Do I? I earned $50,000 for
a few hours of hack time.
What did you make?
Thirty, forty grand
a year punching some
time clock?
So where is it?
What?
The cash?
Dad said he's holding it
for me.
Jesus, you're pathetic.
Like he told me he was
a salvage salesman.
Your dad's a liar, Michael.
Why do you think I left him!?
Isn't that what your shrink
refers to as "denial," Mom?
Dad left you.
He left because he wanted
someone who wasn't so uptight.
Someone who could relate to
what he did.
Is that what he told you?
God! I wish he was half the
man you created him to be!
He never gave me a chance to
relate to what he did, Michael.
He never told me what he did!
He was just gone all the time. Gone!
We're stopping.
I wish he'd make up his mind.
Mom, he's gone!
I gotta get the wheel!
Here! Help me through!
Hold on, we're gonna crash!
Mom?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Are you?
Yeah.
Come on, I'll pull you through.
Hold on, Mom. You okay?
I'm gonna get you out.
Michael... I'm not gonna be
able to get out of here.
I want you to go.
No way!
No. You'll be fine.
Come on! Come on!
I'm not leaving you!
Michael, you've disobeyed me your
whole life, don't do it now!
Get out of the van!
Get out of the goddamn van!
Get out!
Mom!
Can't you listen to me once!?
Just keep kickingl
This is Simmons. Tell Phelps
there's been an accident.
How'd they die?
Dellings says the authorities
picked them up a few hours ago.
Apparently the van transporting
them crashed on route.
How fabulously tragic.
Call Lazar...
Tell him I'll meet
his deadline.
Mom, can we just take a break?
Can't. They'll be all over
this place to check the wreckage.
Then can we just take a minute to
figure out where the hell we're going?
I know where I'm going.
To see a man named Niles.
Why? Can he get us to
the border.
I'm not going to
- Well then where are we going?
- Straight into their hearts.
Would you just stop and tell me
what the hell you're talking about?
Michael, I have spent my entire life
as your mom trying to help you
and if I survive this,
I will spend years trying to
figure out how I failed you.
But right now I am sick of
carrying the guilt of
you growing up fatherless.
What does Dad have to
do with this?
Everything! He got us here.
Him and you lying to me.
So the way I see it...
I gave you your life and you
just helped me give me back mine
so we're even.
You wanna be your own man now, fine.
You can follow me or you can leave.
Fair enough?
Yeah. That sounds fair.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
Who's this guy, Niles?
He's a research scientist for CY-KOR.
We worked on special projects.
He's got a remote node
connection to Central Data.
What good is that?
From there I can shut Avery down.
Force him to make a deal.
These guys don't deal.
You get somebody by the balls and
squeeze hard enough, trust me...
they deal.
You know, there's room in
here for two.
What the fuck happened, Kurt!?
I don't know. Sniper, I guess.
One of Avery's guys.
Bullet hits the tire,
we go over this fuckin' cliff.
Your wife and kid are in the back,
I couldn't get 'em out.
It's all I could do was
jump out of the door.
David, under the circumstances
I think it's best you
take some time off.
Your support team can
follow things through.
I don't need time off,
it's my mission.
It's the Agency's
operation, David.
And you're aware of Agency rules
regarding emotional proximity
to victims.
That didn't stop you from
leaning on me to recruit my son.
You could have refused.
The Agency doesn't
like refusals.
Precisely, so why start now?
Take some time off.
Lester can drive you.
I'll drive myself...
Might be healthier that way.
Well, I guess we weren't
too convincing.
Fuck him.
I'm layin 'here like the Mummy.
I did all I could.
No matter. His role's become
muddier by the moment.
It's best he's deactivated.
Fine with me.
David!
Nine lives, baby.
Nine friggin' lives!
- What are you talkin' about?
- Your wife and kid.
Recovery called, they got
a van, no bodies.
It looks like they're alive.
Kurt said that they were locked in
the back when the van went airborne.
Kurt must've been mistaken.
Van's flat as a pancake.
Ain't no way they gotten out
after it hit.
Does Phelps know about this?
Goin' to tell him.
What is this place,
the entrance to the Bat Cave?
Sort of. It's the back door to
CY-KOR's research facility.
Michael, don't!
Do not alter your coordinates.
Yeah, right!
- Michael!
- I'm outta here.
What was that sound?
You'll see.
Niles, Nile's turn off the alarm,
it's Jane. Jane Doe.
Damn it, Jane. Get inside
before someone sees you.
Come on, Michael.
Who's the little punk pukin'
all over my property?
It's my son.
How in God's name did you
know I'd be here.
Niles, please. I know you work
here alone at night.
There's not much that goes on
around here I don't know about.
Then I suppose you know you're in
a whole lot of trouble.
They say you killed Churnings.
Niles, you know me.
I'm not a murderer.
Avery set me because
I found evidence he's
been selling off
classified data.
Selling the blue prints of
what you build out here.
If that's true, what makes
you think I give a damn?
I'm dyin' to vacate this
place anyway.
I know that. But I also know
they must something that
keeps you here.
I'm listening.
I can find the file.
I can erase it,
I can make it go away, Niles.
Let's just say I buy into this
absurdity for a second and assume
you're tellin' the truth.
What do I gotta do for you?
Let me use your remote node to
access the system.
And then what?
We get to live another
twenty-four hours.
I gotta get outta here, man.
The night nurse in here has
breath so bad she needs
a Tic-Tac with a battery.
Simmons.
- You haven't heard?
- Heard what?
- She's still alive.
- Who?
Whol? Who do you thinkl?
Jane-fuckin'-Doe!
Jesus.
Yeah, he's someone you better
start prayin' to if you don't
find out what she wants and
then find her a body bag.
Alright, alright, trust me.
She's about to be dead along
with that little prick
husband of hers.
David.
Kurt.
Hey, how ya doin', guy?
Deal is... once we're inside
my records get erased first.
Fine. Just piggy-back in on
the D.O.D.'s trunk line,
that way CY-KOR can't trace us.
She's all yours.
If they really set you up
what makes you think you're
still clear to log on?
I'm using passwords only
Churnings knew about.
It'll take me
a few minutes to sequence.
Feel better?
Yeah. Now would you mind explaining
what the hell you did to me?
Sure. You got zapped by
sado-acoustic pulse waves-handy
for crowd control.
It's one of 20 NLWs
I'm workin' on out here.
NLWs?
Non-lethal Weapons Technology.
From the folks who brought
you Hiroshima and Nagasaki.
Opening soon at
a battlefield near you.
What's this?
More crowd control?
Nope. Data control.
It's a mock-up of an EMP bomb.
It delivers an electromagnetic
burst of over four trillion watts-
Incapacitating any electronic
device in a 100 mile grid.
So what does it
do to humans?
Good question. One I ask them
from time to time.
They tell me, "We'll have to
drop one to find out."
Don't look for morality at the D.O.D.,
look for a whole new generation of pain.
I'm in.
You got full access?
Looks like it.
I've been tryin' to break into
these files for ten years and
all this time all I had to
do was ask you?
Niles, until today I've never
illegally altered a record in my life.
Unlike the rest of
my family.
It's all here.
Every last lyin' bit.
Can we lose it?
Permanently?
Say goodbye to
Niles Anderson.
I'm dead.
Just a ghost in the machine.
What's next?
Churnings had a password that
would lock up all data in
the event of a virus
or security breach.
No one knew about it but him.
And me of course,
I set it up.
I just wish I could be
there to see his face.
We're still down.
We've tried everything.
Every CPU is down.
Every trunk line is blocked.
That's impossible.
Initiate the restore procedure.
Start by disconnecting the drives.
Tried that. The first one
we unhooked auto-erased.
What?
The lockup mechanism employs
a fail safe virus that prevents
any storage disconnection
from the CPU.
What are you saying?
We're frozen.
Locked up.
What could have caused this?
You're not gonna like this.
I only managed to
get one screen to boot.
Thanks for the money.
Thanks for the clothes.
Thanks for everything.
No, it's me that
should thank you.
That file you erased was
my ball and chain.
You gonna tell me
what's inside it?
Why?
Maybe it'll help me understand
what I'm up against.
I headed one of D.O.D.'s
early germ warfare projects.
It was only supposed to
be tested on cattle.
But they slipped the agent in
a hepatitis B vaccine to
check its affect on humans.
I never knew.
46 out of 60 patients
died within a year.
I quit when I figured it out.
Threatened to tell
the whole story.
They threatened to pin it on
me if I didn't keep my mouth
shut and stay on board.
Phony vaccination records
were in that file.
These guys play hard, Jane.
And they play for keeps.
You wanna stay and
watch me play back?
I'd love to, but I got
a date with Elvis.
Who?
That's what I nicknamed
the miniature EMP prototype.
It's scheduled for preliminaries
in the morning.
I thought you wanted out.
I worked two years to build the thing.
Like to see if it works.
You take care of yourself,
Jane.
You betcha.
Yeah? Hold on for a second.
Jane Doe on line one.
Hello?
If anyone else is on this line you
may not want them to hear this.
There's no one else
on the line.
I figured out what
you've been doing.
The downloads.
The data sales.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought you might
want to get on line so you could
make your little delivery date.
My mistake.
That stupid cow.
She better pray...
Wait...
Don't hang up again.
Give me a reason not to.
What do you want?
That's more like it.
One million.
Cash.
When?
An hour.
That's impossible.
Then you're history.
Bye.
Wait! Where do you
want the money.
Don't get ahead of
yourself.
All right...
what else?
Safe passage for me and my son.
Invent another patsy for the murder.
Deal.
What do we do now?
Let's play like old times.
What?
Antique Shop,
on Highway Nine.
They'll be a message in
a red truck.
I don't have time for games.
You don't have time, period.
These are my rules, or you don't
get the disc that unlocks
the system, got it?
Got it.
Good.
Oh, and don't send that pissy
little messenger boy like you
did last time.
That guy got shit
faced on the job.
That little slag, she's dead.
D-E-A...
Dead!
It's done.
All right, we're backin' off.
It's in everybody's interest for
her to get Avery back on line
so we can trade the data.
It's after the deal that
I'm worried about.
I want my family to live a long.
Far away from here.
How patriarchal of you.
We'll talk after
the deal goes down.
We'll talk now or
Kurt wears a headstone.
You know me better than that.
Simmons is expendable just like you.
I figured. And I bet you don't
figure yourself as expendable.
Are you threatening me,
David?
You remember the thermal imaging
gun we kept handy on
the black ops back in the day?
Vaguely.
I've got digital imprints of
everything.
They were black ops.
We did what we had to do.
Where do you get off playing
the blushing bride?
I'm sure your brand of chicanery is
pretty much S.O.P. With Company get
ahead quick artists like yourself.
I'm pretty sure there's still some
Americans who'll blanch at government
agents fraternizing with drug lords
and getting blow jobs from
Cuban transvestites.
You wouldn't do that to me.
You wouldn't do that to the Company.
Try me.
I assume you've got an airborne
ranger doing a lock scan on this call.
I'll have it recalled.
No. I want it.
Tell our boys to drop and
clear and you bring me my
family and I fly them out.
You follow,
you trace or surveil...
And I swear to God I'll download
your little film festival to
Diane Sawyer, Dan Rather
and Howard fuckin' Stern.
Okay, David.
You have my word.
I don't trade in that
currency anymore.
Hey, buddy.
I'm seein' snakes out here.
She screwed us!
There's no red truck!
There!
- Well?
- Well what?
What does it say?
It says, "Payphone, Brice and
Arroyo in five minutes.
Don't be late shit head.
Jane."
Let's go.
She's doin' this all, that's it!
I want to kill her fucking truck!
Just shut up and drive.
Wake up!
The man doesn't know
how dead he is.
Hey! Jesus!
Fuckin' Shit!
Shit!
Hello?
Is that you, Lucky?
Don't play games with me, bitch!
You played 'em with me.
Bloody hell!
Suck up to her, damnit.
Don't blow this.
Hello, love.
Long time, no speaky-weaky.
Shut up.
You got the money?
Oh... Have I got the money?
Haliburton case.
Is Haliburton all right?
I mean, we didn't have
time to shop around.
Yeah, that'll be fine as long as
there's a million dollars inside it.
540 Broxton. Third floor.
Ten minutes.
540 Broxton. Third in ten.
Got it. Anything else, love?
Yeah. You've got a little
zit on your neck.
I'd pop it before
the head gets unsightly.
You-whoooo... Janey?
Love? You've got some
explainin' to do...
"Up the stairs, down the hall,
left down the next set of stairs..."
Baby... Darling...
Nice to see you can
follow directions, Lucky.
Drop the case in the hole
in the center of the room.
Well hello, love.
Come out where I can see you.
I've missed you.
There's a nine-mil aimed at your
heart and you know I know how to use it.
Right...
Well, how do I know you won't
shoot me and take the dough.
Just drop it and go.
Right.
Okay.
Anything you say...
Love, anything you say.
Chrome's a fashion fuck-up in
a handgun, boy. It reflects the light.
Shut it!
Lucky, I warned you!
Better not scream,
before I kill you boy.
Mom!
Michael!?
How bloody predictable!
Mom! Behind you!
Well, well, well.
It's my turn to have a bit of
fun, isn't it?
Yes... a bit of Lucky fun.
Mmmm, very nice.
Oh, never realized you had such
a doable little rack!
It'll be a shame to carve it,
love, wouldn't it?
Now, you can pick the pieces or
you can give me back my disc and
I'll do you quick and painless.
I swear to God.
You want to say something, Love?
You want so say something?
Go ahead, say it?
What do you say?
What you gonna say?
That... I'm afraid is gonna
cost you three piggies.
This little piggy...
Oyel Tough guyl
Peter!
What exactly do you think
you're doing, Lucky?
What's it look like I'm doing,
Peter? I'm freakin' workin'.
Why you botherin' me while
I'm freakin' working!
Working?
Looks like you've been
feeling her up!
You have any idea
how degrading that is?
Well, call me a pervert.
Call me kinky but just get
the fuck out of my face...
And call me some
other fucking time!
What'd you do that for!?
We had a deal.
You didn't pay.
I was gonna pay.
I swear.
But this bitch survived and
someone had to take care of it,
didn't they?
Oh, I left you messages.
I would have called you.
I swear on your mother!
I really don't like it when
people swear on my mother.
Look, Peter...
- Get down on your knees.
- We can work this out.
We are working it out.
Now get down on your knees and
apologize to her.
You never told me you
were settin' her up.
You just said to show
her the ropes!
What difference does
it make what we did!?
Tell her that you're
a sadist and a misogynist...
...and that you're very,
deeply sorry.
I'm... I'm sorry.
No, say it all.
Say, "I'm a sadist..."
I'm a sadist...
And a misogynist...
And a...
Why don't you give me a fuckin' word
I can pronounce you stupid little cunt!
God, I hate the "c" word,
don't you?
Michael!
Michael!? Oh, God!
Michael!?
Can you help me get him down?
Oh, God.
Michael...
Move. Move!
Breath.
No!
Michael...
Oh, God... God...
Wait a minute,
where you going?
I've got no fight with you.
They hired me, they didn't pay.
I took care of it.
My business here is done.
What if I was to hire you?
As what?
I don't know...
A body guard?
How much we talking?
A hundred thousand dollars
sound about right?
Sounds real right.
Where you gonna get it?
Did you see a Lincoln
parked out front?
Yeah.
Avery's inside.
Good. He's supposed to
have a million dollars in
a case for me.
And if he don't?
Well... I suppose it don't
cost nothing to find out.
I realize there's been a delay.
I'm telling you not to worry.
The exchange will go down as planned.
Enough!
I'll give you the money!
I've been real busy the last
twenty-four hours thanks to you.
And I am so tired of the bullshit
I feel like I could just... go off.
Like I could just start unloading
the rounds in this clip, like
candy from a Pez dispenser.
I said I've got your money.
Then get it!
Thought you worked for Lucky!
Guy didn't live up to
his name, did he?
It's all here.
Want to count it?
Where's the disc?
Michael, give him the disc.
That's for keeping me
locked in a box.
I don't care what happens to CY-KOR.
Don't follow us or screw us or
I'll leak everything.
Come on, Michael.
How do I know this will work?
You don't.
Need a lift?
Red Tango, this is Control.
Go ahead, Red Tango.
I have a locate on the suspects.
Heading north on I-17
in a black pickup.
You think he took the bait?
He's a desperate fish, ain't he?
Pull off the road!
It's David.
Look, I believed in what we were
doing but I never knew Phelps was
running a rogue op.
He thinks as long as you're
alive his operation's compromised.
I can get you and Michael over
the border but only if we leave now.
If you screw me over,
I'll kill you myself.
It's more than we agreed upon.
But you earned it.
Come on.
Boy...
I know your face.
If anything happens to these two,
I'll track you, I'll find you,
I'll skin you and I'll eat you.
It's been nice meeting you, too.
You set us up,
you sonovabitch!
No, I didn't.
Come on.
All right, let's go!
Come on!
That's the only warning
you're gonna get.
You better listen to me, David.
Get your family away from
the damn chopper... nowl
What do we do?
- Any idea what's on it?
- No. It's totally encrypted.
Can it hurt us?
Well, the system's already
incapacitated.
It couldn't get much worse.
Should I run it?
Yeah.
Are we back?
Tell you in a sec.
Yeah, we're back.
The data seems in tact.
How quaint...
The "Does" reunited.
What time does it go down?
Shut up. This isn't
your party anymore.
No need to be melodramatic,
Simmons.
David set this up. There's nothing
wrong with him seeing it play out.
Especially now that it depends on
his wife's ability to
activate the system.
We're monitoring
Avery's residence.
He's inside. He hasn't
moved for three hours.
Not the behavior of a man about to
make the score of a lifetime.
Any action?
Nothin'. Lots empty.
So it is.
Avery's made a deal to sell off
the data to an international broker
named Lazar.
It was scheduled to be exchanged
an hour ago.
You better pray that little stunt of
yours didn't foul up Avery's plans.
The password was on
the disc I gave him.
That's all he needs to
unlock the system.
Sir, got a van pulling
into the lot.
Is this scheduled?
Yeah. They clean the cafeteria.
Anything unusual?
Nothing. This ain't
how it's goin' down.
Is Avery still inside?
Hasn't moved.
I made a mistake in
your case, David.
I'm already regretting it.
Phelps insisted I recruit Michael.
I listened to him.
What are you talking about?
The Cree Indians used to
take a boy, nine or ten and
indoctrinate him into a war party.
They wanted to teach him the world
was cruel and complicated...
...that life needed to
be cherished and fought for.
He's just a boy, David.
Your boy, your own flesh and blood.
That's why I wanted him to
learn it from me.
Well was it all worth it?
What have you got left to
fight for now, huh?
What does he have left to
fight for, this?
Sir, I was wrong.
Looks like we got activity.
I'm in back of the Data Wing where
they've connected water lines.
They're rock hard and they're
definitely not hoses.
Fiber connection.
What?
Kid could be right. A high bandwidth
optical fiber connection.
They've probably connected to
the main data banks via the...
...fiber line and that's how
they're downloading the files.
How long would something
like this take?
Fiber can transfer a terabyte of
data in five minutes.
Target's in motion.
Let the games begin.
Get the mobiles into position.
Move it, move it, move it!
Sir, are you getting clean audio?
Yeah, but give me more level.
All right, let's get outta here.
Come on, let's go.
Now that I've delivered
I think I'm due an apology.
Screw the apologies. You were
compromised, you cost us time.
What's a day between friends?
Everything. I have
a schedule to keep.
Look, why argue.
It's all here.
Show me proof you've wire-transferred
my funds and we'll part amicably.
When I verify the data.
Kwan?
Yes, sir.
How does it look?
I'll know in a moment.
Is this your idea of a joke?
What are you talking about?
This is useless, it's
completely encrypted.
It looks like some type of
high level PGP encoding.
Playing with us, Avery?
Where is the encryption key?
I don't have.
I didn't encrypt it.
The disc... she gave me to
unlock the system...
...must have installed
the encryption mechanism.
You little twit!
What did you do!?
I downloaded a batch program that
encrypts the data on the trajar boot.
Is that possible?
Yeah. Complicated but possible.
What's the password?
There isn't one.
It morphs randomly.
The stuffs garbage.
Face it, you're screwed.
Are you guys getting this?
Move all units to
the CY-KOR Data Center.
I want every workstation confiscated
and taken to the holding facility.
You don't have
the authority to do that.
Don't I!? Section 518,
National Security Act.
By the time CY-KOR files a protest,
I can duplicate the data and arrange
a sale to Lazar through
one of our assets.
Do you really think some
15 year old punk...
...and Miss Suzie-fuckin'-homemaker
can outwit the U.S. Government!?
Get 'em outta here!
Let's go!
You're out! Move it!
Move it out!
So what do I do with the Does?
This isn't Family Feud, we don't
give consolation prizes. Kill 'em.
All right, that's far enough.
No sense dwelling on it,
who wants to be first?
How about me?
Let's see if you have
the stomach for it.
Cool.
Who's next?
- Come on!
- Michael, come on!
How'd you know he'd
aim at your chest?
They follow procedure.
Never go by the book.
What are we gonna do now?
Beat Phelps to the end of
the rainbow.
I got enough ordinance in
that Bell Ranger to blow
the data center back to
Great Falls.
I thought you wanted
the deal to go down.
I wanted a lot of
things once.
Doesn't mean I'm proud of it.
Phelps isn't gonna have
a sense of humor about this.
But I got a tape underneath
the seat that I can...
See ya.
Oh, God. Dad.
What are we gonna do?
Did they teach you to
fly these things!?
Niles.
Now, I'm not gonna say you're
crazy cause that's just too
damn implicit.
Don't ask me to do this.
It's the only way, Niles.
You gotta believe me.
It's the only way left.
Look, I'm not even scheduled to
launch for three hours.
I can't just...
You can Niles. You can.
You have too.
They'll be there any minute
and it'll be too late.
Niles!
Shut up, I'm busy.
Niles, are you there?
Niles, please talk to me.
Move it, move it.
Come on, let's gol
Niles!
God help me.
What the hell are you doing!?
Jane?
Yes, Niles?
Elvis has left the building.
Ground code, I want the perimeter
sealed and move all the vans to
the exit doors.
You got that?
Okayl Move it boys and
girls, let's gol
Phelps, is that you?
Yes, this is Phelps.
Well, this is Jane and there's
three things you should know.
I'm listening.
One, I'm still alive.
I think I intuited that.
Two, I've got David's tape.
Okay...
What's the third thing?
When you see a shooting star...
Yeah?
...don't wish on it.
Everybody get back!
Everybody get the fuck backl
Good afternoon, can I have
your passport, please?
Thank you.
Go on.
...Investigators will be
revealing more details later
on this evening. Now the irony of
the whole explosion is that
it was one of CY-KOR'S own missile
prototypes that strayed off course.
The loss of CY-KOR's data banks has
sent a mob of credit list consumers
into the department stores today...
...as, for the moment, everyone's
credit slate has been wiped clean.
People are ecstatic.
Yeah?
Sir, I think we got
a locate on Jane Doe.
Let it go.
What?
It's over. We pin
the Churnings thing on Avery.
She walks. Nobody
touches her, got it?
Well, yeah, but why?
Because I've got my orders, okay?
And I don't question my orders.
So, why are you standing there?
I'm not... standing here.
"Dear Michael, if you're reading
this note, then obviously...
Well, what the hell...
Enclosed is the safety deposit box
key where I've held onto your money.
All of it's there...
along with a little bonus.
Actually, it's the rest of
my operational budget.
But don't worry,
they can't trace it.
Remember, always think for yourself
and no matter what happens,
always take care of your mother.
She's the best thing that every
happened to you and the worst
thing you could ever lose.
Take it from me. I found out
the hard way. Love, Dad."
Hey, Mom!
Let's go!
What's the matter?
What happened.
Don't ask.
Just let's go.
Was the money there?
Oh, yeah.
And the bonus?
Well, Christ, Michael are you
gonna tell me how much it was?
Over two million dollars.
Two million?
In cash.
Oh...
You're gonna hate this but...
we should probably give it back.
What are you crazy? How the hell
we supposed to do that?
I don't know.
But I guess there's nothing wrong
with taking forty or fifty years to
figure it out.
Hey, Mom?
I love you.