[mechanical ventilator]
[heart monitor]
[doctor] Okay, Ally, breathe in.
[CT scan working]
[pressing keys]
[doctor]
And a nice slow breath out.
That's great. One more time.
[exhales]
[sighs]
[Nelson] I can't find that guy's
cousin's phone number.
Ryan!
Sorry, man. Sorry.
I got to get going.
All right.
Well, go ahead, you know.
Tell her good luck, all right?
-Give her my best.
-Will do.
[door opening]
[clears his throat]
[Ally] Doc.
Please.
I'm afraid it's not good news.
Your kidney function
isn't improving.
Wait. I thought that by
increasing the treatments,
we would get more time.
Not always.
Again, I am... I'm sorry.
Okay, what's next?
Well, unless you have family or
friends that we haven't tested.
We've tried everyone.
Then, I'm afraid,
we're out of options.
That's not good enough.
I'm sorry.
How long do I have?
At best two months.
Where are we on the donor list?
It's a four-to-six-year wait.
Unfortunately,
not an option at this point.
It's time to get
your affairs in order.
Hey...
I'm not giving up.
[suspenseful music]
[door opening]
-[woman] See.
-Frozen one.
-[woman] That wasn't so bad.
-[man] Gracias.
[woman] This could really
be helpful to your families.
Everything good?
Everything is perfect.
Great.
Where are you right now?
I'm right here.
We fought...
It just didn't go our way.
No, we keep fighting
till the end.
-This is the end.
-No. There's still time.
-Ryan.
-There's still time!
[steps approaching]
Sorry.
-So many things.
-No, that's okay.
All right.
So, you're still going
to get dinner out.
Yeah.
Okay, I forgot some things
over in the office.
Do you need anything?
A new kidney.
[Ally laughs]
[gasps]
[Kate sobs]
I'm scared.
Me too.
[Kate sighs]
Enough tears.
Tell me about this new guy.
Ben.
Ben is a good name.
-[laughing] It's not important.
-Yes, it is.
I need to get my looks in now.
See if he's good enough
for my little sis.
He seems really
thoughtful and... caring.
He's really sweet.
What does he do?
He's a lawyer.
-Strike one.
-[laughs]
No, he's one of the good ones.
He works at the DA's office.
I'll have Ryan
run a check on him.
[laughs]
[hospital murmuring]
-[nurse] Excuse me.
-Here to see Doctor Hayworth.
[nurse] He's right that way.
[speaker] Doctor Jackson, meet
Doctor Jones in the E.R.
[door opening]
Ryan.
I need a minute.
Is Ally with you?
No.
Well, have a seat.
There was an article
in the news a while back.
It was the UCLA scandal
with the Yakuza crime boss
who needed a kidney.
Do you remember that?
Uh, yeah, but--
He bought his way
to the top of the list, right?
So, don't tell me
that we're out of options.
I need you to help me
save my wife.
[sighs] Ryan...
[sighs]
Twelve years in law enforcement.
I have seen some things.
I've learned.
Tell me what you need.
I have access to resources.
You need money? Drugs?
I can make things go away.
Just tell me,
what it's going to take?
-Ryan, stop.
-I know there's a way,
-There's always a way.
-Stop!
You... you just have
to have faith in the system.
Are you kidding me? The system?
The system is broken!
She's got months not years.
You said it yourself.
You can't lose hope.
Hope?
We're past that, okay?
It's time for action!
Doc... please,
I'm asking you for help.
What you're asking me
to do is unethical.
Not to mention illegal.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing more
that I can do.
It's not over. No.
I'm not giving up on her.
I'm not saying that you should.
[speaker] Doctor Craig
with Doctor Jackson...
[elevator's bell]
[suspenseful music]
[Anthony] Hey, man!
What do you want?
I can help you.
Your situation, I can help.
You know I'm a cop, right?
I know who you are...
you and your wife.
-Doctor Hayworth--
-Look, do you want help or not?
-Yeah. Yes.
-Okay.
Call this number.
They'll do what they can.
Wait a minute. Who are you?
Just call the number.
[Ally sighs]
[Ally vomiting]
[Ally coughing]
[knocks on the door]
[vomiting]
Are you okay?
[grunts]
Had some new meds.
I'll get you some water.
[gasps]
[heavy breathing]
[Ally gasping]
[Ryan] Here you go.
[Ally] I can't do this.
[sobs]
What good are an extra couple
weeks if they are like this?
I can't.
[Ally cries]
Maybe you don't have to.
What if there was
another option, Ally?
We find the donor ourselves.
Ryan...
No.
This isn't just about you,
you know.
I have a number.
Let's just see
what they have to say.
That's all.
We don't have to do it.
[Ryan cries]
[crying] Please, Ally.
Just do this for me, okay?
Okay.
[Ryan cries]
Oh. Thank you.
[knocks on the door]
-[Dolan] Mister Graves?
-Yes.
James Dolan.
-[Dolan] Good to meet you.
-[Ryan] Me, too.
-Thank you.
-My wife.
James Dolan.
It's very nice
to meet you, Allison.
Ally is fine.
-Have a seat right here.
-Thank you.
So, how does this work?
[sighs] Straight to the point.
Well you-- uh, I'm sure
you already know the stats.
The thousands of people
that die every year
while waiting for a donor.
You see, US law states
that a donor must be a relative,
a spouse, or donating
for reasons of affection.
Making what you do illegal.
Well, let's just say it doesn't
leave much wiggle room
for people like yourself.
People whose lives
are literally on the line.
[sighs]
My mother...
passed away two days
before my 18th birthday.
A kidney disease.
For five years, I watched...
an exciting... vibrant woman
be reduced
to a shallower form of herself.
We're sorry to hear that.
I was top my class
at Harvard Law.
And, I I've learned
the system from the inside out
in hopes of changing it.
And, when it comes
to donating organs,
let me tell you,
the system is broken.
I couldn't spend another
day working in a system
that shuts out people in need,
like yourself...
or my mother.
I...
I carried the anger of losing
her inside of me for years,
not knowing what to do.
Now, let me do this.
So, I don't regret it,
not for a minute,
because what I do
actually makes a difference.
Saves people's lives.
How long does the process take?
Well, first, we need
to identify a match.
And once that's done, we can go
ahead and schedule your surgery.
Well, how long does that
take to identify a match?
Well, I make no promises,
but I'm fairly confident
we can have your wife
prepped and ready to go
within the month.
And it could be sooner,
depending on availability.
Doctor Hayworth said
it would take months
for me to climb the donor list.
Now, you're sitting
in my living room,
telling me I could have
transplant surgery
within the month?
What's wrong with this picture?
Look, I'm sure
your doctor is a fine man
and a competent physician.
And if you want
to follow his advice,
I say, "Go with God.
But if you want to...
if you want to dance
at your daughter's wedding,
bounce your grandchildren
on your knee,
and, for that matter,
live to see your next birthday,
I say, "Go with me."
My company delivers
a product to the consumer
at a mutually agreeable price.
It's a private,
confidential transaction,
contracted and executed
right here in the United States.
-Organs from the black market?
-Ally!
Well, no, no. It's okay.
She's not wrong.
Let me leave you
with this thought.
Within the next
five to ten years,
the laws for the organ trade
will be revised.
And this exact transaction
will be legal.
It would be a shame
for you to sacrifice your life
because of old ideas
and defunct bureaucracy.
Let me leave you with
the paperwork for you to review.
A few signatures is all
we require to get started.
It's a lot to think about
and you really
should sleep on it.
Okay?
Okay.
It was a pleasure
meeting you, Ally.
-I'll walk you out.
-Thank you.
[Ally] How much does it cost?
[sighs]
Does that matter?
I can't lose your Ally, please.
I don't want to die.
Then don't.
Okay.
[sighs]
♪♪♪
I've got some great news.
We have found a match.
Rosa.
Congratulations, Rosa, you
just helped your entire family
get into the country.
Not the best part of town is it?
No. This is actually
a pretty safe neighborhood.
I think this is it,
up on the right here.
Any trouble finding the place?
No. I work the area.
[wheelchair's clattering]
-Morning, Mrs. Graves.
-Hi.
[elevator's bell]
[suspenseful music]
[door opening]
[Anthony] Try to settle in
and the doctor
will be with you shortly.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
[Anthony] Final installment?
Hi, I'm Doctor Bowman.
You must be Ally.
-Hi.
[door opening]
-[Bowman] Mister Graves.
-Yes.
Hi, Doctor Bowman.
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
So, you must be excited
to start your new life.
-But one thing at a time.
-[Bowman] Not to worry.
I've successfully performed
this procedure literally
hundreds of times.
It's best for you both,
if you just focus
on all the wonderful
moments that lay ahead.
Any kids?
-No.
-Not yet.
Ah! That's the spirit.
We were about to start
trying when I got sick.
Well, in a few months, you'll be
able to start right back up.
We'll have you home
before you know it.
[door opening]
[Bowman] Shall we?
We'll see you in there.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
[door opening and closing]
I love you.
[heart monitor]
[door opening]
All right.
On the count of three.
One, two, three.
Now, nice and easy.
[Anthony] Okay.
Is that my donor?
Yes, it is.
Can I meet her?
It's best if you don't.
So, Ally, what,
what were you doing?
You know,
before your kidneys failed?
Uh... I was a researcher.
Really? Interesting. What kind?
Social Anthropology.
I was about to go through
the stages of your recovery,
but I'm guessing that you...
-Got them printed out at home.
-[Bowman] Okay. Well, listen.
You just take it easy.
Nothing too physical for the
first few months. All right?
Anthony here is going
to take care of your anesthetic
and this will be over
in a blink.
Okay?
[suspenseful music]
No, no, no.
[Anthony] No. Just relax.
Just sit tight.
-No...
-[Anthony] Take it easy.
[Bowman]
We need to find the bleeder.
[heart monitor beeping]
[Anthony] BP's crashing.
[woman] We're losing her.
[heart monitor beeping]
[Bowman]
She's just bleeding out.
[heart monitor flatline sound]
[Bowman] Time of death?
[man] Does it really matter?
[heart monitor flatline sound]
No!
It's okay. It's okay.
It was just a dream.
Did something go wrong
with the operation?
No, everything went smoothly.
It was a huge success.
I got a glimpse of the donor.
She was so young.
I'm sure she had her reasons.
Now just try not to think
about it, okay?
What did you tell Kate?
I pulled some strings and
had you bumped up on the list.
Okay.
I made your appointment
with Doctor Hayworth.
Okay.
[sighs]
We did the right thing.
♪♪♪
It's a nice work.
I'm glad your husband
found another option.
Yeah, he's relentless.
It's what makes him
such a good detective.
Don't you want to know
where I got the kidney?
No. The less I know the better.
We're not crossing
some ethical boundary here?
I'm well within the law
to treat you post-op.
And, ethically,
I'm just glad you're okay.
Looks like you were
in good hands.
These meds...
should help the kidney take.
[sobs]
[woman cries]
[laughs]
[Kate sobs]
God, I don't care how you got
to the top of the list.
I'm just so thankful.
Me, too.
Ryan's a keeper.
[laughs]
So what are you going to do
once I'm better?
You have to get a life.
Oh, funny!
[laughs]
Come on.
Let's go get you drugged up.
[Ally grunts]
All right. I got it from here.
Okay. Are you sure?
Yeah. Thank you.
-[exhales]
-[woman] How did it go?
-[man] It will be okay.
-[heart monitor flatline sound]
-[woman] We're losing her.
-[man] She's just bleeding out!
[suspenseful music]
I just got a call. A Jane Doe.
It's on you two slackers.
Come on, Serge.
You know, we got--
I've passed you over twice
because of Graves' thing.
Everyone else is loaded up.
-It's out of my hands.
-We got it, Serge.
[Serge] All right.
Go down there. Get to it, guys.
How do they always
get here first?
[exhales]
Hey, Princess!
You coming?
[suspenseful music]
[Nelson] You guys worked hard.
[Nelson] Cara, doing good?
Say hello to your wife.
Got enough pictures?
-[Ryan] Time to take a break.
-[man] Thanks, Scott.
[Nelson] Oh! Very ripe.
She's been here a few days.
Damn! She's young.
Cause of death...
[suspenseful music]
[newscaster]
A young Hispanic Jane Doe
was uncovered
late this afternoon,
down an alley in East L.A.
Police aren't
ruling out homicide.
However, the remains showed
an incision indicating
that she may have had surgery
within the last 24 hours.
Detectives are looking
into the possibility
of human organ
trafficking as a motive.
[door opening]
[Ally] You've heard, right?
About what?
Don't be dense,
the girl in the alley.
It's all over the news.
-You should be resting.
-Ryan!
-It has nothing to do with you.
-Whose desk did it end up on?
Mine.
What did we do?
We didn't do anything, Ally.
Please just relax.
Are you serious?
We don't know anything yet.
It's probably not even
the same girl.
Until we find somebody
who can identify her body.
I can. I can identify her.
-Ally, stop.
-Ryan, I saw her face.
So, what if it is her?
What can we do?
I know you're playing naive
just to calm me down. So, stop.
Did she have the incision?
Ally, we're not having
this conversation.
-But if it's her, we can help.
-Enough!
Do you realize the position
that this puts me in?
I'm not the one
being naive here.
-It doesn't matter?
-It does to me!
We can lose everything!
-It's not worth it, Ally.
-[gasps]
Tell that to the girl we killed.
Ally, we can't
bring her back, okay?
So, just stop. Okay?
Stop whatever it is
that you think you need
to do and let it go.
I can't let it go.
Her kidney is keeping me alive.
What about her family?
What do you want me to do?
Send me a photo of her.
If it's not her, I will stop.
And if it is her?
One step at a time.
Fine.
♪♪♪
[typing]
[door opening]
-[Kate] Good morning.
-Hey!
Ryan's gone already?
Yeah, he got an early start.
He's making up for lost time.
Hey, there's somewhere
I need to go today.
Are you free to drive me?
Are you sure it's a good idea
you leave the house?
It's only been five days.
Yeah, I'm feeling pretty good.
A little exercise
will do me good.
Okay.
Where are we going?
I just want to check
something out.
Humor me.
[Ally] Pull up
next to that hotel.
No. Stay in the car.
I'll be right out.
-Ally, I'm not going to--
-Please. I'll be right out.
Okay, fine. But I'm going on
the record this is strange.
On the record?
Things must be going well
with the lawyer.
Funny!
Just hurry up.
[suspenseful music]
[unlocking the door]
[Bowman]
Oh! I can't find the bleeder.
This is really not good.
Forceps.
[Bowman] Hang on there, sweetie.
We can get it.
-[Anthony] Bleeding out.
-We're doing everything we can.
[Bowman] Ah!
-[Bowman] More gauze.
-[Anthony] BP's crashing.
[heart monitor beeping]
[Bowman] Ah!
-[Bowman] Ah!
-[Anthony] Come on,
she's bleeding out!
-[woman] We're losing her.
-[heart monitor flatline sound]
[Bowman] Time of death?
[man] Does it really matter?
[Ally sobs]
[suspenseful music]
[elevator's bell]
[man] Can I help you?
Actually, you can.
I was here last week
and there was this lovely
old man behind the desk.
Frank, yeah. But he doesn't
work here anymore.
Really?
He retired.
Oh.
Okay.
Did you need a room?
Just a bathroom.
-Around the corner.
-Thanks.
What's going on?
I never should
have agreed to it.
To what?
Ryan was so sure.
Ally?
There was a teenage girl found
dead here a couple of days ago.
It was on the news.
She was my donor.
I was so scared.
I didn't want to die.
And Ryan, he--
I wasn't ready.
I know.
But not like this.
We killed her, Kate.
-It's not your fault.
-Yes, it was.
No. Anyone in your shoes
would have done the same thing.
Doesn't make it right.
This girl made
the decision to donate. Okay?
If it wasn't you, it would
have been someone else.
It just feels so wrong.
Well, there's nothing
you can do about it now.
I have to find out
how this happened.
Ally, that sounds dangerous.
This isn't helping. Okay?
[Kate] So, let's get you home.
All right? Come on.
♪♪♪
This new guy you're dating...
Ben.
How do you think he'd react
to learning about my situation?
[sighs] I don't know.
Thanks for rushing the results.
I'll just add that to the pile
of favors you already owe me.
Tell me about the incision
on her side.
Missing a kidney and they nicked
her lung causing a collapse.
Then she bled out.
That's a botched transplant?
It's more common than you think.
Any other identifying marks?
No. This one's young.
No ink, scars.
-Nothing.
-How old?
Late teens. Sixteen, seventeen.
Oh, um, thank you. Thanks.
What's with him?
It's okay. His wife is just
going through renal failure.
Would you do me a favor?
Just send those to us, okay?
Ryan!
[suspenseful music]
[door opening]
What is all this?
-He is covering his tracks.
-Who?
His real name
is not James Dolan.
The real James Dolan
from Harvard,
he died six years ago,
in a car accident.
Yeah. So it's an alias, Ally.
I called that number.
The line is dead.
He had the concierge
at the hotel fired.
The rooms are
totally cleared out.
Ally, tell me you didn't
go to the hotel.
-I didn't drive. Kate took me.
-We talked about this.
You're supposed to be
focusing on your recovery.
-It's the same girl!
-I don't care!
Stop it.
Ryan, she's not the only one
this has happened to.
That's right.
She is not the only one
that this has happened to
because this sort
of thing happens, Ally.
These things happen.
They happen. I see it every day.
They don't happen to us!
Why is it so hard
for you to realize
that the further you dig,
the deeper the trouble
we get into?
Leave it alone. Please.
You know me better than that.
I'm not going
to leave this alone.
Then, it'll be
the end of us, Ally.
Think about that.
♪♪♪
[car approaching]
[speakers] Doctor Ivanesic,
dial extension 3-0-0-4.
[knocks on the door]
Come in.
Hey!
I was surprised when you
called. I thought we weren't
meeting until next week.
This couldn't wait.
Uh, so you said some
complications.
In a manner of speaking.
I don't follow.
Well, the kidney seems
to be taking, but...
I just can't come to terms
with how it all came to be.
Dealing with these desperate
situations day after day
must be... really frustrating.
I'm sorry, Ally.
I'm still not following you.
Watching your patients die
year after year because
of some out-of-date bureaucracy.
It's not my favorite
part of the job.
So, every now and then,
when you come across
a particularly desperate couple,
or say, husband,
it makes sense
that you would do what you did.
I might have done the same.
Which is?
Don't play me, Doctor Hayworth.
I know you guided
my husband to James Dolan.
Who?
James Dolan, the broker
who sold us the kidney?
Ally, if you think
that I had anything to do
with how you got your kidney,
then you've been
sadly misinformed.
This is the young girl whose
kidney is now inside of me.
She couldn't have been
more than seventeen.
-That's awful.
-Yes, it is.
I can't live with myself.
How do you do it?
I'm not sure
what you want from me?
I want to make sure this
doesn't happen again.
I have nothing to do with this.
My husband came to you.
And I told him
I couldn't help him.
You expect me to believe that?
It's the truth. Ask him.
All right.
I know about Dolan's
fake identity, the hotel.
It's just a matter of time
before I uncover the rest.
I wish I could help.
I'm building a case
with the District Attorney.
So, you're going to have
to decide which side
you're going to end up on.
[Ally] Think about it.
-Don't forget your folder.
-Keep it.
[speakers] Orderly to receiving.
Orderly to receiving.
[suspenseful music]
We're supposed
to be saving lives.
What is this?
-What the hell happened?
-I'll look into it. Okay?
I'll take care of it.
Just keep your cool.
[Anthony] Relax.
[elevator's bell]
[suspenseful music]
[Nelson] You know
that's a waste of time.
These organs come in
from all over the world.
-[telephone ringing]
-Yeah. I know.
[telephone ringing]
[sighs] Homicide.
Yeah.
Really?
Oh, okay. Okay.
Yeah, thanks.
[Nelson] I think they got
an ID on the Jane Doe.
How about that?
[steps approaching]
[woman] Diego.
[Diego cries]
[cries]
He got it.
I'll take it.
All right. Thanks.
[door opening]
♪♪♪
[alarm]
[cellphone ringing]
[priest] May I help you?
Oh, hi. No, I was
just looking around.
For anything in particular?
No. I thought I saw a woman
come in here who I know.
A woman?
Yeah. With brown hair,
very pretty.
Perhaps if you had a name.
[Ally grunts]
Pardon me for asking,
but are you all right?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
Well, I can have someone
take a look at that for you.
No, no, no, really. I'm fine.
I should go anyway.
Okay.
Feel free to stop by anytime.
Our doors are always open.
Oh, thank you.
That was the Graves woman.
-What did she want?
-She's snooping around.
She must have followed Anthony
from the hospital.
What do we do?
I'm going to call Dolan.
Damn it!
-[door opening]
-[Kate] Ally.
Yeah, I'll be right out.
Hey, did you get my message?
-No. Sorry my phone was off.
-It's okay.
It's great to finally
meet you, Ben.
You too. I've heard
a lot about you.
Yeah.
-Hi.
-Hi. Come on in.
Please, sit down.
Can I get you anything?
-No. I'm fine, thank you.
-[Ally] Okay.
[Ben sighs]
So, Kate's given me a brief
overview of your situation.
This conversation has to be
completely off the record.
The less details
I know the better.
All right.
My goal is to bring
the broker to justice.
Without involving yourself
or your husband,
who's a detective, right?
Yes. I'm not concerned
about myself, but the less
he's involved the better.
But I'm going to need
first-hand evidence
implicating broker, sellers,
and a complete understanding
of the infrastructure
to build a proper case.
Yeah. I'm working on that.
I'm sorry.
Isn't that more your husband's
area of expertise?
I'm just gathering some data
being as I am the one
who went through the process.
Of course.
You know, there may also be
some considerations
for testifying and helping
the city put the case together.
I could send you over
some basic legal guidelines.
You could sit down
with your family and discuss
how you want to move forward.
Thanks, Ben.
Well, let's just let you
get some rest then.
-[Ben] Yeah.
-Okay.
Thank you again.
-My pleasure.
-It's a pleasure.
Let me know if you need
anything. Okay?
[Ally] I will. I will. I will.
[Ben] Thank you.
[whispering] He's cute.
[grunts]
Hey, you!
Hey, sorry. Go back to sleep.
It's okay.
Nice choice
of reading materials.
How was your day?
Not great.
What happened?
This thing that we did, I...
I don't know how to--
[sighs]
It's just always there.
It's 'cause you're
one of the good guys.
Her name is Rosa Garcia.
Seventeen.
Her father came in
and identified her body today.
It broke my heart.
Why did he let her do it?
I don't know.
He's not talking.
[sighs]
I know it's hard for you,
but I have to do something.
I understand.
You shouldn't have
to do it alone.
So, why don't you show me
everything you have
and we'll do it together.
Thank you.
I know.
Most of my research is
in a folder on the coffee table.
Okay. I'll bring it in
to work tomorrow.
See what I can do.
I think it all centers around
a church near Huntington Park.
Church?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
it's a cover.
Okay, get some rest.
I'll be right in.
[Dolan] So?
She's been doing some digging?
-Not the husband?
-Doesn't seem like it.
She was alone at the hospital.
It won't be good
for him if this came out.
She says she's working
with the DA on this.
-Seriously?
-That's what Anthony says.
Huh, I'll find out.
Well, what should we do?
Business as usual.
It's time to pay Mrs. Graves
a follow-up visit.
[knocks on the door]
[suspenseful music]
-Good morning.
This is pretty thorough stuff.
[Ben sighs] I'm off.
-I'll check in this afternoon.
-Okay.
I want another one.
-One more.
-[laughs]
[suspenseful music]
[knocks on the door]
Mister Dolan.
Beautiful morning, isn't it?
I wasn't expecting you.
Oh, standard follow-up.
Just want to make sure
everything's taking.
Do you mind?
Don't mind my associate.
Can I get you anything?
Tea? Coffee?
No, no. We're fine.
-Excuse the mess.
-Oh, please.
[Dolan sighs]
So, how are you feeling?
I'm doing well.
Getting stronger and stronger
each day.
Excellent!
Now, have you been
to see the doctor to get
the proper prescription?
Yes.
Because most of these
won't take without
the proper medication.
I'm covered. Thanks.
Good.
Wow! Do you remember
what it was like
when you had no hope
and no alternatives?
Such a scary place.
I mean, that makes you realize
how important it is to be...
to be grateful for what we have.
-Don't you agree?
-I do.
Well, then.
Everything is as it should be.
Another satisfied customer.
[chuckles]
No wait.
There is just one little thing
we need to clear off.
And I'll speak plainly so there
can be no misunderstanding.
Accidents happen.
That's all this was.
Now, an accident can be tragic
and difficult to deal with,
but it's called an accident
because it's out of our control.
Unfortunately, it's the price
of doing business.
Understand?
Good.
So, no more digging,
no more threatening the people,
who helped save your life.
It's so disrespectful.
[laughing] The DA.
Really?
Well, we both know that's a lie.
Consider this a warning. Okay?
Good.
You should focus
on your recovery.
Forget the past.
Look to the future.
Okay.
Well, then. I think we've
taken up enough of your time.
You have a wonderful
rest of the day.
What are you doing?
I thought this was
something else.
It's not.
You've been looking
through it all morning.
Maybe.
Seems like there is a little
something to do with our case.
Is there something
you want to tell me?
No. Not really.
We got company here.
This guy's dressed
too nice to be a cop.
-Detective Graves?
-Yeah.
ADA Martin. Can I have a word?
We'll go right on out there.
Kate brought me over to have
a conversation with Ally.
Look, you're so far gone,
you don't even know
who you're dealing with.
What?
The Milano crime family.
James Dolan is Dominic Pino,
a major earner.
We've had him
in our sights for years.
You've seen one of his
operations from the inside.
Find someone you can flip
and we'll do everything
we can to keep you
and your wife out of it.
All right.
Hey.
-[elevator's bell]
-Thank you.
So?
There's something
I have to tell you.
[suspenseful music]
[Ally] Nothing. Thanks.
How'd you find me?
I looked up the bars
closest to your place.
You know there are two
that are much closer.
I like the ambiance.
Does that help with the guilt?
Ask me in an hour.
What went wrong?
This can't be worth it.
-What do you want?
-I need your help.
Lady, my job is done.
She was only seventeen.
This has got to stop.
Now that you have
your kidney, of course.
If I could do it again...
-I'd--
-Have died.
If it wasn't you, it would
have been someone else.
I have to do something.
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
Everyone keeps telling me
to look to the future.
Good advice.
You should do the same.
[chuckles]
This is going down,
one way or another,
that I can guarantee.
You need to decide what side you
want to end up on when it does.
Wait.
I could use some fresh air.
-[Ally] Excuse me.
-Hey, pal!
[priest] We got a match.
We just got to find a doctor.
[woman] I got the word out.
Look, she's coming too.
[blowing]
Hey, hey!
[priest] Welcome back, Ally.
You want to scream? Go ahead.
Get it out of your system.
My husband is a cop.
No. You'll be gone long
before he ever finds you.
Hey, Doc!
How long before this organ
rejects without the meds?
[kicks] Answer the question.
How long?
Could happen anytime.
Now, don't you go dying on me?
-You have a good kidney--
-Okay. That's enough.
I'll tell you when it's enough.
Well, we've got work to do.
Ally!
Baby, I've been
calling you all day.
Ally!
[suspenseful music]
Oh!
Oh, no! No, no.
What did you do?
[cellphone ringing]
[Kate] Hey, Ryan.
Hi. Kate, is Ally with you?
- No.
-Do you know where she is?
She's not at home?
Ryan, what's going on?
I don't know. She's not
answering her cell phone.
Bowman.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Where do you think we are?
Does it matter?
Excuse me, I'm looking
for Doctor Hayworth.
Oh, he's not here anymore.
I don't understand.
Was his office moved?
No. He was transferred, I think.
There was a nurse, an orderly.
His name was Anthony.
Anthony?
He is a tall guy, closely
cropped hair about this high.
I don't think we ever had
an Anthony working here.
Do you know where
Dr. Hayworth was transferred to?
That's admin's department.
You can check with them
in the morning.
All right. This is James Dolan's
known addresses.
Any of these addresses pop,
let me know.
That's what I'm passing on.
[Nelson] Alrighty.
Oh, thank god!
Do we know anything?
-No. Not yet. Thanks, guys.
-What do you want us to do?
We need to find James Dolan.
We'll focus on
the out-of-the-way places.
The warehouses, the docks.
We're going to take the top two.
Yeah. That's good.
We'll focus on East LA.
Perfect. Guys, listen to me.
This is a potential
hostage situation.
If anything seems
strange or off, call it in.
Come on. Let's go find her.
[sirens wailing]
[suspenseful music]
-[shot]
-Ah!
Nothing.
[door opens]
[thump]
[steps approaching]
[suspenseful music]
You just couldn't
leave it alone.
[Dolan sighs]
Do you have any idea
how hard it is to find
a good doctor?
I mean, all you had to do
is look the other way and none
of this would have happened.
But you had to keep prying.
Still viable?
Yeah.
This won't end with me.
The wheel's just going
to keep on turning.
Don't think I've not been
through this before, Ally.
My husband has
all the information I gathered.
He will expose you.
Yeah.
Your husband's going to hit
a long list of dead ends.
No pun intended.
[knock on the door]
Got a new doctor.
Well, that wasn't
as hard as I thought.
Perfect.
Prep her. The new doctor
can whip out this organ
and we can have
this done before lunch.
[woman] Okay.
Well, Ally.
Looks like you're
going to get your wish.
We're going
to take back the organ.
Then you can clear that
overbearing conscience of yours.
[door closing]
[suspenseful music]
May we help you?
[shots]
[distant shooting]
♪♪♪
[radio] Shots fired in a church
near Huntington Park.
Shots fired.
All units in the area respond.
Repeat. Shots fired.
-They said the church.
-What church?
Ally said it all centered
around a church.
-[sirens wailing]
-[Ryan] Come on. Let's go!
[priest] I was almost
frightened for my life.
I mean I've never
seen anything like it.
You know, I'm...
[Ryan] We'll take it from here.
Thanks.
Detective Ryan Graves.
My partner, Detective Nelson.
Detectives.
That's right.
We were in the area when
we heard the call from Dispatch.
So, why don't you
walk me through exactly
what happened here?
[grunts]
[suspenseful music]
So, he didn't say anything?
He just...
He walked in mumbling something
that sounded
like a Lord's Prayer.
Then he just opened fire.
Miracle nobody got hurt.
Thank, God!
What are these doors to here?
This one here,
that's to the basement.
We have just bake sales
and neighborhood programs.
That sort of thing.
[suspenseful music]
[loading weapon]
Shh.
[Nelson] Ryan, come on.
Let the unit handle it.
One of these Dolan's addresses
is actually in the neighborhood.
Let's check this out.
We'll put a call
into the station.
We'll get the number
for that church
that Ally has in her files.
[Nelson] Yeah, okay.
-[Ryan] Thank you, Father.
-Thank you.
Thanks, Father. And go with God.
-[Nelson] Hey, Ryan.
-Surround the building.
This is the place. She's here.
Call for back-up.
Go around the side.
No one comes out.
Freeze!
[Nelson] Hey, come on!
[knocks] Open!
Come on in!
They are coming.
[suspenseful music]
[thumps]
It's over! SWAT is on the way.
Oh, God.
It's going to be okay.
[Dolan] Put your guns down.
She's dead if you don't.
All right.
Everyone just stay calm.
We are all getting out
of here or she dies.
No. This isn't going down
how you want it to.
What the hell are you doing?
[shot]
[Ryan] Get down. Now!
Easy.
[sighs]
What took you so long?
I'm sorry.
-I need my meds.
-I know. I know.
[Ryan] I got you. I got you.
[Ryan] Okay,
sit down right here.
They're going to take
a look at you. Okay?
Who is that?
He's Diego Garcia.
He's Rosa's father.
What's he doing
in the back of the car?
Mister Garcia, could you come
out please? Watch your head.
Okay.
Hey, listen to me.
Don't worry about him, okay?
You just worry
about getting better.
[unlocking handcuffs]
Ally!
I'm so sorry
about your daughter, Rosa.
Rosa.
If I could go back,
I would trade my life for hers.
I'm so sorry.
[Ryan] Mister Garcia...
you're free to go.
Just leaving?
That's right.
♪♪♪
[speaker] Paging,
Doctor Greenberg. Report...
Shouldn't you be on work?
And miss all the excitement?
Besides, I get the feeling
that I can't leave you alone...
for a second.
[door opening]
Inappropriate.
[Ryan] Come on.
Let's get you home.
Thanks, Doc.
Thank you.
[newscaster] In local news,
the DA's office made a breakthrough in the kidnapping of a Los Angeles woman
which led police
to uncover an international
organ trafficking ring.
Deputy District Attorney,
Ben Martin,
is prosecuting the case
against Dominic Pino.
We'll prosecute the case to
the fullest extent of the law.
Our evidence is overwhelming
and we will be charging Mr. Pino with multiple counts of murder,
trafficking, mayhem
and kidnapping.
That's all we have, folks.
Isn't he cute?
He's all right, for a lawyer.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
♪♪♪