[music playing]
[MUSIC - THE COASTERS,
"SEARCHIN'"]
Going to find her.
[car honking] Going to find her.
I'm going to find her.
Well, I've been searching.
I've been searching.
Oh, yeah, searching
every which way.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I've been searching.
Searching.
I've been searching
every which way.
I'm like a Northwest Mountie.
You know I'll bring her in.
I'm going to find her.
Well, now if I have to swim
the river, then know I will.
And if I have to climb a
mountain, you know I will.
And if she's hiding
up on Blueberry Hill,
am I going to find that child?
You know...
Hey, Vic, what you doing here?
That's my stop.
It's OK, Fly.
We took care of it.
[MUSIC - THE COASTERS,
"SEARCHIN'"]
Smile.
I'm like that Northwest Mountie.
[explosion]
You know I'll bring her in.
I'm going to find her.
[car siren]
SAL: Hey, come on, Fly, will ya?
Yeah.
Hurry up, will you, Jack?
Yeah, sure.
Go ahead.
VIC: Hey, Fly,
hurry the fuck up.
MAN: Don't forget the Martini.
[MUSIC - BROOK BENTON, "IT'S
JUST A MATTER OF TIME"]
Some day, some way, you'll
realize that you've been blind.
Yes, darling, you're
going to need me again.
It's just a matter of time.
Oh.
You spill one drop, jerk off,
and you're going to lick it up.
Come on, Fly.
You can do it.
Come on.
I see a drop, Fly.
I see a drop.
There it is.
Come on.
Get the wings going, baby.
Fly man, all right.
You know something, Fly?
You win the grand prize for
the ugliest fucking waitress
I've ever seen in my life.
[laughter]
I ain't a fucking waitress, Sal.
Ah!
You are whatever the
hell I say you are.
Ah!
If I say you're a
waitress, then so be it.
Yeah.
Never talk back to me, Fly.
Because you know where these
are going to end up, don't you?
Yeah.
Give the lady a drink.
Show her what a good
fucking waitress you are.
Ah.
Ah!
[laughter]
[grunting]
That's very good, Fly.
You're going to stand
there like a fucking moron?
[laughter]
Hey, Fly.
I want you to go see Joey.
Tell him I want three
pictures this week, not two.
Tell him to stop
jerking off to his work.
Take Mickey with you, too.
Why do you call him Fly?
Why don't you tell her, Vic.
Because flies eat shit.
[laughter]
[music playing]
Here you go.
It's all yours.
What is it?
It's your lunch.
Where's Joey?
The editing room.
It's Mickey.
Put him on the shelf.
Shake those things.
I'm shaking them.
Shit.
Come on, baby. turn around.
Ow!
Keep still.
I'm trying to read.
FRANKIE: Hi, Margaret.
MARGARET: Oh, hi, Frankie.
JOEY: OK, action.
Wait.
JOEY: OK.
Reslate it.
FRANKIE: She's pretty good.
Oh, yeah.
She's a regular Meryl Streep.
Her concept of improvisation
is sticking a dick in her mouth
sideways.
So what brings you around, Fly?
I had to drop off
a case rubbers..
Of course you did.
We do want to appear to be
safe-sex conscious in case
the kiddies see.
I had to bring Mickey over, too.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
He's the sickest most
perverted son of a bitch
I've ever fucking seen.
He has a strange
way of showing power.
Fly, keeping your enemy's
nuts in a jar on a shelf
is not an expression of power.
It's just a sick and
demented act created
by a sick and demented person.
By the way, Sal
told me to tell you
that you're working too slow.
He says that you're
not meeting his quota.
Too fucking slow?
What does he fucking think
I am, the miracle worker?
Do you know how many hours I
spend with these derelicts just
trying to get them to
suck a little bit of cock
without falling asleep, trying
to get them to look the least
bit excited, and on top of that,
having the incessant burden
of trying to get them speak?
Gah.
They're related?
I did not say incest.
I said... forget it.
You're too sensitive.
I'm supposed to be
fucking sensitive.
I'm a director.
I'm an NYU film
graduate, not some Ellis
Island fucking tutor...
Used to working with artists,
people who give a shit about
their work, insightful
people who want to expand
the boundaries of
their creativity,
not hacking together fuck
flicks for the third world.
You are some ass piece of baby.
Ugh.
I can't...
JOEY: Piece of of ass,
Hans, piece of ass.
You are piece of some ass, baby.
Piece of ass.
JOEY: Jesus Christ,
get him a script.
You know, I might be
able to dub in his voice,
I mean, give him a
more American quality.
Please, Fly.
I almost forgot.
Sal also said to tell you that
the check ain't in the mail.
He hasn't paid me
in a fucking month.
He cannot keep me caged up here
like some laboratory fucking
rat content with a few acorns.
It ain't that bad.
I cannot live
without money, moron.
Joey, there is no reason
to talk to me like that...
No reason.
Now you know you
should never have
gotten that deep in the hole
with Sal in the first place.
You have got nobody
to blame but yourself.
I swear to God, Fly.
Somebody must have
fucking cursed me.
I've never seen a losing
streak like that in my life.
I don't know how you're
ever going to get out.
It's not exactly what I wanted
to fucking hear right now, Fly.
OK?
How much is it, 100 Jesus, huh?
What?
Excuse me, Joey, but how
long before we start again?
Why, Margaret?
Do you have an etiquette
class you have to go to?
Don't be so smart.
I just want to run down
and get a cup of coffee.
Bullshit, a cup of
coffee... she wants to run
down there and get fucked up.
I do not.
I'm just a little tired.
That's all.
Margaret, please
explain to me how
on Earth you could be tired.
You've been on your back
the whole goddamn day.
Hey, if you think it's
so easy on the other end
of that horse cock, you do it.
Could probably do a better job.
Come to think of it,
you probably would.
You calling me a faggot?
If the shoe fits.
You fucking cunt.
- You fucking cunt.
- Hey, hey, look...
I'll go get the coffee.
There's problem.
You ungrateful bastard.
Hey, come on, you guys.
Cool it, will you, you know?
You better watch
your mouth, punkin.
That's delusive outfit
is getting to your head.
Asshole.
Hey.
Misfits... just one
of my fucking misfits.
Hey, Margaret, wait up.
I'll go with you.
It's OK, Frankie.
I can go by myself.
Nah, let me go with you.
You don't know.
I mean, this is a
bad neighborhood.
Come on, baby.
It's a New York thing.
Thank you.
[car honking]
[spanish music playing]
Well, there you go...
Straight from the tar pit.
Thank you.
Oh, you want to sit down here?
I guess Fellini can wait, right?
I mean, what's the jerk off
going to do, start without me?
Wait.
Frankie, I can't sit on that.
That's a good jacket.
Good butt deserves
a good jacket.
Hope I don't get
any jelly on it.
What?
Just kidding... I washed.
- Oh.
- Here... feel.
No.
No, that's all right.
I trust you.
How come you get so nervous?
I'm not nervous.
Come on.
Touch my butt.
No, I don't want to.
See, you're nervous.
No, I'm not.
Are too.
How come i never see
you with any girls?
I don't know.
I got 'em.
Bullshit.
I just don't want
to bring them around.
That's all.
I like you, Frankie.
You're a nice man.
You know, of all the
people that I know,
you're the only one that
calls me Frankie, not Fly.
Does it bother you?
What?
That they call you Fly?
It's a little late for that.
No, it's not.
You can change things
if you want to.
It's never too late.
I used to know this guy...
Used to pay me $200 to put
one of these up my butt
so he could eat it.
He used to come by every
Thursday afternoon.
He never took his
clothes off either.
Want a bite?
No, thank you.
What's the matter with you?
Oh, I just don't
feel like talking
about that derelict shit.
What are you insinuating?
I mean, well, you participate
in that kind of shit,
it don't look good.
You trying to say I'm a
fucking derelict or something?
No.
- I'm no fucking derelict.
- No.
All I meant to say was...
All you meant was I'm a
fucking derelict, Frankie.
Don't deny it.
- No.
No.
I never said that
you were a derelict.
Yes, you did.
You said I'm a fucking derelict.
You said I participate.
I mean, who the fuck are you,
some kind of morals committee
or something, sitting there
in your $3.00 suit, all
high and mighty, judging me?
I'm not judging.
What I do don't hurt nobody, OK?
I don't treat nobody bad
unless they want it that way,
unlike you and your friends...
Fucking animals.
You treat yourself bad.
I'm making a living,
Frankie, the best way I know.
You put that shit in your arm.
That's dying.
That ain't living.
Do you see me putting
that shit in my arm, huh?
Do you see me?
I'm talking...
Hey, no, no.
Don't you fucking hit me.
Well, then answer the question.
Do you see me doing dope?
Not lately.
Not lately... that's right.
Because I've been straight
for eight fucking weeks, OK?
I'm kicking that shit.
Do you understand?
I'm kicking it.
That's good.
I'm saving my money.
And I'm going to get
the fuck out of here.
I came out here to
be an actress, OK,
not a junkie, only I
got a little off track.
[car honking]
JOEY: Carlos, my friend.
Come on, guys.
I'll make it worth your while.
Goddamn it.
Hello, Joey.
How are you today?
Euphoric.
I live for days like this.
Well, that's good.
Every day above ground
is a good one, right?
Regular utopia.
Will that be all?
Unless, Miguel, you can
find one of your amigos
to make a horse bet for you.
Why would I do that?
I don't bet horse.
I know you don't bet horse.
You wouldn't be betting horse.
I'd be paying for it.
Joey, I already
have six children.
It will do me no good to
have my nuts cut off by Sal.
Sal's not...
Joey, please.
Have a nice day.
You, too.
Hell.
No.
You know what your problem is?
You ask too much
of people, Joey.
[car honking]
All right.
I'll come over, you know?
I mean, it's Friday.
I GOT to make my rounds
first, all right?
OK, Joey, Joey, Joey, Joey, is...
Is Margaret working today?
Yeah, oh, good.
Good.
Yeah.
No, I just wondered.
OK.
All right.
Thanks.
Yeah, thanks.
Yeah.
[music - "hey, baby"]
Hey.
Hey, baby.
I wanna know if
you'll be my girl.
Hey.
And action.
Hans.
Number two.
You called my name.
I opened the door.
What do you want me?
[music - "hey, baby"]
Be my girl.
When I saw you walking
down the street,
I said that's the kind
of girl I like to meet.
She's so pretty.
Lord, she's fine.
I'm going to make
her mine, all mine.
Hey.
- Whoa.
Whoa.
Relax, all right?
Come on.
Take it easy.
Yeah.
[gunshots]
[music - "hey, baby"]
If you'll be my girl.
I don't understand this.
This never happens to me.
[music - "hey, baby"]
Turned and walked away.
There's something
that I want to say.
Come on, baby, give me a whirl.
Hey, how you doing?
[music - "hey, baby"] I want
to know if you'll be my girl.
Hey.
[yelling]
Baby.
I want to know if
you'll be my girl.
[tires squealing]
[horns honking]
You've go to say it.
I will not.
It's stupid.
You are the most incredulous
bitch I have ever known.
What's going on?
Artistic differences.
MARGARET: I know what
incredulous means, asshole.
I know what incredulous
means, you asshole.
How did you learn
it, graduate school?
MARGARET: Very funny.
You are the most insecure,
talentless loser!
Hey, hey, what's the matter?
Garbo here does
not like the script.
It's the same corny
shit I say every time.
Excuse me, sir.
I have this tickle in my throat.
Do you have something I
could scratch it with?
Since when, Margaret,
did you ever give a shit
about anything you say or do?
- Hey.
Hey.
Don't fight, you guys.
Excuse me, but could somebody
get me out of this, please?
Shut up.
Ow.
Joey, take it easy.
You're going to hurt somebody.
- He doesn't care.
He's an animal.
You know, Margaret, when
you were a much better
actress when you were high.
You'd know exactly when
to open your mouth,
and exactly when to shut it.
You would love to see
me break, wouldn't you?
The only thing I'd like to see
you break is your fucking neck.
There is no need
to be nasty, Joey.
Fly, mind your own
business right now.
Maybe you should rewrite it.
Rewrite what?
The scene.
God forbid, Mr. NYU.
Fly, this is the last fucking
thing I need right now, OK?
Margaret!
MARGARET: Fuck off.
OK.
I'll leave.
No.
Come on.
I got to talk to you.
- All right.
OK.
But settle down.
Calm down, OK?
- OK.
I'm calm.
And don't pull on my jacket.
OK.
I'm not pulling on your jacket.
Where did you get that?
I've been saving
every nickel and dime
I could get my grubby
little fucking hands on.
Now please, just put it
on the fourth horse in
the seventh race, Sudden Fury.
And I swear to God, I will
not ask you for another favor.
Joey, you're not
such a lucky guy.
You should really think that.
Fuck thinking about it, Frankie.
Come on, just do it.
If Sal gets wind of
this, we're both dead.
Sal's not going to find out.
Besides, my horse is
going to fucking win.
I'll pay him a little
more money back.
He'll be happier than a fucking
gerbil in West Hollywood.
Come on, Frankie, please.
And if he loses, then
you're behind even more.
Frankie, he's the
only chance I got.
I bet my way into this hole.
I gotta bet my way out of it.
This is a big favor
I'm doing here, Joey.
This is a very, very big favor.
What do you want me to
do, Frankie, suck your cock?
I don't play with that
shit, Joey, not with guys.
And you know that.
Frankie, I was not
serious, fucking idiot.
Oh.
Come on, man.
The race is at 4:30.
You got to be there at 4:00.
Don't be late.
- Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
What?
Well, it seems like I'm
taking all the chances here,
all of the risk.
And I'm not sure why.
What do you want, Frankie?
Come on... spit it out.
What do you want?
I want to write a movie script.
What?
[car honking]
That's a great idea.
I mean really...
Really?
Absolutely.
I mean, who knows what kind of
talents might surface there?
You think so?
Yeah.
You know what?
Second you get back
from the track,
you and I will talk about it.
Nah.
JOEY: Frankie.
Frankie, look.
You got my word, OK?
You can write the script.
You've got my word.
[cheering]
[MUSIC - LITTLE RICHARD, "KEEP A
KNOCKIN'"]
Keep a knockin' but
you can't come in.
You keep it close, huh?
No problem.
OK.
I'll be right back.
- All right.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Hey, you take it
real easy with it, OK?
No problem.
[tires squealing] - Hey!
Hey!
Come back!
[tires squealing]
Hey!
[MUSIC - LITTLE RICHARD, "KEEP A
KNOCKIN'"]
Keep a knockin' but
you can't come in.
Come back tomorrow
night and try it again.
What are you, crazy?
Give me the goddamn keys.
I told you to take it easy.
Get out.
Don't you know a
goddamn vintage fucking
automobile when you see one?
I guess.
You don't guess.
It is.
Do you have any idea why it
looks as good as it does?
Cause I don't zoom it around
like some goddamn Hot Wheels.
I take care of it, which
is possibly a concept
that you can't understand.
Sounds like fucking
Chinese to you, don't it?
You ain't got the slightest
idea what in the world
respect means, do you, huh?
Well, let me give
you a little fact.
That's why the world
is turning to shit.
Because you kids, you got
no respect for nothing...
No respect.
Nothing lasts.
You got no Sinatras.
You got no Elvises.
You got nothing.
Here today, gone tomorrow.
It's all just... it's all just
a quick fix, no tradition.
Now you give me my money back.
Get a haircut.
Yo, how much time
before the fourth race?
Just went off.
Who won?
Sudden Fury, that
fucking pig bastard.
Fuck.
Is Sal here, Jack?
Yeah.
He's in his office.
Thanks, Jack.
Sal?
SAL: (SINGING) Oh.
Come, darling.
Oh.
Sal?
SAL: What?
What do you want?
Speak.
I want to make a loan.
SAL: A loan?
For what?
I don't know.
I... I got some
things I want to do.
SAL: Well, what kind of things?
Things, like...
SAL: Why are you
being so evasive?
You trying to hide
something from me, Fly?
How much you want?
$6,000.
SAL: Oh, god.
That's enough.
Oh.
You have no future
in show business.
Can I try again?
I'll get it right.
I promise.
- No.
Get out.
Maybe I made her nervous.
Huh?
She's got teeth like a beaver.
[laughs] That's a
lot of money, Fly.
[inaudible]
[laughs] Oh, Mickey lost his
nuts for a lot less than that.
I'm not looking to lose
my nuts, you know, Sal?
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Hey, come on.
I'm not planning to
lose my nuts, Sal.
Huh?
Yeah, well, neither was he.
You should have seen his face.
I'll do this for you,
Fly, because I like you.
Hey, I like you.
What are you, queer?
Come on, no.
What are you doing?
[laughs]
I'm just checking.
When do you want it?
I want it now.
I hope for your sake, you're
spend your money wisely.
I hate to see you make a
bad investment, you know?
Well, I appreciate this, Sal.
Thanks.
Don't make me spot you, Fly.
I'll spot you bad.
I heard the results
on the radio...
$6,230.
Jesus Christ.
I almost came in my pants.
You fucking counting?
I mean, it's all there.
I just want to feel it.
Do you mind?
Where do you think Margaret is?
Hopefully at the
vets, getting shots.
Hey, try to be
nice, will you, Joey?
She's a nice girl.
Sure she is, Frankie.
She's a fucking junkie.
What the fuck are you?
Touche.
Then you.
Should heed my words even
more closely, my friend...
Once a junkie, always a junkie.
It's just a matter of degree.
We still got a deal, right?
Of courses we got a deal, Fly.
A deal is a deal.
Don't call me Fly.
My name is Frankie.
You really going
to do this for me?
Why not?
And Joey's going to go along?
Loves the idea.
Loves?
What about Sal?
Yeah, well, we're
going to kind of like not
tell Sal till we got
a more solid story.
You're getting my hopes up
again, Frankie, you know that?
Hey, you got to
have hopes, right?
Oh, it sure would be nice...
Get a good piece of
tape of myself, who
people what I can do, you know?
Be like the next Jodie Foster.
Yeah, maybe, although she
was awful good in that movie,
um, the one where
the guy ate people.
I can do that kind of stuff.
Eat people?
No, drama things.
Oh.
No, I'm not saying
that you can't.
Because that's what I came
out here to do, you know,
serious things like...
I know.
I'm not just some low
life who's got no talent.
I know that Hey, timing
is everything, right?
Maybe this is our time...
Make some noise in this town.
Yeah.
It is.
What's the matter?
I'm fine.
Hey, you OK?
I just... I don't feel...
What... Margaret?
Margaret?
Oh.
My god.
Oh, my god.
Oh, shit.
Somebody call an ambulance!
Hey, you OK?
Come on, Margaret, please.
Don't do this.
Someone hurry up.
Hurry the fuck up, will ya?
[door opening]
Is there a problem here?
FRANKIE: Look.
I'd like a little
more coffee, please.
What are you doing?
You were just dead there.
- We're fine.
I'd just like a little
more decaf, please.
Yeah.
What the hell was
that all about?
I was good, wasn't I?
You give me a freaking
heart attack here.
I told you I could do drama.
Nah, it's not funny, Margaret.
You scared the shit out of me.
I was just playing.
Yeah, well, don't play
with people's hearts.
Oh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Frankie.
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
Hey Here you go.
Be right back.
Hey, buddy.
Get the door for
the lady, will you?
Thank you.
Well, thanks for dinner.
It was great.
It was the best I've
had in a long time.
Well, hopefully we'll be
able to do that again sometime.
I would love that.
And I'll behave.
I promise.
Oh, yeah.
Great.
All the luck, huh?
OK.
See ya.
Hey.
OK.
Good night and sleep tight.
And don't let the bed bugs bite.
- OK.
OK?
All right.
Whoa!
Huh.
Ah!
Whew.
Hell, I see you
all are bent to...
OK.
Oh, hell, I see that
you all are bent to set
against me in your merriment.
Can you not hate me,
as I know you do?
Then...
MAN: Shut the fuck up, lady.
Hey.
Can you... can you not
hate me, as I know you do?
But you was...
[muttering]
Oh.
What are you writing...
Secrets?
Nah.
Ideas.
Ideas?
Yeah, ideas.
Well, what kind of ideas?
I don't know.
What do you mean, I don't know?
What, are you a fucking parrot?
I said I don't know.
How could you not know?
They're your ideas.
Because they haven't
come to me yet, you see?
That's what an idea is.
It's something you don't
know but comes to you.
Comes to you how?
It's an idea.
Well, how can an idea
come to you if you're
not thinking of something?
Oh, I'm thinking of something.
What?
An idea.
Fly, [inaudible] one more
fucking time, and I'll slap
your fucking head in.
Look, did anybody ever say to
you, don't get any ideas, huh?
Of course.
OK.
So what does that mean to you?
Tell me.
All right.
What it means is this.
Don't think anything.
Now that doesn't necessarily
mean that you're thinking
anything in particular.
It means don't
think anything new.
And that also does not assume
that you have any old ideas.
Because you can actually be
thinking of nothing, g you know,
just space out.
And then suddenly when you
least expect it, an idea...
Huh... pops up.
Because it's what ideas do...
They pop up.
And that's what I'm doing here.
You know, sitting here,
waiting for an idea,
thinking of nothing.
Capisce?
I get it.
Hey, I got an idea.
Yeah.
Get me a fucking drink.
Hey, there you go.
See, that's an idea.
And that gives me an idea.
Fuck you.
Get it yourself.
You see how it works.
[laughs]
That's very good,
Fly, very good.
Problem is that wasn't
a very good idea.
See how it works?
You're right.
What would you like?
The usual.
Good.
Then if you'll excuse me
now, I'll be right back.
Excused.
Hey, Jack.
Yeah.
Give me a scotch, will ya?
Do me a favor.
Piss in it.
I already pissed in the bottle.
Don't want to
dilute it too much.
[chuckle]
Left some of your
empties on the set.
If Fly comes by,
tell him to wait.
[door closing]
Here.
Really?
I think so, I'll go tell him.
Yo.
Yo, Sal.
[car honking]
[coins in pay phone]
Come on.
Pick up the phone.
Goddamn it, Fly.
Fuck.
[car honking]
Hey, Joe.
JOEY: Frankie.
I've been coming up with
some pretty good ideas.
You got to place a
couple of more bets for me.
Hey, Joey, I don't think
we ought to push our luck.
Frankie, someone has finally
taken the fucking needles
out of my goddamn voodoo doll.
You know what you ought to do?
You give Sal what you got
and don't be fucking greedy.
Greedy?
I'm not fucking greedy.
It's that cocksucker
who is greedy.
Frankie, I'm just trying
to get out of here.
Yeah, at my expense.
No.
He ain't going to
do nothing to you.
If he's going to do anything to
anybody, he's going to hang me.
I'm an accomplice.
To him, it's just as bad.
Do you like like begging
people to make bets for me?
Joey, I don't know.
Come on.
What are you doing?
- Come on, Fly.
You got to do this for me.
What did I tell you
about calling me Fly?
I mean Frankie...
Frankie.
Frankie, he's going to bury
me in this piece of shit.
He's a scumbag.
I can't have a life
with this scumbag.
Please.
OK.
OK, on one condition, all right?
You know this script that
I'm writing for Margaret?
Yeah.
I want to direct it, too.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, sure.
That's a great idea.
And I don't mean none of
these porno flicks, neither.
No.
We're talking an epic, a saga.
Look, Frankie, you
can write, direct,
hold the lights for all I care.
I'll just... I'll just be there
to guide you and help you
when you need me.
Please just make the bet.
And we don't tell Sal nothing?
We don't tell Sal
a fucking thing.
The movie, you and I, we
make it on our free time.
We just use that
cocksucker's film.
OK.
All right.
Whatever you want.
Ah, Frankie, I knew
you wouldn't let me down.
I got two horses...
One in the six and
one in the eight.
[truck honking]
[tire popping]
You're trying to tell
me something, ain't you?
Huh?
RACE ANNOUNCER:
Out of the stretch,
it's Hurly Burly, Happy Time,
[inaudible] neck to neck.
It's Hurly Burly.
- No.
No.
Now shut them the fucking down.
Shut them down.
Shut them.
Yes!
I love you.
Everything all right?
Yes.
This is amazing.
It's going to be the first
porno ever to get an Oscar.
I'm not kidding
you... just awesome.
Here, look.
[inaudible] going to
like my work here.
Ha!
Son of a bitch.
Brilliant.
Here she is, yeah.
Slow down.
[honking]
Vic.
Hey, what are you
doing around here?
Actually, we was
looking for you, Margaret.
- Yeah?
- Come on.
Get in.
Hey.
Hey, doing a little shopping?
Ah, looking mostly...
Picked up a little scarf.
Oh.
[chuckle] That's nice.
It's good that those things will
make you feel good [inaudible],
huh?
Where we going?
Uh, Sal wants to see you.
About what?
Didn't say.
Hey, you all right?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
No work today?
Down time.
Got my period.
Oh.
Yeah.
It's good to have a
legitimate excuse to take
some time off from work, right?
Vic, what's going on?
Huh.
Oh, that?
He's just checking out the
texture of some new stuff.
That's all.
Vic, why don't you pull
over and let me out, OK?
I can't do that.
Why not?
I told you.
Sal wants to see you.
Why does he want to see me?
Well, Margaret,
Sal is a funny guy.
I can't really figure him
out sometimes, you know?
I think he went a little
cuckoo when his old man died.
It's like he's afraid of change,
likes things to stay the same.
Yeah, well, sometimes
change is good.
Personally, I agree with you.
But I also think there's
a time and a place.
How about a little music, huh?
Want some music?
Vic.
Go on, feel it.
Enjoy the music.
Have a little
something with us, huh?
Come on, Vinny.
Come on.
[inaudible].
Stop, Vic.
Stop it.
Stop it, goddammit.
There you go.
Come on.
That's better.
[knock]
[buzzer]
SAL: Hello, Joey.
Sal.
If I'd known you were
coming by, I would have
brought you a cup of coffee.
Oh, thanks a lot.
That's very thoughtful of you.
You want mine?
I don't drink coffee.
So what brings you around, Sal?
Why don't you sit down?
You look kind of tense.
Me, tense?
Oh, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Sit down!
OK, I'll sit down.
Doing a little
reading, have you?
You mean this?
No.
I just like to test
myself, you know,
and see how I've been doing.
It's nothing.
What do you use to play
with, Monopoly money?
[low chuckle]
So... so what are
you doing here, Sal?
You already asked me that once.
You think I'm hard of hearing?
No.
I mean it's just that,
you know, I mean,
you never come down here.
I hear everything, Joey.
I got what's known
as 20/20 hearing.
[laughs]
20... 20/20 hearing...
That's a good one, Sal.
That's really funny.
Is it?
Is it funny?
Sometimes I have trouble
distinguishing what's funny
and what's not.
I never know.
Maybe you can help me
out with something.
Sure.
Want you to listen to this
and tell me whether or not
you think it's funny.
(JOEY'S VOICE ON TAPE) He's
the dirtiest piece of shit.
He's a scumbag.
I can't have a life
in this scumbag.
Please.
(FRANKIE'S VOICE ON
TAPE) OK, one condition...
You know the script I'm
writing for Margaret?
I want to direct it, too.
(JOEY'S VOICE ON
TAPE) Frankie, an epic,
a saga... you can write, direct,
hold the lights for all I care.
I'll just... I'll just
be there to guide you.
Please just make the bet.
(FRANKIE'S VOICE ON TAPE)
And we don't tell Sal nothing?
(JOEY'S VOICE ON TAPE) We
don't tell Sal a fucking thing.
The move... you and I, we
make it on our free time.
We just use that
cocksucker's film.
Is that funny?
No, Sal, that
definitely is not funny.
I didn't think so.
My gosh.
[chuckles]
Man, a microphone.
Even the cocks have
ears around here.
[chuckling] Now that's funny.
Hey, it's Roman Polanski.
[chuckling] Come on.
Hey, Sal.
What's up?
I hear that you
want to make a movie.
[moaning]
Come on.
What's the matter?
You got stage fright?
Is she OK?
SAL: Oh, yeah.
She's fine.
We just gave her
something to relax
her a little bit to get her...
You guys grab Fly
and sit him down.
Give him a comfortable seat.
I want him to see the show.
But Sal, I...
Not a word...
I'm going to do
you a favor and not
allow you to say
one fucking word,
because you're
just going to lie.
And it's going to
jeopardize our friendship.
Now where is Joey's money?
I mean my money.
Oh, it's... it's in my pocket.
Well, get it out.
I don't like to
wait for answers.
Well, you know, I
didn't mean you no wrong.
Well, yes you did.
No.
You broke a trust.
And that is a big no-no.
Oh.
$6,000.
[grunting]
You're a little short, Fly.
That's all I got.
SAL: That's all you got?
[chuckling] Well, we've got
a little problem here then.
According to my sources, uh,
you're about $146,000 short.
Well, I fucked up.
I got a flat on the way track.
And... and I didn't
get there in time,
you know, to make the bets.
[laughs] You fucked up.
You fucked up.
You got a flat.
Oh, I see now.
I understand.
OK.
Well, it's only money, right?
We'll just forget all about it.
But I don't think
so, because we'd
been missing a golden
opportunity to look
into our souls and
search our hearts
and ask ourselves,
why did this happen?
Why?
I must I ask
myself, who is going
to benefit the most from
this little demonstration
here today?
Certainly not Joey...
I mean, let's face
it, it's over for him.
[laughs] He's not in control.
Not only that, but
you know, he's...
He's a scum.
Hey.
Now, I think you will
know never go against me
again for something like that.
That is a pig, Fly.
Sal, please.
She didn't have nothing
to do with this, nothing.
Oh, you're wrong.
She had everything
to do with it.
She corrupted your mind.
She... she... she... blinded you,
much more so than you even
realize.
She's the reason you
were going to fuck me.
No, Sal, you're wrong.
You're wrong.
I'm... I'm... I'm
never wrong, Fly.
I'm going to show you
what a pig she is.
And after that, we're going to
play a little guessing game.
It's called Who's
Nuts are in the Jar?
Give him the jar.
Whose name you think is
going to be on there?
Joey?
You?
FRANKIE: Sal, please.
How do you think they're
going to look, all cold
and shriveled up?
Maybe they'll be magnified
because they're in the glass.
Well, let's not get
ahead of ourselves.
Sit her up.
[moans]
OK, Fly.
I want you to watch this.
Turn him around.
Look how good she is, Fly.
She loves it.
And... and... and... and I love it.
[laughs] Open your fucking eyes.
Everybody, look
at the movie star.
No.
Volare!
Piss on her.
Oh.
Yo, what about him?
Fucking blind him.
[grunting]
Make him a cyclops.
If he ever fucks with me again,
we'll take out the other one,
see how much vision he has then.
[grunting]
[yelling]
Let's go for a ride.
Your hands look kind of...
Kind of tight and tense
on that wheel there, Fly.
That happens to me
sometimes, too, usually
when I want to kill somebody.
You want to kill
somebody, don't you, Fly?
somebody like me?
Now be honest.
You want to kill me, don't you?
Say it.
- Yes.
Yes.
Ha.
It'll pass.
[chuckles] I appreciate
your honesty, I must say.
But do you know, I'm
doing you a favor.
You'll realize in the
long run that this writing
thing is no good for you.
You're just setting yourself
up to get hurt, setting
yourself up for disappointment.
Fly, nobody made
Margaret do drugs.
She did that on her
own, because she's weak.
Weak people will always
go back to doing what
they do best, what they know.
Why don't you take a
couple of days off,
figure out what you want to be...
One of the wolves
or one of the sheep?
[phone ringing]
[pool balls breaking]
There he is.
Thought you'd died.
What, are you disappointed?
Hey, maybe a little.
Shut up, Vic.
How are you feeling?
Yeah, fine.
Want to play?
Nah.
I don't really feel like it.
How about washing my car?
Do you feel like doing that?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
Margaret?
Yo, baby.
Hey, your name?
Frankie.
I'm looking for Margaret.
Have you seen her?
Yeah, I saw her.
She's over by [inaudible].
Garrison Bridge?
All right, thanks.
Uh-huh.
Later.
Bye.
[truck honking]
[honking]
Woo-ee.
You got the big man's car.
Fly man is big time.
Come on.
Get in.
You lonely, baby?
Do you want some company?
Yeah.
Get in.
You're [inaudible], huh?
I didn't know you
was kinky, Fly.
Hm?
- Kinky Fly.
- No.
No.
Put your clothes on.
Hey.
Isn't this what you want?
Hm?
What you always wanted?
Yeah, but not like
this, all right?
Hey, baby.
I'm sorry.
How's the Fly want?
Hey, don't call me Fly, please.
All right?
Come on, baby.
Come on.
Margaret.
Yeah?
Shh.
Yeah.
Margaret.
Oh, that's it.
Yeah.
That's the prize.
You read the Bible,
huh, Frankie?
Yeah, sometimes.
Well, like it says in Psalm
23, the Lord is your shepherd.
And you shall not want.
What did you say?
I make it.
I said the Lord
is your shepherd.
No.
I don't need no shepherd.
I ain't no fucking sheep.
You hear me?
OK.
OK, baby.
So maybe you don't
need no shepherd.
But I bet you sure could
use a little pussy.
No.
Stop this.
Will you stop this?
You're supposed to be strong.
[slap] You've got to be strong.
Don't you ever fucking lay a
hand on me, you piece of shit.
I'm stronger than
you'll ever be.
OK?
- OK.
Ever.
You're the one
who's weak, riding
around in your big man's car.
[inaudible] car from the inside,
hoping for little handouts.
Why did you have
to go and get high?
Why?
Yeah.
Ask your friend Vic,
Sal, your friends.
OK?
That's the ones who
fucking shoved it in me.
Do me a favor, huh?
Stay out of my fucking life.
Hey.
What are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
Here.
It's all washed.
I took it out for a little spin.
I hope you don't mind.
Come on, Frankie.
What the fuck are you doing?
Take me home.
Frankie.
Come on.
Sit over here.
Nobody can hear
us talk out here.
Talk about what?
Our movie.
Our movie?
Frankie, I ain't making
a fucking movie with you.
Do you understand me?
I am not.
Now you gave me your word.
I gave you my word when I
had two fucking eyes, before I
looked like a fucking mummy.
Well, at least, you know,
listen to my idea, OK?
Forget it.
Now would you please listen?
Hey, it's great.
Sit down.
Fuck.
I'm going to kill Sal.
I do not want to hear this.
I do not want to hear...
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck are
you doing, Fly?
Could you please listen to me?
Be careful.
Get the fuck off of me.
Listen to me, please.
OK?
I'm a fucking fake,
pretending, all right?
I never really could
do it, you know?
What you gotta do when you...
Well, when you take
somebody out, make a hit,
it never seemed right to me.
But it seems right now.
And I'm going to
kill that cocksucker.
And I'm going to do it on film.
I want the whole world
to see what a punk he is.
All right.
Bang.
And I'm going to do it.
You've lost your
fucking mind, Frankie.
I don't think so.
Hey, but you could
be right, you know?
There is a fine line
between insanity and genius.
Take it from me...
You crossed it.
We got to do it, Joey.
You got to do it.
We got a deal.
Fuck you, we got a deal.
The deal was you make the
bets, we make a movie.
Frankie, you never
made the bets.
Oh, yes, I did.
You said you got a flat.
I did.
And I wasn't going to go.
And then, you know, I
thought sometimes God wants
you to overcome adversity.
And so I changed that tire.
And I got there.
And I made that bet.
And it was beautiful.
Why the fuck didn't
you tell me or Sal?
It wouldn't have mattered.
It wouldn't have mattered?
They took my fucking eye.
Yeah, chances are he
would have taken it anyway.
You are the most...
Oh, no, no.
Now you're to hurt yourself.
You're going to hurt yourself.
What the fuck do you think this
is, a minor corneal abrasion?
Hey, you want your
goddamn money or not?
Yeah.
- Help me up.
- OK.
We're good.
Good.
Yeah.
Come on now.
Now you just take it easy now.
OK?
There, huh?
So I'm going to need
a little more advice,
you know, on like, on how
to use camera and sound
and shit like that.
And then maybe you could, like,
well, I mean we just go on
and do it like we were
before your little mishap.
Now don't you start
on me, all right?
I mean, this is a
hell of a way to treat
a guy that did you a favor.
A favor?
Yes, a favor.
If I had given
Sal all the money,
you wouldn't have
shit right now.
You'd be standing on the corner
of Alvarado and 6th selling
pencils, staring at people
out of that goofy fucking eye
of yours, begging for change.
So shut the fuck up.
You're rich.
I kill Sal, it's like putting
the money right in your pocket.
How much money have
you got left, Frankie?
I got all of it.
$143,000... is that enough?
I thought it would be.
[laughs] Hey, it's
a beautiful day.
It's like shit.
Yeah, well, I mean, this
will burn off, you know?
[car starting]
[tires squealing]
So you didn't see nothing, huh?
Not a fucking thing.
You know, find this note...
Says got your car, Guinea fuck.
You got any balls,
come and get it.
And you know, sitting on
the front seat of my car.
Guinea fuck.
Yeah, mano, mano, motherfucker.
Hm.
Sounds like a setup to me, Fly.
I don't think so.
I'm thinking that this is
some macho thing, you know?
Like... like he says, mano, mano.
What do you think, Vic?
Jeez, it's hard to figure.
It's a good opportunity.
For what? to get my
fucking brains blown out?
No.
Hear me out.
I think I got a good plan.
You think?
Yeah.
We'll let him think you're
coming alone, like he wants.
And then you won't.
Because I'll be with you.
You?
Hey, what kind of
bullshit is this?
I mean, come on, huh?
Let him... let him talk.
There's one thing
that's bothering me.
Why do you want
to do this so bad?
Well, I got two reasons.
One is I want to film it.
[laughing]
You want to what?
I know it sounds crazy,
but think about it.
It could be really cool.
And what good exposure, huh?
To who?
The fucking FBI?
No.
No... to these kids that
don't know who you are,
show these punks, huh?
Set an example of how
not to fuck with you.
This is fucking stupid, huh?
What the fuck?
Let him... let him say it.
Let him go on.
Yeah.
Mind your own fucking business.
Hey, don't tell me to mind
my fucking business, OK?
I don't fucking like that.
OK.
Well, fuck you, man.
Fuck everybody.
I'll go myself.
I'll get the car back.
OK?
I'll do it.
Yeah, soon as he
calls up at 10:00,
I'll make him
believe that I'm you.
You?
Yeah, me, huh?
Maybe it's about time
I make a hit, huh?
Yeah, maybe it's about
time that the word spreads.
You don't fuck with
Frankie the Fly.
Sit the fuck down,
Maybe he's right.
Maybe we can really
show them, you know?
Let's show them what
big balls we got.
Why don't you run along now in
case you need to get, you know,
contacted.
Mhm.
Yeah, sure.
I'll do that.
All right.
I think I better
take these, huh?
[laughs]
Oh, man.
He's a lot of fun.
You think this
could be dangerous?
The day I've got to
worry about Frankie the Fly
is the day that
I should be dead.
[MUSIC - BO DIDDLEY, "I'M A
MAN"] You pretty women,
stand in line.
I'll make love to
you, baby, one a time.
I'm a man.
And I spell it M-A-N.
Ain't that a man?
All right.
Love that song.
It's so inspirational...
Makes me feel so alive.
This is it.
Is that a guess?
No, I mean, it looks like
the place he described.
Well, what now,
Mr. Camera Man?
Well, I...
I guess I'll go and look.
And I'll see if
your car is there.
[dog barking]
What's all that about?
What are you doing?
I'm going to wear
it like a disguise.
I thought you wanted
everybody to recognize you.
I do.
But I figure, you
know, I'm going,
like, make believe
I'm a homeless guy
till I check it out.
[car door closing]
You thought of
everything, didn't you, Fly?
Now You'll come
if I yell, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
But I'm going to...
I'm gong to take this with me.
You think maybe, uh,
maybe I could have that?
No, I think not.
You don't need a gun, Fly.
Cause you got big balls.
Hey, Fly.
Give me the gun?
I think that we're
going to need this.
Right.
[laughs quietly]
Sal dies... take one.
Take two.
Yo, Sal.
Hey, Sal, Sal, Sal!
Look, here it is.
Here it is.
Ha.
Look.
Wow.
Yeah.
What a surprise.
So where's the dirt bag?
I don't know.
Uh.
But I'll get him.
Hey, motherfucker, come
on out here, just like you
said... mano, mano, huh?
Come on, you cocksucker.
Come on.
You want to mano, mano?
Come on, man.
Come on.
We're here... hand to hand.
Come on, brother.
Come on.
Come on, you piece of shit.
Let's see your face.
Come on out here.
Come on, you prick.
Fly.
What?
Shut the fuck up.
There's nobody here, man.
And you know it.
You took my car.
What are you talking?
It was you, Fly.
Vic saw you do it.
And he told me.
Now why don't you
tell me what it is
you got me down here for, OK?
Because you've
become a problem now.
And it's not fun anymore.
I haven't got all night,
so let's get to it.
OK?
What do you want?
How come you never
call me Frankie?
What was that?
How come you never once
call me by my real name?
What the fuck are
you talking about?
I'm talking about respect.
I'm talking about being
treated like a piece of shit
all the time.
I'm talking about being
crumbs like a fucking pigeon.
I'm... I'm more than that.
I'm more than that.
Is there anything else you
want to say before you die?
Yeah.
There was no reason how
you treated Margaret.
Now there was no reason
for that, no reason at all.
Well, you know, she's a
piece of shit, just like you.
No, uh-uh.
No.
You're the piece of shit.
Yeah, you're a big man
with a gun, aren't you, huh?
You know, this camera
things is not a bad idea.
Maybe you got something.
Like you said, you
know, set an example.
Well, why don't you come
and get me, motherfucker?
Why don't you come and do it
like a man, take me like a man?
Come on, you prick.
Come on, just one
shot, motherfucker.
Why don't you just come
here and take me like a man?
I just want to get one fucking
shot at you, you motherfucker.
Come on.
All right.
[crashing]
Ha!
It worked.
Hey, it worked.
Oh.
Hey, look at the
fucking dog now.
Look at the fucking dog now.
How are you doing, cheetah?
[monkey noises]
I'm going to kill you.
You ain't going to do
dick, motherfucker, but die...
That is, right
after I piss on you,
just like you did Margaret,
just like you did to Margaret.
Here, here, I can do this.
Here it comes.
Here.
Ah!
[fighting noises]
I'll take you with me.
Ah!
Yeah!
[hitting]
Die.
[grunting]
[laughing]
You going to shoot me, Fly?
You going to shoot me?
You got no balls, Fly.
[gunshots]
[MUSIC - CHUCK BERRY, "RIDING
ALONG IN MY AUTOMOBILE"]
Riding along in my automobile,
my baby beside me at the wheel.
I stole a kiss at the turn
of a mile, my curiosity
running wild, cruising
and playing the radio
with no particular place to go.
Yeah, did you get that?
Yeah, Frankie, I got all of it.
FRANKIE: I think we
ought to do it again.
That fucking guy, you
know, he cut me off.
And he screwed up the shot.
Frankie, trust me.
It's good enough.
FRANKIE: I mean, there's nothing
cooler than an overhead shot
if it looks right.
Now you want your money, huh?
Shoot the movie, capisce?
Now I'm going to around
the block again, all right?
I'm going to pull up
in front of this place.
I'm going to get down.
I'm going to a kind of
king of the jungle thing.
You got me, Mr. NYU?
I got you, Frankie.
Fucking actors... king
of the jungle, take two.
Jesus Christ, Frankie.
Frank!
[gunshot]
Son of a bitch.
He just shot my money.
Just need you to sign
these before you go.
Everybody needs help.
Don't be afraid to ask.
Thanks.
Good luck.
Hey, Margaret.
This came for you
while you were gone.
Thanks.
Hi, Margaret.
I prepared a little
something in case
I don't see you
personally for a while.
I'm not from New
York, like I told you.
Uh, I'm from Michigan.
I... I just, I talk
like this because it's
the way tough guys talk.
And... and if I... and I figured...
Ah, it doesn't matter.
Anyway, I just want to tell
you that I really care for you.
Well, if anything goes wrong
with this plan that I got,
this money is yours.
And I want you to have
it, To maybe get yourself
a fresh start, you know?
Be the actress
that you are, huh?
[laughs]
OK.
So maybe I'll never
be an actress.
But you are, huh?
And I hear that New York's
a nice place, friendly.
Actresses go there.
That's the place actresses go.
So, well, um, I guess that's it.
Um, I hope I see you.
Um.
Uh.
Oh.
Um.
Show... show them that you
got what it takes, Margaret.
Show 'em you got it.
OK.
Oh, my god.
Hi, Vic.
Don't say a fucking word.
It won't be just
your ear I shoot.
You're lucky I never
liked the bastard.
It's $5,000.
Come on.
Get out of the trunk.
And we go by my rules
from now, not Sal's.
You get on a train
and don't come back.
You make me look
bad, I'll swat you.
Hey, Fly, change your name.
Try van Gogh.
Ha ha.
Yeah... van Gogh.
Yeah.
Vincent.
Vinnie.
Hey, Vinnie.
Yo, Vin.
Yo, Vinnie.
Yeah, hey, Vinnie.
Yeah, that's good.
How you doing?
Fine.
That's it.
Vince.