23.976 English Closed Caption
DVD Subrip NTSC © 09.11.2019
¶ Jingle bells,
Jingle bells, ¶
¶ jingle all the way.
¶ Oh what fun
it is to ride ¶
¶ in a one-horse open sleigh.
¶ Oh jingle bells,
jingle all the way. ¶
¶ Oh what fun
it is to ride ¶
¶ in a one-horse
open sleigh. ¶
¶ Dashing through the snow
¶ In a one-horse open sleigh
¶ O'er the fields we go,
laughing all the way. ¶
¶ Bells on bobtails ring,
making spirits bright. ¶
¶ What fun it is
to laugh and sing ¶
¶ this sleighing song tonight.
¶ Jingle bells, Jingle bells,
jingle all the way. ¶
¶ Oh what fun
it is to ride ¶
¶ in a one-horse open sleigh.
¶ Oh jingle bells,
jingle all the way. ¶
Has anybody seen
the Christmas lights?
Mom is calling you.
She can't find the
Christmas stuff.
Uh huh, whatever.
Is anyone even
listening to me?
No.
Eleanor!
We're having a holiday
party at school today.
Are you having one?
That's for kids.
We don't have those
parties in Jr. High.
How's that Santa coming?
The glue won't stick.
I like the ornaments
you made last year.
Did you find them yet?
Which ones did we
make last year?
The Popsicle
stick reindeer.
Of course!
I don't know.
We'll ask mom, okay.
Are you girls
ready for school?
Only two more days and
Christmas vacation.
Good, after tomorrow I
can sleep in all day.
Eleanor, you
making an ornament?
No, it's stupid.
What?
How can this be?
I can't believe that you,
of all of my children,
are going to break the great
Ferguson family tradition,
with
no ornament!
Why is there so
much laundry to do?
What is it honey?
Have you seen this
pile of laundry Gary?
Where are the
Christmas lights?
We're the only house
on the whole block
without any up.
Sounds like
fun down there.
Coming.
Dinky lights,
pathetic tree...
another great
Ferguson tradition.
What do you care?
You said you didn't
believe in Santa anyway.
I don't, but I
believe in presents.
I don't know what
you did with them.
Of course, it's my fault.
Mommy, Eleanor
[Unclear] Santa.
-I did not!
Ho ho ho.
Liv, finish
your breakfast.
-You're not my mommy.
What are those, the inside of
the terminator?
No, it's our
Christmas lights.
Those are pretty Gary.
The Fergusons
will have lights.
Right.
It's all right, I
can untangle these.
Perfect...just in
time for Easter.
No, no, no.
I can handle it.
I just need to
find an end.
-Mommy, Elly's being mean.
-Don't call me Elly,
my name is Eleanor.
I might make it work.
Why don't we just
buy new ones?
Oh that's right, we
can't afford new ones.
We've maxed out
four credit cards.
What do you want me to do?
It would just be nice if
maybe you could paid
for some of that work you did.
Oh, oh, see these huh.
Tada!
Wow.
Okay. I'll admit it; it's
going to be a lean Christmas.
Do you have any
work lined up Gary?
Well, I finished
a plumbing job
on the Larrys yesterday, so
I'll send an invoice out today.
Great, and do you think that
maybe sometime this year
you could fix the
downstairs toilet,
because it still
doesn't work.
Look, I've got a few leads
on some things okay.
Something's
going to come up.
Something always comes up.
And what about
if it doesn't?
You know you can't pay
bills with optimism Gary.
Four days till Christmas.
Four days.
I can't buy anything
and we need everything.
Mommy, we're
going to be late.
Oh, what about this?
Wail till you see.
It's going to
be beautiful.
We don't even
have a tree Gary.
I know.
Perfect.
Perfect, I mean what
else could go wrong?
You know what,
don't worry?
Don't worry.
It's going to be
a great Christmas.
I'm going to get a
tree, I promise you.
From where, the park?
Yes, the park.
That's a great idea.
Mom, I have a test...
I'm going to take
the kids to school.
I can't be late; it's
the end of the semester.
Come on Eleanor!
Where's Mom?
I'm giving her a break.
Get in.
I'll walk.
Olivia!
Olivia, you forgot
your cookies.
We stayed up so
late making these.
And you left them
on the table.
Silly goose.
-Oops.
Eleanor, where
are you going?
Where do you think?
(Sigh)
Mommy, are we going
to have a Christmas tree?
Baby, ask your dad.
Absolutely.
It might not have
any branches...
No branches?
Where will we hang
our ornaments?
Do you remember that old
cartoon I showed you?
Well we will wrap the
tree in your blanket
and it will grow to a
full-size Christmas tree.
Like magic?
Christmas is the most
magic time of the year.
It's when wishes
come true.
Right honey?
Have fun at your
party, okay.
Okay.
And eat lunch before you
go eating all the cookies.
Okay Mommy.
Oh, I didn't finish
my Santa yet.
Can I finish it
when I get home?
Yes, of course you can.
Beautiful day!
[engine starts]
Eleanor?
Get in the car,
it's cold.
Daddy, does Eleanor
hate Christmas?
No, no, of course not!
Does Mom hate Christmas?
No baby; nobody
hates Christmas.
Eleanor, get
in the car now!
Mom hates Christmas.
It always puts
her in a bad mood.
Thank you Eleanor, welcome
to the Ferguson carpool.
[Music]
Oh, Olivia,
Olivia, Olivia.
(Phone Rings)
Oh, you didn't
get the payment?
No ma'am we didn't.
We are going to need
that payment right away.
Okay, well, I'm going
to put it on my card.
You didn't get
the payment?
No, I'm sorry we didn't.
Yeah, I sent it.
Well, I have no record
of it here ma'am.
Could you just look over
the bill again, because,
I think there's a mistake.
I guess I just
misplaced the bill.
I don't know...
Well the late fee ...
Yeah, I'm usually so
good about these things.
I was wondering if you
could waive that late fee?
You know, I'm hardly ever
late...we're never late.
This is the first time.
I sent the payment.
I have no idea...right.
You know, I just
pay half...well;
I could pay you
half of that now.
Full minimum payment.
The check's in the mail.
Thanks.
[music throughout]
[in distance]
Ho Ho Ho, Merry Christmas.
-Nick!
-Thank you.
I'm here, Sheila...
Come on, I don't
have that much time.
Can I help you?
Were you interested in
something in the window?
Yeah, the red dress.
How much?
$1200.
Plus tax?
Mhm. Would you like
to try it on?
Uh, oh yes!
Well I'll grab
one for you.
[door opens, closes]
-Paula!
-(Gasp)
I thought
that was you!
Nick, hi.
Yeah, it's me.
Great.
Wow, what a surprise!
Yeah.
So, I mean, you're
back in town.
Well I guess I couldn't
stay in Nice forever,
could I?
What are you doing here?
Ah, yeah, shopping.
How long has it been since
we've seen each other?
-Four years?
-Five.
Five.
Your father's memorial.
Yeah.
You still painting?
Oh yeah.
Hi.
You remember
Paula don't you?
We went to
school together.
She used to work for
my father's gallery.
Of course. Hello.
Hi.
Honey, I need the AMEX.
So how's Gary?
Oh, great.
Still doing construction.
Have you been to
my gallery lately?
No, no.
Not in a long time.
Oh, you should see the
lineup of new artists
I've discovered.
Wow.
Are you still
doing florals?
Yeah, all the time.
Well then, you've
got to come.
You'll love the new show.
Honey, we're late.
I'm inviting Paula
to the opening.
[both]
What?
The new show
opens tonight.
You and Gary should come.
Really?
Yeah, 8 o'clock tonight.
That dress will
look great on you.
I gotta go.
But, um, thank you.
It's really
good to see you.
Are you going to
take any of those?
You know, I'm going
to think about it
and maybe I'll
be back tomorrow.
I'll look forward to
seeing you there.
[sound of streetcorner
Santa in distance]
I have nothing to wear.
Honey, you look
good in nothing.
I mean whatever you wear;
you're going to look great.
I have nothing
good enough.
Well what about the
lime green pant suit
my mom gave you for
Christmas last year?
Okay, forget that I
even offered that.
Why are we even
going to this?
What? What are you
talking about now?
Well you don't even have to
go to this gallery thing.
We never go anywhere
Gary and this is free.
It's something we
can afford, right?
[woman's voice]
Mrs. K.!
you're going to be late
for your appointment
with Armando!
Oooh, losing my mind!
I hope Santa brings
me a pretty dress.
Yeah, have him
bring me one too.
Hi baby.
Mommy, look, do
you like my Santa?
I do, you did
such a good job!
You didn't even see it.
Oh, I did.
It's as adorable
as you are.
Are you dressed
for an 80s party?
You're funny.
Okay, you girls be
in bed by 10, okay?
Gary?
-Hey, you look terrific.
-Oh, thanks.
Can I have this dance?
Come on, let's go.
We're going to be late.
Eleanor, may I
have this dance?
You have to go,
you'll be late.
I'll dance with you daddy.
You will?
Come on.
Hand please?
Yes.
Dad, you're so weird.
Good night girls.
Let's go.
[shivering]
Your chariot has
arrived Mrs. Ferguson.
I left the pin
in my skirt.
I completely
forgot to sew it!
Oh my god.
Baby, you can't
even see it.
Gary!
There's going to be women
in there whose dresses
cost over $1200.
plus tax.
Mine was at the Goodwill
and it has a pin in it.
You can barely even see
it, I'm telling you.
It looks great.
Oh, Prairie Fauvists.
[music and chatter throughout]
And I replied, sweetie...
...nobody does Aspen
on Christmas day.
Oh Aspen's done.
Everyone goes
to Telluride.
Completely out of date.
Gary, can you not push me?
Do you see anyone else
pushing their wife?
Gary! Paula!
Oh great, the
old flame Janine!
Come on, I like Janine.
Well then, you
talk to her.
Hi guys.
Hi.
Can you believe
this place?
-It's amazing.
-It's pretty great.
How are you Gary?
Not bad. Not bad.
Where's Nick?
Over by the window;
he's the one surrounded
by all the girls -
the same as
high school.
Well, go on and say hi.
We'll just stay here
and discuss painting.
House painting.
Good, have fun.
Thank you.
I bet Nick can't
paint a house.
I bet he doesn't do
copper plumbing either.
[chatter throughout]
Paula.
Nick.
Oh, I didn't even see you.
You made it.
Is Gary here?
Yeah, he's over there.
I want to show
you something;
I'm so glad you came.
Hello.
-Hi sweetie.
-How are you?
Hello, gorgeous.
You look lovely,
both of you.
Great work.
Have to tell you, it really
feels great to be back.
So what do you
think of this?
Very modern.
What is it?
Garbage.
(Laughs)
How you been?
Good.
Gosh it must be so nice
to travel around Europe,
buying art.
Well, I've missed people.
You're surrounded
by people.
Not friends.
I was dating this guy
last year but it fizzled,
he didn't
want kids.
Well, you know what;
you'll find someone
because you're
a good person.
So what are you doing to
keep yourself busy these days?
Life.
I've two girls, so
there is always,
always something.
Yeah.
Kids are great.
I never went
down that road.
No?
Yeah, god,
they're your life.
Would you be interested in
working in a Art Gallery again?
You mean like
working here?
Sh, our secret.
Hi.
Sheila, hi.
Nice to see you again.
You too.
Wow, that's a
fantastic skirt.
Honey, Malcolm and Shanite
would like to talk to you
about the large
piece from Florence.
Mr. and Mrs. Kensington,
photo please?
Good night.
Nice seeing you Paula.
Nice skirt...
I know.
Hey, I'm done.
I'm done.
I'm ready to go.
Okay, hang on.
I'm going to go say
goodbye to Nick.
Why?
Well, because I didn't get
a chance to say hello.
Which piece did you like?
Excuse me, just a second.
You know how
lucky you were?
What?
Dating both of them
in high school?
Yeah.
You ended up with the
right guy though.
I bet Gary's a great dad.
Yeah, he is.
[indistinct chatter]
Did you enjoy
the party?
How's Janine?
Maybe I should have
taken her to Prom.
What are you doing?
[radio playing quietly]
What was dad
drinking last night?
Once we put our
ornaments on it,
the tree will look great.
That's not a tree,
that's a branch.
Admiring our Christmas
branch girls?
All right,
let's go ladies.
Last day of school before
Christmas vacation.
Keep it moving.
Mush. Mush.
Hi girls.
-Hi Reg.
-Hey.
Hey Gary, you ready to go?
I got the lights.
Yeah, do you mind dropping
the girls off a school?
I'll meet you
at the sight.
Yeah, sure.
Come on guys.
Back-packs, back-packs.
Let's go.
Love you daddy.
All right, have
a good day.
-Bye dad.
-Thank you.
How about you
sweetheart?
Me?
Oh, I was booking
a flight to France,
taking in the Louvre,
doing a little holiday
shopping in Paris
and then dinner
at the Ritz.
The usual.
Enjoy the Louvre.
[quietly]
I'm sorry Gary.
[quiet music throughout]
[crying]
[music throughout]
[chuckles]
There you are.
[woman's voice]
Mrs. K., you're
going to be late
for your appointment
with Armando!
Remember lunch at
the club afterward!
Mrs. K...
Mrs. K.!
You're going to be late for
your appointment with Armando!
[Music]
(Grunts)
Oh!
[gasp!]
Mrs. K., you fall down!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I think I'm okay.
Let me help you up.
I don't know how
this happened.
Not to worry Mrs. K..
Mrs. K.?
You prefer now I call
you Mrs. Kensington?
[man's voice]
Martina, is Paula up yet?
[whispers]
No!
No, not yet.
Tell her I hired someone to put
up the Christmas lights, okay?
Okay.
Was that Nick
asking for me?
Yes.
Where's Sheila?
Sheila...
At the gallery.
[gasp]
Oh, this is so strange.
I know.
This is a very strange
time for all of us.
Vayamos.
[gasp]
[Music]
[chuckles]
Oh my god,
look at that!
[Unclear]
Oh god, this
is so gorgeous.
Yes, you picked that one
up in Italy this summer.
Very nice.
I picked that up in Italy?
Yes, only the best for
you Mrs. Kensington.
Only the best.
Oh, your hair
appointment...
My hair appointment?
Okay.
One thing.
Yes, yes?
I'm Mrs. Kensington?
Are you feeling all
right Mrs. Kensington?
Why do you keep
calling me that?
Are you're Martina?
Oh please, Mrs. K., it's
been a tough enough day
without you
acting like this.
Did you take too much of
your prescriptions again?
My...? No.
No, good.
There is so much going on;
so much stress already.
You must get going.
This must be a dream,
but it seems so real.
Oh, brunch
at the Club at 11.
Right, brunch at
the Club at 11.
Okay.
Okay!
[¶]
¶ I never imagined
anything else; ¶
¶ always thought I could
take care of myself. ¶
¶ But now I'm making
a brand new start, ¶
¶ and I've had a
change of heart. ¶
¶ Feelings are hidden
deep inside of me; ¶
¶ they have to get out,
they have to break free. ¶
¶ And now I find I've
been playing a part, ¶
¶ and I've had a
change of heart. ¶
Hi honey.
¶ When I see
you smile, ¶
¶ it makes life worthwhile.
¶ Now I've got the style
¶ It's all about you,
it's all about me. ¶
¶ The road may be rocky,
the road may bend, ¶
¶ but we're going to
make it to the end. ¶
¶ And now we're making
a brand start, ¶
¶ and I've had a
change of heart. ¶
[Music]
¶ It's all about you,
it's all about me. ¶
¶ The road may be rocky,
the road may bend, ¶
¶ but we're going to
make it to the end. ¶
¶ And now we're making
a brand start, ¶
¶ and I've had a
change of heart. ¶
[Music]
¶ I've had a
change of heart. ¶
Well, as far as dreams go,
this is 1st Class!
Oh Mrs. K...
[unclear]
You need to get going.
Don't keep
Armando waiting.
Oh, Armando?
Yes.
[door opens]
Oh don't bother dropping
by today, I'm tied up.
Enjoy yourself.
I have a very hard
working husband, don't I?
Si.
Where was I having
lunch once again?
At the Club.
The Club.
-Yes.
-Which Club?
The Montclair.
Oh, oh.
The one up on the hill?
Yes.
Yeah, I knew that.
[Unclear]
Too much prescriptions.
[horn honks]
Merry Christmas!
(Laughter)
Hi.
Yes, I'm here for my
appointment with Armando.
To the Club as usual.
Oh, maybe I'm
meeting Nick.
Paula!
Honey!
Who cut your hair last?
Who did this to you?
Have you been
cheating on Armando?
Yes.
Please take pity
on my hair Armando.
What do you want
me to do with this?
I know, I know, up.
Up and big.
Big.
We need, blonder, we need
bigger, we need sexy!
Who's a bad girl?
Who's a sexual kitten?
Me!
Yes! Scissors!
-Ready?
-Yeah.
[sigh] Another
masterpiece by Armando.
You look beautiful.
[quiet music]
Paula, over here?
Wow, what have you
done to your hair?
Don't you love it?
We're talking about what
to do for New Years.
Didn't you and Nick
ski Aspen last winter?
Oh, I'm sure we did.
I don't you remember you
staying in the condo.
Maybe we stayed
in a hotel.
You wouldn't
stay in a hotel,
because you have a condo
right next to Liz.
-Who's Liz?
-I am.
Right. That Liz.
Are you okay?
We here Nick has
a new publicist.
I think he
needed a new one.
Quite attractive I hear.
I hear she's brilliant
with the press.
Is she invited
to your party?
My party?
Christmas Eve party.
Wow, god, you know
I completely forgot
about that party.
I'm just going to
have to talk to Martina
and we'll throw
something together.
Oh right.
So, what are you wearing?
Mm...the red dress.
(Laughter)
Yes!
Mrs. Kensington, it's so
good to see you again.
Yes, well, it's the dream
dress...for a dream.
$1,200.
I know, plus tax.
Wrap it up please.
And would you like to
see the night gowns
we just got in from Paris?
Just came in this morning.
Just to tempt you.
How much?
$800 each.
$800 for a nightgown?
From Paris.
Right, a steal.
Why don't I just fly the
Paris and pick up a few.
You could.
Yes, yes I could.
We are going to
fly to Paris.
It will be the perfect
Christmas gift.
London, Paris, Rome.
[squeal]
Where are we going?
Oh yes, yes, yes.
Maybe something tropical.
Tropical or romantic.
Tropical/romantic,
tropical/romantic.
[laughter]
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Hello, Mrs. Kensington?
Oh hi, I'm just
here to see Nick.
Mr. Kensington is busy;
he's in a private meeting.
Oh, who with?
He's doing press packets.
Oh, well did he say
how long he would be?
He didn't say.
(Knock on door)
Nick?
Hi.
I told her you
were busy.
I'm in the middle of
something here Paula.
What would you like?
Oh, I just wanted to
ask you something.
Ask me?
It was kind of a
personal matter.
Can this wait until later?
Sure.
Yeah, of course.
Oh, hey, where do you want
to have dinner tonight?
Ahh...
Dinner?
I'll be home
at 7 o'clock.
Okay, I'll have Martina make
up something special, huh?
Don't go out of your way
to do anything special.
Roxanne...
No more
interruptions.
Boy he could really
use a vacation huh?
Which do you think
he would prefer -
a tour of Europe, or a
Mediterranean cruise?
He hates the water.
Right, right.
Well, Europe is still lovely
this time of year, right?
I'm back.
Talk about shop
until you drop,
I'll tell
you what...
and you know,
I used every single
credit card in my purse.
Gosh, wait till you
see what I'm wearing
to dinner tonight.
Oh, where are you going?
We're dining in tonight.
Who is?
Nick and I.
So could you make
something sexy?
I have only
frozen fish.
Okay, well fish
can be sexy.
Fish with a little
something on it.
Something sexy?
Yeah.
[speaking Spanish]
Okay.
And we are having a
party on Christmas eve,
so we are really going to
have to talk about the food.
What food?
It's catered.
-It's catered?
-Yeah.
I am in heaven.
Well I will be up
in my bathroom
having a luxurious Jacuzzi.
[unclear]
[¶]
[sigh]
[laughs]
I love Paris...
when it drizzles.
That's how it happens...
...one day the mind,
she's gone.
And I'm going to love
Paris in the summer
when it's sizzles!
Hey Martina, guess who
bought two tickets
to Paris -
where it sizzles?
Who needs this
many lights?
Nick Kensington does.
Didn't he marry
your old girlfriend?
Just keep doing what
you're doing Reg.
I see you're over her turning
you down for the prom.
Haven't you got some
lights to hang?
I will come down
off this ladder.
Easy big fella.
Gary?
What are you doing here?
Hi Paula, Nick hired me to
put up the Christmas lights.
How are you?
-Good.
So, we haven't seen
each other since...
...since the gallery opening.
Oh right.
Yeah, Janine and I
had a great time.
Thank you.
Oh right.
Oh, so you would
be with Janine?
Well yeah, since
after high school.
We...
How are your kids?
You have kids right?
Yeah, two girls.
Eleanor and Olivia.
Yeah.
Have you met them?
Okay, Gary was here.
Why?
Why, why, why, why would
I put Gary in my dream?
And how long do
dreams last exactly?
And why am I
talking to myself?
Do you think I have
too much jewelry on?
If you were a float
in a parade no,
but for a person, yes.
What time does Nick...
Mr. Kensington, usually
get home from work?
Oh Mr. K, he's often late.
He probably has lots to
do at the office, huh?
Recently, yes.
Mr. Kensington,
it's almost 7,
I'm leaving.
I got more
Christmas shopping.
It's okay,
I'll lock up.
Good night Roxanne.
Good night.
Don't you have some
shopping to do?
I have everything I want
for Christmas right here.
Yes you do.
[music playing]
You know I'm thinking
maybe he stopped off
for some champagne.
Uh huh...
Or maybe even flowers.
Okay.
Hey, I am not drinking
by myself anymore,
so I am pouring
you a glass.
No thank you.
Oh, I insist.
What shall we 'cheers' to?
To new beginnings
at Christmas.
Are you having
a new beginning?
Yes.
I better go and
check the sexy fish.
No wait, wait, wait.
It's my turn.
We're going to 'cheers'.
To new beginnings
at Christmas time.
Did I tell you I feel like
I'm on my first date?
Yes, many times, and your
first date is very late.
Yes, well he was
at the office
meeting with his
new publicist;
they seem to be getting
along very well.
He gets along with women.
I wonder why we
never had kids?
Do you ever wonder
why we never had kids?
No I didn't.
And I'm going to check
the fish, I think,
now it's not so sexy.
Oh wait, what song
should I put on?
What do Nick and I
usually dance to?
He doesn't dance.
-He doesn't?
-No.
Yeah, you know,
he never danced
in high school either.
Now you're seeing
the problems.
[door opens]
Uh-oh.
Dinner ready?
Well hello there stranger!
Turn off that noise.
Well, I thought we'd
do a little samba
before dinner.
What are you
talking about?
I just finished
a long day.
And those damn photos
didn't turn out
for the press packet.
I'm sorry, but you know
samba can be relaxing.
Come on, I'll teach you.
What are you doing?
We don't dance.
Loosen up Nick, come
on, give it a shot.
Come on, it'll be fun.
How much wine
have you had?
Just a couple of glasses.
Why did you stop by today?
Sit down first.
I got you an early
Christmas gift.
We've already
given each other
our Christmas
presents Paula.
Well this is extra.
What is it?
Well, you sir
work way too hard,
and we need a vacation.
I'm starting to feel
very awkward here Paula.
Your dress,
the dancing...
what are you doing?
Paris.
Two tickets; you and moi.
Hotel, spa, museums,
art shows...
We're not going
to Paris Paula.
Okay. It doesn't
have to be Paris.
We could go to Zurich.
What are you
talking about?
What do you mean?
We're getting a divorce.
A divorce?
We're not going anywhere
together, ever again.
That doesn't make sense.
We're having a catered
party on Christmas Eve.
Well, the divorce
is your idea;
come to think of it,
so is the party.
My idea?
Is this some ploy to
re-negotiate the settlement?
Everything is signed.
Paperwork goes through
midnight Christmas Eve.
Midnight?
That's when the sweet
table comes out.
You never could finish
anything could you?
The riding lessons;
cooking classes;
your attempt at art.
Well, I'm finishing
this one for you;
we're over, as is
this conversation.
[soft music]
[sigh]
I need to talk to Nick.
Are you kidding me?
You asked for this
divorce a year ago.
I don't want this now.
Well, it's a little
late for that.
Please, can't we just
try to work this out?
Maybe you should
see Dr. Degolia,
and have him adjust your
prescription again.
No, I don't need a
prescription Nick.
I need you.
After $100,000
in legal fees?
I don't want to have this
conversation with you anymore.
Understand?
Well Nick, maybe
there's something
we haven't tried.
How about counseling.
We spent three years
with Dr. Marson.
But we have everything we
need to make ourselves
perfectly happy.
It doesn't even
make sense.
That's what I
thought a year ago,
but apparently I
made you miserable.
Nick, I don't want us...
this life to just end.
You're unbelievable,
you know that?
You still don't
care about me.
You know I didn't
hear you say, Nick,
I realized I made a
big mistake, or Nick,
I've always loved you,
I'll try to be
a better wife.
All you care about is
having an expense account.
Anyway...
...it doesn't
matter anymore.
The papers are signed.
I'm moving on
with my life,
you should too.
At my age I'd
like the chance
to be with someone
who loves me.
Like Sheila.
Sheila loves me for who I
am, not what I can give.
You know back in
high school Nick,
I dated Gary Ferguson too.
Did you know that?
And I could have gone to the
prom with either one of you,
but in this life
I chose you.
And your point is?
That I chose you!
Life's all about
choices Paula,
every step of the way.
Honey, I just need...
oh...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We're done.
Okay, I'm ready to
go home now, okay?
This isn't fun anymore.
I want to wake up
from this dream now.
[Olivia's voice echoes]
Mommy?
Can we keep him?
Mommy, Mommy...Mommy.
Mommy, look what I made.
I love you Mommy.
Oh.
Well, Toto, looks like
we're not getting back
to Kansas.
Can I get you
anything Mrs. K.?
[Music]
Hello? Hello?
Can you hear me?
You lost a sock?
I can't get back.
I can't get back and I've
made a terrible mistake.
Get back?
Where are you going?
I thought this was
where happiness is,
but I need my family back.
[music throughout]
[family laughing and talking]
-You girls...
-I love you.
[music continues]
Mrs. K., you're just
too tired, that's all.
Let's get you to bed.
[Spanish]
You just
need some rest.
[Spanish]
I just want to go home.
You are home.
[girls laughing]
This is so fun.
[voices echo]
Hey Olivia want to come
and play with me and mom?
Hey Mom, can we go up
to the park please?
I love you mom.
I think you're
the coolest.
So how'd you do on your
Global Studies test?
Okay I guess.
The teacher hates me.
She doesn't hate you;
she says such good things
about on parent night.
Potatoes!
Wait a second, what
is she doing here?
Ellie!
How many times have
we talked about this.
No teacher hates you.
Did you just
call her Ellie?
She hates that.
You hate that right?
Miss Becker hates
me; trust me mom.
What?
Did you just call her mom.
Are you kidding me?
Why can't anybody hear me?
Daddy, can we do that
new dance you taught me,
again tonight.
You know,
the Zipperbug?
It's
Jitterbug sweetie,
but daddy always dances
with mommy first.
This can't be happening!
Why can't anybody see me?
Why has she
stolen my family?
[drill noise]
Gary?
Lights, lights.
It's got that funny
sound in it again.
Really?
Yeah.
I bought it used.
Janine will kill me if I
have to buy another one.
So, what does Janine think
about you working here?
We need the money.
Yeah.
Janine's a great lady.
[clears throat]
Hi Reg.
How you doing Gary?
Oh, good, good.
You'll tell me if the
reindeer are all crooked.
I don't want to give you
any crooked reindeer.
Santa's very meticulous
about the reindeer.
No, it looks great.
I mean, I think the middle
one looks like it's ready
for takeoff, but...
Is that Dasher or Donner,
because usually I have
trouble with Blitzen.
You know what, I'll just
straighten the reindeer.
How come you put up
all these lights
at Nick's house
and not ours?
At ours?
At yours.
At your house.
Well, one I get paid I'll
put my lights up at home.
I got a little trouble
with the drill right now.
Reg can't tell if it's the
motor or the cable, so...
Really?
I'm sorry to hear that,
but maybe it's a really
good time to take a break.
And go grab some lunch?
Lunch?
Yeah, I'm going
down to the club.
It is so festive there;
you would love it.
Actually Janine packed
me a club sandwich,
so that's about the only
club I'm gonna taste today.
Yeah, but I thought maybe it
could be a really good time
for us to do
some catching up.
It's my treat.
Nick's treat.
Yeah, he's doing
pretty well,
but I think I'm
gonna hang with Reg.
Gary, don't you remember
when you used to pick me up
from work and we'd go
have lunch at the Bluffs?
Yeah I do, I do
remember that.
That was a long time ago.
I'm just going to Armando's
and to do a little shopping.
I could be back and pick
you up around noon.
Uh, noon.
I've got a lot
of work to do;
a lot of work to do,
but thank you.
Janine made me
that sandwich,
so that's what
I'm going to have.
You could drive.
Really...
Thank you.
So what's up?
I think she was
coming on to me.
[music throughout]
Olivia!
Oh god, I'm so sorry.
I thought you were
somebody else.
I didn't mean to
scare you, okay?
That's quite all right.
Come along honey.
(Doorbell)
Oh, Paula?
I was in the
neighbourhood.
Are you looking for Gary?
Yeah, I need
to talk to him.
Oh, he's not home yet;
he had to get
something fixed.
[laughs]
Do you know when
he will be home?
Is there a problem with
the Christmas lights?
Yeah, sort of.
-Go fish.
-Whoa, I have 5 aces.
-It's not an ace,
it's the joker.
-Okay, I'll take it back.
-Daddy says the joker mild.
-That's wild, but
not in this game.
You have such
a lovely tree.
Your turn.
Gary probably picked it up
off the side of the road.
He's so creative
that way.
But the kids don't care,
they're just excited
Santa's coming!
Right girls?
-Too men.
-Those are jacks.
Hi girls.
Say hello to Mrs.
Kensington girls.
-Hi.
-Whatever.
-They're mine.
-Okay, go fish.
-I just did.
Thanks.
Wat--
Oh!
Watch up for the pool of
ketchup next to your arm.
[phone rings]
Mom, if that's Cody
I'm not home.
Hello, Ferguson
Construction here.
Ma'am our records indicate
you're way past due.
Honey, if we
could pay you,
we would pay
everyone else too.
Unacceptable...
Well, Merry
Christmas to you too.
Could I use the bathroom?
Sure, you'll have to use the
kid's bathroom upstairs,
the toilet down here is
having plumbing issues.
It's broken?
Of course it is.
Okay go fish.
Are you looking
for the bathroom?
OH! Oh my god.
I didn't mean
to scare you.
It's okay.
Janine told me that
you have something
to talk to me about.
Yeah, I do.
Okay, shoot.
Oh, I'm not quite sure
how to say this thing.
What is it?
I miss you Gary.
I miss our
life together.
Our life together?
Gary?
Do you want your
white shirt for tonight?
Sure.
Paula, that was
ancient history.
That was high school.
No, not really.
Are you guys going out?
Oh yeah, Janine and
I like to go dancing.
You know,
you used to
like to dance.
I still do.
Well, you
know what,
you should Nick on
the dance floor.
We go to this great local
place just down the road.
In fact, I gotta
get changed,
otherwise Janine's gonna
hit me with a wooden spoon.
Gary, I just want you to--
I'm sorry.
I just want you to know
that I think you're
incredibly handy.
Nick, he's not so handy.
Well, Nick has his
talents and I have mine,
so if you need
anything fixed,
I'll be right over
in a heartbeat.
Did you ever wonder
what it would be like
if you married
somebody else?
Like who?
Like me?
Like you and me?
Don't you feel
anything for me?
Well, Paula, I know
about the divorce,
and I'm really sorry
that you couldn't work
things out with Nick.
This is so weird, here
we are you and me,
in our house, with our
kids downstairs...
You know what, you can't
be saying those kinds
of things because my family
is right downstairs.
It sounds a little crazy,
but I know that you're not,
I know that
you're not crazy.
Do you want me to
bring this shirt up?
I'll come and
get it honey.
I'll tell you what,
I'm going to come
over tomorrow
and I'm going
to put up your lights.
That way your house
is looking great
for the Christmas party
and I know that will
brighten up your day.
Is it hard
working for Nick?
I don't think about it.
The kids need things and
bills need to be paid,
and there's just not a lot
of work around Christmas.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay go.
Three nines.
Okay, my turn.
Hey, hey...
Hi...
Mrs. Kensington.
Hi.
I'm gonna go.
Gotta go rest up for your
big Christmas eve party
tomorrow night?
I hope you two
will be there -
and you, of course,
too Reg.
Yeah, Nick already
invited us.
We'll see.
The kids might be tired;
we might be tired.
I think I have plans.
Sorry.
Well, no, I mean, you
guys have to come.
I wouldn't know
what to wear.
No, it's not
like that.
Come as you are.
You two kids go already.
Come on girls, let's get
you upstairs to bed.
Coming.
Night.
Goodnight Dad.
All right, you
ready to go dance?
[laughter]
Okay then,
I gotta go.
Hang on.
Hey, we'll see you
tomorrow; hang in there.
Shall we?
What was that all about?
Problems at home.
What's that got
to do with you?
It's me sweetheart.
You have nothing
to worry about,
so let's go.
Mrs. K., are you
looking for something?
Where's Gary?
I don't know.
What do you mean?
He had a problem with his
drill, so he had to go.
He says not to worry,
the lights still be done
in time for the party.
[Music]
You came back.
I told Martina I
wouldn't let you down.
I just had to get
my drill fixed.
Is there anything
I can do to help?
Come in.
I was just afraid that you
weren't going to come back,
you know.
I just felt like maybe you
were going leave me here.
Please don't
leave me here.
Leave you here?
It's okay.
I just really
want to come home.
I understand.
You do?
Of course I do.
You do? You want me
to come home too?
I want you to be happy.
Yeah, right now I'm happy.
That's good.
You know what I want?
I really just want
you to kiss me.
I can't.
Here's the thing Paula.
I made a choice
a long time ago.
And?
And I'm happy
with that.
Right.
Right. Choices.
Paula, I'm sorry.
I'm taken.
I don't think I can get
out the way I came in,
so...
if you'll excuse me.
Mrs. Kensington,
what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm not
Mrs. Kensington,
I'm Mrs. Ferguson!
You're not okay.
What's really
bothering you?
Oh, everything.
My life is so empty.
Here I am, finally,
with all this money,
and it means nothing.
Why am I so miserable?
Because life without love,
it is not worth anything.
Yeah, that's true.
I know.
I have love in my life.
You do?
Yeah.
I've been married for
23 years with Carlos
and we have raised three boys
and I'm a grandmother too.
You are?
You raised three boys?
How come I
didn't know this?
You never ask.
Oh, I'm sorry Martina.
I should have asked
you about your life.
Was I good to you?
You've been nice.
I make a nice life
with my family,
my boys are happy.
That's what's important.
Yeah, I made a nice life
with my family once too,
and I just let it go.
Now I want it back.
All of it!
But I don't know how to
get back through the dryer.
Do you know that I
have two little girls?
I didn't know that.
And Gary and I, we've been
married for 18 years.
Mr. Ferguson,
the light man?
Yeah.
And now my biggest fear is
that I'm going to be stuck
here in this world and
I'm never going to get
my old one back.
I miss my little girls.
I miss them, and
I miss everything.
It was really good,
you know; it was good.
And Gary and I, we
really love each other.
Mrs. K.
I need to call
Dr. Degolia, okay?
I'm going to go shopping.
I just need to make
sure that they both
get to this address.
This one needs to have
Eleanor's name on it
and this one, this
one is Olivia.
Do you want to
include a gift card?
Um, no.
No gift card.
I need you to make sure
that they get there
tonight, though.
On Christmas Eve?
Please?
Of course,
Mrs. Kensington.
I'll personally see to it
that they arrive tonight.
Promise?
I'll take care of it.
Merry Christmas to you.
Yes, right,
American Express...
Right, same address,
for Gary Ferguson.
And that's the high
speed cordless drill.
Right, and make sure he
gets an extra battery
and a super charger.
No, I know, I need
it on Christmas -
it's a Christmas gift.
It will be there
tonight, right?
Okay, thank you.
Ho Ho Ho.
Merry Christmas!
Ho Ho Ho, holy mackerel!
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas to you.
[Music]
White wine?
Fabulous
decorations,
ample food, and
decent drink.
You'd never know.
Best divorce party I've
been to on a Christmas Eve.
Poor Paula.
And where is she?
No sign of her.
Seen plenty of
Sheila though.
Living room, far corner.
I feel like people
are staring at me.
So what, It's my party
and I want you here.
The timing
might look odd.
The timing is perfect.
In an hour and a half,
I'll be a free man.
You don't want me
to get snaffled up
by someone else, do you?
I do not.
I want you all to myself.
If I were Paula I'd make
sure I got the Condo.
She'll land on her feet.
I know her.
Your guests
are here.
They're wondering
where you are.
Is Gary here?
Everybody else
is here, but no,
Mr. Ferguson is not here.
You should come down
and greet your guests.
I don't really have
anything to say.
Well, just say
Merry Christmas;
thank you for coming;
I like your dress;
try the crab cakes.
[music and chatter throughout]
Thank you for coming.
I love your dress.
[chatter continues]
Oh Paula!
Oh...
have you tried
to crab cake?
No, should I?
I don't know.
I don't know; Martina
told me to say that.
You know, I want
to tell you that I hope
that you and Nick are actually
really very happy together.
Really?
That's good of you to say.
I was never
right for him.
I'm sure he
told you that.
I think you will be.
Merry Christmas.
Excuse me.
For you.
Oh.
This is too beautiful!
Do you like them?
This is too much.
No, no it isn't.
Gosh, you're such a
good friend to me.
You deserve these.
No, this is
too much money.
It's not enough money.
You're always
there for me.
You deserve these.
Merry Christmas.
Gracias.
He's not coming.
You never know when
a door will open.
He's not coming.
Paula?
Hi!
I didn't think you
were going to come.
Here.
For me?
You didn't have
to do that.
Better not be expensive.
Trust me, it's not.
[Music]
How did you know?
You've been so
unhappy lately;
I though this will
make you smile.
Paula? Paula?
-Mommy, wake up!
-Mom, are you okay?
-Paula?
-I think she's waking up!
-Mom wake up!
Mom, are you okay?
Mommy, Mommy!
We were so
worried about you!
Hi. Hi!
I missed you guys so much.
I missed you guys so much!
Let me see you.
Mommy, Mommy,
come upstairs.
Look at the tree.
Okay, let's do that.
No place like home huh?
There's no
place like home.
I'll tell you what, come
on, let's see that tree.
I love the tree.
[doorbell]
[door closes]
Who can these
be from, huh?
Look!
Open them,
open them!
There's no name
on the tag.
Me either.
These are awesome!
Whoever they are, this is
exactly what I wanted.
Maybe it's from Santa.
But he forgot to get
one for you mommy.
I don't need one.
I have everything
I want, right here.
I think I can fix that.
This is for you.
You've been so
unhappy lately,
I thought this would
make you smile.
It's exactly
what I wanted!
[Music]
I love you, you know that?
¶ Jingle bells, Jingle
bells, jingle all the way. ¶
Put this one on
the tree girls.
¶ Oh what fun it is to ride
in a one-horse open sleigh. ¶
¶ Jingle bells, jingle bells,
jingle all the way. ¶
¶ Oh what fun it is to ride
in a one-horse open sleigh. ¶
¶ Jingle bells, Jingle
bells, jingle all the way. ¶
¶ Oh what fun it is to ride
in a one-horse open sleigh. ¶
¶ Jingle bells, Jingle
bells, jingle all the way. ¶
¶ Oh what fun it is to ride
in a one-horse open sleigh. ¶
Honey?
¶ Dashing through the snow
In a one-horse open sleigh ¶
¶ O'er the fields we go,
laughing all the way. ¶
-May I have this dance?
-I'd love it.
¶ Bells on bobtails ring,
making spirits bright. ¶
¶ What fun it is
to laugh and sing ¶
¶ this sleighing
song tonight. ¶
[laughter, chatter]
¶ Jingle bells, Jingle bells,
jingle all the way. ¶
¶ Oh what fun it
is to ride ¶
¶ in a one-horse
open sleigh. ¶
¶ Oh jingle bells,
jingle all the way. ¶
¶ Oh what fun it is to ride
in a one-horse open sleigh. ¶