♪
(crash)
- You okay?
Shit.
(panting)
You okay, man?
- Dude! That was awesome!
(howls)
What took you so long?
- How's your leg?
- It's better now.
- What is this place?
- I don't know, man.
It's like an old mine
shaft or something.
- No.
Not way out in the middle,
holy shit!
- That thing is awesome.
What is that?
It's like a real dead guy.
- What the hell is this place?
- Oh my.
Look at the tits on that one.
- No seriously,
what is this place?
- It's pretty spooky, man.
Woah, man. Get your
light over here.
Check this out.
Let's see if we can
move this thing.
- Hey, hey, hey.
I wouldn't be moving
that door if I were you.
- You're such a pussy sometimes.
Come on, man. Help me out.
- Hey, watch out!
(rumbling)
(screams)
(suspenseful exotic music)
(rock music)
- [Sam] The victim died of
massive internal trauma.
How do you even know
this site is safe?
- [Swartek] Because it's my
job to know how to secure
an archaeological find, okay?
Now, if I need to ever
conduct an autopsy,
I'll be sure to give you a call.
- I'm the coroner in this!
You see what I'm
dealing with here?
- Sam.
Sam, it's alright.
Now look, the last
thing any of us wants
is another accident.
I just think you should
consider stopping the work
here until we can be assured
that your kids will be safe.
- Sheriff, this is a sensitive
historical discovery.
Okay, I will not allow
untrained personnel
to disturb any of the artifacts.
- Where do you get
the authority?!
- The governor's office,
National Park Service,
Secretary of the
Interior, take your pick.
Need I remind either one of you
that we're discussing
federal land here?
- No sir, you don't
need to remind me.
This ain't my first rodeo.
But let's be clear
about something.
Federal jurisdiction or not.
If I decide that this site
is a danger to the public,
including you and your students,
I'm shutting you down.
- Got it. Understand.
- Good.
Come on, Sam.
Take care of yourself, miss.
Be careful.
- Molly.
- Professor Swartek.
- Hey.
- What was that all about?
- Oh, nothing.
You know, just the usual.
Dealing with the bureaucracy.
So'd you have any trouble
finding the place?
- No.
No, not really.
Signs would've been nice, but.
- Yeah. Right.
Well, we don't actually want
anyone else to find this place.
So.
- Why? What's going on?
- Well,
I'm gonna show you.
- Why all the secrecy?
- You'll see.
- Oh my.
Is that?
- Come on.
Careful going down though.
This first step, a
little difficult.
(light apprehensive music)
- This can't be.
- Pretty great, huh?
- [Dr. Ben-David] Be
careful. All of you.
There may be more traps.
- Is that who I think it is?
- Mm-hmm.
- Axel, help me with the door.
- Look out!
- Carter.
It is safe. Just,
Axel, get some lights in there.
Do not touch anything.
Once we get some
lights, we begin work.
- Professor.
Professor, I'd like to
introduce you to someone,
Mrs. Molly Kirnan.
Remember, the grad
student I told you about?
Molly, this is,
- Professor Ari Ben-David
of Cairo University.
I am a great admirer
of your epigraphy
of the sacara in Necropolis.
- Kara, we need the CCS let
out by the end of the day.
- [Kara] Not a problem.
- Molly is a historical
linguistics specialist.
Her work in
pre-dynastic phonograms
is pretty remarkable, actually.
- Ah, so what do you think
of our little discovery.
- It can't be real.
- Preliminary electrocarbon
analysis dates this site
at 2654 BCE.
- What is a Third
Dynasty burial chamber
doing in southern California?
- Well, 10 years ago,
Balabanova discovered
arithrozylin coca
and nicotiana tobacum
in the hair shafts
of ancient Egyptian mummies.
- Yeah, nicotine, cocaine.
- Plants that only existed
in the western hemisphere
during the age of the pharaohs.
- And Professor
Ben-David's long theory
is that the Egyptians
must have formed
some kind of
trans-Atlantic trade route.
- And now I believe my theories
have been proven fact.
There are far too many
similarities between Egyptian
and Inca step pyramids for it
just to be mere coincidence.
- [Axel] Ready doctor.
- Ah. Please, come.
Everybody. Come.
(light intriguing music)
When I discovered the Mustavas
at Tamadosan Sacara,
I discovered an execration text
that described a young priestess
banished from Egypt
because she claimed
to be a living god.
The name of that priestess
is the same as the
one that is in here,
Aneh-Tet.
Aneh-Tet was a priestess of Zet,
the god of chaos and evil.
Zet members believed
they would be given
the great power to cast spells,
to raise the dead,
and to be given eternal life.
But Aneh-Tet's powers
threatened Josier,
the ruling pharaoh at the time,
and so he had her banished
across the great water.
Egyptologists assumed
this meant the Red Sea.
It appears the truth
written on these walls.
It is a mystery that will
take much to unravel.
I see symbols predate
heiroglyphs that we know
by 2,000 years.
So,
let's have a look
at her, shall we?
(suspenseful drum music)
- How did she die?
- The Egyptians believed
that when they passed
to the underworld,
they would become
powerful and mighty,
and Aneh-Tet had
herself mummified,
so that when she is resurrected,
she will return as a living god.
- What happens then?
- It says here,
that the ka or the spirit
of Aneh-Tet
shall return to
her rightful place
as the pharaoh of Egypt.
- Excuse me, but I,
I think that this actually
says that she who's name
brings terror,
shall rise up from
the underworld,
and bring forth those who
will destroy her enemies,
and take her place
as supreme ruler
of both the living and the dead.
- Yes. Well,
what say we all
take a quick lunch.
We have much work to do.
It is Molly, right?
It is very important that
nobody know about this site
until we have finished our work.
Do you understand?
- Yeah, of course.
- If this turns out to
be what I think it is,
it will be the
discovery of a lifetime.
- I understand.
- Your skills will
be very useful here.
- I'll do what I can.
- I don't care
(unrecognizable) Imratep,
not Imsatep.
- That's totally right.
- No it's not.
You read it totally wrong,
'cause I was right
there next to you.
- Come on, baby.
(light intriguing music)
(reading wall)
(intense music)
- Oh shit. Bryan.
- Good, Molly.
Now we can talk about el-Amarna.
- There's nothing to talk about.
- How could you say that?
I mean, we were just,
- Professor Edwards.
- What is it, Carter?
- How do I get
back to the motel?
- What happened to Santos?
- I heard he left.
Everybody's gone.
- Ah, shit.
Carter, you can
take Molly, okay?
- Well no.
I don't wanna, I wanna.
- It's fine.
You have to check in anyway,
and Carter knows
how to get there.
Problem solved.
It's fine.
- Okay.
(light rock music with singing)
Is this the right way?
Is this how it's
gonna be between us?
- What did you expect?
- I thought we could be friends.
Carter, we weren't even dating.
- You know how I felt about you.
And I thought you
felt the same way.
- I did.
- Then why?
- It was a mistake.
His wife had just left him.
He reached out to me.
I was drunk.
Haven't you ever
slept with somebody
and then regretted it?
- Hope you got a
good grade at least.
- Fuck you Carter.
Home.
(light jazzy rocky music)
(phone ringing)
- Yo.
- [Molly] Hey Kev, it's me.
Is mom there?
- No.
She's working a double.
Where are you?
- I'm headed to a hotel.
- Are you with a guy?
- I'm on a dig.
- [Kevyn] Yawn.
- Listen, I didn't think
it was gonna be anything,
so I didn't bring any clothes,
and I was gonna ask mom
to bring a bag tomorrow,
but if she's
- I'll do it.
- [Molly] What about school?
- Do you want your
clothes or not?
- [Molly] Yeah.
Yeah, okay. Alright.
- Cool. Where am I going?
- Is that...
- Alright, got a pen and paper?
Okay, it's the Tropic Motel.
It's at 49001 Route 72.
- I'll see you at noon.
- [Molly] I wanna
be on site at six.
- Dream on.
- [Molly] Okay, eight.
- Cool. I'll see you at 10.
(foreboding music)
(crickets)
(apprehensive music)
(reading wall)
(thunder)
(strange deep whispering voices)
(intense apprehensive music)
- What are you doing here?
Who are you?
- I'm one of Professor
Swartek's students.
I was just, I was
making a translation.
- Not now, you aren't.
No one is supposed to be
in the tomb unsupervised.
- But, they didn't.
- Don't you know there was
a death here five days ago?
- No, I didn't.
- I think we need to
talk to the professor.
- No, that's not necessary.
I'll just go back to the hotel.
- You don't wanna see
Professor Swartek?
I thought you were his student.
- It's complicated.
- Come on.
- Molly.
- [Dennis] I found her
in the tomb, professor.
She said she was a
student of yours.
- She is. It's fine, Dennis.
- [Dennis] You said that
no one goes in the tomb
without yours or Dr.
Ben-David's permission.
- And that's right.
That's right. That's fine,
but I'll take care of it.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Well,
this is good.
Now we can finish
our conversation.
Bryan, don't.
- What's the matter?
You didn't have a problem
with it last summer?
- Last summer was a mistake.
- Oh, I see.
- No, that's not what I mean.
I was drunk.
- So that means you don't
have to take responsibility
for what happened?
Is that what you're saying?
- No, that's not
what I'm saying.
Please don't be this way.
Listen, Bryan.
I respect you so much,
and you've done so much for me,
but I just want our relationship
to stay professional.
That's all.
- Fine.
- I really want
us to be friends.
- Good night Molly.
- I'm gonna be a
little late tomorrow.
My sister's bringing
me some clothes.
- Look, obviously
you're gonna do
what you wanna do. Okay?
So just do it.
Just try and get back
here when you can.
Aneh-Tet's not going anywhere.
- Kara.
Hey, it's Bryan Swartek.
How are you?
Good, good.
I was just wondering if
maybe you could come up
to the site tonight and
help me finish the typology
for the artifacts.
Why not?
(apprehensive wind sound)
(thunder)
(sparks)
(apprehensive music)
(intense rumblings
and wind sound)
- Who's there?
You're naked.
(groaning)
(string music)
- Kara, is that you?
(screaming)
(intense wind)
- I'll go wake
Professor Swartek.
- Oh, is that what you call it?
- Not cool, man.
Not cool.
- I mean...
- Professor?
(screaming)
- Where is my mummy?!
- Piece of shit.
- Kevyn.
- You so owe me.
(apprehensive music)
- Oh, I really appreciate
you doing this Kev.
- You could buy me some beer.
- I'm kidding.
- What's the wait?
I gotta get going.
- [Motel manager] Hey, you!
Get out of there!
- What's that?
- I don't know.
- Come here. Come here.
- Is everything okay?
- Is she one of yours?
Well get some clothes on her.
This is a family business.
- Okay, okay.
Here.
Come with us, okay?
- [Molly] I'll get
some more towels.
- Okay.
My name's Kevyn.
Yeah, I know, I've already
heard all the jokes.
Kevyn. My name's Kevyn.
- Aneh-Tet.
- Annette? Your name's Annette?
Let's cover you up.
Here.
What are you doing?
- How we doing?
- Well, I found out that
her name is Annette.
And she's gay.
- Annette?
(speaking French)
(speaking Spanish)
(speaking Hebrew)
(speaking unknown language)
- What was that?
Did you understand that?
(speaking unknown language)
- What did she say?!
- It's impossible.
- What?
- She's speaking a
language that's been dead
for 3,000 years.
You guys stay here.
I'm gonna go find
Professor Swartek, okay?
- I'm calling Mom and telling
her I'm staying with you
for the weekend.
Stay here, okay?
- Yeah, we won't be able to
properly identify the bodies
until we get some DNA testing.
- My god.
- She's not one of yours?
- No.
- Excuse me, miss.
Miss. Miss, just
stop right there.
Who are you?
Did you hear me?
I asked you a question.
You don't wanna listen, do you?
(rumblings, wind,
unrecognizable voices)
- What's wrong?
- Professor Swartek is dead.
- Oh my god, no way.
- I just saw him last night.
- It was bad.
- What are you talking about?
What happened?
- I've gotta go find out.
Stay here.
- Wow.
- I told you to wait outside.
- Please.
- Dr. Ben-David? Annette?
- Molly.
- What's going on?
- I see that you have met
my assistant from Cairo.
- Your assistant?
- Yes.
I believe she can be very
helpful with the translations.
Why? What were you thinking?
That Aneh-Tet,
High Priestess of Setekh,
had risen from the dead?
(laughs)
- No, of course not.
It's not possible.
- No, it isn't, is it?
- North wall.
Grids seven, eight, and nine
depict the life symbol ankh,
surrounded by six
warrior figures,
and six upside down figures,
unattested in any
known translations.
The six warriors
probably represent
the six mummies
found in the tomb,
but I don't understand
the other figures.
They could be
representations of something
they'll become.
Something more powerful.
(playing and laughing)
(rap music)
(laughs)
- You're drinking this time.
- I told you, I don't drink.
- Oh, shut up. Do it again.
- Oh!
- Don't mess with the reflex.
- Drink dude!
- Kevyn!
- Molly.
- What are you doing?
- Do you know what
this guy can do?
Show my sister what you can do.
- I don't think
she'll be impressed.
- Hey, come back here!
- Hey, you know what?
I think you've had enough?
- Your sister was cool, Molly.
- She's 17.
Give me that.
- Head rush.
- Alright, come on.
Let's get you to the room.
- Hey Axe, we're
going to bed too man.
- You okay?
- Oh yeah, as long as the
bill holds out, I'm all,
"Y'all have fun!"
- We will, we will.
- Go have fun.
- Howdy.
You Dr. Ben-David?
- Yes.
- I'm J.L. Jones.
I'm the county
sheriff around here.
You wouldn't happen to
know where my deputy is?
- No, he left us hours ago.
Why?
- He hasn't checked in.
I found his car abandoned
at the county line
20 miles from here.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- He didn't happen to
say where he was going,
did he?
- No sheriff. I'm sorry.
- It's okay, I'm just
trying to retrace his steps.
You'll call if you or your
students hear anything.
- Of course.
- Oh.
That original call.
Something to do with
a missing person,
or a stolen mummy
or something, right?
- Yes.
But everything is all right now.
We have found her.
- Good, good.
Good evening.
- Finish that water, Kev.
- That Carter guy
is in love with you.
- I know.
- What's wrong? He's cute.
You both like boring stuff.
You're perfect for each other.
- It's not gonna happen.
- Why not?
- Because I did something
that really hurt him.
- So. It's not like
either one of you is dead.
If you care about him,
like do something about it.
- And everyone says
I'm the smart one.
(laughs)
- Jones.
- [Sam] Sheriff, Sam.
- What do you have for me?
- Both victims died of
massive dehydration.
- Look, I admit I'm not the
sharpest tool in the shed,
but I know those two guys
didn't die of thirst.
- [Sam] Talking
about 80% water loss
in less than what I
count at one minute.
- What could cause that?
- I have no idea,
but you haven't heard
the best part yet.
I found foreign skin and
hair samples on both bodies.
- [Sheriff] So,
we have a suspect?
- No, no, no. Not there yet.
Cannot figure a way a human
being could have done this.
I've extracted DNA,
analyzing it now.
- Well, I need answers, Sam.
- I'm doing what I can, Jim.
But this is two deaths now.
Isn't that enough
to shut 'em down?
- I've been calling the
governor's office all day,
but this character Ben-David
seems to have some juice.
I need more.
- [Sam] I'll call you
when I have something.
- Let's hope that's
just soon enough.
- Oh man.
I'm gonna get me something.
Hey, wait for me!
Yes. Thank you.
Hey, where'd you go?!
Shit, you scared me.
Stop.
Shit.
You like it rough.
That's cool.
Oh, hey baby.
Let's take it slow.
Take it, yeah.
(drums)
- Ah, Molly. Good, you are here.
You can help me with
these translations.
- No, I need to talk to you.
- About what?
- Something isn't right.
These heiroglyphics are
unlike anything anyone
has ever seen before.
- That is because
they are older texts
than anything we
are familiar with.
- But, it's more than that.
They're darker, more,
I don't know, aggressive.
See.
A priestess from the West
shall speak the
coming forth into day
and shall awaken
the Hemet Netsher.
She who is all-powerful.
Ankh is never
depicted like this.
It's the life symbol,
but here it seems to me,
more like a weapon.
Most Egyptian funerary
texts are about
rebirth and
democratization
of the afterlife.
These all seem to be about
conquest and destruction.
She will bring death and pain,
destruction and fear.
World domination.
- Does it say how
this will happen?
- Well, I think,
I think that's over here.
- Get out of here Molly.
- What did she say?
Something about a priestess,
I couldn't quite understand.
- I told you not to tell
anyone about this site.
I do not want you back here.
- But I need to know.
- I said get out!
(apprehensive music)
- Carter, I need to talk to you.
- I'm a little busy right now.
- This isn't about us.
I need your help.
It's about Annette.
- Ben-David's assistant.
- She's not his assistant.
She doesn't speak
Hebrew or Arabic.
- What do you think she,
come on.
- The mummy of
Aneh-Tet disappears
and some girl shows up
speaking Old Kingdom Egyptian.
Nothing else makes sense.
She's planning something.
I don't know what,
but the answer is in
those heiroglyphics.
I can translate the text,
but I can't interpret the
religious significance.
I need you.
- I can't help you.
- Carter.
I don't know how many
times I could apologize
for what I did to you.
- How about once?
- Housekeeping.
- Come back later!
(screams)
(birds chirping)
(apprehensive music)
(thunder)
- What the fuck?
Oh my god!
(screaming)
- Need a break, babe?
- I'm gonna run
back to the motel,
check on Axe,
make sure he didn't pass out,
drown in his own
vomit or something.
- Nice.
- See you later?
- Hell yeah.
- Bye.
(suspenseful music)
(banging)
- Professor?
Professor?
- Kara, I.
- I don't understand.
- You should not have
come in here Kara.
- Professor. I
(screaming)
- No! No! No!
- I'm sorry Kara.
(screaming)
(screams)
- Shit Molly!
- Are you okay?
- You scared the shit out of me!
- God, I'm sorry.
Here, I brought you ice cream.
- All is forgiven.
- So, how do you feel?
- I'm never drinking again.
- Good.
Kev, I need you
to do me a favor.
- What?
- I want you to go home.
- Why?
- It's too complicated
to explain.
- It's mummy chick isn't it?
- What makes you say that?
- I don't have to be a
nerd to figure out that.
Bitch is bad news.
- Oh, Kev. Please.
Just do me this favor, okay?
- No, I can help you.
- No, you cannot help me.
- How do you know that?
You think you've
got all the answers
just because you're
Miss Cumma Sum Laude
- Summa cum laude.
- Whatever.
You never think about things
until after you do them.
Like coming to the desert
without bringing any clothes.
- I'm not discussing
this anymore.
I want you to get dressed.
I want you to get
out of here, okay?
- Where are you going?
I wanna go with you.
- Kev, please!
I don't want anything
to happen to you, okay?
Just please go home.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- I'm such an asshole.
What are you doing?
Oh my god, stop.
(screams)
(suspenseful drums)
(speaking ancient language)
- Carter, oh my god.
Carter, what's going
on? You're hurt.
- Just drive.
Drive!
- I gotta take a shit.
I need some fucking
toilet paper.
- Hey, you just get back?
- Yeah, just like
a half an hour ago.
- Did Kara come with you?
- Na, I haven't seen her.
Maybe she came with Jill.
- I already asked her.
Shit.
I better get out there.
- What the fuck?!
- I have a first
aid kit in my room.
- Sit down.
Where's your kit?
- In my bag, the dresser.
- Take off your shirt.
We should get you to a hospital.
- We don't have time.
- Why not?
- Because we have
to stop Aneh-Tet.
- Did she say anything
when she attacked you?
- She said (ancient language)
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
- Why would she say six?
Oh my god!
I am so stupid!
Of course!
In the tomb, there's a
picture of six warriors
and six shadow figures
surrounding an ankh.
- I saw it, the
ankh. She has it.
- Professor Swartek, Axel,
somebody we don't know about,
the deputy, security guard,
you were supposed
to be the sixth.
- Sixth what?
- Offering.
- What's significance of six?
Of course.
She needs a victim's ka.
- We have to stop her
before she gets a sixth.
(phone ringing)
- What do you got for me, Sam?
- I've got the
preliminary DNA results.
- It's Ben-David, isn't it?
- I don't think so.
Your suspect is female.
- [Sheriff] One of the students?
- Nope.
These DNA samples are
over 4,000 years old.
Sheriff?
- Never mind. Never mind.
(light drum and string music)
- Kara!
Kara!
Professor Ben-David.
Your hair.
- Sem priest must be pure
if he wishes to serve
the Hemet Niswah.
- What the fuck are
you talking about?
(strong wind sound)
(screaming)
(rumbling)
- Here, let me help you.
Careful.
I think I know how we
can stop her, okay?
I'll be right back.
- Hey Molly.
Thanks for the note.
(apprehensive music)
- Hey, what's
going on out there?
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
- Carter!
- Molly. Are you okay?
- Carter! Oh my god!
(screams)
- Molly, you okay?
- They're in your room.
I'm not leaving
without my sister.
(screams)
(deep unrecognizable voices)
- [female TV actor]
Un-fucking-believable,
this is amazing.
- [male TV actor]
What is it, Jen?
- [female TV actor]
These are the tunnels
that our dads went into.
(speaking unknown language)
- Kevyn, Kevyn.
(intense drums with strings)
Fuck!
(speaking unknown language)
- Carter!
- You okay?
- We have to get Kevyn.
- We will.
- We have to go to the tomb now.
- No, we need to figure
out how to stop her first.
What does it say?
- Oh god. Kevyn was right.
It was right there in
front of me the whole time,
and I missed it.
The dark ones will bring
destruction and chaos
on all mankind and place
Aneh-Tet in her rightful place
as almighty.
- Does it say the
becoming will take place?
How to stop her?
- The ankh of life when
wedded with pure blood
will have the power of life
or death over any being,
mortal or divine.
What does that mean?
- Oh.
- What?
- She has to sacrifice a virgin.
(thunder)
(apprehensive music)
- Yeah, Sam.
I need you to meet me
at the Tropic Motel.
(suspenseful string music)
- This is it.
(whimpering)
(deep voices)
- Leave me alone!
(speaking unknown language)
- Stop!
(deep voices)
Let her go.
- Kevyn, get out of here.
- I'm staying with you.
- No, no. Get out
of here please.
Go. Your car is right outside.
Call the police. Call anybody.
Go, please.
- You know I love you right?
- I know, I love you too.
Go!
(screams)
(speaking unknown language)
- [Carter] The
mummies, they're gone.
- Kevyn!
- Molly, stop.
(deep voices)
- Just hear me out, Sam.
An ancient tomb is opened,
and people start to
mysteriously die.
- And you think it's
some sort of curse?
- Maybe.
Maybe this missing mummy
isn't really missing.
- Jim, I'm a scientist.
- And I'm a cowboy,
but just because a
chicken has wings
doesn't mean it can fly.
If you have a
better explanation,
I'd sure as hell
love to hear it.
- No, I don't.
But I know for a
fact that mummies
don't suddenly come to life
and start killing people.
Jesus Christ, what
the hell is that?
Jesus Christ, get
us out of here!
- Shut that window.
- I'm trying! Unlock it!
- The one on the right.
(screaming)
- Sam!
(deep voices)
- [Sheriff] Ugly son of a bitch!
(strong wind sound)
(gunshot)
- You okay, honey?
- Look out!
(screaming)
(deep voice)
- Carter.
No.
No no no no no no no no.
(crying)
No (crying)
- [Kevyn] Molly.
(crying)
- Carter is dead because of me.
- That's not true.
- Yes it is.
I can do something about it,
but I need your help.
- We'll do it together.
(speaking unknown language)
Please please please please
please please please please.
- I'm sorry, Molly.
(crying)
- Why don't you
try mouth-to-mouth?
(light rock)
- [Voiceover] In the
western United States,
a group of archaeology students
have unearthed the tomb
of a 4,000-year-old
Egyptian priestess.
- My god.
- It's a sensitive
historical discovery.
- [Voiceover] But when
students start turning up dead,
(scream)
- What do you have for me?
- Your suspect is female.
- [Voiceover] They
realize their discovery
has awakened an ancient evil.
(hard rock music)
- Get us out of here.
Sam!
(scream)
- [Voiceover] Bruce
Boxleitner from Babylon 5.
Zach Galligan from Gremlins.
Andy Lauer from Screamers.
Legion of the Dead