When do the sins of a good man
make him bad?
I guess it all
comes down to choices.
They say justice
doesn't come easy...
in an unjust world.
Sometimes...
If you're lucky...
evil can be destroyed.
But sometimes...
Maybe it's better
to keep evil alive.
♪ Sick and tired of the bottom
Need a better view ♪
♪ Got me looking round
my circle, is it bullet proof ♪
♪ Sometimes I think
until I go insane ♪
♪ Can I even trust somebody
with the same last name? ♪
♪ When it's over,
it's over, it's over ♪
♪ It's over ♪
♪ I'm watching all
the moves you make ♪
♪ Can't turn back now,
it's too late ♪
♪ Checkmate,
there's no defending ♪
♪ This is the start
of the ending ♪
Ever heard of a GPS?
This road to
the left is unlisted,
but it looks like if
we take it down a few miles,
it'll actually
take us back to the highway.
So you're taking me
to slaughter?
Nice.
I mean, what choice do I have?
If we turn back now,
we're going to lose a whole day.
♪ When it's over,
it's over, it's over ♪
♪ It's over ♪
♪ I'm watching all
the moves you make ♪
♪ Can't turn back now,
it's too late ♪
♪ Checkmate,
there's no defending ♪
♪ This is the start
of the ending ♪
Damn it.
Oh...
Erica?
Erica.
We have to get out of here.
There's fucking
zombies out there!
Those aren't zombies.
Ah!
The breach, the chasm...
Between you and nothingness.
I can feel you when I breathe.
I gasp, I choke.
I can still smell the rain,
the fiery exhaust.
You're lost.
I'm beaten. Broken.
And scarred, a lost limb.
It will never come back.
It will always feel attached...
I have... I have a memory.
It haunts me a little bit.
I was ten years old and...
My mom, she was still alive
at that time.
I think she was upstairs.
But when I came home
and opened the door,
a small red sparrow
flew through and...
But it just...
It just kept flying
into the window until it, um...
Until it just broke its neck.
You're not a sparrow, Sarah.
You can see the open door.
The only person
that you can heal is you.
♪ Silent night, holy night ♪
Wow. Would you look at that?
Courtney's going
tomorrow night, too.
Oh, Beth, can you imagine
what it's like to have a dad
who lets you actually do things?
Crazy thought.
Like, how could
you want to miss out
on my world
famous potato skins anyway?
- It's just one dinner.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
It's not just one dinner, honey.
It's the traditional Bishop
family Christmas Eve dinner.
Can we got the stuffy now?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go grab it, honey.
- Dad?
- Yes.
Do you realize that
I'm the only senior with no car,
no boyfriend,
and a 10:00 curfew?
Sounds like you got
one smart dad.
Ha ha ha ha.
Dad, it's not funny.
I'm serious.
Why can't I just go?
What happened to our deal, huh?
What deal?
That you weren't going
to get all grown up on me
without my permission.
Whatever, thank you.
Hey. Wow. That's so cool, honey.
Little guy's going to love that.
Let's pick out some cool
wrapping paper, too, huh?
Can't we just give it
to them like this?
A present is not a present
until it's wrapped.
You can't just take it.
It's over here.
That's our tree. You can't just
take our tree.
What's your problem, dude?
Hey. What's going on, honey?
I was just standing on my phone,
and that guy, he just dragged
the tree away from me
like it was his.
- Okay.
- Excuse me, sir.
You made a mistake.
That's our tree.
Hey, look,
I don't want any trouble.
Hey, is your name on the tag,
or does it say
I'm for sale for 50 bucks?
Hey, pal, look.
I'm not your pal.
19, 20.
Daddy's tougher than the Hulk!
Keep counting, you.
You mean the same tough guy
who's wanted a motorcycle
his entire life but wimps out
every time he goes to get one?
What you call being a wimp,
I call being practical.
Just like how we practically got
the Christmas tree we wanted.
You won't become a teenager,
right, Freckles?
Absolutely not.
- Hey, you.
- Hi.
So, uh...
Still upset about this morning?
Mmm... I mean, I just don't
understand, like,
why do you do all those
push ups and stuff
if you can't even
defend your daughters?
So you think I should
have just punched the guy out
in the middle of
the Christmas tree lot?
Oh, my God.
That is not what I just said.
I'm just saying, Dad.
You watch Die Hard,
what, every day?
What do you think, Bruce...
whatever his name is, would do?
'80s action heroes,
they solve problems
with violence and one liners.
You know, real life
doesn't work that way.
Got it. Noted.
I'm thinking I may actually
address it in my sermon tonight.
Dad, no.
Daddy, please.
No, you can not talk
about me in your sermon.
I forgot to tell you,
you can go to the party tonight.
Oh my God, really?
Thank you.
If you're home by 11:30.
Okay? Yeah, 11:30.
No problem.
All right? You're not back
by the time Santa shows up,
no presents for you.
Okay.
- 11:30.
- Yes.
I'll be here.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ The scars that I'm hiding,
scars that I'm hiding ♪
♪ So cold ♪
♪ Scars that I'm hiding,
scars that I'm hiding ♪
Wow.
How about that, huh?
Don't be surprised if I show up
to next week's service
with blue hair, all right?
Before we wrap up this service,
I'd like to share
a personal story
that happened yesterday.
My girls and I, we were out
shopping for our tree.
Picking up a few presents.
Nothing like last minute, right?
I leave Sarah
in line to pay for the tree
while Rebecca and I go pick up
a few more gifts.
We look back
and we see a man
has claimed our tree as his.
I tried talking to him.
Hey, pal, look...
I'm not your pal.
Sarah's eyes say to me,
"Dad, aren't you
going to do something?"
So I did.
I did do something.
Merry Christmas.
I know, I know.
Not exactly a one liner
worthy of Rambo
or the Terminator.
Should I have knocked
him on his butt
in the middle
of the Christmas tree lot?
Luke 18, verse three.
Here is a parable about a woman
seeking vengeance
for a wrongdoer
who victimized her
and then escaped justice.
"Avenge me of mine adversary."
Day and night,
she begs this judge.
But Jesus tells us...
"When a sinner goes unpunished,
"he is only free from man's law."
"When man's law fails..."
"God's law prevails."
So I leave
you all with one last word
to any of us seeking
justice in a world
where it's lacking.
Trust not in the sword,
but in the grace of our Lord.
Anybody here?
Yo.
You here?
Hello?
Yo, hey, man.
Yo. You in there?
Yo!
Don't touch my car.
Fuck. Trying to give me
a heart attack?
You want to fucking go
right now, motherfucker?
Let's go.
I was just fucking
with you, man.
I'm glad we're doing this.
But, hey, I get it.
You're a,
"You can fuck my old lady,
"but stay the fuck away
from my wheels" kind of guy.
I can dig it.
Sorry I'm late.
Break number seven.
You believe that?
Boom, ah!
The bitch is I keep re-breaking
the fucker over and over.
Yeah.
All right, well, let's do this.
Hey, man, if you had told me
that one day
our clubs would have been
doing business together,
I'd have never fucking
believed it.
Look at this shit, man.
White as Snow White's
ass cheeks.
Mmm.
Oh, hey,
you're Vic's brother, right?
Oh, yeah, man.
I've heard stories, man.
You are one crazy fuck!
Whew!
You brought money, right?
Here you go, kid.
Hey, if I didn't have
a busted ham hock,
I'd be happy to reach
in there, chief.
You want to do me a favor and
hand me
the fucking loot, sunshine?
Oh, I get it.
You just want a good
look at my ass, huh?
All right, man.
Whatever turns your wheels.
Oh! Ah!
No! Ah!
Ah!
Oh!
Get off of me,
fucking piece of shit!
Get off me!
And it really
is special, though.
When you guys come out,
you're the ones who add to it.
Oh, hey, hon.
Excuse me, guys. One minute.
Hi.
Well, thanks for not
bringing me up today.
Hey, you need to put gas
in the car, okay?
Fill it up all the way.
Hey. 11:30.
11:30.
Ah, fuck!
Fucking bitch!
Fuck.
Come on, come on, Dad.
Come on.
Oh, sorry.
- Hey.
- Dad.
Miss me already, huh?
No, Dad.
I stopped at the gas station
before the party, and, um.
And there was this guy there
and I had to pepper spray him.
- What? You had to...
- And he's following me now.
Someone's following you?
Yes, yes,
he's following me right now.
Dad, I'm really scared,
he's following me.
Come on.
I think he's going to hurt me.
Where are you?
Are you near the party?
I'm on Bridge Pardley road.
Please, I need you to help me.
- Sarah!
- Dad!
Get away from me!
Don't...
Ah!
Get off!
Help!
Help me!
Look at me. Look at me!
Look at me!
I'm not going to tell anyone!
Hey.
Hey! Hey!
Help! Please, please.
Please.
No!
Daddy! Help me!
Somebody help! No!
Help me!
♪
My daughter called me
said she was here.
- What's your name?
- John Bishop.
Mr. Bishop? Mr. Bishop!
- No! No!
- Hold him.
No! No!
Ripped from life's embrace.
The space in my soul, stolen.
Spiritual death is nothing else
than alienation of the soul
from God.
Lead me not into temptation...
But deliver me from evil.
How's your brother in law doing?
His knees must be raw.
He's been upstairs praying next
to Sarah's bed all night.
The whole town is here for him.
And Rebecca.
Ma'am.
Johnny.
What?
Mr. Bishop.
Detective Sawyer.
You can call me Jed.
I'm sorry
about your loss, Pastor.
I won't bother you
with any more words of comfort.
Excuse me?
Well, I'm acquainted
with this sort of hurt,
you could say.
I know the futility.
I'd prefer to get down
to business,
if that's okay with you.
Let's have a seat.
The report I got here
says when you spoke
with your daughter,
she said she was being chased.
She say anything else?
Old's black muscle car.
That makes sense to you?
No. Tell me
you have a lead or something.
Mr. Bishop, I don't think this
was a case of road rage.
Sarah was found with her hands
zip-tied to the steering wheel.
I'm sorry.
Who would do this?
She was just a kid.
I promise you, I will find
who's responsible for this.
I'm going to look, too.
That's not a good idea,
Mr. Bishop.
It's probably best
if you go, Detective.
I'll be in touch.
Ma'am.
Up making her way
around the bar, Snowflake.
Remember, don't forget
tip our beautiful bartenders.
What's up?
Hey, job done and some.
Let me talk to Vic.
Hey, Vic, it's Ram.
You want to take this, trust me.
I got the crystal and the cash.
Now they know exactly
who's running this zip code.
Meet you at the bar tomorrow.
Noon.
Woo!
You should come over. I'll grab
a couple cases of beer.
James left
that bottle of tequila
from last weekend,
so we can definitely
have a party, dude,
just let me know.
Yeah, dude, ping pong's
going to be sweet.
It'll be fucking awesome.
Can't wait.
Yeah, for sure, man.
Hey, hold on a sec.
Pump number?
I'm talking to all the gas
stations near downtown.
Two nights ago.
She was in a gray Mercedes
between eight and 9 p.m.
You remember her?
Look, man, let me call you back.
I don't fucking know, man.
She looks cute, though.
Who looks cute?
Can I see you're surveillance
footage from two days ago?
- Easy there S.V.U.
- Hey, you got a warrant?
You got a warrant?
I'm going to need to see
those tapes.
Get the tapes.
♪
What's the trouble, Officer?
Ah!
- Hey, Jimmy!
- What's up, boys?
Hey, man, you seen
Vic's brother?
Can't say I have, boss.
I fucking told him, man.
Otto's going to be
fucking pissed.
Unfucking believable.
He's just gone.
No one's seen him.
No. It's all gone dark.
You're telling me...
You can't find...
your own brother?
Look harder.
You seen my keys?
Johnny, you shouldn't
be driving right now.
I had them.
You had them, I think.
Johnny, this isn't you.
You're scaring me.
Just... Just let the police do
their job, okay? You need sleep.
What I need
is to find out
who did this to my daughter.
Daddy, are you okay?
Baby...
Baby, what are you doing up?
I had a nightmare.
Remember what we talked
about, honey.
When you're in nightmares,
you have to change
the channel, right?
I already tried.
Will you lay next to me?
When I get back.
Where are you going?
You don't need
to worry about that.
♪ Another sun sets
down behind me ♪
♪ Another day comes
crashing in ♪
♪ There's a whispering wind
that's blowing ♪
♪ There's a storm
that's closing in ♪
♪ I can hear the trains,
they're rolling ♪
♪ To a place I've never been ♪
♪ And I can feel her
breath beside me ♪
♪ With an empty glass of gin ♪
♪ As the darkness settles in ♪
♪ I can hear her voice again ♪
♪ I can hear
your voice again ♪
♪ Waiting for someone
to save me ♪
♪ Blinded by the sun ♪
♪ You can take it away ♪
♪ And the darkness settles in ♪
Waiting for you.
Come on, pick it up.
Pick it up.
Hit it like you mean it.
You don't give in.
You don't give up.
Where's Vic?
He's still looking.
He should be sitting
where you are right now.
After a decade of bloodshed
with the Fallen Angels,
I arranged the first truce
in our club's history.
You want to know why?
To keep the noise down.
I asked you to handle
a very simple meet.
Sample the crystal.
Start a working relationship.
And Vic sends in his brother.
- Otto...
- Shh.
I just got off the phone
with their president.
He says one of their guys, Arlo,
magically disappeared.
They went to the meet
to look for him.
You know what they found?
His wheelchair, broken in half.
All his teeth in a pile.
You know, what else seems to
have just magically disappeared?
My money, my crystal, and
Vic's fucking brother.
His fucking brother.
Move your feet.
You ready to fix this?
The President just said that
they're putting trackers
in all the outgoing packages.
They're forming a posse,
calling in all the chapters
from upstate tonight.
They're on the way to pick up
the tracker from the cathouse.
I want you to intercept
and pick it up before they do.
They're always fucked up
on their own shit,
so you won't
find much resistance.
How about the truce?
The truce got fucked
the moment Vic sent his brother
to the meet.
We need to regain
control of the situation, boys.
That means
we need to get the money,
the crystal and Ram Kady
before they do.
No more playing nice.
War is back on.
Get out of here.
And boys?
Tell Vic...
I want him to personally
bring his brother to me...
alive.
Hey!
Where am I?
Hello?
[distorted voice
Your name is now number 21.
Where am I?
When you want to speak,
say your name, then speak.
You're crazy.
Then say your name again.
Fuck you!
For example, you would say,
"Number 21, fuck you,
number 21."
Turn on the fucking lights
so I can rip your
fucking throat out!
Say your name, then speak,
then say your name again.
Number 21...
turn on the fucking lights.
Number 21.
There we go.
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
You going to be okay
at Aunt Jody's?
I've got a present for you.
I...
I meant to give it to you...
Christmas.
It's beautiful.
I can't accept this.
Why not, honey?
A present's not a
present until it's wrapped.
That's right.
Well, then I promise you,
I will have it wrapped
by the time you get back, okay?
Thank you. Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
Wait!
Just needed one more squeeze.
Hmm. Me too, honey.
Me too.
Go.
Come on, go.
What's up, bro?
The fuck?
♪ If the lions want war ♪
♪ We gonna fight 'em
till the battle ends ♪
♪ The Tigers come running
we gonna fight 'em ♪
♪ Till the bloody end ♪
- ♪ When the elephants come... ♪
- Fuck!
♪ They gonna bow
to my brethren ♪
♪ Lock 'em in a cage ♪
Open your mouth.
Fuck you.
You got something we want.
Where the fuck
is Otto's tracker?
Open your fucking mouth.
I'm not scared of you,
motherfucker.
I don't know what
you're fucking talk about.
I don't know shit.
Got it.
♪ We all been lost
we all been called ♪
♪ Everyone rise
to a brethren code ♪
♪ We got your back,
we all been low ♪
♪ Let's all rise to
the brethren code ♪
Motherfucker.
Yeah, atta girl.
Scotch?
Not a big drinker.
Sure can't imagine
a more appropriate day
for a drink, John.
I'm going to tell you
about an opportunity
I was once given.
And I'm going to offer you
that same opportunity.
Then I said to her,
I said, ma'am,
do I sound like a
13-year-old girl to you?
I did not buy a makeup case.
And she says, "Well, sir,
apparently you did."
I say, "miss you've got no idea
what's going on over here."
Okay. I live with my wife,
my two daughters.
Okay? My MasterCard goes missing
in the middle of the night.
You know,
I can guaran-fucking-tee you,
I did not buy a makeup case.
Unbelievable.
So that's what I have
to look forward to.
Running the police
department is easy.
Keeping your house
in order is a son of a bitch.
Pee break.
So, Jed, I got some news.
What's up, Cap?
Quinn Brady was granted early
release today.
Six fucking years.
Unbelievable.
It's the law.
Who's Quinn Brady, cap?
Piece of human trash rapist.
Fucking animal kidnap
random victims
right off the street
in broad daylight.
I screamed Johnny!
Johnny, help me!
He drugged them,
caged them, and
numbered them like animals
and tortured them.
Barbaric shit.
Boom.
♪
Jed's first case as a detective,
got the conviction.
Brady got 15 to 20.
Then the new no balls Governor
implements his dog shit
early release program.
Let's go, I'm tired.
Whoa, whoa. Whoa,
whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
You're not getting out
of here without a toast.
Come on.
And by the way, your man here,
he says I'm not allowed
to ogle at you anymore.
Well, now that
I am officially fat,
I'm going to need
all the ogling I can get.
See that, I can still ogle.
Everybody, come on.
To the best detective I have.
Happy birthday, Jed.
To Jed.
Good morning, baby.
Good morning.
And happy birthday.
Thank you.
So have you thought
of a name yet?
- No.
- Good.
Because I have.
Elizabeth.
We could call her Lizzie
for short.
It's cute.
Kind of sounds like an
iguana to me.
I knew you were going
to make fun of it.
I'm kidding.
- You hate it.
- I don't hate it.
I love you.
- I love you.
- Bye.
♪ Full moon on
a Saturday night ♪
♪ Throwing down
whiskey till light ♪
♪ I swear I ain't ♪
- Hi.
Are you looking for, Jed?
No. I'm looking for you.
♪
Babe.
April?
Babe?
Hello?
♪
Was he caught?
Eventually.
And put away for life.
Thank God.
God didn't have anything
to do with it.
Lost both my girls
that same day.
God wouldn't do that.
How'd you get through it?
I got healed.
How?
I've got the guy, John.
I tracked down surveillance tape
at a gas station.
How would you like one minute...
One minute alone.
At the police station?
Can't do it there.
You need to be sure.
Can't turn back
after crossing this line.
♪
I'll take your jacket.
I'm good, thanks.
It's pretty warm
where we're going.
♪
Atomic age leftovers.
Inherited all this
when my daddy passed.
Came with the cabin.
♪
John, I want to introduce you
to the man
who murdered your daughter.
How do you know it's him?
He was already on my radar.
Drug deal went bad with a
scumbag named Arlo Garcia.
What did any of this
have to do with Sarah?
Wrong place, wrong time.
Found the car.
Arlo's body was in the trunk.
Matched the zip ties.
I got a detailed confession.
You fucking psycho.
Didn't I?
Ten years ago,
I made alone time with
Quinn Brady.
The cretin who slaughtered
my April and unborn Elizabeth.
It healed me.
It's time for you to heal, John.
♪
Just wait til
something calls your name.
There you go, John.
Count the moments.
All of the moments
he stole from your Sarah.
Tiny moments...
that add up...
to an entire unlived future.
Gone forever.
Every single thing Sarah
will never get to experience.
All because of him.
You don't know who
you're fucking with.
Stay strong, John.
♪
No!
No! No!
Do it, Jon.
Do it.
Make him pay.
Make him pay!
Do it, John!
Do it!
I can't kill him.
Who said anything
about killing him?
I'm giving you
exactly what you asked for.
Alone time
with the man who killed Sarah.
I built this room
for people like us.
No cameras, no witnesses,
no consequences.
My only rule is
you can't kill him.
I can't do it, Jed.
That's not good, John.
Only complicit men take
secrets to the grave.
And I can't risk losing
everything I've built here.
John.
No turning back, John.
Please, don't, please!
Please!
Dad...
John.
This one's a troublemaker.
Raped an 83 year
old grandmother.
Three days.
Should I do it, John?
- Should I do it, John?
- No.
Should I do it?
John. Should I do it?
- No.
- No?
Yeah. There you go.
Please, more.
More.
Want a little more?
Yeah.
Week in the torture box puts all
the horses back in line.
I'm disappointed in you, John.
Out of anyone, I thought
you'd appreciate my masterpiece.
Welcome to my church, John.
Child molesters.
Rapists.
Kidnappers.
Cold blooded murderers.
Psychopaths.
This one sold her
three year old boy
to a pedophile for $400.
Ah!
$400, didn't you, 15?
I gave the loved ones of
their victims time alone
with these creatures,
time to get revenge and heal.
It was a beautiful
sight to behold.
Look at them, John.
They've devolved into
mindless beasts.
Subhuman.
Mmm.
There he is, the man
formerly known as Quinn Brady.
Number one, speak,
Speak, Number one,
tell your name.
Number one.
Yeah.
Drano wreaks havoc on
the vocal cords.
♪
Stay on your knees, 21.
Huddle back over here.
21, get up.
Get up.
Get in there.
Just in case there's
no actual hell,
I want every moment of their
existence to be hell on earth.
Watch him, suffer, John.
They're about to
do things to him.
Wait until you see what happens
when they get their hands
on fresh meat.
Get him! Get him!
Yeah!
Look at him, John.
Stop it!
Who the hell are you guys?
Where the fuck is my brother?
Ow!
Get the fuck off me!
So this is usually where
I'd ask you a question.
But see, I don't like questions.
I like answers!
Where's my brother?
Where's Ram?
Oh, what the fuck?
What kind of backwoods
bullshit is this?
Oh, shit!
Ah!
♪
He's mine.
Quinn Brady.
Ah!
Oh...
♪
A present's not a present
until it's wrapped.
♪ Better back down,
you're in my domain ♪
♪ Got the whole crowd
screaming out our name ♪
♪ It's a blowout,
it's a hurricane ♪
♪ It's over ♪
♪ Before you know it ♪
♪ Why you shaking? ♪
♪ We're a dynasty ♪
Fuck yeah.
♪ In the making,
we're the royalty ♪
♪ Now we're breaking
down the enemy ♪
♪ Move over ♪
♪ For the soldiers ♪
♪ We're gonna stand on top
with our hands in the sky ♪
♪ Gonna raise our cup
to the stadium lights ♪
♪ For the glory,
for the glory ♪
Ah!
No!
♪
We have to get out of here.
There's fucking
zombies out there!
Those aren't zombies.
Ah!
♪
Radio Announcer:
Merry Christmas, everybody!
Yee-ha!
♪ Jingle my bells
It's Christmas in the USA ♪
Looking good.
It's nothing special,
just eggs and bacon.
I wasn't talking about the grub.
♪ It won't be long we're
waking up on Christmas day ♪
Come on, pussycat.
Let me hear you purr.
Ed?
Ed!
What?
Don't forget to
take the ornaments off.
Yes, dear.
Excuse me?
Excuse me!
Hello?
Hello!
Oh!
I'm going to need the keys
to your truck.
Oh, no!
Just go away!
Oh! No!
Ed!
- Hey!
- Don't!
Ed!
You.
Ah!
You couldn't
kill me when I was tied up.
You think
you can hurt me now, huh?
You want to know
what her last words were?
Shh.
She said, where's my daddy?
Come on. Come on.
She fought harder than you do.
Ah!
Merry fucking Christmas.
A journey through hell...
has led me to peace.
Every moment...
that we've shared together...
is worth the pain
that every memory brings.
Sometimes when there's
no more tears to fall...
and I feel alone...
Somehow you remind me...
that I'm not.
Thank you for sharing, Pastor.
Before we wrap it
up today, guys,
in close, I want to share
something with you.
Later today, I'll be taking
my baby girl Rebecca
to the batting cages
to practice her swing.
Tomorrow she has her
first softball game ever.
Would it be wrong
for me to ask you guys
to maybe say a little
prayer that her team wins?
No, but seriously.
I'd like
to share a verse with you all.
Especially you, Rebecca.
From the book of Ephesians:
"Therefore put on the
full armor of God,
"So when the day of evil comes"
"you will be able
to defend yourself."
"And when the battle is over,"
"you will be standing firm."
Amen.
My lunch hours cut in half,
so we got to get in and out.
How well you do depends on you.
Has nothing to do with me.
Let's get in here.
Oh, hey, sweetie.
What do you say you practice
that swing outside the cage?
- Okay.
- What are you doing?
Well, cages are for hitting.
First come, first serve. So...
- We were here first.
- Who's we? All I see is you.
Come on, step out.
My dad will be right back.
Where is he right now?
That's my point.
So go on, step out.
Come on.
But if I were you,
I would definitely
hang by watch how
a real slugger does it.
This is what it takes
right here.
All right,
show me your game face.
You got it.
All right, come on.
You have one job.
You know what it is? Focus.
Hey, what's going on?
He made me get out of the cage.
Little on the outside, my bad.
But this one's going
to be perfect.
Okay.
Good job.
- Hey, bud.
- Yeah.
My daughter was in here.
Okay, she was in here,
and now she's not.
Look, my little guy is doing
travel league this summer.
- All right?
- Yeah.
We got to get our licks
in when we can.
It's my lunch hour.
I got stuff to do.
- I just paid for 30 minutes.
- And that's all good.
But, you know, don't...
Don't kick my daughter out, huh?
What?
I said it's all good,
but don't kick my daughter out.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
Hmm?
Get out of the cage now.
You know, I got a better idea.
Why don't you tell your little
daughter pick up the balls?
You know that, Jacob.
Little chickadee
doesn't have any balls.
Honey.
Daddy's sorry about this. Okay?
♪ Retaliators ♪
♪ I'm throwing away all
the blessings it gave her ♪
♪ 21 bullets but it's not
going to save her ♪
♪ 21 bullets,
21 guns ♪
♪ 21 daughters
21 sons ♪
♪ 21 bullets,
21 guns ♪
♪ 21 daughters
21 sons ♪
♪ A fang for a fang ♪
♪ A knot on a rope ♪
♪ The sound of the dead is ♪
♪ What gives me hope ♪
♪ But the blood on my tongue ♪
♪ And the sweat on my neck ♪
♪ You can't outrun ♪
♪ What comes for you next ♪
♪ And now that you're gone ♪
♪ I stepped off the rail ♪
♪ I pray for revenge
but I'm afraid I will fail ♪
♪ Because we live in a world ♪
♪ Where even the angels are ♪
♪ Retaliators ♪
♪ There's blood on my hands
I see the holy father ♪
♪ Taste of revenge it's
as sweet as holy water ♪
♪ Retaliators ♪
♪ I'm throwing away all
the blessings it gave her ♪
♪ 21 bullets but it's
not going to save her ♪
♪ 21 bullets,
21 guns ♪
♪ 21 daughters
21 sons ♪
♪ 21 bullets,
21 guns ♪
♪ 21 daughters
21 sons ♪
♪ 21 bullets,
21 guns ♪
♪ 21 daughters
21 sons ♪
♪ 21 bullets,
21 guns ♪
♪ 21 daughters
21 sons ♪
♪ Retaliators ♪
♪ There's blood on my hands
I see the holy father ♪
♪ Taste of revenge
it's as sweet as holy water ♪
♪ Retaliators ♪
♪ I'm throwing away all
the blessings it gave her ♪
♪ 21 bullets but it's
not going to save her ♪
♪ Retaliators ♪
♪ There's blood on my hands
I see the holy father ♪
♪ Taste of revenge
it's as sweet as holy water ♪
♪ Retaliators ♪
♪ I'm throwing away all
the blessings it gave her ♪
♪ 21 bullets but it's
not going to save her ♪
♪ 21 bullets,
21 guns ♪
♪ 21 daughters
21 sons ♪
♪ 21 bullets,
21 guns ♪
♪ 21 daughters
21 sons ♪