♪ Ooh ooh ooh
♪ Don't you cry, cry
♪ Yeah, are you
♪ Yeah, yeah, are you
♪ Yeah
- An unidentified female
Caucasian has been found
dead on a beach in Micronesia.
Experts are puzzled
by the bite imprint,
which appears to be from
a great white shark,
previously never known to swim
within 1,000 miles
of these islands.
Your call has been forwarded
to an automatic
voice message system.
At the tone, please
record your message.
- Hi, Mom.
Can you call me, please?
I just had really bad dream.
I love you.
- A government bill to-
- Babies.
- Crack
down on laboratory
experiments on animals
is expected to become law today.
Animal activists have
been pushing for the bill
for nine years and have taken
part in mass demonstrations
throughout the nation.
It's expected the bill will
outline just what animals
will be allowed to
be used in the labs,
along with penalties
for the offenders.
36 hours of steady rainfall
have left many homes
in the Metro area
knee deep in flood waters.
Power was over three
hours in eastern metro-
- Mom?
- Because of downed hydro-
- Hi, Guru.
- Police report at least
200 accidents were reported.
- No, I can't reach her.
Is she okay?
- Clean up is expected
to take at least two days.
Damage to homes and property
is pegged at $3 million.
- Okay.
I will be on the
first flight tonight.
Fighting broke out overnight-
- Bye.
Between rival factions along
the Israeli-Syrian border.
Initial reports claim
there's been jet fighters
bombing for days now.
- Auntie Lucy will take care
of you for a while, okay?
Okay?
Attention passengers who are
connecting through flight
697 going to Chicago,
please proceed to gate 51.
This flight has been delayed.
- Hey, Guru.
Please tell me you
heard from her.
- Hey.
- Hey, hi.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- You remember to
remove the battery
out of your phone
during the flight?
- Yeah, of course.
- Okay, let's go.
Your mother was
been acting strange.
Past tense, why?
- I have not seen
her in three days,
making it present tense.
- My mother is a dreamer and
most dreamers are strange.
- Where would the world
be without dreamers?
Stone Age.
- Probably, but your
mother was acting
really strange for herself.
- Guru, when you say
someone is acting strange,
they're either normal or
they grew a third eye.
- I mean a third
eye kind of strange.
- Meaning?
- Hm.
Your mom hooked up
with this scientist guy
and he's also missing.
- Define hooked up.
- He thought they
had a thing going on.
- A thing?
- The day your mom vanished,
she came to me and told
me she had a breakthrough,
but she was afraid
of the repercussions.
- Could you be more confusion?
- All right, the last
time anyone saw your mom,
she went to go visit
this scientist guy.
He wasn't really her type,
but I don't think
he got that message.
- Okay, this doctor, does
he have a name, address?
- Yes and no.
His name's Dr.
Mitchell Linenrose.
He has no address.
Your mom didn't
want people to know
where she was when
she wasn't with us.
Your mother had a secret lab
that wasn't really a secret
because she made a video in
front of the lab she dreamed of,
but she had a real one
in a secret location.
I think the team's
gonna be a little better
at answers than I am.
- Wow, a random word
generator would be better.
- Hello, everyone.
This is Pom here.
We are finally here at
this beautiful island.
Look behind me.
Amazing.
But take a look at the trash.
Make sure that you are sharing
the knowledge with everybody.
We do not want this
world to be polluted.
We love the dolphins.
We love the ocean.
Yes!
We are here with my
lovely friend, Dean.
Dean, tell us, what is the
biggest issue with pollution?
- Plastic is found
everywhere, the world over.
It's found in food packaging,
it's found in household goods,
it's found in electronics.
A piece of plastic like
this can break down
and kill over 1,000 fish.
We have to fix this.
It's not just about
reducing the use of plastic,
it's about coming up with
something to replace plastic,
and that's where
science comes in.
And that's where we need you.
We need young minds to
help work on the problem,
to come up with something
that's gonna work
for the future and
solve this issue.
And you can be a hero, join us.
And instead of just
waiting for you,
I'm gonna get started now.
It starts with me.
- To find out more information,
go to #trashtagteam
and at all of your videos,
all of the information.
Let's encourage the world
to save the planet one
trash pickup at a time.
Please share and
subscribe for me.
Thank you.
- What up, Sheils?
- Hey, Luca.
- Smile!
- Okay.
- Okay, second
pose, second pose.
Okay.
And another one just in case.
Same Pom, same Pom.
- Hey, Sheila.
- Hey.
- I'm sure your mom's fine.
She's just working on something
keeping her busy for a few days.
I'm glad you found an excuse
to come and see us though.
- Yeah.
- Hey, Dean, why don't you
help Sheila with her bags?
Let's get on the ferry.
- Ready?
All is good.
- She's just worried
about her mom.
- Aren't we all?
- Completely.
She's like a mom to all of us,
but she's Sheila's real mom.
- Duh.
- One more duh out of you and
your phone is going swimming.
- You monster.
You touch this phone,
I'm throwing you over.
- Would you like a coconut?
- I could really
use some coffee.
- There's no Starbucks
where we're going.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry
about my mind and my mouth.
Somethings they're
not always in sync.
- Okay.
Are you as sure as Dean
is that my mother is okay?
- I'm not really sure.
I kinda have this sixth
sense, uh, I don't know.
- Has anyone
notified the police?
- You know I only trust
you and your mother.
- Oh, Guru, seriously, we
need all help we can get.
- I know, I know.
I just, I just
don't trust anybody.
I've been hurt too many times.
- Yes, but maybe they know
Linenrose or can locate him.
- If that's even his name.
It sounds like fake
alias, some crazy name.
I don't know.
- Okay?
Welcome.
I think you're gonna find
this room very comfortable.
This is where your mother stays.
You can stay here
until she shows up.
I looked around for some clues.
I couldn't really find anything.
Maybe you'll find something.
Your mother found
inspiration in that.
She believed the oceans
held many secrets
for us to discover.
- The secrets beneath.
That's my mom.
A stubborn dreamer.
- Indeed.
And so was Gandhi
and everybody else
who made this world
a better place.
Unpack your things.
We're gonna meet out here at
the beach side bar for drinks.
See you in a few minutes.
- Mom, where are you?
- There you are, bud.
- Cheers, mate, next one.
- So, what are you
doing in town anyway?
- Just a little snorkeling.
- Snorkeling?
- Mm hm.
- Did you hear about
the lady got taken
by a great white
shark yesterday?
- Yesterday?
- Yeah.
- Cheers.
Guys, guys, come over.
So...
So, the barman just told
me there's been a body
of an unidentified woman
found not far from here.
- What?
- Said it was a great
white shark attack.
- Great whites don't
come near this region.
- It's been confirmed.
It's a great white.
- What does it say, Pom?
- White woman, 40s.
- Oh, my God.
- It's gotta be a tourist.
- Let's not jump
to any conclusions.
- Yeah, let's just into the car.
Let's go to police station.
- The polices are
on the mainland.
We have to wait for the
ferry in the morning.
- Then I'm going at daybreak.
- The body hasn't been
retrieved or confirmed.
- Can you send them a message
or call them to see
where the body is?
- Of course.
- We can go with you.
- No, no, you stay here.
Hopefully it's not her
and we will just
keep looking for her.
Guru will take me.
Right, Guru?
- I'm always with you, Sheila.
Hi.
- May I help you?
- Yeah, the police
sent us to look at
the shark attack victim.
It might be this girl's
mother and unfortunately
I kinda have a bad
feeling about this.
- The police just called.
We can show you.
May I see your passport please?
- Yeah, of course.
- Thank you.
Okay.
We've had the body moved
to a private room for you.
- Why?
- Our cadaver storage has
several other shark victims
that you'd rather not
have in your mind's eye.
- Do you know where these
shark attacks are happening?
- We only know where the
bodies have been found.
The tides and currents can move
a body many miles
along the coast.
Please, this way.
- Okay, yeah.
- The news said it's
a great white shark?
- The bite pattern
and the size match.
We've also recovered a tooth
that's indisputably
a great white.
- Water temperatures screwing
with the migration pattern
of fish, polluted waters.
This world is just going crazy.
- Here we are.
Are you sure you wanna see this?
- It's the plastic people.
- I don't understand.
- Nothing.
- I'm sorry, I need
official identification
from a family member.
- It is my mother,
Amanda Williams.
Her wish is to be
cremated and for her ashes
to be spread in the
sea at the sunset.
- I'll have that
arranged immediately.
Let's complete the paperwork.
- Can I just have
a moment with her?
- Yes, of course, of course.
- Please.
I don't understand
what is going on.
I don't know what you were up to
or where this lab of
yours is, but.
You know I'm stubborn.
I got it from you.
I will, I will find
out what is going on.
I'll just, I'll hunt
that shark down.
And get justice for you.
I love you.
Mom, I love you.
I'm releasing your
earthly remains
into the sea as you wished.
May you find
happiness in eternity.
Where one day it will be...
One day it will be you
and me again, together.
- Yeah, she always
knew what to say.
No matter what the
situation was, she was just,
she had wisdom beyond her years.
But your mother had a way
of just comforting me.
And again, she was like a
sister and she just knew
how to say the
right things to me.
And that's I think where your
mother and I became really,
really close and became
really, really good friends.
'Cause we knew each other then,
but we didn't know
each other that great.
But she just kinda
held me and just said
all the right things, you know?
And it was a beautiful moment.
And we spent a lotta
time that night
walking around the
woods just her and I.
And some of the
friends had thought
we had gotten together or
something, which we didn't.
We were just friends.
We just became very close.
And so, I always
was very comfortable
with your mother, as you know.
But yeah, we had some really
good times when we were younger
and I just, she always
knew what to say.
- Do you know how
I met your mom?
No, she never told me.
- Christmas Eve, years
ago, I was at a bar.
Oh, I was an idiot,
such an idiot back then.
And I was with some
so-called friends.
Didn't know your mom then.
And there, the so-called
friends had tricked me into
thinking that I was having
a drinking competition.
And they weren't drinking
alcohol, just me.
And they kept pouring shot
after shot after shot,
and your mom was watching this.
And I was a state, a complete
state, really in a bad way,
and they left me.
And I walked outside
and I passed out.
And your mom called an
ambulance Christmas Eve,
and I went to the hospital
and I had my stomach pumped,
and I woke up Christmas day
with your mom next to me.
And she gave me the whole
speil like your mom does
about how do you anything
is how you do everything.
And the people who you surround
yourself, you become them.
And then, I never looked back.
Sounds like her.
You want company?
- I don't know what
I want anymore.
- We're all feeling
like that right now.
Your mom was truly
inspirational.
- I'm sorry, Dean.
- For what?
- For how I left
things between us.
- You know that phrase
about if you love someone,
then set them free?
Don't feel bad about it.
- Yeah, but, you know,
I have a life in LA
and I had a boyfriend
at the time.
I shouldn't have
crossed the line.
- So, what, it was
a vacation fling?
- Dean, you know
better than that.
- Sheila, you are amazing,
but life doesn't always
lead us down the roads we want.
I want you to know that I
will always be there for you
in whatever capacity,
except as a stranger.
- Thank you, Dean.
- Are you going right back?
- Are you asking about us or me?
- You.
- I'm not going anywhere.
I made a commitment to my
mom and I have to fulfill it.
What about you?
- I'm gonna change the planet,
the way your mom inspired us to.
- Good, so let's start
by sorting out Guru's
conspiracy theories
and find my mom's work.
And finding this shark is a
priority number one on my list.
- But it's just a shark
doing what sharks do,
like any animal does to survive.
- Dean, you know
I'm an animal lover,
but if I got a chance, I would
skewer it through the heart
and roast it over the fire.
Each of you were here to help
my mother and the planet.
I'm going to stay and pick
up from where she left off.
If you want to
continue, please do.
But if you want to
move on, I understand.
First of all, tonight, tomorrow,
we start looking
for the answers.
- Yep.
- Cheers to that.
- Cheers, guys.
The problem lies
in two main areas.
We've got plastic use
and plastic waste.
- What is the difference?
- The plastic use is
essentially when we have these
uncontrolled landfills and
all the plastic is blown out
into the ecosystem from there.
The plastic waste is when
we have all these uneducated
people coming out of the
markets and they have all these
plastic bags that they're just
tossing out into the streets,
which gets into the environment.
- 13 million metric
tons of plastic
end up in the ocean each year.
Plastic waste kills up to
a million seabirds a year.
Humans are not immune
to this threat.
While plastics are estimated
to take up to hundreds of years
to decompose, some of them
can break down much quicker,
but you know, it all ends up
in the sea, all the particles.
- We've trained and launched
several local cleanup
and recycling efforts
over the past six months.
But the problem lies with
litter and the use of plastic
in general, from drinking
straws to shopping bags.
Eliminating these plastics
will certainly put a foot
in the right direction to
rectifying the situation.
- Yeah, everything up
until now has been focused
on management of the problem.
The company your mother
started, Plant Plastics,
is focused on elimination
of the problem by replacing
plastic with plant-based
organic matter,
that was a biodegradable
lifespan of less than 30 days.
- Hm, and there lies within
the danger to us all.
Plastics is a $1.2
trillion industry.
To put that into perspective,
the tobacco industry
is 1/3 of that.
And we all know the tobacco
industry is pretty evil,
and they're responsible
for killing people
all around the world.
- This is a good
time to show you
a little video that
I made just before...
Here, take a look.
- Plant Plastic is dedicated
to finding a sea-plant
based material to replace
or at least reduce
the use of plastic
in a short term.
Our target short biodegradable
lifespan with organic remains
that are rich in nutrients
rather than plastic that kills.
The technology is within reach.
We're seeking donations and
equity funding to perfect
the process and to farm
genetically modified seaweed
in the planet's largest
farmland, the sea.
Let's plant it for the planet.
- I just finished
editing it last night.
It's not going anywhere, it's
just for you, for us to see.
But where is that lab?
- I don't know.
Amanda gave me the footage.
- Okay, seems like it
would be easy to find
a building with that logo on it.
- Your mother wanted
to keep that a secret.
Secret location.
- But why?
- Apparently this seaweed,
it's kinda like this special
endangered species
or something that you
can't find anywhere,
but she found it.
And it's her secret location
and she didn't want anybody
to know, especially
the plastic people.
Okay, so, anyone
have a chart of the coastline?
- I think I can get one
from the local dive shop.
Cool, let's do that.
- Good day.
- Hey.
- Hey, we're looking
for information
on offshore currents
around these waters.
We found some stuff
on the internet,
but local knowledge
is always best.
- What are you looking for?
- If a small boat drifted
from one to three days
could it have ended
up in Kimsha bay?
- Hm, it's a big area.
Many islands, lost of coastline.
- So, we will need a chart
that will cover the whole area.
- What are you looking for?
- Just the charts.
- Oh and the information
about the currents,
tides and waves
that we can't find
online please.
- Hm, smart girl.
The internet doesn't
have all the information.
- Yeah, neither do we.
- What's your business here?
- Um, we're organizing
a small eco-race,
boat race instead
of gas and oil.
- Sailboats?
- Rowboats.
- Uh huh.
So, the current runs this
way about three knots.
And if you're lucky
with a full moon,
it can go as fast as six knots.
And here, the shallow
water at high tide
is passable for an hour or so,
but the current runs.
- Mm hm.
Okay, we will take all
these and also this.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Well, let me know if
there's anything else
you would like to
know about the sea.
- Do you know anything
about the great white shark
everyone is talking about?
- Huh?
- Um, it's...
Those are small boats
and you wanna steer clear
from any stray shark
if you can imagine.
- Then you gotta steer clear
of the entire southwest area
in the mainland and
all the islands in it.
- Do these charts
cover those areas?
I mean, we wanna make sure
we don't go anywhere near.
- Yes, they do.
And the shark was
suspected of taking one
of our local fisherman
woman just the other day.
And another woman that might've
ended up in Kimsha bay.
- Is anyone hunting it?
- Well, every other game fisher
and local poachers are trying.
- Oh, well, hope
they will succeed.
Thank you.
Yeah.
- Ah, before you guys leave.
We would like to remind you
that we're a certified diving
shop since you guys will
be spending a lot of time
in the ocean and it's also
a fun skillset to have.
- Uh, well, we are
here for work not fun,
but we will consider it.
Thank you.
- Yeah, okay.
Bye.
- Yeah, there was an
American girl here
with some of her
buddy or boyfriend.
She was asking about
the great white shark
and she bought all the charts
for the western waters.
Mm hm.
Yes, I told her about getting
a diving certification.
Yeah, but I'll keep
an eye on her for you.
Yeah, sure.
- I could use more
processing power.
Would my phone help?
- First simulation is done.
- Okay.
- It's everything on 107.
- Uh huh.
- 109 and the
southern part of 100.
- How many drift days?
- One.
And the second simulation
indicates do, do, do...
The same three charts
as the day drift,
but actually all of 100, so.
- Okay.
- If your mother's body
drifted from the northern part
from this region right here.
- Uh huh.
- It could mean that she
might've ended right here.
Anywhere on chart 92, really.
- But we don't have a chart 92.
- It's only international waters
and a couple of
uninhabited islands.
- Mm hm.
Okay, uh, let's leave it
and assemble the troops.
- I'm famished.
You know what consumes more
calories than sleeping?
- No.
- Boom chicka wow wow.
- Okay, so, what we're
gonna be doing today
will be some classroom.
So, we are gonna be learning
all the theory behind diving.
You excited?
So, what we'll do
when we jump in,
we'll practice some skills
when we're down there, okay?
We'll practice how to
remove the regulator
and put it back in and
clear it so we're breathing.
Take it out, pretend
like we've dropped it,
put it back in and
push that button.
- If we are going
to find this lab,
the best clue so far
is my mother's body.
Where it was found is
not where she was killed.
Pom already ran few simulations
and we have two
quadrants to search.
So, Luca and Pom, you
will search this area.
Dean and I, we'll
search this area.
Guru, you will track
down Dr. Linenrose.
- All right, no problem.
But you guys, we have to
be really, really careful
and we can't anybody
what we're doing.
- Yeah, please memorize these
as we cannot walk
around with them.
Yeah?
- Let me have a look
at this real quick.
I might have an id
on the search area.
- Don't anyone what
we are really doing.
And stick to the cover story
of organizing a boat race.
- Um, this looks okay.
- Let's see it.
- Okay, you guys go ahead,
as Dean and I, we have to do
final certification test today.
Okay?
Good luck.
- Yeah, good luck, guys.
I don't even swim.
And be careful of those
underwater sea aliens out there.
Sheila!
Why are you not helping?
- Well, the best to
practice is to be
in real life situations anyway.
You see?
No problem.
- Think so.
- What happened back there?
- I panicked.
- If this sorta
thing's gonna happen,
you shouldn't be in the water.
- Dean, you know I'm good diver.
I know it's been a while,
but I just have too
much on my mind now.
But we have to keep
looking anywhere we can.
- Let's just make sure
there's not another
search team out
looking for us, okay?
- Yeah.
- Can you remember the
last time you were here?
- My mom was here with us.
- Seems like yesterday.
- I hope you guys have
better luck at this.
- Hey, dude.
- Hey.
- Thank you, you're
cleaning up the beach.
- Well, somebody has to do it.
Plastic grows quicker
than mushrooms in forest.
- It's really tragic, but
I'm really glad you're here.
I wish more people
around the world
would think and act like you.
- We have to use social
media to spread the word
and bring awareness to this.
- Absolutely, it's
all about education.
Totally.
- All right, dude,
have a good great day.
- Yeah, you too, take care.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
- Ah, no luck?
- Nope, no luck.
- You?
- I saw some kinda sea
alien, space alien,
shark attack victim, a
dead body on the beach.
But you know what?
Whatever it is, it's not gonna
get me 'cause I know better.
- So, it was the
plastic people after us?
- No, no, no, they don't
do their own dirty laundry.
- What you wanna drink?
- A strong one.
Make it a double.
- Yeah.
- Lovebirds approaching.
- You know young people
can fall in love too.
- Oh, in lust also.
- That too.
You think they found him?
- No, I don't think so.
What makes you so sure?
- Oh, I know, I know, I know,
they, they didn't find him.
Nope, nope, mm mm.
Nope, mm mm.
- How do you know?
- Know what?
- Did you find the lab?
- No, not even close.
We didn't either.
- Dr. Linenrose?
- Guru, mate, what
have you been drinking?
You smell like disinfectant.
- Two, I guess two days of
drinking and not a lotta food
probably does
something stinky, huh?
- So, two days of drinking
and how long have you
been looking for him?
- Hm, um...
He found a
dead body on the beach.
- Well, it was a dead
body, but I don't,
maybe it was the sea aliens
or maybe it was a shark.
I don't know, it's yeah,
it was a dead body.
- Uh huh.
And you stopped looking
for the last person
that saw my mother?
- I know things.
- You know what?
I'm sick of you and your
conspiracy theories.
Sea aliens and plastic people.
You are no wise man.
You're a child believing
in goblins and fairies.
We are better off without
you and your wisdom.
- You all better get outta here.
- We're not going anywhere,
but you did a long time ago.
- I know things.
What do you know?
- I know where the lab is.
I need a drink.
Water is all
you're getting, old man.
- Mm.
You hit me.
- And there's no apology coming.
- I'm sorry.
I know I kinda babble
on when I'm drunk
about all the aliens and stuff.
I don't mean it.
You know I love all you guys
like you're my own children.
- You mean grandchildren?
- Well, yeah.
And your mother, you know
I've loved her so much.
You know, not in a romantic
way, just you know,
her spirit, her energy.
She's just so beautiful.
- Where is the lab?
- Emerald Lagoon, it's
in international waters.
- Yeah, that's chart 92.
- Listen, that's in
super remote waters.
It's beyond jurisdiction,
little to no law enforcement.
If we go out there we're
totally on our own.
- Pom, any recent aerial images?
- No.
- I'm going.
Luca?
Dean?
- Let's do it.
- You're gonna need
me and my paranoia.
It's not just paranoia as
long as it's justified.
- Give us the facts.
No more stories.
- The facts are Dean,
we're gonna need
supplies for over a week.
This is really remote.
- We're going first
thing in the morning.
- Look at these cute
little mushrooms you guys!
Look, let's take a photo!
- Pom, stay away from this!
These are really poisonous.
They'll kill an elephant.
Those really
dangerous, I'm sorry.
I'm just trying
to save your life.
You guys, stay away
from those mushrooms.
They're really,
really poisonous.
All right?
You okay?
Don't worry about, huh?
Welcome to Plant Plastics.
- Guru, you sure?
- Yeah, this is it.
- Explain.
- All right.
Everything was Photoshopped.
The logo, everything you
saw, it was done to impress.
You know, to help investors,
all that kinda thing.
But this is where she spent
a lotta time with him.
- There is literally
no signal here.
Huh, I think I can extend
an antenna up there.
- I'm sure she can.
- Not what I was expecting.
- Yeah, it surprises
a lot of people,
but the real work takes
place in the lagoon here.
I hope so.
- Land shark rumble.
- Damn, Linenrose did this.
What?
This isn't my conspiracy theory.
He had a master plan where
he and your mother were gonna
buy all this and just
live happily ever after.
- Sounds a bit jealous.
- Hey, here's something.
Pom, what do you think?
- Let's see what
we can find on it.
- Hm, 50/50, platter's
not shattered.
- Hey.
- Those are Linenrose'.
- Yeah and so is the bungalow.
You're all trespassing.
Guru, you should know better.
I can't believe
you're still alive.
- I can't believe what
happened to Amanda.
It was them.
You're Sheila.
She spoke about you.
- Well, she never mentioned you.
And who's them?
- The plastic people.
We were on the verge
of a breakthrough
and she used to
swim every evening.
There hasn't been sharks
in these oceans for years.
They put that great
white in the water.
They're trying to kill us!
- Enough about plastic people.
Just tell me about the
current state of research.
- Amanda was working
and strengthening
the seaweed-based material
for practical use.
And to give it a biodegradable
life of less than a year.
Amanda wanted to take
the project global,
and now she's dead.
We all gotta get outta here.
We're gonna die if we don't.
- Shark!
It's definitely a
great white shark.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
You can tell by the blue-gray
dorsal fin on the top.
- I don't know, I can't see.
How can you tell it's
a great white shark?
- They blend in with
that blue and gray,
you can't see from above.
- It shouldn't be within
1,000 miles of here.
They're sniffing
us out organically.
- My mother was right.
Going global is the
only way to stay safe.
Pom, try your idea with antenna,
and let's launch a global
campaign with GPS coordinates
of this lagoon and
a shark warning.
And let the hunters sort it out.
- No, don't do that!
You're gonna regret it!
- Hey!
You're all gonna die!
- No, no, let him go.
- Don't worry, I got
everything on camera.
- No one wanders
alone into the jungle.
Pom, tell Dean and Luca
what you need for antenna,
and let's see what we can
find on the hard drive.
Guru, help me clean
up the bungalow.
What?
- Linenrose kept
calling this his lagoon.
He's crazier than I am.
- Well, it doesn't
make you sane.
- What do you know about your
mother's financial records?
- Nothing.
- Pom, while you're
hacking, why don't you check
and see what you can find on
her mother's financial records.
- What are you thinking?
- He doesn't want us
to be here at all.
- I wonder where
that seaweed farm is.
- No, no one is
getting into the water
until the shark is
someone's trophy.
Protecting Gelidium
longipes is our priority,
but we can save the planet
only if we can stay alive.
Are we good?
Good, let's go.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Um, antenna is ready.
Just make sure you put
it at the highest point.
- Yes, I know.
- Mm hm, go.
Hey, guys.
You ready to go?
- Yeah.
So, it's ready?
- Yeah, it's ready.
- Yeah.
Let's set it up over there.
- Yeah, that's a good spot.
You got the tape?
- Yep, cheers.
- Do you reckon the
AM broadcast range
is gonna be okay on this?
- Yeah, we've got it as
broad as we can get it.
This might be our only
link to the outside world.
- What are we looking at
for the line of sight?
- I think we'll be good.
Between here and the mainland,
we should get very
little interference.
- Yeah?
All right, right that's on.
This just looks like farce.
What you thinking?
- Tape.
- Cheers.
Thanks.
- Do you know what?
I think I'm gonna catch you up.
Don't tell Sheila, I'm gonna
have a little swim to see
if I can locate
the gel, you know,
the gel-whatever
long stuff, okay?
- Okay, but don't take too long.
- No, I won't.
And keep it, don't tell her.
- All right, be careful.
- Yeah, I will.
- The antenna's
up and connected.
- I got the link.
- While you guys are
taking care of this,
Luca and I will be on the beach
collecting trash and firewood.
Okay.
- What was that?
- I saw something.
There's someone out there.
- Linenrose.
- Hm, hopefully.
Uh, Sheila?
I need a drink.
- Sheila, come here
and take a look.
I think we got some videos here.
I've got some footage.
- Mm hm.
That looks good.
- Yeah.
This one.
- What's happening?
Where did it go?
Why it says it's not available?
Where is it going?
Why is it disappearing?
It's all gone?
- What's happening?
Just tell them to go to hell!
- They can't trace
our current location,
but they can get
to the homeland.
I swear this only happens
in B-rated movies.
CIA and NSA level stuff, so.
- Okay, um, just drop our link
and let's stay dark for a while.
- I didn't check this
bungalow for bugs.
Help, help!
- Dean, get out of water!
- Dean, get out!
Dean, get out!
- Dean, Dean!
Get out!
I couldn't hold him.
I saw it.
- And now I'm gonna
kill that shark.
- I know it's horrible,
but we're here to protect
nature, not kill it.
- Pom, are you still connected?
- I'll double check
when we get back in.
- We need to radio the mainland
just to report his death,
just so we don't look guilty.
- Linenrose didn't
report it either.
- That's exactly why
he looked guilty.
Let's get outta here.
Sheila!
You're the smartest girl I know,
but that's as stupid as it gets.
Your obsession with the shark
is losing focus of
the main objective,
which is to recover
your mother's formula.
- I know.
- And I don't wanna lose you.
- And I don't wanna
lose you either.
- Abracadabra, open Sesame.
We're in the hard drive.
- Hopefully formula is there.
- Land deed for Emerald Lagoon.
- Whose name is on that?
- Amanda Williams.
- Who else?
- No one else.
This isn't his lagoon.
It's yours.
Her will passed ownership
of Plant Plastics
and the Emerald Lagoon to you.
- I'm starting to
appreciate good news.
- That's not good news.
That makes Linenrose
more dangerous.
More dangerous than
the plastic people.
He already thinks
this is his lagoon.
- But it's not his.
- No, it's not his lagoon.
And Sheila, what
happens if you die?
- Huh?
- If you die, like your will,
who gets all your
stuff, your inheritance?
- I don't know, I
don't have a will.
- I suggest you
make one right now.
- Okay, I will put a
will on my to-do list.
- To-do list?
Just make sure you do it now.
- Why, so I can leave
the lagoon to you?
- No, but I suggest
like a large corporation
would be a great
benefactor, like Greenway.
They specialize in
plastic alternatives.
Plus with all their
power and muscle,
they can go after
the plastic people.
I'm gonna go for a walk along
the beach and think about this.
- In about an hour,
we'll be packed and ready
to head to the mainland.
- All right, I'll be back
to help you guys out.
I just need to get this clear,
all this craziness
cleared outta my head.
- Don't go in.
- Are you guys crazy?
I don't swim!
Let alone with some
great white shark.
You guys are just crazy.
Man.
- Maybe check this file.
- I don't see Guru anywhere.
- My mom spent every
penny on this research.
We have to find the formula.
The Conservational Institute
of Europe wants to send a team
to check out the
Gelidium longipes.
Huh.
Yeah, we need a team like that.
None of us are
marine biologists.
And unless we want
Linenrose to help us.
- Thumbs down.
- I'm going to look for Guru.
- Okay, yeah.
Check this one.
I don't know is it good idea.
- You own the place.
It's like owning the
land that has oil.
- Okay, then, send
them a private message
with our coordinates and
ask them when they can come,
but don't sound too eager,
and not too chill either.
- Like ticking clock emoji?
- Let's stay emoji
free on this one.
Okay, okay, good.
Send that.
Now, let's wait.
Huh, they respond fast.
Day after tomorrow.
That's great.
- Fireworks emoji.
I found Guru.
- That's great.
Tell them maybe if they can-
- Guys!
His body is too far
out to retrieve.
It wasn't a shark,
but someone wanted
to make it look that way.
I found his sandal on the beach
with a trail of blood
leading to the water.
- Must be Linenrose.
- That's my bet.
- We have to get Guru's body.
- I agree, but it's not possible
without putting our
own lives at risk.
- We need to get outta here.
- Call a water taxi.
They won't come out at night,
but first light's just as good.
Sheila, we have to
report the deaths.
- Yes, Pom, please report it.
- I need to get outta here
before something bad happens.
- Okay, please ask water taxi
if he can come tonight
we'll triple the rate.
- Okay.
- My mom, Luca, Guru, I don't
know who to blame anymore.
- We're not giving up.
We're surviving.
We'll come back with
the research team
and whatever police are willing
to hunt down Dr. Linenrose.
- Please make sure you get
Guru's body on the way back.
- You're not staying here alone.
- Without formula or
seaweed, we have nothing.
- Now's not the
time to be stubborn.
- Maybe, but if Linenrose
thinks that we left,
he will come back and I will
be waiting for him with this.
- Oh, so, now you're
gonna kill him
like you were gonna
kill the shark?
Murder is murder and
there's a penalty to pay.
- It's gonna be self defense.
Anyway, I'm just
gonna cripple him
and let the shark do the rest.
Organic elimination, isn't
it how Guru would call it?
- Sheila, you're not
thinking straight.
- Dean, it's a good plan.
What if Linenrose comes
back and kills what's left
from the seaweed and
grow it somewhere else?
- You heard Pom,
you own all this.
- Okay, so, I will put "No
Trespassing" sign here.
That will do the work.
The problem with all the
save the planet people
is that all the kill
the planet people thinks
they can do whatever they want.
- You can't meet
violence with violence.
- Yes, I can.
- Then I'm staying with you.
- No, you have to
be decoy with Pom.
- Sheila, I'm staying with you.
- Dean, he isn't gonna hurt me.
He loved my mom.
- How do you know
he didn't kill her
and let the shark
take the blame?
- You're an idiot.
- Maybe, but I'm an
idiot who loves you.
- You know what?
You were just a vacation fling.
- Are you sure
there's nothing else?
Anything before, just
anything before it?
Okay.
Okay, thank you, bye.
Any luck with taxi?
No water taxi until 7:00 a.m..
No water taxi.
Okay, can you check the
disk again for the formula?
Did, done, none.
- All right, the next
thing that comes through
this door is getting skewered.
- Are you sure there
are no hidden files?
I'll take a look again.
- There's so many
secrets in the sea.
- Secrets in the sea?
Secrets beneath.
It's the formula.
In the most secured
old fashioned way,
handwritten on the paper.
- So, you'll come
in the morning?
Sheila?
- What's going on?
- Sheila was
thinking of staying.
Thumbs down emoji, no.
- We need to protect
that formula.
- My mother made a mistake
of protecting this formula.
Let's post it for the
whole world to see and use.
- It's worth millions if
not billions if it works.
That's not greed,
that's reality.
Giving it away-
- It's the best way
of protecting it.
When it's out, we are all safe.
- No link.
7:00 a.m.?
- I can check the antenna.
- And leave us here alone?
There's only one
speargun thingie.
- Okay, we all go.
- I'm not gonna shoot anyone.
I'm gonna go hide
in the closet, okay?
You guys just get back
as soon as you can.
- We can do it
from the mainland.
- No, sooner is safer.
Until then we're all targets.
- Yeah, this is where we put it.
Maybe Pom can repair it.
- Mm hm.
He's out there.
- Let's go.
Pom!
She's still breathing.
- A speargun?
Are you serious?
Put it over there.
Now!
Both of you, get out.
I said, out!
Keep moving, come on.
Let's go.
You are as stubborn
as your mother.
You idealist.
Neither you or her
have what it takes
to make this world
a better place.
And so, you're gonna
sign the company
and the lagoon over to me.
And then, I will let you live.
- As simple as that?
Our lives for everything
my mother built?
- Oh, by the way, I have
the paperwork ready for you.
Just need the signature.
- How did you know my
mother left it to me?
- She told me.
Then I killed her!
- I will need a pen.
- What happened?
It's over.
Save the world?
- Save the world.