[intense music]
[blood splashing]
- Hello there.
My name is Lincoln Maazel.
On my next birthday,
I'll be 71 years of age.
I am an actor, I'm working.
I have a family.
Despite the many problems
and frustrations of the world
as it is today,
no one will deny that there
is still a basic fulfillment
which is drawn from living,
being active, and contributing.
There is a joy to life
available to those who
can interact with nature,
with their fellow man.
Unfortunately, this interaction
is denied to many groups,
for many reasons.
Levels of income,
environmental deprivation,
geographical accident,
perhaps the saddest cause
of denial and rejection
is very simply, old age.
Man lives his mature
life with hope.
He looks forward to the day
when he can reap the benefits
of his experience, his
earnings and his wisdom.
And yet, he often finds
he is not regarded
as a productive
member of his society.
And if he doesn't
have a reputation
and doesn't have
financial substance,
the situation is a
hundred times worse.
Some of the many problems
of aging are loneliness,
failing health,
inadequate transportation,
inadequate medical care,
inadequate housing,
lack of money,
improper nutrition,
and perhaps most acute,
the lack of compassion
and supportive services
from the younger
members of our society.
The oldest citizens
of the world represent
a much misused natural resource.
The wasting of this great
resource is a worldwide tragedy,
but this can be
corrected by people.
People who can be made aware.
People who can care and who
can respond to the need.
Oh, you've heard the statistics,
and you've been preached
to about the problem.
You've seen news reports
and documentary material
dealing with the
plight of the elderly.
We will not repeat
what you have heard.
The amusement park which
you are about to visit
illustrates some of
the many problems
people of my age face
on a daily basis.
We intend for you to feel the
problem, to experience it,
and we ask for your
sympathy as you watch.
And when the film ends,
we hope you will have
the concerned interest
to take action.
The supporting players of
this film are not actors.
They are volunteers,
many of whom are
actively involved
in services to the elderly.
The older people in the
film are also volunteers
who are either concerned
enough to give us of that time
or who, in real life, are
living in institutions,
in lower income housing
areas, or in city slums.
The time spent in
shooting at Westview Park,
which facility was
donated to the production,
was for some of the
elderly players,
the only enjoyable time they
have had in recent years.
Remember, as you watch the
film, one day you will be old.
[heart beating]
[clock ticking]
[clock bell ringing]
[roller coaster moving]
[girl screaming]
[door opening]
- Hello?
I say hello there.
Don't you care to talk?
- No.
- Uh, tell me, um, would
you like to do something?
- No.
- Do you, um, do
you ever go outside?
- No.
- Don't you want
to ever go outside?
- Th-there's nothing,
nothing out, outside.
- Well, I'm going
outside anyway.
- You, you won't, you won't
like, you won't like it.
- Well I'll, I'll see for
myself if you don't mind.
Goodbye.
- Th-there's nothing outside.
Nothing.
[people chattering]
[amusement park music]
Nothing.
[calming music]
[amusement park music]
[amusement park chatter]
- [Man] I can't give
you more than $5 for it.
- Oh no, they're
worth more than that.
- [Man] No, I'm
afraid not, ma'am.
- Oh, please.
- They may have
sentimental value to me
but they're worth $5
to me and that's it.
Take it or leave it.
- [Woman] All right then.
Okay, thank you.
- This is silver.
- All right, let me
take a look at it.
- [Man] That's real silver.
- I can't give you more than $5.
- Oh man, what you
talking about, listen.
- [Merchant] $5,
take it or leave it.
- [Man] You ain't looked
at the thing right.
- [Merchant] Not worth
anything more than $5.
I've examined it
very thoroughly.
- Well come on, come
on I'll take it,
but you are, you
are beating me now.
- [Merchant] There you are.
- How much you give me for it?
- I'll give you a buck.
- No, you can't, $15.
- What, take a buck, that's it.
- Oh my goodness.
- Who's next?
Yes sir?
- I'd like to get some tickets.
- Okay, fine.
Cash, that's what I like to see.
How much you have to spend?
- Well, I.
- Time is money,
let's come on now.
- I'm, I'm on a budget, you see?
I have to be very careful.
- How much do you want to spend?
- Well, I.
- Just a minute folks, I'll
be with you in a second.
- I can afford about half.
- Half, all right,
fine, fine, fine.
- And this is gonna
be for an emergency.
- Sure, okay.
That's okay with me.
Sure okay, here you go.
- Thank you very much, sir.
- Who's next?
Step right up.
- Okay, it's fine.
- Oh!
Why don't you watch
where you're going?
- I'm terribly sorry.
I'm terribly sorry, I, I.
- Okay, step right across.
Here, that's fine,
go ahead, here.
One more, watch your step
there, watch your step.
Two, take two more here.
Hurry up, you're
gonna miss the car.
Okay, good.
Sorry ma'am, you're not aloud.
Read the sign there.
Let's go, come on, next, next.
Fine, fine.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
you can't get on.
- Oh please, please.
- Read the sign,
just read the sign.
- How come we can't get on?
- [Worker] Maybe next year.
- [Worker] Go right
through there?
- [Man] How come
we can't get on?
- [Man] We're going down!
We're going down!
We keep going downhill.
No we're going up,
we're going up!
[screaming]
[calming music]
[bell ringing]
[amusement park chatter]
- [Captain] All aboard!
[bell ringing]
All aboard!
Okay!
[people laughing]
[amusement park chatter]
[box crashing]
[engine starting]
[amusement park music]
- Read the chart.
Start at the top, just
work your way down.
- E-F,
C.
Z.
D.
- [Woman] All right, you be
calm, Harry, take it easy.
- T.
- Okay, ma'am, you're okay.
But, sir, you're gonna have
to be a passenger from now on.
Cannot renew your
license with those eyes.
[clock ticking]
- [Worker] Hurry, hurry, hurry!
[car engines revving]
[tires screeching]
[cars crashing]
- See where you're going
for crying out loud.
If there's anything stupider
than a woman driver,
it's an old woman driver.
- What do you mean?
You made left hand turn
with a right hand signal.
- How old are you?
- Well, if it's any of
your business, I'm 67.
- If that's true you shouldn't
even be allowed on the road.
Anybody over 65 should
be made to ride the bus.
- What do you mean?
Don't you know, your left
hand from your right?
- [Man] Ah, you.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, one minute.
What happened?
- [Man] She hit me from behind.
- Well, for goodness sake.
My version is, he doesn't know
his left hand from
his right hand.
- [Officer] Your
driver's license, please.
- [Man] She hit me from behind.
Now isn't it true
when somebody hits you from
behind it's their fault?
Right in front of your eyes?
- Okay listen,
that's why I'm here.
- Since I'm so old,
you better have a little
more respect for me.
That's what I say.
- There's no sense
arguing about it.
I'll make the report
of what I see.
- Oh, here's our insurance man.
- [Man] You can see the damage,
you know how much
something like this costs.
- [Woman] You're not even old
enough to be an insurance guy.
- We're here to
represent our client.
- [Woman] A kid in kindergarten
knows left and right hand.
- Officer, excuse me please,
but I was driving coming this
way and I saw the accident.
This man actually made
a left hand signal
and made a right turn.
I saw him do that.
- [Man] Aw, come on.
- [Woman] Exactly, good.
- Well, sir, all I can tell you
is the same thing I told them,
since I didn't see the accident,
I'll be glad to put
down what you said
and your name and address,
the insurance companies
will contact you.
Can I see your drivers
license, please?
- Yes.
- [Man] I would guess that
our company's gonna require
a slight adjustment in the rate.
- Good grief, man.
We can hardly afford it now,
the rates are high enough.
- Don't you worry, Harry.
We're not gonna have
any rate increase
'cause this was not our fault.
- According to your license,
you're supposed to be
wearing eyeglasses.
- Oh, yes, well.
- [Officer] Do you?
- I, I, I have them.
- [Man] Aha, aha.
- [Woman] Oh, what?
- [Man] Blind man, blind man
says he saw the accident.
- [Woman] Oh my goodness, Harry.
- [Man] I'd like to see
this hold up in court.
- [Woman] He didn't
have his glasses on.
- [Man] How could he be
a witness to anything?
I'm telling you,
I made a signal.
She smashed into me from behind.
That's all there is to it.
- [Woman] You made
a signal, all right.
- [Man] Clearly, you're wrong.
Look at this damage.
Gonna have to have
a new paint job.
- [Officer] Look I'm
gonna tell you something.
I've had about enough
of both of you arguing.
I'm not gonna tell you again.
- [Man] I got my
own insurance man.
I'll take care of this myself.
[amusement park music]
[clock bell ringing]
[upbeat restaurant music]
[fingers snapping]
[cash register dinging]
[dishes clinging]
[cork popping]
[plate thumping]
- [Worker] Hurry, hurry, hurry!
[people chattering]
[people laughing]
[merry-go-round music]
- Hey, you!
What are you, some
kind of a degenerate?
What are you doing
with those kids?
I'll give you about two
seconds to get out of here!
- [Worker] Hurry, hurry, hurry!
[amusement park chatter]
[people chattering]
- [Man] You enjoy, you enjoy.
- [Woman] Oh no, it's
fun, you'll like it.
- I'm not sure that
I want to go in here.
- [Woman] You'll really like it.
[clock ticking]
[droning buzz]
[chaotic music]
[people chattering]
- [Man] Get back in there.
- You're supposed to
have fun in there,
You gotta have fun in there.
Hey buddy, come here.
[amusement park chatter]
[amusement park music]
[calming music]
[mystical music]
- Ah, two young lovers.
You want to fortune told?
- We want to see what
life is gonna be like.
- What part of life?
- When we get old.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, we want to know if we're
still going to be together.
- Well, there are conditions.
You must see it
all, is that agreed?
- Yeah.
- [Fortune Teller]
You must see it all.
All the way to the end.
- Sure.
[magic ball pulsing]
- Look into the future then.
Into the magic ball.
Into the future, into the
future, into the future.
[magic ball pulsing]
- I'm Alan Ross
with Mr John Wilson,
the landlord here who
owns the building.
Mr Wilson, why haven't you
made any repairs
to this building?
It's in deplorable condition.
- Well sir, do you
realize the kind of taxes
that we have to pay here?
- [Reporter] But aren't
the conditions here
unsafe for the people who
pay you rent, good money?
- [Mr Wilson] Well,
actually rent that I get
is no more than about $10
a week from these people.
And with that kind of money,
do you expect me to make
any more improvements
than what we have already?
- [Reporter] Well if you can't
make the repairs yourself,
Mr Wilson, then why don't
you sell this property
and let someone else make them?
- [Mr Wilson] Well, we tried
desperately to do that,
but who will buy it? Would you,
sir, would you consider
buying this property?
- [Reporter] I'm asking
you the question.
I'm asking the question
of you, Mr Wilson.
You tell me why
you can't sell it.
- [Mr Wilson] Well, not
too many people today
would take the chance to
buying this kind of property
knowing the circumstances
and the conditions here.
[woman laughing]
- [Reporter] Seems
the condition is that
you haven't made
any improvements.
You're telling me you
don't have the money.
- [Mr Wilson] Yes.
- [Reporter] What about
the condition inside?
Don't you have an
obligation to your tenants
to make these repairs
and make them now?
- [Mr Wilson] We have
made some repairs,
but unfortunately they're
the type of people
that just will not
take care of themselves
nor the place that
they're living in.
[train warning bell ringing]
[sirens wailing]
[phone ringing]
[people chattering]
- Well you look better
than my mother looked.
You look wonderful.
[phone ringing]
- Oh, hello there.
- Dr Jones, my
husband is so bad.
I can't talk to him,
he won't answer me.
He doesn't take his medicine.
- I'd love to talk for
a longer period of time.
- You're too busy to come.
- Goodbye.
[sighing]
[mystical music]
[amusement park music]
- [Reporter] Could you
explain to our audience
if someone in this building
is burned to death tonight
or be injured in a fall down
these decrepit stairways,
how would you explain it, sir?
- Sir, I sincerely hope
that never happens.
[mystical music]
[heart beating]
[clock ticking]
[mystical music]
[sirens blaring]
[phone ringing]
- I can't understand.
I can't get him to
even recognize me.
[people chattering]
Why can't you come to
come to see my husband?
We've always been good patients.
As poor as we are we've
always paid our bill.
Why are you punishing
me like this?
For heaven's sake,
didn't you take an oath
when you studied medicine
that you would be
kind to people?
Isn't that one of the things
a doctor's supposed to do?
What kind of a man are you?
I want you to come here.
Would you, please?
[people chattering]
- Doctor, I have a
ringing in my ear.
[people chattering]
- Well then, God help you
if you have to have
this on your conscience!
[drums beating rhythmically]
Mister, please, mister.
Oh my God, mister, please.
Can you give me a dime, I
have to make a telephone call.
Oh, why are people so mean?
Why can't anybody help me?
[drums beating rhythmically]
[Fortune teller chuckling]
[amusement park music]
[clock bell ringing]
[engines revving]
[heart beating]
[men laughing]
- Tickets, man, dig, dig, dig.
Pick him, pick him.
Tickets, tickets, man.
No, no, come here, man.
Go through his pockets,
go through his pockets.
What you got, what you got?
Hey give me, give me
some of those tickets.
His tickets, man.
Give me some of that.
Wow!
[engines revving]
[amusement park music]
- [Woman] Your name, sir?
- I, I.
- [Woman] Your name, sir.
- I, I, I have no receipt.
I can't.
I've got insurance.
- That's an awful
lot of paperwork.
Can't you pay cash?
- Cash, yeah I, I
uh, I got some cash.
- Get in there.
[heart beating]
[people chattering]
- Looks like a bandage.
Bandage, bandage here.
Bandage.
- Bandage?
- [Doctor] Bandage.
- [Nurse] Bandage.
Move down the line.
- [Doctor] This
looks like a bandage.
- Bandage?
- [Nurse] Move down the line.
- I need more.
I more than a bandage.
- Bandage?
- Bandage.
- [Old Man] I need
more than a bandage.
- [Nurse] Move down
the line please, sir.
- Did you have your
forms filled out, sir.
- I don't have any forms.
- [Nurse] You don't have any?
- No.
- [Nurse] We need your forms.
- I don't have any.
- [Nurse] Oh come on sir,
you'll have to go back to
the beginning of the line.
- I need a doctor.
- We need our forms.
Look, you should be
feeling a lot better,
they put a bandaid on you.
Take this and just go
back to the beginning.
- Go back?
- [Nurse] Yes, we
need our forms, sir.
- Go back.
[old man crying]
- Bandage.
- [Old Man] I need
more than a bandage.
- Low cost of installation,
low heating process.
Something you've always dreamt
of in a perfect climate.
- As I've walked down
the road of life,
one thing's been true to me,
and that is that a man's
home is his castle.
Now home is just like the body.
That home gets old, it
gets weak, it gets tired.
Now there are many things
that can happen to a home.
The roof can leak, gas, fire.
All the devils of the
night can sneak in
and wipe out your
investment all at once.
Now ladies and gentlemen,
my father and I many years ago
decided that man's
home being his castle,
we formed Castle Rebuilding.
And we've been rebuilding
castles around this area
for a long, long time.
Saving the life investment
of many and many a person.
- [Merchant] Big five,
big public space.
Ma'am, let me show you that
just one moment please.
A place to live, a place to
live with nice big roomy houses.
Ma'am are you tired of
watering your grass?
Are you tired or
watering your plants?
Are you tired of
painting your house, sir?
You're darn right, you are.
Well I've got something.
- I am now gonna come on Monday.
And for those of
you who are willing,
I am gonna give you my card.
Castle Rebuilders, founded
by my father and myself.
- We'll accept your
home in a trade in
at a very fair market value.
In fact, you can have your
home independently appraised,
let us know what it is, our
appraisers will check it out,
and if that's a fair market
value you can trade your home in
for one of these
retirement, carefree homes.
- We make an estimate
absolutely free of charge.
Never do we charge one penny
for inspecting your furnace,
for inspecting your roof,
for inspecting your
electric wiring.
- What you have to do is watch
out for these fast talkers.
What one really
needs is a friend.
- Oh, yes, sir, you're
quite right, quite right.
- I think this is about the
best place to find a friend.
Round an amusement park.
- Yes, it is a beautiful place.
- It's a beautiful
place, you're right.
And I want to thank you
for taking a few
minutes to talk with me
and I'll see you later.
God bless you.
- [Merchant] 85% of a
man's savings is wrapped up
in just one single
possession, his home.
Do you spend a lot of time
fixing your home, sir?
- [Man] Yes, I do.
- [Merchant] Do you find
that things go wrong?
- [Man] Yes, I do.
- [Merchant] Do you find
it that it makes you tired?
[ominous music]
Do you find it makes you sick?
Do you find it makes you say,
I wish this home would
stop breaking down.
- [Man] But when do
I have to pay you?
- [Merchant] You don't
have to pay me, sir.
[amusement park music]
- Hurry, hurry, hurry!
The big show is
just about to begin.
Step right up here, young man.
Tickets are 25 cents each.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
The freak show is just
about ready to begin.
The biggest show on the
lot, oh wait, your change.
Here's your change, thank you.
Hurry, hurry, hurry,
the freak show is just
about ready to begin.
Hurry, get your ticket.
There's your ticket,
there's your ticket.
Thank you very much.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
- [Man] Come on, start the show!
- [Audience] Yeah!
Come on!
[audience applauding]
[band music]
[crowd jeering]
- Oh, what a waste!
What a waste!
[crowd jeering]
- Hey, one of
them's getting away!
Get him!
- [Woman] Don't
let him get away!
[crowd yelling]
[church bells ringing]
[people chattering]
[marching band drumming]
[serene music]
- I'm so tired.
It's so nice to find
a nice little girl.
Oh, what a lovely book.
Would you like me to
read the story to you?
Would you?
Oh, I would like to very much.
Let's see.
Oh, this is "The
Three Little Pigs."
Once upon a time,
three little pigs
went out into the world
to seek their fortunes.
- Want some chicken?
- Oh, I'd love to have
a piece of chicken.
I haven't had anything
to eat for some time.
Well, thank you, dear.
Wouldn't you like to
have a piece, too?
- No thanks, I already had some.
- Now the first thing
each of them had to do
was to build a house to live in.
The first little pig
met a man carrying
a bundle of straw.
Please, sir, he said.
Give me some straw to
build myself a house.
The straw house
was quickly built,
and the little pig was
just settling down nicely
when a big, bad wolf knocked
in the door and said,
little pig, little
pig, let me come in.
Not by the hair on
my chimney chin chin,
said the little pig.
Isn't that funny?
Then the big, bad wolf,
uh, huffed and he puffed.
And he puffed and he huffed
and blew the house in.
He ate up the
frightened little pig
and that was the end
of that little pig.
- [Mother] Girls, come
on now, it's time to go.
- Now the little pig
had built himself
a house of bricks.
It took him much longer to
build a house, a straw house
and a house of sticks,
the little pig that just
got to the brick place.
When the big, bad wolf
knocked the door and said,
little pig, little
pig, let me come in!
And not by the hair of
my chimney chin, chin.
Hi there.
Oh, don't go.
[old man crying]
[people chattering]
[serene music]
♪ My true love ♪
♪ And gently drops the rain ♪
♪ I never had but
one true love ♪
♪ And in Greenwood
he lies slain ♪
♪ I'll do as much
for my true love ♪
♪ As any young girl may ♪
♪ I'll sit and mourn
all on his grave ♪
♪ For 12 months and a day ♪
♪ And when 12 months and a day ♪
[people chattering]
♪ The ghost did rise and speak ♪
♪ Why sit you all on my grave ♪
♪ And will not let me be ♪
♪ How oft on yonder
grave, sweetheart ♪
♪ Where we were want to walk♪
[door opening]
♪ The fairest girl
that ever I've known ♪
- Hello.
I say, hello there.
Don't you a care to talk?
- No.
- Would you, um, would
you like to do something?
- No.
- Do you, um, ever go outside?
- There's no, there's nothing.
Nothing out there.
- Well, I'm, I'm going outside.
- You won't like it.
- Well, if you don't
mind, I'll see for myself.
Goodbye.
- There's nothing out there.
Just nothing.
Nothing.
- One of these times,
the door will open in your life
and you will step into
the amusement park.
Full of hope, anticipation
for the future,
and curiosity for what
you will find there.
And whether you return
to the white room,
desolate, destroyed, and
without any hope for the future,
will depend on a
number of factors,
which when the time comes,
will be beyond your control.
In anticipation for that day,
consider now that the
man in the amusement park
is a mirror image of yourself,
separated only by
the passage of time.
Consider taking
some positive action
while you are young enough
to be a positive influence.
It should be obvious to all
of you that the amusement park
need not to end in a
sterile white room.
You can help.
If you have been
moved to action,
there are a number of
programs already established,
which enable concerned persons
to offer volunteer
services to the elderly.
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you in
the park someday.
[thunder roaring]