(emotional piano music)
(traffic hums)
- [Woman Voiceover] You
ever look up and realize
you're like 12 exits
further than you thought,
and on a totally different parkway?
Sometimes, I think I'm
gonna wake up and realize
I'm still eight years
old, and the last 14 years
have been my imagination.
- What a relief.
(driver sniffles)
- [Woman Voiceover] My mom always told me,
when you're trying to make a decision,
follow your stomach, not your heart.
Whatever path makes you
less sick to your stomach
is the right one.
(playful music)
- You were named after
my mother's sisters,
you know that, Sara and Beth.
Sara was a mother of five beautiful boys,
and Beth was an artist, just like you.
They all died at Auschwitz.
- For some reason, I'm ruled by guilt.
That's what makes me an activist.
I feel responsible for
the world around me.
My parents think I'm dark in spirit,
but noticing evil isn't so pessimistic
if you think you can change things.
I've never been that popular,
and, now that I'm grown up,
I'm a feminist artist.
And I'm even less popular.
Another neato gadget for middle-aged men
to buy at the mall?
- Another biting protest for feminists
who already agree with you?
- Someday, the religious
right will hate me.
Someday, there will be assassination
attempts on my life, yes.
What is that rocket gonna do for you?
- Well, some people think
this crap's actually useful.
Yeah, that's why I have a
job lined up after school.
- So, that thing like flies
and lights up and stuff?
- Would it impress if I gave
you a demonstration and stuff?
- I don't know.
Let me see it.
The best ideas take you by surprise.
Can I borrow this?
Thanks.
- What the hell did you do to my rocket?
- [Sarabeth] And the best revolutionaries
challenge each other.
(Sarabeth laughs)
I got it. (laughs)
My final college thesis was
on progress and evolution.
Then I graduated, and moved
back home with my family.
- [Mother] Aren't you done yet
rebelling against your parents?
- Are you crazy, you made this?
Take this down, or move out.
- If you're gonna censor me
as an artist, I might have to.
- Taking out a second mortgage to send you
to some fancy design college,
is that how we censor you as an artist?
- Religion thrives at the cost
of the female spirit and body.
- What would Sara and Beth think?
- Can't you ever just
let them rest in peace?
- You have no right to
disgrace them like this.
- All right, all right!
- You know what the Talmud says,
"If I'm not for myself,
who will be for me?"
- [Sarabeth] I know, Dad.
- If Jews are not for
ourselves, believe me,
nobody will be for us.
My mother was lucky to survive
and make it to this country.
Otherwise, none of us would be here!
- I'm from Brooklyn.
I spent my childhood staring
across the river at Manhattan,
knowing that there were
these great artists
right there, shaking things up,
wishing I was right there with them.
Now I'm back in Brooklyn.
Only 30 minutes away by subway,
but the promised land has always been
just beyond my reach.
(upbeat music)
- Commuting halfway across Brooklyn
for a waitressing job, are you crazy?
- Well, it's close to Manhattan.
I'll be living there soon
enough, if I can just save up.
All right, Ma, half of this
is gonna wind up in the trash.
Starving children in America, you know.
- Smart-alec.
You're too smart to be
serving people all day long.
- So are you.
- Waitressing, after four
years of this fancy college?
Ruthie, get me a razor blade.
I gotta scrap the college
sticker off my station wagon.
- Not a regular waiter, a cater waiter.
They make really good money.
- Oh, I see, this really
is a brilliant career move.
- I only have to work four nights a week,
leaving my days free
to paint in the light.
Don't you understand how
important this is to me?
- Sweetheart, if you
become an art teacher,
you get to take the whole
summer off to paint.
- Customers treat waitresses like crap.
Sarabeth, you're not gonna like it.
You don't even like helping
your mother in the kitchen.
- Ain't that the truth.
(light, percussive music)
- [Sarabeth Voiceover] I don't know why
my mother is so surprised.
She's been training me for
this job my entire life.
During the holidays, she turns
my sisters and me into servants.
What's wrong with being paid for it?
- [Ruthie] Careful, Sarabeth.
Easy, watch it!
- Okay, you don't have to yell.
- Maybe I should prepare
for Passover all by myself.
- Is that supposed to be a threat?
- Very funny.
- Sarabeth, why don't you
just do the silverware?
- [Ruthie] I would think
you'd be better at this,
considering your new line of work.
- You know what, if
you don't like waiters,
maybe you shouldn't go
to restaurants anymore.
- What kind of men are you going to meet
in that environment, huh?
- Mom, my boyfriend is
on his way over here.
- [Ruthie] I mean a man that
you would consider marrying.
- Ma, she just got out of
school, leave her alone.
- Yeah, why do you wanna
marry me off so bad anyways?
You're not getting a dowry for me.
- I wanna see you safe
and settled and secure
with somebody that cares about you.
You're not getting any younger, you know.
I can't do this forever.
- Mom, we can take care of ourselves.
We do take care of ourselves.
- Would it be so terrible to see
a few Jewish grandchildren
running around here,
from any of you?
Children, I want these
dishes very well organized.
Look at the way Becky's doing this,
perfect, perfect!
- Please.
- Perfect, my darling.
- Perfect little Becky.
- [Ruthie] In eight days, we
gotta put these dishes back.
We've been doing this since
you were a little girl.
- Do you ever feel like the
Torah invents extra housework?
- Oh, please, I don't do half
of what my mother used to do,
and she didn't do half of
what Grandma used to do.
You know what they say, something is lost-
- In every generation.
- What, do you think that
Daddy's the only religious one?
What am I?
Just some schlub that does
all the housework, what?
When do I ever forget to
separate milk form meat?
When do I ever forget
to keep God in my mind?
- Cracking the whip!
- It keeps you very spiritual.
- What, slave labor is spiritual?
- Living your life
according to your beliefs
and not just running off at the mouth is.
- This is exactly why I'm
against organized religion.
- Right, we're brainwashed
and you're an original.
I don't know one kid that hasn't graduated
from university that doesn't wanna do away
with organized religion.
Down with organized religion,
down with capitalism,
down with health
insurance, until, one day,
you get by a truck, God forbid,
and then, my darling Sarabeth,
then you will see that
life is not so simple.
- Ma, why can't Dad help?
Why can't Howie help?
Where's he at, huh?
Simon's coming over in enough time
to help with the cleanup and the setup.
We're equal partners,
and we always will be.
- I bet the Pope
would be proud.
(doorbell rings)
- Oh, God.
Ma, be nice.
You invited him.
- I'll be cordial.
I'll really be cordial if you bring me
a gorgeous medical student
as brilliant as you, my sweetheart.
Then I'll really be cordial, I promise.
- [Sarabeth] Mom, Becky,
Raquel, this is Simon.
- Well.
- Hi, Simon.
- [Simon] Hi.
- How do you do?
- All right, nice to meet you, Mrs. Cohen.
- And you.
- These are for you.
- Oh, my heavens, thank you so much.
- [Raquel] Have a seat, Simon.
Can we get you something to drink?
- No, actually, I'm good.
I came early so that I can help,
so what needs to be done?
- [Becky] We are in the
middle of changing the dishes
and cleaning the cabinets.
- [Ruthie] Oh my God, I
didn't realize it was so late!
- We're on top of it, Mom.
Come on, I'll wash, you
dry, we'll get it done.
- Good Yomtov.
I see every car I have
ever owned in the driveway.
That must mean my girls are home.
Is there an almost-doctor in the house?
- Why, you finally wanna
get that cough checked out?
- [Dad] As soon as you
check your smart mouth.
- [Sarabeth] Hi, Daddy.
- Hi, (speaking foreign language).
- Daddy, Simon Stanton.
Simon, Isaac Cohen.
- I thought his name was Christianson
or something like that.
- Dad!
- I can't keep up, I'm sorry.
I'm still waiting for Becky's husband
and Raquel's kids and the Messiah, so.
- [Raquel] You'll probably
see the Messiah first.
- Listen, I'll take anything
as long as it arrives
before I die.
- Ma!
- In the words of Spinoza,
the secret to life
is that it stops.
- That's Kafka, Daddy.
- You send your kids to school,
and how do they thank you?
They become wise-apples and throw
their knowledge back at you,
and, the more years they spend in school,
the more they throw back in your face.
How's this apartment search working out?
- Horrible, I can't
even find a dumpy studio
with a shared bathroom.
- Maybe Becky will be of help with this.
- My roommate just moved out on me.
Maybe you can stay with me temporarily.
- Really?
That would be awesome.
- I know you wanted to be downtown,
but it's right by Columbia.
It's a pretty fun area.
- I can pick up extra
shifts at the restaurant!
- Great.
- It's a mitzvah.
- It's too bad that
Howard isn't as motivated
as Sarabeth to work.
- Ma, he is working, very hard.
- Working hard, spending
your money working hard.
- You don't even know
what you're talking about.
- I don't?
- No.
- So why are you always broke?
Where is your money?
And what are you kids gonna do
when you wanna have a child?
- Ruthie, he's just having
trouble starting a business.
- Ma, he's working with his brother
every day, every weekend.
- That brother, that
brother's the worst thing
that could happen to either of you.
The farther that you stay
away from that brother,
the better it is.
- Why are you so hard on him?
- Instinct.
- He tries so hard to get you to like him.
Why do you think he's
always walking around
opening jars and squashing bugs for you?
And you never make him feel welcome, ever.
- [Man Voiceover] Hello, hello?
- All right, subject
close, subject closed.
Hello, Howard!
- Hi, princess.
- Hi, honey.
Good Yomtov, everyone, I
brought some macaroons.
- [Ruthie] Aw, that's
lovely of you, Howard.
Welcome, Howard, welcome.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you.
If there's anything you need me to do,
you'll let me know.
- Yes.
- Any jars that need opened?
- Not yet.
Oh, Howard, have you met Simon?
This is Sarabeth's boyfriend.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- How are you doing, Simon.
- Howie.
- Her Catholic boyfriend.
- I'm sorry about her.
I'm sorry about all of them.
They are freaks!
You know, they don't know how
to behave in front of company.
It's so embarrassing!
When the Seder's over,
we'll just come back
up here and hide.
- Okay, stop.
So you're really excited about New York?
That's what you want forever?
- Yeah, I'm really excited.
Manhattan.
- You know, sometimes, I can't look at you
without thinking about forever.
Does that scare you?
- It's kinda scary.
I mean, it's all scary
and exciting, you know?
It's like being on a rollercoaster
and that feeling you get in your stomach
right before the drop.
- Well, tonight, each one
pours another person's glass,
just to remind us that
we are no longer slaves.
Why?
Because we have to treat each other
with a sense of decency.
And now for the (speaking
foreign language).
(family sings in foreign language)
- [Ruthie] Drink up, drink up.
- On this night, every Jew should imagine,
should personalize, and
personalize this intimately,
what it would be to be freed from Egypt.
- I'm finally getting
out of my parents' house!
So, I move in April 1st.
Smack in the middle of
my sister's living room.
- Welcome to New York, baby.
- My boyfriend is never
gonna want to visit me.
He just got this new apartment
over his uncle's garage.
- Honey, you can't afford New York
without a major sacrifice.
- Or a trust fund.
- Well, she said I could
have the walk-in closet.
- [Waitress] So?
- I'm thinking of making that my bedroom.
I mean, it's only six by four,
but it fits a mattress,
and at least it has a door.
- I haven't had a door
since I moved to New York.
- You haven't?
- I live in a studio
with six other dancers.
- That's fucked up.
- Yeah, I'm one of them.
Gina lives alone.
- Yeah, right.
Not if you count the
mice and the cockroaches.
Sweetie, you'll be fine.
(upbeat jazz music)
- I can't imagine how you're gonna find
room to unpack all this.
I thought you said this
living room was big.
- For New York.
- And this apartment is
considered a good deal.
When I came to this country,
we moved to the city because
it's all we could afford.
Who knew I was so glamorous and
cosmopolitan before my time?
- Yeah, I think we've
seen this episode, Dad.
- You know, Simon, for
what they could sell
this apartment for, we could
buy two houses on Long Island,
three houses upstate, and
five houses in Atlantic City.
- Yeah, and trade them all in for a hotel.
(Isaac laughs)
- Good one, Christianson,
good one, not bad for a goy.
- Stanton, Simon Stanton.
- You're all right, kid.
Sarabeth, believe me, I feel so good
knowing he'll be looking out for you.
- I'll look out for me, Dad.
- [Becky] Yeah, Dad, I think
we can take it form here.
- Oh, I get it, I get it.
Like they say in Vaudeville,
"Here's your hat, what's your hurry?"
Simon, I remember the days when they used
to fight over my time for piggyback rides.
All right.
- Thanks, Daddy.
- Use it in good health,
and, most importantly,
be safe.
Take care of them, Simon, will you?
Bye bye, princesses.
- Goodnight, Dad.
- Thanks, Dad.
- [Sarabeth] Thanks, Dad.
- I have six chapters to
read for my eight am class,
so I'm I'm gonna go in my room.
- Have fun studying.
- Night, you two.
- So, now what?
- Well, we go to my luxurious new bedroom.
(door creaks)
- This is nice.
- [Sarabeth Voiceover] Finally, I'm right
where I'm supposed to be.
Now, make something brilliant.
So much to say, and only eight
million people to say it to.
Paris had impressionists,
London had romantics,
and, for better or worse, New York,
the capital of attitude, has me.
- Well, honey, I guess I'm going
to have to be the one to break it to you.
Female anger, demands for equality,
rebelling against men,
all very early '90s.
I'm afraid I won't be able to sell these.
- Okay, well.
What about that one?
- Well, these are a little too optimistic.
See, in the art world, remember,
cynicism never goes out of style.
You just have to keep
up with what it's hip
to be cynical about.
- [Becky] Wow, what's this?
- Oh, just something I made.
- This is funny.
You should do more stuff
like this, fun stuff.
You're really funny.
- What, you don't like
when I question things
with my art?
That's right, you don't question anything.
- Relax, I was trying to
give you a compliment.
(train clacks)
- [Simon Voiceover] It's a bit of a drive
from the train stations, but
it's nice up here, right?
- Yeah.
This is so perfect.
Some weekends, you can come to New York
for culture and excitement,
and other weekends,
I can come here for hiking
and biking and inspiration.
(gentle music)
Oh, man, are they serious?
You gotta pay a toll over here?
- Well, us rednecks need
to pay for our roads
somehow, too, Missy.
Hi.
I haven't even shown you the best part.
(gentle, upbeat music)
Wait, wait.
Ready?
Keep them closed, keep them closed.
All right, right there.
Open up!
Check out all the shit I bought!
- Wow.
- I got a plant, a TV,
a VCR, a DVD player, stereo,
and they're all hooked
up to these speakers.
- Where?
- They go here, and here.
And, the best thing is that I got it all
on my first two paychecks.
- How are you gonna pay your rent?
- No, my rent's cheap, yeah.
The way that the whole work thing goes
is that I get paid next week
and the week after that
and the week after that.
It just keeps going.
Yeah, yeah.
So now we can watch movies,
and we never have to leave.
- Cool!
(upbeat jazz music)
All the waiters here
are struggling artists,
and every one of us
thinks that we're the one
that's gonna make it.
And every restaurant in
New York is the same way.
The most creative people serve drinks
to the most boring ones.
But it's okay, we're all in it together.
- Sarabeth, why do you
have so much laundry?
- Don't you feel like this
takes you away from composing?
- I'm saying, it'd be nice
to have a maid, but, uh.
- Yeah, it'd be nice to
have a social life, too.
- You know, it's frustrating,
but I'm under the belief,
that when you're an artist,
a part of you is creating every minute.
Like, for example, listen to the sound
the wheels are making on the sidewalk.
(percussive music)
(Gina grunts)
Here we go, yeah.
Right?
- [Sarabeth] You're
never selling this song.
(percussive music)
- [Gina] One day, one day, we won't
have to do this anymore.
(percussive music)
- [Sarabeth] Hey.
- Hey.
- [Sarabeth] What is that?
- Dinner from Mom.
- Why?
- [Becky] She sends it every week.
- She sends mashed potatoes and turkey?
The kid in medical school gets everything.
- She would've sent
you meals in your dorm,
but you always said no.
- I thought everyone said no.
- Not everyone is as dumb as you.
(percussive music)
- I know.
I'm trying to paint something patriotic,
but I can't do that
without being sarcastic.
(Becky and Sarabeth chuckle)
It's not funny.
Simon's mom is having this
big 4th of July party,
and I can't show up empty-handed.
- Well, why don't you just
take a bottle of wine?
(people chatter)
(light music)
- [Dad] Well, hello, is
this the famous little lady
from New York City?
- Dad, Sarabeth, Sarabeth.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Bill Stanton.
And Mom, hey, Mom.
- Oh, hi, sweetie.
- Maddie Stanton.
- Hi, pleased to meet you.
- Oh, how fancy, wine at a BBQ.
Thank you.
- New York City style.
- And my sister Stacey Stanton.
- Hi.
Nice to meet you.
- Sarabeth.
And her boyfriend Tony.
- Hi.
- Happy Independence Day.
- Hey, Tony.
- Hey.
- It's my favorite holiday.
And I have some amazing news.
Tony just proposed to me,
we're getting married!
- She's the luckiest girl in the world.
- [Bill] You better treat
my little girl well,
ya big fuck-up!
- [Maddie] I'm gonna cry.
- It's really cool to
finally meet you, Sarabeth.
You know, we could be
sisters-in-law someday.
- Yeah, and then you'd be the
luckiest girl in the world.
(Stacey chuckles)
- Happy 4th of July! (laughs)
- Why don't we celebrate July 4th, Daddy?
- Because it's silly
patriotism, that's why.
It leads to fascism.
When we Jews hear loud
explosions like this,
we always think the big
government is out to get us.
- We do?
Sounds a bit paranoid.
- Where'd you learn that word?
- Woody Allen says, "It's not paranoia
"if everyone's out to get ya."
(fireworks pop)
- Ooh!
(people shout)
- Come on, Sarabeth, come on!
- Well, now that my
girlfriend lives in New York,
I can get my fireworks from Chinatown.
- Oh, those chinks know
how to blow stuff up.
- Hey, that's not funny now
that they've been stealing
all our military secrets
and shit over there.
- Tony, take it easy.
- Like the fucking war machine
Jew Israelis.
- Yo, shut the fuck up.
- Fucking Jews always fucking us sup.
- What, shut the fuck up!
- It's true, I'm just saying.
- That's enough,
that's enough.
No fighting on our nation's birthday.
- Baby, he didn't mean anything by it.
- Not directly.
- I thought we didn't have religion.
I don't understand why
you're getting so upset.
- He insulted my family,
he insulted my ancestors.
Simon, this guy's marrying your sister.
- He's a good guy, he
just got a little wasted.
- You know, the thing is,
is that, if I wasn't there,
I don't think anyone would
have been mad at him.
It's like it's never
uncool to knock down a Jew
unless another Jew is there.
- Sarabeth, your family is
way more prejudiced than mine.
(traffic hums)
- Why do Mom and Dad have to call Simon
a goy every time they see him?
- They're just calling him mainstream,
like they're calling him "the man."
They have a watch-your-backs
attitude about "the man."
- You're so hip-hop.
- Mom's just trying to protect you.
- It's like she doesn't even
realize that she's oppressed.
- Come on, Sarabeth.
Don't you remember the
stories she's always telling
about Grandma and the haystack?
- Don't you think we dwell
on that a little too much?
- Just because something's older than you
doesn't mean it's out of date.
- Your great-grandmother Ada, she survived
these pogroms, and, God
knows, she would want
you to know about them.
There were these mean
soldiers called the Cossacks,
and they would come on horseback,
and they would attack the Jews.
And the so-called police,
you know what they would do?
Sometimes, here, I'll help you,
sometimes, they would
side with the attackers.
Sometimes, they even were the attackers.
And your grandma Ada,
guess how old she was.
15 years old, and her father was so afraid
that these bad men would hurt her
that, when he would hear them coming,
he would hide her away in the haystack,
and she would wait there until they left.
Grandpa was very, very terrified
that they would rape her.
And, one day, the Cossacks came galloping,
holding these sticks of fire,
and they set fire to all these homes
with families in them, and Ada was buried
in her haystack, suffocating,
afraid, scared to death.
She could even smell the smoke,
afraid to come out, afraid to stay put.
"What if this hay catches on fire?
"I'll burn to death."
God forbid, God forbid, God forbid.
(exciting music)
For a sweet year.
(Ruthie speaking foreign language)
May God inscribe us all
in the book of life.
God bless my beautiful children.
(Isaac speaking foreign language)
(family speaking foreign language)
- Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year, Christianson.
Glad you could join us.
- Happy New Year.
Time to come clean.
- What?
Have you been hiding some brilliant,
millionaire Jewish doctor?
Or a medical student?
I'll settle for a medical student.
- Well-
- Speaking of coming clean.
I've been keeping a really
big secret from all of you,
waiting for the right time to tell you,
which I think is now, I'm pregnant.
(Ruthie cheers)
- I don't believe it, darling,
(speaking foreign language).
You did it, Howie, you did it.
- Wait, what?
What, what?
I knew, I was kidding.
- I didn't know.
- You silly goose.
I can't believe you kept
that from me, Raquel.
- I want this baby to be
completely surrounded by love,
so you all better be ready to play.
- [Ruthie] Sweetheart, nothing unifies
a family more than a baby.
(Isaac speaking foreign language)
- I mean, this is news, real news!
News to make the
great-grandparents smile in heaven.
- I cannot wait to be an aunt.
I'm gonna be the coolest aunt.
- How far along are you?
- Just seven weeks,
so keep it quiet, okay, 'cause it's early.
Keep it quiet, Mom, don't go
tell the whole neighborhood.
- [Sarabeth] Yeah,
right, Mom keep a secret?
- [Ruthie] Hey, you, mind your manners.
- Wait, I'm on the brink
of something very big.
- I have some...
I have something to tell everyone, too.
- Oh, we've gotta go shopping.
- Listen.
- [Ruthie] This is the
happiest day of my life.
- I'm a lesbian, I like women!
(Raquel laughs)
- Rebecca, there are other
ways to get our attention.
Next time you wanna say
something, just say "excuse me."
(Ruthie chuckles)
- Excuse me.
I'm trying to tell you, I'm a lesbian.
- What?
- Why do you always have
to steal my thunder?
- Oh, honey.
- Really.
- Raquel.
- Are you jealous?
Are you jealous of your sister
because you can't find a boyfriend?
- I'm not jealous.
Mom, I'm happy for Raquel.
I don't want a boyfriend, I'm a lesbian.
I want a girlfriend.
(sighs) It's out, I'm out.
- Beckala, what have we ever done to you
to deserve this kind of talk?
- Every kid needs a flighty,
neurotic, lesbian aunt.
- Oh, Howard.
(Raquel laughs)
- Yeah, yeah, that's your crazy, lesbian
Aunt Becky, honey.
- I didn't mean to shock you,
but I've been keeping
this a secret for so long.
- And you suddenly think it's no longer
something to be ashamed of?
- You're saying it's better to hide?
- Like great-grandma,
who hid in the haystack?
If she comes out, she might be hurt,
but if she stays in, she
might be burned to death?
- [Ruthie] Don't you dare.
- Why did you have to ruin
the best day of our lives?
How can you do this to Raquel?
We should be celebrating.
- It would be nice.
- Isaac, Isaac, please, I understand.
Rebecca, you're our perfect child,
our beautiful, perfect child,
but you're under a lot of pressure now.
We know that.
I mean, here it is,
your sister is pregnant,
and you feel absolutely
terrible that it's not you,
but-
- Ma!
- You should know that you can come
to your father and me about anything.
It's safe here, it's safe.
We know about Columbia Medical School.
It's absolutely impossible.
No, you know what, you know
what, we give you permission.
You can get a B, once in a while.
Get a B, get a B, anytime you want.
Isaac, we put too much
pressure on this child.
- You put too much pressure-
- You have put too much
pressure on her.
- I accept them always!
- Not me!
- I accept them, I love them
for who they are.
- Gay?
- I have the most wonderful idea.
I want you to take a
vacation over spring break.
You've never done that before.
We'll pay for it.
You can take Sarabeth with you,
and you'll get away
from all this pressure.
Honey, you try to do too much.
I understand, you're cracking.
- You're cracking, I'm fine.
I'm a lesbian, and I've
been fine with that
for a long time.
- It must be very, very difficult
to live up to all the nice
things I say about you.
- Rebecca, it's the high holidays.
It's time to resolve
differences, not create them.
- This difference has been
unresolved my whole life.
Dad, if I'm not for
myself, who will be for me?
- Hillel.
- You can get a B.
No problem, get a B.
- Mom, why won't you listen?
- You know what, let's go.
- No, baby, don't go.
- Wait, wait, don't leave.
- Please, please, don't go, my darling.
It's (speaking foreign language).
I made this, Sarabeth-
- You know what?
I would stay, but you
people, you make me sick.
- [Ruthie] Please, please, don't leave.
- Yeah, go, go, go, get out.
You think I want to see any of you?
Get out!
Drive carefully.
- I can't stand them.
We were raised by oppressors,
but all they can talk about
is how they were oppressed.
Fuck them.
I am so proud of you.
- You still think I
never question anything?
- I'm a jerk.
I didn't know you like I thought I did.
- I'm a little more
interesting to you now.
- I'm gonna support you, okay?
Anything you want from
me, you let me know.
- Really?
Good, thanks.
Would you do me a favor then?
- Anything.
- Please, go to Synagogue
with me this Yom Kippur.
- What, after all this
bullshit, you still wanna go?
- Of course.
- You know, I have a better idea.
Let's get that trip out of Mom.
We could go to Club Med.
I could introduce you to some women.
That would totally fucking show them.
- Can't you understand
that I just want to be
with family on the High Holidays?
You're my only family now.
- You're killing me, Becky.
You know I hate it with
every fiber of my being.
- My synagogue in New
York is really different
than Mom and Dad's.
The rabbi is super cool
and super progressive.
Super beautiful, too.
(chanting in foreign language)
- "Guard our lips from evil.
"Guard our hands from wrongdoing."
God, she's so cool!
- That's from the Amidah, Sarabeth.
You've been hearing that
at our parents' temple
your whole life.
- I know, but Mom's rabbi never connected
it to activism.
- Why do you think they were involved
in that coat drive every year?
- Becky, why do you have to defend them
when they're being such jerks to you?
- There she is.
Wow, isn't she beautiful?
Let's go say hello.
I'm nervous.
- Don't be nervous.
You look awesome.
What kind of moves have you made so far?
- Well, I go to her services
every Friday and Saturday morning,
and I go to her discussion
groups every Tuesday night.
- That's it?
- I always make really good points.
- Okay.
Don't you think it's
time to step it up a bit.
- Oh, no.
See that girl standing next to her?
That's Naomi.
She goes to all the same stuff I do,
plus she's always dressed to kill.
She's always wearing
jewelry and full-on makeup.
She always has her hair done.
She's always wearing mini skirts.
- I might be completely new at this,
but that doesn't really strike me
as a way to get a lesbian rabbi.
- Yeah, you are new at this.
- Good Yomtov, Becky Cohen.
What are you doing?
- I have a question for the rabbi.
- I have a question for the rabbi, too.
- Good Yomtov, Becky.
- Good Yomtov, Rabbi.
- Good Yomtov, Naomi.
- Rabbi.
- Rabbi, this is my sister Sarabeth.
It's her first time here.
- Oh, it's a pleasure to meet you.
- I really enjoyed what you said.
- Good.
- We, my sister and I, we had a question.
We were wondering if you could have
a discussion on interfaith dating.
- As a matter of fact, yes.
I have one planned for November,
so keep your Tuesday nights free.
- Thank you, Rabbi, thank you.
- Yeah, thanks.
- Did you have a question, Naomi?
- No, actually, I was just wondering
the same thing Becky was.
- Well then, I will see you ladies soon.
Have a meaningful fast.
- Becky, are you going to
discussion group on Tuesday?
- Maybe.
- Wanna get a cup of coffee after?
- Why, to discuss interfaith dating?
- God, you are so intense.
I love that.
No, actually, to discuss anything, Becky.
- Oh.
Oh, okay.
Sure, why not?
- All right, Becky Cohen, it's a date.
I can't wait.
- What if that is a ploy to lure
me away from Rabbi Glickstein
so she can make her move.
- Do you like her?
- I don't know.
I mean, she's no Rabbi
Glickstein, but she is cute.
And intelligent, really
intelligent, actually.
She called me intense,
and I'm not sure if that's a compliment.
- Beckala.
(percussive music)
Yes, I'm getting enough sleep.
Ma, will you stop thinking
of new things to worry about?
(Ruthie chuckles)
- And how's Becky?
- She's happy and gay.
- That's not funny, Sarabeth.
- Becky's going through
a very difficult time.
- True.
Coming out to your
parents is very difficult.
- Sweetheart, why don't you
take your sister out at night?
You know, introduce her
to some of your friends.
Be the wonderful sister that you are.
- Sure, I could do that.
I know some bull dykes.
- Is she eating?
- You know what?
She'll be home in 10 minutes.
Why don't you ask her yourself?
- Is she sleeping or is she trying
to pull those all-nighters?
- [Sarabeth] Why don't
you ask her yourself?
- How late is she staying at the library?
- Why don't you ask her yourself?
- Why don't you give me a
straight answer, damn it,
or you'll live to regret it!
- When she stays out
past 12, she takes a cab.
You feel better?
- No.
I may never feel better,
as a matter of fact.
(sinuous music)
- [Sarabeth Voiceover] This religion is
more than 5,000 years old.
But, frankly, it still has
a lot of growing up to do.
- [Man] Sarabeth, pay attention!
- [Sarabeth Voiceover] And my mother,
she's not so young, either.
When is she gonna wake up?
(sinuous music)
One minute, she says she's suffering,
the next minute, she wants her daughters
to be just like her.
Great, where do I sign?
Nobody notices the great
mothers and wives of the Torah.
What is the point of being chosen
when you don't have any choices?
- [Simon] Stop.
- Why won't you look at me?
- [Simon] Well, maybe I
feel a little bit rejected.
- Sometimes, I have
other things on my mind.
- Sometimes?
- Yeah, sometimes.
- You know, we only get to see each other
like every other weekend,
so, if we don't have sex now,
then we go like another
whole two weeks without it.
- Is that why you come here?
- No!
- Then stop treating
me like a blowup doll.
- Oh, back again, are we?
- I took your advice
to be less optimistic.
- Yes, I see that.
You should also try to
be a bit less literal.
(sinuous music)
(light music)
(traffic hums)
- I need to remember to relax more.
Like this.
- Baby you don't feel relaxed.
What's wrong?
- I wanna see you more.
I wanna see my friends more.
I wanna watch more great movies,
and, somehow, I always wanna paint more.
- And you wanna work out more
and sleep more and read more.
Is there anything you wanna do less?
- Yeah, wait tables.
(Simon chuckles)
- I think you should move in with me.
- Here?
- Yeah, here.
I mean, I make enough money now
that you would only
have to work part-time.
You can use the loft room
as your painting room.
I mean, as of now, you only get
like every other weekend off.
We never get to see each other.
And we're ready, Sarabeth, we're in love.
(percussive music)
- [Sarabeth Voiceover]
Hi, professor Willow,
this is Sarabeth Cohen.
I'm living in New York now,
doing the whole bringing my slides
to the galleries thing.
Anyways, I was just wondering,
you said we should call you
when we're ready to go professional
because you have a lot of contacts.
I would love to talk to
you any time about that.
I'm living here now, and loving it.
I guess I'll try you again later.
Thanks.
(lush music)
- [Women] Surprise!
- Oh my gosh, I had no idea!
I thought Mom and I were just
gonna carve pumpkins today.
- We've got bigger plans, come on.
Sit on your throne.
- Oh my gosh, you guys.
- Okay, I'm gonna write down the gifts.
Monica can make the hat,
and Marie can give her the presents.
- I always make the hat.
- Oh my gosh, I can't believe
all these presents are for me.
- Oh, you deserve it, honey.
- Thank you, guys.
Wonderful.
- Yeah, that's the fastest
blender on the market.
- Really?
- People underestimate the
importance of a blender.
- You can get the dinner
on the table in minutes.
- Thanks to you guys. (chuckles)
- It's so pretty, I
hate to ruin the paper.
Oh my gosh, Mom!
- Now I don't have to worry about you two
going through life with unprocessed food!
(women laugh)
- I registered for two of those.
- Really?
Oh, this is adorable.
Great, look at these.
Terrific.
- Yep, you can never have too
many wooden spoons, right?
(women chuckle)
Did I just say that?
- I use a wooden spoon every single day.
- [Stacey] They come in handy, don't they?
- This wasn't on the registry.
- Oh, let's see.
Oh my gosh, this one's from Sarabeth.
Let's see what it is.
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh,
oh my gosh, oh my gosh!
You remembered!
This is my dream house.
- Oh!
- It's exactly like
I described it to you.
It's beautiful.
- Thanks.
- This is the greatest present
anyone could ever give me.
Tony and I are gonna put
it on the mantelpiece
and look at it every time we forget
what we're working so hard for.
I dream about having children
in a place like this.
Sarabeth, I love it!
Come here, I wanna give you a hug!
Come on, come here!
Get over here!
(women clap)
- And now it's time to
put Stacey's crazy hat on.
- Oh, no, you don't actually
expect me to wear that thing!
- Oh yeah!
- Okay.
(women laugh)
You don't know how you're gonna feel
until you're actually
wearing one of these things.
(women laugh)
- Don't freak out.
You know how important this is to me.
Remember, he's making an effort.
- You don't even ask who it is?
- Hi.
- Gonna let Jack the Ripper
in one of these days.
- Hi.
- Oh, it feels so good to be social.
You know, this is the like the first time
in a week I haven't thrown up.
- Special delivery form your mother.
- Well, where is she?
- Here, in spirit.
This place is filled with canvases,
my little Leonardo da Vinci.
I was wrong, I admit it.
The waitressing agrees with you.
- Well, you weren't completely wrong.
I do hate it.
- Better hate your job
at your age than mine.
How is school, Doc?
- Well, I'm finally getting
used to looking at cadavers.
- Rabbi Mendelson asks
about you all the time.
He remembers how smart you are,
fighting with him, a lot,
making him think more than anybody else.
Valedictorian of your Hebrew School.
You should go pay him a visit.
- Sure.
- Raquel made some cookies.
Good practice for motherhood.
- I don't wanna eat them all by myself.
I'm getting fat enough as it is.
So come on, here, they're still warm.
- Tell them about Howie.
Things are finally looking
up, and just in time.
- I don't wanna say
anything too prematurely,
but looks like he and Steve
have sold all the properties
they invested in.
Isn't that great?
He's so happy, he's been singing Van Halen
songs in the shower. (laughs)
- Van Halen?
- It's what we liked to listen
to in high school, thank you.
- Okay.
- That's wonderful, Raquel.
- You know, I'm always rooting for Howie,
waiting for him to sort of
prove himself to the world.
He's gonna be a great dad.
- And, if he makes enough money,
Raquel may even be able to
stay at home with the baby.
- That's great.
- Oh, great, great life.
- Sarabeth.
- (sighs) You love to teach.
- And I will love to spend
time with my baby even more.
Why do you always have to make
everything the Russian Revolution?
- No, it's just, you know,
I wish I was a lesbian
so I didn't have to buy
into all the expectations.
- Baby, when did you
get to be so nasty, huh?
When was your life ever so hard?
God, you used to be
like the sweetest child
anybody ever knew.
What happened?
- I'm sorry, Raquel,
I'm happy for you guys.
And, Daddy, I think it's
great that you came here.
- I'm glad I came here, too, baby.
Becky, you were always so religious.
- I live a modern spiritual Jewish life.
- That means you pick and
choose which laws to break?
Remember what Tevye says
in "Fiddler on the Roof."
"What happens to a beautiful fabric
"when you pull out even a tiny thread?"
- A fabric can bend to fit the person
who chooses to wear it.
- But Tevye also says,
"If you bend me too much,
"I will break."
- You don't follow every rule, either.
- All right, you're right.
Well, in the words of
Hannibal the Cannibal,
"Let's forget what's
eating us, and let's eat."
- That's lovely, Dad.
Yum.
- What do you mean?
(Becky laughs)
(soft music)
- [Sarabeth Voiceover] Growing up
doesn't have to mean giving up.
All the waiters I work with have been
pursuing their art careers
for five to 10 years.
- Just leave your postcards here, sweetie.
We'll get back to you.
- You will hear from us just as soon
as the curators have a
chance to see your work.
- [Sarabeth Voiceover] I'm
not sure if anybody gets
Gina's music or cares that Charlotte
can do a split in the air,
but we all keep trying,
no matter what anybody tells us.
You ever hear the sound
of eight million people not clapping?
(percussive music)
- The world's just not
ready for you, kiddo.
- Maybe I'm not ready for the world.
- Don't sweat the small stuff.
- Don't call it small.
You know, I remember when
you wanted it badly, too.
(traffic hums)
(pulsing music)
(wind whistles)
- [Simon] So, what are
you going to wish for?
- I'm not sure.
- Well, maybe that's because
you have everything you need.
- I don't know.
Sometimes, I think me and the real me
have been out of touch for years,
and neither seems to wanna call first.
- Maybe you should make the first move.
- I should make a wish that
I can make happen myself,
stop relying on these stupid candles.
- [Boss] All right, honey, I
got two minutes, what is it?
- I know you're really busy.
You know how this place
is never really booked
on Monday nights?
- Mm hmm.
- I was wondering if maybe I could have
a showing of my artwork here.
- You know, you're like the worst waitress
that we have here.
- No, I didn't know that.
- Yeah, I'm always on
the verge of firing you
but, you know, I just can't
bring myself to do it.
- How about I give you $500?
- And you give me five Saturday nights
in addition to your regular shifts.
Call that a deal.
- Deal, thank you.
- [Boss] Well all right.
(busy music)
- Matisse said,
creativity takes courage.
Here's my heart, soul, and
belief system on a canvas.
Go ahead and judge me.
(busy music)
(TV chatters)
Aren't you happy to see me?
- I'm just tired.
After work, I had to
make the half-hour trip
to the train station to pick you up.
- Oh, yeah, that's tough.
Oh, I just spent three
hours with motion sickness
on that broken-down
local train to nowhere,
and then 10 minutes freezing
my ass off, waiting for you.
(TV chatters)
- I'm sorry.
- So, Tom said yes about the show.
February 4th.
- So what exactly does that mean?
- Well, we'll invite everyone I know,
plus everyone you know.
We can invite art press,
some professors from school.
We can invite-
- The ones who aren't calling you back?
- Well, this will just give
me a reason to call me back.
He's only charging me $500.
- Only $500.
And you have to pay for
your own food, right?
How the hell are you gonna pull this off?
- Hey, I'm still young.
I can max out my credit cards
without ruining my entire life.
(train clacks)
(gentle music)
- [Becky] What's wrong?
- (sighs) I just realized I'm too old
to become a child prodigy.
- Well, you've got a lot of
years to become a Grandma Moses.
- Swell.
- Why do I think everyone
should listen to me?
- When you answer that,
then you'll create something wonderful.
- (chuckles) Why do you always
sound like a fortune cookie?
- Ow.
(Sarabeth chuckles)
- I remember my first cynical thought.
I was eight.
My dad told me even though
Moses busted his ass
and brought the Jews out of Egypt,
he never made it to the Promised Land.
Excuse me, but what
part of "promised land"
didn't God understand?
Seems like when you stand
up for your beliefs,
you're usually alone.
(busy music)
Where do you wanna go to eat?
- Do you need this for your show?
- No, I think I'm just gonna use a photo.
I can't believe you
took this off your wall.
- [Simon] I'm sorry.
- It's okay, you were just being nice.
- No, baby, I mean I'm sorry.
- About what?
- I'm sorry that I can't
do this anymore, that-
- You're bringing up with me?
Why are you doing this?
Because of the show?
Are you worried you're gonna get ignored
because of the show?
- No, I've just done
some thinking, and I realize
I can't do this anymore.
- Because I won't move in with you?
Because I can move in
with you after the show-
- Sarabeth, you know that's
what I've wanted for months.
Your career is just taking off,
and there's no room in it for me.
You might not be able to
see that now, but I can.
I want you to know that I love you,
and I believe in you, and I always will.
- But not enough.
- I couldn't love you any more.
Can't you see that you've
been my whole world?
I could never be your whole world.
The one thing that I want
in my life is simplicity,
and it's the one thing too
difficult for you to give to me.
- You're scared, you're scared
to have a different life
than our fucking parents and your sister!
- Sarabeth, I'm sorry.
- I have like 10,000
letters where you promise
you would never leave me,
and I promised you, too,
but I meant it.
- That's because you're
relentless, not because it's right.
- Shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up.
- I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- You don't even wanna keep the rocket?
- You keep it.
I gotta go.
You have to work tonight, like
you do every Saturday night.
I gotta go.
- I love you.
(Sarabeth weeps)
(people chattering)
(Sarabeth sighs)
- Come on, sweetheart, latkes!
These were your favorite
when you were a kid.
- Mom, it's getting late,
can we light the candles?
- Remember when Sarabeth was seven,
and she made those Hanukkah ornaments
to go on the school
Christmas tree? (laughs)
You can't stop laughing, Sarabeth.
You know what they say
about Jews and comedy.
It's in our blood.
Like Mel Brooks says,
"Make the big Aryan laugh
"and maybe he won't hit you
on the head with a big stick."
- Listen, when they come in, please,
pretend that you don't know anything.
Happy Hanukkah!
Is this for me?
- Happy Hanukkah.
(Isaac speaking foreign language)
- Howard, one, two, excellent.
I didn't tell them anything.
- Well, it's okay, we'll
give them a chance to hear it
right out of the horse's mouth.
Finally sold all the properties.
- He made a really good profit.
- (sighs) Then my brother took off,
and took off with everything.
He's a mess.
I've been trying to help
him change his life.
- We put everything into that business,
more than you know.
- So, we're going to move in here.
- Yeah.
- Temporarily, thankfully.
- It's wonderful, really.
We can spend time with our new grandchild,
get to visit with you, it's perfect.
Everybody's happy.
- Howie, that business,
it meant so much to you.
- Sometimes what's important changes.
- Listen, what's really
important, darling,
is your health, your happiness,
and the fact that this baby, whoa,
is on the way, so eat (speaking
foreign language), eat.
They're good, they're fresh, they're hot.
Becky, maybe you can
babysit for them, huh?
I mean, if you decide to
take next semester off.
- I'm not taking time off.
- I think it would do you good.
- Oh, that's right, I'm
gay because I'm overworked.
- Ooh, I don't wanna hear this.
- I know, that's why you only call
to talk to Sarabeth when
you know I'm not home.
- Do you know what my
mother would've done?
- What?
- My mother would've said Kaddish for you.
- Oh, that's wonderful.
- Do you know why?
- No, why?
- Because unlike you or me, she lived
according to the Torah,
and not just sometimes,
but every day, every minute of every day.
Now, I don't claim to be
the saint that she was,
but these traditions, they
enable us to survive, Becky.
I know, I know.
Something is lost in every generation,
but to what degree?
I never planned to condone
this kind of behavior.
- There's a Yiddish folk saying,
if you wanna give God a good
laugh, tell him your plans.
- [Ruthie] Very funny.
- In the words of Spinoza,
the secret to life
is that it stops.
- That's Kafka, Daddy, that's Kafka.
- Okay, the truth is
your father's very sick.
- Not very sick, Ruthie, a little sick.
- [Ruthie] You know that he
has trouble breathing, right?
Well, it's not because of
all your antics or my antics.
- Well, what is it then?
- An infection in the lungs.
- Are you surprised, after 35 years
of having to work at that printing press?
- I'm lucky that I breathe any air.
(Isaac speaking foreign language)
- But you're gonna be okay, right?
The doctors, they can help you, right?
- [Isaac] Of course, baby, of course.
- Daddy has to go for some
more tests with the doctors,
but you know Daddy, he is a strong man.
- I'm much stronger when I
have my whole family around me.
- Well, yeah, you're gonna
be here for the baby, right?
- My plan is to be around
for all your babies.
But what did I just say
about God and plans?
The light's going down,
let's light the candles
and remember this as a joyous occasion.
We have enough misery in our history.
On Hanukkah, we remember great miracles.
(graceful music)
(Isaac chants in foreign language)
(Isaac and Ruthie chant
in foreign language)
(graceful music)
- [Family] Amen.
- Thank you, everyone.
It's nice to hear your mother sing.
(graceful music)
Sara was sweet and liked to sing.
She had the nickname Sparrow.
But Beth, Beth was an
artist, just like you.
Always hard at work.
She used to like to play with clay.
She used to make clay children.
She always seemed so happy,
but the clay children
always seemed so sad.
The clay children were all destroyed,
just like the real children.
- Stop!
(Sarabeth sighs)
(energizing music)
- Stop shaking.
- Sorry.
- Are you nervous?
- I invited some gallery owners.
- Oh, they're gonna love it.
- I wish we could just stay home
til they're all done looking.
- What?
Baby, you are way too
talented and gorgeous
to shrink away from anyone.
- Let's just put my hair up.
- I always knew I'd be going
to things like this with you.
(Raquel chuckles)
- Yo, yo, yo woman of the hour!
You've got some kooky thoughts
swimming through that
head of yours, Sarabeth.
- [Charlotte] This is the kind of work
you have to go home and think about.
- Great job, I really mean it.
- Wow, I totally cannot
believe how much work
you have done since college.
I'm in shock.
- You're so talented.
- It's amazing.
- What's your favorite work?
- Remember when you won that poster award?
- And it's only the beginning.
Congratulations.
- Thanks.
- Oh my god, so, please,
please, tell us about it.
- Yeah, I have, trust me.
You know what, I'm gonna be right back.
- Congrats.
- Thank you.
(people chattering)
(Sarabeth sighs)
- Simon.
- I hope you don't mind.
I couldn't not come.
I tried to stay in the background.
- How are you?
- Good.
I'm good.
You look great.
Baby, this show is incredible.
I'm really proud of you.
- Thanks.
My dad's really sick.
- I just saw him.
He was dragging your cousins around.
He was gloating about you.
He looked good.
Your mother glared at me.
She looks good to.
(Sarabeth chuckles)
- How's Pennsylvania?
- Good.
I bought a boat.
- A boat?
- Yeah, I'm renting some
dock space on the lake.
- You bought a boat?
- Maybe when it gets nice
out, I'll take you for a ride.
- A boat.
- [Raquel] Hey, Simon.
- Hey.
- Thanks for coming.
Wanna come say hi to Mom and Dad?
- All right, I gotta go.
- I still think about the loft
room as your painting room.
Baby, I haven't done anything to it.
(people chattering)
(jazz music)
- Sara and Beth, (speaking
foreign language).
- [Raquel] Can you believe it?
- [Isaac] I'm speechless.
- [Howie] That's even harder to believe.
- Oh, Howard.
Darling, when did you do all this?
- Mostly after Hanukkah.
- You never wanted to listen,
but you always made Sara, Beth,
and my mother so proud in heaven.
- They would want you to
work things out with Becky.
- Everything with Becky's fine.
She has a few problems,
and we're standing by her.
- This is what we need to
get ourselves ready for?
Is that what you're trying to say?
- Yeah, if we're lucky and
Becky finds a nice Jewish girl.
(Ruthie speaking foreign language)
- Maybe we should be happy
there's a Chuppah, Ruthie.
At least there's a Chuppah.
(Ruthie snaps)
- I'm ecstatic.
Is that Simon Stanton you were talking to?
What does he want?
- He came to see the show.
- Really?
He should be so lucky
to get your autograph.
(jazz music)
- Mom, Dad, I want you to meet
my nice Jewish girlfriend Naomi.
- Hi.
- Hi, Naomi.
- Naomi is getting her PhD
in Comparative Religions.
Her father is a dentist,
and her mother is a teacher.
She has everything you
could possibly hope for
in a life-partner for me.
- Actually, she's missing
something pretty crucial.
- It's just love.
It's not really so strange.
- Naomi, how ironic, Naomi.
In the Book of Ruth, Ruth says
to her mother-in-law Naomi,
"Whither thou goest, I shall go.
"Thy land shall be my land."
- "And thy people, my people."
- Naomi, would you like to
come to the Passover Seder?
- I would love to.
My parents are in Florida.
- Well, then it's settled.
- I'm not so sure it's settled.
I may need more time, but, meanwhile,
you'll come, you'll eat.
Now, where's the bathroom?
- Well, Ma, the Progressive Women's room
is right over there,
and I think you qualify.
- Do they have toilets, or do I have
to straddle a urinal to prove my point?
(Sarabeth chuckles)
(jazz music)
- That was all so exciting.
- You were amazing, you sparkled in there.
- I'm sure if any gallery
owners did show up,
they would've loved you.
We'll buy another painting.
- Yeah, anybody got any money? (laughs)
Sorry, honey.
- So many of your friends came.
- I have a long way to
go before I'm great.
- But it's all so worth it.
It's so obvious.
- Daddy seemed okay, right?
- Honey, he's not going
anywhere for a long time,
so don't worry about it.
- You guys have both
your cars here, right?
Can I please borrow one?
I'll bring it back in the morning.
- [Raquel] Where you going?
It's almost midnight.
- Do you need a ride?
- No, I just need to think.
Sometimes I like to drive and think.
- Are you upset about Daddy?
- I just have some decisions to make.
- [Raquel] About Simon?
- [Becky] You're not
gonna go back to him now.
What about your painting?
- Look, it's late.
Why don't you wait til the morning,
then you'll make the right decision.
- No, I can't make any
decisions right now.
I just have to go, I just
have to get in the car and go,
I have to get out of here!
- Okay, okay.
Just drive carefully.
- Whatever decision makes you less sick
to your stomach is the right one.
(soft, emotional music)
(Sarabeth sniffles)
(dramatic, emotional music)
- [Sarabeth Voiceover]
If I am not for myself,
who will be for me?
But if I'm only for myself, what am I?
And if not now, when?
(dramatic, emotional music)
(upbeat, energizing music)
(funky, percussive music)