- YEOW-ZAH!
- OH!
- UGH!
- OW!
THIS IS  LMNOP NEWS
COMING TO YOU LIVE.
I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW,
WHAT'S YOUR TAKE ON
STEEL MAGNOLIAS, SIR?
CHICK FLICK.
THAT'S HARSH.
WOULD YOU RATHER HAVE SEEN
BORN ON THE FOURTH OF JULY?
NOT A CHANCE.
HE WIGS OUT WHENEVER
WE DRIVE PAST A HOSPITAL.
OH.
- AFRAID YOU'LL CATCH SOMETHING?
- NO.
MY GUY'S SENSITIVE--
IN THE HEART.
OH, I SEE.
YOU'RE A WUSS.
AHH!
EXCUSE ME!
HOW CAN YOU SET ME UP
WITH THAT DWEEB?
DON'T ASK ME.
I JUST MET HIM.
HE BEGGED ME TO HOOK YOU UP
WHEN YOU STOPPED BY THE STORE.
DIDN'T NANCY REAGAN
TEACH US TO JUST SAY NO?
GEEZ LOUISE, TUESDAY.
STOP BAGGIN' ON THE GUY.
HE'S CUTE.
THE CUTEST WASTOID EVER.
AHHH!
Wallace:
WHAT'S THE MALE
TO FEMALE RATIO
THAT BUYS TICKETS
FOR STEEL MAGNOLIAS?
- I'D SAY AH...
- SIXTY PERCENT?
HEY GUYS,
WHAT'S CRACKALACKIN'?!
SO, WHERE ARE
WE HEADED NEXT? HUH?
HOME.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
WOULD YOU WATCH THE ROAD?
SO...
HOW DO I KNOW
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO BAIL ON ME AGAIN?
WHAT?
HOW'RE YOU GUYS
DOING BACK THERE?
YOU KNOW IF,
LIFE ISN'T PERFECT?
LIFE DOESN'T
HAVE TO BE PERFECT.
AS LONG AS YOU BECOME
A RICHIE-FOOTBALL STAR
THEN NO WORRIES, MATE!
WHOA, WHOA!
SLOW DOWN, BARNEY!
RELAX...
I'M DRIVING WITH MY KNEES,
I CAN LOOK AT YOU,
A BEAUTIFUL GIRL,
AND I CAN DRIVE WITH MY KNEES.
LOOK HOW STRAIGHT I'M DRIVING.
- RIGHT?
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[CRASHING SOUND]
[CONTINUOUS BEEPING]
Woman's Voice:
THEN HE LEFT FOR WORK.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
HE JUST WALKED OUT.
THE DOOR BARELY SHUT BEHIND HIM
WHEN I THREW MY SHOE-- HARD.
JINKIES!
LEFT A SCUFF MARK.
HE DIDN'T HAVE A CLUE.
HOW CAN
HE BE SO OBLIVIOUS?
HOW COULD HE NOT SEE
HOW UPSET I WAS?
I SHOULD OF SAID,
"EVERYTHING IS  NOT FINE."
NOPE, PLEASE, LAMBY,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY IT.
YOU'VE TOLD ME
A MILLION TIMES.
RUDY IS NOT A MIND READER.
...IT WASN'T
RUDY'S FAULT.
IT WASN'T RUDY'S FAULT
I GOT CAUGHT OFF IN TRAFFIC.
AND IT WASN'T HIS FAULT
THAT ARCHIE GAVE ME A WRONG FILE
MAKING ME LOOK DUMB.
IT WASN'T RUDY'S FAULT
THAT WHEELCHAIR
APPEARED OUT OF NOWHERE
TRIPPING ME
AND LANDING ME ON A BEDPAN.
I DIDN'T TELL HIM
ABOUT ANY OF IT.
[MUFFLED VOICE]
I WONDER IF HE'LL NOTICE
THE SCUFF ON THE DOOR.
[GASPS]
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
WHERE...?
YOU'RE IN THE HOSPITAL,
LAMBY.
[MUFFLED VOICE]
YOU HAD A LITTLE ACCIDENT.
YOU'RE OKAY.
NO BROKEN BONES.
NO COURSE FOR ALARM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HOW LONG HAVE I BEEN HERE?
NINETEEN--
NINETEEN HOURS?
DAD MUST BE
A TOTAL SPAZZ.
YEAH.
WE REALLY NEED TO FIND HIM.
JOYCE,
COULD YOU FIND MR. WYATT--
AND A DOCTOR.
NOW.
[NERVOUS CHUCKLE]
HEY, WHAT'S YOUR DAMAGE?
I THOUGHT
YOU SAID I WAS OKAY.
YEAH,
YOU LOOK FINE TO ME.
HAVE I BEEN HERE
NINETEEN  DAYS?
UGH! I'M GOING
TO FLATTEN THAT WALLACE
LIKE A FRUIT ROLL UP.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY,
HYSTERICALLY]
WHY ARE YOU
ACTING ALL PSYCHO?
DON'T EVEN TELL ME
- IT'S BEEN NINETEEN WEEKS.
- NO,
IT HASN'T BEEN
NINETEEN WEEKS.
MONTHS?
WHO'S PRESIDENT?
WHAT'S THAT, LAMBY?
THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES.
- WHO IS IT?
- GEORGE BUSH.
OH, THANK GOD.
DAD.
GEEZ LOUISE,
YOU REALLY DID FREAK.
YOU HAVEN'T SLEPT.
N-NO, HONEY,
THESE LINES ARE NOT
FROM LACK OF SLEEP.
DAD, ARE YOU SICK?
I-- I AH...
JUST GOTTA FIND
THAT DOCTOR.
I, I'VE AGED.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU'VE AGED?
WHERE'S BEN?
WELL HONEY,
YOU DON'T...
YOU DON'T EXPECT HIM
TO SIT BY YOUR BEDSIDE
- 24/7, DO YOU?
- 24/7?
I-- WELL UM...
- HE'S PROBABLY AT WORK.
- WHAT TIME IS IT?
HIS SHIFT ENDS AT FOUR.
I DON'T THINK HE'S AT
ORANGE JULIUS ANYMORE.
WELL, THAT NEUROTIC NURSE
SAID HE WASN'T HURT.
HE DID BREAK HIS ARM.
AND AH, TUESDAY
WAS PRETTY BRUISED UP
AND SHE CUT HER LIP,
BUT THEY'RE BOTH
FINE NOW.
- WHAT ABOUT WALLACE?
- HUH.
AMAZINGLY HE WALKED AWAY
WITHOUT A SCRATCH.
YOU SEEM...
YOU,
YOU SEEM TO BE
JUST FINE.
OH, COME ON, DAD,
GIVE ME A BREAK.
MONICA,
YOU DON'T REALIZE
WHAT A MIRACLE THIS IS.
WE WERE TOLD
THAT IF A COMA PATIENT
DOENS'T GAIN CONSCIOUSNESS
WITHIN THE FIRST YEAR...
AFTER THAT,
THE WINDOW OF RECOVERY
- STARTS...
- WHERE'S MY RING?
WHERE'S MY RING?!
CALM DOWN, HONEY,
CALM DOWN, HONEY.
EVERYTHING IS OKAY.
WE...
HAVE A LOT
TO TALK ABOUT.
MUCH HAS HAPPENED
SINCE THE ACCIDENT.
YEAH? HOW MUCH
COULD POSSIBLY HAPPEN
IN NINETEEN YEARS?
[RINGING]
-  HELLO...
- BEN?
YOU'VE REACHED
RICK AND AMY LIVINGSTON.
-  WE'RE NOT AROUND...
- THE "LIVINGSTON'S"?
...WE'LL GET BACK TO YOU
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE...
PRAISE GOD.
EVEN LOOKING RIGHT AT YOU,
I CAN HARDLY BELIEVE IT.
ME OF LITTLE FAITH.
I CALLED MY MOM.
SHE WANTED
TO HOP ON THE NEXT PLANE
BUT GRETCHEN'S GOT THE FLUE
AND TOBY'S SOCCER GAME
IS SATURDAY.
THEY LIVE IN TENNESSEE NOW,
DID YOU KNOW?
WHO ARE YOU?
AUNT MONICA.
IT'S ME, JORDAN.
WHERE'S MY DAD?
WOULD YOU
LIKE SOME WATER?
OR WOULD YOU LIKE--
I'D LIKE YOU
TO TELL ME ABOUT BEN.
YOU REMEMBER HIM,
YOUR FUTURE SON?
YES,
I REMEMBER HIM.
SO, HE DUMPED
THE COMA GIRL.
- NO, NO, NO...
- NO?
IT WASN'T LIKE THAT.
BEN LOVED YOU.
BUT HE WAS A YOUNG MAN
WITH HIS ENTIRE LIFE
AHEAD OF HIM.
NOBODY COULD EXPECT HIM--
-- EXPECT HIM
TO SIT BY MY BEDSIDE
NINETEEN YEARS-- 24/7?
THAT'S BOGUS!
BEN IS STRONG AND BRAVE!
HE WOULDN'T MOTOR ON ME!
SOMETIMES...
PEOPLE SURPRISE US...
EVEN SURPRISE THEMSELVES
AT A TIME OF CRISIS.
SOMETIMES...
THEY JUST CRUMBLE.
♪ HAVE YOU SEEN ♪
♪ MY SMILE? ♪
♪ I HEAR IT'S BEEN GONE ♪
♪ FOR A WHILE ♪
♪ I'M SO CONFUSED ♪
♪ LIKE AN ABANDONED CHILD ♪
♪ I WANT TO KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT'S LEADING YOU ♪
♪ I BELIEVE SO STRONG ♪
♪ OH, TELL ME ♪
♪ I WANT TO KNOW ♪
♪ WHETHER DREAMS COME TRUE ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'VE BEEN DREAMING ♪
♪ FOR SO LONG ♪
♪ OH, I HAVE BEEN ♪
♪ DREAMING SO LONG ♪♪
- DAD!
- WHAT IS IT?
AH--
IS SOMETHING HURT?
I WANT TO GO.
OH, YOU--
YOU GOT IT, HUN.
GO WHERE?
TO SKYLINE HIGH'S
20 YEAR REUNION.
OH. AH...
HONEY, I,
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S--
WHY?
I'LL BE ABLE TO SEE...
EVERYBODY.
- I'M GOING.
- I, I DON'T THINK THAT--
I CAN WEAR THAT BRAND-NEW
GOLD LAME DRESS
I GOT FOR
THE ENGAGEMENT PARTY.
YOU GOT IT, HUN.
♪♪
♪ IT'S BEEN SO LONG ♪
♪ I CAN'T REMEMBER ♪
♪ WHAT IT'S LIKE ♪
♪ SHOULDA SEEN
RIGHT THROUGH YOUR EYES ♪
♪ YOUR DISGUISE ♪
♪ I FELL FOR YOU
AND AT A TIME ♪
♪ I DIDN'T KNOW BETTER ♪
♪ HEAD OVER HEALS ♪
♪ PARTNERS IN CRIME ♪
♪ I SHOULDA KNOW BETTER ♪
♪♪
♪ I WAS WAITING FOR A SIGN ♪
♪ HAVING TO SIGN
THE DOTTED LINE ♪
♪ WASN'T LIKE
I WAS SCOPING OFF
THE DEEP END ♪
♪ I DIDN'T
NEED TO PLEAD THE TRUTH ♪
WANT TO HOLD YOU SO ♪
♪ I JUST WANTED TO SEE YOU
OFF THE WEEKEND ♪
♪ WOULD YOU DECIDE ♪
♪ WE'RE LIKE DAY AND NIGHT ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ YOU DECIDE
THIS IS DO AND DIE ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪♪
RICHARD!
♪ [DANCE MUSIC PLAYING] ♪
SHOULD I AH,
SHOW YOU HOW TO USE
THAT PHONE AGAIN?
NO, I GOT IT.
OKAY.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO GO IN WITH YOU?
OKAY.
DUMB IDEA.
WHAT IF HE'S NOT HERE?
WHAT IF HE IS HERE?
YOU'LL BE FINE.
[EXHALES]
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
- EXCUSE ME.
- AH-- OH...
SORRY TO USE
MY UPPER-CASE VOICE
BUT I COULDN'T HEAR
A THING IN THERE.
TUESDAY, HEY.
OH, MY GOSH.
YOU'RE OLD.
MONICA?
I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
WHOA,
YOU'RE NOT DEAD.
DEAD?
DEAD.
AS IN SIX FEET UNDER--
FOR THE PAST EIGHTEEN YEARS?
OKAY.
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY! ALL RIGHT!
STOP ACTING LIKE A MOM!
OKAY!
MOM! YES!
WOULD YOU MIND
IF I TAKE A PICTURE
FOR MY MOM?
- SURE.
- SHE'LL FLIP.
- OKAY.
- WHERE'S THE CAMERA?
OH, MY GOSH!
YOU HAVE A CAMERA
IN YOUR PHONE?!
WHAT ARE YOU,
A SPY?
SMILE.
[CAMERA CLICKS]
OH, BABE,
I'M, I'M SO SORRY.
I WAS SO HOPEFUL
THAT YOU WOULD WAKE UP
BUT AFTER A YEAR...
THEY SAID
IF YOU DIDN'T COME OUT
OF IT BY THEN...
...THE WINDOW FOR RECOVERY
BEGINS TO CLOSE.
I KNOW.
I'VE BEEN TOLD.
I DIDN'T
WANT TO SEE YOU DIE.
I COULDN'T.
I TOLD MYSELF
THAT IF
YOU CAME OUT OF IT,
YOU'D CALL ME.
BUT NOW I SEE
WHY YOU DIDN'T.
I'M A HORRIBLE FRIEND.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
THEN YOU FORGIVE ME?
WE ARE RAD,
WE ARE GREAT--
Together:
WE'RE THE CLASS OF '88.
- GAG ME.
[GAGGING NOISE]
[LAUGHING]
SO, WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN UP TO
FOR THE PAST UMPTEEN YEARS?
UM...
NOT MUCH.
YOU LOOK MARVELOUS.
WHAT'S YOUR SECRET?
AH,
WHOLE LOT OF SLEEP
AND NO SUNSHINE.
[LAUGHS]
UM...
SO, IS OUR
THIRD  AMIGO HERE?
- WHAT?
- AREN'T-AREN'T--ER--
WEREN'T WE THE THREE  AMIGOS?
YOU KNOW,
YOU, AND ME, AND UM...
OH. BEN.
BEN HUDSON.
YEAH, HE'S,
HE'S INSIDE.
WHOA, WHOA, BABE,
ARE YOU OKAY?
UM-HM.
THAT'S BOOZE.
DIDN'T THEY CARD YOU?
PSYCH.
COME ON.
NO, YOU, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
FOR REALS?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO PULL
A CRISS ANGEL AND DISAPPEAR?
I'M SO SURE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHO SHE IS.
[LAUGHING]
OKAY.
OKAY, MONICA,
YOU CAN DO THIS.
HE'S RIGHT INSIDE THAT DOOR.
NOT.
MONICA?
IT IS YOU.
I SAW YOU FROM INSIDE
AND I THOUGHT
I WAS HALLUCINATING.
WOW, LOOK AT YOU.
YOU LOOK...
GNARLY?
AH...
SUPER GNARLY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M SO SORRY.
IF I COULD GO BACK
AND CHANGE THINGS, I--
YOU KNOW,
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE JUST
LET BYGONES BE BYGONES?
SERIOUSLY.
I'D LIKE THAT.
I'D LIKE THAT A LOT.
[CHUCKLES]
SO...
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN
UP TO THESE DAYS?
UM, I JUST AH...
AH,
FINISHED A POSITION
THAT I HELD FOR
A REALLY LONG TIME.
YOU KNOW,
IT WAS RATHER CONFINING.
AND IN THE MEANTIME,
I'M STAYING WITH DAD.
HOW IS HE?
GREAT.
HE'S GREAT.
- WHAT IS IT THAT YOU DO?
- I'M A REALTOR.
HOW BORING.
I'M SORRY.
I, NO, I DIDN'T MEAN,
- UM...
- NO, NO.
IT'S OKAY.
I THINK I REMEMBER
SOMEBODY ONCE BOASTING
THAT THEY WOULD NEVER
TAKE OVER THE FAMILY JOB.
BUT I GOT TO SAY
THAT IT GREW ON ME.
AND, MAYBE IT'LL
DO THE SAME FOR MY SON.
SON?
YOU HAVE A SON?
MM-HM. SETH.
HE'S FIFTEEN.
OH, WHOA...
UM,
SORRY I'M FINE.
I'M JUST...
- HAVE YOU EATEN ANYTHING?
- NO, I'M FINE.
UM, SO,
WHAT'S HE LIKE?
SETH...
TYPICAL TEENAGER.
HE LIKES
"MYSPACE", "YOUTUBE",
"ANNE HATHAWAY".
THAT'S SO FREAKY.
UM...
WELL, I SHOULD LET YOU
GET BACK INSIDE TO YOUR WIFE.
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD?
WE'RE NOT MARRIED ANYMORE.
YOU REALLY SHOULD
EAT SOMETHING.
THEY HAVE
A GREAT SPREAD UP THERE.
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
THEY HAVE
GOAT CHEESE AND SALMON
AND SOME KIND OF PATE--
I THINK IT'S GOOSE.
BARF ME OUT.
UM...
HEY, DO YOU
WANT TO GO TO THE TACO BELL
DOWN THE STREET?
TACO BELL?
YOU DON'T HANG OUT
IN THE OLD NEIGHBORHOOD
MUCH ANYMORE, DO YOU?
IT'S A STARBUCKS NOW.
A WHAT?
A STARBUCKS.
COFFEE.
THEY USE THAT
ENTIRE SPACE FOR COFFEE?
YEAH, MOSTLY.
ALL RIGHT, WELL THEN,
HOW ABOUT SOME COFFEE?
I WOULD LOVE TO...
BUT I REALLY SHOULD
GET BACK INSIDE
AND FINISH CATCHING UP
WITH SOME OLD FRIENDS
AND THEN I SHOULD
PROBABLY GET HOME
AND SEE HOW MUCH TROUBLE
THAT SETH'S GOTTEN INTO.
HOW'S YOUR MOM?
DID YOU GET A CHANCE
TO CHECK YOUR ORGANIZER?
I ALREADY TOLD YOU,
THE LAST WEEK IN JULY
SHOULD BE FINE.
OKAY, YOU NEED
TO EITHER COMMIT TO THIS
OR BE STRAIGHT WITH ME.
SETH WANTS
TO SPEND THE WEEK A YOU,
BUT I'M NOT GOING
TO SET IT UP
AND HAVE HIM
DISAPPOINTED AGAIN.
NO NEED
TO THROW A MANTRUM.
I WILL
CALL YOU NEXT WEEK.
OKAY?
FINE.
MONICA, IT WAS NICE
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
OH, AND TELL SETH
I LOVE HIM.
HE DIDN'T TELL YOU?
YOU SKANK.
BABE, WAIT.
MONICA!
SO, ARE YOU READY
TO TALK ABOUT IT NOW?
I GUESS NOT.
THEY THINK
I HAVE ROCKS FOR BRAINS.
HONEY,
WHY DON'T YOU TELL THEM
WHERE YOU'VE BEEN?
I MEAN, YOU'RE
- A LIVING MIRACLE.
- THEY THOUGHT I WAS DEAD.
I SHOULD OF
JUST LEFT IT THAT WAY.
CAN WE HAVE
MARGE OVER FOR DINNER?
MARGE?
BEN'S MOM?
SHE WAS GOING TO BE
MY MOM, TOO.
SURE HUN.
I'LL-I'LL CHECK TO SEE
IF SHE'S STILL IN THE AREA.
YOU MEAN, SHE...
I JUST THOUGHT, I MEAN,
I CAN SORT OF UNDERSTAND
WHY BEN WOULD KIRK OUT,
BUT I FIGURED
MARGE WOULD STILL BE
IN THE PICTURE.
I THINK
SHE WAS ASHAMED.
I WOULD HAVE BEEN
IF BEN HAD BEEN MY SON.
YOU SAID
YOU DIDN'T BLAME HIM.
I DIDN'T.
HE WAS
SO GRIEF-STRICKEN
HE EVEN...
DISAPPEARED FOR A WHILE.
- DISAPPEARED?
- MM.
HE EVENTUALLY TURNED UP,
BUT HE COULDN'T FACE ME.
I HAD TO GIVE TUESDAY
THE RING TO RETURN.
[SCOFFS]
AND SHE INTERCEPTED IT
FOR HERSELF.
DIDN'T YOU KNOW?
THEY GOT MARRIED.
THEY HAVE A KID.
I'M SORRY, HUN.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
TUESDAY WAS A GOOD FRIEND.
SO WAS WALLACE.
WALLACE?
I BARELY EVEN KNOW HIM--
KNEW HIM.
YEAH, HE SHOWED UP
AT YOUR HOSPITAL ROOM
JUST ABOUT
EVERY MONDAY NIGHT FOR...
LEAST TWO
OR THREE YEARS.
WHAT?
HE BROUGHT
THAT PICTURE.
SO, THE LOVE
OF MY LIFE DISAPPEARS
AND A SALES REP
FOR MEN'S SHOES
BECOMES MY BEST BUD.
NOW YOU CAN IMAGINE
THE GUILT HE MUST'VE FELT
HAVING PUT YOU THERE.
WELL, HE SHOULD.
I TOLD HIM
I FORGAVE HIM.
BUT...
HE STILL
HAS TO LIVE WITH IT.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
COME IN.
YOU LOOK NICE.
ARE YOU GOING OUT?
YEP.
HOW WAS THE REUNION?
FINE.
PAPA JACK MENTIONED
BEN WAS THERE.
YEP.
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU KNOW,
I'M NOT REALLY COMFORTABLE
TALKING TO YOU ABOUT THIS.
WHY, BECAUSE YOU
THINK OF ME AS A CHILD?
MENTALLY,
I'M OLDER THAN YOU ARE.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU
MAKE A FOOL OUT OF YOURSELF
OVER THAT CREEP.
THAT  CREEP
HELD MY WORLD TOGETHER
WHEN YOUR GRANDMOTHER
PASSED AWAY!
THAT  CREEP AND I
WERE IN THE MIDDLE
OF PLANNING OUR WEDDING
LESS THAN TWO WEEKS AGO!
THAT  CREEP
WAS GOING TO GROW
OLD WITH ME!
AND NOW, HE'S GONE,
HE'S OUT OF MY LIFE,
NO BREAK UP, NO GOODBYE,
- NO NOTHIN'!
- SO YOU NEED CLOSURE.
I NEED THE CAR.
DAD!
CAN I BORROW THE CAR?
OH, HONEY,
YOU DON'T HAVE A LICENSE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I JUST GOT IT...
TWENTY-ONE YEARS AGO.
- I'LL TAKE YOU.
- NO, IT'S FINE.
I'LL RIDE MY BIKE.
I AM NOT SURE
YOU ARE STRONG ENOUGH.
I'M NOT GOING FAR.
WELL, HERE.
NOW,
CALL ME IF YOU--
LATER.
- GOOD MORNING.
- HI. IS BEN HERE?
NO, I'M SORRY.
OH.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO WAIT.
OR I CAN TAKE A MESSAGE.
NO. NO MESSAGE.
THANKS.
♪ OUTSIDE ♪
♪ MY WINDOW ♪
♪ I'M SEARCHING ♪
♪ I'M WAITING FOR YOU ♪
- OH!
- OH, I'M SO SORRY.
MONICA?
NICE PLAY, MONTANA.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'VE SURVIVED WORSE.
OH, YOU'RE A YUPPIE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
OH, I WAS JUST
UM, SHOPPING
AND, UM...
JUST GETTING SOME FRESH AIR,
ENJOYING THE BLUE SKY AND...
I THINK I'LL JOIN YOU.
ELISE, I'M GOING TO GO GET
SOME FRESH AIR, BLUE SKY.
NOT TOO MUCH,
I HOPE.
YOU HAVE A MEETING
IN SEVEN MINUTES.
CHECK.
OH, UM,
I BOUGHT SOMETHING
FOR SETH.
YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO DO THAT.
YEAH, WELL,
I SAW IT AND THOUGHT...
"HISTORIC STRATFORD-ON-AVON."
IT'S VERY NICE OF YOU.
I HOPE
HE DOESN'T ALREADY
HAVE IT.
PRETTY SURE HE DOESN'T.
WELL,
IT HAS THIS SCHEET CHAPTER
ON WILL
AND ANNE'S COURTSHIP.
I COULD
HARDLY PUT IT DOWN.
- WILL AND ANNE?
- YEAH,
WILLIAM SHAKESPEARE
AND ANNE HATHAWAY.
DIDN'T YOU SAY
SETH WAS INTO ANNE HATHAWAY?
OH,
I MEANT THE ACTRESS
ANNE HATHAWAY.
- THE DEVIL WEARS PRADA...
- OH, RIGHT.
- THAT ANNE HATHAWAY.
-  GET SMART?
OH, I'M SORRY.
I'M SUCH A BIMBETTE.
OH, NO, NO,
HE'S GOING TO READ IT.
BE A GOOD BREAK
FROM HIS COMPUTER.
"YESTERDAY'S
TREASURE TROVE"!
WHEN DID THEY
STOP SELLING OLD STUFF?
OH, NO WAY!
LOOK! IT'S STILL HERE!
THE LAST TIME WE WERE HERE
YOU PICKED ME A POM-POM FLOWER
OFF THAT BUSH.
HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY REMEMBER THAT?
I'M AN ELEPHANT.
- [CELL PHONE RINGS]
- OH,
THERE'S ELISE,
RIGHT ON CUE.
YEP, THE MEETING'S
ABOUT TO START.
- HOW DO YOU KNOW?
- HER TEXT.
HER WHAT?
HER TEXT.
NOT A REAL BIG FAN
OF MODERN TECHNOLOGY,
- ARE YOU?
- NO.
OH, THAT'S RAD!
LOOK AT THAT!
I BET
YOU DON'T REMEMBER
WHAT YOU DID
- WITH THAT PURPLE FLOWER.
- YEAH, I PRESSED IT
IN THE "COMPLETE WORKS
OF SHAKESPEARE".
AS IN, WILL AND ANNE?
- WHAT'S WITH THE BIG GRILL?
- NOTHIN'.
WHAT?
NO COME ON, TELL ME.
TELL ME.
JUST KINDA...
I DON'T KNOW,
IT'S LIKE...
TIME TURNED BACK
TWENTY YEARS.
SHUT UP!
YOU FEEL IT, TOO?
BEN, I NEED
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
UM, I ACTUALLY
ONLY JUST RECENTLY WOKE--
- [CELL PHONE RINGING]
- OH, I'M SORRY.
YOU JUST WHAT?
ONLY RECENTLY...
NOTHING.
THEY'RE WAITING FOR YOU.
MM, ACTUALLY,
IT'S ALREADY STARTED.
ELISE, SHE RUNS
A PRETTY TIGHT SHIP.
SHE STEPPED IN
WHEN EVERYTHING
SPUN INTO CHAOS
AFTER MOM DIED.
NEXT TIME,
I'LL PICK YOU
A FRESH FLOWER.
THEY WERE BEING
TOSSED ABOUT IN A LITTLE BOAT
IN THE MIDDLE
OF A MERCILESS STORM
AND JESUS
IS SOUND ASLEEP.
"THE DISCIPLES
WENT AND WOKE HIM UP.
"AND JESUS GOT UP
AND REBUKED THE WIND
AND THE RAGING WATERS,
AND ALL WAS CALM."
THAT IS
A PERFECT EXAMPLE
OF FAITH AND TRUST.
TO BE
SO COMPLETELY AT PEACE--
THAT YOU CAN
JUST SNOOZE RIGHT ON
THROUGH THE STORM.
IT SOUNDS LIKE
SOMEONE I KNOW.
WAS THAT COMMENT
DIRECTED AT ME?
WHAT?
- THE "SNOOZING" COMMENT.
- NO, AUNT MONICA, IT WASN'T.
SORRY, I'LL TRY
TO BE MORE SENSITIVE
WHEN I MENTION "SLEEP"
IN THE FUTURE.
PAPA JACK
TOLD ME ABOUT BEN'S MOTHER.
I'M SORRY.
I REMEMBER HER
AS BEING A VERY NICE LADY.
AND I REALLY DID
THINK HER SON WAS A PRINCE.
WHEN THE DOCTORS
COULDN'T DO ANYTHING FOR YOU,
I THOUGHT
YOU WERE IN A DEEP,
MAGICAL SLEEP--
LIKE A STORYBOOK PRINCESS.
BUT I WASN'T WORRIED.
I HAD NO DOUBT
THAT UNCLE BEN WOULD COME
GALLOPING INTO YOUR ROOM
ON A WHITE STALLION,
KNEEL BESIDE YOU,
AND WAKEN YOU
WITH LOVES TRUE KISS.
HE CAME, ALL RIGHT.
HE EVEN KISSED YOU.
LOVE'S TRUE KISS GOODBYE.
Woman's Voice:
HELLO, CARE BEAR.
JENNY.
- YOU LOOK LIKE...
- ONE OF THE  GOLDEN GIRLS?
JUST LIKE MOM.
OH.
BEN BROUGHT ME HERE
THE NIGHT HIS TEAM
CREAMED THE PANTHERS.
SO WHAT
SOUNDS GOOD FOR DINNER?
I'M COOKING.
I GAVE HIM THE NEW
"MILLIE VANILLI" ALBUM.
I HAVE A GREAT RECIPE
FOR LINGUINI AND MUSHROOMS.
BEN LOVES "MILLI VANILLI".
I CAN ADD
LOTS OF CHEESE
IF IT SOUNDS
TOO GROWN UP
FOR YOUR TASTE.
I DO THAT
FOR GRETCH AND TOBY.
YOU KNOW,
PRETENDING HE DOESN'T EXIST
DOESN'T MAKE IT TRUE.
OH, YEAH? WELL,
IT DID FOR MANY YEARS.
JENNY,
PUT YOURSELF IN HIS SHOES.
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY.
WHAT IF YOU
SUDDENLY FOUND YOURSELF
ENGAGED TO A VEGETABLE?
ENGAGED.
THAT MEANS I MADE
A COMMITMENT.
NOT TO A VEGETABLE.
I JUST
HATE TO SEE YOU REGRET.
I MEAN,
IT MAY BE A  GOOD THING
YOU DIDN'T MARRY BEN.
ANY HARDSHIP
OR CRISIS TO COME ALONG
WOULD'VE
CAUSE BEN TO...
SPLIT?
OR IT COULD'VE BEEN ME.
I BROKE UP WITH BEN
RIGHT AFTER GRADUATION.
WHAT?!
OUR CLASS WAS LIKE ALL AMPED UP
WITH "LIFE IS JUST BEGINNING!"
AND I JUST THOUGHT, LIKE,
A FRESH START WOULD BE WAY COOL
AFTER THIS THREE YEAR
EXCLUSIVE RELATIONSHIP.
SO...
HE WAS SO HURT.
BUT HE JUST SAID,
"I WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY."
I WAS A DITZ, THOUGH.
A MAJOR DITZ.
'CAUSE I WAS
SO NOT HAPPY WITHOUT HIM.
AND AFTER JUST TWO WEEKS
I WENT BACK TO HIM.
AND HE JUST
PUT HIS ARMS AROUND ME...
AND DIDN'T SAY A WORD.
THAT'S LOVE, JENNY.
IF HE LOVED YOU SO MUCH,
WHY DIDN'T
HE CONTACT DAD LATER ON,
JUST TO SEE
HOW YOU WERE DOING?
EVERYBODY SEEMS TO ASSUME
THAT I EITHER, LIKE, WOKE UP
OR DIED A LONG TIME AGO.
BUT HE DID APOLOGIZE
AT THE REUNION.
HOW BIG OF HIM.
AUNT MONICA!
HAVE YOU
TALKED TO ANTHONY LATELY?
NO, NOT FOR AGES.
I HOPE THE REASON
YOU'RE NOT MARRIED BY NOW
ISN'T BECAUSE OF BEN.
BEN? AH, NO,
BEN IS NOT RESPONSIBLE
FOR MY STATUS
AS AN OLD MAID.
I STILL BELIEVE THERE ARE
A FEW PRINCE CHARMINGS OUT THERE
WHO WOULDN'T
GALLOP OFF INTO THE SUNSET
WHILE I LAY IN ICU.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
AH, TELL YOU WHAT?
THAT MY FINGERS
STILL SMELLED LIKE
POPCORN BUTTER
WHEN BEN GALLOPED
OFF INTO THE SUNSET.
I'M GOING
TO GO GET THE LINGUINI.
THIS ISN'T HAPPENING.
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
THIS IS JUST A BAD DREAM
AND I'M GOING TO WAKE UP
- ANY MINUTE NOW.
- YOU DID WAKE UP.
THEN IT'S ALL
JUST A JOKE, RIGHT?
ANY MINUTE NOW
GOD'S GOING TO COME DOWN
AND SAY "PSYCH!"
OR ED MCMAHON'S
GOING TO KNOCK ON
THE FRONT DOOR
AND GIVE ME A CHECK
SO I HIRE DOC BROWN
TO BUILD ME A TIME MACHINE
OUT OF A DELOREAN
AND I CAN
GO BACK TO 1989,
AND ALL WILL BE WELL
IN MY WORLD!
THIS IS SO UNFAIR!
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING TO ME?!
EVERYTHING'S GONE!
MY, MY FUTURE,
MY YOUTH, MY MARRIAGE,
MY CHILDREN--
- EVERYTHING IS GONE!
- IT COULD HAVE BEEN WORSE.
OH, YEAH?
HOW COULD IT POSSIBLY
BE ANY WORSE?!
YOU COULD'VE
EMERGED FROM THAT COMA
WITH SEVERE BRAIN DAMAGE--
OR NOT EMERGED AT ALL.
THAT WOULD
NOT BE WORSE.
I'M SORRY, DAD.
BUT INSTEAD OF "PRAISING GOD"
FOR MY MIRACULOUS RECOVERY,
WHY DON'T YOU
GRILL HIM ON THE FACT
HE LEFT ME IN LIMBO
FOR NINETEEN YEARS?!
I MEAN, COME ON!
BE REAL!
OH. OH, I GET IT.
I'M SURE THE TWO OF YOU
SEE SOME GREATER GOOD IN THIS,
SAME AS JENNY,
RIGHT?
LIKE, "PRAISE GOD,
HE DIDN'T LET MONICA
MARRY THAT WUSS."
PRAISE GOD THAT I SLEPT
THROUGH NEARLY TWO DECADES
OF WHAT-WOULD-HAVE-BEEN
A MISERABLE MARRIAGE!
WELL I AGREE!
PRAISE GOD MY EYES ARE OPEN,
I SEE THE LIGHT,
I SEE BEN'S A CREEP,
AND I DON'T EVER
WANT TO SEE HIM AGAIN!
EVER!
[DOORBELL RINGS]
AH, YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO BELIEVE THIS.
IT'S HIM.
HIM? BEN?
WELL, DON'T JUST STAND THERE!
LET HIM IN BEFORE HE LEAVES!
NO, WAIT!
I'M FREDDY KRUEGER SCARY.
COME ON, DAD.
JUST LET HIM IN.
DAD,
JUST STAY BACK HERE.
JUST GO, GO!
HI, BEN.
JORDAN?
YOU'RE SO TALL.
THAT TENDS TO HAPPEN.
IS UM...
IS YOUR
AUNT MONICA HERE?
YES, SHE IS.
COME IN.
- NO WHITE STALLION?
- EXCUSE ME?
AUNT MONICA,
BEN'S HERE.
HEY, MONICA.
I WANTED TO SEE
IF YOU WANTED TO GO
TO STARBUCKS.
I SEEM TO REMEMBER
TAKING A RAIN CHECK
AT THE REUNION.
AH, NO, ACTUALLY,
YOU DIDN'T.
OKAY. WELL,
DO YOU WANT TO GO--
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
ACTUALLY, I'VE BEEN
CONCERNED ABOUT YOU.
HA, HA!
YOU CONCERNED
ABOUT  ME?
AS IF!
I THINK THERE
IS PROBABLY SOMETHING
I SHOULD
BE DOING ELSEWHERE.
MAYBE I SHOULD, UH...
I'M GOING TO GO.
YOU KNOW,
I DON'T WANT TO GO,
MONICA.
YOU DON'T?
NO, I DON'T.
I CAME HERE ON A MISSION
AND I PROMISED MYSELF
I WOULDN'T CHICKEN OUT.
SIT DOWN.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
HOW TO SAY THIS.
JUST SAY IT.
THERE'S A RUMOR GOING AROUND
THAT YOU WERE IN A CONVENT.
YEAH...
AH, COME AGAIN?
WELL, YOU MENTIONED
IN YOUR LAST POSITION
YOU WERE "CONFINED".
AND YOU JUST SEEM--
SHELTERED
FROM THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
SO YOU PUT
TWO AND TWO TOGETHER.
YOU ARE TOTALLY WARPED.
WHO IS MONICA LEWINSKY?
AN ANSWER ON  JEOPARD?
- WHAT IS "Y2K"?
- THIS IS BOGUS.
- DESERT STORM?
- MAJORLY BOGUS.
WHO'S JOHNNY COCHRAN?
- DOLLY THE SHEEP?
- BEYOND BOGUS.
SEPTEMBER 11th?
YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW,
DO YOU?
SO WHAT IF
I HAVE BEEN IN A CONVENT?
WHAT'S IT TO YOU?
- WELL, I...
- WELL,  YOU?
I WAS CONCERNED
THAT MAYBE I WAS THE REASON
THAT YOU WERE THERE.
OH. OH. OKAY!
OF COURSE, BEN!
YOU RUINED ME
FOR ALL OTHER MEN.
- MONICA--
- [DOORBELL RINGS]
- MONICA!
- GOODBYE, BEN.
THANK YOU
FOR YOUR CONCERN.
I'D REALLY LIKE
TO TALK ABOUT THIS.
HELLO, LAMBY! IT'S ME.
ROSA FROM THE OFFICE.
SISTER ROSA
FROM THE CONVENT.
HUH?
BEN, YOU BETTER GO.
ROSA AND I
HAVE NUN STUFF TO DO,
LIKE ALL THESE
"HAIL ROSARIES"
BEFORE SUNDOWN.
MONICA!
AND I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO DO DOUBLES
FOR LETTING
A MAN IN THE HOUSE!
UGH!
I'M SO OVER HIM!
- YAY!
- [HEAVY SIGH]
SO, SO YOU HAVE NEWS
FROM THE HOSPITAL?
OH, YES, YES.
IT'S OFFICIAL.
JOYCE AND THAT SURFER
GOT ENGAGED.
COWABUNGA!
- AH, WHAT ABOUT ME?
- WHAT ABOUT YOU, LAMBY?
WELL,
DON'T YOU HAVE SOME NEWS
FROM MY DOCTORS?
OH, NO, NO.
I'M SORRY TO SCARE YOU.
YOU'RE FINE.
I'VE COME TO VISIT.
OH. OH, WELL,
AREN'T YOU NICE.
WE'VE ONLY
TALKED A COUPLE OF TIMES.
LAMBY,
WE'VE BEEN FRIENDS
FOR ELEVEN YEARS.
OH.
THAT PEEK-A-BOO HAIRSTYLE
WAS QUITE THE RAGE BACK THEN.
HOW BOSS.
THAT'S YOU
CELEBRATING THE MILLENNIUM.
GOOD TIMES.
PUNKY.
YOU WON'T SAY ANYTHING,
WILL YOU?
I'LL GET IN TROUBLE
FOR LETTING HER IN.
YOUR SECRET'S
SAFE WITH ME.
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN GOOD
AT KEEPING SECRETS.
HAH! GO FIGURE.
LIKE THAT DAY
I DECIDED TO LEAVE RUDY.
OH, LAMBY,
YOU'VE GOT A CHIPPED NAIL.
OH-- OH, UH...
RUDY HAD PROMISED ME
ON OUR FIRST DATE
HE WANTED KIDS.
THEN,
AFTER TWO YEARS OF MARRIAGE,
HE CONFESSED HE DIDN'T--
-  EVER.
- OH, THAT--
HE KNEW
THAT WOULD DEVASTATE ME.
- MY--
- NOW I HELD MY HEAD HIGH
AS I BATHED YOU,
QUITE PLEASED WITH MYSELF.
BUT LATER,
AS I WAS PUTTING YOUR LEGS
IN THE BLOOD
CIRCULATION MACHINE,
I FOUND MYSELF
GIVING YOU A SECOND BATH--
A SALTY BATH.
MY TEARS
WERE SPILLING
ALL OVER YOU.
JINKIES,
I WAS A MESS.
I SAT DOWN BESIDE YOU
AND I SAID,
"LAMBY,
WHAT SHOULD I DO?"
"TELL ME
IF I SHOULD LEAVE RUDY,
TELL ME."
AND YOU DIDN'T SAY A WORD.
SO I TOOK A DEEP BREATH,
WENT TO  ME CAR
AND DROVE HOME.
I HOPE
I ADVISED YOU WELL.
TODAY, RUDY AND I HAVE
TWO LOVELY LITTLE DAUGHTERS,
LISA AND JOSEY--
WHO JUST HAPPEN TO BE
THEIR DADDY'S PRIDE AND JOY.
Monica:
THANK YOU FOR THE FLOWERS.
Rosa:
IT'S THE USUAL "JOEL" VASE.
EVERY WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON,
A VASE A WILD FLOWERS
GETS DROPPED OFF FOR YOU.
EVERY WEDNESDAY
SINCE WHEN?
AT LEAST ELEVEN YEARS
THAT I KNOW OF.
I DON'T KNOW ANY "JOEL".
THE CARD ATTACHED IS A VERSE
FROM THE BOOK OF JOEL--
YOU KNOW,
FROM THE BIBLE?
IT'S ALWAYS THE SAME.
"SO I WILL
RESTORE TO YOU THE YEARS
"THAT THE SWARMING LOCUST
HAS EATEN,
"THE CRAWLING LOCUST,
THE CONSUMING LOCUST,
AND THE CHEWING LOCUST."
IT'S A LITTLE HITCHCOCKIAN.
BUT THE THOUGHT IS NICE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
[HEAVY SIGH]
SEVEN HUNDRED
AND TWENTY-THREE CHANNELS
AND NOTHIN' TO WATCH.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I KNOW YOU HATE ME,
BUT JUST HEAR ME OUT.
NO--
- MONICA--
- I MEAN,
NO, I DON'T  HATE YOU.
YOU DON'T?
WHOA...
DID I JUST
STEP THROUGH A TIME WARP?
I JUST DON'T GET HOW YOU CAN
MARRY THE CREEP AFTER--
LOVE IS BLIND, MONICA.
I'VE PAID THE PRICE
FOR MY STUPIDITY
AND MY BETRAYAL TO YOU.
- IS HE SEEING ANYONE?
-  I DON'T THINK SO.
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU AREN'T INTERESTED IN...
NO, DON'T BE AN AIRHEAD!
I HATE HIM!
I HATE HIM  SO MUCH!
HEY, DO YOU
WANT TO PRANK CALL HIM?
BOO THAT.
HE'D SEE THE CALLER I.D.
OH. HM.
YOU WANT TO GO
EGG HIS CAR?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
TWENTY-THREE SKIDOO.
SO THIS IS BEN'S CAR.
DOES IT FLY?
SOARS PRETTY FAST
IN THE OPEN HIGHWAY.
- SOMEONE'S COMING!
- [LAUGHING]
I'VE FALLEN
AND I CAN'T GET UP!
OH! ARE YOU OKAY?
I WAS DOING THAT COMMERCIAL,
YOU KNOW, WITH THE OLD LADY--
NO,
I DON'T WATCH COMMERCIALS.
I TIVO EVERYTHING
AND F.F. THROUGH THE BLATHER.
RIGHT.
DO YOU MIND
IF I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
ASK AWAY.
WHY DID
YOU AND BEN SPLIT UP?
HE'S A CONTROL FREAK.
BEN?
HE NEVER LETS SETH
MARINATE WITH HIS FRIENDS.
- MARINATE?
- HANG OUT WITH.
OH, THAT'S WRONG.
MM-HMM.
SO HOW 'BOUT YOU?
YOU EVER BEEN MARRIED?
NO. NO,
I HADN'T REALLY
HAD THE OPPORTUNITY.
OH.
UM...
YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO BELIEVE THIS...
UM...
I ACTUALLY
JUST CAME OUT
OF THE COMA.
NO KIDDING.
WHOA, YOU WOULD THINK
THAT WOULD'VE MADE THE NEWS.
DAD WANTED TO GO ON T.V.
TO "PROCLAIM THE POWER OF GOD!"
BUT,
HE SAID IT WAS UP TO ME
SINCE IT'S MY LIFE.
- SO YOUR DAD GOT RELIGION.
- DID HE EVER.
JORDAN, TOO.
WELL,
THEY HAVE A POINT.
OH, COME ON, TUESDAY!
NOT YOU, TOO!
I NEED YOU TO BE
THE VOICE OF REASON.
YOUR DOCTOR
TOLD ME TO MY FACE
THAT YOU WERE A GONER!
NOT IN THOSE EXACT WORDS.
I MEAN, HOW CAN YOU EXPLAIN...
TUESDAY,
IF GOD WAS SO POWERFUL,
I WOULDN'T TAKE HIM
NINETEEN YEARS.
I MEAN,  NINETEEN YEARS!
I'M GOING TO BE FORTY SOON!
BABE,
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD?
FORTY IS THE NEW  THIRTY.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- IT MEANS
WE'RE ONLY GOING TO BE,
LIKE, THIRTY.
THIRTY!
OHHH...
SORRY TO BREAK YOUR CRAYONS.
THIS'LL MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
COME ON.
LET IT RIP.
Ben:
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
JUST MARINATIN'.
SERIOUSLY, MONICA?
YOU WERE GOING TO EGG MY CAR?
YOU'RE VERY IMMATURE
FOR YOUR AGE.
AM NOT!
OKAY, IF I'M IM-MATURE,
THEN YOU'RE WAY MATURE!
AS IN MAJOR MATURE,
BORDERLINE GEEZER,
- MATURE-O-RAMA!
- EXCUSE ME?
OH, I'M SORRY,
WHAT'S THAT?
DID YOU
LOSE YOUR HEARING,
OLD MAN?
YOU'VE FORGOTTEN
WHAT IT MEANS TO BE  YOUNG!
- AND HOW WOULD YOU KNOW THAT?
- OH, I GOT THE 411 ON YOU.
HOW YOU DON'T LET YOU  SON
HANG OUT WITH HIS FRIENDS.
YOU TOLD HER THAT?
MY BUST.
THAT REEKS!
TAKE CARE,
LADIES.
WHAT-- LET GO!
UH...
- UGH!
-  FEEL BETTER?
HOW COULD I BE
SO WRONG ABOUT HIM?!
HE QUIT ON ME,
HE QUIT ON HIS MARRIAGE TO YOU,
HE QUIT ON HIS DREAM
TO PLAY FOOTBALL!
WELL,
IN ALL FAIRNESS
TO THE GEEZER,
QUITTING FOOTBALL
WASN'T ENTIRELY HIS CHOICE.
IT WAS JUST
A ROUTINE PRACTICE
ON THE FIELD.
NO ONE
SAW IT COMING.
- HOW BADLY WAS HE INJURED?
- BOTH LEGS WERE CRUSHED.
WE WERE TOLD...
THAT HE COULDN'T
EVER PLAY FOOTBALL AGAIN.
EVER  WALK AGAIN.
WERE YOU TWO
MARRIED AT THE TIME?
NOT QUITE.
HE TRIED
TO DISCOURAGE ME
BY SAYING
I SHOULDN'T SETTLE
FOR "HALF A MAN."
BUT I ALWAYS WANT
THAT WHICH I'VE BEEN DENIED.
THAT'S TRUE LOVE,
TUESDAY.
IT WAS A LONG, HARD HAUL.
BUT THERE
WAS SOMETHING THRILLING
ABOUT BEN'S DETERMINATION
TO DEFY THE DOCTORS.
THEN SHORTLY AFTER
HE TOOK HIS FIRST STEPS,
WE CELEBRATED
BY GETTING MARRIED.
I THOUGHT HE'D AT LEAST
TRY TO GO BACK TO FOOTBALL,
BUT HE JUST NEVER DID.
SHORT STORY LONG,
LIFE WITH A REALTOR HUSBAND,
AND A NEWBORN BABY
JUST BECAME...
ORDINARY.
ENOUGH SAID.
EAT YOUR EGGS.
IT'S MEDIEVAL
TO THE REST OF US,
BUT TO YOU
IT'LL BE BRAND NOODLES.
CARRA-OAK.
♪ LET ME CALL YOU ♪
♪ SWEETHEART ♪
♪ I'M IN LOVE ♪
♪ WITH YOU ♪
♪ WITH ALL OF YOU ♪
[CHEERS, APPLAUSE]
Emcee:
ALL RIGHT EVERYBODY.
NEXT UP WE'VE GOT JOHNNY!
LADIES.
WHAT CAN I GET YOU?
A DIET POP.
OH, PLEASE!
LIVE A LITTLE!
WE'LL HAVE
TWO APPLETINIS PLEASE.
CAN I SEE SOME I.D.?
OH.
NOT YOU.
YOU.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIGGLING]
DON'T LOOK.
DOOFUS ALERT,
TWO O'CLOCK.
- I DON'T SEE ANYONE.
- WHAT ARE YOU, BLIND?
- HE'S SITTING  RIGHT THERE.
- WHO'S SITTING RIGHT THERE?
WALLACE.
NO, THAT'S NOT WALLACE.
WHATEVS.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
IS HE A T.V. REPORTER?
I GUESS
YOU COULD SAY THAT.
I'VE SEEN HIM ON CABLE
DOING FLUFF STORIES--
WHEN THEY HAVE
AIR TIME TO FILL.
MY MOM THOUGHT HE WAS
THE "APPLE OF GOD'S EYE"
BECAUSE HE WALKED AWAY
FROM THAT CRASH--
LITERALLY,
WALKED AWAY.
BOY,
WAS MY MOM  WRONG.
GOD DEALT WALLACE
A ROTTEN HAND.
HE'S HAD
THREE FAILED MARRIAGES,
CAN'T HOLD A JOB,
HAS BEEN
BUMMING AROUND THE COUNTRY--
INCLUDING NEW ORLEANS
WHERE KATRINA
TOOK HIM FOR  EVERYTHING.
THE LAST I HEARD,
HE WAS
LIVING IN A TRAILER,
IN THAT SPOOKY LOT
- BEHIND PINE STREET.
- NICE WORK, SHERLOCK,
BUT YOU SHOULDN'T BELIEVE
ALL THE GOSSIP YOU DIG UP.
I DIDN'T  DIG IT UP,
WATSON.
DID THIS KATRINA
TELL YOU HERSELF, FIRST HAND?
NO, KATRINA DIDN'T TELL ME.
Bartender:
ONE APPLE MARTINI
AND ONE DIET POP.
I'LL HAVE TO GIVE YOU AN "A"
FOR ORIGINALITY.
USING YOUR MOM'S LICENSE
FROM THE '80s...
I'VE NEVER SEEN THAT BEFORE.
Announcer:
ALL RIGHT FOLKS,
NEXT UP WE'VE GOT ADAM.
HE'S GOING TO MIX IT UP
A LITTLE BIT
AND SING US ALL A LULLABY.
GO TELL HIM HELLO.
WHAT?
GO TELL WALLACE HELLO.
MMM, MMM.
DON'T YOU WANT HIM TO KNOW
THAT HE DIDN'T KILL YOU?
♪ THESE TIMES ARE TOUGH ♪
♪ AND SINKING SAND ♪
♪ I LOST MY WAY ♪
♪ A FOREIGN LAND ♪
♪ AND I... ♪
♪ HOLD YOU TRUE ♪
♪ A GUIDE ♪
♪ I SEEK IN YOU ♪
♪ COME BACK TO ME ♪
♪ LULLABY ♪
♪ A SYMPHONY ♪
♪ COME DROPPING BY ♪
♪ AS I GET ♪
♪ TO THE NIGHT ♪
♪ BY WAY FOR THIS ♪
♪ I SING ♪
♪ MY LULLABY ♪
OH, HEY, MAKEUP.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT.
ANYONE EVER TELL YOU
IT'S KIND OF POINTLESS
TO KEEP IT IN YOUR CAR
INSTEAD OF ON YOUR FACE?
WE NEED MILK.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
I JUST CASED ON YOU!
WHY DON'T YOU
DEFEND YOURSELF?!
BECAUSE YOU FEEL LIKE FIGHTING.
I, ON THE OTHER HAND, DO NOT.
WAIT.
I'M SORRY
THAT I WASN'T HERE
OVER THE YEARS
TO HELP GUIDE YOU.
SO YOU COULD SHOW ME
HOW TO APPLY MAKEUP?
EXACTLY.
BUT IT'S NEVER TOO LATE, RIGHT?
HOW 'BOUT WE GO HOME
AND I GIVE YOU A MAKEOVER?
HOW 'BOUT YOU DON'T?
FINE! STAY OOGLY.
SEE IF I CARE.
AUNT MONICA, I DON'T BLAME YOU
FOR FEELING SORRY FOR YOURSELF.
I DON'T EVEN BLAME YOU
FOR BEING ANGRY AT GOD.
BUT YOU'RE NOT
THE ONLY ONE THAT THIS
HAS BEEN DIFFICULT FOR.
OH, I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT  I WAS THE ONE
IN A COMA.
"WAS" AND STILL IS.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
I THOUGHT WE NEEDED MILK.
WHY WOULD YOU
BRING ME BACK  HERE?
[BABY CRYING]
DAD?
WHO'S THAT WOMAN?
A PERFECT STRANGER.
THE WOMAN'S
TWO-YEAR-OLD SON
WAS SEVERELY BURNED
IN A KITCHEN FIRE.
OH, NO.
WHY IS DAD HERE?
HE'S ALWAYS HERE
WHEN HE'S NOT WORKING.
HAVEN'T YOU EVER WONDERED
WHY PAPA JACK ALWAYS WORKS
AT THE KITCHEN TABLE?
IT'S BECAUSE HIS OFFICE
FOR THE PAST NINETEEN YEARS
WAS YOUR HOSPITAL ROOM.
HE DIDN'T
WANT YOU TO BE ALONE
WHEN YOU...
OPENED YOUR EYES.
SOMETIMES I WISHED
YOU HAD DIED IN THE CRASH.
THEN AT LEAST
HE COULD'VE MORNED
AND MOVED ON.
THEN ONE DAY
I HAD DROPPED BY TO SEE HIM.
ROSA WAS WITH YOU.
SHE SAID HE'D COME OVER HERE
TO THE E.R. TO COMFORT PEOPLE.
HOW?
- BY TELLING THEM ABOUT YOU.
- ABOUT  ME?
HOW CAN YOU
POSSIBLY GIVE ANYBODY HOPE
WHEN HIS DAUGHTER
IS ACROSS THE STREET
IN SUSPENDED ANIMATION?
BECAUSE YOU WERE
ACROSS THE STREET
IN SUSPENDED ANIMATION.
THESE PEOPLE
WERE ALL IN CRISIS,
YET BEFORE THEM
STOOD A MAN
WITH SUCH PEACE--
THE "PEACE THAT SURPASSES
ALL UNDERSTANDING."
PAPA JACK HAD NO DOUBT
THAT GOD WAS IN CONTROL--
WHATEVER THE OUTCOME FOR YOU--
BE IT LIFE OR DEATH.
HE COULD COMFORT OTHERS
AS NO ONE ELSE COULD.
HOW'D YOU DO IT, DAD?
HOW DID YOU SURVIVE
ALL THOSE YEARS
WITH A CATALEPTIC KID?
" THAT WHICH
DOESN'T KILL US
MAKES US STRONGER."
WHICH BIBLE HERO SAID THAT?
THAT WAS
STEEL MAGNOLIAS.
[LAUGHS]
I THOUGHT
IT SOUNDED FAMILIAR.
AS LONG AS YOU WERE ALIVE,
THERE WAS HOPE.
AND BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
WHEN THINGS
SEEMED THEIR MOST BLEAK...
THAT'S WHEN...
GOD'S GRACE
ABOUNDED ALL THE MORE.
IS THAT WOMAN'S BABY
GOING TO BE OKAY?
BONO.
HIS NAME IS BONO.
IT WILL TAKE SOME TIME
FOR HIM TO HEAL.
DAD,
I THINK THAT IT'S TIME
THAT YOU
BROUGHT ME UP TO SPEED
ON THE 21st CENTURY.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE READY FOR THAT?
OKAY. WELL,
WHERE SHOULD I BEGIN?
HOW 'BOUT SEPTEMBER 11th?
EXCUSE ME.
I THINK
THOSE ARE FOR ME.
WHO'S "JOEL"?
HOW'D YOU EAT?
I DON'T REMEMBER.
WHO'S JOEL?
WEREN'T YOU LIKE, BORED,
JUST LAYING THERE
ALL THOSE YEARS?
DON'T MAKE ME HURT YOU,
DEXTER.
WHO DO YOU WORK FOR?
CIRCUIT CITY.
BUT RUMOR HAS IT
MY DAYS ARE NUMBERED.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT GOOD ARE FLOWERS
TO A DAZED FREAKSHOW?
WELL,
YOU'RE NOT DAZED NOW.
SO ENJOY.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
THIS PLACE?
- IT KINDA SEEMS LIKE A DIVE.
- IT IS A DIVE.
BUT THEY HAVE
THIS REALLY COOL THING
CALLED "CARR-OAK".
♪ I HAVE NO PEACE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU AND I ARGUE ♪
♪ BOY IT MAKES ME WEAK ♪
♪ THOUGH I STAND MY GROUND ♪
♪ BELIEVE ME
THERE'S NO VICTORY ♪
♪ NOT FOR ME ♪
♪ WHEN WE DON'T AGREE... ♪
I'LL BE BACK IN A JIFF.
HEY, WALLACE.
WHAT'S CRACKALACKIN'?
OH, SORRY.
IT'S ME, MONICA.
FROM THE SHOE DEPARTMENT.
OH, I KNOW THAT LOOK.
SURPRISE!
I'M NOT DEAD.
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M NOT DEAD EITHER.
OH. GOOD.
LOOK, UM...
THIS ISN'T REALLY
A GOOD TIME, OKAY?
OH.
HOW 'BOUT NOW?
DAD TOLD ME
THAT YOU CAME TO VISIT ME
IN THE HOSPITAL.
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
I AM GLAD
THAT YOU RECOVERED.
ABSO-TIVELY.
EVERYTHING IN TACT.
NO WORRIES.
GOOD AS NEW.
WELL, I GOTTA BOOK.
TAKE CARE.
UM, HEY, WALLACE,
I KNOW
IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO,
AND YOU PROBABLY
DON'T EVER EVEN
THINK ABOUT IT ANYMORE,
BUT, UM,
I JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW
THAT I DON'T BLAME YOU ANYMORE
FOR THE ACCIDENT.
I KNOW THAT MY DAD
ALREADY TOLD YOU HE FORGAVE YOU,
BUT I JUST WANTED YOU
TO HEAR IT FROM ME, TOO.
SO...
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
OKAY.
TAKE CARE.
LATER DAYS.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
♪ I SAW YOU
WALKING DOWN
THE AVENUE ♪
♪ I COULDN'T TAKE MY EYES ♪
♪ OFF OF YOU ♪
♪ THE SUNLIGHT IN YOUR FACE ♪
♪ AND NOTHING OUT OF PLACE ♪
♪ ON YOU... ♪
THANKS FOR COMING OUT.
HEY.
YOU COULD'VE COME IN.
I WAS AFRAID
I MIGHT BREAK SOMETHING.
UM, I WANTED TO APOLOGIZE
FOR ACTING MENTAL.
YOUR RULES FOR SETH--
NOT MY BUSINESS.
I AM PROTECTIVE OF SETH.
I DON'T LET HIM
DRIVE WITH TEENAGERS.
YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
SHOULD UNDERSTAND THAT.
'NUFF SAID.
YOU KNOW,
I'VE BEEN THINKING...
ABOUT...
WHAT YOU SAID ABOUT ME
BEING A GEEZER.
OH, I WAS PEEVED.
YES, YOU WERE,
BUT YOU MIGHT'VE BEEN RIGHT.
I CAN'T HONESTLY REMEMBER
THE LAST EXCITING TIME
IN MY LIFE.
WHAT ABOUT THE SUPER BOWL?
YOU WON'T BELIEVE IT.
I MISSED IT.
I WAS ON THE ROAD
THE WHOLE TIME.
I ACTUALLY MEANT
SUPER BOWL XXIII--
AT MY HOUSE.
Mimicking Sportscaster:
THE CINCINNATI BENGALS
LED BY BOOMER ESIASON...
...LEAD
THE SAN FRANCISCO 49ers
- BY THREE POINTS.
- THREE POINTS,
TWO MINUTES TO GO.
SAN FRANCISCO WITH THE BALL.
JOE MONTANA
STRUTS OUT ONTO THE FIELD.
IT'S MONTANA TO RICE.
LIKE A PERFECTLY
CHOREOGRAPHED BALLET,
NINETY-TWO YARDS
DOWN THE FIELD.
THIRTY SECONDS REMAIN.
MONTANA THROWS!
JOHN TAYLOR--
CATCHES!
- TOUCHDOWN! WHEW!
- TOUCHDOWN!
Together:
WAY TO GO, JOE!
I WAS
SORRY TO HEAR ABOUT
YOUR INJURY.
AH...
IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
HOW DID YOU EVER BEAT THE ODDS
AFTER THE DOCTORS TOLD YOU
YOU COULDN'T EVEN WALK AGAIN?
FIRST I WENT
STRAIGHT INTO DENIAL,
FOLLOWED BY ANGER,
MOPING, POUTING...
LASHED OUT
AT EVERYONE AROUND ME,
I WANTED THEM
TO FEEL MY MISERY.
YEAH,
I SEEM TO BE ABLE
TO RELATE.
THEN ONE DAY,
DURING MY USUAL ROUTINE
OF MAC AND CHEESE AND T.V.,
I WAS WATCHING
THE THREE AMIGOS.
AND I HAD AN EPIPHANY.
WHILE WATCHING
THE THREE AMIGOS?
MY LEGS
HAD BECOME MY  EL GUAPO!
I COULDN'T LET THEM
LORD THAT OVER ME ANYMORE.
THEY HAD TO BE CONQUERED.
SO I STOPPED CRYING.
"WHY ME?"
"HOW COULD YOU, GOD?"
WELL, THOSE ARE
LEGITIMATE QUESTIONS.
NOT THE WAY
THAT I WAS ASKING.
IT WAS MORE RHETORICAL.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
THAT GOD DIDN'T ANSWER.
WHAT WAS THE ANSWER?
THAT IT'S NOT ALWAYS ABOUT ME.
IT TOOK TWO YEARS
OF PHYSICAL THERAPY.
INTENSE.
EXCRUCIATING AT TIMES.
BUT AS YOU CAN SEE...
MY  EL GUAPO BIT THE DUST.
I JUST UM...
WITH THAT I COULD'VE...
BEEN WITH YOU
BY YOUR SIDE.
Tuesday:
AM I INTERRUPTING
"SOMETHING"?
IS THERE SOMETHING
I CAN DO FOR YOU?
I CAME TO TALK ABOUT
SETH'S VISIT.
OH,
I GUESS I SHOULD GO.
NO, MONICA.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL YOU, ALSO.
"PRIVATELY."
I'LL BE IN MY OFFICE.
COME BY WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
DON'T BE A NOOB.
TAKE A CHILL PILL, TUESDAY.
WE WERE JUST TALKING.
LOOK AT YOU.
YOU'RE, YOU'RE ALL GAGA.
HOW CAN YOU
ALLOW YOUR HAPPINESS--
YOUR ENTIRE WORLD--
TO REVOLVE
AROUND A  GUY?
I MEAN,
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE
WITH YOUR LIFE?
I'VE BEEN UNCONSCIOUS.
WHAT'S YOUR EXCUSE?
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
THE CAR ACCIDENT?
THE ONE WHERE BEN BROKE AN ARM
AND LEFT YOU FOR DEAD?
NO...
I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN.
WHERE'S MONICA?
SHE TOOK OFF.
YOU KNOW HOW THAT GOES.
DON'T BE A NOOB.
WHAT?
I SAW WHAT WAS
GOING ON OUT THERE.
SO, ABOUT SETH.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
THE CAR ACCIDENT?
YOU KNOW,
THE ONE THAT LEFT MONICA
WITH A BROKEN ARM...
AND YOU
WITH TWO  CRUSHED LEGS?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
COME IN.
HEY.
BEN CALLED EARLIER.
AND YOU DIDN'T
HANG UP ON HIM?
I COULDN'T.
HE GOT THE MACHINE.
THIS IS BEN'S NUMBER?
YOU'RE ACTUALLY
GIVING ME BEN'S NUMBER?
JUST  DON'T MAKE
A FOOL OUT OF YOURSELF, OKAY?
JORDAN!
THANKS.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
HEY MONICA,
I'M GLAD YOU CALLED.
I KNOW
THINGS GOT A LITTLE
WEIRD YESTERDAY.
YEAH,
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
BOLTED LIKE THAT.
LISTEN,
I DON'T HAVE A LOT TIME.
I'M EXPECTING CLIENTS BUT...
I THINK WE SHOULD TALK...
ABOUT THE ACCIDENT.
I KNOW
THAT IT MUST'VE BEEN
HARD FOR YOU--
HARD?
TRY DEVASTATING.
I COULDN'T GRASP THE REALITY
THAT ALL OF OUR HOPES,
ALL OF OUR DREAMS
WERE JUST...
GONE.
I KNOW.
I KEPT HOPING
THAT YOU'D COME BACK
LIKE YOU DID
AFTER GRADUATION.
YEAH,
IF ONLY I COULD HAVE.
HOW COULD ANYBODY EXPECT YOU
TO GIVE UP YOUR DREAM
OF BEING A
RICHIE-FOOTBALL STAR'S WIFE
TO TAKE CARE OF HALF A MAN?
I...SAY WHAT?
NO ONE BLAMED YOU.
WELL, I TAKE THAT BACK.
I BLAMED YOU.
FOR AT LEAST NOT COMING
AND TELLING ME, FACE TO FACE.
YOU WERE INJURED
IN THE ACCIDENT?
YOUR LEGS WERE  CRUSHED
IN THE CAR ACCIDENT?
I KNOW IT HURT YOU
TO SEE ME LIKE THAT.
- TUESDAY TOLD ME.
- TUESDAY TOLD YOU?
DID TUESDAY TELL YOU...
THAT I  WASN'T HURT
IN THE ACCIDENT?
NO.
SHE TOLD ME ABOUT YOUR ARM.
[LAUGHS]
MY BROKEN ARM,
OF COURSE!
WHY DIDN'T YOU
TRY TO CONTACT ME
OR CALL MY DAD?
IS THAT WHAT YOU'D HAVE WANTED?
FOR ME TO CHASE YOU AROUND
IN MY WHEELCHAIR?
HELLO?
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
LISTEN,
I GOT TO GO.
- BUT, NO, BEN, WAIT...
- BYE, MONICA.
HOW'RE YOU DOING,
BEN?
HI, GUYS.
UGH!
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
WHAT DID I TELL YOU
ABOUT TRYING TO REKINDLE
THAT OLD INFERNO?
YOU'D GET BURNED.
ALL THE YEARS
WE'VE BEEN FRIENDS.
I NEVER REALIZED
HOW BRILLIANT YOU ARE.
WELL,
NOW THAT YOU KNOW,
I HOPE YOU'LL LISTEN
AND STAY AWAY FROM SCORCHERS.
[DOOR CLOSES]
HOW'D YOU PULL IT OFF?
IT'S TRUE
WE LIVE IN A BIG CITY,
BUT BEN AND I
WERE  ENGAGED.
BABE,
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
YOU SLEPT THROUGH
THE WHOLE THING.
TO FOOL SO MANY.
HOW DID YOU EVER EXPECT
TO GET AWAY WITH IT?
I DIDN'T.
LOOKS LIKE
I'LL BE SPENDING THE NIGHT.
DO YOU,
DO YOU NEED ANYTHING?
MY MOM'S ON HER WAY
TO PICK ME UP.
IF YOU COULD
DROP BY THE HOUSE
AND FEED PUNKY...
I KNOW THAT, AH,
MONICA WILL BE
WORRIED ABOUT HIM
WHEN SHE WAKES UP.
OKAY, SURE.
IT'S, IT'S ON HER WAY.
YOU HUNGRY?
HM?
IT'S OKAY.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[ANSWERING MACHINE PICKS UP]
HEY,
YOU'VE REACHED THE WYATT'S.
THIS IS MONICA, DAD,
AND PUNKY.
LEAVE A MESSAGE
AND WE'LL CALL YOU BACK.
LATER...
[BEEP]
Ben:
HEY, MONICA.
[CLEARS THROAT]
IT'S ME.
UH, THEY'RE TRANSFERRING ME
OVER TO MEMORIAL.
SO...
CALL ME.
OR JUST COME OVER.
ALL RIGHT.
I LOVE YOU.
BYE.
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
YOU HAVE ONE NEW MESSAGE.
[BEEP]
Ben's Voice:
HEY, MONICA.
[CLEARS THROAT]
IT'S ME.
UH, THEY'RE TRANSFERRING ME
OVER TO MEMORIAL.
-  SO...
- [BEEPING]
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
MESSAGE DELETED.
YOU MADE HIM THINK
I WAS A MONSTER.
SUCH A MONSTER THAT...
EVENTUALLY MY GUILT WOULD...
DRIVE ME TO DO PENANCE
IN A CONVENT.
[SCOFFS]
WHY DID HE SAY HE WAS SORRY
AT THE REUNION?
HE SENT
A NASTY LETTER ABOUT YOU
TO THE  ALUMNI GAZETTE.
HE THOUGHT IT WOULD
MAKE HIM FEEL BETTER.
THAT WAS IT?
A LETTER?
IT WAS PRETTY BRUTAL.
DID YOU EVER LOVE HIM?
YES.
THEN HOW COULD
YOU WOUND HIM LIKE THAT?
I NEVER INTENDED TO  WOUND HIM.
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
YOUR PLAN...
WAS TO LICK HIS WOUNDS...
BY REPLACING ME.
W-WHAT'RE YOU GOING TO DO?
LEAVE.
HOW CAN YOU BE SO...
BLASE?
WHY NOT?
I SLEPT THROUGH
THE WHOLE THING.
COME ON!
SCREAM AT ME!
BREAK SOMETHING!
TAKE ME TO BEN FOR A SHOWDOWN!
I FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.
YOU'RE JUST
A SELF-ABSORBED CHILD
WHO CAN'T THINK OF ANYBODY
BUT HER OWN HAPPINESS.
AND HOW WOULD YOU KNOW THAT?
IT TAKES ONE TO KNOW ONE.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
UGH-AH!
AH, THE FORMALLY BLIND MAN
ADMITS HE'S CLUELESS.
AH...
BUT SAYS,
ONE THING I DO KNOW.
I WAS BLIND
BUT NOW I SEE.
DID YOU NOTICE THE DISCIPLES
ALSO WANT AN EXPLANATION,
- FROM JESUS?
- AH, LET'S SEE...
THEY ASKED,
"WHO SINNED,
THIS MAN OR HIS PARENTS,
THAT HE WAS BORN BLIND?"
"NEITHER THIS MAN
NOR HIS PARENTS SINNED,"
SAID JESUS,
"BUT THIS HAPPENED
SO THAT THE WORK OF GOD
MIGHT BE DISPLAYED IN HIS LIFE."
SO WHAT DOES
THAT TELL YOU?
IT'S NOT ALWAYS ABOUT "ME."
♪♪
♪ TAKE A MOMENT
TO REST YOUR EYES ♪
♪ CLEAR YOUR MIND
LIKE A SUMMER SKY ♪
♪ THERE'S A MIRACLE ♪
♪ HERE ♪
♪ STEADY PASSIONED
WHEN YOU AND I ♪
♪ TAKES ME
I FEEL LIKE I CAN FLY ♪
♪ THERE'S A MIRACLE ♪
♪ HERE ♪
♪ ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE ♪
♪ WHEN WE BELIEVE ♪
♪ TO FEEL IS TO BE ♪
♪ ALIVE ♪
♪ SO LET'S QUIETLY
FLY FOR A WHILE ♪
♪ LIKE A NEWBORN CHILD'S
FIRST SMILE ♪
♪ THERE'S A MIRACLE HERE ♪
HELLO?!
ANYBODY HOME?!
IT'S YOU.
YOU'RE JOEL.
YOU WERE
SURPRISE TO SEE ME,
NOT BECAUSE
YOU THOUGHT I WAS DEAD,
YOU THOUGHT I WAS STILL
AT THE HOSPITAL.
WALLACE!
YOU NEED TO STOP
BLAMING YOURSELF.
YOU HAVE--
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN ME
IN TWENTY YEARS!
TWENTY  DAYS.
AND THE CONTRAST IN YOU
BETWEEN THEN AND NOW--
IS DRASTIC.
AH.
I APPRECIATE YOU COMING BY
AND TRYING
TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER, OKAY?
LOOK, I DIDN'T COME HERE
TO TRY TO MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
WALLACE,
JUST HEAR ME OUT.
THE ACCIDENT
WAS  NOT YOUR FAULT.
- OF COURSE IT WAS MY FAULT.
- NO--
YES!
I RUINED YOUR LIFE!
I RUINED...
- YOUR FIANC'S LIFE!
- NO, I MEAN, BEN AND I
DIDN'T GET MARRIED,
BUT HE HAS A SON NOW
THAT HE ADORES.
AND WHAT ABOUT YOU?!
YOU LOST NINETEEN YEARS.
IF I HAD BEEN PAYING
BETTER ATTENTION TO THE ROAD,
IF I HADN'T BEEN,
BEEN SHOWING OFF
AND ACTING LIKE AN IDIOT,
IF I HADN'T BEEN SPEEDING--
WALLACE, STOP!
HOW OFTEN
DO YOU RECITE THAT?
LOOK,
YOU CAN'T CHANGE
WHAT'S PAST,
BUT YOU CAN
JUST LET IT GO!
NO...
I CAN'T.
WHY NOT?
YOU'RE JOEL.
DONT YOU THINK
GODS FORGIVEN YOU?
YEAH...
I BELIEVE THAT HE HAS.
BUT THAT DOESNT CHANGE
THE CONSEQUENCES OF MY ACTION.
WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
HOW LONG
ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO SUFFER
FROM GUILT?
WALLACE,
IVE FORGIVEN YOU,
MY  DAD
HAS FORGIVEN YOU,
AND  GOD
HAS FORGIVEN YOU.
THE ONLY PERSON LEFT
WHO NEEDS TO FORGIVE YOU
IS  YOU.
DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE THAT
"GOD WILL RESTORE THE YEARS
THAT THE LOCUST
HAS EATEN FROM ME"?
YES, I DO.
THEN I BELIEVE IT, TOO.
FOR  YOU.
YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO DO THIS--
WITH ME, I MEAN?
YOU COULD
GO TO ANY WELL-KNOWN--
I'M SURE.
THANKS FOR COMING,
BEN.
WHAT IS THIS?
DID I MISS SOME KIND
OF BREAKING NEWS?
YES, YOU DID.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, YOU READY?
LET'S DO THIS THING.
ALL RIGHT.
WE ARE ROLLING.
AND...ACTION.
IN 1989,
MONICA WYATT AND THREE FRIENDS
WENT TO THE MOVIES.
LITTLE DID THEY KNOW
THAT MONICA
WOULD NOT RETURN HOME
FOR NINETEEN YEARS.
MONICA,
HAVE YOU REALLY BEEN
IN A COMA
- FOR THE PAST TWO DECADES?
- I HAVE.
UM, THE LAST THING
I REMEMBER
WAS DRIFTING OFF
IN THE BACK SEAT
OF THE CAR--
THE CAR
THAT CRASHED THAT NIGHT.
- IN 1989.
- UH, YEAH.
UM...
AND THE NEXT THING I KNOW
IT'S 2008.
WOW.
SO HAS IT BEEN
HARD FOR YOU TO ADJUST?
I'M STARTING TO CATCH ON.
UM, MY NIECE
HAS REALLY HELPED
TO OPEN MY EYES.
YOU ARE QUITE
AN AMAZING PERSON, MONICA.
NO, I'M NOT AMAZING.
MY  DAD IS AMAZING.
AND MY FIANC
WAS ALSO
BADLY INJURED IN THE WRECK,
UM,
BOTH PHYSICALLY
AND EMOTIONALLY
HE'S AMAZING.
SO...
WHY DID YOU DECIDE
TO SHARE YOUR STORY TODAY?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW MUCH,
BUT ONE THING I DO KNOW.
I WAS OUT,
AND NOW I'M UP.
I DIDN'T WAKE MYSELF.
THE DOCTORS DIDN'T WAKE ME.
THIS HAPPENED
SO THAT THE POWER OF GOD
MIGHT BE
DISPLAYED IN MY LIFE.
AND...CUT!
WE GOT IT.
AH. WOW,
VERY NICE, MONICA.
IT WAS GREAT.
LET'S HEAD ON INSIDE
AND HAVE A LOOK.
YOU DID GREAT,
HUN.
Wallace:
OH. OH, MY. WYATT.
YOU'RE UP NEXT.
SOUNDS GOOD.
HADN'T PLANNED ON
TELLING YOU LIKE THIS.
YOUR DAD CALLED.
HE TOLD ME
I'VE WAITED LONG ENOUGH.
HE'S RIGHT.
WHY DIDN'T YOU CALL ME
WHEN YOU WOKE UP?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
AT THE REUNION?
WE THOUGHT YOU KNEW.
TUESDAY TOLD MY DAD
THAT YOU WALKED AWAY
FROM THE ACCIDENT
WITH A BROKEN ARM.
YEAH.
I'M AN IDIOT.
I SHOULDA CALLED YOUR DAD.
I SHOULD OF
VERIFIED TUESDAY'S STORY.
- I SHOULD OF--
- BEN, PLEASE!
NO MORE "SHOULD OF'S."
IT DOESN'T MATTER NOW.
THEN...
THEN?
THEN WHERE DO WE GO
FROM HERE?
I'M NOT SURE.
I THOUGHT I HAD
EVERYTHING FIGURED OUT,
AND I KNEW
EXACTLY WHAT I WANTED.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO LIVE
FOR SUPERFICIAL THINGS ANYMORE.
WAS I A SUPERFICIAL THING?
HARDLY.
I FEEL LIKE
I'M TWICE YOUR AGE.
YOU'RE NOT.
MONICA,
I'VE LIVED
LONG ENOUGH TO KNOW
THAT IF WE PICK UP
WHERE WE'VE LEFT OFF...
LIFE'S NOT GOING TO ALL BE
POM-POM FLOWERS
AND WEDDING CAKE.
I UNDERSTAND.
YOU'RE SAYING WE MIGHT
COME ACROSS
A FEW  EL GUAPO'S.
YES.
BUT I THINK
WE CAN TAKE 'EM.
HOW WOULD YOU AND SETH
LIKE TO COME OVER
FOR DINNER TONIGHT?
I'D LIKE THAT VERY MUCH.
I KNOW
HE'S DYING TO MEET THE WOMAN
WHO GAME HIM
"HISTORIC STRATFORD-ON-AVON".
LAMBY!
OH, NO!
IT'S ROSA!
SISTER ROSA
FROM THE CONVENT!
SHE HAS
RELENTLESS LIP
SYNDROME.
ROSA! HEY!
I WAS SO HOPING
TO SEE YOU!
WELL, OF COURSE!
YOUR REPORTER
IS GOING TO PUT ME ON T.V.
I BROUGHT PICTURES
FROM OUR TIME TOGETHER
TO SHARE WITH
HIM AND HIS VIEWERS.
OH, TH-THAT'S GREAT!
THEY'RE HAVING A LITTLE
TECHNICAL DIFFICULTY.
IT COULD TAKE HOURS.
LET ME SEE YOUR FINGERNAILS.
♪ ALL I REALLY WANT TO DO ♪
♪ WITH YOU ♪
♪ WELL,
I CAN'T REALLY SAY ♪
♪ AFTER ALL
THAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH
THERE'S SOMETHING NEW ♪
♪ COULD REALLY MAKE MY DAY ♪
♪ SO JUST
TAKE FROM MY SACK ♪
♪ YOU'LL SEE
WHERE I'M GETTIN' AT ♪
♪ WELL, OH ♪
♪ IT WILL BE PERFECT ♪
♪ JUST LIKE THAT ♪
♪ OH, WHOA ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ FAST FORWARD
A FEW YEARS ♪
♪ AND NOW YOU'RE MINE ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE TELLING ME ♪
♪ YOU HEART IS ♪
♪ ON THE LINE ♪
♪ YOU SAY,
DO YOU STILL THINK OF ME ♪
♪ AS THE ONE
THAT'S MEANT TO BE ♪
♪ AFTER ALL THIS TIME? ♪
♪ AND I SAY ♪
♪ WELL,
WHAT I REALLY WANT TO DO ♪
♪ WITH YOU ♪
♪ WELL,
I CAN'T REALLY SAY ♪
♪ AFTER ALL
THAT WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
NOTHING NEW ♪
♪ IS EVER GONNA
GET IN OUR WAY ♪
♪ SO JUST
GET FROM MY SACK ♪
♪ YOU'LL SEE
WHERE MY HEART IS AT ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ AND WE ARE PERFECT ♪
♪ JUST LIKE THAT ♪
♪ WE ALL MAKE MISTAKES ♪
♪ WE ALL HAVE THOSE DAYS ♪
♪ WHEN NOTHING EVER SEEMS ♪
♪ GOOD ENOUGH ♪
♪ BUT ALL IT REALLY TAKES ♪
♪ IS A LITTLE BIT OF FAITH ♪
♪ IN LOVE ♪
♪ SO LISTEN, GIRL ♪
♪ ALL I REALLY WANT TO DO ♪
♪ WITH YOU ♪
♪ WELL,
I CAN'T REALLY SAY ♪
♪ AFTER ALL
THAT WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
NOTHING NEW ♪
♪ IS EVER GONNA GET
IN OUR WAY ♪
♪ SO JUST
GET FROM MY SACK ♪
♪ YOU'LL SEE
WHERE MY HEART IS AT ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ WE ARE PERFECT ♪
♪ ALL I REALLY WANT TO DO ♪
♪ WITH YOU ♪
♪ WELL,
I CAN'T REALLY SAY ♪
♪ AFTER ALL
THAT WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
NOTHING NEW ♪
♪ IS EVER GONNA GET
IN OUR WAY ♪
♪ SO JUST
GET FROM MY SACK ♪
♪ YOU'LL SEE
WHERE MY HEART IS AT ♪
♪ OH, OH ♪
♪ AND WE ARE PERFECT ♪
♪ JUST LIKE THAT ♪
♪ MMM ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ JUST LIKE THAT ♪♪
♪♪