Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[Woman]
Who's next?
John?
[John] Yes.
[Woman]
Stand up, please.
[John]
Okay.
[Woman]
What's the square root of 225?
[John] I don't know.
[Woman] John, we have been
talking about this
for the last...
Come closer.
Closer.
[John]
Okay.
[Woman]
And stop saying okay.
- Okay.
- [soft laughter]
[Woman]
Take a look at this.
You understand it?
Yes.
- [Woman] John.
- Yes.
[Woman]
What's the square root of 225?
I don't know.
[Woman]
Yes, you do, John.
- Fifteen.
- [Woman] Fifteen?
- Are you sure?
- No.
Yes, fifteen.
[Woman] How did you arrive
at that conclusion?
I don't know.
[Woman]
You don't know?
Fifteen is correct.
Can I sit?
[Woman]
Yes.
Okay, so now
if you pay attention to...
[skate board whirring]
[no audible dialogue]
[spitting, water running]
[gargling]
- [drawer opens, closes]
- [spitting]
[pill bottle opens]
[drawer closes]
[switch clicks]
[insects chirping]
[blinds whirring]
[blind locking down]
[knocking, door opens]
Good night, buddy.
Good night, Dad.
I have to stop by
the office tomorrow,
but if I don't come back late,
maybe we can go hit some balls.
Practice that
two-handed backhand?
Okay.
Good.
Oh, hey, buddy?
What?
When was the last time
you looked under your bed?
I think you better
look under your bed.
[♪♪♪]
[whirling, screeching]
[crashing]
[whirling stops]
[footsteps approaching]
[beeping]
[branches breaking]
[buzzing]
- [buzzing fades]
- [distant crash]
[birds chirping]
[birds cawing]
[electronic signal]
[beeping, whirling]
[whirling]
[whirling stalls, beeping]
[beeping]
[drone falling]
[grunting]
[crickets chirping]
[groaning]
[machine running outside]
[pill bottle rattling]
[car honking]
[leaf blower whirring]
[pill bottle opens]
[drawer closes]
[water running]
- You okay, buddy?
- [Anna] What's wrong, baby?
Nothing.
Just tired.
[Laurie]
Can you pass me the water?
You take the drone for a flight?
Yeah.
I hope you read
the instructions.
Always read the instructions.
Hear that drone has a camera.
The guy at the store said
it had a pretty good one.
4K.
It's the best drone they had.
- This morning I lost it.
- What?
You lost it?
- I was looking for it...
- You lost the drone?
[car horn honks]
Oh, he's here.
Who's here?
- Josh.
- Who's Josh?
[Anna] Next time, ask him to
knock and introduce himself.
[Laurie] Okay, I will.
He's just really shy.
- [Brad] Who's Josh?
- [Laurie] Bye, love you!
[Anna] Love you too, honey!
[Brad sighing]
- Did you know about this?
- [Anna] About what?
About this... Josh?
Yes.
I found the hole.
What?
The hole.
On the other side of the trees.
The bunker, you mean?
You found the bunker?
What bunker?
The hole...
The abandoned construction.
That was supposed to be
a bunker.
- A bunker?
- Mm-hm.
What's a bunker?
Sometimes people...
They build these
underground homes.
Why?
In case something bad happens.
Something bad?
Yeah, like a big storm.
Like a bunker is a house
underneath the earth
where you can hide
from a big storm.
Exactly.
They started building it...
When was this?
- But after a week...
- A month.
They worked on it for
at least a month.
I don't think so.
There's almost nothing there.
No, they worked on it
for a month,
and then they ran out of money
or something.
They didn't get
their permits approved.
How long ago?
- Hmm, a few years.
- Five, at least.
Five, already?
My God!
They're gonna finish it?
I don't know. I'm pretty sure
they still own the land.
Who owns the land?
I don't know, buddy.
No idea.
Are you all right, baby?
Yeah.
I'm just tired.
- [ball launcher fires]
- [racket stroke]
[Man] Knees bent.
- [ball launcher fires]
- [racket stroke]
- [Man] Come on, John.
- [Man] Finish the swing.
- [racket stroke]
[Man] You got this.
[racket stroke]
[Man] There you go.
Watch it.
Knees bent, John, c'mon.
You know this.
Okay, finish that swing,
follow through.
Focus.
[tennis ball bouncing]
[footsteps approaching]
[sighing]
Can you please stop?
Why?
What do you mean "why"?
- Stop!
- Why?
It's annoying.
Okay.
- Okay, what?
- I'll stop.
Don't be an asshole, John,
I'm trying to read.
- What?
- What what?
What are you trying to read?
A biography,
Alexander the Great.
How many pillows do we have?
What?
Why are you reading that?
- Book club.
- [bouncing continues]
I can help you.
Yes, you can't even stop
the fucking ball!
I can't. It's not that
I don't want to, I can't.
You have to ask my body to.
I literally can't.
[footsteps receding]
[skate board whirring]
[leaf blower]
[John] Hi, Charlie.
Hey, John.
What are you doing?
[Charlie] I'm weeding.
- Weeding?
- [Charlie] Yep.
What's that?
Taking out the weeds.
Why?
[Charlie] Well, they...
rob the other plants
in the soil
of nutrients and water
that they need.
You like the lemonade?
Yeah.
So...
How do you feel?
- Sorry?
- How do you feel?
Good.
Very good?
Great.
You have a spider on your back.
- What?
- A spider...
On your back.
Oh.
That's a...
That's a garden spider.
Also called a golden spider,
writing spider, corn spider.
It's a good spider.
Keeps the garden clean.
- Clean of what?
- [Charlie] Pests.
- Pests?
- [Charlie] Yep.
- Like rats?
- No.
Fuck!
Fuck.
I'll bring more lemonade.
[stomping]
[♪♪♪]
[stirring]
[sprinkler running]
[video game sounds]
[Pete] Stop hitting the...
I'm there.
Stop hitting the ball.
[John] It's your fault.
- [John] No!
- [Pete] Yes! There you go.
Run after that one.
See your energy disappear.
[John] Go fuck yourself, Pete.
[video game sounds]
[Pete] And now a drop shot.
Did you see that?
Of course you saw that.
You're playing against me.
[John] I'm not playing against you.
I'm kicking your ass.
[Pete] Not for long.
[John]
Of the last 377 games,
this being number 378,
I won 312.
- [Pete] That can't be right.
- [John] It's right.
- [Pete] You kept count?
- [John] Yes.
- [Pete] That's sad, John.
- [John] You're sad, Pete.
Sliced backhand chip.
Now I charge. Break point.
[Pete] Boston is sad.
[John] Boston's sad
now that you live there.
- [Pete] Fuck you.
- [John] Fuck you!
- [Pete] Sorry, Mom.
- [John] Sorry, Mom.
[Pete] Fuck you.
Fuck you twice.
Want to play another one?
[Pete] Sure.
- [Pete] How's training?
- Good.
- [Pete] When do they start?
- Three weeks.
- [Pete] You're not gonna make it.
- I will.
- [Pete] You won't.
- I will!
- [Pete] How's your sister?
- Fuck you.
- [Pete] Fuck you.
- [Pete] Say hi to her.
- Okay. I won't.
- [Pete] How's your mom?
- Same.
[electric toothbrush buzzing]
[snoring]
[toothbrush buzzing]
- [spitting]
- [water running]
[drawer opens, closes]
[drawer closes]
[crickets chirping]
[door squeaking]
[footsteps approaching]
[John]
Laurie?
Hey...
[sheets rustling]
[door opens]
[clapping once]
[clapping twice]
[thumping]
[cell phone buzzing]
[thudding]
[body sliding]
[clicking]
[door opens]
[animal noises]
[knocking on door]
[Woman]
You finally cleaned in here.
What did you use?
Show me your pajamas.
[sighing]
Do you wanna go to the bathroom?
- Do you?
- No.
You haven't left the room
since yesterday.
I like the room.
Yeah, of course you do.
You know, when I first saw it
I thought,
"This is Lily's room."
I like it.
You want a banana?
No.
I dreamed something.
You mean you dreamt something?
Yes.
What did you dream?
I was a balloon.
A blue balloon.
Filled with blue air.
I floated.
The sun was blue.
The sky was blue.
Nobody could see me
in the blue sky.
I was blue in the blue.
- You were blue...
- I was blue.
In the blue.
- Yes, the blue.
- [laughing]
Your dad has a blue car.
- Dad?
- Mm-hm.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Is he coming back?
Yeah.
Of course he is.
When?
I don't know.
I learned how to dance.
- Did you?
- I did.
- I think you're lying.
- I'm not.
What did I tell you about lying?
I forgot.
Come sit.
You want me to
tell you a story?
- Yes.
- Okay
Charlie and the Spider?
No. The one about the hole.
John and the Hole?
Yes.
[moaning]
[birds chirping]
[sighing]
Dad!
Dad, where are we?
Mom?
[rapid breathing]
Mom!
Hey, Mom!
- Mom, wake up! Please!
- What time is it, baby?
[gasping]
Mom. Mom!
Help, help...
Mom, wake up!
Dad, what...
[groaning]
Mom! Mom!
- Where are we?
- I don't know.
- What the fuck is going on?
I don't know,
but Mom's not waking up!
Mom!
- Baby?
- [moaning]
Is there a window open?
Are you okay?
[giggling]
Yes.
[Anna] What's going on?
[Brad] I don't know.
Where's John?
[water splashing]
- [distant screams]
- [Brad] Hello! We're down here!
- [Anna] Help!
- [Laurie] Help!
[Brad]
Anybody up there? Hello!
[Anna] Help!
[Laurie] Hello, somebody!
[Anna] Hello!
Hello, this is Bradley Shay.
Hi, this is Anna.
Leave a message after the beep.
Charles?
Hi, Anna Shay.
Yes, hello.
No, I'm calling
to let you know
that we don't need you
to come anymore.
My husband has
some health issues.
His heart.
No, nothing serious.
But...
He's going to stay home
for a while.
He wants to take care of
the garden himself.
His doctor recommended...
Charles, I understand.
No, I'm...
We don't need you
to come anymore.
No, Charles.
I'm sorry.
I said I'm sorry.
[garage door opening]
[garage door closing]
[seat whirring]
[engine starts]
[♪ classical piano music
on car radio ♪]
continues ♪]
[engine and music stop]
[beeping]
[heavy rain sounds]
[heavy rain sounds stop]
[doorbell rings]
Paula?
Up here.
Hey, John.
Can you tell
your mother I'm here?
No.
We're gonna be late.
The rehearsal starts...
She's not here.
She left.
- What?
- She left.
- That's not possible...
- They all left.
Mom, Dad and Laurie.
They went to go visit Grandpa.
He's in the hospital.
Oh...
But...
- Anna never called me.
- They left in a hurry.
Well, in that case...
Yes, I hope your grandfather
gets better...
He had a heart attack.
Mom told me he's in a coma.
Induced coma.
They have to wait.
So sad.
Yes. Sad.
Do you know when
she'll be back?
No. No one knows.
I stayed because I'm training
for the state qualies.
Okay.
If you talk to your mother,
please tell her to call me.
I will.
- Will you?
- I will.
Thank you, John.
Let me know
if you need anything.
I will.
Good luck with the qualies.
[car engine starts]
John!
Oh, son,
thank God you're okay.
Are you hurt?
Is the house okay?
[Anna] What happened, John?
- Do you know who did this?
- Did you see anyone?
You wanna help us, buddy.
What do you got there, a rope?
Go and get the ladder,
the one I use
to fix the roof tiles.
Remember the ladder?
Go and get it.
I'll help your mother
and your sister.
What are you doing?
- [bag landing]
- No!
I don't know what you think
you're doing, buddy...
- [Anna] Baby, please!
- [Brad] John!
- [Brad] John.
- [Anna] Please call 911,
or call Paula and...
[Brad] Run right now to
the house and bring the ladder!
You hear me? Right now?
Stop looking at me like that!
He did it.
- What?
- He did it.
Don't say that!
[Laurie]
He's not going to help us.
[Anna] Shut up, Laurie!
Why'd you do it?
You're in so much trouble,
little man.
So much trouble!
Go bring
the fucking ladder, John!
Brad, please!
No!
Where're you going?
John!
[Pete]
Luckiest asshole ever.
I don't think your guy
wants to play any more.
When are they coming back?
They don't know.
Luckiest motherfucking
asshole ever.
Wanna come for a few days?
Fuck! Third time
the net helped you!
You need help from
the net to beat me.
I'm playing against
you and the net.
What do you say?
You can stay in my room.
Oh, the loser's room.
Sounds great.
Fuck you.
[video game noise]
So, what do you say?
Ah, maybe the weekend.
Weekend sounds good.
I can pick you up
at the station.
I'm driving Dad's car.
- You're driving?
- Yeah.
- Then I'm staying.
- Fuck you.
Fuck you!
Come on Laurie,
just give me all you got.
- Come on.
- Dad.
Oh!
- I can't.
- You have to jump.
- Just a little jump.
- I'm done.
Why don't we take a break?
Come on, Laurie!
No, I'm coming down.
No, come on, don't.
Ahh!
Goddamnit!
Let me down.
- Fuck!
- Why did he do it?
I don't understand
why he did this.
Laurie.
Hey, hey, look at me.
I know you can do this.
Trust me.
I wasn't even close, Dad.
Just one more time.
Hey. Don't touch that.
What are you doing?
- Why?
- Don't do that. Don't!
- What?
- Don't!
We are not...
We are not eating here.
I'm starving, Dad!
Well, we can't stay.
We're not staying.
There's no way out.
We can't stay here.
Give me the bag.
[gulping]
[bag landing]
[♪ classical piano ♪]
[♪ continues ♪]
[music stops]
[thunder rumbles]
[♪ resumes ♪]
[rain falling]
[thunder cracking]
[♪ classical piano continues ♪]
[rain continues]
[♪ ends ♪]
[birds chirping]
[Anna]
What's going on, John?
Hey!
Talk to us.
Is someone making you do this?
Are they hurting you?
[Laurie]
It's so cold down here.
Oh!
Why don't you talk to us?
Please.
- At least...
- No.
[buzzing]
[Pete]
I think I'm scared.
- Of what?
- You... driving.
[car accelerating]
Dude, slow down.
Slow the fuck down!
[♪ classical piano ♪]
What is this bullshit?
No idea.
- Turn it off.
- No.
- How's your grandpa?
- Same.
My mom wants your mom
to call again.
Something about
eating broccoli.
Okay.
Have you ever tried
to drown yourself?
[choking, yelling]
So?
I was almost there.
- Did you see anything?
- No.
- Nothing?
- No!
- My turn.
- Okay.
Okay?
Just give me a second.
Remember, I start thrashing,
hold me a little bit longer.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Wait.
What's a little bit longer?
I don't know.
I don't want to know.
If I knew,
this wouldn't make sense.
- Okay.
- You ready?
Yeah.
[water gurgling]
[water bubbling]
[splashing]
[gasping, coughing]
Breathe. Breathe.
- What the fuck, man!
- So?
So what?
- Did you see anything?
- No.
- Nothing?
Nothing at all?
- No!
- Fuck!
Okay. What are we
supposed to see?
I don't know.
- You don't know?
- No.
- You ever seen anything?
- No!
- Okay, then, who told you...
- My friend, Ethan.
In Boston.
Not my friend really.
He saw the Virgin Mary.
- The Virgin Mary?
- Yeah, Jesus' mom.
- Wearing a swimsuit.
- Go fuck yourself.
It's true.
I want to go again.
[video game sounds]
I told you, doubles suck.
They suck 'cause you
don't know how to play it.
You want to hit every ball.
No, I don't.
There. That's my side.
I'm the left
and you're the right.
Ones that come to the middle
are mine.
That's where my forehand is.
I'm Roger fucking Federer!
My backhand is better
than my forehand.
[Announcer]
Game!
I hate you.
Don't look.
[plastic bag landing]
[sighing]
Oliver has to call the police.
Paula must be going insane.
I was supposed to help her
with catering.
And center pieces.
She begged me to help her.
I miss Josh.
You barely knew him.
Last month,
John asked me something.
It was a weird question.
And I think I...
What did he ask you?
He wanted to know
what it's like to be an adult.
He asked me what it feels like.
When do you stop being a kid?
It was...
you know,
one of those weird questions
he comes up with
every once in a while.
Like when he asked me...
why does the water in the pool
not feel like real water?
Why people are allergic to nuts
when nuts are a natural thing.
I didn't know what to tell him.
I have no idea
what it feels like
to be an adult.
I said something about...
responsibilities.
I told him
you never stop being a kid.
That you get older...
And grow up, but...
You're still a kid inside.
A kid with
more responsibilities.
I don't think he liked that.
I think he was...
you know, disappointed.
[spoon tapping]
- What are you doing?
- What?
What did you just do?
What?
Don't lick the spoon
and put it back in the jar.
- Why not?
- It's disgusting.
- You're disgusting.
- Your mom's disgusting.
- What did you just say?
- Nothing.
- What the fuck.
- What?
Licking the spoon
is not the same as spitting.
Yeah, it is.
- It's not.
- Yeah, it is.
It's not!
You're so dead.
Son of a bitch!
[clattering]
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
What should we do
with the other one?
Ohh!
[♪♪♪]
[drone buzzing]
Leave us alone!
[buzzing]
[Pete] Where we going?
Why are we here?
John?
I'm gonna miss the bus.
Hey!
Hey.
[car door beeping]
[beeping]
Hey.
[door closing]
What's this?
Money.
I know it's money,
but what is it for?
It's for you.
- It's for me?
- Yeah.
You can buy whatever you want.
Whose money is this?
Yours.
- You have an ATM card?
- Yeah.
This is crazy.
What do you want to buy?
Nothing.
What?
I don't want to buy anything.
Of course you do.
What do you want?
Nothing.
- This is a lot of money.
- Yeah.
Can I keep it?
It's yours.
Thanks.
So you don't want
to buy anything?
Nope.
[engine starts]
[♪♪♪]
[laughing]
Oww!
Is there anything you need?
Anything I can help you with?
- No.
- Are you sure?
Yes.
I mean, they've been gone
for a while now.
I'm fine.
Is someone coming
to clean the house?
Yes.
When?
Next Wednesday.
At two.
Okay then.
Wait.
Don't go.
Is there anything
you need, John?
Yes.
- What?
- Stay.
Stay a little while.
I don't have much time.
Just a little while.
Okay.
- What do you...
- Sit.
I'm 13 years old.
I know.
How old are you?
You don't ask that to a lady.
- Why not?
- You just don't. It's rude.
Okay.
My mom is 50.
I know.
We had a big party
in this house.
I was here.
Don't you remember?
Are you also 50?
What's with you today?
Nothing.
Are you?
Yes.
How does it feel?
- What?
- To be 50.
Not that bad, I must say.
At first I was terrified,
but now that it happened...
Don't you want the banana?
It's all right,
I already had lunch.
[sighing]
I have to go.
- Don't.
- John!
Please tell me
if you need anything.
I need something.
- Okay. What?
- I need you to stay.
Stay?
Sleep here.
We can watch a movie.
We have butter-flavored popcorn.
I can't stay here, John.
I have a family, things to do.
You know what?
Let me call your mother.
- Don't
- Yes, this is crazy.
They can't just
leave you here like...
Don't call her.
[cell phone ringing]
John.
She left her phone here.
They left in a hurry.
[car starts, drives away]
[insects chirping]
[Brad] Hey.
- What happened?
- What?
- When?
- Between you and John?
- What?
- Are you...
- Tell me what happened.
I don't know what you think
that you are...
You can tell me, Anna.
Turn that thing off.
- Just tell me.
- Turn it off!
- [Laurie] Hey, what's going on?
- Nothing.
Go back to sleep.
I need to know what happened
because something had to happen.
[Laurie] I'm thirsty.
Don't drink it all.
Nothing... happened.
[flashlight clicks off]
[footsteps approaching]
- Lily.
- What?
- I'm leaving.
- Where?
It doesn't matter.
I'll be fine, I just...
I want you to know that
you are on your own now.
- On my own?
- Yes.
I'm leaving
and I'm not coming back.
There's money for you
in a shoe box under the bed.
It should last you ten months,
maybe a year,
if you don't misuse it.
- Can I come with you?
- No.
Why not?
Because you're old enough
to be on your own now.
I'm 12.
- I thought you were 13.
- I'm 12.
Well...
You know Grandma
was 15 when she had me.
- I never met Grandma.
- Here, eat that.
You told me
we were having chicken.
We're not having chicken.
There's no time to cook
a chicken. I'm leaving soon.
- Don't.
- I have to.
- No, you don't.
- Yes, I do.
They're picking me up, Lily.
Who's picking you up?
That's none of your business.
- Dad?
- No.
- Stop it!
- Take me with you!
There is no room in the car!
I can ride in the trunk.
I can hold my breath
for almost a minute.
- Okay, promise me something.
- What?
Promise me
you will not quit school.
I can go to school
wherever you're going.
- You promise me.
- No!
You promise me or
I'm taking the money.
- Take it, I don't need it.
- Yes, you do.
- I have the house.
- What house?
This house.
You don't have this house, Lily.
Yes I do,
and I'm going to sell it.
We don't own the house, Lily.
We pay rent every month and
the money that I've left you
is enough so that you can
continue to pay rent
every month for the next year,
if you don't misuse it,
as I said.
- I'm going to misuse it.
- Well...
Do whatever you want,
it's your money now.
- And where will I go?
- When?
When the money's gone.
That's not my problem.
This is your life.
You get to make
your own decisions now.
I don't want to make
my own decisions.
Well, you have to.
Okay.
Enough.
That's enough.
You are not gonna stop me
from going.
I can work for you.
- What?
- I can do whatever you want.
I can be your assistant.
You are no assistant, Lily.
My daughter is
nobody's assistant.
You're nobody's assistant, Lily.
[footsteps]
[door opening, closes]
[door handle jiggles]
[doorbell rings]
[no audible dialogue]
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
[ball launcher fires,
racket stroke]
[Man] Come on, John.
[racket stroke]
[Man] Focus.
[ball launcher fires,
racket stroke]
[Man] You got this.
Let's go.
You're not.
- I am.
- You're not.
I'm ready.
How's your mother?
Good.
Still waiting on the checks.
You owe me two weeks.
I can pay you.
Are you following the diet?
Yes.
What'd you have for breakfast?
Low fat yogurt with cereal.
Everything okay at home?
Yes.
Let me know if you need
anything, I can help you.
Okay.
- You don't need to.
- I want to.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- You don't need to.
- I know I don't need to.
Just let me know how.
You know, it'd be a pity
for you to miss out...
- I'm ready.
- Stop saying that.
Okay.
You're not ready, John.
You need these last days.
You need to keep training.
You need me.
These qualies... are tough.
Very tough.
There are very good
players out there.
There are kids your age
who train every day,
every hour,
like professionals.
You know what I'm saying?
Do you?
Yes.
You know, I had my experience
with parents
who don't support
their children,
who don't believe
in their potential.
And let me tell you,
I shouted at them more than once.
This is your life, John.
This is what you want to do.
This could be who you are.
I want to.
You want to what?
I wanna be who I am.
Are you gonna ask your mother
to send me the checks?
Yes.
Today?
Great.
Finish picking up your stuff
and get outta here.
I need to use the court.
[sighing]
Did you hear that?
Yes.
It's like I have a dog inside.
A starving dog.
[sighing]
He has to bring us
something today.
When was the last time
he brought us anything?
Two days.
Almost two and a half.
[sighing]
He's trying to kill us.
He's gonna let us die here,
starve to death.
- Don't say that.
- Why not?
It's the truth.
What if something
happened to him?
What if he never comes back?
- Shh!
- [Anna] What?
No, not you, the dog.
I think it's the first time...
The first time I've been...
hungry.
Like really...
really hungry.
It's about to become...
a pain.
A new kind of pain.
I've never been hungry before.
I'm always hungry.
I hope nothing happened to him.
[Laurie] He's trying to
kill us, Mom.
[vomiting, spitting]
[water running]
[running footsteps]
Fuck!
[water splashing]
I thought you...
It's fine.
It's just a game.
- A game?
- Yeah.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
I'm working next door.
I came to see your dad.
See how he's doing.
- My dad?
- Oh, my God.
- Yes.
- He's not here.
- Your mom?
- No.
The garden looks like shit.
Do you want something to drink?
No.
Thank you, no.
I'll come...
I'll come back tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yeah, after work.
Do we owe you money?
- What?
- I have money.
No.
No money, John.
No money.
I just...
Tell him I said hi.
- I will.
- Okay.
You're a good kid, John.
Tonight I'm cooking risotto.
Great.
Good for you.
I'll see you later.
[blowing bubbles]
[chopping]
[indistinct dialogue on TV]
[sizzling]
[All] If blue bugs
bleed blue blood,
and black bugs
bleed black blood,
do blue black bugs bleed
blue black blood?
If blue bugs bleed blue blood,
and black bugs
bleed black blood...
[♪ classical music
playing in distance ♪]
[Brad] John.
Hey.
When are you gonna talk to us?
Come on, John.
You made your point.
We're not going to punish you.
What is it you want, John?
Help us.
Let us help you.
[Laurie]
Please, John.
We're so hungry.
It stinks down here.
This can't continue
much longer, John.
Someone out there,
somewhere...
they're gonna get worried
and call the police.
[rope sliding]
I tied it to a tree.
[grunting]
[rope snapping]
I cooked risotto.
You have forks.
You haven't tried the wine.
Your favorite.
[cork popping]
- Ahh.
- Mmm.
I have mine.
[sighing]
[cork popping]
Mmm.
Today I hit 300 serves.
[♪♪♪]
[wind blowing]
[Laurie]
John.
What time is it?
I don't know.
[Laurie]
Don't you have tennis soon?
Yeah.
Thanks for the risotto.
We really liked it.
I'm sorry.
For what?
I don't know.
[wind blowing]
[sighing]
- [zipper unzips]
- [whispering] What are you doing?
[whispering]
What do you think I'm doing?
- Don't do that.
- Why?
- Laurie...
- I told you, she's asleep.
- She can hear us.
- So let's be quiet.
[muffled moaning]
[metallic banging]
[metal scraping]
[screaming]
[insects chirping]
[vehicle approaching]
[beeping]
[♪♪♪]
[footsteps]
[birds chirping]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull