[music playing]
Do not.
Forget about that.
Sorry.
Hey, Uncle Guy,
how's it going?
Your father's
looking for you, Ali.
OK, Uncle Guy.
Ali!
You going to come over
for some dinner later?
Naw.
I got things to do.
So I'll catch you later.
- Sure.
- All right.
OK, man.
Hey, John.
Hey, Ali boy.
How you doing?
Good.
Your dad is in the back.
OK.
Hey, Dad, check it out.
That a boy, Ali.
We're going to see
your name in lights.
Al Stanco, drummer
extraordinaire.
That's when I retire.
Take this home to your
mother, all right?
But I'm supposed
to help you close up.
No, it's all right.
Tonight I close up by myself.
I got a few things to do.
All right?
OK.
You go right home
to your mother.
Take that.
Give me these.
All right.
Which way?
There we go.
Go.
Get out of here.
Hey.
What do you got?
Aw, Dad.
- Ali.
- Hi.
Hi, sweetheart.
Listen, I'm going
to play the numbers.
You tell your mother
I'll see her later.
All right, sweetheart?
- OK, Aunt Rose.
All right.
Bye, sweetie.
You're in big trouble, Ali.
Why?
Ali, get in here.
Mrs. Rizzo called
and said you and
that no good Nicky Vetrino were
throwing things from her roof.
Is that true?
[gunshot]
- What was that?
- That sounded like a gun.
Maybe a car.
I don't know.
[gunfire]
Ali, no!
Ali!
[music playing]
[buzzer]
[drumming]
Hey, Rivera, open
up the fucking door!
We know you're there.
MAN: How do you know?
Because I show your butt
ugly face looking at me
out the window, that's why.
MAN: He went out the back!
Last chance, asshole!
It's moving day.
Go to him.
He's at your old
man's place, isn't he?
I don't see why
we gotta do this.
Could be worse.
Could be the middle
of the winter.
Did you see that?
Right out the
freaking window, man.
These spics, they got
no heart at all, man.
I mean, we gotta send
these people a message.
It'll make it a lot
easier for us next time.
Smoke hash crack.
Smoke hash crack?
Can you believe
this shit, man?
Christ, man.
Someone's gotta do
something about this
freaking neighborhood, man.
Sweep all the shit
right out, man.
Oh, man!
No heart.
[music playing]
What are you doing?
Ali?
Are you going to
eat dinner, or what?
No, no.
I can't.
No, no, look.
Ali, I've got some
very good news for you.
Ali, I rented the
upstairs apartment.
That's great.
We'll talk about it later, OK?
No, we're not done yet.
Ali?
I'll see you later, all right?
Wait.
[non-english speech]
I'm going to leave something
for you on the stove, OK?
I know you will.
See you later, OK?
[music playing]
Yeah, Vinnie, how short is it?
Well, when was the last payment?
When?
Vig, when?
Last Tuesday?
Put him on the phone.
I want to talk to him.
Hey, Prince John.
Check it out.
What did he-- what did you do,
buck the white horse out front?
Yeah.
It's relieving itself on the
hood of your car right now.
Hey, hey.
Not my car, OK?
What do you want, JB and water?
No, a bloody Mary.
Make it hot, will ya?
Come on, Ali.
You know I hate making them--
Oh, it's a tough
life, isn't it, Louie?
Hi, Ali.
How are ya?
How's it hanging, Eddie?
Are you kidding?
I can't even find the
fucking thing anymore.
Maybe you should put
a string on it, huh?
Hi, baby.
Hey, sis.
How you doing?
Oh, I just love
a man in a tux.
Yeah, I guess that's
why you married Louie,
that frigging Fred Astaire.
Watch what you're
grabbing there, huh?
Be careful.
He's my brother,
for Christ's sake.
Yeah, it doesn't
matter nowadays.
Look at Joey and Tina Vanchi.
First cousins.
What happened to their kids?
One's a hairy dwarf, the other
one's a hairless monster.
That is an ugly
family, let me tell ya.
You guys are
sick, you know that?
Yeah, we're sick.
Get back in the kitchen
where you belong.
We're talking business here.
- See you later.
Gambling ain't
business, Louie.
Gambling?
Me?
Come on, baby.
Don't break my balls.
Sweetheart.
What a pain in the ass.
How was yesterday's number?
How the hell should I know?
It's in the paper.
You've got the paper,
you fucking genius.
Look it up.
Yeah, I think it was 107.
You think it was 107?
You're another big help.
Hey, Louie, is Nicky around?
In the corner.
They're lovebirds.
You're telling me shit.
That's what you're telling me.
- It ran late.
- What ran late?
What?
- The job.
The job?
You see something you like, huh?
I'm gonna rip your fucking
eyes out, you cocksucker!
Have the fucking money here!
I'm tired of this bullshit.
It's all bullshit, Nicky, OK?
I'm sick of it.
And don't give me
no fucking bullshit!
Ali boy.
Give me an ear.
Uh-oh.
Here he goes.
Watch their back, guys.
It's Eddie the hat.
Watch him move.
Look at him.
Come on.
Move, baby.
Hey, look at that Eddie.
Come on, it's--
What do you think I'm
sending you out on jobs for?
You think the fucking
Puerto Rican Tenants
Association asked for you?
You gotta find a
business to go into.
You understand?
Danny, come on.
That's a business?
Throwing people out on
the street like that?
Hey.
You know, every day you
remind me more and more
of your father.
Well, maybe if I got
to know him better,
that would mean
something more to me now.
He was too good.
He was too honest.
How the hell are you supposed
to make a living like that?
It's fucking fantasy land.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Danny.
Everything OK?
Angie treating you good?
- She's great.
Good.
Yeah, OK.
Um, hey, Danny, um-- can I have
a word with you for a second?
Dan, I I know I, uh--
I owe you Some money, but, uh--
I got something really
solid-- you know, 500.
I get off big.
I really do.
Solid.
Thanks, Dan.
Dan, I appreciate it.
[inaudible]
So, what do we got here?
Summer meeting, here?
Well, Al here ain't 100% happy
about the realities of running
a successful business.
What about you?
You got any complaints?
Well, while we're
on the subject,
you could stand to
pay a little better.
Al's very sensitive.
He's a musician.
All right, listen up.
I have a nice little
piece of business
coming down on Thursday.
I can use a couple
of guys with brains.
Brains are expensive.
Right, Al?
For $5,000 bucks, I
expect fucking genius.
Who we gotta kill?
Who do we gotta kill?
This fucking kid
don't stop, huh?
Thursday.
[opera singing]
Her name is Gabriela.
That's all I know.
Yeah, well, where's she room?
You got her references, or what?
References?
Ali, give me the olive
oil, please, you know?
It just don't feel
right to me, Aunt Rose.
Yeah, but it
feels right to me.
That apartment's been
empty for a long time.
She comes here, she
gives me three months
in advance, what am I gonna do?
Ask her questions?
That's great.
Great.
That's a good way to get
yourself killed, is what it is.
You're putting those
peppers too close together.
I don't think so.
So what is she?
Italian, Spanish, what?
She's from the old country.
Straight from the old county.
Well, what is she
doing here, then?
Listen, Ali, you're so
interested in this woman,
why don't you just go upstairs?
You ask her for yourself.
Please.
You gonna move
those peppers, or not?
No, Ali, I'm not
moving the peppers.
Not, not, not.
[music playing]
Hello?
[knocking]
Oh!
Jesus Christ.
Who are you?
I come from downstairs.
You deaf, or something?
I tried knocking.
Did I answer?
I just wanted to
introduce myself.
So, you must be the nephew.
Al.
Gabriela.
Gabriela--
That's right.
I live in the
basement apartment.
So, welcome to the neighborhood.
You a photographer?
No.
A filmmaker.
Oh, really?
Well, if you're ever
looking for a leading man--
well, anyway, I'm
sorry I bothered you.
I don't know.
She says her name's Gabriela.
I said, yeah, Gabriela what?
She says no.
I go look at the lease--
just Gabriela that's it.
She says she's from
the old country.
She could be from
Jersey, too, you know?
You never so.
I mean, I know
it's my aunt's house,
you know, and she
can do whatever
she wants with it, but--
I don't know.
She's just-- kind of weird.
How were her tits?
Big, or what?
Huh?
Her tits-- were
they big, or what?
I didn't notice.
Guy don't notice
a girl's tits?
If she ain't got none--
I mean, it's just
a rule of thumb.
I just don't like the
idea of someone else living
where I grew up, you know?
Oh, who's this coming in?
Par here?
- You mean Parente?
- Yeah, yeah.
He here.
- Uh, no, uh--
what do you want?
When's he coming in?
I couldn't tell you.
Who should I say
is asking for him?
Never mind.
I'll be back.
Who was that?
A cop?
Drug dealer.
You never know.
Hey, Louie, what gives?
Hey, who the fuck knows?
That's why I don't like
Parente hanging around here.
You never know who's
going to come in
and shoot up the fucking joint.
Come on, he's not that bad.
Danny's a good guy.
[music playing]
Thought you might be thirsty.
Look at this human
display case here.
You white boys get lost?
Yo, the pizza parlor's
around the corner.
Cessie, my man.
I dig that necklace, man.
You look like a goddamn
Aztec, or something.
Fucking Montezuma.
All you need is a
red hat and a gong.
You'd be all set.
I gotta talk to you
one of these days.
You can talk to me now, cuz.
No.
What?
You, me, and your machete?
A nice, long talk.
Anytime, anywhere, cuz.
Man, his sister is
some piece of ass, man.
I think she digs me.
I'll be right back.
[music playing]
And, you know,
I learned when we
were living way down on Grant
Street, in Little Italy--
my mother told me, she said,
make sure you use olive oil
in everything you cook.
But, you see, the
reason I do all this
is because olive oil
is good for everything.
Everything.
It goes down nice
and smooth, the food.
And then when it comes up, it
comes out on your complexion.
It makes it moist--
and it's attractive
to boot, right?
See?
All right.
Now, in the morning,
remember-- you have to put
a drop of olive
oil in your coffee
with the [non-english speech].
And at night, when you
go to eat the dessert,
make sure you have a drop of
olive oil on the ice cream.
Ali.
This is my nephew.
Come on, Al.
Al-- Ali-- come on.
Come in this picture with me.
Good morning, Alfonso.
Get that thing off me.
Hey, Gabriela's
making a movie.
Yeah, I know all about it.
We're all going
to be in the movie.
Not me.
I'm going to call the
family for Saturday,
and we're all going
to get together.
We're going to get you
all the material you need.
- Aunt Rose--
- I'm going to go call Angie.
The camera likes you, Alfonso.
How do you know
my name is Alfonso?
A little birdie told me.
So, what are we
supposed to do?
Just tell stories
about the old times.
Uncle Guy, you tell
the story about when
you saw Mr. Botzel with a goat.
- What?
- Goat.
The one with the bushy tail.
You remember, you told
him it was a pony?
You remember?
Come on.
So, uh, you're making
a movie about us?
No.
It's a movie about Brooklyn.
It's about families, really.
[inaudible]
Tri Television wants to show
what keeps them together.
Thanks.
You're talking,
uh-- you're talking
about the old Brooklyn, huh?
I mean, it's all changed.
It's not the same anymore.
Some things never change.
OK, so it's different?
How?
What do you remember?
Well, um--
I remember the time Vinnie
Correlli had this affair
with Mr. Gumali's daughter.
Yeah, in the
funeral parlor, right?
Right.
And he took the
dead guy's pants
by mistake because they were
doing it in the dressing room,
right?
And then they buried his
pants, and his wallet--
everything in it.
That-- that was pretty funny.
Yeah, but it wasn't
Vinnie Correlli.
It was Augie Bonacci.
No, no.
No Augie Bonacci.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Augie Bonacci?
He had the brother?
No, the one with the hairlip?
No, no, that wasn't a hairlip.
That's where his wife hit
him with the genoa salami.
You should have seen this woman.
[non-english speech] I mean,
she was built like Pavarotti.
She had a neck-- remember,
her neck was like-- it
was thicker than my waist.
Ba bum, ba bum, ba bum.
So, Mr. Parente, you
said it's not the same.
But you still didn't say how.
One word, honey.
Royalty.
Yeah.
It used to be that the
whole neighborhood was, uh--
one big family.
Everybody knew everybody.
We left our doors open at night,
our wallets on the counter.
Well, those days are gone.
Is that camera pointing
at me, or at you?
Now it's on me.
But it was on you.
- Her eye.
Excuse me.
Her eye is looking at you,
and the camera's at me.
Right?
- Talking to the--
You looking at me?
I don't know--
[laughter]
She's getting me nervous.
Who was I say-- oh, yeah.
It used to be that
the whole neighborhood
was one big family.
Everybody knew everybody.
And, uh-- you grew
up in one house.
And most of the time, your
kids would grow up there, too.
And their kids.
We all wanted the same thing.
Good friends, good food--
and, uh-- good, uh--
you know what I mean.
Tell her, guys.
You know I'm right.
And-- oh, hey, and nobody
ever left the neighborhood.
Of course, there
was no reason to.
We had it all here.
We looked out for each other.
Loyalty.
I'm getting nervous.
And I never get nervous.
Anyway, uh-- well, you
know what I'm saying.
Right, Guy?
Augie Bonacci's wife
used to go into the bakery
and order 2 pounds
of cannolis a day.
Remember that?
Yeah.
She used to make you
carry them home for her.
Yeah, I remember.
Oh, Grandma Stanco's cannolis.
They were the best.
Those were the cannolis.
Hey, whoa, Rose.
Rose.
Yours weren't too bad, either.
You know, Ali, your
aunt Rose and I,
we shared a cannoli or two on
a couple of those [inaudible]
lazy summer nights.
Now we know, eh?
What are you talking about?
Are you kidding me?
Wait, wait just a minute.
They were the best damn
pastries in Brooklyn.
Stop it, already.
Shut up.
Yeah, I remember the
first time I saw Angie.
She was behind the
counter at the bakery.
She was wearing that
cute little white apron.
Lots of baby fat.
But that was the past.
Past.
We think about the future now.
Right, Guy?
Al, she's nice.
She'd be good for ya.
- Angie, please.
- Hey, Al.
Ali.
[non-english speech]
You know, we shouldn't
be telling her all
this stuff about our family.
- Why not?
I like her.
She reminds me of your
mother, when we first
came from the old country.
She's something different, Ali.
Yeah, but she's not.
She has nothing to
do with our family.
And Danny was right.
Family used to be
about neighborhood.
People you grew up
with were the only ones
you should really trust.
No, no, no.
I don't-- no.
I trust who I trust, and I don't
care if she lives in my house.
[non-english speech]
You owe me money, and
I'm giving you more, huh?
I must be [non-english speech].
Don't worry, Danny.
I'm-- I'm good for it.
Thanks.
Hey, I got a tax
check coming soon.
You'd better get a new line.
That one's got a hair on it.
Yeah.
Uh, Louie, look, if you
really want to pay me back,
I got a proposal for you.
I have some associates, uh, who
need a comfortable little place
to direct their business.
Well, I'd consider
it a favor to me
if you make the bar available.
You talking about drugs?
Watch your fucking mouth.
And show some respect.
I'm talking about friends.
Friends, Louie.
Danny, I can't.
I mean, this--
this place is my--
Give me a 77.
Come on.
I love these windows.
Remember when Jeannie
Papsadel lived next door?
We used to look
up her dress when
she was waiting for the bus.
Polka dot panties.
And little curly blonde
hairs on the fringe.
20 years ago, bro.
I got a photographic memory.
Yeah, more like pornographic.
- Hey, that's good, too.
- How's this shirt?
Is it good?
Is this--
Yeah-- it's out of fashion.
Sure, it looks great.
Hey, check this out, man.
What?
Oh, is that the
girl from upstairs?
AL: Gabriela.
Gabriela?
Sounds like a high
class guinea to me.
Yeah, well, she's
weird is all I know.
Don't matter, bro.
You gotta jump on
that shit, man.
That's prime cut, baby.
If you don't, I will.
- Come on.
Let's go.
Piece of ass, man.
That's the last of the minks.
Let's go.
Come on.
- Hold on.
What are you doing?
Let 'em finish up.
They'll go inside, they'll
sign off with the foreman,
and we'll grab 'em.
I ain't waiting around here
for another fucking hour, bro.
Hey-- oh, you're an idiot.
You're a regular freaking idiot.
Nobody argues with
a fucking gun, man.
Yeah, except someone
with a bigger one.
What, do you
mean like this one?
[gun cocking]
- Jesus Christ.
What, are you fucking--
- Relax.
Relax.
Hey.
We gotta stick together.
You hear me?
I look out for you,
you look out for me.
So let's go.
Come on.
Fuck me.
[gunshot]
Good news, guys!
Quittin' time!
Yee-haw!
Yeah, baby!
Un-fucking-believable.
It worked, didn't it?
Besides, anybody can
just jump in and drive
the fucking thing away.
Hey.
You want to get ahead
in this business,
you gotta make a
name for yourself.
[gunfire]
Oh, fuck!
What--
Mother fucker!
[gunfire]
Cocksucker!
What the fuck was that?
One of them jerks must
be stuck in the back.
You're going to make a
name for yourself, all right.
Biggest fucking
idiot in Brooklyn!
Put the goddamn
thing away, will ya?
Yeah, what are you, my
fucking mother, or what?
Shit, I'm empty.
Yeah, well, you'd better
hope to God he is, too.
Maybe I got the prick.
Hey!
MAN: What?
You listen to me!
I'm gonna open this
door up further, OK?
And then you are
going to take off.
And you're going to run your
ass out of here in 5 seconds.
And if you do, we won't
shoot your ass, OK?
Go.
Come on.
No!
Nicky, no!
Come on!
Nicky, what the
fuck are you doing?
[shouting]
Nicky!
That's enough!
Enough, already, all right?
- Get the fuck up, huh?
- No, Nicky!
That's fucking enough!
- You motherfucker!
- No!
No, no!
Shrimpy motherfucker!
I'll kill you!
Let's get the hell outta here!
Come on!
Get in the fucking
cab, will you?
Get in the cab!
No!
[groaning]
How do you like that?
Go.
Come on!
Shit.
Nine.
50.
Like I said, five grand each.
When are you gonna wise up, huh?
I don't need a clown
for a right hand man,
with blinking Christmas
lights, and pinwheels
sticking out of his ass.
That's not in my best
interest, you understand?
What are you talking about?
I didn't do nothing.
- Yah?
Then how come I got 30
mink coats with fucking
bullet holes in 'em?
Huh?
maybe I can sell 'em as
real soft toilet paper?
I even gotta take a
discount on the truck, which
was all shot to shit, too.
The next fucking bullshit
stunt you pull like that,
I'm not going to be sticking
my knife in a fucking table.
You understand?
Take it.
Come on, you earned it.
Let's take a little
walk outside.
That's what you call
employee management.
It's the only thing
he understands.
He's gotta learn.
He's loyal.
Yeah, and he's tough,
and he's street smart,
but he's got no fucking brains.
He's a lowlife, and
he always will be.
Look, I like the kid,
but I ain't making
no future plans with him.
You're the man.
- Naw.
Not me, Danny.
- Listen, listen.
- No, no--
Hey.
What are you telling
me, all right?
You're practical,
you keep your head.
You never jump before you
know where you're gonna land.
That's what it takes.
I mean, look around.
Look.
Everything's changing.
I mean, spics jumping off
the boat every minute.
Niggers marching up and down
the streets like they own it.
Well, the old days are over.
You know that.
That's OK.
That's OK, though.
Change equals opportunity.
They all want something, Ali.
You know what I'm saying?
They get the money for
it one way or another.
Now, somebody's gotta
control the flow.
Why not me?
Why not you, huh?
Look, Danny, I know--
I know you're looking out
for my best interests.
I know that.
I mean, you've always
been there for me.
But I'm not a businessman.
I'm just not.
You know, I got my drums.
That's enough for me.
Hey, fuck your drums.
You can play the bongo with
your dick, the kind of money
you'll be making here.
Listen, I promised
your father I was
gonna see you set up proper, and
making something of yourself.
So I don't want no more
fucking discussion.
Humor me.
Together, you and me--
we're going.
Danny?
You got a telephone call.
I'll see you here
tomorrow night, OK?
Yeah.
Aunt Rose?
Aunt Rose, I gotta run.
[music playing]
You know, that act
with the camera's
getting pretty old, OK?
But I'm getting
a lot of material.
You're getting
a lot of bullshit,
is what you're getting.
You'll end up with a
feature length documentary
on the art of bullshit.
You really think
they buried somebody
else in Augie Bonacci's pants?
Please, spare me.
Some of it must be true.
They was just having
fun with you, that's all.
They don't know nothing
about the real Brooklyn.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you don't know anything
about the rest of the world,
so we're even.
You're pretty good, you know?
Thanks.
Except you play
with no passion.
Well, you know, Parent
has a cleaner sound.
You say Parente to some of
these white bread snobs,
and right away they got
you tied to the mob.
Parent has, uh-- warmth to it.
Like a mom and pop operation.
I'm not going to talk into
that thing, you know that?
Why not?
You talked that night.
And did I say anything?
So, now, what do
you want to ask me?
Well, they tell
me that you are--
They?
Who's they?
Just the people I--
They got names?
You see, that's what
I'm talking about.
In the old days,
people would never
talk shit behind your back.
How do you know they
were talking shit?
I was born in this
neighborhood, sweetheart.
And while I feel a
deep moral obligation
to improve my own community,
some people resent my methods.
Don't ask me why.
Maybe it's because some people
are losing their apartments,
and businesses?
What can I do about that?
That's the American way.
The food chain, see?
We all feed off each other.
Big fish eat little fish.
And you are the big fish?
I ain't been eaten yet.
What the hell does this have
to do with your little movie?
You are one of the
leaders of the community.
You say you don't like
what's happening to it.
That people shouldn't leave.
But what do you do about it?
What do I do about it?
I take care of my own.
And what if, uh--
Al wanted to leave?
This is his home.
This is where he belongs.
But what if he wanted to?
You're a very
attractive woman.
You know that?
You know that.
Yeah, of course you know that.
And it just so happens
that I have a weakness
for attractive women.
As a matter of fact, I'd do
almost anything for them.
So I'm gonna do
something for you.
I'm going to give
you some advice.
If you don't want to get eaten,
don't swim with big fish.
The interview is over.
Gabriela.
Bonjourno.
[drumming]
ROSE: Ali!
Cut it out!
Enough!
What would you
say if I asked you
to do the music for my movie?
Come on, I ain't no composer.
How do you know?
Are you afraid?
Just like you are afraid to
show me the real Brooklyn?
Hm?
What?
Think I'll bite?
[music playing]
Somebody's going to
rip that thing off.
Look, listen.
They are just like you.
- Let's go.
- No.
They are wonderful.
I said, let's go.
What's the matter with you?
You're not prejudiced,
are you, Alfonso?
No.
I just got sense enough to know
when I'm in enemy territory.
That's all.
What's the matter, Louie?
It won't turn over.
Look at this new
friggin' battery.
I'm ruining my manicure.
I used to be a mechanic.
You were?
What, you didn't know that?
I thought you knew everything?
I want you to reconsider
my proposal, Louie.
Aw, come on, Danny.
I can't do that.
I run-- I run a clean place.
I want to keep it that way.
Clean fucking business?
I was clean enough
when you were riding
on the balls of your
ass, looking for a loan
to get started.
The money wasn't too
fucking dirty then, huh?
Mikey?
Try it now.
You're welcome.
Look, Danny-- Danny, please.
Come on, Danny.
What are you doing, huh?
Come on.
It's me, Louie.
I don't know who
the fuck you are,
but you ain't no friend of mine.
And you obviously don't
know the fuck I am.
I'm always looking out
for your welfare, Louie.
And what do I get in return?
Nothing.
No respect.
- Danny, I
Nothing.
No, you use me.
You use me.
And then I ask you for a favor.
Please!
You call that respect?
Danny-- please, Danny.
No, Danny, please!
No!
Please?
You're asking for help?
That don't seem fair, you know?
When I asked you for help,
you told me to go fuck myself.
I mean, it's gotta
be a two way street.
Gotta be.
- Danny, I'm family!
Family my fucking ass.
Angie's family.
You're just a fucking leach.
No.
No!
Louie!
What, are you gonna screw
around with the car all day?
I got customers inside.
It's all right.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's all right, Ang.
Look, we're doing a
little business here.
He'll be right in.
Be right out, hon.
I think we've got everything
straightened out now, don't we?
Yeah.
So, what kind
of music you want
for this film of yours, huh?
Something with drums.
Well, I kinda figured that.
So, how'd you get started with
all this movie stuff, anyway?
Hey, small freakin' world.
Yeah, a little too small.
Gabiriela, this is Nicky.
Is this one of your
prejudiced friends?
Prejudiced?
Who, me?
I just don't like niggers.
This is Miranda.
Hi.
How's your brother
Cessie doing?
Oh, he's good.
As a matter of fact,
he bought me this ring.
You dating him, or something?
I'll get you
something nice, baby.
I'll get you a nice
ankle bracelet.
She's got great ankles.
So, I hear you're making movies.
I could be a movie
star, you know?
I even hung with De
Niro for a while, there.
He bumped into him
coming out of a restaurant.
He never stops talking about it.
Yeah, whatever.
Excuse me.
Listen, papi, I'm gonna
go powder my nose, OK?
Powder everything, cause
I'm gonna be leaving prints.
Don't miss me.
What the fuck is
the matter with you?
What are you, crazy?
I don't know who's going
to cut your balls off,
Donna or Cessie.
I like living on
the edge, my man.
You know that.
Besides, who's gonna tell 'em?
Here.
What's that?
It's your half of
the five from Parente.
Hey-- we stick together, bro.
No matter what.
My man.
Yes.
Nick is really something.
I must get him on tape.
Yeah, well, you'll get
more than you bargained for.
Believe me.
And Parente?
He is trouble, no?
Naw.
He's a good guy.
And so you are going
into business with him?
I don't know.
I haven't decided yet.
Sit down.
Relax.
You know, sometimes, late
at night, I come out here,
and there's nobody around.
And it's real peaceful--
I start to think that maybe the
world's not so bad after all,
you know?
Do you have a
girlfriend, Alfonso?
Please, enough with
this interview already.
Why don't you want anyone
getting close to you?
You know, I'm gonna start
charging you by the question.
I'm the one who
should be asking.
Now, I don't know
nothing about you.
Except that your-- your
mother was an artist.
That's all I know.
What about your father?
Hm?
Where's he?
What does he do?
Tell you what--
you don't interview me,
I won't interview you.
Deal?
Fair enough.
Walk me to my door.
Come on.
How do you like the apartment?
You know, we used
to live up here.
I know.
Sometimes I can feel your
spirit moving through the rooms.
It's very restless.
You know what this is, here?
This is me growing up.
My father used to--
he'd make a big deal about
measuring me, you know?
I was like, five here.
Six.
10.
11.
I should, uh--
Mm-mm.
You don't have to go.
[music playing]
All right, ante up five.
- Replay.
- Jacks are better.
Don't make any difference.
He wins, anyway.
This prick.
What about Ali and this girl?
They were out last night.
He was showing her the sights.
She's asking a
lot of questions?
Well, she's making
a movie, or something.
Well, maybe you'd better
keep your eye on her.
One.
What?
See what they're up to.
How many?
I told you, she's
making a movie.
Yeah, and I told you
to keep an eye on her.
Find out where she's from, who
she's with, and what she wants.
All right?
Want me to check her for
crabs, too, while I'm at it?
Very fucking funny.
- All right, all right.
- What do you got?
- You're the boss.
- What do you got, huh?
- Pair of aces.
- Pair of aces?
What do you got?
Sixes, and a straight--
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
The fuck you doing?
Hey!
Ali boy, come here.
I want you to do a
little job for me.
All right.
I want you to go over
to [inaudible] bridge.
Don't jump.
[inaudible]
And then the fourth--
the Groovy Groove.
Make it 1,000--
- What the hell are you doing?
- Hang on.
I can't believe you.
This is getting out of control!
Excuse me, I think this
is still my fucking phone.
Come on!
Angie's getting ready to have
a baby in a couple of months,
you're throwing it all away.
Hey, would you
mind your business?
I know what I'm doing!
How you doing?
Hey, how you doing?
Listen, uh, Mr. Parente, he'd
like to start the remodeling,
you know?
So, uh, he'd like to
get the inspections
cleared up soon as possible.
Yeah, it's a big job.
I gotta tell you, this
building don't look too
good from where I'm standing.
Yeah, well, uh--
do what you gotta do.
All right?
I'll wait for you outside.
I'll have the building's
safety certified
by tomorrow afternoon.
It's a pleasure doing
business with you.
All right.
What are you doing here?
I was in the
neighborhood, and I thought
maybe I could get a ride home.
Yeah, well, you
shouldn't be drifting
around out here by yourself.
You could get yourself
in some serious trouble.
How do they keep their spirit?
They buy it.
$10 bucks a rock.
When they're all drugged up,
they don't care about nothing.
What are you looking
at me like that for?
Hey, I'm a realist, you know?
You see how they live.
Drug dealing, burnt
out buildings.
They trash their own homes.
You don't see any of that
in my neighborhood, do you?
That's cause we have pride.
And what about the mafia?
Hey!
My family has always
earned an honest living,
you understand me?
Until now.
Because now your uncle
Danny controls everything.
Whoa, whoa.
First of all, he's not my uncle.
He's a family friend.
And you are just a
stranger, so don't act
like you know everything, OK?
Danny's a businessman.
That's all he is.
But you work for him.
I help him out
whenever I feel the need.
And that means throwing
people out into the street?
You don't know
nothing about me.
So tell me.
I want to know.
YOUNG AL: Hey,
Dad, check it out.
AL'S FATHER: That a boy, Ali.
We're gonna see
your name in lights.
Al Stanco, drummer
extraordinaire.
YOUNG AL: Hey, John.
JOHN: Hey, Ali boy.
How you doing?
YOUNG AL: Good.
JOHN: Your dad is in the back.
YOUNG AL: OK.
Dad?
AL'S FATHER: No, it's all right.
Tonight I'll close up by myself.
Cakes and pies.
Over here.
And down here, all the
pastries, eclairs, Napoleons.
And all the breads.
[inaudible]
Right here you
had your cannolis.
The best around.
And the cookies went over here.
$1.50 a pound.
And you'd weigh them over
here, and box 'em up.
You see this?
My mother used to--
you know, she used to
ask Miss Savors for a--
a, uh-- tomato plant,
and tie 'em up.
You come back
here a lot, Alfonso?
AL'S FATHER: Go right
home to your mother.
Go, get out of here.
Hey.
YOUNG AL: Dad?
See this?
That's a bullet that missed.
One out of the four.
She spent hours trying to get
the blood out of the tiles.
Scrubbing and scrubbing.
There's still a
trace here and there.
Didn't even take nothing.
Shot my father
for the fun of it.
That's how they are.
They?
Who's they?
You know.
How do you know he was black?
What do you think
he was, an Eskimo?
You just assume--
My uncle Guy was at
the deli down the block.
Saw the guy running away.
Ran right past him.
That doesn't mean--
He was black, he
had a gun in his hand.
Case closed.
But they never caught him?
The police never caught him.
But he was taken care of.
Oh, you sneak around
like a little thief.
Where's Ali?
I don't know.
He went out.
He's coming back at 5:30.
We're going to eat some scampi.
You want to join us?
Oh, naw.
Too busy.
Listen, when are you going
to settle down with Donna?
There's only one woman
in the world for me.
You know that?
They don't make 'em
like they used to, Rosa!
[non-english speech].
You're crazy.
Get outta here.
You're busy?
Go.
[non-english speech]
Tell Ali I'll give
him a call later.
All right.
This is my past.
Empty room, bare walls.
Topped off with the
blood of my father.
I get so angry, Gabriela.
I get so angry when
I think about it.
I never spoke to anybody
like this before.
It's OK.
I understand.
Put the others in, and then
at night, when you have--
MAN: No trouble.
Pay every month.
And once we miss--
[whistling]
What do you think?
For the movie.
I mean, it's still rough,
and everything, but--
you know, I'm gonna work on it.
It's beautiful, Alfonso.
Why do you keep
calling me that?
It's your name, isn't it?
Only one person
ever called me that.
Hungry?
[car horn]
Hey.
Hey, Ali, I gotta talk to you.
What's up?
Not here.
ANNOUNCER: They come over
the top of the stretch
off a half in 45 seconds flat.
Brazen Prospector, and
now Dances With Fire,
Dancers With Fire on
the outside by a head.
Brazen Prospector, Ice Agent,
trying to close at the top--
Pick up.
Come on!
Come on.
ANNOUNCER: Here comes--
We got it.
ANNOUNCER: Moreno.
Yes.
In one--
[inaudible].
He came outta nowhere.
Keep an eye on the place.
Hey, baby.
Just need to use your VCR, OK?
What?
Let me call you back, all right?
- If this some kinda bullshit.
- Just watch.
Just watch.
Sit down.
What are you doing?
Not now, baby, OK?
Yes, now.
And don't give me
that baby shit.
You can't just waltz in
here and use my things.
This street-- we live.
All of us.
Together.
No trouble.
Pay every month.
But once we miss--
they throw us out.
GABRIELA: Who throws you out?
Parente.
Street crap.
And this-- this is my shit.
This is the best.
Fuck you up real good, baby.
GABRIELA: And Mr.
Parente's aware of this?
Aware?
Yes, I do believe Mr.
Parente is very much aware.
Mr. Parente?
Parente?
Shit.
He runs the whole goddamn thing.
Fucking got his fingers
in everybody's pockets.
You see that blood right there?
Right there?
That's his blood.
Believe that.
Nice little movie, huh?
All that's missing
is a scene with me,
you, and Parente walking
hand-in-hand to jail.
Did you ever find
out her last name?
Maybe it's Jackson.
Or Jones.
I got nothing.
King, jack-- ace high.
Pair of threes.
I win again.
[inaudible].
Where'd you steal that?
We gotta talk, Danny.
Alone.
I it's time for me to run my
own business in my own way.
Your business?
That's right.
All my life, everybody's
been breaking my balls.
But not anymore.
I'll keep this between us
so as not to embarrass you,
but this is my business,
and nobody's going
to break my balls here anymore.
You understand?
There's one problem, Louie.
This is my building.
Yeah, well, when my
lease runs out in 10 years,
then you come talk to me.
Oh.
Until then, I'm calling
the shots around here.
And that don't include
catering to you,
or any of your scumbag friends.
Hey, Richie-- get
rid of that tail, huh?
What's happened?
I don't understand.
Want you to do the
music for my film?
I do.
Don't bullshit me, Gabriella!
I already seen your film, OK?
You took me for some stupid
greaseball guinea who'd believe
anything you told him, right?
Listen to me.
Now I know why you wanted
fucking Danny on tape.
What did you expect me
to do, hand you Parente's
head on a silver platter?
You want me to betray my
family, and my friends the way
you betrayed me?
Huh?
Why did I trust you?
Jesus Christ!
That was fucking stupid.
[non-english speech].
You're right about one thing--
I didn't really come here to
make a movie about Brooklyn.
I told myself I
did, but deep down
I really came here to meet you.
Oh, don't give me
that shit, Gabriela.
OK?
Don't even bother.
Bam.
Four.
And you know when you
hear shots, you go down.
That's what you learn in a war.
You go down.
You don't try to be a hero.
Curiosity killed the cat.
So I go down to the
floor, and I wait.
And it gets real quiet, until
I hear someone screaming.
Then I hear footsteps
coming out of the baker.
Fast.
So I stand up, and there he
goes, running by like the devil
himself.
Diabolo.
The black devil.
I make my living
talking to people.
I know when someone's
holding back.
There is something
about your father.
Hey.
Shut up already about my family.
Keep your lying
ideas to yourself.
Yeah, I know why you don't
want to talk about your father.
All that time I was stupid
enough to tell you everything.
You couldn't tell me nothing.
What's the matter, you
can't face what you are?
Because to me you're still a--
Go on.
Say it.
What do you think?
You think I never
heart it before?
I grew up in this neighborhood.
That's right-- just
a few blocks away.
I'm proud of my past.
My father was a good man.
A man who cared
about his family,
and stood by his principles.
Just like yours.
You don't know
nothing about my father.
You're wrong.
You and I are so close.
You were 12 when your
father was killed.
I was only five.
We were sent to Italy
to live after he passed
away, until everyone forgot.
My mother told me the
truth just before dying.
And that's why I came back here.
Back to where my
father was killed.
You see-- they said a black man
shot a white man in his bakery.
So, a black man had
to die in return.
If it was the same black
man who did it, fine.
If not-- well, they're
all the same, aren't they?
Hm?
It was my father, Ali.
My father, my mother, me.
We all paid for
your father's death.
And now just get out.
I don't want to talk
about this anymore.
What's going on?
What happened?
[non-english].
Al?
Aw, you mother-- dirty--
[sigh]
This fucking neighborhood.
[car starting]
Thank you.
Huh?
Louie.
[gunfire]
Give us this day
our daily bread,
and forgive us our
trespasses, as we forgive
those who trespass against us.
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
Amen.
Eternal rest grant
unto him, oh Lord,
and let perpetual
light shine upon--
Fucking Louie, man.
Who would have believed it, huh?
REVEREND: And the souls of all--
I always knew there would
be trouble sooner or later.
Those niggers are
always causing trouble.
It's fucked up.
Louie had that big
payday with the ponies.
They probably found out he
was carrying extra dough.
Bastards.
Motherfucking animals.
Those We should hang
them by their balls.
I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
Come here.
You got a problem
with me, Uncle Guy?
Huh?
He was family, Danny.
Family.
This is the old way.
This is not right.
It never was.
Get the fuck out of my face
before I put you in a fucking--
get the fuck outta here.
Get outta here.
I have nothing to say to you.
You're Parente's boy now.
Your father's son anymore.
Please, Uncle Guy.
Don't give me that shit, OK?
Now, who are you to talk?
You've taken as much from
Parente as any one of us.
No, never.
Not a dime I took from him.
Not a penny.
Not like you.
Louie made that mistake, but
he tried to make it right.
He was a good boy.
He was like your father.
Too honest.
He stood up to him.
Not like you.
What are you talking about?
He pays you to be
blind, doesn't he?
Well, not me.
I know what I see.
Hey, if you're
so goddamn noble,
how can you just walk away?
If you're so much
better than him,
and me, and all the rest of us,
why don't you stand up to him?
Tell me what you know.
I want the truth, god dammit.
We'd better get going.
And it gets real quiet.
And I hear screaming,
and then footsteps
coming out of the bakery fast.
So I stand up.
And there he goes, running
by like the devil himself.
Diabolo.
A black devil.
- Right.
A black man.
Black.
A black mask.
A mask?
GUY: Your father was in trouble.
He wouldn't allow them to use
the bakery for their purposes.
Danny?
What are you doing?
He was an honest man, so
he had to be taken care of.
It's going to come
get this, Danny?
Danny-- we're family, Danny.
We're like family, Danny.
[gunfire]
Poor Vincenzo.
Hard head.
Like cement.
He wouldn't listen.
Parente was paying his dues.
He didn't have the
courage to refuse.
You knew this?
All these years, you knew this?
I came from the old country.
It was our way.
Silencio.
And in my stupidity, I thought
it was the right thing.
Now?
Now I know better.
He can't do anything to me.
But it's too late.
I'm sorry.
It's too late.
Where did you get this?
Uncle Guy gave it to me.
He said you should have it.
Where are you going?
I gotta get back to the wake.
This music is driving me nuts.
Stop it.
He was always
blowing his stack
about one thing or another.
Sure, he'd get all pissed off--
and then an hour later,
it was all forgotten.
He was a good man.
I'm saying right now, no
matter who winds up running
this place, it'll always
be called [inaudible]
as long as I'm around.
Let's hope that's
not very long.
Where You been?
You get lost coming
from the cemetery?
I've been talking
to some ghosts.
Louie's ghost.
My father's ghost.
They had some interesting
things to say about you.
Some gotti better get
my man here a drink.
He's seeing things.
No, I'm seeing
you real clear now.
What's the matter, huh?
Huh?
You're acting all stupid.
Well, I was just wondering--
a man who can kill
his own people--
his own kind-- and then laugh
and drink at their funerals--
a man that rotten--
how come I can't smell him
when I'm standing so close?
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey, what the fuck?
Hey!
What the fuck are you doing?
Stop it.
That's a nasty cough
you got there, son.
You should take some medicine.
What, the same medicine
you gave my father?
Huh?
I'm a busy man, Ali.
You got something
to say, then say it.
Yeah, I got something to say.
When I'm good and ready.
Why didn't I hear
about these tapes?
I told Ali.
I thought he was your man?
Is he going to talk?
Sure, he'll talk.
He's a fucking weasel.
We gotta take care of him.
He spit at you, Danny.
We all saw it.
Just sit there and
shut the fuck up!
Nicky, I want you
to take care of it.
Me?
And the broad, too.
I never liked her
from the start.
You gotta trust your instincts.
Why are you sending me?
Because it's time for
you to make your bones.
You know how I
feel about you--
Good.
Then you take him out tonight.
And I want you to sever
his motherfucking eyeballs,
and I want you to put them
right here, on this table.
What if he stays home?
Do you need a fucking diagram?
No.
I don't.
Nicky-- Nicky,
where are you going?
You know, that prick's
no bargain, either.
You know what I'm thinking?
Maybe you should not out
two birds with one stone.
Cessie.
Come here.
Sit down.
You have a sister.
What's her name?
Uh-- Miranda?
Yeah.
Uh-- would you like to know
what she's been up to lately?
Yeah.
She's been seeing Nicky.
Naw.
Yeah.
That scumbag
bastard [inaudible]..
She has been seeing him.
Some people told me.
I didn't see it with my own
eyes, but good people told me.
You screw some
[inaudible] spic and then
you come back to my bed?
I hope he fucking kills you.
I hope he does!
You hope who kills me?
Your fucking brother
in law, Cessie.
He's coming for
your ass right now.
Parente told him everything.
That prick is dicking
us every which way.
Fucking incredible, man.
Come on.
Let's get outta here.
I'll lead him down
towards Palmer Street.
Give me a few minutes,
then you head north, OK?
I'm going to go with you.
Give me a break, will ya?
You trying to
be a hero, Nicky?
You don't worry about me, Cuz.
Cause that'll be the day I run
scared from some PR coke head.
You be careful.
You and that freaking camera.
Man.
Nicky!
[gunfire]
Stay here.
Stay here!
Nicky!
DONNA: Nicky!
Jesus Christ, Nicky.
You and me, bro.
Nicky!
No!
Baby!
Nicky!
Jesus Christ!
Baby?
Nicky!
[crying]
Nicky always was a
useless motherfucker.
At least he had a heart.
It's OK.
Why don't you go home
and change your clothes?
Come on, you're
beginning to stink.
Vinny.
Vinny, please.
Come on.
So I guess that leaves
me and you, huh?
That's what you said
the day my father died.
You look a little
nervous, Ali.
Just sit down.
Have a break.
No, I don't drink
with scumbags.
It's a personal thing.
No, I'd say that's you.
You're the worst kind
of scumbag there is.
You sold me out.
Sold me out for a
little taste of pussy.
And a bitch with
nigger blood, no less.
She's better than
you'll ever be.
Because you're nothing.
Nothing.
You're a lying, low life,
gutless sack of shit.
You killed my father, your
own best fucking friend.
I just want you to
admit what you did.
You sure?
Oh, yeah.
That's all I want.
But that puts me in a very
awkward position, doesn't it?
[gunfire]
Peekaboo.
I see you.
Scumbag, huh?
Now look at you.
Look.
Just like the rat
bastard you are.
Why don't you cut the shit,
and do what you gotta do?
Open your mouth real wide.
I'm going to send one in.
[gunshot]
Don't fucking move!
Aw, shit!
Shit!
- Don't move!
Don't move!
Sit down.
You motherfucker.
Sit the fuck down.
What's the matter, Danny?
You look a little nervous.
Why don't you just
skip the bullshit?
We can make a deal here.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
You know what I got going.
Real estate, loan
shark, and drugs.
Oh, you-- I got deals
going everywhere.
You want in?
Whatever you want.
There's enough money
in it for everybody.
Let's just forget about
all this bullshit,
and we'll start fresh.
I'll take good care of ya.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
That's right, yeah.
You told my pop that you
would take good care of me.
That's right.
But let me ask you
something-- was
this before you blew his
fucking brains out, or after?
Ali!
That was business.
If it wasn't me, it just
would've been somebody else.
Did you kill Nicky?
Yeah.
Did you kill Louie?
I ripped his fucking
eyeballs out, and I ate 'em!
Did you kill my father?
Yeah, I killed him!
Big fucking deal!
Everybody dies.
That's just the way it is.
That's a part of life.
It's a part of growing up.
Hey, you want to show me?
Shoot!
Huh?
Just don't waste
my fucking time!
Yeah.
Yeah, I figured.
You didn't have
the fucking balls.
No!
Don't shoot me!
Don't shoot!
[siren]
Too late.
Always shoot first.
Talk is just bullshit, Ali boy.
You get that?
Get what?
Huh?
Yeah.
I got it.
[screaming]
You forgot to wear
your mask this time.
- Hey, Al.
- Where you going?
We're going to go to Coney
Island for a couple of hours.
You gonna be OK?
Yeah, of course.
I got Aunt Rose in the kitchen.
You kiddin' me?
Hey, come here.
Give me a kiss.
You gonna give your
uncle a kiss, or what?
All right, listen, you have
fun in Coney Island, OK?
Now listen, don't eat
nothing, whatever you do.
Because we got something
special planned for dinner.
Oh, really?
Like what?
I'm not going to tell you.
Then it's not a surprise, is it?
All right, be careful.
Have fun.
Ciao.
Ciao, ciao.
[music playing]