(suspenseful music)
(humming)
(warbling music)
(suspenseful music)
(humming)
(warbling music)
(pounding rock music)
♫ Looking good and look at me
♫ Got this woman and she'll never see
♫ Got a spear in her hand or two
♫ Some call her anxious
and some call her rude
♫ But I know her and all her kind
♫ The old Spanish
scripture and clubs divine
♫ Prehistoric bimbos in Armageddon City
♫ Prehistoric bimbos in Armageddon town
♫ It's true what they say
♫ Can't keep a good bimbo down
♫ Don't make em mad or
they'll kick your ass
♫ Except for mutants
like beach for the glass
♫ Silence and beauty for the whiffering
♫ Some more bad like a bing
♫ But I draw breath and all them guys
♫ Won't fit the description
that comes to my mind
♫ Prehistoric bimbos in Armageddon City
♫ Prehistoric bimbos in Armageddon town
♫ You know that it's true you can't keep
♫ A good bimbo down
♫ Prehistoric bimbos in Armageddon City
♫ Prehistoric bimbos in Armageddon town
♫ Prehistoric bimbos
♫ They don't ask for a penny no
♫ Know that you can't keep these bimbos
♫ Can't keep em down
♫ Prehistoric bimbos in Armageddon City
♫ Prehistoric bimbos in Aramageddon town
♫ Prehistoric bimbos are
going to Aramageddon City
♫ You know what they say is true
♫ You just can't keep a good
♫ Bimbo down
♫ No bimbo oh oh oh
♫ No bimbo
- [Voiceover] Bimbo.
(moody rock music)
- We just got back from the scourging.
We went to the barn,
we didn't find anything useful that way.
You guys go tend to the horses.
(gasping)
(dramatic music)
- Oh my god, Trianna!
(moody rock music)
- Let me help you.
- Thanks.
In here.
(crying)
A little more.
Okay.
Chuck it in.
(coughs)
Lab's lookin' better, Doc.
- Thank you, I'm just
trying to make the best of
the combinations that I have,
which are more than barbaric.
- We're sorry, it's the best we can do.
After the war, nothing
has ever been the same.
They were born under ground
in those caves, in those fallout shelters,
And while the scientists
were living in luxury,
they were reeing day and night,
50 feet under ground, why--
- That's enough.
Larry, Doc joined us to help our cause.
She believed in what we stood for.
She gave up her luxury for us.
So can it.
- He's right in a way, though.
We're in the wrong, you guys are right.
I mean, we made the chemicals
to destroy the enemy
and instead we made mutants and beasts.
Strange beasts like those found
in prehistoric times on this planet.
I joined you guys to find
restitution for what I've done.
And try to reverse those process.
What's happened to your leader?
- We don't know.
We saw her laying outside,
bleeding to death so
brought her in here to you.
- Syringe.
- Come on, Rachelle.
- [Larry] Well Doc, what is it?
- She's been bitten by a talnid.
Their bite is very deadly.
First it just makes them sick.
And then they go into a coma.
And then they rot from the inside out.
- Oh my god!
Then we can't save her?
You mean to tell me there's no cure!
- There's only one cure,
and it's back in my old
office in Armageddon City,
and I'm forbidden to ever
step foot there again.
See the talnid is our baby,
a genetic hybrid, a toxic nightmare.
It could destroy all the
people on this planet
if it weren't for the
fact that they only lived
for an average of 90 days.
- Why in Armageddon City?
- Because the use of toxic chemicals
has been outlawed everywhere else
except for in Armageddon City.
That ignorant major, Salacious Thatch,
has promoted the use
of genetic alterations
that my coworkers still do.
What Thatch plans to do
is buy up all the land
and build more cities
so he can make more income for himself.
- Whoever this Thatch is
is not going to stop us
from saving Rachelle,
or at least me.
- Me either.
That fat piece of shit's
not going intimidate me!
He slaughtered my family
that lived in Armageddon City
when it was New York.
My father owned his own business,
he was a formal retailer.
He rented out clothes to
people who were in need.
Thatch tried to buy my father,
but my father wouldn't sell out to him.
And he killed my father.
I'm not gonna let him do anything else.
I'm gonna barbecue his balls!
- Trianna, it's up to
you to save Rachelle.
We can't afford to let you
have a large group of warriors.
We need all the protection we can get.
What I want you to do, is go out,
find two of your most trusted warriors,
meet me at the assembly
hall in 30 minutes.
(dogs barking)
(foreboding music)
(growling)
(crashing)
(dramatic music)
(growling)
(screaming)
(yelling)
(laughing)
- [Julia] Trianna!
- Trianna!
Trianna!
Fucker!
God damn fucker!
(yelling)
Get him!
You better stab him!
(yelling)
- [Man] You can go faster than that.
- [Janna] Get your arm outta the way.
(yelling)
I don't wanna hit your arm.
- That was easy!
- Mr Thatch?
I'm afraid I got some
bad news to tell you.
- What!
Spill your guts or I will!
- Two more experiments got away.
And they're loose in the
city, what should I do?
- Calm down, no big deal.
We simply wait for...
A few mangled bodies to show up and...
If they show the right signs,
or if there's any trace of
the saliva in their wounds,
you know cus people die here all the time.
There's no need to panic anyone.
We'll search the area
where the bodies are found.
- [Soldier] And what
if they don't turn up?
- We burn the files and
tell we know nothing.
That's it, we just, and you can go relax,
play a video game,
watch a good comedy like
I Spit on Your Grave, that cheers me up.
- Yes, sir.
(laughing)
(dramatic music)
- Let's tie em up to these poles.
(moody electronic music)
- Are you sure you can handle this battle?
It's better to lose one than all of you.
- No!
If she dies, so does years
of priceless information.
And so does her child, our newest warrior.
We will exceed
if it destroys all but one of us.
- Okay.
But be on guard and utilize all the skills
that you have learned through the years.
May God be with you.
- Everybody get their weapons, okay?
Alright?
Let's go.
- Wait for, no no, wait for me Mama!
- No, you can't go.
- I wanna go!
- No, you can't.
- Go back in there.
- The weather's getting worse, Mr Thatch.
I fear it's acid rain.
I don't think we're gonna have any luck.
- Get me General Morbius right now!
- General Morbuis?
Yes sir.
General Morbius!
- You idiot!
I'll send you down
to fucking sewage waste depot!
Let you wallow with all, in
all the shit with our slaves!
- But--
- The prisal can send you down
to the disease-infected whores
who work in our city's ghettos,
and let them wipe the puss of your
sweating, oozing sores all over you!
- Hey, I just do what you told me to do!
- You're gonna talk back to me!
- I did what you told me!
- If I wanted you to yell out
at General Morbius like this,
General Morbius!
I can do that myself!
(door closes)
- You sent to the Torture Room for me sir?
- Yes, Sergeant Romero has just reported
that non-mutant life
has entered the Nightmare Zone.
I want you to take
three,
three men and intercept them.
Oh, and--
- Armor!
- Armor, yes.
Pringle here has just informed me
that it looks like we're
going to have some acid rain.
And I was wondering what
kind of armor our men had,
if it could take the acid rain?
- The only kind of armor we
have available at this point
is nikad clave.
It covers the head
and torso area, but
leaves the groin exposed.
- Good job!
- Yes!
- Very good job, that means
that they won't be having
any more rugrats to run around this city!
- No, no little impies.
- Wipe out the sexual organs,
it's gonna be a fun town.
Good job, good job.
- You have a good future
in this company.
- Very good job.
- You will stay in the city.
As long as you don't screw up.
- Thank you sir.
Now back to this non-mutant life,
suppose theyre wanderers or survivors?
- Terminate them.
(determined music)
- You know what?
Hey.
It really makes me made
Lotus backed out on us.
- Yeah, well that's a bimbo for ya.
- Come on.
- [Janna] I got it.
- Oh god, I think I'm gonna get sick.
- [Larry] You alright?
- Don't do that.
(exclaims)
- Nasty!
- Thanks.
- [Larry] Hey yuck, I
think it has a wallet.
Be careful!
- [Both] Who is it?
- Oh man.
(exclaims)
- You know what?
- [Janna] He was ugly to start out with.
- It's probably some poor bastard
who drank the chemical waste.
- [Larry] Farmer maybe?
- Oh man.
- Well, just leave it there, let's go.
- Come on.
(dramatic music)
- You ready?
Careful Trianna!
- Alright, come.
Check on that side.
- [Larry] Clear.
I hear something, what is it?
(shushing)
- [Sapphire] Help!
Help me!
- What's that noise, Trianna?
- I don't know.
- Please!
Help!
Get me out of here!
- [Larry] What is it?
- Get me out of here!
Help me!
- Sapphire!
(exclaims)
Help me!
- [Larry] I'm trying!
- I thought you were dead!
(dramatic music)
- [Sapphire] This place is
a trap, you have to leave!
- [Larry] A trap!
- [Janna] Come on!
Don't leave her, get her up.
Get up!
- It's all clear.
- I'll get it.
- [Trianna] We gotta get out, come on!
(dramatic music)
(groaning)
- I know they're in here.
Morbius may have given
up, but I'm not going to.
You men ready?
- [Soldier] Yeah, I smell bimbos!
(shouting)
- Come on through, Doug.
This way.
(dramatic music)
- Come on, guys.
- Wait stop, let me get her.
Here, hold this.
- You're okay, Sapphire.
- [Larry] I'll pick up the weapons!
- It's okay.
- [Pringle] Let's go soldiers.
I smell bimbos!
This way!
Bimbos!
(yelling)
- Retreat!
You bimbos go that way,
I'll distract them!
Here, take these!
- Be careful!
- [Larry] Yes.
(shouting)
- Bimbos!
- Okay.
(screaming)
(shouting)
- Go over there!
- [Triann] Where?
- [Janna] Over there!
Now!
(screaming)
(yelling)
(swords clashing)
(whimpering)
- Sit down.
Right here, right here.
Right here.
Okay.
Lift your head up.
You're gonna die, you need food!
- Water.
I need water.
- Stay here.
Sapphire, listen to me.
Listen to me, sweetie.
Stay here.
You're gonna be okay.
Oh my god!
You listen to me!
Oh shit.
I'll be right back!
- [Sapphire] Water.
- Ya!
Come on, ya bimbo!
(yelling)
- Come on, fight me like a man!
- You want it like a man?
- Yeah!
(exclaims)
You fight like a man, you piece of shit!
(yelling)
- Draw on that!
- Son of a bitch!
- You can't hit the broad side of a barn!
Oh, my wrist!
(swords clashing)
(groaning)
(birds singing)
(exclaiming)
- Shew.
- Dr West, come on.
Doc, you alright?
(groaning)
She get you too?
Come on man, come on.
It's alright.
We gotta go report this to Thatch.
We got to.
We'll get back at them bimbos,
if it's the last thing I do.
Come on, it'll be alright.
We'll get em back.
I just had the fight of my life, too.
Let's go get Thatch,
tell him what Morbius did to us.
(energetic rock music)
- Wait.
Wait.
- You there?
(exclaims)
You okay?
- Yeah.
I'm alright.
- Where's Julia?
- Julia?
Julia!
- Julia!
- [All] Julia!
- There she is.
- Julia!
- You okay?
- [Julia] I'm right here.
Look at their weapons.
- [Trianna] You okay?
Well now we gotta find their weapons, too.
(chatting)
(pole clanks)
- Here.
(exclaiming)
(whistling)
- That's so cool,
you can see your face shine!
- [Janna] God!
You lucky dog!
- Trade ya.
- No way.
(moody electronic music)
- Professor Thatch.
General Morbius is here to see you.
- Well now, let me guess.
You bring me bad news.
News that you fucked up another mission!
- You should listen to him this time.
- Alright.
- So there's a small band of warriors
heading up from the south.
They seem barbaric in nature
and extremely pissed off.
They killed three of my best troopers,
and they're women.
- Women!
Fucking women!
What is this the ERA revisited!
What do they want!
- I don't know!
They're heavily armed and very pissed off.
Kinda like ninja commandos.
Only with a great set of
tits and a mean ass attitude.
(yelling)
- God, somebody in the Nightmare Zone!
That's it with you,
you're done, you're out!
(laughs)
- [Pringle] What do you
plan on doing about this?
- That's what they don't know, sir.
You can only enter the Nightmare Zone.
No one ever reemerges.
- They did it once
before, and they beat you!
- Women only get one chance with me!
Never a second!
- Never raise your voice with me, ever!
You act that way again, if
you fuck up on this mission,
that's it, your human's due and
the camel mutants out there,
do you understand?
- Yes sir.
- Good!
- Now, unless you have
something else to say
get out of my office!
- Thank you.
- I'll go with him.
- You do that!
And if he fucks up, you bring me his head!
- [Pringle] Oh he won't do that.
(dramatic music)
- We got five miles to the Nightmare Zone.
One hour and 37 minutes of daylight left.
- We better get a move on.
We have got to do this for us,
and Rachelle.
Let's go.
(mysterious music)
- Let's stop and rest right here.
Hey, Sapphire.
(swords clashing)
(grunting)
(Larry talking)
(dramatic music)
- [Man] Go ahead, kick it down.
(rumbling)
- What's going on?
Wait!
Hold on, hold on!
Hold on!
Wait!
It stopped.
(yelling)
(screaming)
(grunting)
(Larry grumbling)
- Okay!
It's dead.
(celebrating)
- Great job, Janna.
- Leave it me to raise a little hell,
literally.
- We're not even there yet.
The sun's setting down,
so let's just turn back.
- No!
We have come too far!
We are not turning back, we have to go.
Let's start walking.
I don't want to hear any
complaints from anyone!
- [Man] Action.
(cocks gun)
- If you want something right,
you gotta do it yourself!
(talking)
- Well?
Here we are guys.
Armageddon City.
- I swear to god, the
bimbos were right here!
I know I saw em!
- Well where are they now?
- I don't know where they are!
- Where are they?
- I don't know!
- Well where's General Morbius?
- General Morbius
left us the minute we left the camp.
- Well where the fuck is he now?
- I have no clue where he went!
- I want him brought
to me, I want him dead!
- He's a deserter and
we gotta get the bimbos,
so if you wanna grouch him
get your fat ass and get him yourself,
I'm going after these bimbos, buddy!
(splashing)
- [Thatch] Come on!
(dramatic music)
(talking)
(yelling)
(screaming)
(energetic rock music)
- Let him go, let him go now!
Let him go!
- [Trianna] Drop your weapons!
- Stop, the weapons, now!
Get in line, back up!
(yelling)
- [Sapphire] Let her go!
- Give me your weapons,
gimme your weapons, there.
- Get back!
Don't even reach for it!
Stop ya little ho!
Welcome to Armageddon City!
We even have your rooms
ready for you here.
In our jail!
(laughing)
- Sorry, we really can't stay.
We were just--
(yelling)
- [Thatch] Why have you come to my city!
- Well it wasn't for those
warm, friendly smiles.
- [Thatch] Shut up!
- I think people need to line up here.
Line up!
Get in line!
- Let go!
- Shut up!
- Line up, now!
Now!
- Just let her go!
- Line up.
(yelling)
- Can you believe this!
She was trying to take
the gun outta my hands!
(screaming)
(yelling)
- [Thatch] Shut up!
(talking)
- [Trianna] You are sick!
- Move it, keep moving!
I don't wanna see anyone stopping.
(exclaims)
Come on, move again and I'll
take this bitch out, move!
Drop it.
- Drop it!
- Drop the weapon!
(club clatters)
- Alright now, get in line!
Get in line!
Get in line, get in line.
To the door, now!
- Just keep marching!
Move it!
(yelling)
You.
I got a problem with you, buddy.
If you ever attack us again
- Let go!
I won't give you a trial
- Keep walking!
- Before I kick your ass!
I'll cut you to pieces.
And I'll feed ya to Thatch.
I think you need to quit
squirming now, don't you?
Alright, move it!
(talking)
- Wait!
You men take
the rest of the bimbos
to the cell.
This pretty little butterfly goes with me.
Come my dear.
(dramatic music)
(howling)
- Oh my god, what is that?
- It's a talnid.
- [Lotus] Are they dangerous?
- Very dangerous, they're deadly.
(growling)
Why didn't you go with the other girls?
- I didn't feel like I was
ready to go on a mission yet.
Felt like I had
make it my way.
- Since you haven't had a lot of training?
- [Lotus] No.
- There you are.
(groaning)
Where you think you've been?
- Sorry General Mr Thatch.
Ow!
- Get in here!
- I in fact can slide in.
- Well, I can forgive you this time.
But this is twice you've fucked up now!
- [Morbius] Sorry, sir.
There are mutants everywhere.
And I saw three more talnids!
They're fighting the toxic waste.
- So the talnid population is growing?
- [Morbius] Yes sir.
- Good!
Exactly as a planned!
- It's not my fault, sir!
I can't help it if you
armed me with poor men
who can't seem to fight god damned women!
- Just remember you're one of those men!
Now, we have these
women, these bimbos,
down in our holding cell.
I want you and Dr West to interrogate them
and find out why they are here.
- Then let me interrogate them!
Let me find out what you want to know!
- If you ever raise your voice
to me again, I will kill you.
Do you understand?
- Yes sir.
- [Thatch] Get up!
- Fine.
- Oh, and after you interrogate them,
I want you to gather some weapons,
and get my troops and meet
me here in half an hour.
We're going to put our plan into action.
(suspenseful music)
- Yes sir.
(grunting)
- Hello.
I'm Dr West.
I've been sent here to interrogate you.
Now this can go easy, or it can go rough.
(grunts)
(laughs)
Now tell me,
what were you doing with the bimbos?
- Well, you idiot.
I'm John Apollo.
I work for the Armageddon Street Patrol.
And anyway,
I was with those bimbos
because I thought that
I might try an orgy--
- Silence!
Looks like we're gonna have
to do this the hard way.
Soldier get me the truth serum, please.
(coughing)
- [Man] Squirt.
Cool.
- Hold still.
(screaming)
(laughs)
(dramatic music)
Feel better?
- I have failed.
- No you haven't.
We have failed, not you.
- This isn't over yet!
Julia, how much time do we have left?
- Approximately 11 hours.
- That's not enough time!
Even if we did leave,
we still don't have enough time
to get the antidote for our leader.
- Dr West.
Yes, Lord Thatch.
Yes, we have the bimbos and
they've been incarcerated.
I'm questioning John Apollo.
Yes.
What would you like us to do with them
once the questioning is finished?
Ah the Nightmare Zone.
Excellent.
Okay, thank you.
Now, tell me the truth.
What were you doing with the bimbos?
- A woman named
Daria Solomon,
(dramatic music)
you call her Doc.
She used to work with you.
But she had the guts
to get out.
You didn't.
- Soldier,
leave me with this man.
I'll finish him.
- Even
when you knew
what that fat bastard was
doing with them chemicals.
- Doc's alive?
I thought she was dead.
I thought they'd killed her.
If I'd known she was still alive,
I would have joined her.
(sighs)
Okay,
first we need to get you
the antidote for the drug.
(suspenseful music)
Ah the bimbos!
- [Trianna] Get away!
- Now don't get your
panties all bunched up.
I'm John Apollo.
Doc sent a radio transmission
that you all would be coming here.
So I thought I'd
meet ya little bit halfway in.
- Yeah?
Prove it!
- Well what do want, sperm sample?
Look, I know some great
shortcuts in Thatch's building
so you guys are gonna have to trust me
or
fight you way through
this hell hole yourself.
- I'll give you one chance.
You mess up,
I'll run this spear through your ass.
- Yeah,
almost sounds like fun.
Let's go.
- [Trianna] Alright guys, let's go.
(footsteps)
- Hurry.
- Got it!
- Come on, come on, let's go, let's go!
- The bimbos have escaped.
Damn!
Thatch'll be furious!
- Oh my god!
Where do we go?
- Great, dead end.
- No!
(yelling)
(grunting)
(screaming)
- Let's lock him up!
Let's lock him up, come on!
(yelling)
Come on, let's get the rest of these guys.
In there.
- Are you okay Sapphire?
- We kicked some ass!
- Yeah!
- Good job!
- You'll be alright, you'll be alright.
- How'd you guys manage
to pull this one off?
- Well, I'm known as the man
of a million miracles around here.
- Hey!
We gotta find Janna!
Thatch took her!
- Thatch's quarters are
on the seventh floor,
and heavily guarded.
Before we go up there though,
we need to stop at my office
and get the antidote
for the talnid bite.
- Where's your office?
- It's right over here.
- Go, go.
- It's here somewhere.
Alright.
Let's go.
- Tasty, just the way I like it.
(screaming)
Why Janna, say hello to your friends.
(laughing)
- You bastard!
(energetic electronic music)
(screaming)
Die bastard, die!
- Where's Thatch?
He's dead?
- They killed him.
- [Both] Yes!
- [Larry] You're next!
- No!
- You don't understand!
Wait a sec!
- We're glad!
We're at warriors reigning with power!
- We got families.
- Drop your weapons!
- Here have it, have
it, give em the knife.
Come on here, take the knife.
- This isn't some kind of scam!
- There's no scam here, I'm
gonna tell you something.
He and I both have families, he doesn't.
But we have families.
He said he would feed
our babies to the talnids
if we didn't do what he wanted.
- [Morbius] But now
that you've killed him,
we have no loyalty to the son of a bitch!
- We had no choice!
It's either that, or
lose everything we had.
- What do we do?
- Thatch paid him to come
up with the machines.
- Now that he's gone, I have no loyalty.
- Hey, you trust Dr West,
he's the one who created the damn talnid!
- Well I...
Had help in that.
- If you want to save your
leader, follow me now.
If not, let her die.
- Then why are we talking, let's go!
- Let's go!
- [Larry] Let's get our weapons!
- You bastard!
- There's not much time left.
(footsteps)
I hope they make it.
(gasping)
Thank you for bringing this!
Oh you guys have come
through, I can't believe!
We're gonna save her life!
Oh my god you guys are wonderful!
Thanks John!
Thanks John for coming through for me.
- What can I say?
I'm the original Wonder Man.
(laughs)
- [Trianna] This'll make you better.
We better go.
Let's go, come on.
- John, I'm sorry we had to hurt you man.
(talking)
- Stop!
- Whoa, listen.
Who's that?
Who's she?
- Trianna?
- [Pringle] Who's that?
- You've done very well on this mission.
You saved Rachelle's life.
She's grown very tired
and she can't fight anymore.
Rachelle wants me to
present you with this sword.
She wants you to be the queen.
All those in favor of Trianna being queen,
let it be known!
(cheering)
(talking)
- [Trianna] Do you want me to use this?
- Nah that's alright.
I don't need my hair cut.
- Well you guys are on our team, but!
There are some major rules.
One.
We are not called "bimbos".
- [Pringle] Tell him!
- I must apologize.
- Who called em bimbos?
Did we call em bimbos?
We ain't called em nothing!
- Number two!
You will not
hit women.
- I never did, he hit women.
- That would be me again.
- Bonehead!
(bickering)
- [Morbius] I can do that well.
- [Man] Speech.
- We are one.
Together we have fought hard.
You were there for me
as I was there for you.
I will be your queen.
All I ask is
that you return for a sequel.
(dramatic music)
(laughing)
- I can't believe, we finally
got John a part of something
where there's no bad assholes.
- Sorry about that cut.
- Doc you're still an
asshole, but I love ya.
(laughing)
(energetic electronic music)
(singing)