[ORGAN PLAYING]
[BIRDSONG]
[CRYING]
[CRYING AND SNIFFING]
Uh, I've got to get to work, honey.
[SNIFFING]
Do you like the way we've done her?
[GASPS]
[MUSIC- JIMMY VAN HEUSEN, "ALL  THE WAY"]
(SINGING) --come what may.
Who knows where the road will lead us?
Only a fool can say.
[CLOCK TICKING]
[SIGHS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[FAST TAPPING SOUNDS]
Um, did you call the caterers about the deposit?
Yes, dear, yes.
Quiet a minute.
I want to see this.
Joe, how many times have I told you not to wear
dirty sneakers in this house?
Aw, they're cleaner than my socks.
MAN (ON TV): --craziest one yet, the midnight insanity sale!
That's right, folks.
We're open till midnight every day
this week with prices so low, I think I'm gonna be sick.
[CHUCKLES]
We have name name-brand washers for, golly,
an unbelievable $329.95.
Wait a minute, Dee, that's under invoice!
$399.25?
Oy, yoi, yoi.
Sometimes I wonder why I hired this woman.
Then I look at her, and it all comes back to me.
Gee, Archie, I've done it again, haven't I?
Will you ever forgive me?
So what's a bankruptcy or two?
[GROWLS]
[LAUGHS] Oh, she's something, isn't she?
[CLEARS THROAT] Well, what's for dinner?
Don't look at us.
We just live here.
Dad!
Will you please talk to mom.
We have a million things to do before the wedding,
and I can't get her moving.
She's so weird lately.
Oh, honey, you might be a little weird, too,
if you just lost your best friend.
[SCOFFS] I know!
But that was almost a week ago!
Life can't just stop.
Yeah, tell me about it.
It's almost inventory time.
She hasn't even touched the books.
[MEOWING]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Somebody please feed the cat.
Sure.
[CAT SCREECHES]
Surprise!
Aunt Peg, Uncle Bernie!
You're two days early?
[LAUGHTER]
[INAUDIBLE].
Well, honey, better early than never.
Tanya, honey, you look beautiful.
[KIDS SHOUTING] - Aw, hello, bride-to-be.
I cannot wait to meet your mom.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Oh, no, god, please, you wouldn't.
BERNIE: Archie!
Bernie!
What a surprise!
My brother, the TV star.
[LAUGHS]
[INAUDIBLE].
Come on in.
Hey, hey, hey, [INAUDIBLE],, go get him!
All right.
Let's go!
[CAT SCREECHES]
Ah!
How many people are going to be at wedding
Only about 100.
Hi!
Honey!
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
Look what I found!
Bunny, honey, How are ya?
How are ya?
Listen, uh, I'm gonna have to run to the store for a minute.
Just go to it.
I love getting away and being taken care of.
Bye!
Hey, Bunny?
Get this stuff for me, would ya?
Why, Archie?
I wanna stay young and sexy.
Can't you eat regular meals just this week?
The seaweed burdock root takes me twice as much time.
Oh, just get it for me, would you, please?
Oh, and, uh, get me some Boulder beer, too.
And hurry up.
I can't take these kids.
TANYA: Mother! Mother?
[FOOTSTEPS FAST APPROACHING]
Wait for me.
Those brats are driving me crazy.
This better not be ruined.
[GASP] My flute!
God, those little jerks got peanut butter
all over my wedding dress.
It's fragile.
My mother bought me this flute.
Those kids need lobotomies or something.
She worked a whole summer picking
string beans to pay for it.
I don't need any poverty stories, OK?
Can we go?
[CHURCH BELLS RINGING]
I'll be in the bridal boutique.
Listen to me, Tanya.
Let's stop at the bank right now, draw out all my savings.
We'll put you on a plane.
You'll just disappear.
I'll explain everything to the family.
Mother, what's the matter with you lately?
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[MUSIC PLAYING IN STORE]
WOMAN (ON SPEAKER): Price check on number two.
Seaweed, rice cakes, burdock root, broccoli, Boulder beer.
Bonnie!
Gee whiz, you drink this?
Archie does.
CHILD: Look, Ma!
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[CRASH]
WOMAN (ON SPEAKER): [INAUDIBLE] on aisle five.
WOMAN (ON SPEAKER): Clean up on--
MAN (ON SPEAKER): [INAUDIBLE] clean up on aisle [INAUDIBLE]..
(TEARFULLY) Oh, god, I want to disappear.
[CRYING]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[CRASH]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[CHURCH BELLS RINGING]
[CRYING]
[BIRDSONG]
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
[HORN HONKING]
Come on.
Move over, lady.
[HORN HONKING]
I got all day.
Got the whole damn road. Come on!
Move it!
[HORN HONKING]
Come on, Pinto, giddy-up.
Giddy-up, you can do it!
Thank you!
Yo, horse.
[EXPLOSION]
Wow!
Look out! Whoa!
Whoa. Oh.
Ooh.
Oh, [INAUDIBLE].
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you all right?
Can I help you?
Yeah.
You can drive.
I'm a desperate man.
You are going to drive a little faster
after you calm down, right?
What do you want from me?
I haven't made up my mind yet.
Wow, she's a real honey of a car.
Please take it.
Just let me off by the side of the road.
I wouldn't mind doing that, ma'am, but I can't.
See what you got in your purse.
Please, I have two children at home.
What Is this?
[LAUGHS] [PLAYS NOTE] Oh.
Ow!
Damn, that was a real mean-spirited thing to do.
You can't have that!
You can have anything I've got, but not this.
Do you hear?
Jeez.
[INAUDIBLE],, I don't want your old flute.
Throw the damn thing in the back, will ya?
You're [INAUDIBLE].
There we go.
20 measly bucks?
Isn't this a Mercedes you're driving?
I'm sorry.
Ah-ha.
There we go-- instant money.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
Just be cool now.
Smile a little.
That's good.
Ah, put your card in.
Now punch in the number.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
Hey, you oughta work on your makeup.
It'll do a lot for your self-esteem.
No, really, it would.
Hello, Mrs. Winifred Brown.
Winifred?
Everybody calls me Bunny.
Cute.
My name's Walter Sh--
[CHUCKLES] I almost went and told you my whole name.
Then you would have been in trouble.
Come on.
come on. Relax, would ya?
I don't like this any better than you do.
What, are you afraid I'm gonna kill you?
Yeah, I haven't killed but five or six people in my whole life.
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
I don't even know one thing about you.
You don't have to keep me. - Yeah.
Well, you know I was driving that Pinto.
You're the only one who knows that.
I stole the dumb thing.
- You stole a car? - Mm-hm.
That's all?
You're kidnapping me for that?
Here, lady, don't make more of this than it already is.
I'm borrowing you for a little while.
That's all. I'm just borrowing ya.
Come on.
I used that car in a bank robbery.
Trouble is I don't keep up with the times.
They put this little dye bomb in with money.
[CHUCKLING] It turned it all red.
I can't even spend $1.
But this, this is clean as a whistle.
BUNNY: OK, please let me go.
My family expects me to cook dinner.
We have relatives over.
Well, let your husband cook tonight.
It'll do him good.
Hey, you getting hungry?
Want something to eat?
Let's see what we got back here.
Oh, hey, want a peanut butter sandwich?
[SIRENS] BUNNY: No.
Damn.
[INAUDIBLE]
Just be smart, lady.
I'm gonna could hurt you, if I have to.
BUNNY: This isn't happening.
All right.
I got a gun aimed right back of your seat, you understand?
I can blow a hole clean through you.
BUNNY: Oh, god!
May I see your license, ma'am?
I thought it might be you, Mrs. Brown.
Are you all right?
Your husband gave us a call about an hour or so ago,
said you were missing.
I'm not missing, officer.
Are you OK?
Looks like you've been crying.
Um, I lost a friend a few days ago.
And I just need to drive and be alone for a while.
I'll be home soon.
What's that in the back?
In the back? OFFICER: Mm.
Is there something in the back?
Oh, that.
That's, um, a big thing for my husband's birthday.
OFFICER: Drive safe.
Buckle up.
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
WALTER: The gun's still aimed at you, lady.
Just keep driving and don't look back.
You sure could use some lying lessons.
[CRYING]
WALTER: Now what's the matter?
It's my birthday today.
[SOBS]
She'll be home, Mr. Brown.
Said she needed to be alone for a while.
Is she OK?
She looked pretty upset, that she'd been crying.
Uh, but she drove steady.
I followed her for about a mile or two.
Why would you just ditch me at the mall?
Something's wrong, Daddy.
You want to go look for her?
Can I at least order some pizza then?
Oh, by the way, happy birthday, Mr. Brown.
But who told you it was my birthday?
Oh, she did.
What could she be thinking?
My birthday isn't until next--
oh.
What's the date today?
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
WALTER: You all right?
No, I'm not all right.
What are you going to do with me?
I have a right to know.
Yeah, well, Jane, I've never been much at planning.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
Oh, god, I hate lightning.
Gives me the willies.
Does it bother you?
No.
That's because you've never been hit by it.
I have.
Burned every last bit of body hair off me.
Boy, was I ever funny looking.
[BAG RUSTLING] Look at all this good stuff.
We can get by for a week.
I have a daughter getting married on Saturday.
They need me.
Oh they're big kids, huh?
Come on, eat some.
Boy, I wish you were having more fun.
Well, I'm not.
I'd like to stop for a drink, but I can't because I don't
know what I'd do with you.
So we got a lot of problems to work out, don't we?
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
There's-- there's beer in that bag in the back.
What?
Well, now we're going off on the right foot, aren't we?
[BAG RUSTLING]
WALTER: [INAUDIBLE]
BUNNY: Oh!
[CHUCKLING] I'm too fast for you, Bunny.
I can't trust you.
That's too bad.
Things would be better if I could.
Nothing would be better.
What do you want, my body?
Would you let me go then?
You think I'm sick?
Jeez Louise, what do you take me for?
A kidnapper and a bank robber, that's what.
Yeah, well, I bet you're not perfect either.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
BUNNY: Where are we now?
WALTER: This is my hometown.
Got a nice feel to it, doesn't it?
BUNNY: Not particularly.
WALTER: Well, anyway, pull into that driveway right there.
They'll be looking for this car.
Pull it right up there and stop.
All right, pull it in.
They won't find it here in a million years.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[INAUDIBLE]
This, a '77 Monte Carlo, a classic.
What is this place?
Just mind your own business.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
BUNNY: Ah!
[TSKING] Really, Walter.
For a ladies man, you're slipping.
Oh, you leave her alone, Sebastian.
She's got nothing to do with it.
Nice outfit, ma'am.
Well, Mr. Sharphorn, Walter, my friend.
You're a day late, but you better
not be even a dollar short.
Hey, look, that's what I wanted to talk to you about.
I'm already uncomfortable with the sound
of your voice, Walter.
[LAUGHS] Look, I just need a couple more days.
Sebastian, I'm on the edge of the biggest deal of my life.
30 grand is a lot of money, hard to come up with.
Hey, here, I've got money.
This ain't even close to 30 grand.
That was a set up.
You suckered me on that bet.
A bet's a bet.
Yeah, you sure act tough for a midget, Stubbs.
Ooh!
No!
Oh!
[GRUNTING]
Ah!
Stop it!
Tomorrow at 6:00, Walter.
I'm not waiting a couple days for a scum bucket like you.
It's been a real pleasure, ma'am.
[DOOR OPENS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
Oh, dear god.
[GRUNT]
Wait.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
If I help you, will you promise to let me go?
Yes, ma'am.
I cross my heart.
Ooh, I think your nose might be broken.
Is there any trouble you aren't in?
Hm.
Mm-mm.
You have hands like a lady I knew once.
You aren't a healer, are you?
Who, me?
This lady was a healer.
I had this bad shoulder, chronic bad shoulder.
And she just lay hands on it.
And the pain would vanish right into thin air.
Any time I had a pain anywhere in my body,
she just laid then hands on it.
I miss that girl.
What happened?
I asked her to heal my hernia.
I got to go to the bathroom.
Ah!
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Happy birthday, honey.
[SCRAPING SOUND]
So this is what a life of crime's like.
Don't bug me.
Why are you doing that? The dye is indelible.
I said don't bug me.
There's a way to do it.
Brought in your groceries--
peanut butter, Cap'n Crunch, seaweed,
burdock root, and 15 packages of thawed out broccoli.
You people in a cult or something?
Something happened in the grocery store.
I think I had sort of a breakdown.
Is it over already?
I guess.
Some breakdown.
My life has been like that.
Every once in awhile something big
happens, like having a baby.
Then I just get back to business.
I married a man who's very business like.
[SIGHS] I guess I better go.
WALTER: Grab yourself some coffee.
It's on the stove. - No.
I know they're worried about me.
Well, relax.
BUNNY: What are you gonna do about those men?
Well, I'll worry about those men when the time comes.
When the time comes?
That's only a few hours away.
Uh-uh, honey.
It's 10 hours away.
And I'm not going to get an ulcer worrying about something
10 hours from now.
Did you rob that bank to pay them?
Why don't you mind your own business?
BUNNY: I would take then seriously, if I were you.
They almost broke your nose already.
Wait a minute.
Are you my mother?
You think you have to take care of me?
You're not taking very good care of yourself.
[SCOFFS]
I'm talking too much.
I got to go, Walter.
[INAUDIBLE],, sit down, and maybe you try scrubbing.
Try some bleach or something.
I really don't want to.
Look, look, look.
I appreciate you coming back and fixing me up.
I'll never forget it.
But, um, don't ever trust me again.
I can't let you go.
They'll get the story out of you for sure.
- You are such a liar! - I always was.
Walkin' out of here ain't gonna be as easy as you think.
BUNNY: [GASPS]
WALTER: Stubbs's been there all night.
But Walter Sharphorn's got a plan.
[BIRDSONG]
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS] This isn't gonna fool anybody.
It just has to get us to the car.
Oh, I didn't realize there was that much woman
under that sweatsuit.
Cheap and tacky.
Now, no need insulting my old girlfriend.
I liked her taste.
It suits you.
It suits you too, honey.
You coming?
Come on.
All right.
Sell it, honey.
[BIRDSONG]
[DOG BARKING]
Good dog. Good dog.
Good dog.
[BARKING]
Follow me.
[GATE SQUEAKS]
Leave the damn gate!
Come on.
(WHISPERS) You're supposed to be a woman.
Well, I forgot.
[INAUDIBLE]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
Nice and easy.
I don't believe it.
They don't expect imagination, honey.
[LAUGHS]
How come I drive all the time?
I don't have a license.
Ah.
Anyway, [CHUCKLES] I always had bad luck driving cars.
I'm not surprised.
[CHUCKLES] Want to hear something funny?
I have a kid who's 18.
And the only way he can get insurance on this car
is to promise that I don't drive it.
[CHUCKLES]
You're married?
Can hardly believe it.
Well, not anymore.
Sal threw me out a long time ago.
But I still see my kid every now and again.
He's a-- he's real different from me.
[CHUCKLES] We used to be thick as thieves.
But I don't know.
If you don't spend time with them, then get away from you.
Happens even when you do.
Hm.
I'm hungry.
Yeah.
Oh, I brought your flute.
That flute means a lot to me.
I figured that.
Here we are.
What do you want, a burger? BUNNY: OK.
WALTER: All right.
Pull way back in the back lot.
BUNNY: Why?
WALTER: Because I don't trust you in public.
That's why.
All right, you slide over here on this side.
Why?
Just do it, would Ya you sure as hell
were more agreeable yesterday.
I was scared yesterday.
Oh, you're not scared anymore?
What are you doing?
Damn it.
I will scream my head off!
WALTER: You do, and you won't need it.
BUNNY: Stop it!
[INAUDIBLE] me.
[SCREAMS]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[BUNNY SCREAMS]
I [INAUDIBLE] picked a crazy woman.
[INAUDIBLE] get off.
[SCREAMS]
[LAUGHS] I should have tied it around your neck.
No funny business, OK?
OK.
Hey, how you doing?
A couple coffees and, uh, two of those jelly rolls, please.
- That'll be $1.65. - Great.
Just take it out of that and keep the change.
WAITRESS: Thank you. - Mm-hm.
What'd you do that for? We have to save money.
I've always been a big tipper.
Now shut up and eat your jelly roll.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE].
Come on, let's go.
Hi, number 42.
Backseat will be fine.
What are you doing?
You're stealing those groceries?
Shh.
Great.
Thank you.
Pretty slick one.
What's that poor woman gonna do?
Oh, the store will make good.
How could you do that?
See what we got.
- [SCOFFS] - Come on, Bunny.
It's my worry not yours.
Come on.
That woman's got a baby at home.
Now she's got to shop all over again.
You are some crook.
Mm-mm, blueberry buckle, want a bite?
WALTER: You sure there isn't any bread in there
to make a sandwich?
No.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
[INAUDIBLE].
Well, why didn't you ask me when we were in the market?
[BIRDSONG]
[CHUCKLES]
Now what your trouble?
Walter, do you think you're some kind of guardian angel?
You all right?
I think I am.
I think I'm better than I've been in a long time.
Good. Stop talking rubbish.
You don't understand, Walter.
Yesterday I stood there in the produce aisle
just wishing I could disappear.
And look what happened.
I did.
You did it for me, Walter.
You poor guy, you have to be responsible for me.
I don't have to do one single thing except drive and sit.
You have to feed me, find me a bathroom when I want one,
worry about me, money, and the police
and those rough characters, those crooks.
Day and night, worry, worry, worry.
Well, I know what it's like, Walter.
And you can have it.
Yeah, well, that's the difference between you
and me, Bunny.
You let it get to you.
If you had my problems, you'd be a basket case.
Look at me, calm as a clam.
I don't believe you one bit.
Where you gonna find $30,000?
That's for me to know and you to find out.
BUNNY: Mm.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Break it down.
Walter!
Yoo-hoo, Walter!
We're looking for you.
Got something for you.
Sebastian, look at that.
He's killed himself.
If he killed himself, where is he?
He's gone, you idiot.
I've been here since last night.
Nobody went out.
The only people I saw all day was two women come out
of the house across the street.
I'm telling you his car's still in the garage, you watch.
Woo-wee!
Where'd he get a car like that?
Jeffrey's life has been turned into a living hell by her.
She treats him like a dog [INAUDIBLE]..
Who would buy this crap?
Specialist says sex may cause cancer.
I'm tired.
Where we going?
Just make a left at the crossroads
at the far end of town.
I love the way you always pretend like you
know what you're doing.
Want to get dumped in the ditch?
You don't scare me anymore, Walter.
I bet that gun of yours isn't even loaded.
You're getting awful cocky in your old age, Bunny.
How come you never pulled it on those crooks?
I bet because there's nothing in it.
That's why.
Crooks is a dumb word.
Don't say it anymore, all right?
If I had pulled it on them, we'd probably both be dead by now.
Bull.
[GUN CLICKS]
[GUNSHOT]
[SCREAMS]
[RUMBLING SOUND]
See what you made me do?
You are weird, Walter.
You really are.
Woo-wee!
This is my kind of vehicle.
Listen to that engine.
I don't trust foreign cars.
Stubb, you're a redneck.
You're low class.
A guy like you could never appreciate a car like this.
I'll take an American car over this any day.
I live in this country.
I buy American.
Yeah, right.
Buy American, you steal foreign.
[SIREN]
Well, don't look at me.
I'm driving good.
[SIGHS] This is car is hot.
That slime, Walter.
Pull it over.
What do we say?
SEBASTIAN: I'll do the talking.
Shut up and play dumb.
Just act natural.
All right, everybody out of the car, hands on--
Oh, man.
OFFICER: What the hell.
Sebastian, what are you doing with this?
Hey, Marty. How do you like my new wheels?
You're crazy.
There's a missing person's report
out on a woman who owns this.
I'll kill him.
Look, Marty, we had nothing to do with it.
We took this as collateral on a debt.
Yeah, no keys-- I see.
You took it.
Jerk's name is Walter Sharphorn.
He had a woman with him.
He just disappeared without paying
me a large bundle of cash, and I'm very unhappy with the man.
Is this her?
She looked a little rattier than that,
but yeah, that's the one.
Well, maybe we have a kidnapping on her hands.
Walter? [SCOFFS] You got to be kidding.
She acted like his girlfriend.
OFFICER: Hm.
Can we go now, Marty?
Yeah, on foot.
Hey, you guys, just leave this right here.
I'll do you a big favor.
I'll tell 'em I found it abandoned.
Just return the favor at the end of the month.
[SIGHS] Maybe he did kidnap her.
Maybe that's what he was talking about.
Well, why didn't you tell Marty?
If the cops catch him before we do,
we'll never get a cent, peanut head.
BUNNY: Where are we now?
We're lost, aren't we?
I'm freezing.
WALTER: Just quit complaining, would ya?
Trust me.
BUNNY: You've never done one thing to make me trust you.
WALTER: Well, that's a fine thing to say.
You're about to meet my mother.
First you kidnap me, and then you
take me to meet your mother.
I wish you'd stop saying kidnap.
It gives me the willies.
I don't understand you, Walter.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
I didn't kidnap you, Bunny.
I got you out of the house, didn't I?
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
What's your mother like?
[SIGHS] Nobody you ever met.
Is it Christmas already?
You aren't married again, are ya?
Mm-mm.
Thank god.
That's a blessing.
He's the dumbest one of my kids.
Yeah, I take after my ma.
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS]
Come here.
Damn, if you don't make me laugh.
[LAUGHS]
Rowena Sharphorn, meet Bunny Brown.
Bunny Brown, what a cute little name.
Well, come on in.
I'm skinning a bobcat.
You had your dinner yet
Rowena's a taxidermist.
Come on in and make yourself at home.
[CAT SCREECHES]
Ah!
Don't mind the cats.
Only two mean ones, and they hide from company.
They earn their bed and board, cats do.
Keep the dust down.
I never thought about that.
You, uh, like my son, is that right?
Well--
Don't be so nosy, Rowena.
We just met yesterday.
And we thought we'd come by and visit my sweet little mother
for a couple of days.
He's got a real good sense of humor,
Walter has, but no more common sense than a stud monkey.
I never met a man had both, did you?
I've never thought about that either.
Ah.
Not much of a thinker, is she?
Takes a lot of patience, that kind of work.
But it keeps me occupied.
It's relaxing, sort of like knitting, know what I mean?
Walter, don't even think of touching that bird.
I worked on that thing for two months.
It's the best ring-neck I ever did.
Now, let's see, I got some steaks in this freezer.
What do you say we grill 'em up?
ARCHIE (ON TV) --the midnight insanity sale!
That's right, folks, we're open till midnight every day
this week.
Hey, what's the matter, Bunny?
All those dead animals getting to you?
That's my husband.
Which ad?
BUNNY: There on the TV.
WALTER: Him?
You're kidding?
Archie Brown is your husband?
So what's a bankruptcy or two?
WALTER: How do you put up with that,
huh, him half doodling that blond right there on TV?
Take it easy, Walter.
Looks to me like she's upset.
How you like your steak, honey?
Medium.
It's just that I didn't expect to see him here--
I mean, in other towns.
I never even thought about that.
Tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna give you a little ginger brandy, put some color
back in those cheeks of yours.
Thanks.
One medium, two rare-- let's go.
[MUSIC PLAYS ON TV]
That's it.
Tomorrow I hire a maid.
Maybe you should have done that before she left.
[PHONE RINGS]
[SIGHS] Please, somebody!
Yeah?
[PANTING]
Who is this?
Ah, heavy breathing, huh?
You must want my sister.
[LAUGHS]
Can I help?
Sure.
What's the matter, Bunny?
[SIGHS] I don't know.
Is your husband really tally-whacking
that blonde on the television?
I think so.
Well, let me be honest with you.
If you're running off with Walter because of that--
Oh--
--there's a few things you ought to know about Walter.
He is a walking disaster.
Oh, he'll charm the pants off ya,
but he's trouble, big trouble.
Don't get me wrong.
I love him.
I'm his mother.
I ain't got no choice.
I didn't run off with him, honest.
[CLEARS THROAT] Well, then, what the hell is going on?
Well, you see, Walter kidnapped me.
Oh.
But please don't tell him I told you.
I mean, god almighty, kidnapping?
It's OK.
Don't worry.
I'm actually a willing prisoner.
I don't understand that.
Well, it's just that I wasn't with him by choice at first.
But I think I am now.
Well, what'd I tell ya?
He's a charmer.
And I'll tell you something else.
There is not a reliable, dependable,
honest-to-god decent man left on the face of this earth.
[GLASSES CLINK] We've
Recovered the Mercedes, Mr. Brown.
But we still have not found your wife yet.
WHAT in that hell?
You ever heard of a man named Walter Sharphorn?
Walter-- no.
Why are you asking?
She was reported seen in his company.
We're really not sure what this means.
But they seem to be on friendly terms,
so we've kind of ruled out kidnapping.
Wait a minute.
Are you suggesting that she's run off with this man?
We don't know that, sir.
We're hoping you might be able to help.
Bunny?
No.
She does have the spunk.
Mom ran off?
You're kidding.
She'd never do that. - [CHUCKLES] No.
Maybe that's why she took $1,000 out of the bank.
You keep out of this!
I hate to say it, but the kid makes sense, Archie.
No!
Officer, we think she might have gone
a little haywire because of all the pressure she's been under.
But we've been married--
happily married-- for 22 years.
And I know that she wouldn't just go running
off with this Walter Sharphorn.
Come on.
What it's gonna take to keep all this out of the newspapers?
I'll take care of it.
Don't worry.
Good man.
Thank you, Mr. Brown.
We'll find your wife for you.
OK.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Daddy, if she ran off with somebody--
Now, don't worry, honey.
Don't worry.
She's not going to ruin your plans.
Come hell or high water, we're gonna have this wedding.
It's paid for.
[FLUTE PLAYING]
Pretty, mighty pretty.
Where'd you learn to play like that?
My mother gave me this when I was 10.
I almost went on the road with the Glad Dog Band.
And played for a living?
Well, what stopped Ya
I married Archie instead.
[SIGHS] Oh, man.
All of us in the band had this dream of going
to Ireland to study the music.
We were going to visit all the little towns
and find songs nobody ever heard of before.
We even saved up the money to do it.
Then graduation night, Archie asked me to marry him.
It shocked me so much I said yes.
So you cashed in your chips and played it safe.
It's the old story.
Married at 17.
Had Joe at 18.
That's about it.
Good thing you met me.
Don't break your arm, Walter, patting yourself on the back.
I know how Bunny got here.
You are some dead beat.
I wish I'd knew what kind of trouble
you were in that you had to go around kidnapping people.
I never kidnapped anybody.
Why'd you go and tell her that?
He didn't really kidnap me.
Rowena, I told you.
I explained that to you.
WALTER: That's right.
Don't you protect him.
He's in trouble again.
And this time I don't even care what kind of trouble
it is he's in.
Look, just stop giving Bunny such a bad impression.
Well, I'm sick and tired of you running me down, Ma.
[CHUCKLES].
Yeah, I know you think it's funny,
but it isn't funny a bit.
There is something between you two.
Yeah, I like her.
What of it?
Remember what I told you, Bunny, just remember.
Oh, hell, I'm going to bed.
Come on, Bunny.
[SNAPS] Come along now.
To bed?
Yeah, it's been a long day.
We both need some sleep.
I am a married woman.
WALTER: I don't mean with me.
I mean there's a guest room that's next door to my room.
Women.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Bunny, you need something to wear to bed?
Yes.
WALTER: How about this big old shirt?
That'll do.
If you like sleeping with the light on.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
WALTER: Bunny?
Can I come in a second?
You never bothered asking before.
Uh, I--
I just want to know if I could trust you to stay put tonight.
Uh, I want to get some sleep.
I'm not going anywhere.
This is almost like being on vacation.
[CHUCKLES] Well, good.
That's all I want to say.
Why did you say you like me?
I don't know.
It just slipped out.
It struck me kind of strange.
Did it?
It was nice.
It meant something to me.
I didn't expect it to.
Well, I think you better listener to Rowena.
She knows me like a book.
Well, goodnight.
I'm gonna be just on the other side of the hall, you know,
in case you need me.
[FIRE CRACKLING]
Mm.
[INAUDIBLE]
Oh, hey!
Hey!
Hey! Help!
Help!
Help! - Ah!
Come on in, honey.
We need to talk to you too.
Last night you mentioned something
about a real big deal, Walter.
I want to hear about it.
How the hell'd you get in here?
Stubby had to persuade your mother a little.
She's an unruly old crocodile, isn't she?
If you hurt Rowena, I'll cold cock you.
BUNNY: Stop it!
Have you got the money, scum?
[SPITS]
BUNNY: [GASPS] No!
[SCREAMS]
Have you got the money, scum?
- Ah. - No, please!
He's-- he's going to have money.
He's going to have it Monday afternoon.
What's this?
Don't you understand?
I'm his hostage.
My husband is raising the ransom.
SEBASTIAN: Is that so?
How much?
Half a million dollars.
[WHISTLES] [INAUDIBLE] half a million?
Think about it, Walter.
I'm gonna make you a deal.
Right after that pick up, I want 50 grand cash
delivered to me at the bar at the Pig 'n Whistle Motel,
5:00 PM sharp.
I don't owe you 50 grand.
50 grand or your miserable life!
And we're gonna be watching you every minute.
Look-- look, I--
I've been putting this deal together for three months.
You hang too close, you're gonna screw it up.
Come on, Stubb, I don't like people
bleeding all over [INAUDIBLE].
Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
Better see the old lady.
She's locked in that big old freezer.
[CHUCKLES] I hope you know where the key is because I don't.
Rowena!
[DISTANT POUNDING]
All right.
[INAUDIBLE]
Are you all right?
ROWENA: Well, I don't know.
All right, look, where is the key to lock?
ROWENA: In the pocket of my sweater.
Where's your sweater?
ROWENA: I've got it on.
What we gonna do?
Break it with a crowbar or a screwdriver.
We need a crowbar. [POUNDING FROM FREEZER]
ROWENA: [INAUDIBLE]
[INAUDIBLE] find anything in this mess!
[INAUDIBLE] Crowbar.
Wait.
I got an idea. [POUNDING FROM FREEZER]
ROWENA: Walter
Keep moving, Rowena.
Walter just went to get something.
He'll be right back.
[FOOTSTEPS RUNNING] - All right.
Stand back.
[INAUDIBLE].
[GUNSHOT]
Rowena, Rowena, you all right?
Can I help?
I had a lot of help getting in here.
I don't need any help getting out!
Give me your arm.
Thank you, Walter!
Oh, my god almighty.
You got my ring-neck pheasant!
Rowena, I got half a mind to put you back in there.
Oh, I'd be tickled pink if you did have half a mind.
Goodnight.
Rowena.
[PANTING]
[DOOR OPENS]
You trying to get me real trouble.
I just got you out of real job.
Oh, sure you did.
Thanks to you all of a sudden, I'm a big-time criminal--
kidnapping, grand theft.
We're talking about life imprisonment, Bunny, or worse.
I only told them that.
You haven't done it yet.
Bunny, if I don't do it, they're gonna kill me.
They would have killed you an hour ago
if I hadn't said something. - All right.
All right. Don't get all hot about it.
I don't even think Archie's got that kind of money.
Does he have that kind of money?
Archie's rolling in it.
He's the biggest appliance dealer in Colorado.
I'm his bookkeeper.
Well, where did you come up with such a crazy idea?
[LAUGHS] I don't know.
I just said the first thing that popped into my mind.
Well, you know I happen to be a big believer in impulse.
No kidding.
Come here.
Now, you know, we, uh--
we're talking about your own money.
Archie's money not mine.
Well, Why should you--
Why shouldn't I?
I had to get kidnapped to start enjoying life.
Well, it has been pretty lively, hasn't it?
[LAUGHS]
This is-- this is crazy.
Mm-hm.
This is crazier than even what I'm used to.
Oh. Ow!
Ow! - Ooh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let me get you some ice.
I don't need it for my nose.
How's this?
That's nice.
Very pretty, my darling.
Oscar, come on, cut it out, would you please?
Oscar, stop.
Stop it.
Hey. Hey.
Don't touch the goods. Come on.
- Dad. - Come on.
All right, let's go. Set 'em up along the aisle.
TANYA: Dad!
Honey?
Damn it, where is she?
Oh, honey, will you stop thinking about her, please?
Hey, she'll show up.
I bet you any amount of money she will.
Besides we're getting through this whole thing just fine.
Oh, what if she hasn't run off?
What if she's in trouble?
If she's in trouble, it better be big trouble.
[LOONS CALLING]
WALTER: So when I'm in prison, are you gonna think about me?
BUNNY: If it scares you that much, don't do it.
[LOONS CALLING]
WALTER: You know, robbing that bank was the only real crime
I ever committed.
BUNNY: Come on.
Well, I've done lots of little things that don't count,
like those groceries or stealing a car.
One time I got arrested for impersonating
an usher at the World Series.
- [LAUGHS] - I did.
I really did.
But nothing they could ever get me put away for life.
If the police did catch you, just say they did, what
if I just told them the truth?
The truth?
That I was with you in my own free will,
that I helped to take money that was rightfully,
sort of, mine already.
If Archie pressed charges, it would
have to be against me, too.
He would never do that.
And you would say that, for sure?
Cross my heart.
Don't say it that way.
[LAUGHS]
I guess you must be pretty fed up with ol' Archie.
He's a bastard.
I guess he's probably not the worst one in the world.
But if we do this, he's gonna have to choose
between a half million or me.
I like that.
[LAUGHS]
You are one crazy woman.
Oh, no, Walter. Walter!
Walter!
[SHRIEK] [SPLASH] Oh!
WALTER: [LAUGHS] Grab on.
BUNNY: [INAUDIBLE].
WALTER: [LAUGHS] Good.
Save yourself then. BUNNY: [INAUDIBLE].
WALTER: You [INAUDIBLE].
BUNNY: Oh!
WALTER: [INAUDIBLE].
BUNNY: No!
WALTER: Come here.
[INAUDIBLE]
Woo!
BUNNY: Ah!
All right then. There we go.
There we go.
Oh.
WALTER: [LAUGHS]
BUNNY: You bastard.
You are a dangerous person.
Hey.
Hey, come on, Bunny.
Come on.
Every time I turn around you're risking my life.
All right. All right.
Let's get out of these wet things.
BUNNY: Wouldn't you like that.
Oh, for crying out loud.
I didn't mean-- oh, forget it.
BUNNY: You're always acting like some dumb kid!
Now you see, you don't have to tell me that.
I know that already.
You see, Bunny, that's what I'm like.
(TEARFULLY) This is how I've been the whole time.
You've never once seen me looking decent.
Well, you look decent to me.
No, I don't.
I got much all over me.
My hair's filled with pond water.
I don't care.
I like you anyway.
You're not even looking.
You're hitting me like you mean it.
You're damn right. Ahh!
[PANTING]
You're crazy.
Don't you patronize me!
[PANTING]
(WHISPERING) You're a witch.
BUNNY: [GROANING] [PANTING] That's right.
I'm a witch.
[LOONS CALLING]
[FEET POUNDING ON STAIRS]
Walter.
WALTER: Yeah?
ROWENA: Where's Bunny?
Oh, she's around.
If you're in there, Bunny, I give up.
OK, Rowena.
Jimmy from the gas station just called.
A couple of deputy sheriffs just stopped by there
asking the way to my house.
Is that of any interest to you two?
WALTER: I suppose so.
I suppose so.
You suppose so.
[FEET POUNDING ON STAIRS]
[GRUMBLING]
Come on, honey. Get up and hustle.
We got about 10 minutes to clear out.
Oh, Walter, I can't do this again.
Mwah.
Oh.
ROWENA: [INAUDIBLE] money?
I think we could use a little, 20
bucks, if you could spare it.
Yeah, spare 20 bucks, here take that.
That's two ring-necks and a bobcat.
- Thanks, Mom. - Look out er yourself.
Go on the back road.
WALTER: Don't tell him anything you don;t have to.
- Would you get out of here.
Take it easy.
BUNNY: Bye.
Go.
Get out!
Floor it, Walter~ [GRUMBLING]
BUNNY: Do you know where this road goes?
WALTER: Oh, I know it like the back of my hand.
BUNNY: You always say things like that.
WALTER: Hey, you got to start believing me, Bunny.
Now, we got a little puddle to get over just ahead.
BUNNY: What do you mean a little puddle?
WALTER: Hold on, Bunny. Hold on now!
Hold on tight!
Here we go!
Hold on to your hat, Bunny!
BUNNY: [SCREAMS] Oh, my god!
WALTER: Woo-hoo!
[LAUGHS]
So you have no idea where Walter is, huh?
Nope.
Saw him last Christmas.
That's about it.
Ross, come look at this.
A car wen down this path not long ago.
Could be.
It's not my road, you see.
Where's it go?
Back into the woods.
Some folks fish the streams in there.
Nice talking to ya.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
WALTER: Woo! We're cookin' now!
BUNNY: This isn't a road, Walter.
WALTER: Oh, it is now, honey.
BUNNY: Look out!
WALTER: You holdin' buddy?
SHAW: Oh, they're out here.
I can just feel it.
ROSS: Hold it.
What's that in the road up ahead?
SHAW: Water.
Afraid of a little water?
SHAW AND ROSS: Ah!
You and your Dick Tracy ideas!
Hey!
Somebody's been down here.
I just know it.
Yeah
Well well, how'd they get over this, fly?
Oh, hey, hear something?
I hear cars.
Ah, there's road up ahead.
Trust my instincts, Ross.
Your instincts?
Look at us!
[BIRDSONG]
[CAR APPROACHING]
I wouldn't pick us up on a bet.
[BIRDSONG]
Ha-ha.
Look at this, just as I thought.
Shaw, you are brilliant.
Too bad they'll probably be in the next state
before we get out of here.
WOMAN: Bye, now.
Thank you.
MAN: You betcha.
Give me those.
That's it.
There you go.
Blind leading the blind, Walter.
Honey, we are in a lot better shape than you think we are.
Now, get yourself some coffee, some donuts,
and I will be back in a flash. - Walter.
Come on.
WOMAN (ON SPEAKER): Service department, line three.
Hi.
[PHONE RINGING IN DISTANCE]
- May I help you? - No.
No. I'm just looking.
Thank you very much. - All right.
- This is nice. - Very nice.
WALTER: Don't you work too hard.
WOMAN: I won't.
[WOMEN LAUGHING]
Yes, sir.
Oh, hi.
Uh, I just got to call.
My new Thunderbird's ready.
Name?
Charleston-- John Charleston.
Eh, actually, it might say Jack because my wife brought it in.
Yes, sir.
She's all done now.
He's at the cashier.
- Great, what's the damage? - No charge.
It's all under warranty.
Well, that about makes my day, doesn't it?
[LAUGHS] Thank you very much.
You know it is good doing business
in a place you can trust.
[HORN HONKING]
Hey, Bunny Brown!
Hoo-hee!
Now, is this more your style, air conditioning,
quadraphonic sound.
Anything you want, it's got it. Come on.
Hop on in.
[BIRDSONG]
Next I'm gonna buy you a new dress, honey.
Hey, Rowena gave me a couple hundred bucks.
We got to look sharp for business.
Smile, Bunny.
We're doing fine.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[BELL RINGS]
Good evening, folks.
How are you doing?
A room for two, please--
honeymoon suite, if you got it.
Just married?
Well, the second time around.
[CHUCKLES] Well, you can't expect to get it right
without a little practice.
Uh-uh.
Practice makes perfect, doesn't it?
[CHUCKLES]
Well, Mr. And Mrs. Uh--
Charleston.
--Charleston, that room happens to be on special.
Don't care what it costs. Don't even tell me.
Just surprise me on Tuesday morning.
- Oh, paying with a credit card? - Uh-uh.
I'm a cash-only man--
first thing Tuesday morning.
By the way, brother, if you have a screwdriver,
I'd like to borrow it to fix the license plate
of my brand new Thunderbird.
See it out there?
[CHUCKLES] Isn't that a dandy?
Well, uh, we have a cash-in--advance policy.
Oh, well, why didn't you tell me?
This might take care of one night,
in case we change our minds.
Um, I was about to say we'll make
an exception for you folks.
Tuesday's just fine.
You sure now?
Thank you very kindly.
Have a good night.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Why don't you, uh, just stand by that post there,
honey, for a second just enough to block the old boy's view.
You are the most unprincipled man I ever met.
I don't know why I even like you.
This mattress is as hard as tin!
My back aches.
My nose is broken.
You're just too damn rough and tumble for me, Bunny.
Let me sleep, Walter.
[CHUCKLES] (SINGING) I'm going down to Florida
to get some sand in my shoes.
Oh, yes, I'm going down to Florida
Take the Orange Blossom Special and lose these New York blues.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Woo-ooh-woo-ooh.
Woo-ooh-woo-ooh. (SPEAKING) Come on, Bunny.
[CLAPPING] Today's the day.
Come on, we got plans to make.
Walter Sharphorn never plans.
Hey, this is serious.
Now, here's what I think.
Come on, wake up.
[CLAPS] Wake up.
We have Archie coming along, right?
He's got the money in a suitcase.
And he sets it down someplace where we can see him from up
so we can watch for cops.
I think we get a-- a room in some hotel downtown.
Then the second he leaves, [CLAPS] we jump on it,
beat it out of there.
I think I want it all in 20s, too.
You'll need three suitcases.
It'll have to be 100s.
Ooh, I hadn't thought of that.
It is about a wagon load full of money, ain't it?
Oh, man.
[CHUCKLES]
I think he ought to put it in a black double trash bag,
leave it in an alley someplace near the trash
can so it won't look out of place,
tie it with a red ribbon.
WALTER: Oh, yeah, so we can tell it from other trash.
BUNNY: And I think we ought to pay some bum to come and pick
it up and bring it to us.
And that way if Archie pulls something, they won't catch us.
That's real good.
But when did you have time to think of all that?
I read it one time in a book.
Oh. Huh.
OK.
I thought it sounded pretty planned out.
You're all right, Bunny.
You're smarter than you look.
Mm-mm-mm-mm.
[PHONE DIALLING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGS]
Brown residence?
WALTER: Uh, Archie Brown, please.
[ORGAN PLAYS "WEDDING MARCH"]
I'm afraid he's busy right now.
Look, you tell him it's an emergency.
Get in here.
What's the matter?
[ORGAN PLAYING]
Emergency call, sir.
Hello?
WALTER: Archie?
No, but he's busy.
Call back later.
What the hell's going on?
(WHISPERS) My son.
Wait a minute, dipstick.
You tell him it's an emergency.
Tell him it's about your mother.
Hey, look, this is Joe Brown.
Who the hell's this?
Look, I want to talk to your father.
You have exactly 30 seconds, moron.
Now get him!
[ORGAN PLAYING]
I don't believe it.
They're having the wedding!
I'm not there, and they're having the [HORN BEEPING]
damn wedding!
For Pete's sake, Bunny, I got enough problems.
That kid of yours is a real dink.
They're all dinks!
God, I am kidnapped, and they're having
champagne and wedding cake. - Shh!
They don't even know you're being kidnapped.
PASTOR: Dear friends--
Dad!
PASTOR: We have gathered here in the presence of God
to join Lionel-- [WHISTLE]
Dad! Come here.
Come here.
The phone is for you.
It's important.
Ah, would you hold on just one moment, please?
[CROWD MURMURING]
Play.
Play-- anything.
[ORGAN PLAYING]
He's coming.
[CROWD MURMURING]
Yeah, hello? This is Archie Brown.
Who the hell is this?
Look, you're pressing your luck, Archie.
Don't be a wise guy.
Don't act tough.
Just listen.
Now, your wife is my hostage.
And if you ever want to see her in one piece,
take a big, black double garbage bag, fill it with $100 bills,
50 to a packet, then tie it up with a red ribbon.
I'll call you Monday noon and tell you where to drop it.
Bunny's kidnapped? [CROWD GASPS]
WALTER: [INAUDIBLE] you're catching on.
Well, how much do you want?
Half a million.
Are you out of your mind?
I don't have that kind of money.
Look-- look-- look, I'm not here to bargain, bozo.
Half a million, or you never see your Bunny again.
Hold on, wait a minute.
How do I know--
how do I know you really have her?
Archie, is this you?
Oh, my god, it is you.
Are you OK, honey?
My only daughter, and you had the wedding without me.
You are such a creep.
I don't believe it!
Bunny, hold it!
We-- we didn't know that you were kidnapped!
We thought that you just--
well, that we thought that--
Put my daughter on.
Hello, Mom?
Mom, are you OK?
Oh.
Do you know where my Stones T-shirt is?
Get off the phone, you jerk!
I'm gonna talk to Tanya.
For god's sake, Bunny, you're supposed
to be scared and helpless.
Hello, Mom?
[CRYING] Are you getting married?
We didn't know!
We thought you ran off with somebody.
This is awful.
What are we going to do?
What about my honeymoon?
Go on your damn honeymoon.
See if I care.
Mom, we've got plane reservations to Hawaii.
If your father pays the money, I'll be home Monday.
So go, enjoy yourself.
What difference does it make?
I promise we'll call.
Hello, Archie?
You'll hear from me Monday noon.
No paying, no more Bunny.
[DIAL TONE]
God Almighty, Bunny!
What kind of nitwit are you?
This is supposed to be a kidnapping!
[BIRDSONG]
[FLUTE PLAYING]
That's a mighty lonely song.
But the Good Humor man has arrived
with a little bit of this and a little bit of food--
tacos, enchiladas, what not.
And, uh, a little bit of this.
Oh.
Oh, Walter!
[CRYING]
WALTER: It's OK.
Did they both have to turn out like Archie?
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
WALTER: All right, listen hard, Archie.
I'm only gonna say this once.
There's phone booth outside the Colorado Saddle Company.
It's on Wabash Street downtown.
Now, you park your car out front and wait for it to ring.
Answer it, and I'll tell you where to make the drop.
When I'm safe, and the money's counted,
you'll get your Bunny back.
If you try anything with the cops, she's history.
Oh, all right. Just tell me--
[DIAL TONE]
Not enough time to trace to call.
You're in competent hands, Mr. Brown.
OK, everybody, everything is planned.
Let's fall out.
Let's go.
[MURMURING]
This is what I figured a life of crime was like.
I'm not cut out for this.
Well, let's just quit right now.
At least you could have pick someplace nice.
There was a cockroach in the sink.
The toilet is filthy.
I'm not going in there for anything.
This is my fault?
You're the one who wanted to have the bum in the plans.
Well, there ain't no bums out uptown!
You want a bum, there's a bum.
All right, just stay put.
I'm going out and get us some [INAUDIBLE]..
What do you say?
Well, I don't know.
What do I have to do?
Three minutes work.
That's my kind of job.
All right.
I want you to meet RJ Okie, a genuine, bona fide bum.
How do, ma'am?
Good afternoon.
[SIGHS] Oh, here, come on, sit down.
Make yourself comfortable.
Thank you.
Oh.
Here, read the Bible?
[CHUCKLES] Oh, know it by heart.
Oh, well, good.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES]
OK, this is it.
OK, dial.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
WALTER: Hey, Archie Brown.
How you doing?
All right.
What's next? - Good.
Good.
You're getting into the spirit of it.
You see that alley on your left?
Now, take a trash bag and put it next to the fifth garbage can.
Got that?
Then you go back to your car and get the hell back
to your midnight insanity sale.
No tricks, no cops, or Bunny has had it.
Now go!
Go on, Okie.
Go on now!
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
No.
Get it, Okie.
Hey, you can't have that.
That's my job.
Give me that. Give me that!
That's my job!
Give me that!
Get it!
Oh, no!
[SIRENS]
[INAUDIBLE] cops.
That's our man.
Get him!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Wait a second.
Those are Archie's [INAUDIBLE].
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
There he is.
Follow me.
all right, bastard, I got a gun sticking in your back.
Now, where's the money?
- Uh-- - Where is it?
Uh.
It's in the trunk.
WALTER: [INAUDIBLE] open it!
Come on.
Take it out.
I want six hours to get away.
No cops, and I'll let her go.
Nobody gets a second chance, you understand?
I understand.
- Get in the trunk. - What?
Get in the trunk.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Look at it.
Oh.
Look at all that stuff.
Oh, Bunny, you have no idea how it
feels to have to give 50 grand to that cheatin' pole cat
Sebastian. I--
Whatever you're thinking--
Hey, don't worry.
Even I'm not that dumb.
I want you to know, Walter, no matter what happens--
Hey, now, don't say anything dumb.
It was worth everything Archie had to pay for it.
[LAUGHS]
Woo!
Mm.
[SHOWER RUNNING]
BUNNY: [HUMMING]
(SINGING) [INAUDIBLE] with a broken [INAUDIBLE]..
[INAUDIBLE]
[INAUDIBLE] again.
I [INAUDIBLE].
OK, I'm going.
I'll be back in about half an hour.
I'll be ready.
Can I use that little red suitcase for some of my things?
What things?
My flute and stuff.
Mm-hmm.
Walter?
Yeah?
Can I ask you something personal?
Mm-hm.
Do you ever think about your wife and son?
Oh, come on, Bunny.
One of the things I always liked about you was you
didn't ask questions like that.
Never mind then.
Yeah, I think about 'em, OK?
And it don't break my heart either.
[SIGHS]
[PHONE RINGING]
[SIGHS] Come on, Rowena, you're never gone.
[SIGHS]
So if you have him hanging over the curb like that,
all you do is come straight down on him.
You have no problem.
We were just talking about the best way
to break your legs, Walter.
You really should work on being more punctual.
Cut the crap, Sebastian.
I'm in a real big hurry.
I can imagine you are.
Relax, have a drink.
So I hear you're off the hook, my friend-- at least our hook.
[CHUCKLES]
It's all there.
You learn slowly, Walter, but you do learn.
You're lucky to still be among the living.
You made us very unhappy for a while.
What did you expect when you flimflammed me?
See, if I had any guts, I'd tell you to get your whole deal
and stick it where the sun don't shine.
[CLICKING]
Fortunately, you don't.
One more thing, here, there's a surprise
waiting for you in room 13.
Rowena? ROWENA: In the [INAUDIBLE].
All right, easy now.
I'll get it.
I'll get it/ I'll get it.
All right, get this.
Now [INAUDIBLE] do the talking.
You are a wiffle cattin' no-good craw bait.
And you got my craw for the last time-- the last time, Walter!
Now, you go around lettin' a bunch of low-life rotten,
law-breakers make a fool out of your ma.
I'm done looking out for you, you hear me?
I'm done.
WALTER: Now, for once in your life,
I want you to do what I tell you to do.
I want you to get on the bus and go to Aunt Tess.
Look, I'm gonna send you more money and a plane ticket.
I'll meet you in Mexico City in two weeks.
We're gonna have that vacation like we never had before.
I don't want those boys coming after my momma again.
Walter, please, let's get going.
You've been gone over an hour.
Oh, yeah.
I just had to see it again.
Hold your breath, Bunny.
Next stop, paradise.
Walter, you did pay off Sebastian, didn't you?
I most certainly, sweetheart.
Top and bottom bill in each stack [INAUDIBLE]
the rest are dye-marked idiot.
Nobody's perfect.
You liar, Walter.
You had to be greedy, didn't you?
You never, ever think of the consequences.
Well, Bunny, looks like I got a little apology
to make to you.
[SCOFFS] Oh, you just make me ill sometimes!
What were you looking at?
If your brains were dynamite, you couldn't blow your nose.
The sleazebag cheated me.
You can't let somebody walk all over you like that.
Might as well just toss in your cards.
[INAUDIBLE]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Woo-hoo-hoo! I lost him!
[CHUCKLES] That wasn't so dumb, was it?
Walter.
Hit it!
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
There they are again, Walter.
[INAUDIBLE].
BUNNY: They're gaining on us, Walter.
All right. come on.
If I did it once, I can do it again.
Just find me a road up here.
[HORN HONKING]
Walter.
WALTER: Get out the way!
Get that thing out of the way!
[HORN HONKING]
God, what is that stink?
Life, Bunny, life.
What the hell is that thing?
It's a a manure sprayer.
WALTER: [INAUDIBLE].
[GUNSHOT]
[SCREAMS]
[INAUDIBLE] believe it.
We're gonna get caught.
I'm blowing it again.
Walter, [INAUDIBLE]!
Do something.
Please, Walter!
[INAUDIBLE] damn luck.
[GUNFIRE]
Walter!
Hang on, honey.
Woo-hoo!
BUNNY: Walter!
Oh, honey, you're my good luck charm.
Ah-ha-ha!
This is good luck?
You-hoo-hoo!
[HORN HONKS]
Hey, [INAUDIBLE] thing.
[GUNFIRE]
[INAUDIBLE]
SEBASTIAN: Oh, I can't see.
STUBBS: Hit the brake.
Hit the windshield wiper.
SEBASTIAN: I can't see!
I don't believe this.
Walter, I'll get even with you!
[LAUGHS] Look at that!
Look at that!
That'll teach you to mess with Walter Sharphorn!
[AIRPLANE ENGINE SOUNDS]
Well, this is it.
We've been together five days.
Seems like 20 years.
It's been crazy.
Crazy is right.
And look at you--
15 years younger.
I am?
You look good, Bunny.
I think I know what you're going to do.
Come on with me.
You're the best woman I ever met in my life.
What'd you have to go and say that for?
Look, I--
I can't go without you.
I'd just be worrying about you all the time.
You?
Walter!
Yeah.
I care about you, Bunny.
I know.
Walter, you've been the biggest temptation of my life.
Come on.
I just can't.
Bunny, Mexico City, Acapulco--
just think about it.
Sounds nice, Walter.
But someday you'll understand.
Don't get caught for both our sakes.
Damn.
You're some spunky woman, I'll say that for ya.
Hey, you want to know what I like best about you?
You kept surprising me.
I don't deserve you, Bunny.
That should cover it.
Thank you.
Well, you have an hour in Houston and then straight
through to Mexico City.
Much obliged.
May I check that bag for you, Mr. Sharphorn.
Oh, uh, I really would prefer to carry it on, if I could.
Sure.
Looks like it'll fit under the seat.
I'll sit on it, honey, if I have to.
[LAUGHS] Hi, may I help you?
WOMAN (ON SPEAKER): Final call for Continental Airlines Flight
34 non-stop service from Denver to London
Gatwick Airport, departing on time from Gate 19B.
[GASPING] (WHISPERING) Oh, yeah.
BUNNY (VOICEOVER): Dear Walter, I'm off to Ireland.
I filled the little red suitcase,
but I've left you enough money to pay off
Sebastian or go to Mexico whichever
and some extra for Rowena, too.
I love you, Walter, but not enough to screw
up my life all over again.
I'll never forget you.
Love and kisses, Bunny.
PS, I'll keep my promise if you ever get caught.
Bunny.
Bunny!
[LAUGHS] Bunny!
[IRISH MUSIC PLAYING]
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]