[crowd clapping]
[dramatic instrumental music]
[puppy whimpering]
- Naughty baby, whatever will you about?
What if everyone should
run away from home?
Why, there would be no more home at all.
And then what should
your mommy do but cry?
You don't want your mommy to cry.
Do you?
- Elizabeth?
Elizabeth, we're leaving.
We're leaving now.
- Come back, you naughty baby.
- Oh yes, and if it were up to
you, we'd accomplish nothing.
- Sarah, no one doubts
your drive for a moment.
- Elizabeth.
Elizabeth Taylor, are you
deliberately being naughty?
- I merely question if it's natural
to put a child out to work.
- Oh, and you're such an expert
on the natural order, Francis?
Besides, I'm hardly sending
her off to the coal mines.
To have a chance to be more than an--
- Art dealer's wife?
- Oh my, we're full of canny
wisdom this morning, aren't we?
Get the bloody dogs.
Elizabeth, tell Daddy
this is what you want.
Tell him Mommy isn't
forcing you to do anything.
Tell him you have always
dreamed of being a movie star.
- But I haven't.
- What?
Is this your doing?
- Bye, bye Elizabeth.
- Bye, Daddy.
I want to be an actress.
Actresses can make
people believe anything.
- Yes, well, actresses go hungry.
I know, I saw enough of them when I tried
for a career in the theater.
Here you go.
Hop in.
But movie stars have everything.
All right now, we mustn't
keep Aunt Hedda waiting.
- Is Miss Hedda really my aunt, Mommy?
- Hedda Hopper may well turn
out to be our fairy godmother.
♪ Danube's so blue ♪
♪ I'm longing for you ♪
♪ My heart's ever true ♪
♪ Today ♪
- Sarah?
Perhaps if she had some accompaniment.
- I can't play.
Perhaps you?
- Oh god, no.
That's just there for show,
like everything else in this town.
And Sarah, she is a lovely child, but...
Elizabeth, the would is full
of things for you to do.
You can marry, teach, be a nurse.
You don't have to be an actress, you know.
Not to be happy.
- Aren't you a love?
Aren't you Mummy's precious love.
You're so pretty.
- You know, Sarah.
I might just have a
rabbit or two in my hat.
- Okay Hedda, what'd I do wrong?
- [laughing] Well don't
be such a goose, Sam.
Oh, I do hope I'm interrupting.
- You are.
We're just about to cast
the little girl for Lassie.
Stick around, you're gonna
have a scoop for your column.
- Oh really?
Well, Sam, you are about
to make a huge mistake.
- None of them are above four feet, Hedda,
it can't be that huge.
- Well, if you had read
my column recently,
you would know that
very dear family friends
have just arrived from London,
moments ahead of the blitz, as it were.
- I'm sorry Hedda, we pretty
much made our decision.
- Huh, you think you have.
Elizabeth, Sam Marks,
permit me to present,
Miss Elizabeth Taylor.
- [chuckling] I know all
about this little lady.
Her father Francis and I were
air raid wardens together.
He told me his wife was dying
to see her in the movies,
I told him I'd try and take a look at her.
Elizabeth.
- Yes sir?
- Elizabeth, do you think you can act?
- I have, many times.
- Where was that?
- A bit at Universal.
There's One Born Every Minute?
You must have seen it.
- I don't think so.
Elizabeth, do you think
you could talk to a dog
and make us believe you believe it?
- Could you wait a moment?
- Sure.
- I know you love me, Lassie,
because no matter how far away you go,
you'll always come back.
You know why?
Because you love me.
You don't want your Mummy to cry.
Do you know a secret, Lassie?
If everyone ran away from home,
there would be no more home.
- Hedda.
I owe you.
- Uh huh.
- Of all time, the
original Lassie stars in,
Lassie Come Home.
You must see the original Lassie
in her greatest movie
role, Lassie Come Home.
Introducing, Elizabeth Taylor.
- Darling girl, you got wonderful reviews
for your work in Lassie.
I wrote one myself, remember?
Why not rest a bit on your laurels?
- But Aunt Hedda, it
truly is my favorite book.
- Elizabeth, I think Mr. Mayer knows best.
Besides, your plate is quite full
with White Cliffs of Dover.
Your time will come, dear.
It has to, with Lassie
such a huge success.
- It isn't fair.
I was born to play Velvet Brown.
I ride.
I ride like a--
- Listen to me, Elizabeth.
You could turn yourself
into a flying horse
and they still won't
give you National Velvet.
They're looking for someone more mature.
- Taller?
- Well, taller, yes.
But someone more developed.
- You mean?
- Uh, we'll stick with taller.
[sentimental music]
- National Velvet, scene 28, take 2.
- Heels down, Elizabeth, heels down!
- What a determined
young lady, Miss Taylor.
Elizabeth has really
blossomed into Velvet Brown.
[cries out]
- Elizabeth!
- Cut!
- Let's go, come on!
- Are you all right?
Is it your back?
Get an ambulance, she's hurt her back!
- No no, don't do that.
I'm fine.
Smashing.
I ought to know to have kept
my heels down a bit more.
- That was quite a tumble, kiddo.
Let's call it a day.
- No no, don't.
I'll be fine.
Just let me catch my breath.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- Darling.
I know you think I push
too much, too hard,
but even I don't expect.
- Mummy.
I know that at first I didn't
want to be a movie star,
but now, now if I couldn't be in films,
I'd feel like a tree that fell down.
A tree without roots.
Isn't he wondrous?
I loved him at first sight.
Do you think they'd give
him to me after the film?
- Darling, after this film,
I imagine they'd give you anything.
- A sweeping saga of love,
tenderness and courage.
You'll thrill to the new screen sensation,
Elizabeth Taylor, as she
steals your heart in,
National Velvet.
[dramatic music]
- Bye, darling.
- Janie?
Why don't you continue with
your essay on Wordsworth
that you started last week.
Dickie, Darrell.
- More like last month.
I've been writing the same
essay through my last two films.
- Oh, children!
I'm afraid you'll have to forgo
your science test until tomorrow.
Mr. Strickland of
publicity wants to come in
and make a few suggestions
before you meet with photo play.
- Night shoot?
- Three in a row.
Been up at the bloody crack
of dawn to study my lines.
- It's worth it, though.
Everyone says National
Velvet will make you a star.
- I'm already a star.
- Three, two.
[bright music]
- This is Hedda Hopper.
And this is Hollywood.
Elizabeth Taylor is in New
York to be photographed
for her 17th birthday
spread in Life Magazine
by Felipe Hoffman.
- It's rather scary.
I mean, Life Magazine.
- It's your birthday spread in Life.
I think it's time the studio realized
that their baby girl is all grown up.
- At 17?
- 17?
Famous.
You're uncomfortable?
- No.
Maybe.
- Know why?
Because I am focusing on your whole body.
It is a woman's body.
Stunning.
Like a woman.
Free, like a woman.
Sensuous.
- I don't know.
Inside I still feel like a girl.
- But you're not a little girl.
You are a woman.
Yes, yes.
You have bosoms.
So stick them out!
[romantic music]
- Well.
There's your Mr. Montgomery Clift.
- He's beautiful, isn't he, Mummy?
- Go say hello.
- Coffee?
Don't do that.
- Do what?
- Stare at me.
- Oh.
Me too, I'm so tired
of people staring at me
and telling me I'm beautiful.
I hate it.
- Well you are beautiful.
And it says so right here.
And I'm beautiful.
This is the movies, even the
ugly people are beautiful.
So what?
- I'm Elizabeth Taylor.
- Monty Clift, how do you do?
Listen, you know what
the word is around here?
You're the girl on the candy box cover.
Is that what you want?
To be a thing?
Because I have to be honest
with you, Bessie Mae.
I don't do my best work
against a mannequin.
- Well then you'd better help
me, mister method acting,
because I've done my finest
work opposite a horse and a dog.
[barking]
[laughing] Stop it!
- Uh oh.
Oh, dear.
- What's wrong?
Are you all right?
- Dog biscuits.
For the shakes.
Great method actor, huh?
Still getting stage fright.
- Pain pills.
For my back.
Came courtesy of National Velvet.
- Oh, we're a sorry pair, Bessie Mae.
A sorry pair.
- Bessie Mae.
[laughing]
Monty look at you, you're so thin.
Come, let's eat something.
- Oh dammit, I'm not hungry.
- Oh come on, you look as if
you never eat, and you have to.
You can't live on.
Go on then, do it for me.
Do it for Mama.
[laughing]
- Oh, good grief, I got the
same hand I got last time.
- I bet a dime.
- Me too.
- Come on, Elizabeth.
- Rewrites for the next scene.
- Excuse me George, but
what the hell is this?
This is, this is ridiculous!
No young lady would speak
this way to the man she loves.
- She will.
- Potato face.
- Elizabeth, will you pay
attention to the game.
[sweeping romantic music]
- I'm the happiest person in the world.
- Second happiest.
- Oh Angela, if only I could
tell you how much I love you.
If only I could tell all.
- Tell 'em.
Tell 'em all.
- And, cut.
Print.
[bell ringing]
I was right, wasn't I?
About that new line.
- Don't be ridiculous.
No woman wants to be Mama
to the many she loves.
[dog barking]
- Why don't you take the day off work?
We could drive down to
the beach or something.
- Knock knock, I come bearing gifts!
- Well hello Bessie Mae!
What a lifesaver.
Uh, give me a minute Billy
and we'll go for our little drive, okay?
- Right, I'll see you later.
- I'm sorry, I'm interrupting.
- No no no, no no no.
Now you hate me.
- Hate you?
My God Monty, I love you.
- I know.
I know.
- I have since that first day
when you refused to speak to my breasts.
- Well Bessie Mae, let me
now address your breasts.
- [laughing] Stop it.
- Don't give me so much credit.
- Oh, damn you.
You've broken my heart.
- I know.
Hell, I've broken my own.
You're the girl, Bessie Mae.
If anyone could have lured me
away from my wicked loving.
- It doesn't matter.
Whatever happens, I will
always be here for you.
Mama will always be here for you.
[bright jazz music]
- Aren't you ever gonna dance?
- I suppose.
- It's Monty, right?
- Oh, that is so silly,
just because I want to be
alone with my thoughts.
- You are still in love with that guy.
- Monty and I have great
respect for each other.
He understands the nature of me.
- Excuse me?
Ever since A Place In The Sun,
you have become queen of the world.
- You know, Debbie, it's like
your souls meet somewhere else
and they come here.
And if they don't meet again,
then you spend your whole life
like a wanderer, searching.
- Jeepers.
- Jeepers?
I tell you something as
deeply moving as that,
and you answer me like a teenager!
- I am a teenager!
And so are you.
- [sighs] Will no one
treat me like a grownup?
- Well that handsome hunk over there
seems to think you've grown up enough.
- Who is that?
- Nicky Hilton.
- Who?
- His parents only own
the Waldorf Astoria,
and about a hundred other hotels.
- Hmm.
He's coming this way.
Say something.
- [squeals] Broccoli broccoli!
- Stop it, Debbie. [laughing]
- Excuse me.
You don't know who I am,
but you're Liz Taylor.
- Oh, I hate that name.
- Liz, or Taylor?
I can change one of them.
- Liz.
- I'm Nicky Hilton.
- And this is a close friend
of mine, Debbie Reynolds.
- Debbie.
As her close friend,
do you think Elizabeth
should dance with me?
- I'm always telling Elizabeth what to do,
and she never listens. [laughing]
- Okay wiseguy, what should I do?
- Go dance with him.
[slow jazz music]
- Test for picture number
17271, Father Of The Bride,
director Vincent Minelli,
actor Elizabeth Taylor.
- Turn, please.
Turn right.
And left.
- It's crazy, I know, so sudden.
But if I mean to escape
I've got only two options.
College, or marriage.
And with everyone making
my decisions for me,
I can't even pee without instructions.
- Uh oh, Bessie Mae, sound
like you're going method on me,
what with a the Father
Of The Bride and all.
- [laughing] Be serious.
- Okay.
Do you love this guy?
- Would you mind?
- [sighs] I just want you
to be happy, that's all.
You be careful, though.
Whatever you decide,
I heard a few things.
- You mean he's not an
actor or a suffering poet.
[laughing]
I do believe you're jealous.
- Okay, maybe I am.
- Well, good.
[cheering]
- What's next, Liz?
- Well I want nothing more than
to spend the rest of my life
as Mrs. Conrad Nicholson Hilton Junior.
- Oh good evening.
Hasn't it been a lovely day?
Do please follow me.
Miss Taylor, this is your table.
- Wrong, pal.
We're looking for the table
of Mr. and Mrs. Hilton.
- Oh Mr. Hilton, I do apologize.
This of course is your table.
- Thank you.
- Bon appetit.
- Husband.
I've only been able to
stay that for a week.
Husband, husband, husband.
Promise you'll love me forever.
No, more than forever.
- Fine.
- If you were an actor, I'd
make you work on that reading.
- Well I'm not an actor, okay?
You got that?
- Oh please, this is my honeymoon.
- Oh please, just one.
- Yes, please.
- Are you famous too?
- Not to old bats like you I'm not.
- The nerve of him.
Thank you.
- This is my honeymoon.
- Mine too.
- Don't embarrass me.
- Waiter.
Bring us a fifth of something.
Gin!
And raise.
- Three threes, fold.
[wistful piano music]
[glass breaking]
- Nicky, honey?
That you?
- Yeah.
- Are you all right?
- Win big?
- Yeah.
Don't ever pull that Hollywood star crap
with me again, you bitch.
[cries in pain]
- There were many violent outbursts.
He was indifferent to me.
- I'm sorry Mrs. Hilton,
we just can't hear you.
- He was indifferent to me.
It caused me great mental anguish.
- I understand that you have
substantial income of your own
and you wish to waive any alimony,
and that you petition for the
right to use your maiden name.
- Yes.
- Divorce granted, this
marriage is dissolved.
[people shouting]
- Miss Taylor, what's next for you?
- How do you feel, Miss Taylor?
- I've let myself in.
- Mother, this is my place.
- Well, shall I go back out to knock?
What's that your cooking?
French toast for lunch?
Well I won't say a word.
Isn't this nice?
Your own place.
My little girl, all grown up.
You know, we haven't said
a thing about Ivanhoe yet.
- [sighs] I am committed,
but it's a terrible script.
- Well that may well be,
but a few months in London,
away from all the press,
help them forget about your marriage.
- Mummy.
- Darling, clean up that egg, will you?
It's dripping.
- Mummy, have you spoken with Ben Thau?
- About what?
- About London.
- [laughing] Well I know
all about London darling,
we used to live there.
- About how I won't be
needing a chaperone there.
- This was Mr. Thau's idea?
- And even though you'll be staying,
you'll still be on salary.
Benny promised.
- I see.
- I'm sorry, but it's as you said.
I'm all grown up.
- You're burning the toast.
- All right, turn over.
Camera rolling.
Speed.
Ivanhoe 72, marker.
[board clapping]
And, action.
- That is the way it must be, Rebecca.
That is the way it must be.
Take it again.
- But I don't understand why.
- It is the law of the land.
- And cut.
Is there some problem, Elizabeth?
- Yes, this headpiece weighs a ton.
It's killing my poor back.
- Well I'm more concerned about dialogue.
Can we put a little life into it?
- You should have told that to the writer.
- Sir Walter Scott?
He's dead.
- You're telling me.
- Well, if it isn't Michael Wilding,
England's answer to Robert Taylor.
- I could never aspire to
fill your chain mail, Robert.
- [laughing] Well, slumming, Michael?
Or have you rediscovered a
passion for Sir Walter Scott.
- As a matter of fact,
I've become all curious
about the ways and habits
of Hollywood starlets.
- Well, this one's having a fit.
- Quite fantastic, just
like a storm at sea.
Don't care how many ships go down,
just as long as we can watch them.
[laughing]
- Am I allowed to meet your friend?
- This is Michael Wilding.
Michael, this is Elizabeth Taylor.
- Hello.
[bell ringing]
[sentimental music]
- My dear, you look enchanting.
Please.
- Can you believe this is the first night
I've been out on the town?
- You know, I don't.
A beauty like you.
- Strange, everyone takes for granted
that I have a date every night,
and nobody thinks to ask.
- Oh, so I'm Mr. Nobody?
- [laughing] You are funny.
- For an older man?
- Stop that, my father's an older man.
- Are you quite sure
you wanted to say that?
[laughing]
- I like older men.
They're wise about things
like, you know, life, love.
- I'm not sure anyone's really that wise.
Not about love.
The poets claim it, but I don't think
they really know what
they're complaining about.
- God, if you couldn't believe in love.
- Do you believe in love?
- I used to.
Used to be the most
important thing in my life.
- I'm terribly sorry.
- I'll bet you'd marry me if
I were older, wouldn't you?
- I tell you what.
You stay the same age,
and I'll get younger.
- Elizabeth, please, no
thanks are necessary.
We've always been a family here at Metro.
Beside the, Michael's a great actor.
We'd be more than happy
to put him under contract.
- Oh, it'd be such a
help to us, thank you.
- Good.
- Also, a loan.
We would love to get a house, a big house.
We're so eager to start
a family, you know.
And have dozens of children. [laughing]
- Well yes, but not too soon.
Elizabeth, we have big
plans for you, you know.
[laughing]
- You are certifiable, you know that?
- Michaelangelo had the
roof of the Sistine.
I make due with only slightly less space.
- Bugger off, you British weasel.
- You're as big as a
barn and mad as a hatter
and I love you and I want you.
- Don't forget to sign.
[laughing]
- Oh, Elizabeth.
You won't believe this
script the studio sent me,
it's nonsense, utter nonsense.
- What is this, the third,
fourth script you've rejected?
No pay, no play, Michael,
read the fine print.
- You'd think they'd send
me anything top drawer.
I mean, a man does have his dignity.
- Dignity doesn't pay the bills, I do.
I've done four dreadful
films back to back,
and to be perfectly honest
with you, I feel as...
I feel as though I'm drowning.
A bit of help from the home
front wouldn't be amiss.
- And cut!
[whistling]
Print.
Get this over to the production office.
- Hey dollface, you made it.
You meet Jimmy?
- Hello, Jimmy!
Is he always like that?
- No, sometimes he's just rude.
Hey George, look who's here.
- Hello Mama.
- Hello potato face.
- That's right dollface,
you show him who's boss.
- You know why you're here?
Because I told old George
I wanted Liz Taylor
or I wouldn't do this damn thing.
What do you think of that?
- Well I think you're
pretty terrific, Mr. Hudson.
A film like Giant doesn't
come along every day.
- Well neither does a face
and figure like yours.
You're so beautiful Liz,
a man has to squint.
- That's the problem.
Until you get rid of
that phony MGM veneer,
you never will be an actress.
- Excuse me, Mr. Stevens.
[playful music]
Is this what a real actress
is supposed to look like?
Hey, I want it understood,
I'm more than a pretty face.
Got that?
[laughing]
- God pity the guy that doesn't pay homage
to that pretty face.
[bright country music]
- What you got there?
- I got a little vodka,
mixed with a vermouthy.
- I got no vermouthy, partner.
- Well here partner, what are you having?
- Kahlua.
[laughing]
- Hey, do you mind?
You know what you get when
you mix vodka with Kahlua?
Chocolate martini.
[laughing]
Chocolate martinis!
- City folk.
- Good evening.
Could you direct me to
Miss Taylor, please.
- I'm sorry, sir.
- I've just flown into this place
from an air core base in El Paso.
I'm tired, I'm hungry,
and I'd like to see Miss Elizabeth Taylor.
I'm the husband?
- Oh yes sir.
I believe she's having
dinner with Mr. Hudson.
[laughing]
[emotional music]
- Hello.
I always seem to
fall a little in love with my leading man.
Guess I always will.
It's nothing.
- Well I guess everything
ain't perfect in paradise.
- Come on, little one, let's go.
It's nap time, we can get
up and play later, okay?
- Thank you.
My God am I having fun.
- You will try to be pleasant, won't you?
There's some people here
that could help you.
- You know I haven't got
your talent, Elizabeth.
I can't just snap my fingers
and have any man do what I want.
- Am I really so bad?
- Bad, no.
Spoiled, maybe.
- I didn't mean for it
to turn out like this.
I do love you.
- When business permits.
But why should I complain?
- Come on, Bessie, have some bubbles.
- [laughing] Rock.
- What's the skinny on Rain Tree?
- Strictly hush hush.
The South loses, you know.
- Good script?
- I suppose it's sort of
a Scarlet O'Hara gone mad.
But I don't get to kiss Clark Gable.
I get that sweet pea.
- I thought you were too tired to come.
- Too tired to come, Michael.
But Bessie Mae called and called.
- And what?
- She always wins.
- Oh, yes.
- I guess you wanna talk about, um.
Well, you know.
She has marital problems.
- She does indeed.
You know, I think Elizabeth's
biggest problem is,
she can have any man she wants.
- And that compelled you
to cavort in the pool
with a couple of, what were they, Michael?
Strippers?
Who told everything to
Confidential Magazine.
- Utter nonsense.
These girls dropped by,
nothing really happened.
And how was I to know
they'd sell the story?
- Michael.
- Uh huh.
- You live in Hollywood.
And you're married to Elizabeth Taylor.
- I heard she was in
Texas with whatshisname,
doing God knows what.
And what was I supposed to do here?
Scoop up after the bloody dogs.
You know, she sleeps every
night surrounded by her animals.
I mean, where does that leave me?
- Here's to the dogs of marriage.
- Cheers.
[laughing]
- Why don't you just sleep here?
- No no really, I'm fine.
- You know, it's okay.
I'll get in front of him.
- What good will that do?
- It'll keep him slow,
guide the way for him.
- So long.
- Be careful.
- I'll call you tomorrow.
[tense music]
[tires screeching]
[crashing]
Okay.
What? You can't breathe.
It's a tooth.
Mama's got it, it's okay.
[indistinct chatter]
- It's Monty Clift.
- Stop it, get the hell out of here!
Vultures, get out of here!
Get away!
[sirens blaring]
Yoo hoo!
Monty!
Here he is, Monty.
Your replacement if you're
not back on the set in a week.
Now, he's good, baby.
Trained in the method, you know.
- Oh no.
- Yes.
I've missed you, you sweet old disaster.
But you look great.
- So they tell me.
- Well they're right.
- Why are you so excited
about, what's going on?
- I ran into Mike Todd again last night.
- Oh.
- He's really great fun.
[sighs] And so different from Michael.
- What about Michael?
[phone ringing]
- Michael Wilding.
- Michael, it's Elizabeth.
- Elizabeth, so nice to hear you.
Tell me, how's Monty getting along?
- Oh he's fine, fine.
Um, Michael.
I need you to know that I love you
and I will always love you.
- That's very comforting.
- What I'm trying to say,
and I want you to hear it from me
before it appears in the papers,
darling, I filed for legal separation.
- Well thanks, but I'd rather
have read it in the newspapers.
- Yes?
- I could have pretended it had
to do with two other people.
- You tell me if I'm
interrupting, I'll get lost.
- Not at all Mike, we
were waiting for you.
- Yes we were, though I'm not sure why.
- Are you leaving?
- Me? No, why?
This is my office.
It says so on the door.
Benny Thau.
- I thought you was going some place.
- Benny, I think he's being subtle.
- Oh. [chuckling]
Hey, excuse me.
- Well don't run off, Benny.
Please, don't run off.
- Please, play nice Mike.
- Well I'm not used to being
summoned this way, Mr. Todd.
I've been waiting, what is it, 30 minutes?
- You comfortable there?
- Hey, get your mitts off of me!
- Hey there, is that more comfortable?
Now you're the damnedest
prettiest woman I ever saw.
That's for openers.
Now, I'm gonna lay my lot on the table
and I think you'll have to take a look
and consider the cards I have showing.
I was president of my own
company when I was 18.
The age I am now, and that ain't that old,
I've produced 16 shows up in Central Park,
maybe you've heard of it?
The Hot Mercado?
Anyway, the bottom line is,
I grossed 18 million bucks on Broadway,
and that's just the cards I have showing.
Now, you didn't ask me
what my hold card is.
You only see the up cards.
Nothing but aces.
But the hold card is, Miss Taylor,
and I will turn it over for you,
the hold card is, I'm in love with you.
Don't argue against it,
because I know how I feel.
- You what?
- I know it surprised
the hell out of me too,
but not half as much as this, baby.
I not only love you,
I'm gonna marry you.
What do you say to that?
- Speechless.
- Oh, great!
You believe in fate?
- I believe I'm leaving.
- Liz, Liz!
Now don't get on my bad side now.
- Don't call me Liz, Mr. Todd.
- All right, Miss Taylor.
We're getting married because
like I said, it's fate.
And I love you.
- Do you understand I'm a married woman?
- I understand you're breaking up.
- It's none of your damned business.
- I'm making it my business.
- And I don't like being
mauled in an office,
thrown around the furniture,
and told who I'm going to marry next!
- You know what this means?
- What what means?
- It means you and me,
you are never going to see me again!
Ever!
[door slamming]
- Great to have you back,
Monty, you look terrific.
Hell, we all should look
so good before a car crash.
All right everyone, we'll
block in half an hour.
- I have a present for you.
- What?
[gasps] Ooh.
Monty.
- It's the tooth.
[laughing]
- I like a good joke.
- What are you doing here?
- Well I was flying east on business
and I heard you were back on your feet
and I thought I'd make a little detour,
and, Mike Todd.
- Thanks, Mike.
- Roses.
How very ordinary.
- Well then I'm glad I
didn't bring them for you.
My mother had a fondness for roses.
I thought they would add
to your general enjoyment of the occasion.
- Thanks again, Mike.
Excuse me.
- You're right, roses are ordinary.
And there ain't nothing
ordinary about Liz Taylor,
or Mike Todd for that matter.
This is for you.
- Mike.
[gasps] God, it's beautiful.
- I can be a horse's butt, Liz.
I think we've already established that.
But I think also that
I am the man for you.
I think we both know that too.
- Mike, I don't know what to say.
- Well I do, so you just do
the listening, all right?
Lizzy, you've been married
to a kid and an old man.
It's time you took a mate.
You know, one who gives
as good as he gets.
Sure, I'll roar.
So, you roar back.
Then we'll laugh our asses
off while we spend my money.
[laughing]
- I heard you always get what you want.
- Is that bad?
- No, no.
I admire a man who get
anything what he wants.
As long as he sets his heart to it.
- I already told you
where my heart is set.
- Now it's time to kiss! [laughing]
[clapping]
[bright music]
[booming]
[laughing]
- Oh Mike, look, our initials.
We're up in the sky together.
Oh Mike look, there's something.
Promise me you'll never leave me.
Promise.
- You get the picture?
The plane is about to taxi out.
I'm looking for her.
Where is this fathead I married?
- This is extraordinary,
you mixed mashed potatoes with the corn?
- And cream.
- So I called airport security and I say,
you guys seen some
overdressed fatass around?
- We're not listening, Mike.
- You know, it's real important
that you two are here with Debbie and me.
- Come on Eddie, now I'm
trying to tell you the story.
- Debbie.
- Will you listen please?
- To Elizabeth, to Mike,
a man as important to me as my own father.
- Thanks, kid.
Thank you.
So anyway, I'm at
Heathrow, and our plane's
about to hop over the pond, as
they say, and I got no wife.
She's in the bar.
- Flying makes me nervous.
- Sucking up all the bloody marys.
- I was sitting right
underneath the loudspeaker,
waiting to be called.
They never announced the flight.
- Liz, you listen to me.
You don't hear nothing
you don't wanna hear.
You're like that damned
Alice in Wonderland.
You are sitting on the other side
of the damned looking glass.
- Imagine, Mike has read
Alice in Wonderland.
- Sure I read it, it's a classic.
- And you read the entire book?
Or some kindly adult read it to you?
[laughing] He's such a child.
- I like children.
- Yes Deborah, we know.
- Golly, is it a federal crime?
All I said is I like children.
- Look broad, I'm the man here, all right?
I'm your kindly adult.
So you just zip up your lip!
What's the matter with you?
You stop.
[playful music]
- Get off of her!
Get off of her!
- Debbie.
- Hey, don't be such a Girl Scout.
You really are square.
- Is there desert?
- Mike loves desert. [laughing]
- It's a wonderful world,
if you'll only take the
time to go around it.
- Formally challenging me to
go around the world in 80 days.
- Michael Todd's Around
the World in 80 Days.
We make all the stops.
Two oceans.
Five seas.
And 16 countries.
- Welcome home.
I guess it's safe to say
that you've taken the world by storm?
- It's all Mike, it's his picture.
I just went along.
- Well there is an awful lot of publicity
about your public spats.
- What? Bite your tongue.
- Well you see, I heard
that at the London airport
they had to call security
to separate you two.
Something about a champagne bottle.
- That is the most filthy thing
I've ever heard in my life.
I don't usually get cross.
- Well, what about this?
- Look, I just wish everybody
could be as unhappy as we are,
then there'd be no wars and no problems.
The world would be quite nice.
- You know, when I have something to say,
I holler, hey Liz, she says, hey Mike.
You wanna make a case
out of that, too bad.
- It doesn't matter.
- We're so happy.
- I don't care what anybody
thinks, because we know,
and we'll know 10 years
from now, 20 years from now,
if we're still alive.
- Liz, Liz, Liz.
I'm quoting you now.
You once said that you had
the mind of a child and
the body of a woman.
- That's when I was 15, yes.
- Well now that you're married to such a,
such a man of the world as Mr. Todd,
do you think that you're
maturing somewhat?
- I hope so, otherwise I'd be
slightly retarded, wouldn't I?
- You're not playing with children here.
That was a very good comeback.
Okay, broad.
I am the man here.
- Yes.
- Huh, babydoll?
- I'm fathead.
[laughing]
Meow.
- Oh, now don't start with the cat.
- Meow, you don't want me?
Hmm?
You don't want your little
cat to purr for you?
- You're not gonna do that picture.
- You don't want me on a hot tin roof?
- [laughing] You're
doing Don Quixote next,
and you're doing it for me.
You understand?
- Hey bozo, you wanna fight?
- Yeah, you want one?
- I'll ask you first.
- Why you little!
[laughing]
- So how do you feel, Miss Taylor?
- What are your plans for the future?
- What's the baby's name?
- Eliza Todd.
- Oh, then it's a girl.
- Of course it's a girl.
The world's not ready
for another Mike Todd.
[laughing]
- Action.
Cut!
And print.
[bell ringing]
- Ah Lizzie, I have to admit
it, you're damn good, you are.
- Hello.
- Now who's gonna believe
a story like this?
What guy's not gonna
fall for a dame like you?
How's the old back, Lizzie?
- Not so bad.
Why?
- I sure do wish we were alone right now.
I love you so much, it hurts.
[thunder booming]
- It's not too bad.
- Well it doesn't take
a medical genius to say,
lady, you are sick!
104 is sick.
- I'm flying to New York tonight.
Medical genius.
- Nuts, too.
- Delusional.
It's the fever.
- Oh, Mikey Mike.
My fathead sweetie.
They're giving you Showman
of the Year tomorrow night.
- So?
They'll name me it every year.
- 1200 people at the Waldorf Astoria.
- Am I wrong, doc?
- I'd say there's gonna
be one less than 1200
at the Waldorf tomorrow night.
- Hey!
[laughing]
Hi you guys, Mommy's real sick now.
[children shouting]
- Let's take the puppies,
and we'll go rustle up some cookies, huh?
- Say bye to Mommy.
- I love you, I love you.
- This is a good angle.
- For what, a picture about a corpse?
- I'm gonna use it in my next picture.
- Kiss me.
- I already did, won't change my mind.
- Then kiss me for the hell of it.
- Oh God, you make me so happy.
[thunder booming]
- Oh, Mike.
- Don't you worry, sweetie.
I can fly above any storm.
I married you, didn't I?
I'll call you from Tulsa.
- What time?
- Three AM sharp.
- Don't forget.
- Yes, Mummy.
Oh, forgot something!
[laughing]
I love you.
- I love you.
[thunder booming]
[suspenseful music]
Doctor?
This isn't a medical
emergency or anything.
- Elizabeth, what's wrong?
- It's after three.
- Tell me.
- Mike was supposed to
call from Tulsa, by three.
- Mike can take care of himself.
- I have this feeling.
- I can hear you smoking.
- I'm not.
- Liz, you're sick.
Go to sleep.
- When Mike calls.
No, no!
[crying]
- I'm sorry Liz, I'm so sorry.
Mike, the plane went down.
There were no survivors.
- No!
No, God!
Why?
[people talking from outside]
[car honking]
- Eddie.
- Mike.
- I'm glad you're here!
- I got here as fast as I could.
Is she?
- Go to her.
- You think?
- You're the perfect one.
Mike loved you so much.
- You're right.
Oh, this is a nightmare.
But, for Mike's sake.
- For hers too.
- Eddie.
You know what I figured out?
Mike and I were married 413 days exactly.
No one's ever gonna know
how much I loved that man.
- Me too.
- You did, didn't you?
- Did I ever tell you
about the time he said,
most boys dream of growing up to be
the president of the United States,
but not me, he said.
I dream of growing up and
marrying Elizabeth Taylor.
- Big, overdressed,
fatass broad. [laughing]
- You know, when we were
in Europe, Debbie and me,
and we ran into you and Mike,
I have to be honest, I was so envious.
- Of what?
Our brawls? [laughing]
- Yeah.
Yeah, you two were so close.
- I feel like half a pair
of scissors without him.
- I think,
Mike would want you to
get on with your life.
- Gonna invite me in?
- No, I'll come to you.
- I didn't get a chance to tell you, but,
the trouble with people
dying is, it's stupid.
- That's what Mike would have said.
Oh Richard, Mike's barely cold
and all they can think
about is their damn movie.
- This town.
I found things to shoot,
shooting around you.
Hey, kid.
I've been worried about you.
- Thanks.
[sighs] Oh, gosh.
I haven't been on this
lot since I was a child.
Went to school here.
I've given MGM my entire life.
And all they can say is,
all they want is to stuff me
back into the meat grinder.
- Hey, I'm with you on this.
We'll manage.
- They fired Judy.
Judy Garland, for God's sake!
Gable, Tracy, oh, and
they let Garbo sneak away
without so much as a thank you.
- Look.
I don't give a damn about this picture.
We'll recast.
You, please, go home.
It's a movie, for crying out loud!
- You're one of the few men
in this town who'd say that.
- Yeah, I'm a hell of a guy.
[emotional music]
- I think Mike would want
me to get back to work.
- Well, if that's what you
think Mike would have wanted.
- I came here today so you
would convince me to come back.
- No, you came here to convince yourself.
Now get your butt over to wardrobe.
[dogs barking]
[laughing]
- Hey, I got your message.
What's wrong?
- Oh no, nothing.
I wanted to give you something.
It was Mike's.
- His gold money clip?
Are you sure?
- Positive.
Mike loved you like a son.
Me too.
Sit down.
- I'd love it if you could come to Vegas,
to my opening at the Tropicana.
Or maybe that wouldn't
be such a good idea,
people might think...
- Not if Debbie's with you.
- She hates Vegas.
She can't stand the guys I hang out with,
she thinks I gamble too much.
- Well, you do.
[laughing]
- Yeah.
Is that a crime?
- Not in Vegas.
That's the charm.
Eddie, what do you want?
What do you really want?
- I want out.
- And what does Debbie want?
- She wants the marriage to work.
- That is a problem.
- I've got a bigger problem.
I think I'm falling in love with you.
I wanna marry you.
[popping]
[laughing]
- Fill her up.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
- Yeah?
Deb.
Debbie.
How did you know?
Oh.
Well that was a good guess.
Debbie, uh, listen.
This isn't easy.
Uh, Elizabeth and I are together here.
We're in love, Debbie.
- What did she say?
- She said, we'd discuss
it, just come home.
- Are you going home, Eddie?
- God, how could I?
- Frankly, I'm shocked
such lies would be printed.
Eddie and Liz are just good friends.
Now what's wrong with a good friend
taking another friend out for the evening.
- Debbie, you do that very well, but,
this is Hedda.
Level with me.
We both know Eddie is not
exactly mister picket fence.
What's really happening?
- All I'm saying, is Eddie's a great guy.
I love him.
Don't blame Eddie.
- Level with me.
I'll find out anyway.
The word is, that they are breaking up
and you are the cause.
- That's bull.
I don't break up marriages.
Besides, you don't break
up a happy marriage.
- You cannot hurt Debbie this way
without hurting yourself more.
Elizabeth, she truly loves Eddie.
- He doesn't love her, he never did.
The marriage was a farce.
- What do you think Mike
would think about all this?
- Mike's dead!
I'm alive.
What do you expect me to do, sleep alone?
[phone ringing]
You viper!
You depicted me as something
cruel and absolutely heartless!
- Darling, I only wrote what you told me.
- I didn't think you'd
print it, for God's sake!
- Darling, that's my job.
- You betrayed me, Aunt Hedda.
I will never forgive you.
- I would imagine Debbie's
singing the same song these days.
[crashing]
[clapping]
Eddie's ruined, of course.
Hate mail is flowing in like a flood
in the streets of this town.
The network's dropped him.
Only that element out in Las
Vegas will hire him any more.
The man does have a full-time job.
Full-time Elizabeth.
But then, you'd know all about
that, wouldn't you, Sarah?
- I won't say a bad word about Elizabeth.
But if she had listened to me,
this never would have happened.
That Fisher man has taken her
off to Europe for a honeymoon.
Elizabeth says she
hopes it lasts 40 years.
- Poor Eddie.
[speaking in foreign language]
- Do you speak English?
No that's okay, that's
okay, just put it down.
Very good, very good, that's fine.
This can go downstairs in storage.
[speaking in foreign language]
- Could you order me up a scotch?
- In a sec, babe.
[phone ringing]
- Really, I'm in so much
pain, my back again.
Are you going to answer that?
What in God's heaven is this?
- Oh, it's fine.
Just medicine.
Don't worry, it's all
been prescribed for me
by Dr. Jacobson in New York.
- Oh Eddie, don't you read the magazines?
That's Dr. Feelgood!
He's notorious!
- It's just vitamins, and
a bunch of other stuff.
- Stuff?
Damn right, stuff.
Stuff mixed with amphetamines.
With all kinds of stuff.
- Yeah, uppers, so what?
- God, this frightens me, Eddie.
How long have you been doing this?
- For a while, it helps me perform.
What about all the pills you take?
- Mine are prescribed
but a real doctor, Eddie.
Come on.
[phone ringing]
- Yeah?
Oh yeah, hi Walter.
No, I can hear you.
It sound like you're next door.
Oh, you're next door to Daryl Zanuck.
You're in Hollywood.
Very funny.
It's Walter Wanger.
- Oh, it's that Cleopatra thing.
You talk to him.
- He says Fox is ready to
go the distance with you.
- Tell him I'm too young
to go the distance.
- Walter?
She's in her room now,
she's learning French verbs or something.
But go ahead and I'll write it down.
- Tell him I'll do it for a million bucks
against 10 percent of the
gross from the first dollar.
- No one's gotten a million dollars.
- Or a percentage of the gross.
- Well she just stepped in.
Are you sure you wanna hear?
She says she'll do it
for a million dollars
against 10 percent of the gross.
- From the first dollar.
All right, Walter.
- So what'd he say?
Forget it?
- No.
- Then what'd he say?
- He said,
I'll get back to you.
- No! [laughing]
- Liz, before we can let you go to England
to play Cleopatra, for one million,
[laughing] 10 percent of the gross,
I have to remind you that
you owe us a picture,
and that picture's got
to be Butterfield 8.
- That is outrageous!
- I'm afraid it means that
you're gonna have to do
Butterfield 8 for considerable
less compensation.
- You're asking me to play a whore.
- That word does not
appear in our screenplay.
And I want to remind
you that Butterfield 8
is a bestselling novel by a renowned
and respected American author.
- I don't care!
I won't do it, under any circumstance.
- Well, if you refuse to abide
by the terms of our contract,
I'm afraid it leaves us
no choice but to block you
from working anywhere
for the next two years.
- And this is how you choose
to end an 18-year relationship.
- Liz, sentiment went out
of this business years ago.
Adjust! I've had to.
Oh yes, but that's the business.
Personally, me, I'm still
a very sentimental guy.
I remember the luck we
made with National Velvet,
and that horse, that
beautiful horse, King Charles,
that you loved so much.
- Thanks a lot, you SOB.
I'm still paying for the
feed on that damn nag!
- Liz! Elizabeth!
Don't do this to me.
- You can make me do it, but
you can't make me act in it.
I'll be unprepared, I'll be late.
- I think you're too much
the professional for that.
- In a pig's eye.
But I want Eddie there.
- Well of course.
- To play the role of Steve.
- What?
He's a singer!
- Singing is acting.
He's acted in front of
hundreds, thousands of people.
He's perfect for the role.
Do this for me, please.
You really are mad at me this morning.
- Put your coat on!
- Why this morning?
- Because I'm sick of opening
this door every other day
and finding you burned
out, boozed up, and...
Burned out, boozed up, and...
Sorry, baby.
- [sighs] Eddie, you're not even trying.
We broke early so that you could rehearse.
- I am trying!
I never said I was an actor.
- No, I did.
And what this hateful film
doesn't destroy, you will.
I staked my reputation on you.
- Did I ask for this?
Did I ever ask to be in this?
- No, you don't ask.
You just sit around waiting
for Mama to make it better.
- Hey hey hey.
Come on you two, you don't wanna do this.
- I do.
I want to kill something.
- No no, Bessie Mae.
Come on, go get dressed, we
have reservations at eight.
Go on.
Eddie, come here.
It's all right, come here.
Now look, you can't just say the words.
- You're telling me.
- No no, I mean you gotta
feel past the words.
They're nothing, an envelope, maybe.
The message comes from here, the gut.
- Sure.
- Okay, over here, come on.
This guy Steve.
He looks at this woman, he's had her.
Right?
And he looks at her and
he sees filth, dirt.
You have to look at
Elizabeth and see filth.
- But I love her.
- Now.
Now come on, pal, you can do it, come on.
Come on, from the gut, you can do it.
- I'm sick of opening that door every.
I'm sick of...
Let me walk, I'm better walking.
I'm sick of opening that door every day
and finding you boozed
out, burned up, and ugly.
Boozed out, burned up, and ugly.
I'm sick of...
[dog barking]
- God, not more hate mail.
- Fox is on my back about
delays on Cleopatra.
They're way over budget.
Baby?
- What?
I'm sick, okay?
- I don't know how much
of this I can take.
- What about me?
- Everything is stalled here.
I have no career!
You're too sick to work.
Even if you could,
the rain won't stop.
[coughing]
This town is like living in
the bottom of a damn well.
- I hate it too, Eddie.
- Maybe I should go back
and try and get some work, something.
- Now don't start that again.
- I said I'm just thinking about it.
- I'll tell you what I think about.
Every man I've ever known has either
died or abandoned me.
[crying]
[dramatic music]
- Oh my God.
Help!
Someone help!
[gasping]
What is it?
- Congestion.
She's not getting any air.
- Can you believe this?
Tons of letters and telegrams.
And look here, here's your obituary.
- I saw.
- Everyone loves you.
- Everyone loves me dead.
Alive, I'm the whore of Babylon.
- No babe, they love you.
The fans, they forgive you everything.
- I'll let them know when I have.
- Now is that any way to get better?
[knocking]
- Mummy.
I've missed you so.
Daddy.
Mummy.
I saw Mike, I did.
- Where, baby?
- When I died, I saw him.
I wanted so badly to be with him.
But he said no.
No, you can't.
It's not your time.
Go back.
Back.
- Did he, darling?
- Fight to go back.
That's what he said.
I'll be here.
He said that.
[people chanting]
- Can you hear that, hun?
Would you get a load of that?
[people cheering]
- Burt Lancaster wins his Oscar
against an outstanding
field of movie favorites.
The distinguished audience is hushed.
The tension is great when to Yul Brynner
falls the assignment of
telling who is Best Actress.
- Elizabeth Taylor.
[clapping]
- Escorted by her husband, Eddie Fisher,
the star who was honored for her portrayal
in MGM's Butterfield 8 comes
up to receive the Oscar.
A pleasure indeed, for Elizabeth
Taylor has won a victory
over a near-fatal illness.
And this too is her fourth consecutive try
at winning an Oscar.
And now it is hers at last.
She is overcome with emotion
as the presentation is made.
- Oh.
I don't really know
how to express my gratitude
for this after everything.
I guess all I can do is say thank you.
Thank you, with all my heart.
[clapping]
- Academy Awards, a reminder
that every moviegoer
is also a star maker.
- Butterfield 8.
- Congratulations.
I'm so happy for you.
Now, would you like some more good news?
- Yes.
- We're gonna start up
again with Cleopatra.
Only this time we're going to Rome.
We're going to pretend that Rome is Rome.
And here's the kicker, Joe
Mankiewicz said he would direct.
- Oh Walter, that's wonderful.
- But he wants to recast the men.
Only English actors, the cream.
- Rex Harrison, of course.
- For Caesar, yes.
A real actor, a man of the field.
- And Antony, who will play Antony?
- You're gonna love this.
The best, the new Olivier.
- Who?
- Richard Burton.
[dramatic orchestral music]
- Hmm, what's that line again?
- I need to--
- Heard it.
[group murmurs]
[water pours]
- Please, will you stop fiddling.
- I'm trying to fix it, Mr Burton.
- Ah hail,
Encuador!
- What's in the cup, Richard?
- Oh, I've grappled with the grape,
and now I'm grounding with the beans.
- Well, lucky it's not nitroglycerin
with your hand shaking like that.
- Ah.
Well Joe, when in Rome, one has to
celebrate the local gods, I ...
Late last night, I know,
but it's all in honor of Bacchus,
the sweet God of Wine.
- Call sheet, Mr Mankiewicz.
- And none for the little
boy who lives down the lane?
- Oh, goodness, I thought
I gave you one, Mr Burton.
- Oh really?
We must do it again then sometime.
- Sheila, please see if Miss Taylor's ready.
- I told her twice.
- Well tell her I said get her butt out here.
- Just like that, Mr Mankiewicz?
- Yes.
But tell her I said it
with enormous charm.
- That strumpet will be late
for bloody Judgment Day.
- I hope you can curb your
tongue around Elizabeth.
- My tongue's as tame as a geldy.
- You have a long summer ahead.
- Well, who was it who
said that she's all ...
Breasts?
No legs, and the voice of a fish wife?
[men shout]
- Hmm.
Well ...
- Fish wife and Queen.
- Your majesty!
Has anyone ever told you
what a pretty girl you are?
- Why no, you're the very first!
Better stick to the dialogue.
- The thing that motivates these two,
they both needed Caesar.
But he's dead, so to keep the power,
she hooks into the new guy.
But the hook gets her too.
For the first time in her life,
Cleopatra falls deeply
and passionately in love.
- But she ...
She loved Caesar, yes?
- No, not like this.
This is mutual.
Cat and mouse where
the cat gets the mouse,
and the mouse gets the cat,
and they both go under.
No survivors.
- Well that's a chilling thought.
- Yes,
we must beware, my lady.
You can't act falling in love
without actually falling in love,
if it's deliberate.
- Not me.
Maybe a few schoolgirl crushes,
but you'll notice I never
marry my leading man.
- I didn't say marriage, I said love.
- Well I'm an old-fashioned
girl Mr Burton,
just like Mummy raised me.
First I love, then I marry.
- She says,
she's an old-fashioned girl, Walter.
Whatever that means.
Okay, let's see what this looks like!
- Right everyone, this is a run-through.
- Silencio--
- And ...
Action!
- Ahh!
- Cut!
- Terribly sorry.
- Oh don't be sorry.
Joe, give us a moment.
Are you all right?
- Oh, just the, the night,
or the early morning, can't figure out
which one of them got to me.
- Mmm.
What you've done.
- Cleopatra,
I see how you conquer.
- You're not still drunk, are you?
- No.
Still Welsh though, same thing, love.
[sips]
Thank you.
I promise you better results
tomorrow, my Empress.
- Well, why don't we call it a day,
you go home to your wife and
get a good night's sleep?
- Yes.
Yes, good idea.
And you get down with your
merry little fellow too, hmm?
- Don't be rude.
- You started it.
- No, you did.
- You did.
- Why don't you just try
and turn up sober tomorrow?
- I'll turn up sober
if you turn up on time.
Hmm?
[light playful classical music]
[birds tweet]
- Not right now.
Hello baby!
Hi.
Oh.
[laughs]
Ah, he's giving me a big hug!
Oh sweetie, I love you.
What you been doing today, hmm?
- How was shooting?
- [giggles]
Shooting?
- Wasn't this the first day with Burton?
- Oh ...
Yes.
Hmm, yes it was.
[church bell rings]
- So was he sober?
- Reasonably.
[chuckles]
[peacock calls]
Eddie, are we happy?
- Kind of question is that?
I think we are, I ...
Nobody is happy all the time.
- Truly.
I don't see why not.
- What got you so stirred up?
- I don't know.
Something ...
Maybe only something a woman would get
stirred up about.
Eddie, I want another child.
- [sighs]
Why?
You've got Wilding's boys, you've got
Mike's daughter.
- They're all grown up!
I want a baby.
- That's too dangerous,
you've had three caesarians!
- Oh, I know, I know,
three caesarians are out.
I know a baby would make me happy.
A baby would need me, Eddie.
- All is in order.
There you are.
- I named her Maria, after
my friend, Maria Shell.
She found her for us.
- German orphanage.
- Hmm.
[baby babbles]
- This child was examined,
declared healthy.
- Yes.
- Miss Taylor, she has a malformed hip.
- So what?
She's an angel.
- What's involved, Doc?
- For her to ever walk,
a very long process.
At best, she'll have a
cast on the left side
for at least six months.
- Well, it doesn't matter.
What else is our money good for?
[peacock calls]
I told you she'd need me.
- And ...
Action!
Cut!
[bell rings]
- You intrigue me, my lady.
[speaks in foreign language]
- I'd be flattered, except
you always fall in love
with your leading ladies.
- Oh, a gentleman never tells tales.
[laughs]
- Gentleman, my foot!
So you did sleep with all of them.
- Hmm, long story.
What are you doing tonight, love?
- Oh, stop that.
We're both happily married.
- Are we?
- I can speak for myself.
- [laughs] Can you?
- I can.
- [laughs]
Yes, in the force ...
But you have the responsibility
of the entire company.
[laughs]
- I'd say.
- It was so good, we're
going to do it again.
- Oh, we're going to do it again.
- Right, everyone!
We're gonna go again--
- Of course, I never did find you my type.
- For me, you've always been
extraordinary full of yourself.
- Oh.
- Excuse me for saying so.
- Oh, not at all.
- I don't mean to be rude.
- Perish the thought.
[slow magical music]
- Cut!
Am I intruding?
[music drops]
[laughs]
- Bloody old man!
- You old sour you, have a drink.
- I don't think they were acting.
- You know, Joe,
if anything starts up between these two,
it could ruin us.
- Well,
he's punctual.
At least he might get
her to the set on time.
- Yeah.
Why him?
He always looks like
he needs a good scrub.
- He's nasty to her,
the only thing she can't
stand is a nice guy.
- I am like a patient
etherized upon a table.
[laughs]
And I will be after this.
[rock n roll music]
A little more I think, of this.
- No.
- I'm not getting drunk.
- Well, don't you look handsome?
Please, eat.
- Oh, thank you, but I
think I need a little more
of this bucking water first.
One thing you Italians know is food.
You'd think they were Jewish.
Well of course, did you say that the
Welsh are in fact the
lost tribe of Israel,
did you know that?
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- I didn't know that.
- Mm.
It is a bit,
this is Sybil, my wife.
- Hello.
- Glad you could come,
how do you do?
Oh Eddie, the music's too loud.
- What?
Oh.
- There.
- Well there are two
of them there, Richard.
Work your time.
- Oh Cybil, please.
- You better hurry, they might leave.
- [laughs]
My pet, you wound me.
- Why, because I'm not blind?
Well of course.
When it comes to you.
[birds tweet]
- Is this
the face that launched a thousand ships
and burnt the topless towers
of Elyium, sweet Helen?
Make me immortal with a kiss.
[clock ticks]
Her lips suck forth my soul,
see how it flies.
- What is it Richard, tell me?
- The play, about a rather
crazed and wonderful chap,
named Faustus.
- Crazed and wonderful?
- Oh yes, brilliant fellow,
but poor sod,
sold his soul to the devil.
- Why?
For the love of the most
beautiful woman in the world,
of course.
- Hmm.
Doesn't sound so brilliant to me.
[plays piano out of tune]
Eddie, will you please,
we can't hear ourselves think!
[clock ticks]
I'm sorry, you were reciting.
[slams]
- Oh, how art fairer
than the evening's air,
clad, in the beauty of a thousand stars.
[magical sweeping music]
[tires screech]
- So this is your charming hideaway.
- Oh, I sincerely hope so.
Not one single paparazzi in sight.
- How do I look?
- [laughs]
Ridiculous.
- At least no-one will spot me.
- Spot you?
You like you're wearing a
bloody marshmallow on your head.
Ow!
[music swells]
[birds tweet]
At last,
we seem to have thrown off the shameless
shackles of fame and shuffled
off that mortal coil.
- It's amazing.
They were looking for
Elizabeth Taylor in Rome,
and we left her there.
[laughs]
- I suppose it will be a bit of cliche to
jump into bed.
- Yes, I think so.
- Would it?
- Yes.
- Oh.
[laughs]
What a pity.
- I've come too far for that.
- And how far have you come?
- Too, too far.
[laughs]
You know, Richard, silly as it sounds,
I can't remember a time
when I wasn't famous.
And that hasn't left much
time for anything else.
- Such as?
- Well, love.
I mean, when I was a child,
I never felt like I could get enough love,
and all my life, all I wanted was love,
more love.
- Well, I can understand more lovers.
- No, not lovers, more love.
The kind of love that you surrender to,
and it surrenders to you.
What do you think?
- Oh.
I'm just ...
I'm just a confusion of liquids.
But really I was, I suppose
like all good Welsh boys,
I was in love with my mother,
whom I never knew.
And with my sister,
and ever since, all my life,
I've searched for someone to compare.
- Sybil?
- That's out of bounds.
She makes no demands.
- Hmm.
And I demand?
- [sighs]
Yes.
- You want me?
Flaws and all?
- [scoffs]
Flaws?
Flaws, yes, I do want you.
You're a deep, vast,
[slow emotional music]
terrifying ocean,
and I do think ...
That I could ...
quite happily drown in you.
[music builds emotion]
[church bell rings]
- I got a call from the coast today.
Apparently there are a lot of rumors
going around about you and Burton,
all the way from the coast.
Who'd have thought?
Are they true?
Elizabeth, are they?
- Yes.
[slow sad music]
[baby babbles]
I love you.
Hi Taffy.
Could you excuse us, please?
Are they ready for me?
- Terrible reading, Ducky,
not even you believe it.
Yes, there's a lot of
proles sitting out there,
sitting their duffers waiting for you.
- Mm, where does the time go?
- Oh, I wonder.
Hmm.
You were rather a bit
of a mess this morning
when you came in, weren't you, old girl?
- You look like something
the cat dragged in, old boy.
- Yes, I was hungover.
A little too much of the vine last night.
- Me too.
Pure love.
And 100 proof.
[kisses]
- Ocean, you deceive yourself.
That was never love.
- No?
- No.
It was lust.
- Love, you bloated old goat!
Love!
- You silly trollop!
- I see you need some
coaching on the finer points.
- It's my blunt point that you admire.
- [laughs]
You bloody coward!
- You ...
- Coward!
- You scurrilous slag!
- [laughs]
- Joe.
- Don't.
- I'm--
- You were going to
remind me that I've been
sitting here for 40 minutes,
and I don't want to be reminded.
- Oh good.
- What in hell were they up to?
- They were rehearsing the love scenes.
Everything but the lines.
- All right, places everybody!
- Elizabeth, you look radiant, my darling!
Mmm.
The sunshine of our day!
Come, let me show you.
Richard?
[exciting music]
- Camera ready?
[music builds drama]
[men shout]
[slow Mediterranean music]
[speaks in foreign language]
- Where's Eddie?
Eddie?
We're about to sit down,
what's going on?
- Socks.
Underwear.
- Eddie, stop this!
- Look,
I'm not going away for good,
so don't go nuts, okay?
- Of course you're not,
there's too much going on!
Eddie, I'm in the middle
of a picture, I need you.
- I'm taking off for a few days,
I'm going up to Switzerland.
I'm gonna go get a chalet.
Do you remember, a chalet?
Our dream.
- Eddie, you can't do this.
- Why not?
You've got people here.
You've got Richard.
- He has his own wife!
- Somebody told me I should
buy a gun and shoot the guy!
- Oh, stop it!
- You think there's a judge in this would
that would convict me?
Especially in Italy!
Here, you know what they would do?
Hell, they would stand
up and they'd applaud!
They would have a parade!
- Eddie, listen.
Please stay here.
I need you.
Please stay.
[knock on door]
- Ah, good evening Sir,
did you know that the verb, to be,
is the most brilliant verb
in the English language?
I am ...
You are!
We are!
Yeah, [laughs].
They are!
- It's Richard.
- I see.
[laughs]
- We were just about to sit down.
- What's he doing here?
What are you doing here?
- I am in love!
With this girl.
- You have your own girl.
You have Sybil.
- Sybil.
And Elizabeth
are both my girls.
You are
my girl, aren't you?
[slow sad music]
- Yes.
- You're my girl.
Come here.
And kiss me.
[music builds concern]
[crickets chirp]
[phone rings]
Yes?
Ah.
Sybil.
Yeah, she is.
Yes, I am.
Yes, well I do know one thing.
Will you let me speak!?
Thank you.
I know that,
that it will soon be dawn,
and in that harsh light,
my thoughts will clear
and I will, I will rescue my Guinevere,
I will do the right thing, I ...
[phone clicks]
[ice clinks in glass]
- You're not going?
- I have to.
- You don't have to.
You want to?
- She's my wife, I have to.
[sighs]
What do you wanna do?
- I want to love you.
You said you wanted to
get more out of life,
and that's what we've got.
We are more!
- What we get in life, Elizabeth,
is that we get to love a little,
just a little, and then
we get to die, a lot.
- I don't want to die!
- [laughs]
I'll tell them when I get there, hmm?
- Richard.
- Oh, I thought I could get away with it.
- With what?
- With you.
I'm drowning in you.
You're an ocean.
[emotional music]
- You're not actually leaving, are you?
- Yes I am.
- Damn you, Richard.
How dare you run away from me,
I've given up everything for you!
I've made a spectacle
out of myself for you!
- For me?
- Yes!
- Love, you have thrived for years
on the Elizabeth Taylor merry-go-round,
and I expect that you always shall.
[slaps]
At least until your looks go.
- Richard!
[door slams]
[cries]
[car turns]
[tires screech]
[cries]
[music gets more suspenseful]
[phone rings]
- Am I glad to see those eyes open?
- Oh, Mick.
- Our underwriters are so
thrilled, I should mention.
- It's not what you think.
Where's Eddie?
- Eddie's gone, dear.
Some time now.
- Ah yes.
I'd forgotten.
I'd forget my head if it wasn't ...
I've been a bad girl, Mike.
Did you see this?
It's from the Vatican newspaper.
I didn't even know the
Pope had a newspaper.
No-one's gonna tell me
who I can and cannot love.
- Ah.
Ignore it.
- And they say I'm some sort of
erotic vagrant.
Whatever the hell that is.
- It ain't flattering.
- It's a lie is what it is.
I mean, I love my children!
I'm a wonderful mother.
I am, you can ask anyone.
God, Mike, what if they try to take
little Marie away from me?
I've gotta wire my lawyers,
I can't let that happen.
- Nobody's gonna take your kid.
You just concentrate on giving
your feet back under you.
- Can you sue the Pope?
- [laughs]
Get yourself up.
We'll get on down to his kid,
put you on a barge and
finish this picture.
- Well I don't know when
I'm going to be able to.
- I do.
Real soon.
[phone rings]
- Where's the old Welshman?
- Putting his wife on a plane.
- Oh?
- Yep, Sybil decided to take
the kids back to London.
Can't say I blame her, can you?
- Hmm.
- Hey, hey, no.
What are you doing?
- Escaia, what is that,
that's an island, isn't it?
What a break that would
be, the sea, the salt air.
- And the moonlight.
- [laughs]
Does Escaia have a great moon?
- I'm afraid so.
[laughs]
[kisses]
[light happy music]
[speaks in foreign language]
- God, will these hyenas go away?
- But love, how else am I to become
a Hollywood star?
Patience, patience, you vultures!
Take one last tear at our tender flesh,
because soon we will end
this endless venture.
- Excuse me, can I come through?
- Wait, I can't hear.
- Is that some new jewel?
- Oh yes, this is a little emerald broach
Richard bought me at Bulgarry.
- Yes, I introduced her to beer,
she introduced me to Bulgarry.
- Are you two going to marry?
- Marry a girl?
Never.
- Then what's the deal?
- Well,
not sure I should share this with you,
it's such a private thought,
but sometimes the heart
speaks and you have to.
I always believed that I
was a child of destiny.
If that's true,
then Richard Burton's surely my fate.
- That's sweet, love.
[press shout]
[cameras click]
[phone rings]
[church bell rings]
- Darling, what is it?
- That's enough destiny for one day.
- Ooh, are you in one of
your black Welsh moods?
- I received this.
- Hmm, from who?
- Whom.
- Whoooom.
- Sir Lawrence Olivier.
So Larry asks me a question,
do I want to be a household name
or do I want to be a great actor?
- Well, what do you want?
- Both.
[birds tweet]
[big dramatic music]
[men shout]
They've all folded their tents.
Romans and Egyptians,
and they've all gone home!
Battle's over.
- Battle, is that what it's been?
- From day one, yes.
- So where do we go now?
- Some place terrifying, like reality.
- Oh, do we have to?
- No, we could always
stay intoxicated for lovely always.
- I've always hated the end of filming.
[water runs]
People rush together and make
some intense crazy family,
and then everybody goes their own way
and, it's like 20 forms of abandonment
all at once.
- Everything ends, Elizabeth.
[emotional music]
- Everything?
- The truth is,
you always knew I could never leave her.
- I understand.
She's a good woman.
That's what everyone tells me, constantly.
She stood by you all these years,
through all your bad behavior.
- Yes, I know the story.
- So should we go home?
- Yes.
- Our separate homes?
- I could make you stay.
- Yes.
- Then I won't.
- Please, Mr Burton.
Please, would you hold that please?
Right there.
- Thank you, sir.
- Could I just get one more?
- What's that for?
- Oh, it's for Mrs Taylor
in case that she needs.
- Take it away, Miss Taylor will be fine.
- This way please.
- Thank you.
- Just turn around slowly, Mr Burton.
Right there.
There, thank you.
- Could you just give me one more?
[emotional music]
Would you mind looking this way, sir?
Please?
Excuse me, Mr Burton?
- Go ahead.
[car drives]
[birds tweet]
- You?
[children laugh]
Lovely!
- Come on Grandma, let's go play!
- Oh wait, let us be alone for a bit,
and then we'll come see you, okay?
- Run along, I'll be up later, all right?
[children giggle]
Oh, Elizabeth!
This is a dream.
An absolute dream.
It's perfect for the children,
you have everything you
could possibly need here.
- Well, except a man.
Oh Mummy, have you heard,
since we stopped shooting,
Fox has fired everyone?
And Walter Wanger, and
poor Joe Mankiewicz,
now he should have gotten a medal
for having to deal with me.
- Elizabeth.
You must really try and
put Richard behind you.
- Well I've put the
English channel between us,
that's a start, isn't it?
- It's so strange, you know.
You and Eddie bought this house
and then the scandal.
Liz Scandale.
Oh, honestly, you'd think the press
would have more to write about.
[laughs]
So, you really haven't seen him, since?
- The parting was amicable.
And mutual.
[laughs]
[phone rings]
Oh.
[speaks in foreign language]
Well, hello.
How are you?
[people laugh]
[car drives off]
Hello.
- Miss Taylor!
- Please, call me Elizabeth.
- This way.
May I take your coat?
- No, I'm fine.
[people murmur]
- You've been well?
- Mmm, very busy.
- Good.
- You?
- Oh, flat, stale.
Unprofitable.
- Mmm.
I keep busy working on the chalet, mostly.
It's so beautiful, the children love it.
- Work.
That's what you need, real work, not this
doily arranging.
Have you read the script?
- Is that why you wanted to see me?
Talk about the VIP's?
- I've always wanted to see you.
Life is worthless without you, but ...
You have seen the script,
I know it's lightweight, but the deal ...
- And you really think that's a good idea?
Us working together?
- Why not?
It's half me and each,
London, you like London.
- And where will you be?
- Well, London, of course.
- I mean, Sybil's in London.
Your family.
- Yes.
Ah, thank you for that.
- Oh, you're welcome.
[pours]
- Richard,
I don't ever want you to hate me.
- Oh, I couldn't possibly--
- And lose for respect
for me, and think I'm--
- What's got into you, lovey?
- You used to call me Ocean.
- Well, I still do.
My ocean.
To me, you're boundless.
[concerned music]
- I've had a great deal time to think.
And Richard,
I need you.
All the time, I need you.
I know you don't want to marry
me or you can't marry me,
I've accepted that,
just like swallowing a rock,
but it's okay.
I'm willing to be your secret.
- My secret?
- I'll be your mistress.
The world will eat me
alive if they find out,
but at least I won't be
hurting anyone anymore.
- Oh, my Elizabeth.
- But you must promise me something.
You must promise never to think bad of me.
- Never.
Never, not one single bad thought in
this old drunken Welsh head.
Not for Elizabeth.
- Promise?
- Yes.
[happy music]
[lazy jazz music]
Did I ever tell you ...
About Sir Larry, as we know him?
Stanley Baker!
I'm just having me a tall anesthetic.
- One pint sir?
- Poison all around.
- I missed you at the film, Rich.
- Yes, I know, I know, don't tell me.
It was rubbish.
- It was Cleopatra.
- Ah, Cleopatra's in the loo,
losing what little faith she had left,
and losing her lunch.
- They're saying you sold out, Rich.
- Yes.
I am old Faustus.
Or the latter day Faust.
Got a three picture deal
with the devil himself.
Or, Elizabeth herself,
depends on which rag you read.
- She's ...
Something.
- Mmm.
- Oh, I spent two years
making that lousy film
and they cut it to pieces.
It's appalling.
- Seldom in a mountain of film
have given birth to such
a mouse of a performance.
- They're killing me by inches.
- Oh love, this one's better.
It says here you're not the
worst actress in the world.
[laughs]
- How can you read that?
- Well, the cure is in the poison.
- Oh, what the hell is
that supposed to mean?
- That means, darling, that it's time
I returned to the theater.
- Reading that garbage.
- Oh.
- Apologize.
- No.
- Apologize!
- Make me!
- You little spitfire.
I apologize.
[kisses]
Have another drink.
[laughs]
[cars honk]
£150,000.
How much is that in dollars?
Half a million?
- Mhmm.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
- They must be the most
beautiful stones I've ever seen.
Are you really ...
- Well, it's either that
or I buy you half of Wales.
[laughs]
- You know there's only one
thing that can make me happy.
- Shh.
- Don't be a boozy old Welshman.
- I said, shut up.
I have something to ask you.
- Yes?
- Will you marry me?
[slow emotional music]
- Have you told Sybil?
- Tomorrow.
[kids shout]
[car drives past]
- Dada!
Are you coming home soon?
I love you.
I've missed you so much.
- I'll make up for it soon.
Why don't you go play with the children?
Don't be sad.
- Over here, it's me!
Over here!
[birds tweet]
- Are you coming home, Rich?
- Dada!
- Oh, and he's got the ball
and Burton's dribbling it around
and he's gonna throw it to Jenkins Junior.
Score, love!
What?
- Are you coming home?
- Home.
Yes, yes.
- For good?
- Yes.
- Have you told her?
- I'll tell her tonight, hmm?
[door opens]
[siren blares]
- It's after four, I was concerned.
How did she take it?
Sybil, what did she say?
- Not much.
- You told her?
- No.
[laughs]
Oh.
No reproaches, no rampage,
no threats of death
and destruction, Richard you fool,
Richard you lout, you
worm, you insipid ...
[groans]
Where the hell you think you're going?
- I'm going to my room,
and you're going home to Sybil.
- To hell I am.
I'm coming through that door.
- Well, you better bring a locksmith.
- You can't toss me out
like some errant schoolboy!
- Richard, you can have
a wife and a mistress,
you cannot have a wife and a fiance.
- Why not?
- Because,
I'm the fiance.
[door slams]
- You think just because I'm drunk
I'm not gonna remember any
of this in the morning,
you cow!
[yells]
You sow!
[dials]
[swigs bottle]
[cars drive by]
[sighs]
Sybil, hello love.
Yes, yes, I know it's rather late.
Well, it's early actually [laughs].
No, no, I didn't tell her.
Well, the thing is love,
I do believe I'm going to need a divorce.
[puts phone down]
[police siren blares]
[blows whistle]
[crowd yells]
- This is like being
swallowed up by an avalanche.
- Yes, every night the same thing,
more of these ...
- Vultures!
- No fans, love, fans.
All come to see me, me.
- Love, they come to see us,
we're a pair of circus freaks.
Well it's true, the
only reason they're here
is to see sinners on display.
[crowd cheers and applaud]
[crowd applaud]
- That man is a child of the theater.
- Mmm, just a natural chic bea.
It's where he belongs.
- You wouldn't mind if he stayed?
- I just want to be with Richard.
- Congratulations.
[crowd applaud]
- Thank you.
You're such a kind audience,
all of you.
However,
my heart feels either appreciations,
I have at last married the girl.
[crowd applaud]
And indeed, she is such a treasure
that I must honor her.
[crowd cheer]
My bride.
You see, they love us.
- Mmm, please don't turn your back,
they love the lions as much
as they love the Christians.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
as the bard would have it,
we will have no more marriages.
[laughs]
[crowd applaud]
[birds tweet]
- So you've both
undergone a lot of changes
to play in Virginia Woolf.
- You'd be sure and tell your readers,
this is part me, part foam.
I gained 15 pounds in 15 years,
and the first time the
studio insisted on it.
- You ever feel like
you've become this woman?
- Only on the set.
Richard doesn't let me use
four letter words at home.
- Yes, I've cured Elizabeth of
that rather unfortunate tendency.
- You bet your ass.
- That's a three letter word.
Of course my only concern
is that my quality
is not exactly this American professor
I've gone to see, he's not ...
- Rich?
- He's not me, this moon-faced chap,
beaten down by a woman.
- Richard!
- Thank you, Mr Burton.
[Richard mumbles]
- You're mumbling!
- I'm running my lines.
- Mumbler!
- One of your less glaring
defects, Elizabeth,
is you've never been able to distinguish
between art and mumbles.
- Can too.
You're a mumbler!
Accurate lines?
- Page four, it says,
George takes the bottle,
and pours.
[pours]
- Don't you think you've
rehearsed that one enough?
- Oh, it's method, darling.
You see, I'm sending my way
into the role of a drunk.
- Hah, for years!
- You see, that hurts.
I have a reason to drink.
- Page 27, Martha takes a chicken leg
from the refrigerator, it's in the script.
- Haha, I've never have for the life of me
understood your attraction
to those poor birds.
- Really?
Well listen, buster, maybe
that's one of your defects,
in a big, fat glaring way too!
- Why don't you swallow first?
- All your nutrients come in bottles.
You know, you oughta try food sometime.
- Oh, it's all of God's poor little birds
that I'm concerned for,
they seem naked and vulnerable.
- Oh, brother.
- Have you ever considered that you should
eat only what you can kill?
- I've considered your snapping
your fat little Welsh neck!
- Give me vegetables myself.
For instance, the hops, or the juniper
one finds in gin.
The--
- Blah, blah, blah.
- Take to the Russians
take to the magic of vodka.
I'm a vegetarian.
- I'm speechless.
- Oh, I hope not,
I'd miss your voice, my little dove.
- You'd be thrilled.
- No so, like the sailor, I take comfort
there off into misty distant
hooting of your little horn.
[laughs]
- Bullseye!
- I am prepared to sacrifice many things
for our relationship, Elizabeth,
but to my dignity ...
- Oh, dignity?
- No.
- Dickie's little dignity.
- That's enough.
- Yes, you gave up dignity
you popped the cork
on that bottle!
Pop!
What a shot, a shot heard round the world!
Dickie's popped his little cork!
Pop, pop, pop!
Pop!
[laughs]
- Snap, snap, snap,
you little viper!
- Stop it!
- Oh!
You missed.
Come on, come on.
[smashes]
[concerned music]
[cries]
This is the hymn of chicken, hmm?
- I don't like our games.
I hate our games.
[cries]
- Don't be sad, hmm?
- I'm not sad.
I feel lost.
[door opens]
- What on Earth?
Will you stop that dawdling!?
Come on!
[laughs]
[makes chicken noise]
- It's all of these bloody petticoats,
takes me, it's like getting
dressed five times over again,
not like you.
These pantyhose.
- Madam, may I remind thee
that I am thy husband and thy Lord,
thy life?
[kisses]
And like frumpet, thy ...
- Thy pain in the ass.
- Oh, yes indeed.
Come!
Ah.
Elizabeth, it's for you.
I feel a cocktail coming on.
Elizabeth?
What is it?
- Monty!
[cries]
Monty's dead!
- Let him go.
He was a broken heart.
Nobody could have saved him.
[emotional music]
- We were too busy being us.
I'd forgotten Monty.
- He fell in love, you were married,
he never expected anything from you.
[cries]
Even a job.
Reflections in a golden eye.
- He was the only one I
could tell everything to.
Even things that were very private.
- He loved you.
[cries]
- Bessy May.
[laughs]
He left Bessy May.
God, I had many proposals,
but he was the only man I
should have asked to marry me.
- Is that a fact?
Was it a drug overdose?
- A life over.
[sweeping dramatic music]
[audience applause]
- Elizabeth Taylor is not here tonight,
she's in the south of France,
accepting her Oscar
will be her dear friend,
Miss Anne Baxter.
- They just gave you an Oscar,
and you're complaining.
- I'm not complaining for me,
I'm complaining for you.
- Oh, I'm a chronic complainer,
I don't need help.
- Damn, this is your
fifth nomination, Richard.
You deserve the Oscar, not me.
- Shh.
We've named the yacht
after our three girls,
Kate, Liza and Maria,
Kalizma!
[laughs]
- I'm so happy.
- Oh.
It's quaintly comforting that
a mere yacht can make you happy, my love.
[men shout]
[cameras click]
- Thank you.
[seagulls cry]
Where are you going?
People are coming, we're gonna celebrate.
- Yes, I hadn't forgotten,
I'm taking a launch to
pick some of my mates.
- You mean those other drunks?
- No.
I mean the other actors,
the thespians, Elizabeth,
who have come from afar to celebrate
your crowning achievement.
- Hmm.
I was just asking.
- No you weren't.
You were concerned about
whether I was going to
fall off the wagon that
I've been clinging to
so desperately for the last 13 days,
and well, don't worry love,
because you see, I'm one of
its last remaining passengers.
Toodleoo.
[ship horn blows]
- Toodleoo.
[French music]
I can't tell you all of the, whatevers,
specifications, Richard knows them.
Bonjour, Jean Paul.
- Bonjour, Elizabeth!
- All I know is,
it feels like home.
[men shout]
[crowd murmurs]
- We win!
[laughs]
- Thank you very much.
Jean Paul!
[speaks in foreign language]
[laughs]
[pops cork]
- You're late.
- Oh.
And you're a very pretty girl.
- Richard, you started drinking again?
[laughs]
- Have I?
Hmm.
[laughs]
[country music]
- Thank you.
- Elizabeth, oh my darling!
[kisses]
Mrs Taylor, happy birthday, my dear.
I have to tell you, 40?
You don't even look--
- Well, how about my being
a Grandmother last year?
Would you believe it?
- I refuse to believe it.
- Oh, well then don't,
I need all the help I can get.
[laughs]
- I can't believe it,
who would allow Richard
to put on this shindig
here in Budapest?
But to fly in all these guests?
- Well Mother, we have to,
because he's shooting Bluebeard here,
and with eight wives, I don't want him
hanging around all those Bluebeard broads
without me.
- Oh, seriously.
- I don't!
[laughs]
- Here you go, Mom.
- I was painless, shall we say,
legs tied together.
- Oh dear.
Who's Richard boring over there now?
- Ah, it's the Swiss
ambassador and his wife.
- Hmm.
I see.
- Noah's Ark gently
flowed down my left thigh.
- [clears throat] Oui.
- Darling, not one of
your old stage stories.
Hmm, give the old Vic a break, will you?
- Oh.
- Please excuse us.
- I'm terribly sorry, she's terribly rude.
- Mother.
- I'm sorry, Richard, I
have to see this up close.
- Oh, of course, your highness.
- The Krup, isn't it?
The Krup diamond.
- Yes.
Little present from Richard.
- I saw it in the paper, front page.
- Yes, that's the way we like it, love.
Diamonds on the front page,
and bad reviews on the back.
[laughs]
Oh, you look a little thirsty, love,
let me fill you up.
- Thank you.
- The most vulgar thing I've ever seen.
[laughs]
- Would you like to try it on?
- Oh ...
- Well, doesn't look
so vulgar now, does it?
[laughs]
[traffic passes]
[door buzzes]
- Darling?
The scribbler is here from the whatever,
that journal, the cinematic magazine.
I'll handle it!
Ah--
- Mr Burton!
- Yes, Mr Durham.
- Durlam.
- Oh, whatever, it's nice to meet you.
Sit down.
- I'm extremely grateful--
- Sad to see that my beloved is ill today.
- I'm sorry, maybe I should come back.
- Oh, nothing serious,
we just think it's German measles.
- You're joking.
- She'll be up in a day.
We've prescribed her Italian vodka.
Quite remarkable, tastes like a paragoric.
[thunder rolls]
Go ahead.
- Sir.
- Your interview.
- Oh, yes.
- I hope you haven't come prepared to ask
us about the recent
flops we've been having.
- Richard, I can hear you!
- Yes.
We've only had four
flops in a row, actually,
but some of them had merit, small merit.
- I'm sure this gentleman
would prefer to come back
when it isn't raining.
- Not so.
He's a veritable duck.
Hmm?
You don't mind the rain, do you?
- Not at all.
- When it isn't raining,
perhaps you'll have
sunnier things to say, hmm?
- Hmm, yes, yes.
[church bell rings]
You're racing.
- We're crawling.
- I've always been of the opinion
that mother nature, like
one's mother in law,
should be visited, but sparingly.
- It's the drink that wears you out.
And the cigarettes.
- It's arthritis actually.
It reminds me, medication time.
- Oh Richard, I worry about you.
- Me too, that's why I drink.
[wind howls]
- You really regret
taking a few days here?
I mean, look around, the
chalet, the mountains ...
Did you ever believe you'd
have a life like this?
- Oh yes, this is
precisely the kind of life
I thought we'd be having.
Apart from our occasional
trip to this snow palace,
we have a life of hotel
rooms and rented houses,
and, oh yes, that yacht,
that luxuriously
appointed floating prison.
- I don't like your tone, Richard.
- It's a life,
or a half life, actually.
And to make up for the missing half,
I drink twice as much.
- Oh stop it, Richard.
- Oh, I'll stop, I'll die of drink,
and you shall go on
blithely in your half world.
- Do you have to say these things?
I mean, I know you think them,
but must you say them?
Constantly?
[plane flies]
Are you going to hold up?
- I'll hold up.
Bloody Marys'll hold me up.
Bob, two large Bloody Mary's.
- Okay.
- I hate to leave you,
New York is dreadful this time of year.
- Oh.
You go off to the coast, I'll be fine.
It's always dreadful out there anyway.
Always open season if you like small game.
- We haven't gone off on our separate ways
in a long time.
We're doing the right thing?
- [laughs]
It's been a long time since
we've done the right thing.
- Richard!
[laughs]
- Doing the right thing.
Huh.
It's like seeming and being.
Being and seeming.
The Dick and Liz Show.
We're like Laurel and Hardy.
- I've always been fond
of Lauren and Hardy.
- Oh yes, well we're not as cute,
not anymore.
Everybody's sick to death
of us, especially me.
[phone rings]
Especially me.
I know.
We need, new writers.
- Premier airlines, flight two,
two lost--
- That's my last plane.
- Miss Taylor, we'll escort you.
- You've been waiting for an hour.
Just so they know that it's you.
- Goodbye Daffy.
- Bye bye.
- Would you give this to the press?
[phone rings]
[slow sad music]
- Like this?
To the press?
- I just can't face him.
[cries]
I am convinced it would be
a good and constructive idea
if Richard and I were
separated for a while.
Maybe we loved each other too much.
I never believed such
a thing was possible.
But we have been in each
other's pockets constantly,
never being apart but for
matters of life and death.
I believe with all my heart
that the separation will ultimately
bring us back to where we
should be, and that's together.
It's just while during
this difficult time.
Pray for us.
[car horn blows]
[door buzzes]
[clock ticks]
[door opens]
- Evening.
I'm your date tonight.
- Oh, then you must be John Warner.
- Yes ma'am, there's no
question who you are.
- Oh, call me Elizabeth.
Well, I can't even remember a time,
I must have been a teenager
when I had my last blind date.
[laughs]
- Well we're all awfully grateful over
at the bicentennial committee
that you agreed to attend
our little ball here
in Washington.
- Well, consider it my patriotic duty.
So tell me about yourself.
- Well there's not much to tell.
I'm a Virginian, I got a farm down there,
I work in the government, and one day
I plan to run for Senator.
- Oh.
You have a farm?
- Yes ma'am.
- And you have animals?
- You betcha.
- I love animals.
[happy magical music]
[cow moos]
[dog barks]
[car passes]
It's so beautiful.
- It's nice of you coming
all the way out here with me.
- This is my childhood.
Really, I feel like I'm back in England.
- You like it?
- Mhmm,
yes.
Have you ever instantly fallen in love?
With a place.
- Tell me about yourself, Elizabeth.
- I'm still reeling from my
second divorce from Richard.
Richard Burton.
- Yes, I know who he is.
- Oh, you've met him?
- No.
But I've read about him.
Like everyone else in America.
[laughs]
- Well, for a change,
what you've read in the
papers is pretty much true.
I've had five husbands and five divorces.
- Sounds a little discouraging.
- Hmm.
Well ...
Only if you believe in love.
[celebratory big band music]
[crowd cheers]
[brakes screech]
- Howdy folks!
I'm John Warner and I'm looking
to be your next senator!
And this here's my lovely wife Elizabeth!
[crowd cheers]
Now remember folks, a vote
for me is a vote for her too!
[jolly band music]
- Oh, thank you, [laughs].
[birds tweet]
Now what do you say to
Republican fat cats?
- I wish you wouldn't say that.
- Oh God, I haven't even met them,
I've already said something wrong?
- You sound like you're
in the enemy party.
- Well, I'm your wife, that's my party.
[crowd applaud]
- And it is a privilege to introduce
the next senator from
the Old Dominion state,
our new senator, John
Warner and Mrs Warner!
- Well thank you.
I would like to introduce the real power
behind my campaign:
my country wife, Elizabeth.
[crowd applaud]
- Now thank you all for your wonderful
warm Virginia welcome.
I want you all to know how at home
I feel here in the Old Dominion.
And I haven't felt this
way for quite some time.
Thanks.
[crowd applaud]
- That sort of get-up
might go in California,
but here in Virginia, we have something
we like to call taste.
- It doesn't bother John.
- The more attention that lady gets,
the closer he is to the senate.
- We Virginians have to stick together.
Now I would never
minimize the contribution
that women have made to this country,
but we cannot ask the fairer sex
to go into combat, that is not acceptable
to most Americans.
- John.
- And any so called equal rights amendment
that would put a woman in harm's way,
that cannot be condoned.
[crowd murmurs]
Women cradle civilization,
and to ask them to face
the harshest reality
of modern existence, we can't do that.
- Oh, boo!
- What, Elizabeth?
- Don't women have been
facing the harshest
realities of life since
the beginning of time?
I just don't see how you can ...
- Well I think, and I
see that we will have
a discussion of foreign policy.
[munches]
[celebratory big band music]
[birds tweet]
I'll be on the hill til late.
Stay in Georgetown.
- I see you want a milk maid
to stay down on the farm.
- Well you don't wanna
become a Washington wife,
they all turn ugly.
- Yeah, and fat.
- People are talking.
Making jokes on TV.
- Oh, why the hell
don't they run the news?
And not my before and after pictures.
I didn't marry you sit on the sidelines.
- Why did you marry me?
- To be happy.
But I'm stuck out here
in this chicken coop,
in paradise, alone!
[slow sad music]
[cries]
[cars pass]
[police siren blares]
[knock on door]
[bird calls]
- Are we ready?
- Yes.
Almost.
How do I look?
No response required,
never putting on that weight again.
- You look wonderful.
In fact, if my arthritis permitted,
I'd do a pirouette myself.
I see that you've been
medicating your back again.
- Ah, yes I have.
- Oh.
- It hurts me [laughs].
- You know, it's not the pills,
it's the cocktail of pills and booze
that'll kill you.
- Oh, don't be ridiculous.
- Yes.
- Oh well.
- See you on the boards, love.
[laughs]
[crowd cheer]
- Like a great daff of love.
- What?
- This applause.
Every time, it's like
being loved all over again.
[laughs]
[crowd cheer]
- Elizabeth, do you know who Sally is?
- Sally, oh yes, of course I know Sally.
- Hello.
- Hello Sally.
So you two have been naughty.
I understand you went to Las Vegas.
- Yes.
For the weekend, and got married.
- I beg your pardon?
- Married.
[laughs]
- That's strange, I
thought you said married.
- Yes.
It's like a great part of love,
and sometimes we all have
to lower ourselves into it.
- Well,
congratulations.
Richard?
- Elizabeth.
[slow emotional music]
[smashes]
- Well there you go, she's awake.
- What?
- Mom?
Listen to me.
You're in trouble.
You are in very serious trouble.
- Wait a minute.
What happened, did I faint or something?
What happened?
- It's pills, honey.
And alcohol.
You do have a very, very serious problem.
- That's ridiculous,
I don't have a problem with alcohol!
- Listen to me, you are
hurting yourself, mother!
- I've never had a problem with alcohol!
- You are hurting yourself!
- Elizabeth.
Elizabeth, listen, please!
You're hurting your family too.
Do you know that?
- Am I hurting you?
- Yes!
Please.
[cars pass]
[birds tweet]
- Yoohoo, sir?
- Is there a problem, Miss?
- Well there's a real problem,
I don't like the name, Liz.
- Sorry.
- And I don't do kitchens.
- Ma'am,
this is the Betty Ford Center.
We do whatever it takes.
And above all, we don't drink or use.
Even if--
- Even if our ass falls off, yes, I know.
[slow concerned music]
I'm Elizabeth Taylor and I'm an alcoholic.
- Thank you all for sharing
your experiences with us.
Um, Elizabeth.
Can you recall what event
or incident it was that caused you
to recognize the fact that
you had a problem?
- I still have a hard time believing
I'm actually here [laughs].
But yes ...
[sighs]
I remember waking up in hospital,
surrounded by friends and family,
and they said that I had a problem.
- We all have a problem,
that's why we're here.
- Well I guess I'd become an alcoholic,
and that combined with the
pain killers I was taking,
I couldn't handle it.
- At least you didn't try to hide it.
You had the courage to
come out in the open.
- Well ...
Yes, I just hope to God
that's all behind me now.
[slow optimistic music]
- That woman doesn't have one
single unexpressed thought
in her head.
[laughs]
No longer mourn for me when I am dead,
than you shall hear
the surly, sullen bell.
Give warning to the world
that I am fled from this vile world,
with vilest worlds to dwell.
[men shout]
- Miss Taylor!
- Madam!
[cameras click]
- One photograph, just one!
[speaks in foreign language]
- I love you, Richard.
And I will never cease loving you.
Hey, Rock.
[laughs]
- Hi Bessy.
Careful who you kiss.
- I always kiss gorgeous men.
- Not so gorgeous.
Not no more.
- Oh baloney.
- Not like you, you piss me off.
You look as good as you
did when we made Giant.
- Oh, boy, are you some actor.
Who wrote your lines, hmm?
- Nah.
I'm serious.
You look great.
[coughs]
How's your life?
- Oh, you know me, kiddo.
I'm a survivor, it's in the genes.
- You always did look hot in your jeans.
[laughs]
- Hey partner.
What do you say we head
on back to Texas, hmm?
- I'd like to go back.
[slow concerned music]
Anywhere.
- I know.
- You know what I miss about Texas?
Chocolate Martinis.
[laughs]
- Okay, then I'll give you one.
- Just one.
- A whole batch.
[birds tweet]
- Chocolate Martinis.
- I am tired and I am grieving.
I am tired of us having to
convince the world out there
that AIDS is a universal
threat to all mankind.
[crowd applaud]
I have held a good friend in my arms
as his body began to fail,
and I am compelled by grief.
[cameras click]
The delays in confronting AIDS
tragically remind me of
the high price to be paid
when prejudice prevails.
AIDS has taught me how
fragile human existence is,
and that every life is to be cherished.
[crowd applaud]
- Are you gonna act again, Miss Taylor,
or are you just gonna
pursue this AIDS work?
- I don't know if I pursue
it or it pursues me,
but--
- Miss Taylor?
- Since Rock Hudson's death,
I guess it's made the
work a little easier.
- Yes, but I'll tell you what amazes me.
It's truly amazing,
I call good friends of mine
to ask them to be a part of this,
lifelong friends,
and they duck out on me, they
just don't return my calls.
- Well, you know, it's AIDS.
People are embarrassed.
- Yes, but that's terrible,
I mean, it's like alcoholism,
it shouldn't be a disease
of shame, and it is.
- Well, what can you do?
- Well, we can all do something.
Try to make people aware,
I believe that's the first step,
that's what I'm trying to do.
Thank you.
- Over here, Miss Taylor, over here.
- Miss Taylor?
- One more question.
[pours]
- Uhuh.
No, she's handling the press pretty well.
Right?
[plane takes off]
Well, we arrived at 2:30 LA time.
I'm afraid she's gonna have
to see a doctor though.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm afraid so.
Mhmm.
- I don't know what
got me back here, I ...
I don't know, I'm trying to booze, food.
Pills, again.
- Yeah.
- It's always the pills for me too.
- Yes, but these were prescription.
- Yeah.
- They were prescribed to me for my back.
Damarall, percoden, valium.
- All in one day?
- Give me the name of that doctor.
[laughs]
- Oh honey, you're just like me.
- I beg your pardon?
- Give me pills, booze, food, men.
Nothing's ever enough.
- Yes, but you don't equate
alcohol and pills with men?
- Yes, it's a love addiction.
Look at me, I've been married four times,
and I never found anything,
not in this lifetime to fill up
that great big emptiness inside.
- Oh my God,
I've never thought of
love as an addiction.
So your name's Larry?
- Yeah.
Larry Vercinski.
- Hmm.
And what do you, Larry?
[ducks quack]
- I move earth.
[laughs]
- I'll bet.
- Operator, moving equipment.
- Ah, I'm impressed.
- Do you wanna walk?
- Okay.
I'm a bit slow at the start.
[clears throat]
Maybe I should get a job
moving earth [laughs].
God knows I need something.
My career, ugh, almost dead.
- But you're Elizabeth Taylor.
- Being Elizabeth Taylor used to be
good and sufficient reason
for waking up every morning.
Now it just seems so nothing.
- Oh come on, don't talk like that.
You're still full of fire,
you have your AIDS charity.
How many people that matter
care about people like you do?
Even that's bigger than
being Elizabeth Taylor, huh?
No offense.
[laughs]
- It's okay, kid, I can take it.
Someone suggested I start a new career.
In perfume.
- There you go.
What would you call it?
- Hmm.
What do I know best?
- What?
- Passion.
[laughs]
[happy rock music]
- John.
Just walk in.
- This is it.
- Wow.
[laughs]
[till dings]
[sexy country music]
- That is a double-decker.
Pickles, onions, relish, mustard
and mayonnaise with fries.
You got enough fries?
- Oh yes.
Of course I haven't been to
a place like this in years.
- Right well,
it's not exactly the typical
beller palace, but ...
Ready to leap?
- Mmm.
Yes, let's leap.
[laugh]
What?
- I've never met anyone like you before.
It's scary.
It's wonderful.
- Well, it could be dangerous.
What if we fall in love?
- I think I already have.
[cheer and applaud]
[birds tweet]
[truck drives]
[water trickles]
[cat meows]
[sighs]
- How's my little girl?
- Happy.
And about to be 60.
- Well, that's not so bad.
What's important is that those
60 years have been good ones.
You've had a wonderful life.
- And I've known great love.
- And you've given great love.
- Hey!
- Oh, hello!
- Picture time.
- Uh oh.
- Here we go.
- Come on everybody.
- Oh, Mikey.
- All right, line up, let's
get it all together here.
Good.
- Oh no, no, everybody in the picture.
Can you, will you take this please?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
- Okay, get down low,
you'll be coming here.
[laughs]
[dramatic triumphant music]
Oh wait, what about my makeup?
- Oh!
[laughs]
- Just kidding!
- There's only one Elizabeth Taylor.
- Thank God for that.
Smile.
[music swells]
[camera clicks]
[emotional string music]