- [Emcee] Ladies and gentlemen,
receiving his fourth decoration
for meritorious service,
Lieutenant Ray Harlan.
(audience applauding)
- [Dispatcher] All
units in the vicinity
of central Manhattan
bus terminal respond
to a possible hostage situation.
Shots have been fired.
(gunshots banging)
- [Ray] No!
- [Mom] Oh god, my boy!
- [Doctor] It's the
opinion of this doctor
that due to his involvements
in recent events culminating
in the death of an 11-year-old
boy, it would be best
if Lieutenant Harlan be
relieved of duty until...
- [Vlad] My people and I
make millions each year
while you scrape by
on the cop's salary.
Justice, hm.
- [Lou] Ray, will you come home?
There are other
cops in New York.
You don't have to be there.
You need some family.
Besides, I need you now.
- [Darcy] Ray Harlan,
ladies and gentlemen,
whose accomplishments
include four service awards,
three years with the NYPD, and
one very distinguished honor,
jumping the bones of
Mary-Jo Bronkowski.
- How you doing, brother?
Hey, that was cute.
- [Darcy] Yeah, I
thought you'd enjoy that.
Now get in, man,
we're in a hurry.
- Lookin' good.
(upbeat electronic music)
(siren blaring)
What's with the cherry?
- Well, the Black Rose Boys
are up to some mischief.
- Black Rose, huh?
- Russians.
I thought you should
hit the ground running.
(gunshots banging)
So they tell me the crime rate
in the Big Apple has dropped.
- Yeah, action's
getting a little stale.
I'm glad to be out of there.
- I can tell the boys here are
gonna love you coming back.
- I can always ride with
you, little brother.
- Just remember, that's
ride with me, not on me.
(gunshots banging)
- Gimme a break.
If it wasn't for me, you'd
probably be rotting away
in some cell with a bunkmate
who calls you Sally.
- I miss those lectures.
That's beautiful.
- You know, by the
way, those cigarettes,
they kill more people
than car accidents, drugs,
alcohol, and bullets combined.
- You quit again, huh?
How long's it been?
- Three days.
- Three days. (laughs)
(gunshots banging)
Let's go.
- Put that away.
- Oh, you've got that
look in your eye.
(gunshots banging)
(tires screeching)
- What the?
(fence clattering)
(gunshots banging)
- We can't stay here.
- What are you doing?
- Let's go inside, inside.
Split up.
- Of course.
- Cowboy Ray Harlan, I
should've known it was you.
- How you doin', Frenchy?
Good to see you.
- What's going on in there, huh?
- They knocked off a
high-stake poker game.
- Frenchy, the door.
Clear!
Just like hold times, eh?
- And as usual I'm
still watching your
back, little brother.
Nice homecoming.
(gunshots banging)
Go.
(man shouting)
- He's gone over,
the son of a fell.
(man groaning)
(gunshots banging)
You have the right
to remain silent.
- Help, oh god!
(gunshots banging)
- The guy's a real
Einstein, huh?
- Noo too bright.
- Help, help me!
- I suggest you drop
that pea-shooter first.
- Help, help!
- Drop it!
- Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, it is gone, okay.
Help me, help me.
- How you doin'?
- [Man] Help.
- Say uncle.
- You crazy bastard, uncle.
- Say uncle please.
- Uncle, uncle please, help me.
- I don't know, I say
heads we drop him.
- Heads we drop him.
- I don't have any change,
you have any change?
- What are you doing?
Oh my god.
(dramatic music)
- [Dispatcher] 911.
- I think there's an
intruder in my apartment.
- [Dispatcher] One moment.
Megan Stewart, 2 Bolton
Street, Apartment 3.
Mam, the police have
been dispatched.
Stay where you are until
the officers arrive
and keep the line open.
- Hey, Frenchy, catch.
Heads or tails?
- Tails!
Hey, listen, Yankee and
Doodle, dispatch got a call.
Intruder.
- What are you doing?
- 2 Bolton, number 3.
The building behind you.
- What'd he say?
- Come on, move!
- Where are you going?
- Get this guy down, now!
Let's move!
- Hey, what are you doing?
Freaks! You can't...
(dramatic music)
- You want the front or rear?
- I'm a backdoor man.
Stay behind him, let's go.
(Megan screams)
- [Dispatcher] Miss Stewart,
are you still there?
(Megan gasps)
- Drop the weapon.
- Do not test me,
I will kill her.
- You kill her, I kill you.
- Hey!
- Shut up!
- Drop the weapon
and maybe your lawyer
will have you out on
the street by morning.
Now drop it.
- Yeah, don't do this, don't.
- All right.
- Easy.
(gunshots banging)
(Ivan groaning)
- What kind of stupid, macho,
Neanderthal move was that?
- You're welcome.
- Who the hell do
you think you are?
You could've killed me.
- Ain't life a bowl of cherries.
(Frenchy and Darcy laughing)
- Ouch.
- I work for the police
department, I've got friends.
I want your badge number
because I'm gonna report you!
- What the hell happened here?
- That moron blew up my toilet.
- Well, that's a hell
of a first day, brother,
considering you
haven't punched in yet.
- [Ivan] Be careful!
- Wait till you
get to your cell.
Cuff him.
- [Darcy] Come on, scumbag.
- We got right to
make phone call.
- Don't tell me about
your rights, you moron.
- Can I have some
service over here?
Go on.
Gonna miss you guys.
Go in.
- Lou.
- Goddamn, it's good to see you!
It's hard to believe you've
only been here a few hours.
The whole station is buzzing.
Your reputation as a
hard-ass precedes you.
(upbeat rock music)
- [Vlad] The reports
I am getting are not
favorable, Mikael.
- [Mikael] Yes, Uncle.
- [Vlad] You waste
my time and my money.
- Uncle, they are lies.
We've had a few setbacks,
but nothing unusual.
I need more money for
bribery, to compete.
In this respect, the
competition is well ahead of us.
- [Vlad] No, there will
be no more investment
until I see results.
This opportunity you
are squandering will
not last forever.
And Mikael.
- Yes, Uncle Vladimir?
- [Vlad] I have just
learned that my old friend
Lieutenant Ray Harlan has
arrived in your back yard.
- [Mikael] Should
this concern me?
- [Vlad] Very much so.
He has been a big problem
for me here in New York.
Do not underestimate him, he
doesn't play by the rules.
- Neither do we.
Do not worry, I will
take care of it.
- [Vlad] Do not let
me down, Mikael.
Even if you are my
blood, you will die.
- Now, Ray, you know
better than most
how Russians love payola.
You talk to me, huh, and
anyone I say is okay.
We'll put you on the
clock starting tomorrow.
Okay then.
Darcy, get him out of here.
Oh, hey, tonight you and
Darceú are coming for dinner.
- Oh, oh.
- What?
What are you looking
so warm and fuzzy for?
- Thanks for bringing me back.
New York was getting a little
shaky, you know, empty.
You two guys are the only
family I got, you know.
It's good to be home, Lou.
- Go, will ya?
I'm about to shed a tear.
- Thanks.
(light jazzy music)
- It's great having
you boys here.
I miss all the great
dinners we used to have.
- Great, I don't
know about that.
- Hey, wise guy, I
make a great stew.
- Brace yourself, Ray,
here comes the stew speech.
- Stew's a real healthy meal.
Did you know that poor people
don't get sick like the rich
because they eat a lot of stews?
Yeah, it's cheap to make,
and it has all the
necessary vitamins.
Now eat, you
ungrateful delinquents.
(Ray and Darcy laughing)
- I'm sorry, Lou, it must
have been tough for you, huh?
Raising a couple of
tough heads like us.
- Ah, it wasn't so bad.
As a matter of fact, most of
the time we had a ball, right?
You boys, you turned
out just fine.
I love you both very much.
Welcome home, Ray.
- Thanks.
- [Crowd] Surprise!
- Hey, Frenchy.
- Hey, nice to see you, buddy.
Hey, that's great.
What's up?
- Tequila.
♪ You got to reap
just what you sow ♪
- Hey, Darcy.
- Welcome home, Ray.
♪ It's the same the
whole world over ♪
- Welcome home, mon ami.
- Thanks, Frenchy.
- Hey, Ray, this is
my new partner, Blue.
- Hey, Blue.
- Hey, Ray, heard a lot
of things about you.
- Nothing good, I hope.
- As good as good gets.
- All right.
- What in the hell
is he talking about?
You haven't changed,
learn English.
♪ And all the sexy plans
♪ It's a sin for everyone
♪ You know you got to
reap just what you sow ♪
♪ It's the same the whole
world over everywhere you go ♪
- Hey.
(crowd cheering)
- [Frenchy] Hey, she's
a computer wizard.
She's not supposed
to be good with guns.
- Oh, quite a looker, huh?
What the hell's she doing here?
- I invited her.
- Why?
- Because she works for me.
And she's gonna be
working with you.
- What?
- Yeah, she came to the
precinct raising hell.
I mean, she was so
pissed off at you
that she wanted me to have you
busted down to traffic cop.
Anyhow, after I calmed her down,
I found out that she worked
at Central Database
uptown at 21st Division.
- [Ray] She works
for the department?
- Yeah, yeah, I
offered her a raise
and invited her to
join our precinct.
I like her ballsiness.
- Oh yeah, hey, nothing
like a chick with balls.
- Oh yeah.
- Come on, I'll introduce you.
Come on, come on.
Come feel her balls.
- Aw Jesus.
♪ You got to reap
just what you sow ♪
- Megan, Megan Stewart.
I'd like to introduce
you properly to
Lieutenant Ray Harlan.
He just transferred
in from New York.
- Must be my lucky day.
♪ It's the same the
whole world over ♪
- Oops.
- You're quite the
character, Mr. Harlan.
- Oh, I can speak for Ray's
character, Miss Stewart.
When Ray's father
died in Vietnam,
Darcy and Ray came
under my roof.
Raised 'em both from pups.
- Listen, I'm really
sorry about any mishap.
If there's anything I can
do to make it up to you.
And by the way, call me Ray.
- Well, how about buying me a
new toilet bowl, Mr. Harlan?
- Maybe we could take
up a little collection.
Maybe we'll pass around
a bowl, huh? (laughs)
Oh baby.
- You jerk.
Frenchy.
- What am I supposed to say?
- She likes you.
- Hey, Darcy.
- Yeah.
- I need a signature on this.
- Turn around, will ya?
Thanks, Jimmy.
- What was that all about?
- Just a little business.
- What kind of business?
- I'm a part owner
in this place.
- Yeah right.
- Seriously.
- Get the hell out of here.
What are you talking about?
- Yeah, three years now.
Just a little investment
for the future.
You know, can't be
cops forever, right?
- You and who else?
- Oh, a couple of guys,
Frenchy, Lou's in on it.
- Lou?
- Yeah, hey, let's
get out of here, huh?
You remember that
Skanky's, the bar Skanky's?
- Oh yeah.
- Hey, Lou, Lou?
Ray and I are gonna
go over to Skanky's.
- No, no, no, you stay here.
You got to close up the joint.
- Come on, don't listen to him.
Come on, we'll go.
- I gotta, it's Lou.
- Hey, French, you want to go?
- No, thanks.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah?
- Can I talk to
you for a second?
- Sure.
(phone ringing)
- Yeah?
- [Darcy] Ray, it's Darcy.
The Black Rose Boys just
hit the bank on Maple.
They're holed up in a
church a few blocks down.
- Where?
- Corner of Spruce and Goose.
Listen, they took hostages.
Meet me there in 10.
- Spruce and Goose.
Spruce and Goose.
(officers chattering)
(siren blaring)
Hey, Blue, Frenchy.
- [Frenchy] Hello, Ray.
- Take your best shot?
- Nice church, how many?
- [Darcy] Only four, but they
got the caretakers hostage.
I think they might be going
for the padre as well.
- I don't mind taking out a
gas station, but a church?
- Listen, anything or anybody
comes out those
doors, shoot 'em.
Let's go, little brother.
(dramatic music)
- I'm telling you,
we can't stay here.
They're stacking up out there.
- Who did Mikael put in charge?
- So what are you waiting for?
- Shut up and let me think.
Would you like to pray?
I'll let you pray
to me. (laughs)
- Look what I found.
- Excellent, Father, come here.
I have something
I want to confess.
- You mustn't do this, it
is an offense against God.
- We are your new
congregation, Father.
However, I must warn you,
we are pretty much atheists.
(men laughing)
- Boris, look out!
(gunshots banging)
(man shouting)
(smack cracking)
- How dare you!
- Get down!
(gunshot banging)
(gunshots banging)
- Stop this, this is blasphemy.
- Amen.
(gunshot banging)
(priest groans)
(gunshots banging)
(gunshot banging)
(man groans)
(blows cracking)
(blows thudding)
- Freeze, you son of a bitch.
You take your hands out
of that coat real slow.
Take 'em out slow!
- Relax, it's only a phone.
(laughing) I love America.
I'm going to call my lawyer.
He's going to get me out in
a few hours for a fraction
of the price that I used
to pay in bribes in Moscow.
We own you, Yankee.
- You all right?
(phone beeping)
- What are you doing?
I give up.
- Two people died,
one was a priest.
(gunshot banging)
(man groaning)
- You shot me!
You shot me!
- Guy's a real Einstein, huh?
- You missed.
- [Ray] No.
- You all right?
- He resisted.
- Uh huh.
- Hey, by the way,
thanks, little buddy.
- Oh, you're welcome,
Marshall Dillon.
- You have the right
to remain silent.
You have the right
to an attorney.
Everything can and will
be used against you
in a court of law.
♪ I am blind, wrong or right
♪ It is my burden now
♪ I am sick from a thing
I assumed was right ♪
♪ And I am cruel, really
rude not to say the truth ♪
♪ Darling, make your move
♪ Ba da ba ba da
ba da ba da dum ♪
♪ Ba da ba ba da ba
- Sit down.
I think you might want to take
it easy for a little while.
Internal Affairs is
already sniffing around.
- I don't think you
should get involved, Lou.
- You know, when I asked
you to leave New York
and come and work with me,
and you said you were glad to,
I did everything I
could to make it happen.
Well, I called in favors
I didn't even know I had.
And now I owe favors.
The point that I'm making is.
- Thanks.
- You're like my
own flesh and blood.
There isn't anything in the
world I wouldn't do for you.
But there's still a
job to be done, hm?
I'll deal with Internal Affairs.
You take care of
Mick and his boys.
And honestly I don't care
if they leave on a bus
or in a body bag, I
just want 'em wiped out.
- You know, Lou, I haven't seen
anything on these guys yet.
I mean, what do we
really know about them
besides the fact that Mikael
and Vladimir are related?
Nothing.
- Yeah, it is a
little disorganized
around here, isn't it?
Let's go to the computer room.
I think it's time you and
Megan got reacquainted.
- I don't think she
likes me too much, Lou.
- Use your boyish
charm, come on.
- Please, come on.
- Megan, you remember
Lieutenant Harlan.
- Not by choice.
- Well, good to see you
again, too, Miss Stewart.
- Megan, I know this isn't
your job description,
but I'm in a time crunch.
I want you to work with Ray.
Get this fancy equipment
to work up a composite
of what we're up against.
- I'll start on it
right away, Captain.
- Good, well then I'll leave
you two to get to work.
- Are you gonna keep circling
around like a Mexican ass
grinding grain or are we
gonna get some work done, huh?
- Hey, what is
your problem, lady?
- You, I just don't like you.
- Why, because I
shot up your toilet?
Hey, you don't know me
well enough to dislike me.
- I know all about you.
Did you know that the FBI and
the NSA have files on you?
- Oh really, I had no idea.
- I know that you
received four decorations
for meritorious service.
- Well, see, I guess
I'm not so bad then.
- I also know you were
the biggest disturber
in the history of your precinct.
I know that you were on
sick leave for six months,
then had to go through a
psych evaluation because of
your unorthodox behavior that
almost cost you your shield.
- That's privileged information,
could get you arrested.
- I'm covered.
- I'll bet you are.
- Look, the point
is, Lieutenant,
don't brush me aside.
I'm not some chick, I'm
an asset to this force.
- Hey, files don't tell you
everything, Miss Stewart.
They have a tendency to
leave out the person.
- Oh, fill in the blanks for me.
- Well, maybe one day when
you cut me some slack, I will.
- You're so full of it.
The captain stole that
sword from some sushi bar
in San Francisco,
everybody knows that.
- You know, this was
given to Lou by a family
of sword masters on
the island of Shiku--
- Shokoko.
- Shokoko, it doesn't matter.
Anyway, it's not about that.
It's about the steel
and the force of spirit
behind that steel, which
you wouldn't understand.
- We've listened to
lot of your stories,
but there's no way that you
can expect me to believe that
the lieutenant here can cut
through steel with that sword.
- This is Japanese samurai,
strongest steel known to man.
Wrapped over 200 times.
Ray.
- You got money that
says this can't be done?
- 100 bucks.
- Whoa.
100 bucks, man, put
that money up here.
- He's a rich boy.
- You hear that? 100 bucks.
We got any other takers?
French, collect
the money, come on.
- Here, take it.
- 100 bucks.
- Hey, anybody else?
Come on, losers.
- What are you
packin' in here, man?
- .357 magnum.
- Oh, that's a big boy.
- That's stopping power.
- I'll tell you what that is.
You know what that is?
(sword clanging)
- [Man] Whoa, nice one, Ray!
(Frenchy laughing)
- That's a snub nose.
(crowd laughing)
- My gun.
You son of a gun, Jesus.
- Show me the money, baby.
See ya, Frenchy.
- Wine, red, French.
♪ I just might fall in love
(Ray knocking)
(Ray laughing)
(Megan and Ray laughing)
- Well, it's too late, I
already had one put in.
- Aw, too bad.
Because you never know when
a spare might come in handy.
Well, me and Darcy, we went
to get a little bite to eat.
- And?
- And he seems to think
that you're nuts about me,
only your hostility
is just a way to hide
the way you really
feel about me.
- Hm, what I think
he probably said
was that I think you're nuts.
- Oh.
So you gonna invite me in,
have a little cup of coffee?
Maybe use your toilet. (laughs)
- Well, I'm gonna have to
suggest you put it down first.
It's late, I'll
see you tomorrow.
Good night, Lieutenant.
♪ Just might fall in love
(blow cracking)
- We have a message
for your brother.
You, you'll deliver it.
- Go to hell.
- You first.
(blow cracking)
- You better make
damn sure you kill me.
- You got balls, huh?
Now maybe I show
you mine. (laughs)
(Darcy groaning)
(smack cracking)
(gunshot banging)
(Darcy groaning)
Lucky for you, Mikael ordered
us not to kill you, hm?
This is the message.
Tell him Mikael says an eye
for an eye, a hand for a hand.
- How is he?
- He shot him in the hand.
He's all messed up.
- He'll bounce
back, he's strong.
Did he say why
they targeted him?
- Because Mikael Pushkin,
he had a message for me,
and he sent it through Darcy.
This is bull.
I think I'll send a
little message of my own.
- Be careful, don't do
anything stupid, Ray.
We'll get this Pushkin
punk, Darce, I promise you.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Sweetie baby,
hello, come over here.
- Yeah, come on, you're cute.
Hey, American boy, hello?
Come back here.
♪ Taste, lay down,
touch, get up ♪
♪ Rollin' around
♪ Taste, go down,
touch, keep it up ♪
♪ Feeling around till
the sun comes up ♪
♪ Taste
- Yeah, come on.
Come on, try something.
Come on, yeah.
♪ Need, oh how I need
♪ Oh now your ass is mine
♪ Taste, go down,
touch, get up ♪
♪ Feeling around
♪ I want to taste, go
down, touch, get up ♪
♪ Feeling around
(crowd cheering)
(man speaking in
foreign language)
What a show.
- Have Nadia search
him and send him in.
(patrons chattering)
I'm Mick Pushkin.
- No kidding, Mikael.
Nice little sleazy
place you got here.
Two-way mirror's a cute idea.
- I like to keep an eye
on the occasional scum
that enters the bar.
Would you like
some Russian vodka?
- Nah, I don't much
like anything Russian.
- Are we having a
pissing contest here?
Your reputation as
trouble precedes you.
- Oh, let me guess.
I guess you've been talking
to your Uncle Vladimir, huh?
- He says you've caused
him a lot of grief.
- Not as much as
I'm gonna cause you.
- We are growing more
powerful every day.
America, what a country, yes?
And with us controlling
it, we'll make it greater.
- Oh, so you think you
can just waltz in here
and take over, huh?
- Not alone.
We do get home from your
greedy little politicians.
- You wouldn't want to share any
of these names with
me now, would you?
- Why don't you ask someone
in your own department?
It used to belong to you guys.
- Bull, Mikael.
- You mean, no one's
approached you yet?
- Who? Who, Mikael?
Who hasn't approached me?
- I don't know who yet, but
a small group is fighting us
for territories we
are taking over.
- So you're not
telling me anything.
Why the hell should
I believe you?
- It doesn't matter
to me what you think.
- Look, I'm gonna quit
dicking around with you
and get right to the point.
I want the ass who beat
and shot my brother,
and then maybe I'll let
you live a little longer.
- And I want the ass
who beat and shot Boris.
My uncle wants you dead.
I want you dead.
Do you see any reason why
I don't do it right now?
- Ethics?
How's your prickly little ass?
- How's your brother's face?
- Ray, listen to me.
I got my revenge
with your brother.
I'm satisfied with that for now.
But the next time we
meet, I will kill you.
- You're a dead man.
(men laughing)
- I heard about Darcy, sorry.
- Me too.
- How is he?
- A little shaky.
They said they're
gonna release him
from the hospital tomorrow.
So you hungry, you want to
get a little bite to eat?
- Girl's gotta eat.
Come on, I know a good spot.
- So what's your story?
- Well, I grew up in Vermont.
My dad got transferred here.
I went to college, I got
interested in computers,
started working for
the police department.
I'm single, so end of story.
You got a girl?
- Nope.
Mm, these are great, huh?
- So Lou said he
raised you and Darcy.
- Mhm, my mom died about six
months after Dad passed away.
- How did she die?
- I guess a broken heart.
- That must've been really hard.
- Well, abandonment
is always tough.
- I guess Lou had to pull a
lot of strings to get you here.
- Yeah, well you know Lou.
I'm glad he did.
I mean, Lou and Darcy,
only family I've got.
- Lou seems to have a
really protective demeanor.
- He's got a good reason to.
I mean, him and my dad,
they were like this.
They were closer than brothers.
And he saw my father die along
with a lot of other guys.
And then he came home to what?
Not exactly a hero's
welcome after Vietnam.
And how he's a cop,
a damn good one too.
Another thankless job.
- I don't why anybody would
ever want to be a cop.
I mean, it certainly
isn't the money.
What is it?
- Free parking. (laughs)
So any information
on Pushkin yet?
- No, no, but hopefully soon.
Oh, and Ray.
- You know, it's been a
long time since I picked up
one of you boys
from the hospital.
- Hey, nice, Lou.
Last time I was driving
in the car with you,
I think you had tape
on your ripped seats
and it smelled like cat piss.
- Come a long way since then.
Things have changed,
for Darcy too.
Our investments have paid
off, haven't they, Darce?
Hey, slugger, we gotta
talk about your future.
You know, getting
you on board with us.
We're family, right?
Got to stick together.
- I don't have any money, Lou.
I mean, I spend it
faster than I make it.
- Did you hear me ask
this guy for a loan?
I'm talking about making money.
- Paid Mikael Pushkin a visit.
- You what?
You're one crazy son of
a bitch, you know that?
I'm surprised you
didn't get killed.
What happened?
- He went on about how great
and powerful his people are.
- Hey, the only thing they're
good at is drinking vodka.
What else?
- Some bull about how some
of the city's police
department is corrupt.
- Those Ruskie bastards, they
think everybody's corrupt.
- Yeah, well I asked
him for some names.
He couldn't give me any, so
I told him he's full of it.
- And then what happened?
- He said one thing or another,
I said one thing or another.
And then he threatened to
kill me next time he sees me.
- Jesus, Ray, come on,
take it easy will you?
Be careful.
I can use a drink.
Why don't we go to our
place and have a few, huh?
Darcy could probably use
one, what do you say?
- You're the boss, Lou.
Anything you say.
(twangy rock music)
♪ Some people got to
preach the golden rule ♪
♪ Do unto others as
they do unto you ♪
♪ But I know out back they
don't live like that ♪
- Just tell me something.
- What?
- How does a blue
collar boy like you
end up putting together a
place like Kops and Krooks?
- It's not just me, you know,
it's like a pension fund.
Except we decide where
the investments go.
- And Lou's a full partner?
- Yeah, and he's still
pushing me around
just like when I was a kid.
He never got away with
that stuff with you.
- Believe me, he had his ways.
We turned out okay,
didn't we, huh, right?
- I'll believe it if you do.
To the best, forget the rest.
- What's the matter with you?
Come on, look at yourself.
I mean, you are sitting
on top of the world.
You made it to lieutenant,
you took care of your money,
which is way more
than I could ever do.
What, are you lonely, huh?
You got women problems?
You have men problems, huh?
- See, what you don't see,
there's no escape for me.
You know, before I even wipe
the sleep out of my eyes,
I go to my day job.
I finish my day
job, I come here.
And I have to stay
here till close.
And I'm not talking about
this little bar stuff
because there's a lot
of things about this
that I can't tell
you, and it's messy.
♪ I heard somebody talk
about live and let live ♪
- You know I love Lou, right?
♪ I know I've taken
much more than I give ♪
♪ If you can't speak the truth
- This partnership
with him is killing me.
I mean literally.
- Man, you're depressing.
I mean, we know Lou has
always been a power-tripper.
It was like growing up
in a marine bootcamp.
But you're a big man now.
You don't like it, you get out.
- Get out, how am I
supposed to do that?
It's not that easy, Ray.
- Why not?
- Why not? Because the
stuff that's in my head.
I could take the whole
friggin' town down
with what's in my head.
High level people, I
could take them down.
- What, the Russians?
- [Darcy] High level people.
- What's up, boys?
- Hey.
Just explaining business to Ray.
Glorious business.
- Better days are ahead.
- I'll believe it if you will.
- Hear hear.
♪ All right
- [Darcy] Another round, Jimmy.
(Frenchy singing in
foreign language)
♪ The rockets red glare
♪ The bombs bursting in air
♪ Gave proof through the night
♪ That our flag
was still there ♪
♪ Oh say
(gunshot banging)
(dramatic music)
- Stay down!
Lou, you see anything?
- No, no.
- Darce, Darcy!
Darce, hey, Darce!
Damn it!
- Darcy, Darcy.
Darcy, come on!
Come on, talk to me, come on!
- Darcy.
- Come on, talk to me!
- Darce, man.
- No.
God, please tell
me he's not dead.
- You're a dead man, Pushkin!
You're a dead man, you
hear me, you low-life scum?
You're a dead man!
- Get him, Ray, get
that son of a bitch!
Bring him back in a body bag!
Go, Ray, go!
Darcy, my Darcy. (crying)
(upbeat electronic music)
(gunshots banging)
(crowd shouting)
- Go.
- [Man] Get down,
duck, get down.
- Hold it.
I got a message for
you from my brother.
(gunshots banging)
(women screaming)
(men shouting)
(gunshots banging)
(Mikael gasps)
You're about to die, you
filthy little stinkin' itch.
Now kiss Mother
America good bye.
- Hey, let's work
something out, make a deal.
- A deal? You want to
make a deal with me?
You killed my brother and you
want to make a deal with me?
- Your brother? I
didn't kill him.
I had nothing to do with it.
- Maybe you didn't pull the
trigger, but you ordered it,
and that's the same thing.
- I swear I don't know
what you're talking about.
What purpose would it
serve me to kill him?
- Maybe your shooter was
after me and he missed.
- I could've killed
you here earlier.
- You lying piece of.
(glass shattering)
- I didn't do it, I swear.
- Your last chance.
Now I want to know who
killed my brother Darcy.
- Check your own
department, Ray.
That's where the answer is.
(Ray growling)
- Oh my god.
- I'm gonna sue you
for busting my bar.
- Shut up, you'll get a
chance to tell your story.
Book him, start
with racketeering.
- You can't make that stick.
I'll be out of
here in two hours.
- Make sure he gets
his one phone call.
- [Officer] Right,
take him away.
- Ray, Ray!
For what it's worth, I'm
sorry about your brother.
But it was not I who killed him.
Watch your back.
Ray, it wasn't me. It wasn't.
- Ge him out of here.
- Be careful, Ray.
Trust no one.
- Hi, Ray.
I heard about
Darcy, I'm so sorry.
- I loved him so much.
- I know.
- Boy, Lou took it really hard.
He took it real, real hard.
- Ray, I don't know
how to tell you this.
- What?
- I think Lou was involved.
- Oh, come on, Megan,
don't do this to me.
Not right now. Come on, please.
- No, Ray, you
need to hear this.
I had suspicions.
There were rumors
about crooked cops,
so I ran a random
check on the computer.
I found something on Lou.
- Can't be. You have no proof.
- No, Ray, I know how
hard it is to hear this,
but I do have proof.
He's got $1.3 million
in a Cayman account.
- I don't believe this.
- Lou and Frenchy
have about the same.
- What?
What?
What about Darcy?
Well, goddamn it all.
Goddamn it all.
That does not mean that Lou
had anything to do with
Darcy's death though.
Pushkin has got to have
something to do with this.
Hey, Joe, it's Ray.
- [Joe] Yes, sir?
- Listen, I want you
to bring Mikael Pushkin
to the interrogation
room right now.
- [Joe] Blue and Frenchy
just picked him up.
- What?
- [Joe] Yeah, Captain's orders.
- When?
- 15 minutes ago.
- Thanks, Joe.
- Sure.
- [Megan] What is it?
- Blue and Frenchy
just picked up Pushkin,
and Lou ordered the release.
(blow cracking)
(man groaning)
- Hello, Ray, look what I got.
- What are you doing, Lou?
- What you should've
done when you had him.
You're not getting soft
on me, are you, Ray?
- He didn't kill Darcy.
- No?
Then who did?
- Ray, please help me.
Please, I know.
(gunshot banging)
(Mikael shouts)
- That's for Darcy, you
Ruskie son of a bitch.
- What did he know, Lou?
- Nothing. What's there to know?
- I know about your
Cayman bank account.
I know about yours too.
And yours.
- Well, that's very interesting.
How did you come by
this information?
Of course, Megan Stewart.
Who else have you shared
this information with?
- Nobody yet.
I want to know who
killed my brother.
Was it you?
- I could never do that.
He had no choice.
- No choice, huh?
No choice?
And you stood by and
you just let it happen.
- I didn't know
anything about it.
It's out of my hands.
This is way bigger
than you, me, or Darcy.
Ray, I'm just a pawn
in the king's court.
You wouldn't believe the power
of the people involved here.
- A pawn, you mean like me?
You called me in here
to take care of Mikael
because he was cuttin'
in on your business.
And that's the only
reason, isn't it?
- No, I wanted you
to come in with us.
You, me, and Darcy, we
would've been great together.
- You know, I
might've done it, Lou.
I might've done it, but now
the sight of you makes me sick.
I thought you were our father.
I was wrong because a
father would never, ever
let anybody do that to his son.
- We had no choice, Ray.
He was getting
weak. He wanted out.
People above thought he
was talking too much.
- You always have
a choice, Frenchy,
and apparently you
guys have made yours.
Now I'm gonna make mine.
- Ray, I'm begging you, join us.
It's not too late.
- Oh, come on, Lou.
Oh, it's way too late for that.
Jesus Christ.
What are you gonna do, Lou?
You gonna kill me too, Father?
(gunshots banging)
(glass shattering)
(dramatic music)
(horn honking)
- [Frenchy] Should
we make a call?
- No, this is personal.
He'll be back.
I know him well.
- Megan!
God, are you all right?
- Ray, what the
hell is going on?
Where have you been?
I've been leaving
messages all over town.
- Just listen to to
me, listen to me.
- What happened?
- I gotta get you out of here.
- What's going on?
- Look, I can't explain it
to you right now, okay?
- Where are we going?
- I don't know, a motel maybe.
- A motel?
- I don't even know
who I can trust.
But you got to trust me, okay?
Please, please, come on.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
- Why don't you take a shower
and grab a couple hours' sleep?
I think you could use it.
- Yeah.
(somber music)
Oh Jesus.
Never, ever let anybody
do that to his son.
- [Darcy] Just a little
investment for the future.
You know, can't be
cops forever, right?
- [Megan] There were
rumors about crooked cops,
so I ran a random
check on the computer.
- [Mikael] Check your
own department, Ray.
That's where the answer is.
- [Megan] I found
something on Lou.
- [Lou] Things have changed.
- [Megan] He's got $1.3
million in a Cayman account.
- [Lou] Our investments have
paid off, haven't they, Darce?
- [Megan] Lou and Frenchy
have about the same.
- [Frenchy] People above
thought he was talking too much.
- [Darcy] You know
I love Lou, right?
This partnership with
him is killing me.
- [Ray] Are you gonna
kill me too, Father?
- What are you doing?
- I'm going.
- Where are you going, Ray?
- What are you doing?
- I'm not sitting around here
while you get yourself killed.
I'm going back to the police
station to back up the files
so nobody erases them.
- Hey, that's a
really good idea,
but I don't want you doing it.
Now come on, this is very
personal to me right now.
This is between me and Lou.
I don't want you involved.
- I'm already involved, Ray.
They want me dead too.
Besides, I'll be at the police
station where I can be safer.
- Know how to use one of these?
- Yeah.
- The safety's on, take it.
- [Frenchy] I can't
believe you came back, Ray.
I thought you were
smarter than that.
You may not be in New York,
but you're way out of
your league, mon ami.
Welcome home.
- You're gonna wish I
never came back, Frenchy.
When you shot my brother,
you killed yourself.
(gunshots banging)
(gunshot banging)
(Blue shouting)
(gunshots banging)
(gunshot banging)
(siren blaring)
- I'm standing behind you, Ray.
Drop your guns.
It's all been said before.
There's nothing more to say.
- Wrong.
Drop the guns or I drop you.
Now!
One.
Two.
Three.
(gunshot banging)
(kick thudding)
(Frenchy groans)
- Run!
(gunshots banging)
Geez.
Gimme the gun.
Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, are you?
- What are you doing here?
- You're welcome.
- I can't believe you shot him.
- I said I would.
- That you did.
(gunshots banging)
We can't stay here too long.
Oh geez.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
- There's some gas in there.
I hope there's enough.
Hey, take my tourniquet off.
- What?
Oh god.
- Just take it off.
- Oh god, oh god, there.
Careful.
(gunshots banging)
- Oh, damn it, I shouldn't
have quit smoking.
- Here, here, here.
- You smoke?
- Gimme that.
- Damn it.
Try to get it there.
- [Megan] There, I got it.
That's it, it's going.
- Okay, now run like heck, go.
(gunshots banging)
(dramatic music)
- Oh my god.
(explosion booming)
(Frenchy shouting)
- Megan?
- I remember teaching
you how to use that.
Hurts like hell,
but I'm still alive.
- You all right?
- It's the final
scene, huh, Ray?
Father against son.
- No, Lou, no.
Father against himself.
Megan and I are
walking out of here.
- I don't think so.
- Trust me, he won't shoot you.
- Don't move.
Ray, don't test me.
Ray.
Ray!
I'm sorry.
Darcy!
Darcy.
(dramatic music)
(triumphant music)