When are they gonna come?
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
Can't believe
we're running late.
Why didn't you wake me?
I did wake you up.
You just went back to sleep.
You should've woken me up again!
You should be able
to wake yourself up.
I'm eight!
I was up baking all last night-
Kids, stop arguing.
Brie, get in the car.
Hurry up.
Buckle your seatbelt.
♪ Been broke and beaten down ♪
♪ Tasted dirt as
I hit the ground ♪
You look awfully spiffy today.
It's show and tell day.
Booger face.
Poop head!
Hey, I don't
wanna hear it today.
♪ How far you gonna go ♪
Wait, Dad!
I left my phone at the house.
Go back.
We're already
running late, sweetie.
But, Dad!
What do you need a phone for?
You'll be in school.
I don't wanna be
late for school.
I wasn't talking to you.
Don't talk to your
brother like that.
Can you please calm down?
Fine.
Apologize to your brother.
Sorry for yelling at you
even though you deserved it.
You call that an apology?
Brie.
Sorry.
Okay.
There we go.
Now it's a subpar morning again.
♪ Live like a drop of rain ♪
♪ Love like a hurricane ♪
Good morning, Cardinals!
Don't forge we'll have
an early dismissal
today for our bake sale.
I hope you all
brought your bakes.
Winners will get to compete
in our annual Spring
Bake Off Challenge.
So please cheer your
fellow students on!
You still asleep over there?
No, I'm just a little nervous.
You got this.
Remember what I told you?
Yeah.
You'll be fine.
Okay.
Now go get 'em.
Thank you.
All right, have a great day.
And sell those bakes!
Thank you.
Ew.
Do you really think those bakes
will sell better than mine?
Those look like poop.
These happen to be the
most amazing brownies ever.
Not if they look like that.
See mine?
These taste as
good as they look.
Those look like you
bought them from the store.
I'm just good at baking
and I'm going to
sell the most today.
Well I hope you didn't
mistake sugar for salt.
I hope you don't
accidentally drop your bakes.
You wouldn't.
After you.
Don't.
Don't do it.
Hey.
Why were you talking to Vanessa?
She thinks she's
gonna win the bake sale.
Did you tell her that
it's your grandma's
super secret recipe?
No, she was too busy
calling them poop.
She doesn't know what
she's talking about.
I know.
Where's your bakes?
Ms. Melanie had us take some
to the big fridge already.
You might have to go too.
Great.
What?
Vanessa said "I hope
you don't accidentally"
drop your bakes."
Oops.
Is everything all right, Millie?
Yeah.
You know, I just got a
whiff of Brie's brownies
and they took my breath away.
So good.
Brie, why don't you go
to the cafeteria fridge
where the rest of the bakes are?
Yes, Ms. Melanie.
Ms. Melanie, I need
to put mine away too.
All right, go ahead.
Anyone else have bakes
for the bake sale?
Sorry.
Wish me luck.
Wishing your
bakes a safe voyage.
Oh, why
Jody, those look fantastic.
Why don't you go with
the girls to the fridge?
Hey, wait for him, girls.
Hey, Jody, those
look really good.
Thanks.
All right, everyone.
Settle down.
Take out your
writing assignments
and send them to the front.
So, who taught you how to bake?
My dad's a baker.
That's so cool.
My dad's lame.
Why? What's he do?
He's...
He, uh...
He's a doctor.
Oh, he must be really busy.
Very.
Oh, shoot.
I forgot my whipped
cream in my backpack.
I'll be right back.
A doctor?
Don't say anything, or else.
I'm not really gonna
drop your bakes.
I'm gonna beat you
fair and square.
Yeah, well, we'll just
have to see then, won't we?
All right, let's go.
Om.
Namaste, everyone.
Namaste.
Now, in honor of
today's bake sale,
and because we have
shorter classes,
I thought it would be fun
for each of us to draw
our favorite desserts.
Nice.
Now, here's some
paper to draw on.
Pass those back.
Now really think about
the feeling you get
when drawing out the
details of your desserts.
Okay?
Splendid.
I am not a cheese wheel!
Brie, what on earth
are you talking about?
Nothing.
What's on that piece of paper?
Brie, show me what's
on that paper.
Who drew this?
Brie?
Millie?
I don't know.
Someone tell me who drew this
or none of you will participate
in the bake sale today.
What?
One last time.
All right.
I'll tell Ms. Melanie
that each of you
will be waiting in the cafeteria
for your parents to
come and get you.
It was Vanessa.
Is this true, Vanessa?
Kind of.
You know better than to
gossip about other people,
especially your classmates.
You're going to the
principal's office.
And let this be a lesson
to the rest of you.
There will absolutely no
name calling of any kind.
In this classroom or out of it!
You're such a tattle tale.
Vanessa!
The aura in here is
completely tainted.
Continue working
on your drawings
until the bell rings.
I can't believe
you just did that.
Did you hear how quiet she was?
I know, but to call her out
in front of everybody?
Mr. Claymore
would've made us
sit out on the bake sale.
Yeah, but tell him in private
like in a note or after class.
Something else.
Oh, yeah.
I guess that
would've been better.
Oh my sweet tart.
There's Vanessa.
Do you think they'll still
let her in the bake sale?
I don't know.
I hope not.
Only nice people
should be able to do it.
Well, if she doesn't,
then we're definitely winning
those tickets to Cosmo Land.
I don't know.
Jody's pies smelled really good.
Maybe she'll get detention
for like the rest of her life.
Yeah, right.
Wait.
Something's wrong
with your pizza.
What the?
Ew.
It's still frozen.
Go ask for another one.
BRB.
I can't wait
for the bake sale today!
Vanessa's cupcakes
look really pretty.
I wanna try Jody's pies.
Yeah, we'll see who wins.
Patricia says she
doesn't know what happened.
Weird.
So, I just got fruit instead.
Well that's healthier
since we've been eating
a lot of sweets lately.
Yeah, yeah.
At least we get out early today.
I love early dismissal days.
I cannot wait to win this thing.
Me too.
Here we go.
We got this.
Millie, Vanessa's in.
Sugar, we don't got this.
All right, kids.
Who's ready for the bake sale?
Mm-mm-mm.
Whoever hired him
deserves a medal.
Whoever made him
Agreed.
This is your first bake sale?
Yeah.
We didn't do anything like
this at my other school.
Ms. Melanie, I'm
a little concerned
about the calorie consumption
that's gonna take
place here today.
Oh, yes. Me too.
It's an awful lot of sugar
for such small children.
Yeah.
I think we're ready to start.
Trying to get on
his good side, I see?
No, it's true.
You were one of the first
to yay the Bake Off, remember?
Shh!
I'm trying to listen.
All right, kids.
Who's ready to
start the bake sale?
That's the spirit I like to see.
All right, a couple
of reminders.
One, try not to eat all
your bakes at once, okay?
We don't want you
guys going home
with severe stomach pains.
And two, this is the big one,
the top four contestants
who sell the most bakes today
will have the
opportunity to compete
in our annual Spring
Bake Off Challenge.
All right, and now
I'm gonna hand it over
to Ms. Melanie for some
more exciting news.
Thank you, Lester.
Okay.
The winner of this year's
Spring Bake Off Challenge
will win the usual,
four tickets to Cosmo Land
and, new this year,
is $5,000 towards
your college tuition
thanks to our new
corporate sponsor DCBX.
Now DCBX is going to
be providing our school
with the necessary
tools and technology
to create more extracurricular
activities such as these.
$5,000?
Oh my great jellybeans.
Millie, that's enough to
pay for my culinary school.
Or a new computer
for The Mighty Realm.
They said it's
for college tuition,
not computer games.
Oh, I guess it
can go to that too.
All right, children.
Ready, set, sell those bakes!
How much?
How much do you think
these delicious
brownies are worth?
They have a perfect crust
and an ooey-gooey
surprise in the middle.
Hmm.
Three tickets.
Great!
But would you like
another brownie
for just two more tickets?
That's a great deal.
I'll take it.
Thank you!
Thank you. Tell your friends.
I thought you said
just one ticket?
I saw an opportunity
and I took it.
Dang, you're good.
Plus my dad taught
me all about upselling.
Oh.
What's that?
Here you go.
Thanks.
Don't forget, ♪Vanessascupcakes,
♪ bakesale, ♪bakes,
♪ bestcupcakesever, ♪delicious.
Got it.
Tag me @Vanessabakes.
Social media.
That's brilliant.
Why didn't we think
of that, Millie?
I didn't know you could do that.
Where's your phone?
I left it at home.
Where's yours?
Mine's still broken.
Oh, Millie, you have a customer.
Oh, why, hello there.
Hello.
Would you like a cookie?
Duh. How much is it?
How much do you think
this cookie is worth?
It is baked to perfection
and has ooey-gooey chocolate
chips in the middle.
Um, a ticket?
Um, how about three tickets?
That's too much.
I said one ticket.
Two tickets?
How about I take
my ticket elsewhere?
For an extra ticket you
could add chocolate on top.
Okay, okay, okay.
One ticket it is.
Now that's more like it.
Thank you very much.
Come again.
Whew, what a tough customer.
You handled that well.
Thanks.
We would like more
brownies, please.
Great seeing you again.
Can you give us
a group discount?
Um, I normally wouldn't do that
but I'll make an exception.
Instead of three tickets
per brownie, how about two?
Okay, we can do two.
These are amazing. Thanks.
Thank you.
Pleasure doing
business with you.
Likewise.
Okay, kids, bake sale is over.
Bakers, please bring
your pencil boxes
over to Ms. Melanie's
station right over here.
Oh my God, this pie is so good.
Mm-hmm.
Who do you think is gonna win?
Whoever made this pie.
Ms. Henderson!
Ms. Henderson.
Hi, hi.
Hi, did you get my text?
No, I didn't get anything.
Really? Oh.
I sent it at 11:00
o'clock last night.
Oh, well I was
probably sleeping.
Stuart did not understand
the math homework last night.
Mom!
Okay, well yes we
went over it today.
Okay, well just so you know.
Come on, dear.
You need to change your number.
I have, twice.
Here you go.
All right, everyone,
we are ready to
announce the winners
of today's bake sale.
In fourth place we have
Jody selling 40 tickets.
Fourth?
Congrats, Jody.
Happy you made the cut.
My dad is not gonna
be happy about this.
In third place we
have Millie Thompson
selling 47 tickets.
Good job, Millie.
Way to go.
Yes.
In second place
we have Brie Hayes
selling 52 tickets.
Second place?
52 is a lot.
Good job, Brie.
And in first place we have-
Don't say Vanessa,
don't say Vanessa.
Vanessa Weiler
selling 53 tickets!
Yes!
Wow, what a close race.
We should get a recount.
What?
What did you just say?
Oh, me?
Um, nothing.
You're gonna regret that.
All right, today's bake sale
helped raise $936
for the school.
That's great.
You four will compete
in our annual Spring
Bake Off Challenge
for a chance to win four tickets
to Cosmo Land and $5,000.
All right, guys,
let's clean it up.
Why did I have to
say that, Millie?
Good question.
I just wanted to
win first place.
I mean, you got second.
That's still pretty good.
Not when Vanessa wins first.
The important thing
is that we made final four.
That was our goal.
That means I'm
only second as good.
No, that just means Vanessa
had a better marketing strategy.
My grandma would not be proud.
That's a terrible thing to say.
I'm sure she was
the sweetest lady.
She was actually kinda mean.
They all are.
I'm so sorry, girls.
Dad, it's 4:37!
I know.
I got distracted
with a phone call.
How'd the bake sale go?
We got in!
Yes!
I told you girls.
Why the face, Brie?
I got second.
That's great, sweetie.
Millie, did you get first then?
She got third.
Vanessa got first.
Vanessa Weiler?
Yes, Dad.
What other Vanessa is there?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Drop the tude, Brie.
You should be happy
you're in the Bake Off.
All right?
Come on.
Let's get you guys home.
Did your dad
really just say tude?
Yeah.
Hurry up, ladies.
Brie, wake up.
You got drool on
your face, toots.
Millie, don't call her that.
Brie, finish your homework.
How can you concentrate?
It's so boring.
I don't know.
I guess I just really
like the story.
Sweetie, you
have got to cheer up.
That's easy for you to say.
You're a grown-up.
Well if you focus
on your homework,
maybe you'll forget
about what happened.
Oh, can we make chocolate cake?
I said focus on homework.
Actually, can we, Dad?
You wanna bake more?
Yeah, like you say in your book,
I need to vent out my feelings.
Nice.
Okay, if it'll
make you feel better.
Just make sure you
finish your homework.
Thanks, Dad,
Thanks, Mr. H.
Call me if you need anything.
I'll mix the dry ingredients,
you mix the wet.
On it.
Mm, cocoa powder smells so good.
Here's the wet
ingredients for your mix.
I'll butter the pan.
Holy pretzel sticks, Peter!
You made us drop the mix!
It's all over the floor!
Dad!
Are you okay?
What's going on?
What did you guys do?
Us?
Peter scared us and
made us drop the mix.
Our cake is ruined.
Peter Ivan Hayes, get down here!
So much for baking a cake.
Peter, help your
sister clean this up.
Why did you do that?
I thought it would be funny.
Well, not today.
You get 30 minutes of time out.
30?
Mm-hmm.
It should be an hour.
Or three.
Hundred.
I'm watching you.
After you girls clean this up
you can bake another one
while your brother is
upstairs, all right?
I don't know why we're helping
to clean this up, but okay.
Here's my phone.
Do you think if
you had your phone today
you would've won the bake sale?
Millie, I don't wanna
think about that right meow.
Sorry.
Oh my goodness, this question
doesn't make any sense.
Yes!
I wanna go check the cake!
No, Peter! You stay.
We don't want you messing up
our chocolate masterpiece.
Stay, Peter.
Stay.
Ah-ah! Sit!
Good boy.
Hey, Dad.
The cakes are ready.
Mm-hmm. Okay.
Bye.
All ready.
Oh my goodness,
they look so good.
That looks good, girls.
It rose perfectly.
Hello!
Jamie, kids!
Can someone help me with
the groceries, please?
I'll be right there.
Oh!
Hi, sweetie.
Hi, honey.
Mommy!
Hello, Peter!
Let me help you with this.
Thank you.
Oh, I see you baked again.
Yeah, but Peter scared
us and made us drop it.
So we made it again.
Now, Peter, if you're
gonna scare someone,
at least make sure they're not
holding something important.
Got it.
Okay, good.
Marcy.
What?
I mean, Peter, don't
you ever do anything
like that again, okay?
Okay.
Now go get the groceries.
Come on, buddy.
So, I'm assuming you sold
all your brownies today?
No.
No?
What do you mean no?
I got second place.
Second?
Oh.
Well, at least
you got in, right?
Yeah, but Vanessa got first.
Oh.
Vanessa Weiler?
Yeah.
Well what did she make?
Cupcakes.
She used social media tactics
to market her cupcakes.
Oh, wow.
Well why didn't you do that?
I left my phone at home.
And mine's still broken.
Well did she say anything
to you afterward?
Uh, no.
Oh, you got donuts.
Yes, they were on sale.
Where do these go?
In that cabinet right there.
So what place did
you get, Millie?
Third.
Oh, the winners get more
than just Cosmo Land tickets
if they win this year.
Oh yeah, what's that?
$5,000.
$5,000?
Jamie, did you hear that?
Yeah, I heard.
Brie, how come you
didn't tell me sooner?
She was too bust moping.
I was not!
Uh-hmm. Was too.
Well you two will have a fun
opportunity to bake together.
Who ate a donut?
Peter!
How many times do
I have to tell you
not before dinner?
That boy never listens.
Tell me about it.
Dad?
Hmm?
I have some great news.
I got first place
in the bake sale today.
I helped to raise
a bunch of money
and I get to compete
in the Spring Bake Off
Challenge for $5,000.
That's great, sweetie.
Yeah.
The Bake Off is in like a month.
So I have to practice some more.
Who took you home today?
Maxine's mom.
Oh, good.
Did you finish your homework?
Yeah.
Perfect.
Are you serious?
There was nothing else, huh?
Go!
Stay close.
That chocolate
cake tastes so good.
Mm-hmm.
I'm surprised you had room
after having
seconds and a donut.
I couldn't help myself.
Shh, guys!
I'm trying to listen.
Eight years old
from Harrisburg, Pennsylvania
with an IQ of 250
which is way higher
than most Americans.
I can't believe how
much these kids are.
Me neither.
Millie, that is your mom.
Why don't you get your stuff?
You don't have to get up, honey.
I'll get it.
Oh.
Thank you, sweetheart.
You're welcome.
Peace out.
Thanks for dinner, Mrs. H.
You're welcome.
Have a nice night, Millie.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Hey!
Hi, Barb.
Thanks for keeping
Millie so late.
Of course.
I got caught up at the hospital.
It's not a problem.
They finished all their homework
and they baked
another cake today.
Another cake?
Mm-hmm.
Okay. Thank you.
What's up, Mamma?
Congratulations, little star.
Thanks, Mamma.
I'm so proud of you
for getting in.
Hey, did you hear
about the sponsorship?
Yeah, Marcy told
me on the phone.
Yeah, $5,000.
I know.
Well, that is exciting.
Well, we'll let you go.
Of course.
Thanks again.
You're welcome.
Thanks, Mr. H.
All right.
Have a good night.
Take care.
And remember, kids,
be smart and keep on studying.
This is your hostess
with the mostest.
My name is Leonard Moe.
All right, you two.
It's time for bed.
And I will see you
next time.
Okay.
All right, go brush your teeth.
I'll be up in a minute.
Okay.
I'll do the dishes, honey.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
You're being
unusually sweet today.
What's wrong?
I haven't got my
advance yet from Grant.
What?
I know.
I've been on the phone
with him all day.
He said it's gonna be
another couple of months.
Another couple months?
Doesn't he know we have
a family to support?
I told him.
We're barley making
ends meet on my salary.
I know.
I feel terrible.
Maybe I should just go
back to a full time.
It's more secure.
No.
Don't do that.
We'll dip into our savings
and just put it back
when you get it.
I'm sorry, honey.
I waited to tell you
without the kids.
No, I'm glad you waited.
I just feel bad.
You're the only one
bringing home the bacon.
Like both food and money.
Honey, it's fine.
We've been in worse places.
I do wanna give Grant
a piece of my mind though.
I know. It's so frustrating.
She leaves
this thing everywhere.
I just hope my book sells well.
It will.
It'll be all right, honey.
Thank you, baby.
Vanessa hasn't
said anything to me today.
What?
Oh, I almost forgot she
heard you wanting a recount.
I think she forgot.
I mean, she got first place.
Yeah, maybe she'll forget
all about it just like I did.
Exactly. We good.
Dip and dodge.
Here we go, come on.
Bop and weave.
All right, here we go, guys.
Dip and dodge. Dip and dodge.
This doesn't look
very good, Brie.
I know, just keep dodging.
Burn some calories.
Yep.
You call that a throw?
Use your tricep.
Get your shoulders into it.
Come on.
Mr. Lester said no head shots.
Oops.
Mr. Lester!
You can do it,
Brie. Grab a ball.
Brie, what are you...
Don't hide behind
other kids, no.
Use your instincts, come on.
I'm sorry, Mr. Winters,
but you signed the contract.
The Montgomery Ballroom was
never available on the 26th.
Yes.
As I told you before,
another event has booked it.
The other option is
the Hartford Ballroom.
It's similar in size
but at the opposite
end of the hotel.
I understand that, sir, but...
No.
Yes.
All right.
Have a good day.
Brie, you heard what
the doctor said.
It's just a small fracture.
Mom, the Bake Off is next month.
How am I supposed to practice?
Brie, you are a wonderful baker.
You have great instincts.
Instinct is what got me here.
What are you talking about?
Mr. Lester told me to use
my instincts in gym class
and what do I do?
I hide behind Jeremy
thinking I would be safe.
And what happened?
I get squashed.
I should've just taken a
dodge ball to the face.
To the face?
Why would you take a
dodge ball to the face?
Um, that was just an expression.
What did you mean by that?
I...
Well...
Brie Alexandra Hayes,
why would you take a
dodge ball to the face?
Vanessa was kind of attacking
me and Millie with her friends.
What?
Brie, why didn't you tell me?
I can't believe this
is happening again.
I should call the principle.
No.
I'm sure she didn't
mean to hit Jeremy
and have him fall on me
and then break my arm.
It just happened.
Brie, it is not okay
that she keeps targeting you.
It's also not okay
for you to stick up for her.
Now I know you used to be
best friends in Kindergarten
before, well, you know.
But this is just ridiculous.
I should call her father.
Mom, please stop!
I'm handling it.
Not if you come home with
a broken arm, you aren't.
I can't believe
you never told me
that Vanessa was there.
Oh.
Is that why Millie had a
bruise on her forehead?
Yep.
Dodge ball right to the face.
It was not pretty.
But that's why I didn't tell you
because I knew you would
make a big deal out of it.
Because it is a big deal.
Now, Brie, as your mother,
you are my responsibility
and right now you're
not safe in school.
I've just gotta win
the Bake Off, Mom.
Then I can prove to her
that she's not better than me.
Please don't call her
dad or the principal
or anyone else.
It's embarrassing
and it's just gonna
make things worse.
You really don't
want me to do anything?
Just help me win
the Bake Off, please.
All right.
If that's what you want.
But, Brie, if Vanessa
threatens you,
if she makes fun of you
or so far as puts
a finger on you,
you better tell me.
You got that?
Yes, Mom.
Okay, good.
Thanks, Mom.
You're welcome.
I am gonna push you really
hard to win this thing.
Good.
This weekend,
it's on.
Can't wait.
Ready, and mix!
Come on, guys!
Faster!
You call that mixing?
Let's see those spoons move!
30 seconds left.
Ready,
set,
go.
Yes!
16 seconds.
49 seconds.
Fudge Popsicle sticks!
Come on, ladies.
Push yourselves.
Hustle, hustle.
You can do it, let's go!
Why are we doing abs, Mrs. H?
Don't question me, young lady.
Yes, ma'am.
Brie, why are we doing abs?
I don't know.
All right, ladies.
That's enough for today.
Tomorrow we practice
taking cakes
out of the oven without a timer.
We're doing more tomorrow?
I'm exhausted.
Yes.
You know I have
to work all week.
Ladies, we are three weeks away.
It's time to hustle.
I'm gonna hustle my way to
the living room so I can relax.
Come on, Millie.
You're welcome.
Thanks, Mom.
Thanks, Mrs. H.
Your mom's hardcore.
Yeah, she's crazy.
You did really good today.
Not really.
I'm still slow at everything.
You just need to strengthen
your good arm a little more.
That's all.
I don't think I should
be in the Bake Off anymore.
Don't say that, Brie.
Millie, my arm is broken,
I'm super slow, and you're
doing better than me.
You should just win it
and take me to
Cosmo Land with you.
Doesn't your cast come off soon?
Yeah.
Maybe I should go.
I'm sorry.
I'm just not in a
chipper mood right now.
Okay.
Can I borrow your phone?
I'll call my mom.
Yeah.
Hi, Mom. Can you
pick me up meow?
We're done practicing.
Yeah, we're done practicing.
Okay.
Okay, Mom.
Love you. Bye.
Bye.
Okay, bye.
She'll be here in 15.
So, what did you end up
painting for art class?
What are you talking about?
We have final
paintings due on Monday.
What?
Yeah.
Remember he said it when...
You know what?
You had your doctor's
appointment that day.
Millie, why didn't
you remind me?
I thought I told you.
Remember on Friday Mr.
Claymore was all like,
"Don't forget finals
are due on Monday."
You were there.
I don't remember that.
You know what?
You went to the bathroom.
Completely missed it.
What are the chances of that?
How am I supposed
to make a painting
with a broken arm?
You've been doing okay
with your other arm.
How am I supposed to
make a painting in one day?
I got it.
Just make it abstract.
You'll totally get an A.
Once I went to an art museum
and saw a painting
of a line in a square
worth millions.
I still don't get it.
I was with you that day.
Oh, yeah. Wasn't it fun?
Who are you?
I was trying to draw bushes
and then I gave up.
So I drew some random stripes.
It looks like Teletubbies.
I think this is
supposed to be grape juice.
Lemons, orange juice,
and strawberries.
Wow.
I see some very great
pieces of artwork
in front of me today.
Vanessa, why don't you go first?
I don't have mine
today, Mr. Claymore.
What happened?
I, uh, left it at home.
Okay.
Well, that'll be minus
five points for tardiness.
Brie, how about you next?
Come on, don't be shy.
Um, so I did something
a little different.
When I thought about my happy
place I thought of the park.
So...
Oh my.
Brie!
I'm sorry.
No!
You really went out of your
way to express yourself here.
Yeah, I did.
Which arm did you use?
Well, I started out
with my broken arm
but that didn't go so well.
So mainly my left arm.
Very good.
I can really sense the struggle
within yourself
in this painting.
Excellent work.
A round of applause for Brie.
Campbell, you're next.
Okay, has everyone had
a chance to present?
There's the bell.
Okay, excellent work
today, everyone.
Vanessa, can I see
you for a moment?
I got it.
You sure?
Mm-hmm, yeah.
I'll see you in the cafeteria.
Okay.
Hey.
What do you want?
My mom almost
called your dad today.
Figures.
He wouldn't have
answered anyway.
Well, I just wanted to say-
I gotta go.
I got the baked
potato and sides today.
No more frozen pizza for me.
Yeah, that was pretty gross.
Yeah.
Did you talk to Vanessa?
No, she just stormed off.
Typical.
At least you tried.
Yeah.
Are you gonna tell your mom?
No.
Ugh!
What?
It's as hard as a rock.
Dude.
You have got to start
packing your own lunches.
I know but my mom never
has time in the morning.
Can't you pack your own?
Oh.
I guess that's a
better solution.
So are you gonna
get another potato?
No, I'll just eat the sides.
Here you go.
Oh, thanks.
So do you know what recipe
you're gonna use
for the Bake Off?
I have no idea.
Yeah, I think a few online.
Ooh, what is it?
I don't know if
I should tell you.
I'm not gonna copy you.
Oh yeah, I know.
I just don't think we
should tell each other.
But we're BFF's and we
tell each other everything.
Yeah, but we're kinda competing
against each other, so.
I was gonna tell you mine
once I figured it out.
I don't wanna know yours.
Brie, do you even
think you telling me
is gonna change anything?
I mean, it could.
You could change yours
after I tell you mine.
Wow.
You know what?
You're right.
We shouldn't talk about the
recipes or the Bake Off.
Or at all.
Millie!
Millie, I didn't mean to...
Do you know where
the donuts are?
You ate them all, remember?
Dang it.
I thought I had one more left.
What you baking now?
A lavender vanilla cake.
Are you gonna make
me spill it again?
No, not today.
What's lavender? No chocolate?
No, and it's a flower thingy.
Oh.
Can you put chocolate on it?
I can but I won't.
Why not?
Because the recipe
doesn't call for it!
Okay, sheesh.
What's up with you today?
Nothing!
Now go away.
Bye. Leave, go.
Hey, sweet pea.
Hey, Dad.
Wow, that looks good.
Thank you.
All done.
Do you wanna try some?
Uh, yeah. I'll have some.
Peter, you want some cake?
This is a new
recipe I found online.
Looks great.
Yes!
Oh, that looks so good.
Oh, wow.
Okay, for you.
Thank you.
All right, here we go, ready?
Uno, dos, three.
Hmm.
That's um-
Nasty. I don't like it.
Maybe I added too much lavender?
Yeah.
It's a little too-
Gross.
I was going to say floral.
Maybe you should
take out the lavender
and add chocolate instead.
But this recipe got
so many good reviews.
Maybe I messed it up somehow.
Why don't you ask your mom?
Oh yeah, she
has a bunch, doesn't she?
Yeah.
And she'll be picking
you up tomorrow
for your doctor's appointment.
I thought you were taking me.
Yeah, I have a call I
have to deal with now.
Okay.
Wait.
You're getting out
early tomorrow?
Yep.
I can't wait to get
rid of this thing.
Well your mom
should be home soon.
Okay.
Here, let me help
you clean this up.
Give me that
and that.
All right.
Get that outta here.
Mom?
Yeah, sweetie?
Do you have any recipes
I can use for the Bake Off?
I'm sorry. What?
Do you have
any recipes I can use
to practice with
for the Bake Off?
Oh yeah, of course.
I completely forgot about those.
I'm trying to think
where I put them though.
Is everything okay with work?
Yes.
I'm just finishing up
a couple last
minute things here.
They should be in the kitchen.
Let's go.
Let's see.
Oh, here they are.
Whoa, these
recipes are in cursive.
Yeah, old school handwriting.
I don't know how
to write in cursive.
Are you serious?
They're not teaching
you that in school?
Nope.
Well, just my name.
Wow.
Oh, here.
This one's my favorite.
Black forest gateo...
Black forest gateaux.
It has chocolate
and cherries and...
Oh, it is so good.
Thank you.
This one will definitely
impress the judges.
Thanks, Mom.
Can we practice this tomorrow?
Yeah, sure.
That'll be perfect.
You wanna invite Millie
along to practice too?
Um, we're not really
talking right now.
Sweetie, why?
Because I wouldn't tell her
what I was making
for the Bake Off.
Well that seems unfair of her
and for the rest of the
kids in the Bake Off.
That's what I was thinking.
Well did you tell her that?
No, she just stormed off.
Well, I'm sure she'll understand
as soon as you talk to her.
Yeah.
This recipe looks
really hard, Mom.
I know you can do it.
I hope so.
Well, let's leave these here.
It's getting late.
And let's get ready for bed.
Okay. Thanks, Mamma.
Oh, you're welcome.
9:37?
Dad!
Mom!
Why didn't you wake me?
I'm gonna be late for school!
Sweetie, everything is fine.
You don't have school today.
What? How come?
Well, there was a fire
in your school last night.
A fire?
What happened?
Did anyone get hurt?
Thankfully nobody got hurt.
But apparently the ovens
never fully shut off like
they were supposed to
and, well, exploded
in the kitchen.
Exploded?
Luckily the kitchen
has metal doors
so the fire was
somewhat contained.
I read the rest of
the cafeteria is fine.
What? Oh my gosh.
Dad, is there still
gonna be a Bake Off?
Sweetie, everything
will be fine.
They're probably figuring
that out right now.
What are we gonna do?
Why aren't we in
the faculty lounge?
Because the aura in
here is much better
than in that hole.
Okay.
It does smell
really good in here.
Thank you, Lester.
That's my calm mind and
confidence boost essential oils.
You know it's really good
for muscle tension too.
You know, I've heard of those
but I'm not sure I
could find a diffuser
big enough for the entire gym.
I could help you
look for one in stores.
That store Big Buys
might have something.
Oh, don't be silly, Lester.
You can borrow my
essential oils.
That way you can try them out.
Okay, thanks, guys.
Mm-hmm!
All right, everyone.
Let's try and focus here.
Ms. Henderson, what did the
fireman say the damage was?
He said an estimated $20,000.
What?
Oh my Lanta.
Ms. Silvera, did you
see how much contingency
we have in our budget?
Yes, we ran out of
contingency two months ago.
How is that possible?
The bathroom
leak on the third floor
really took a hit to
our budget this year.
Well, what about DCBX?
They're the ones sponsoring
the Bake Off prize money.
Why not ask them for
help with the kitchen?
Well, I'm afraid
even if they did help,
the kitchen would not be
done before next week.
The parents are gonna have a fit
if we don't have this Bake Off.
Well, I know.
I'm not...
No.
What if we have
it in the summer?
Oh wait, I got it!
Why don't we just do a no
bake Bake Off Challenge.
Hmm.
Bake, no bake Bake Off.
I guess that could work.
I mean, it can.
I make no bake
bakes all the time.
What?
You bake too?
Yeah, on my days
off with my nieces.
Wow.
That's the sweetest
thing I've ever heard.
Lester, I think you just saved
the Bake Off Challenge.
I think I'm in love
with this new plan.
Yeah, me too.
What do we do next?
Well, we'll announce it
first thing tomorrow morning.
In the meantime,
let's figure out what
changes we have to make.
All right.
Oh, you're getting some paper.
Oh, Lester, you
didn't come prepared.
There you go.
Thank you.
Hey!
You got your cast off.
Yeah.
Where do you think you're going?
To class.
Your arm looks so much better.
Yeah.
Can't wait to play
dodge ball with you again.
Maybe we'll get your other arm.
Hey! Come on, let's go.
I'm so mad about the fire.
All right, everyone.
Settle down, settle down.
I have some news this
morning to pass onto you.
As you all know, we
had a bit of a fire
in the cafeteria kitchen
a couple of nights ago.
Luckily, the damage
was contained.
However, our ovens
for the Bake Off
are completely destroyed.
So, who are my
contestants, please?
Raise your hands.
You four will now compete
in a No Bake Bake Off Challenge.
Like last year, the first two
challenges will be a surprise
and you'll have 15
minutes to complete it.
As for the third
and final challenge,
unlike last year,
instead of you baking a cake
for the ultimate showdown,
you will now be making
an Ultimate Spring No Bake
Cheesecake, all right?
Don't forget next Friday we
will have early dismissal.
Now any students who are not
participating in the Bake Off
please be sure to be there
to cheer your peers on.
Does anybody have any questions?
Oh, Vanessa.
We're still having it
in the cafeteria, right?
Yes.
And in the meantime,
we'll be having our lunches
here in the classroom.
Okay.
All right, now if everyone
will open their book
to page 133, we'll read the poem
"A Chance I Have"
by Kate Miller.
All right, go ahead.
Yes, Ms. Melanie.
"A Chance I Have"
by Kate Miller.
Chances come and go.
Some we take, some we miss.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to
make you mad at me.
No, I'm sorry.
I was being a ding-dong.
Well now I really
don't know what to do.
A No Bake Bake Off?
I know, right?
Well, don't tell me.
I don't wanna know.
And the chance
I have each and every day.
A chance I often miss
and a chance I often run from.
Brie, next verse.
And the chance I have
is the chance I have
that makes life worth
taking another breath.
Millie, next verse.
Get some rest, sweet pea.
You're gonna do
great tomorrow, honey.
We got all the ingredients
for the cheesecake, right, Mom?
Yes, I checked five times.
Okay.
How's your arm doing?
It's a little stiff
but it's so, so much better.
Well no matter what
happens tomorrow,
we're proud of you.
Thanks, Dad. Goodnight.
Goodnight, baby.
Goodnight, sweetie.
Goodnight, Mamma.
Dad! You're home so late.
I know.
Crazy day today.
I still need
to go to the grocery store.
We'll go tomorrow.
Dad, I can't tomorrow.
Hello? The Bake Off.
That's tomorrow?
Yeah, I told you like 100 times.
Hey, don't take that
tone with me, young lady.
Did you forget?
No.
Can we please just go now?
All right.
Let's go.
Wow.
There are a lot of people here.
Oh hey, there's Barb.
Hey, Barb, come here.
We saved you a seat.
Okay, great.
I don't believe we've met.
I'm Jamie.
Hi, I'm Don Fisher.
Nice to meet you.
Samantha.
How are you doing, Samantha?
Who are you all
rooting for today?
Oh, we're rooting for Jody.
He's the only boy in
the contest this year.
Oh, nice, nice.
Jody?
Isn't that a girl's name?
Jody is short for Joseph.
Kinda like Jamie.
Right, right.
Marcy, meet Jody's parents.
Oh, hi. Marcy Hayes.
Hi, Samantha.
Our daughter is Brie.
That's wonderful.
Jody has been
practicing nonstop.
Right, right.
Have you seen Eugene?
Who?
Vanessa's dad.
Oh, oh.
No.
Are you gonna say
something to him?
No.
But he should be here.
All the other parents are.
I know.
Hello, Ms. Melanie.
Oh, hello, Daniel.
How are you? So good to see you.
I see you brought the big prize.
Yes, of course.
This must be your wife, Betty.
Hi, so nice to meet you.
Thank you for having us.
The pleasure's all mine.
Your seats are
reserved in the front.
Thank you.
Hello, everyone.
We will now get started.
The winner of the Spring
No Bake Bake Off Challenge
will receive four
tickets to Cosmo Land
and $5,000
thanks to the wonderful
Daniel and Betty Kauffman
over at DCBX.
I will now introduce the bakers.
First up we have Jody Fisher.
Look at that face.
Beautiful.
Next we have Brie Hayes.
Brie, Brie, Brie, Brie,
Brie, Brie, Brie!
Millie Thompson.
That's my baby!
Woo!
Hi, Mom.
And lastly, Vanessa Weiler.
All right, I will now
move on to the judges.
First up we have Mr. Claymore.
Ms. Silvera.
And Ms. Henderson.
They will be judging
the contestants
on presentation, creativity,
and of course taste.
All right, the game plan.
Just take care of her, okay?
There will be three No
Bake, Bake Off Challenges.
For the first two rounds
the bakers will have 15 minutes
to complete the challenge.
For the third and final round,
they will have 45 minutes.
I, Lester, will be
tracking the time.
Once I say time, bakers,
hands off your bakes.
Got that?
Let the challenge begin!
Get the table.
Okay.
Contestants, please step forward
with your baskets.
Your first challenge
is the No Bake Rice
Crispy Treat Spectacular.
Now you may only use these
ingredients here at the table.
Lester, the time.
Ready, set,
bake!
Yeah, Brie!
You got this, Jody.
This is so exciting.
Where is he?
Five minutes left, bakers.
20 seconds left.
Remember, presentation
is important.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
And that's time.
Hands off your bakes.
That was crazy.
I can't wait to see
what happens here.
You know, we should really
get two of these next time.
I agree.
Contestants, please step
forward with your bakes
to the judging table.
I'm just gonna write yaas.
Millie did great
with the sprinkles,
and the jelly beans are a
nice touch too over here.
I wonder how they're gonna-
I don't know.
It's really intense.
Oh my goodness.
What a wonderful
suspenseful first round.
We will now take
a 15 minute break
to set up for the next round.
Thank you.
Hi, Jody.
Hello.
That looked amazing.
It really did.
It was like incredible.
Where did you learn
to bake that good?
My dad's a baker.
Wow.
That's so cool.
Thanks.
The way you stirred
the batter with your
wrist was perfect.
The technique is on point.
It was.
Thank you.
You did great, Millie bear.
So proud of you!
Thanks, Mamma.
You did so great, honey.
Thanks, Mom.
That was intense.
Yeah.
Can I have some of
the stuff you made?
Um, I'm pretty sure they're
cleaning up right now.
Dang it.
Sorry.
You gotta wait
your turn, mister.
Um, I'll be right back.
Okay.
Vanessa, are you okay?
Go away, Brie.
I'm sorry your dad isn't here.
I just wanted to tell you
that if you ever need anything
you can count on me,
even if you make my life
miserable sometimes.
Brie, I don't wanna talk to you.
Now go away!
You know what?
Maybe if you weren't such
a brat all of the time,
your friends would be in
here trying to help you.
Instead, they're out
there talking to Jody.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm just trying to help.
I don't need your help.
Now go away or I'll-
You'll what?
Call me names, embarrass
me in front of everyone,
break my arm?
Oh wait, you've already
done all those things.
I don't even know why
I try with you anymore.
We will now start
the second challenge.
One of my favorite
desserts growing up,
this is my Auntie May's
marvelous no bake banana pudding.
You will have exactly 15 minutes
to complete this challenge.
Lester, are you ready?
I was born for this.
Yeah, you were.
Ready, set,
bake!
Oh my gosh.
There's a lot of
mixing in this one.
Focus, Brie. 15 minutes.
Come on, Brie, hustle.
Let's go, Jody.
Mix it all together.
This is a tough one.
I know. I am so nervous.
How much time is left?
Three minutes,
bakers. Three minutes.
Oh no.
Brie, Vanessa just left.
Whatever.
I hope she's okay.
And that's five,
four, three, two, one.
Time! Hands up, bakers.
It's getting hot in here, wow.
Bakers, please bring
your banana puddings
up to the judging table.
Yeah, I think that
one looks the best.
I mean, that one's missing
cookies altogether.
Oh yeah, that's Vanessa.
We're still gonna have
to deduct the points.
I think she tried.
Yeah, but I'm
still gonna have to
give her zero points
for presentation.
Mm-mm.
Yes, Jody!
Oh my god.
That is the best
pudding I've ever had.
But we can't show them.
Why am I not floating up
in an angel cloud right now?
This is amazing.
This is so good.
It is so good.
Mm.
Okay.
Yep.
You guys ready?
How's your arm feeling?
It hurts a bit.
I can't believe she
just walked out.
Yeah, her dad isn't here.
I know.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Where are your parents?
I don't know where my dad is.
What about your mom?
I don't have one anymore.
Oh my gosh, I am so sorry.
I had no idea.
It's fine.
Vanessa.
Dad!
I'm so sorry, Vanessa.
I tried leaving early
but my boss wouldn't let me go.
You missed like
almost all of it.
I know.
But I'm here now.
Please don't be mad.
I thought you weren't
gonna come at all.
You're the worst dad ever.
I can't tell you
how hard it's been
not having your mom around.
I can't do everything myself.
You're never home
and you never care
about anything I do.
I hate you.
Please understand, Vanessa.
I'm so sorry.
I just wanna go home.
I already messed up
in the second round.
Sweetie, if your mother
were here right now,
she'd be so proud of you.
I want to go home.
Come on, Vanessa.
You still have a chance.
But I already messed up.
So what?
This last challenge is
what matters most anyway.
All right,
children. It's time.
Mr. Weiler.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Yes, apologies.
Well, please have a seat.
We're about to start.
Come on.
Thanks, Jody.
Don't mention it.
Bakers, this is your
third and final challenge.
You have your
ingredients with you
that you brought from home.
You will have 45
minutes to create
the Ultimate Spring
No Bake Cheesecake.
Okay, ready?
Okay.
Ready, set,
bake!
Go Vanessa!
You got this, Jody!
Go, Brie!
Go, Millie!
You got this, Jody.
Yes, Jody!
Push through, Brie.
I'm trying.
Yeah, she just broke her arm.
Oh.
♪ Oh ♪
Oh my sweet jellybeans.
Oh my gosh.
This would be so much easier
with an electric mixer.
Brie, if you need to stop, stop.
It's okay.
Don't hurt yourself.
I'm fine.
How much time is left?
Oh, right.
20 minutes left, bakers.
Sugar!
You okay, Millie?
Yeah, I dropped my blueberries.
Luckily I have more.
Go, Millie bear!
Three minutes,
bakers. Three minutes.
Look at Jody.
I mean, he is just like so
good at what he's doing.
One minute left, bakers.
I know!
Woo-hoo!
You're almost there.
Go, Millie bear, go!
Five, four, three, two, one.
Time! Hands up, bakers.
Good job, Brie.
That's pretty close, guys.
Woo!
They all look
really, really good.
Bakers, you will
now individually
present your final bakes.
Jody, we'll start with you.
For the final challenge
I made a salted caramel
no bake cheesecake
with graham cracker crust
and a cream cheese filling.
Thank you, Jody.
You may now go back
to your station.
Next, Brie.
I made a milk chocolate
no bake cheesecake
with crushed Oreo crust,
chocolate cream cheese filling,
and caramel swirls with
whipped cream on top.
Mm, chocolate!
Thank you, Brie.
You may go back to your station.
Next, Millie.
Hola.
Today I made a vanilla
no bake cheesecake
with vanilla lemon
cream cheese filling,
topped with fresh
strawberries and blueberries.
Thank you, Millie.
And, lastly, Vanessa.
Today I made a strawberry
no bake cheesecake
with a graham cracker crust
filled with a fresh
strawberry filling.
Thank you, Vanessa.
Please go back to your station.
I mean, come on, it's a cat.
Who doesn't love a cat cake?
That was very cute, right?
Was that just whipped cream?
That was a little lazy.
I think I'm good.
All right.
Oh my god.
Is it Oreo?
Oreo is my favorite.
Seriously good.
Eat that.
I'm going to.
Oh my god.
They put caramel
on this one too.
She did this, didn't she?
Like OMG, right?
That is the best
dang cheesecake I've ever had.
Pass me the cake.
I mean the cat.
Pass me the cat.
Mmmm-mm.
Hold on, I need another
bite of this one.
It's not half bad.
It's kinda good.
Does it look better
than it tastes though?
Probably, yeah.
You gotta be careful for that.
Is this the one she screwed up?
I don't know.
It just looks like a cat.
Hey, at least there's
some cheesecake.
There's no sugar.
I actually like that.
It's not as rich.
Exactly.
This is like a diabetic cake.
Like this is what
my grandma eats.
This one's very fruity.
It's good, it's good.
This is Vanessa's.
I think I'm good guys.
I've got mine up.
I just need to try
this one more time
because it's plain.
I need to cleanse my palette.
You go ahead.
Come on, Brie.
Are we ready?
The winner of this
year's Spring No Bake,
Bake Off Challenge
and the winner of four
Cosmo Land tickets
and $5,000 is
Brie Hayes!
No way!
Yes! Congratulations!
Are you serious?
She doesn't even believe it.
Go Brie!
Go, Brie!
Go, baby! Go, baby!
I knew it!
I told you, I told you!
Let's go, let's go.
Hey!
I am so proud of you.
That's our girl.
I'm pretty sure you can go get
some chocolate cheesecake now.
Yes!
How's your arm feeling?
It's good.
That's good.
It doesn't hurt very much.
Yeah?
I am so proud of you.
I knew you could do it.
It was all those trials, Brie.
I told you they were gonna work.
You did so good.
You did so good,
I'm so proud of you.
My heart was beating
way above average.
What a great Bake Off.
It was, it was.
But how did I do?
Oh, you did a
fantastic job announcing.
Why, thank you.
You did a great job judging.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, honey!
I'm so proud of you.
Thank you, love.
Andrew, this is my wife, Sophia.
Hi.
Of course it is.
Oh, wait, Andrew.
You gave Lester the
essential oils, right?
I absolutely love them.
Yes, yes I did.
Great meeting you.
Yeah, you too.
Excuse me.
It's okay.
You're a strong independent man.
Yes.
Now I just need something
to fill my heart.
Cheesecake.
And a glass of wine.
Excuse me, guys.
Hey, Sophia.
Hey.
It's so nice to see you again.
Oh, nice to see you too.
How are you?
How's everything?
It's good. How's the business?
Oh, it's
fantastic. It's great.
Good, you
did such a good job today.
I forgot you
two know each other.
Thank you.
You did great, Millie bear.
Thanks, Mom.
I'm so proud of you.
How should we celebrate?
Hmm. Cheesecake.
Okay! Let's do it.
Son, we practiced
this 100 times.
You must've measured the
vanilla extract wrong.
Sorry, Dad.
Hon, don't be so hard on him.
He did great.
You did great, Jody.
Thanks, Mom.
You did great.
Mom would've been
so proud of you.
Your cheesecake looks amazing.
Thanks, Dad.
Mm, smells like chocolate.
Thank you.
Whoever
made this did a real good job.
Which one?
That one.
Can I sit with you?
No, but you
probably will anyway.
I'm sorry for everything
I did to you, Brie.
You think a sorry
will unbreak my arm?
No.
I never meant that to happen.
You never even said
sorry when it did happen.
Because I didn't
think you wanted to talk to me.
Well, I just wanted to tell you
that I never meant
to not be there
when your mom died.
Yeah, I know.
Do you really?
Yeah.
I was just mean to you
when we were younger
so you wouldn't
come over anymore.
Why?
Because my mom
loved having you over
and you got all the attention
when you were there.
So I started being mean to you
so that we wouldn't be friends
and then, well, you know.
Well, I'm sorry
for everything too.
I know.
Vanessa, can I talk
to you for a sec?
Uh, yeah.
Sorry I lied to
you about my dad.
He's not really a doctor.
Oh, no.
I wanted to see
if you would like
to eat dinner with me tonight.
Really?
Yeah, I mean, my
parents would be there
but they can sit
at another table.
That's awesome.
Do you think my
dad could come too?
He needs more
company these days.
Yeah, of course.
You wanna go inside now, Brie?
I'll wait for my dad.
You guys go ahead.
Okay, see you in there.
Don't tell me any
bad news, Grant.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
You didn't?
Yes!
Thank you! Finally!
All right.
Okay, I'll call you tomorrow.
Bye.
Looks like you're
not the only one
getting a big fat check.
They tripled my advance,
more stores want my book.
What'd you say?
♪ They want my book ♪
♪ One more time ♪
♪ Want my book ♪
♪ They want my book ♪
That's amazing, Dad.
Make sure to go tell Mom.
She'll be super happy
that you don't
have to take money
out of your savings anymore.
Savings?
You know about that?
Uh, no, no.
Well, it doesn't matter
'cause we're good now!
Come on, let's go inside.
Oh, Dad.
Yes?
Is $5,000 enough
for culinary school?
Not even close.
Well then, I'm almost going!
♪ You won the Bake Off ♪
♪ She won the Bake Off ♪