(ambient music)
(gentle elegant music)
(sneakers squeaking)
(girls yelling)
(bell tolling)
(gentle elegant music continues)
(ball thumping)
(bell tolling)
(gentle elegant music continues)
- Hear oh Lord, when I cry with my voice.
Have mercy upon me and answer me.
When thou said, seek ye my
face, my heart said unto Thee,
Thy face Lord, will I seek.
The gospel of the Lord.
Let us pray.
Heavenly Father,
You sent Your own Son into this world.
We thank You for the
lives of these children
entrusted to our care,
that we are all Your children.
And so to love and nurture them
that they may attain to that full stature
intended for them in Your eternal kingdom.
For the sake of Your dear Son,
Jesus Christ, our Lord, amen.
Welcome to Saint Tammany's fall semester.
I do believe this is
the best looking group
we've ever had here.
St. Tammany, as they say is on a roll.
Enrollment has nearly doubled
in the last three years.
And as a result, we've had to
make a few slight adjustments.
Academically, St. Tammany
ranks right up there
in the top 5% of all private schools.
And in no uncertain
terms, academics will be
even more challenging yet more
rewarding than ever before.
(girls giggling)
The fifth chapter of Romans tells us
that tribulation brings
about perseverance,
perseverance proven character,
proven character hope.
Now,
because of the rigors of my schedule
I will no longer be coaching
the basketball team.
- Ah.
(audience members clapping)
- Now, now, we were two and 10 last year,
it wasn't that bad.
So I'd like to introduce
to you the new coach,
coach Lootie Pfandder
has joined our staff.
(all applauding)
Expecting big things from you,
so I expect you all to
come out to the games.
Now, there will be an orientation
for the freshmen this afternoon.
(inspirational music)
(horn honking)
(inspirational music continues)
(ball hitting net)
♪ Yada da-da ♪
♪ Lada da-da-da da-da-da ♪
♪ Ya pum-pum-pum, ya ♪
Mornin' Missy.
- Mornin', you must be Sam.
- You'd be the new coach.
- Yes.
(Lootie laughs)
Hey, where's the locker room?
- We got this one and there's
one just on the other side.
- Great.
(disheartening music)
(doors clanging)
(metal clanging)
(balls thudding)
(Lootie laughing)
(Lootie sighs)
St. Tammany on a roll, huh?
Sure didn't waste any of it
on the basketball facilities, did we?
- No, we didn't.
We blew our sports budget
on smallpox inoculations
for 3,000 yolly tribesmen.
Coach Pfandder, we're just a
small Episcopal girls' school here.
We do things a little differently.
(disheartening music)
(Lootie sighs)
(bright inspirational music)
- Hi, Laura.
- Nice to see you again.
- Welcome home.
- Thanks.
- Hi, Bridget.
(bright music)
- Fine, fine, fine.
So fine.
- Come on.
Hey, everybody.
- Man.
- This is Shalonda, our new girl.
Shalonda, meet the girls.
This is Kimberly, Donna, Bridget.
(bright music)
- Show you how to, sit.
- A new mate?
- Ah-huh.
- You six foot?
- Six, one.
- Yeah, right?
What position you play?
- Post.
- You any good?
- Pretty good.
- Pretty good?
See this is Bridget over here,
we call her the bridge.
She blew out her knee last season.
She was the best Post player we ever had.
Are you good or are you great?
- I'm good.
- Did you get a scholarship?
Or did you just have rich parents?
- I got a scholarship.
- Oh yeah?
What was your point average last season?
- About 16.
- 16, and you got a scholarship?
- This is a little
tougher than junior high.
(ball thudding)
- Hey guys, take it easy.
- Shut up, wimp.
(bright music)
- Some iced tea.
- I'm famished.
- Father Thomas, could you
bring me some more tea?
- Sure, wait there.
Stop, stop, stop.
Here you go, you're welcome.
- Thanks.
- Father Thomas,
you'd better sit down
and get something to eat.
- Yeah, come on, sit down, Father,
I'll go get you something to eat.
- No, you just go ahead and pour your tea.
Just don't worry about it.
I'm good, I'll eat as soon
as everyone is served.
- Please.
- Don't even look like you wanna be here.
What's your name again?
- Dunn, Kimberly Dunn.
- Oh, right, Kimberly Dunn.
Father Mulberry tells me
you're our star player.
You sure don't shine like a star to me.
Aren't you having any fun, Kimberly?
(Lootie sighs)
All right.
Front and center, let's go.
- Move over, wimp.
(Lootie sighs)
- All right, Ms. Dunn, close your eyes.
I said close them.
Now when you were a little
girl, I bet you could run
and jump faster than any of
the other kids, boys and girls.
And you were probably
laughing and playing, playing.
because it was just a game.
Yeah, you were a tomboy, all right
but inside you wanted
to be a tiny, petite,
dainty, little ballerina, didn't you?
Daddy's little princess.
Do you remember what it was
like to really want something?
Give her the ball.
Now close your eyes,
Kimberly and see the basket
through the eyes of that little girl
and take that shot.
(dramatic music)
(ball thudding)
Thank you very much, Ms. Dunn.
Back in line.
- Good job.
- Goofy.
- All right, who's next?
- Can I try?
- Not yet.
Shalonda, come here.
Yeah, here, let me see, let me see.
Oh, nothing, nothing.
Can I tell you secret?
I really wanted to be a ballerina.
- Me too.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Great.
Close your eyes.
Give me the ball.
You remember dancing
around your living room,
really feeling that music?
Okay, hear the music, Shalonda.
Whenever you're ready.
(gentle music box music)
(ball thuds)
(Lootie applauds)
Congratulations, that was beautiful.
- But I missed it.
- Yeah, you missed it by a mile
but you were focused and you
were committed from inside.
That's what I'm talking about, girls.
You have got to play big.
Look, you're gonna make shots
and you're gonna miss shots.
It's gonna happen anyway.
But if you play with God in your heart,
a smile on your face,
that, that inner strength.
That's what makes winners.
All right, I want you all to try this now.
One at a time.
Get back in line.
(suspenseful music)
Woo! Ah, there we go!
(Lootie applauding)
All right.
Close your eyes.
(ball thudding)
It's okay.
Attagirl, attagirl.
Woo, ah, there we go.
(Lootie applauding)
(knocking on window)
Hey, you wanna see me?
- Have a seat.
(Father Thomas sighs)
I hope you haven't already unpacked.
- What?
- You were their coach,
you know how bad they are.
What was your record last year, oh and 12?
- Two and 10.
- Look,
you hired me to coach the
way I saw fit, was I wrong?
- I didn't know you were
going to be so creative.
- You're upset with me
for being a little too unconventional.
- That would be a fair statement.
Look, coach Pfandder,
we're just a small Episcopal
girls' school here.
- And you do things a little differently.
- Right?
- What do you want me to do?
Use your playbook?
- Excellent idea.
Just until you get your feet wet
and see how we operate here.
- Zones.
- Why yes.
I'm a big believer of play
in the zone, it's simple.
It works sort of like
Christianity, wouldn't you say?
On your resume, it did say you
were a Christian, didn't it?
- Yes.
But we already use the
same playbook for that.
(melancholic music)
(Lootie sighs)
Lord, are you sure this is where I belong?
I mean, what's with the zone business?
I can't work under these conditions.
I felt like I was being led here.
So, if this is where You want me,
this is where I'll stay.
just stick it out together?
(Lootie chuckles)
(upbeat music)
♪ This is what ♪
♪ This is what you need ♪
- Victoria.
- Ah-huh?
- You have to get them Rattigan
shoes out of my locker.
They're Pfandder' up everything.
- My shoes aren't stinky.
- Your shoes stink, your feet stink,
your breath stinks.
- Oh,
let's not get started,
who's the basketball player here?
- Yeah, but my feet don't stink.
You're stinkin' up the whole locker room.
- Okay.
(Victoria chuckles)
(phone ringing)
- Kimberly.
- I told you I recognized her.
- Recognize who?
- Coach Pfandder.
(phone ringing)
You know, Lootie?
- Yeah, Lootie.
How'd she get that name?
(Kimberly laughs)
- Kimberly, she was in All American.
- What kind of a name is Lootie?
- She was in All American.
- Yeah, right,
In All American?
- Oh, you don't believe?
- No, let me see that.
- See for yourself.
- You're such a liar.
(upbeat music)
I don't believe it.
- See, I told you.
- Stace, look at that.
- Let's see.
Man, she must've been something.
- What?
- Let me see that.
- Coach was in all American.
- Are you serious?
- I don't understand.
- Let me have that.
- I mean, why would she
come to St. Tammany?
- I don't know.
- Well,
maybe it was her best offer.
- Guys, maybe she just wanted to coach us.
- Yeah, right.
(Kimberly laughs)
I don't understand why
she wouldn't tell us this.
It's gotta be something else.
- [Kimberly And Victoria]
Jack, will there be
something else?
(girls giggling)
- Oh yeah.
Stop it.
(girls giggling)
I'm gonna find out, why'd
she hide that from us?
- I don't know, 'cause she don't like you.
- Oh, she don't like
you either, four eyes.
(girls giggling)
- Okay.
- Stop!
(all laughing)
Watch the hat, watch the hat.
(bright trumpet music)
- [Announcer] And if
you're just now joining us,
we've got St. Tammany Episcopal
in the season opening
against the Lady Tigers.
For St. Tammany, it looks
like it's going to be a long night.
And a very warm welcome
for first year coach,
Lootie Pfandder who is a
second team on American NSE.
Kimberly Dunn, we had the St. Tammany team
in scoring last season,
was Dunn all the light with
14 points and seven rebounds.
(upbeat music)
Freshman, Shalonda Win,
playing the post tonight,
has eight points.
We're not disappointed in Coach Pfandder.
(crowd cheering)
- What are you doing in there, Shalonda?
You can't go skipping,
throwing in for a rebound,
are you listening to me?
- Coach, come on.
- Come on, watch it!
(suspenseful music)
(whistle blowing)
Let's go, girls, come in here.
- Great going, Kimberly.
- Listen up, girls.
- Thanks, Sam.
- Can't we do something else?
We're getting hammered out there.
- No.
- Coach, send me in.
- Not now, Julia.
- Listen now, girls.
- Can we do something else?
Let's at least go man to man.
- We can't.
We're just gonna execute
the zone better, okay?
- Ah.
- Hey, listen up.
Anticipate the move, get
to the outside, okay?
Let's focus, girls, hands.
Ready?
- [Altogether] Team!
- Come on.
(all applauding)
(birds chipping)
(bus engine roaring)
- Why'd you come out here?
- Well, St. Tammany is my calling.
Look, I know that being
this first-year coach,
people don't expect me to win.
I don't care.
- You don't care?
- No.
- You don't.
- No, I don't.
- Coach, I gotta tell you,
my folks, they live less
than 30 minutes away
and I can't even remember
the last time I was home.
See, my good Christian step mother decided
that she was just too young and attractive
to have a young girl
running around the house.
She was afraid all the
neighbors might think
I was her daughter.
So when I got stuck here,
the only thing that's kept me
going is playing basketball.
I ain't come here to get saved.
- What makes you think the
two can't go hand in hand?
(upbeat music)
(water splashing)
(ball bouncing)
- Hi.
Actually, I thought
they looked pretty good
for the first term game.
- If you think that looks good,
I'd hate to see what you think looks bad.
(ball thudding)
Honestly, Father Mulberry-
- Call me Thomas.
- Thomas.
When are you going to turn me loose
on these girls and teach
'em some basketball?
(ball bouncing)
- Basketball?
- Yeah.
(ball bouncing)
- Basketball or something else?
Understand you took them
to an amusement park.
(ball thudding)
- So?
Look, I figured they needed
a little outside stimulation.
No offense, but St. Tammany is a little
like the bland leading the bland.
If these girls learn nothing else from me,
at least let them learn
how to have some fun.
(ball bouncing)
- I don't need a 23 year
old hot shot blowing in here
making a lot of changes.
(ball bounces)
- That's right, I forgot.
St. Tammany is a small
Episcopal girls' school
and you do things a little differently.
(ball bouncing)
Why don't you do things
really different, Thomas,
and win a basketball game.
(ball bouncing)
- Coach Pfandder-
- Lootie.
I think we should reconsider
our working relationship.
- Definitely.
I'm not so sure on what you had in mind.
- I'm not sure either.
I mean, I wouldn't wanna put you
out on the street or anything.
I mean, what would you do?
- Hey, don't worry about me.
I got a job in broadcasting standing by
in case this didn't work out.
(ball bounces)
- You do?
- Yeah, I do.
- Well,
how do you think it's working out so far?
- I don't know.
- Well, do you think you're
gonna take this other job?
- I don't know.
(ball bounces)
- I see you're just sorta
keeping your options open,
is that it?
- Got that right.
(ball bouncing)
(adventurous music)
- [Announcer] St. Tammany
Episcopal is running
on the top rows last week
in the season opener
against the Lady Tigers.
New head coach Lootie Pfandder's looking
for her first win tonight
against a tough team
who won last week against Loyal.
(adventurous music)
(crowd cheering)
St. Tammany takes its final time outs.
- Hey girls,
You are playing one good game,
I'm so proud of you and
we've tied up the score
but they are tough
and they're gonna
continue to give it to us.
But we can beat them.
I know we can.
And don't forget girls,
it's just a goofy game.
All right, girls, bow your head.
Lord, we most reverently pray
for Your continued presence.
And we thank You for allowing us
to be healthy, strong athletes.
And we pray that we will play
for Your glory alone, amen.
- Amen.
- All right, ready?
- Team!
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
(vehicle whooshing)
(engine whirring)
(gentle music)
(bell tolling)
- I didn't get to sleep on the road.
- You didn't?
- No.
(both laughing)
But you were out.
- I was out.
How embarrassing.
- It was cute.
- Why couldn't you sleep?
- I've had a lot on my mind.
(dog barking)
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Me too.
Look, you and I-
- I don't.
- What?
- No.
- No, go ahead.
- No, please.
- I just wanted to let you know that,
I hope you'll stay.
- I don't wanna go.
- You don't?
- No.
- Great.
- [Lootie] Yeah, great.
Well, and I wanted you to know
also that as your employer,
I think we should maintain that.
Look. I know we don't
have a lot in common, but-
- I like you too.
Even though you're a little stuffy.
(Lootie chuckles)
- Stuffy?
- Little, a little stuffy.
We'll work on it.
(both chuckling)
Look, you gotta let me
coach the way I wanna coach.
- I know.
- You gotta.
- I promise.
- [Lootie] Okay, okay.
- I can still come to
the games though, right?
- Yeah, but you gotta, all right.
- Look,
I mean, we must maintain.
- Yeah, yeah, right.
(Lootie chuckles)
Yeah.
- [Altogether] One, two,
five, one, two, six, one, two.
- Just touch the ball, just touch it.
Light pass, light passes.
(exciting music)
Very good, girls, focus.
- [Altogether] One, one,
two, five, one, two, six,
one, two, seven, one, two, eight.
Pick up, pick up.
All right, spot on, pulse.
Great job.
(whistle blowing)
(exciting music)
- [Altogether] One,
two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
- That's okay, stay with it, stay focused.
- [Altogether] Five, six, seven, eight.
- Watch what you're doing,
light pass, very good,
let's go, let's go, let's go.
(exciting music)
- [Altogether] Five, six.
One, two.
Five, six, seven.
- Park it.
(music drowns out Victoria)
(upbeat music)
- Focus.
- Keep your eye on the ball
at all times.
pretty annoying.
You're a lousy, Father Thomas.
- You know I bet you are.
I don't see you as a star.
- Oh, that was low.
That was so low.
You sick little girl.
- Can you believe that?
(gentle piano music)
- Oh, yes, please.
- [Waiter] Would you like some more tea?
- No, thanks.
(gentle piano music continues)
What?
- What?
- What do you keep looking around for?
- Oh,
oh, no, it's nothing.
(Lootie chuckles)
- [Thomas] Okay.
- Aren't you afraid that
we're gonna be seen here?
- Should I be?
- I dunno, should you be?
- Lootie,
I'm an Episcopal priest.
It's okay if we go out and date.
We're not celibate.
(Lootie chokes)
You all right?
- Hmm-mm.
- You ever think about getting hitched?
- I was engaged once.
- Really?
- Hmm-mm.
It didn't work out.
What about you?
- My wife was killed in an
accident 12 years ago, December.
- I'm so sorry.
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
- [Announcer] St. Tammany
who's always too so far
this season is hoping
to turn things around tonight
against the Lady Rebels.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
St. Tammany brings the ball up,
beautiful no-look pass to Stacy D
who pulls up for a jump and nails it.
- And you guys, you're doing
a great job with man-to-man.
And Shalonda, you've
gotta stay with your girl,
I mean she's killing us on the inside.
- I know.
- And the rest of you,
you need a better upside defense
to help Shalonda.
- Come on, do it.
- Okay?
- Sort it out.
You're doing great.
(Lootie sighs)
- All right,
just stay focused, girls.
Be patient, let's take this one home.
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheers)
(siren wailing)
Kimberly, Donna, hustle.
Get in here.
Girls, We've gotta do a better job
protecting this basketball.
Amy, set a better pick for Kimberly
and then roll to the ball.
(girls clapping)
- Okay, girls, listen up.
All right, keep up with them.
- Donna, find your man
and then get it to her.
We're doing fine, girls,
just relax and focus.
Remember what we've learned in practice?
- Put the pressure defensively
just keep doing what you're doing.
Now, we have to set up on the
offense, penetrate, Carrie.
(siren wailing)
- All right, come on, team.
Ready?
- [Altogether] Team!
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
- [Announcer] Lady Rebels
take the ball down court,
Kimberly (indistinct) doesn't look alone.
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
- Okay, girls, we've tied
it up with two minutes left,
that's the way to play basketball.
- Yes!
- All right.
I want motion offense, nothing but layups.
You got that? Nothing but layups.
- We can do it.
- We got this one.
- Yes!
- Let's go get 'em,
girls, come on.
Ready?
- [Altogether] Team!
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
- [Announcer] Shalonda Win
ushers down the court again,
looks like Coach Pfandder has
finally put up entirely on the promises.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(siren wailing)
And St. Tammany wins in a major turn
over the fifth rank of Lady Rebels.
♪ Hey there, Katie,
you're a real cool cat ♪
♪ You got a lot of this
and a lot of that ♪
♪ We all think that you're real neat ♪
♪ So come on down to the
chickie chickie beat ♪
♪ Hands left, chickie
chickie, chickie chickie ♪
♪ Hands right, chickie
♪ Hey, there, Josh,
you're a real cool cat ♪
♪ You got a lot of this ♪
(gentle music)
(phone buttons beeping)
(phone ringing)
- Hello.
- Did I wake you?
- No.
No, it's all right.
- I just wanted to,
just, you know,
just wanted to say good night.
- Good night, Lootie.
- Good night, Thomas.
(dial tone ringing)
(gentle music)
(car engine roaring)
(kids laughing)
(people chattering)
(car doors slamming)
(footsteps pattering)
(edgy music)
(people chattering)
(mellow guitar music)
♪ She was standing in her mind ♪
- Come on, Kimberly.
- Wimp.
- Drunk.
- I am not.
(people chattering)
(car dor slams)
- Give me the keys.
- I don't think so, eagle eyes.
Come on, Joey, get in
the car so we can go.
Dork.
- You don't have to go.
- I'll be fine.
Call me at the dorm tonight, bye.
- Come on, Julia.
(door slams)
- Let's go.
(car engine reviving)
- Guys.
- [Kimberly] Bye, dork face!
- [Julia] You didn't have
to call him a dork face.
- [Kimberly] Yes, I did.
- [Julia] You can't even
drive, you're so drunk.
- [Kimberly] I can too
drive, it's this old car.
It don't wanna go.
(brakes screeching)
(Julia screaming)
(cars crashing)
- Julia?
Julia!
(suspenseful music)
- Lotta school drama,
take the end, the one
person's unconscious, good?
(suspenseful music)
How're the vitals?
Eagles react to the scene.
I'll let you go through,
it's usually when it falls.
- Dr. Drew, telephone please.
(doctors chattering)
- Hook her up to an IV
for me, get her a monitor.
Fresh set of vitals..
(equipment rattling)
- [Doctor] I'm gonna need a 12 CT.
Can you get me
a new set of vitals?
- 120 over 80.
- Hook her up to the monitor.
- You two, get outta here.
- Somebody, get these two outta here.
- I'm gonna need a cross
table monitor of her C-spine.
- Barney, quit pacin'.
- I'm not pacin'.
- Yes you are.
(phone ringing)
- [Announcer] Dr. David,
telephone, please.
Dr. David, telephone please.
- Hey!
(phone ringing)
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- How's Julia?
- Well, she hit here head,
so they're runnin' some tests on her.
- Is it bad?
- Didn't even break the skin.
- And this happened outside of Riverboat?
- Yes, sir.
- Were you driving?
- Were you drinking?
- No, sir.
- If you're lying to me,
you kicked off the team,
you realize that, don't you?
That's the least of your problems.
Police give you a ticket?
- Yes, sir.
- May I see it please?
(machine beeping)
- So your blood level's
below the legal limit.
- Yeah, but I wasn't drunk at all.
- Don't make it worse for yourself.
And you were there?
- Yes, sir.
- And you saw everything?
- I saw everything.
- Okay.
I called in Dr. Leakage from the church,
I'm 'onna see what I can find out.
Don't you go anywhere, you understand me?
- Yes, sir.
- You come with me.
- I didn't mean to hurt anybody.
- I know.
I know.
- I didn't know it was gonna happen.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
(footsteps pattering)
It's all my fault.
It's all my fault, you hear that?
- No.
- He knows it, it wishes it'd been me.
- Hey, hey!
Listen to me, she's gonna be all right.
- Oh yeah, wouldn't you know it?
- I know it.
It's in the Lord's hands now,
you've gotta believe that.
Okay?
- Okay.
(sirens wailing)
(Lootie sighs)
- [Bill] We're gonna run some tests.
I'll keep you informed.
- [Thomas] All right, thanks, Bill.
- [Bill] Okay.
(bell dinging)
- [Announcer] Dr. David
to telephone please, Dr.
David to telephone, please.
- [Lootie] What'd you find out?
- It's not good.
(Thomas sighs)
Skull fracture.
She's unconscious.
And she broke her heel.
- Okay.
Look, will you please go in
there and talk to Kimberly?
She's a mess.
- Did I ever tell you
how my wife was killed?
(melancholic music)
(footsteps pattering)
- Sam, where's Kimberly?
- She's in there.
(door squeaking)
(metal clanging)
- Heading out?
- Yup.
(Lootie sighs)
- Talked to the hospital today.
Julia is in stable condition
and the doctor says she's
got an excellent chance
of full recovery.
- If she wakes up.
- She'll wake up.
- How do you know, did you pray about it?
- You bet I did.
You know, if Julia was
here to give us her opinion
you know she'd want you to stay.
She really looks up to you.
Don't give up so easily.
Do it for Julia.
You wouldn't want her
to give up, would you?
- Of course not.
But she ain't got
anything to say about it.
You've heard Father
Mulberry, I'm off the team.
- Look, she might not have
anything to say about it
but I do.
- That's right.
I forgot you have Father Mulberry's
undivided attention, don't you?
It's all right, everybody knows about it.
- Knows what, Kimberly?
Father Mulberry and I are friends, period.
(Lootie sighs)
Look, if he says you
can stay will you stay?
- Look,
I don't fit in here, you
know that and I know that
and I've already made up my mind, okay?
I've caused everybody enough trouble.
- Have I ever told you
how much you remind me
of me when I was your age?
I wasn't a scrawny as you, but,
I was the best player on the team too.
And it would just burn me up
when people would talk about teamwork.
You gotta work as a team,
but when it came down to it
and we were in a jam,
who did they look to?
You know, everyone thought
that I had it all together
and everything going for me, but inside,
I was so uncertain and insecure.
- Until you found God?
- Yeah.
I didn't have to look very far.
Search your heart, Kimberly.
(gentle music)
- I've been searching.
Julia and your stupid shoes.
(gentle music)
(phone ringing)
- You what?
- You heard me.
If she goes, I go.
- You're bluffing.
- Am I?
(phone ringing)
(Thomas sighs)
- You sure are.
Coach, Pfandder, I don't wanna let you go.
And I'm not just thinking about the team.
(gentle music)
(machine beeping)
- Julia, can you hear me?
You're the only girl I know
who could score cute guy
like Barney while you're
laid up and looking goofy
in a hospital bed.
(machine beeping)
It's just not fair, you asked me to drive
and I wouldn't let you drive.
Why'd you have to be such a wimp, huh?
Why'd you have to be such a wimp?
Everybody loves you, everybody loves you.
Everybody loves you so much.
So why, it should be me
here, it shouldn't be you.
It's not fair.
- [Announcer] Dr. David, telephone please,
Dr. David, telephone please.
- God, I just wish that we could help,
I wish you would would smile for me.
I wish you could.
I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry,
I wish you knew how sorry I was.
(machine beeping)
- You're Kimberly Dunn?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry, Kimberly.
This is Mr. Tumminello,
he's Julia's grandfather.
- You were driving the car?
- [Kimberly] Yeah.
- [Barney] I'll be out in the hall, okay?
- Look, I know,
all I can say is I'm sorry.
- It was an accident, right?
Well, wasn't it?
Then that's fine.
Are you all right?
Me?
- Hmm-mm.
- I'm just fine.
I'm not the one laying there unconscious.
I just wish you could read the letters
Julia's been writing me.
I've often prayed that
Julia would find happiness
and she has, and as it usually is,
happiness is spiritual.
Julia's gonna be fine.
But how about yourself, Kimberly?
How are You going to be?
(gentle music)
- Girls, we need to just keep playing
like we're at practice.
Just 'cause your mom and dad
are out there taking pictures
of you, I don't want you all showing off.
We need to make the basket.
Keep movin' that ball.
Take the shot when you know you have it.
We need more points than
the other team to win.
Enough!
(Lootie sighs)
- [Stacy] Coach, where's Kimberly.
- Yeah, where is she?
- Kimberly has been through
a lot since the accident.
And I think that maybe she's
gonna take some time off
from basketball right now.
Can't say that I blame her.
We're gonna miss her, there's
no doubt about that, but,
we can still win this game.
That means that we have to play tougher
and harder and truly stay focused.
We have to play like a team more than ever
and let our thoughts and our
prayers be with Julia tonight.
I wanna dedicate this game to her.
Let's take a moment of silence.
(crowd faintly cheering)
- This one's for Julia
- Amen.
- Welcome to tonight's presentation
of the RGV Times Classic
Tournament finals.
Tonight, they're defending
for a Texas State champion
and last year's tournament
winner, East Texas High,
brings an unbeatable record
into a contest with a
surprising, local favorite.
A Class 3A, St. Tammany
Episcopal girls' school,
a team who is so new to
competitive basketball,
they haven't even had
time to find a mascot.
(crowd cheering)
- Shoot!
- Why didn't you call me?
I didn't know you were gonna be here.
- Well, I wouldn't miss
this for the world,
you know that I wouldn't.
- Ah, it's good to see you.
- Look, can we do an interview?
- Of course, yes.
- Here we go.
All right.
On the air.
- Yeah.
- I am standing here with
the St. Tammany coach,
Lootie Pfandder, coach,
surprise, surprise.
- Yeah, no kidding.
- Tonight, she gave the
East Texas team the shock
of their life.
Did you expect to win?
- Hey, look, we always play to win,
these girls have been
playing well all week
and Kimberly Dunn, did you see
that three pointer?
- Amazing three pointer.
- They have got the spirit now.
- And you showed it tonight.
- Yeah.
- Well, congratulations.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Thank you, thank you, cut.
- How was that?
- Oh, it was good, it was good.
It was good to see you,
am I gonna see you later?
- Of course, of course, I'm
just gonna do an interview
with the captain, but I'll see you,
just go in the locker room,
I'll see you there.
- Go girl.
(crowd cheering)
(melancholic music)
(Thomas exhales)
- Hi.
Good game.
- Thanks.
- Here, let me get that.
I'm gonna buy you the
biggest porterhouse steak
this side of Kansas City.
- Wow.
- Lou, there you are.
Honey, I've been looking all over for you.
Are you ready?
- Yeah, well.
- Oh, hi father.
So what do you think of your new coach?
- Oh, it's just great.
- Oh, yeah, she is, great.
- I'm sorry, Father Thomas,
this is Carl Hastings.
- Hi there.
- Hi, pleasure.
- Carl and I are old friends.
- Good old friends.
So, you ready, honey? Dinner.
- Right, oh, dinner.
- You two go ahead.
Come with us.
- No, really.
- Sure. Come on, it's on me.
- Take a rain check.
Really, I'll talk to you after chapel.
- Are you sure?
- I'll take that.
Well, let's go, Lou, bye, Father.
- Bye.
(melancholic music)
(door slams)
- Well, what he say?
- He said it was a good sign.
- Barney, that's all he
said was it was a good sign?
- It's not all right, you
I'm sick of this garbage.
Now was supposed to go out
and I was supposed to win
a game for you and I did.
- She did.
- See?
The deal was you were supposed to wake up.
You're supposed to wake up, Julia.
You're supposed to wake up.
She was always such a wimp.
(suspenseful music)
- Who you calling a wimp?
- Julia?
- Hey, you.
- What about me, you little wimp?
- You wimp.
(victorious music)
- I'm gonna go find your grandpa.
(suspenseful music)
- Okay.
Hello, everyone, I'm Carl Hastings
and I'll be play-by-play
announcer for tonight's contest
which has a real David
versus Goliath flavor.
And with home court advantage,
the Southwood Lady Cowboys
bring the ball down court.
Lady Cowboys are 10 and four this season
with Trish Dixon number 32,
the Lady Cowboys point
guard working the ball
down under and scores with a short triple,
pulling the southern team
St. Tammany brings the ball up,
works it around at the top of the queue
over to Stacy Keen for a 12 footer, yes!
St. Tammany back on top (indistinct)
(crowd cheering)
The Lady Cowboys bring it across the floor
and get the ball down to their big center
and she gets stopped by
the freshman, Shalonda Win
of St. Tammany.
Andrews wield in a triple double
in the last three games,
it's finally living up to her potential
according to Coach Lootie Pfandder.
But it's number 23, post
guard, Kimberly Dunn,
who has clearly established
herself as team leader.
Rumors of Dunn quitting the team
after an automobile accident
that landed teammate Julia
Tumminello in the hospital,
apparently are unfounded.
Much to the delight of St. Tammany fans.
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
And they started to play
the Cowboys with the ball,
brings it around and over to the forward
for a spinning double.
And Shalonda Win with another rebound.
Coach Lootie Pfandder might be
showing the wrong(indistinct)
(crowd cheering)
St. Tammany with the ball.
Using their tricky stumble offense.
Pass the ball down to
number 12 for Stacy Keen
Who shoots the jumper end.
It's foul.
(crowd cheering)
Baskets wouldn't have counted
as a foul was committed before the shot.
- One shot
(ball bouncing)
(ball thudding)
(crowd cheering)
- [Announcer] Southwood with
the ball and Southwood foul
(crowd cheering)
- St Tammany scores.
St. Tammany Scores again.
(crowd cheering)
First trial, this St.
Tammany team is amazing.
(crowd cheering)
- This one, no way.
This one this one, perfect.
- This one?
- Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
- Okay. Yeah.
- It a paint , it got my name all over it.
(Lootie laughs)
Whoa! Oh, boy.
- Yeah.
(Lootie laughs)
What is with the hat?
- What hat?
(Lootie chuckles)
That one on your head.
- Oh, this hat?
- Yeah.
Its cute.
- You like it?
- Yeah.
Would wanna to be a
cowboy when you grew up?
- Yeah.
(Lootie chuckles)
I thought I was Hoot Gibson.
- Hoot Gibson?
- Hoot Gibson. You don't
know who Hoot Gibson was?
- Ah.
- Gibson was this great
big stuffy old cowboy.
(Lootie chuckles)
Well, it fits.
- So Lootie.
- Yeah.
- You're serious about
this TV reporter guy?
(gentle music)
(crowd cheering)
- [Announcer] And here the ball gone,
St.Tammany team is at it again.
(crowd cheering)
- They bring the ball on
court, no the ball just trip,
once again is Kimberly Dunn and it's
another easy basketball for
the team from St. Tammany.
(crowd cheering and applauding )
And the ball goes to freshman
sensational, Shalonda Win.
It's in and that's 26 points.
(crowd cheering)
- Can I get an interview right now?
- Sure.
- Stand by everybody. Quiet on the set.
Roll tape.
Here we go.
In five, four, three, two.
- So here we are.
- Here we are.
- Tell me, coach, what was
the point that you realized
that your team was special?
When did you first realize
that you were headed for
the state championship?
- Well, one day we were
practicing our free throws
with our eyes closed.
- With your eyes closed?
- It's like I told you,
practicing with faith.
Believing in oneself and
all the possibilities.
We just take it one at a time.
- Now your team doesn't have a mascot
but you have been dubbed
the St. Tammany Miracle.
And I understand that you
particularly don't care for that.
- No, I don't.
I mean it belittles our team's
athletic talent and efforts.
We will and do accept any
and all help that might come our way.
- Well, be that as it may,
it's been nothing short
of miraculous the way that
you've taken this team
from nowhere to where they are now.
- We are on a roll, all right?
But it's not a miracle.
It's good old fashioned
work and fundamentals
and ideals and a strong foundation
in belief in something
higher and bigger than us.
- Yeah, I know not
everyone could take a team
that was two and 12 and a
district a year ago to this level.
You have done the impossible.
You don't have the height
except for Shalonda Win
and she's a freshman and
you don't have the speed
except possibly in your
top scorer, Kimberly Dunn.
And I couldn't characterize
her as having blazing speed.
- No, but Kimberly just
knows how to beat you.
I think it's called heart.
- I think they call it
the St. Tammany Miracle.
And moving on, coach Pfandder,
a personal question if you don't mind.
- No, I don't mind.
- The rumors are running rampant Lou
and the suspense is killing me.
It is no secret that several
schools are interested
in you as well as a one sports
network that I can't mention
but Lootie right here
on television right now.
Tell us what you're gonna
do after the season's over.
I understand that your contract
might not be picked up by St. Tammany.
- It's not about contracts.
It's about believing in something.
Whether Father Mulberry
renews my contract.
Well, I'll pass that
bridge when I burn it.
- And cut.
Beautiful.Beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Great.
- Thanks. It's all right.
- Good.
(gentle music)
- Wow!
- That's hot.
- That is hot.
(gentle music)
- [Lootie] Thank you.
- Thank you.
(gentle music)
- Are you sure?
Whoa! Whoa!
So this religious thing,
it sort of made you a
miracle worker, is that it?
- No, Carl, once again,
you're missing the point.
- Am I?
- Yeah. I don't like it.
We're not a miracle team.
We're a basketball team.
And we've worked really
hard to get this far.
- Who happens to be leading the conference
on a wing and a prayer.
- Right.
- Look, don't exploit us.
It's not fair to my girls
and it's not fair to my personal beliefs.
- Why are you being so blatant about it?
- Frankly, Carl,
I don't think we're being blatant enough.
Look, we're a small
private Episcopal school
and we do things a little differently.
Do things a little differently.
- You have people thinking
that your team can just walk on a water.
It is this religious thing.
And that is why I'm...
If you remember correctly
that we didn't get married.
You said you that you
couldn't fully love someone
who didn't share your faith.
I never claimed to share your faith
but neither did I criticize or
interfere with your beliefs.
- You don't think it's interfering
by exploiting this miracle angle.
I mean what am I supposed to tell my girls
when you tell them that all
their hard work is some
sort of hocus-pocus.
- Tell him I love you.
Tell him I never stopped loving you.
(gentle music)
(air whooshing)
- Okay.
In five, four, three, two.
Hello, everyone. I'm Carl Hastings.
And I'll be your play by play announcer
for tonight's contest.
Not only has the Nichols high
team been extremely successful
over the past few years in this tournament
but there's an added drama
to the picture tonight.
They are riding a 56 game
winning streak which has spanned
over two years and they can
establish a new state record
with their 57th straight win
if they can gain a victory tonight.
But standing in their way
is the St. Tammany team,
a small team, which no one
expected to win 10 games
a season, much less, make
it to the state finals.
They have ridden the shoulders
of star, Kimberly Dunn
and freshmen Shalonda Win
who together have combined four 50%
of the team's points and
most of the rebounding.
But everyone is wondering
if new coach Lootie Pfandder
and her St. Tammany team
has run out of miracles.
We'll see right after this brief message.
- Ladies we're gonna win this game
'cause we're the better team.
We're bigger, we're faster
and we've been there a lot.
You've played better teams
than this in junior high.
- Did you see 'em guys are huge.
- Hey guys, we can do it.
- But did you see "em? They're giants.
- Did you see the size of number 13?
- It's a monster.
- Okay. They're big, but we can do it.
- Hey girls, this team is
gonna give us all we can handle
and then some, have to find out
if we have learned what
it takes to be champions.
- Now, you've seen the game film.
They've got one hot shot
then we're gonna take her out, right?
- [Altogether] Right.
- Don't forget where we've
come from to get here.
All the hard work, all the sacrifices.
We have the power to
make things go our way
and we will make things go our way.
- I don't want you to just beat 'em.
I want you to humiliate 'em.
I want you to kick that.
(coach chuckles)
I want you to crush them.
- I hard off the back
boards, even up the brakes
and girls, remember,
it's just basketball game.
All right take a knee.
Father.
- Lord, accept our thanks and praise
for all that you have done for us.
- And these people stand
for everything I'm against.
I wanna teach these, do gooders a lesson.
- Thank you for the splendor
of the whole creation for
the beauty of this world,
for the wonder of life, and
for the mystery of love.
We also thank you for setting us at tasks
which demand our best effort
for leading us to accomplishments
that satisfy and delight us.
We also thank you for
those disappointments
and failures that lead us
to acknowledge our dependence on you alone
and above all Lord, we thank
you for your Son, Jesus Christ.
The truth of his Word and
the example of his life
in Jesus name, amen.
- [Lootie] Amen.
- Get the tip off.
(whistle honking)
- [Announcer] Nichols
High sensational takes
on St. Tammany on the state championship.
(crowd cheering)
Nichols are state champions
and are so for undefeated.
(crowd cheering)
Kimberly Dunn brings the
ball down over to Win
and over to Kelly who
scores and St. Tammany.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
- Nichols stand up Olivia
with a three point land
and boy
(Crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
- Nichols with the ball
at the top of the team
and they pass it to the big number three
(indistinct)
Nichols up by four.
(Crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
St. Tammany with the ball (indistinct)
and nails it.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
This S. Tammany team isn't going
to go quietly I'll tell
you that right now.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
Nichols with fast play and St.
Tammany better do something
if they wanna stay in this ball game.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(whistle blowing)
And St. Tammany draw the foul.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
Nichols with the ball and (indistinct)
but she's kept over the line.
(crowd gasping)
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
- Well, maybe they're just too good,
too big, too talented, too fast.
Are you afraid to be champions?
'Cause that's what I see.
I'm seeing fear out there
and fear will defeat us
before we even get started.
(Lootie sighs)
Girls. You've got the tools.
Now's the time to use them.
Don't leave anything out there.
Give 'em everything you've got.
Face that fear girls and let it go.
(whistle hooking)
(crowd cheering)
- [Announcer] Olivia
with the three point shot
and St. Tammany, Shalonda win the rebound.
(crowd cheering)
(ball bouncing)
St. Tammany with the ball.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
Here comes Nichols High
, absolutely fearless.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
Kimberly Dunn with the ball, goes up
and St Tammany is on fire.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
- And sport fans, we're on the verge
of an incredible offset
tonight, incredible offset.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(whistle blow)
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
- Time out.
- [Announcer] And the young
coach calls for time out.
That will be interesting to see
what she gonna do now.
- All right. Listen up.
Listen. What?
We're are going two three zone.
- What?
- Hop in there, don't let them penetrate,
make them work the outside.
Crush the balls. Help each others.
Work together.
(whistle blow)
- What are we doing?
- Two three zone!
- Right.
One, two, three.
- Team!
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(coach giving instruction)
(whistle blows)
And one of St Tammany is down
and coach Pfandder doesn't
have anyone else to send.
Wait a minute, What she doing?
Who's that?
Julia Tumminnello
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
- Number 31 for 40.
It's St. Tammany with the ball,
the shot , the foul and the basket counts.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(coach shouting)
- Come on gie me a break. Will you?
It's the end of the game.
- [Announcer] The Nichols
coach is going crazy.
And here we go.
Nichols coach has been ejected.
He didn't see that one coming.
- Yes, if we make it but if we don't,
we still have the ball, okay?
The 14 seconds left, this one is all ours.
- We can do it.
- Kimberly.
It's that bad?
- I can.
- No I'm serious about
that, don't you shoot.
Donna, I want you to do this.
Number 32.
- 32 let's go.
- Good luck.
(crowd cheering)
- [Announcer] And Donna
is the shoot to technical.
And the 14 seconds left
to St. Tammany team.
Nichols on top by two.
She takes the first shot.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(ball bouncing)
Now for the second shot.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
(victorious music)
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
- So you gotta admit that the zone defense
still belongs in girl's
high school basketball.
- Yes it does but you have
to know when to use it.
- All right.
- Right.
- U admitted it.
- Yes.
(Lootie laughs)
- And you certainly know when to you it.
- Well, that's why you hired me.
- That's right.
- Are you sure you gonna be all right?
- No, it's fine, really I promise.
- Really.
- All right.
- You should go.
- Well, you have always got St. Tammany.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I always got St. Tammany.
(car hoots)
(Lootie sighs)
(birds chipping)
- I gotta go.
- Yeah.
(gentle music)
(car door bangs)
(Gentle music)
(birds chipping)
(car engine reviving)
(ball bouncing)
(Thomas breathing heavily)
(Breathing heavily)
(melancholic music)
(footsteps pattering)
(Thomas Sighs)
(melancholic music)
- Can I help you?
- Yes.
How about little one-on-one?
(ball thuds)
- I'm so sweaty.
(melancholic music)
I'm so afraid to touch.
(ambient music)