Can I try?
Careful. It's hot.
Ok, right there.
Right there.
Ok.
Try again.
Don't give up.
The only way to succeed
is with hard work.
That-a boy.
All right, let's try.
Can we work on the music box now?
Not today.
We have to go to mrs. Martin's
house to fix her stove.
But it's christmas eve.
Exactly, which is why she's
paying extra for me to fix it,
so she can cook
christmas dinner tomorrow
for her family.
How do you think I paid
for all those gifts
waiting for you under the tree?
We have to earn our gifts in life
through hard work and sacrifice.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
I just...
I wish you didn't have to work
on christmas eve.
I do all of this so you can
have a better life than me.
One day, you'll be
rich and successful.
All your christmas wishes
will come true.
Come on, brian,
let's make a wish together.
You ready?
And in other news,
santa will have a harder time
delivering gifts
this christmas eve.
It seems that ginger the reindeer
has escaped
from the local petting zoo.
Sounds like ginger
has finally snapped.
Ahh!
Oh.
Ah, merry christmas, brian.
Still no decorations, huh?
Some of us are busy
working for a living.
Besides, it's not christmas day
until tomorrow.
Well, managing my trust fund
takes a lot of work.
I'm sure your parents
are very proud.
Well, yeah, they ac...
- oh, whoa, be careful.
There's a slippery patch there.
Merry christmas, folks.
Good morning, mr. Conway.
What makes it good, jet?
- Nothing.
It's a horrible day, sir.
You'll never get anywhere in life
with that kind
of negative attitude.
There is an ice slick out front.
It is a lawsuit waiting to happen.
On it, sir.
You have the board meeting
at 9:00.
And I need you to sign off
on some of these details
for the christmas carnival
fundraiser tonight.
Ugh, christmas.
Schmoozing with a bunch
of people I don't even like.
The hell is this?
Never show me one of these again.
Yes, sir. Sorry, sir.
I'm disappointed in you.
Just think about all the joy
this party brings to people
every year.
Or think about all the money
you'll be raising
for the hospital.
And it's a giant tax write-off.
- Oh.
Now there's a ray of sunshine.
Morning, all.
How are the numbers on our big
pre-christmas event, hmm?
Did the coupons we mailed out
bring in the business
we'd hoped for?
I'm afraid
the numbers aren't good.
We are down...
20% from last christmas,
which is down...
10% from the year before that one.
Well, we're just going
to have to work harder.
I would like a plan
for improving our retail sales
on my desk by the end of the day.
I don't care
if you have to work all night.
Um, it's christmas eve, sir.
I took my father's
tiny appliance repair shop
and turned it
into a multimillion-dollar
electronics retail chain,
number one in the region.
I didn't do it by taking days off.
It took hard work and sacrifice.
That is the key to success.
But I am a benevolent boss,
so if anyone can come up
with a solution right away
then you may all get home in time
to put out a plate
of cookies for santa.
Anyone?
Well...
some of our research shows
that pc electric is not reaching
our younger client base.
What about a rebrand?
Something fresher, more electric?
I love that idea.
We could hire a marketing firm
geared towards millennials
and gen z.
Maybe connect
with some influencers.
Oh, that sounds ridiculous.
And expensive.
How am I supposed to finance that?
We could get an investor.
Uh, I know business
has been off for a while,
so I've been researching
potential investors
in my spare time...
When I'm home alone,
because I live alone
and I have no life
outside of this job.
I mean, I do have a hamster.
But she's ignoring me right now,
because I ran out of her favorite
organic carrot crackers...
- Focus, jet!
- Sorry.
So the other day,
I heard from nina nishi
that she might be
interested in investing.
Oh, wait, nina nishi?
As in the founder of pocket.
That's the shopping app, right?
How do you possibly know her?
She follows
my hamster fashion account.
Oh.
Anyway, she's in town
today, actually.
So I could set up
a lunch or something.
Why would she invest in us?
So she just sold pocket
for a ton of money,
and she's looking
for her next project.
She seems to think
pc electric might be it.
Fine.
Set it up.
Nina wants to meet you
at the store
so she can check it out.
So I don't have
to pay for lunch, perfect.
I should warn you, though,
she's a bit, um, unpredictable.
- What does that mean?
- Papa!
- Harkin! Michelle.
What a surprise.
Hi.
I have a surgery scheduled today,
and my nanny just called in sick.
Dave is in paris
with his new girlfriend.
I need someone to watch her again.
- You want me to babysit?
What about your mother?
Well, besides the fact
that I trust her even less
with a child than I trust you,
she is in brazil in a yurt,
ironically enough
searching for her inner child.
Ha.
I... you can just put her
in a conference room
with her ipad.
She won't bother anyone,
right, sweetie?
- I can do a cartwheel.
Want to see?
Well, maybe later, sweetie.
I can't.
Today's a really busy day
with work.
Please, dad, I'm desperate.
This is a really
important surgery.
- I would love to.
It's just not a good day.
I'm really good at cartwheeling.
I'm sure you are.
I'll figure it out.
It's fine. Come on.
So I'm not going to play
with papa today?
No, no, not today, sweetie.
Michelle.
You'll be at the carnival later?
After all, it is a fundraiser
for your hospital.
Of course.
I always do what's expected of me.
Come on, let's go.
Boy, today could not end
soon enough.
Think we'd have more people here,
the day before christmas.
I'm sure it'll pick up
with last-minute shoppers.
Oh, there she is!
Nina.
- Jet.
It is so good
to finally meet you in person.
This man is a creative genius.
- Oh, stop it.
Hamsters are the new ferrets.
- If you say so.
- I do.
I have very good instincts
about animals...
And people.
Shall I show you around the place?
- Oh, of course.
- After you, please.
Thank you.
Whoa. Love it, love it.
So old-fashioned and out of touch.
Well, I prefer the term "classic."
- gumdrop?
- Oh, no thank you.
- Oh, come on.
Just... nah, nah, nah, nah.
Mm.
Listen, I've been running
the numbers jet sent.
Your overhead is too high,
but there's a real opportunity
to leverage market share
by expanding the omni-channel
retail strategy.
I'm definitely interested.
We have been experiencing some...
Some supply chain issues.
Is that the newest pokémon game?
I'll take all of them.
What will you do with so many?
Give them away, of course.
I mean, I love buying presents.
What fun is being rich
if you don't spend it?
Speaking of spending money,
I hear you have
a big fundraiser tonight.
Yes, for bradley hospital.
We're raising money
for the new children's wing.
You should come.
I know how much
you love christmas.
Presents and shiny decorated trees
and santa and candy everywhere.
I mean,
who doesn't love christmas?
Oh, I love christmas.
I knew we'd get along.
All right, I've gotta run.
There's a gingerbread house
eating contest
I plan on winning.
I'll see you tonight
and we'll talk later.
See you there.
You know, I'm starting
to like this day.
I may even be feeling
some of that christmas spirit
they talk about.
No, that's just heartburn.
Thank you so much for coming.
Oh, heavens... well, listen,
save a dance for me, ok?
Brad, bernadette,
go have a couple of drinks.
We'll talk about
your checkbook later.
Take care.
Oh, dr. Angeloni,
thanks for coming.
With the money you raise
for the hospital
and the work
your daughter does for us,
I'm the one
who should be thanking you.
It's the least I can do
for the children.
Merry christmas, brian.
- Sarah brown.
How long has it been?
Since you broke my heart?
As I recall, you're the one
who broke up with me.
I got tired of waiting for you
to come home from the office.
I was building a business.
Silly me. I was building a life.
Well, what brings you here?
Was it to see me?
No, I volunteer at the hospital.
I'm here on a date.
I should go find him.
Merry christmas, brian.
- Oh, great, you made it.
- Yeah.
- Let me introduce you...
My daughter,
the brilliant surgeon.
She works at bradley, you know.
It's been a bit
of a rough day, dad.
I'm sorry, I have to go talk
to someone important.
- you know what?
Just give me the whole can.
Did you just tip him $100 for
a whole can of whipped cream?
It should be $200, right?
I mean, it's christmas.
I'm glad you could make it.
I can't resist
a good christmas party.
This is not
a good christmas party, though.
I mean, it's called
a christmas carnival,
but there's no games,
there's no fun,
there's not even a santa claus.
You should dress up as santa.
That will never happen.
It's really not
that kind of party, anyway.
It's more of a fundraiser
for the kids.
Well, people would give a lot more
if there were actual kids here,
having fun, opening presents,
spreading sticky candy cane
joy everywhere.
I'll keep that in mind
for next year.
Well, next year you won't
have to worry about it.
Why is that?
Because I don't want
to invest in your company.
I want to buy it.
Buy it?
The whole thing?
I'm an only child.
I might like to give things away,
but I don't like to share.
I need to be in charge.
This company, it's my whole life.
I'm gonna bypass the deep
sadness of that statement
and just point out,
you're gonna make
a lot of money in this deal.
You'll be so rich
that you will never have
to worry about money again.
You'll be able to do
whatever you want.
You won't have to answer
to anyone.
Your life will be all about you.
It's a family business.
My father...
- Would want this for you.
You took his tiny, struggling shop
and turned it into a company
worth millions.
Think of how proud he would be.
You'd have to promise to keep
the fundraiser every year.
Bradley hospital is very
important in this community.
Of course.
Why not?
- Really?
- Yes.
I have worked hard.
It's time I got
what I deserved, huh?
Let's drink to that.
Here's to my just desserts.
Mm.
- Mm.
- Ah.
You know, I'm beginning
to like this day.
I wish it would never end.
Sir, it's time for your speech.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I'll just go
spread the good news.
Mm.
Good evening, everyone.
I'd like to welcome you
to the pc electric
christmas carnival.
I'd like to thank you for your
support for bradley hospital
and for giving so generously
of your time...
And your money too.
Now, my commitment to the hospital
isn't based solely upon the fact
that my brilliant daughter,
michelle,
happens to be a surgeon there.
There she is, yes, yes.
Don't be so shy, honey.
But I am also dedicated
to this community.
And in the name of community,
I would like to announce
that I intend to forgo
the customary christmas bonuses
this year
and instead give
a sizable donation
to the hospital
on behalf of my employees.
- So we get nothing.
- And he gets a tax write-off.
Generous and business savvy.
The man is a machine.
It's the least I can do.
And the least you can do
is go have some fun.
Enjoy yourselves, please.
May your christmas be
full of gifts,
preferably purchased
from pc electric.
Go on out there. Enjoy yourselves.
Thanks again for coming.
How was that?
Pretty great, I'd say, huh? Huh?
Yeah, you were great, yeah.
It's just been
kind of a tough day for me.
Listen, something else
has come up.
I'm thinking about selling
the company to nina nishi.
- Who? What?
You're selling the company?
What are you gonna do?
What's gonna happen
to your employees?
That's not my problem.
- Brian. Brian, come on!
Let's celebrate!
We'll talk about it later.
Oh, my.
I had no idea
you were so much fun.
The heck is going on?
Merry christmas, brian.
It's not christmas yet.
Ooh, you're right.
And I'm afraid
it never will be for you again.
Am I dead?
Pretty much.
I'm just here
to send you on your way.
The angel of death is santa?
It's different for everyone.
And, well, tis the season.
- But I'm not ready to die.
Not today.
I'm just about to get
everything I ever wanted.
Really? Are you sure about that?
Please, give me a second chance.
I'll do anything.
Well, you're not quite
on the naughty list,
but you've never been
particularly nice.
I'll change.
I promise, I'll work harder.
I'll do better. Just let me live.
Oh, you know,
I'm feeling generous today.
I'll tell you what, I'll give you
12 days to get it right.
12 days of christmas eve.
Oh, 12 days.
12 days. So I'm not gonna die.
Well, that's up to you.
If by the time
the 12 drummers drumming
have beaten their last note,
you still haven't figured out
the true meaning of christmas...
The true meaning of life...
Well, then, it's off to that
giant christmas tree farm
in the sky.
I promise, I'll learn it.
I'll live it.
I won't let you down.
Blow out the candle
and go deck those halls.
Is that...
Weird dream.
And in other news, santa will have
a harder time delivering gifts
this christmas eve.
It seems that ginger the reindeer
has escaped
from the local petting zoo.
Sounds like ginger
has finally snapped.
Ah, merry christmas, brian.
Yes. It's not christmas, is it?
It's still christmas eve.
It was all a dream.
Ok.
Oh, whoa, be careful.
There's a slippery patch there.
Merry christmas, folks.
I'm afraid
the numbers aren't good.
We are down...
20% from last christmas,
which is down...
10% from the year before that.
Some of our research shows
that pc electric is not reaching
our younger client base.
What about a rebrand?
Something fresher, more electric?
- She doesn't want to invest.
She wants to buy the company.
Who is she?
Nina nishi.
How do you know that?
She told me yesterday.
You spoke
with nina nishi yesterday?
It wasn't a dream.
It happened,
and it's happening again.
What's happening again, sir?
I can't... I can't breathe.
It's real.
Santa was real.
I've got to get out of here.
Are you ok? Do you need cpr?
Have to find santa.
Papa!
Oh, I can't watch her today.
I can't!
How did you know
I was gonna ask that?
Because it's the second day
of christmas eve.
Gotta find santa.
I gotta find santa.
- Hey, watch out for the...
ah!
Oh, damn.
Well, that was quick.
Why are you doing this to me?
You asked for this.
You begged me.
You said you wanted to live.
We made a deal.
You said you would do better.
This isn't a dream,
and it isn't a joke.
You've already wasted one day.
You've got ten days left.
Don't blow it.
You just watch.
I'm gonna make this
the merriest christmas eve
anybody has ever seen.
Oh, hey. Merry christmas, brian.
Jason, have you ever seen
one of those time loop movies
where a person gets stuck
in the same day
over and over again?
Oh, yeah, I love those.
How do they usually get out of it?
Well, they usually get out of it
when they stop being selfish
and start helping other people.
- Exactly. Yes, that's it.
That's the answer.
- Well, yeah. To what?
- To life.
All I have to do is make
everybody's christmas wish
come true, and I'll live.
This is gonna be so easy!
Ooh, he's cracking up.
Morning, sam.
Merry christmas!
So since the christmas spirit
is all about giving
and caring for others,
I have decided to give you all
the week off.
And I'm going to give you
a 10% raise
and a week's salary as a bonus.
Everyone?
Yes, jet, everyone, including you.
Although I do still need your help
with the christmas carnival
stuff this evening, all right?
I have to raise as much money
as I possibly can for santa.
I mean, for the hospital,
of course.
How are we going to pay
for all of this?
The numbers are down.
We'll worry about that
tomorrow, dale.
Today, our only concern
is that everyone is happy.
Ooh, that reminds me,
I'd better get going
if I'm going to get all
of my good deeds in today.
Papa!
Oh, guys, guys, hi.
Listen, this... this should...
Should cover a sitter.
And I'll tell you what,
no... why don't you just
take the day off
and go shopping on me?
What's going on?
- Can't talk!
Gotta go save the world!
Whoa, whoa, hey, listen.
Didn't get me this time, huh?
Oh, sorry, I'll have to owe you.
I'm fresh out of cash.
Wow, there's a lot of them.
What the heck. I'll take them all.
Ah! Stop! Stop!
Excuse me. Excuse me, miss.
Thank you.
Merry christmas. Here we are.
A little something for you,
just because it's christmas.
And how about
a nice big green box?
Come to my party later.
Oh, look.
Yes, a little triceratops.
Give that to a youngster you know.
Hello, my friend.
Here you are.
What am I supposed to do
with this?
- Well, whatever you like.
You see how unselfish I am?
Merry christmas.
You see, santa?
You see all the nice things
I'm doing?
You can't kill me now.
Santa kills people?
No. It was a joke.
I was kidding.
Here, have a toaster.
That one doesn't count.
My goodness, I love this jacket.
You know what,
I haven't seen that since...
What was that movie
with dennis hopper?
Brian has lost his mind.
And most of next year's budget.
Good evening, everyone.
Thank you for being here
and supporting me
and bradley hospital.
I have been selfish
and stingy sometimes,
but that is all about to change.
Now, I am interested
only in giving.
After all, isn't that
the meaning of christmas?
So let's keep giving
to bradley hospital
and to each other.
Aha!
Merry christmas.
You guys, you came.
Oh, this is wonderful.
Did you see? Did you see that?
Did you see how generous I was?
Dad, what is going on?
I am making everybody's
christmas wishes come true.
Ooh, speaking of making
wishes come true,
wait till you see what I got you.
Jet.
It's the dog you always wanted.
She's allergic.
Barely.
A few sniffles never hurt anybody.
- Let's go, let's go.
- What?
I have to get her some benadryl.
- Why?
- Ok?
Michelle.
Oh. Oh!
I was only trying
to make her happy.
She doesn't need a dog
to make her happy
or any of the 10,000 presents
you had delivered today.
She just needs a grandfather
who pays attention to her.
I was paying attention.
I knew she wanted a dog.
I got her a dog.
Ok, well, we will see you
at christmas tomorrow.
And get that animal out of here.
Oh!
This is pointless.
If helping all those people
doesn't get me
to christmas day,
then nothing will.
Who were you helping
besides yourself?
And what would
an 80-year-old grandmother
do with an electric razor?
Did you happen to notice
her facial hair?
All right, all right, all right.
I get it.
I'll think of a better gift.
Christmas isn't about gifting.
It's about giving.
Giving what?
Well, that's something
you'll have to figure out
on your own.
These numbers are unacceptable.
If you people can't come up
with a plan to improve them,
I'm just gonna sell
the whole company
and hope they fire
each and every one of you.
Jet, get me an appointment
with nina nishi.
She's in town
and she's interested.
Wait, I was gonna...
But how do you know that?
I don't pay you to ask questions.
I pay you to do what I tell you.
Yes, sir.
No one appreciates what I do.
I am tired of working this hard
and getting nothing in return.
When is it my turn?
When do I get what I want?
What do you want, sir?
To be happy,
just like everybody else.
Papa!
Harkin, hi!
And you, my beloved child,
here to tell me again
what a selfish person I am
for not wanting
to watch my granddaughter.
Not wanting to watch
my granddaughter
go another day without telling her
how much I love her.
What?
Don't you have
a very important surgery today?
You need someone
to look after her, I will.
- You will?
Of course, no problem.
- Yay!
Can I show you my cartwheel?
Maybe a little later.
Thanks, dad.
I wouldn't ask
if I wasn't desperate.
I know how busy you are.
It's really generous of you.
From your lips to santa's ears.
Ok, then.
I will see you guys
at the carnival tonight.
- Great.
Have a good surgery.
Yeah.
After all, it's not like I haven't
raised a child of my own.
And you're a good kid.
How hard could it be?
- Can I have a nintendo switch?
- No.
- Can I have an iphone?
- Can I show you my cartwheel?
- No.
- Can I get a puppy?
Jet, when does nina get here?
Any minute.
Listen,
take her, give her some candy
or something.
Just to keep her distracted.
Are you sure?
She's already had
two hot chocolates
and, like, five candy canes, so...
- I don't care.
Just keep her away.
- Yes, sir.
Come on, harkin, let's go.
Oh, nina, how lovely to see you.
Well, I am so happy to be here.
Papa, I don't feel good.
I'm sorry about this.
This is my granddaughter, harkin.
How sweet, learning
the family business already.
Yes, you know me,
all about the children.
I want to go home.
Not now, honey.
Papa has to finish this meeting.
I want to go home now.
Kids.
Just give me
one more minute, all right?
Maybe I should come another time.
No, no. No.
I'll just go wash up. It's fine.
You should come to
the christmas carnival tonight.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
We'll talk then.
I feel much better now.
You're happy here, honey?
Nina can't make it.
She said she'll meet you
in town next time she's here.
- No, it has to be today.
There's no tomorrow.
Tomorrow is today.
Yesterday is today.
Now is all I have.
That's so deep.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I had a rough day.
Oh, did you?
Did it involve getting puked on?
Or losing out on the business
deal of a lifetime?
'cause that was my day.
I'm sorry, papa.
Oh, it wasn't your fault, sweetie.
Really?
Now what?
You're on the right track.
You're just going
in the wrong direction.
Maybe try asking harkin
where she wants to go?
Mmm!
Thanks, dad.
Are you sure you can keep her
all day?
We'll see you at the carnival.
Great.
- Bye.
Well, harkin,
what would you like to do?
Today is your day.
Really?
Really.
Today is all about you.
Oh, my god.
You're a mess.
Oh... oh, yeah,
everybody needs a triceratops.
Let's try to...
Oh, yes, take that for sure.
Oh, boy. Whew.
I have not been sledding
in a long time,
not since your mother
was a little girl.
Gosh this is... this is fun, huh?
This is the best day ever.
You know those kids?
They go to my school.
Why don't you go on
down there and play with them?
They don't like me.
Oh, come on, harkin.
You gotta make some friends,
you know.
If you're gonna be a leader,
you gotta have some followers.
No.
Why are you being so difficult?
You're acting
just like your mother.
Yeah, well, I'd rather be
like her than you.
She's right,
you are just a mean old man.
Harkin.
Harkin, I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm coming. I'm coming.
Ahh!
I gave her everything she wanted.
You did, but what about
what she needs?
And then benjamin farted
and the whole class smelled
like dead fish.
That is terrible.
It was awesome.
What is it about those kids
that makes you look so sad?
They think I'm weird.
Everyone thinks I'm weird.
You know what you have to do
to make those kids like you?
What?
Nothing.
Huh?
Do you like them?
Not really.
Do you like yourself?
Yes.
Then that's all that matters.
Because you are amazing.
And life is too short
to worry about people
who do not appreciate
your big, beautiful heart.
How did you get to be
so smart, papa?
- I'm still learning...
Something new every day.
Let's play a song.
Oh, yeah, good idea,
let me pull a quarter out...
I have a quarter.
You put it up there.
It's broken.
It's too bad
I don't have my tools.
You know what,
I bet I could fix this.
You can fix stuff?
Yeah.
Actually, I'm pretty good at it.
I can fix things.
Can you teach me how to fix stuff?
Let's find out.
This is where it all started.
My dad, your great grandfather,
was a real whiz at fixing things.
And he and I would go
to the junkyard together,
and we'd find some stuff,
and we would fix it together.
When your mom was little,
I'd come out here late at night
and tinker just to take my mind
off of things at work.
Boy, it's been forever
since I've been out here.
Let's get started.
You need to know
some of the basics, all right?
This here, this is a wire stripper
and a pair of pliers,
needle nose they call them.
Almost everything you need to do
in any kind of repair work,
you have to use screwdrivers.
You see that? Ok, cool.
Here's what we'll do.
You take the negative
and I'll place this
on the positive.
You see that?
There you go, that's it, honey.
Yeah.
Very good.
Ok, great.
Now, let's give her a try.
You can do the honors.
Well, here, hang on.
Let's adjust a little bit.
It works. We fixed it.
This is the best day ever.
Now, that's enough of that.
I wish I could fix my mom
like we fixed the radio.
What's the matter with your mom?
She works too hard
and she's stressed out
all the time.
If I had one christmas wish,
it would be for her to be happy.
Well, you know what,
let's just see what I can do
about that.
After all, I'm pretty good
at fixing things, aren't I?
Really? You're the best.
- you're the best, kid.
Hey, you know what?
We got some time
before the carnival,
why don't we go over and deflate
all of jason's
christmas decorations?
Come on.
- That sounds naughty.
Let's do it!
Hey.
Today was awesome.
Can I spend every day with papa?
Yes. No. Maybe. I don't know.
What is going on here?
I'm gonna go get some cookies.
Ok, we'll see you in a little bit.
Is this the twilight zone?
More like groundhog day.
What?
We went shopping together.
I taught her how to love herself.
And then we went to the workshop
and fixed an old radio together.
You let her go in your workshop?
You never let me go in there.
Now, I've got
a great surprise for you.
You've been working so hard
lately at the hospital,
with harkin, and all
the volunteer work you do.
You've done so much
for everybody else,
I thought it was time
someone did something for you.
So I called you boss.
You're free for the week.
We're going
to the bahamas tomorrow.
Tomorrow is christmas.
I'd like to spend
christmas at home.
I don't want to be on a plane.
- But...
and those are
really important surgeries
I have next week.
Honey, you need to have a break.
- You don't know what I need.
You never have.
You were always too busy
working to know what I needed.
I did that for you.
No, it wasn't for me.
It was so that you could prove
to the world
and to your father
what a success you were.
You've never loved me.
- That is not true.
- Well, that's how it felt.
Come on, harkin.
We'll make...
- I want a cookie.
No, we'll make some cookies
at home, ok, honey?
Hey b-man, I heard you were
looking for investors.
Let's talk.
Not the best time, nina.
Make it quick, santa.
So what have you learned
so far, brian?
I've learned how important
my family is to me.
How their happiness
is what matters.
I want to make
harkin's wish come true.
I want michelle to be happy.
I want to make her love me again.
But I... I just don't know how.
Well, you've got six days
to figure it out.
Don't give up.
Christmas is
just around the corner.
Christmas or die.
That is the choice, right?
Afraid so.
Well, then, I choose christmas.
"better off alone."
"raised by wolves."
"when parents don't care
about you."
I care.
I'd say I'm more of a bear
than a wolf.
What's that, papa?
Oh, nothing, honey.
You know, I'd like to get
something really special
for your mom
for christmas this year.
What does she like?
She likes food carved
to look like animals,
animals dressed up like food,
she likes pretzels
dipped in frosting,
rolled in sprinkles,
and she likes dancing
in her pajamas
to irish folk songs.
Her favorite is...
how did you know that?
I used to sing it to her
when she was a little girl,
just like my dad sang it to me.
Mostly she likes helping people.
That's why we have
all those bills.
She's always giving
her money away to charity.
Well, and all those
massive student loans
you made or take out to teach her
"fiscal responsibility."
yes, everybody has to learn
that nothing in this life
is for free.
Mom and j.Lo say
that love don't cost a thing.
Oh.
Well, today,
at least these christmas cookies
are for free.
With milk?
Just like santa.
Here comes the big finish.
Wait for it.
That always used to make
your mom laugh her head off.
And then it was lights out.
Here we are.
I told you not to call me today.
I know, sir, but it's nina nishi.
She wants to meet with you.
She's very interested
in investing.
Well, look, I promised harkin
that I would teach her
how to fix a radio.
Training her to take
over the family business?
Maybe.
That gives me an idea.
Thanks for coming all the way out.
Yeah.
Oh, that's my granddaughter
there, harkin.
- Hi.
- I promised her
we'd fix something together.
Oh, that's so sweet.
My grandfather also loved
to fix things.
It's one of the reasons
I'm interested in pc electric.
It reminds me of him.
Would you like to have a seat?
Oh, no, go ahead.
Oh, thank you.
Now, I have been
doing some research.
And it's my understanding
that in order to make
whipped cream,
you've got to have
some heavy cream,
a few drops of vanilla,
some powdered sugar,
and you whip it
until you get stiff peaks.
Am I right? Hmm?
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Mmm. Oh, so good.
Look, I'm not gonna
waste your time.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
Pc electric is struggling.
We need an investor.
I can stay stuck in the past
and, apparently, in the present.
But if I want to save my company,
I have to look to the future.
I believe you are
the kind of person
who can lead me to tomorrow.
What makes you think that?
Well, like I said,
I've done my research.
You graduated top of your class
at harvard business school.
Hm.
All the startup companies
you've invested in,
every one is making strides
in innovation
and in market share.
You know how to work hard.
And you go after what you want.
Well, work is pretty much
all I have going on in my life,
so I better be good at it, right?
What about your family,
friends, love?
I'm not really good at that stuff.
It's just easier right now
to just focus on work.
There'll be plenty of time
for family and friends later.
That's what I used to think,
but I was wrong.
Sometimes you just gotta reach out
and eat that cookie.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, wait. Mm-mm. Oh!
Do you like the cookies I made?
You made these?
Oh, my god, they're so...
I'm sorry,
I cannot lie to this face.
They're horrible.
What?
Ew, gross. Papa!
How is this my fault?
It was a mix.
Whew!
I've never seen you
quite so loose, brian.
What happened to that
tight grip you always had?
It's a lot more fun
when you let go.
Hmm.
Sara.
Yeah?
I wonder... oh, sorry.
Have fun.
- come on. All right, now.
What's this one?
Oh, I like that. I like that.
Honey.
What's the matter, honey?
You look upset.
It's just...
my patient, they almost died
during surgery.
I'm so sorry.
It's my fault. I...
I could have done
things differently.
I should... I should be better.
No.
You are smart, kind,
and hardworking.
Maybe I don't say this enough,
but I'm proud of you,
and I always have been.
Thank you.
Did somebody spike the eggnog?
Not yet, but the night is young.
Yeah, go dance.
- You sure?
Today was a rough one for her.
She told me.
She thinks she's a bad surgeon.
- Ridiculous.
She's one of our best.
Her patient had a brain bleed
that no one caught
until it was almost too late.
She's too hard on herself.
Good thing she has
a father like you,
always looking out for her.
Ok.
Well, I had
the most wonderful time
with you today.
You are a great kid.
Yep, my mom tells me all the time.
Hey, why don't you go get
some candy canes, hon?
Ok.
I don't know
what's gotten into you,
but thank you for watching harkin
and for whatever medication
or food substitution
that has somehow managed
to shift you
from scrooge to santa.
Santa is not the saint
some people think he is.
Oh, really? You know this how?
Let's just say he has
decked my halls several times,
thank you very much.
Oh, ok, well,
the next time you see him,
tell him I said hi
and that I'm still waiting
on that cabbage patch kid
he owes me.
Speaking of things that are owed,
I know I wasn't really around
for you that much
when you were growing up,
but I am here now,
and I have a very special
early christmas gift to give you.
I have paid off your debts
and your student loans.
How do you know
how much debt I have?
Well, I happened to look
through your mail earlier.
You looked through my mail?
It was just sitting out,
and I thought...
so you're spying on me?
No, no, it's just...
I wanted to do
something nice for you.
I love you.
I'm not a spreadsheet, dad.
You can't just clear up
your debt by paying off mine.
That's...
- What do you want then?
I don't want your money.
I just... I want a dad
who doesn't have to ask me
that question.
- Hey, come on. You ready?
- Ok.
Let's go do all of our fun
christmas traditions, ok?
I am gonna figure this out.
You hear me, santa?
I'm gonna make her happy,
and I'm gonna
make her love me again.
I'm gonna show you...
oh, you sure showed me, huh?
Just shut your chimney hole.
Dr. Angeloni, I was hoping
you could do me a favor.
Papa!
- Harkin!
- I don't understand.
That surgery's been
on the schedule for weeks.
I don't need a day off.
Yes, dr. Angeloni,
whatever you think is best.
Of course, yeah.
I'll see you tonight.
What's wrong?
I was just coming here to ask
if you could watch harkin
during my surgery, but it just
got taken off the schedule.
I don't get it.
I'm sure they have their reasons.
Yeah, maybe dr. Angeloni
doesn't think I'm good enough.
Well, I know for a fact
that's not true.
Maybe they just wanted
to give you a little time off.
Ok, well, we don't need
to bother you now.
Why don't we get going?
- No, no, no, wait, wait.
Please, please.
Maybe we could spend
the day together.
I could ditch work and...
And we can go out and do
some of that christmas stuff
that you guys always do.
You'd ditch work
to do christmas stuff?
Or other stuff, whatever you like.
I want to go sledding
and sing christmas carols
and bake cookies
and eat cookies and...
that sounds like a great day.
What is this? What's going on?
Are you dying?
I hope not.
Look,
I know you don't think
I know who you are
or what you need.
You're right.
I was so busy trying
to give you a better tomorrow
I wasn't in any of your todays.
But I'm here now.
Today is your day.
Show me who you are.
Ok.
Where to?
You'll see.
Oh, and you'll need
different clothes.
Ah. Thank you.
Hi. These are really big.
- there you are. Thank you.
Let's move on.
You know,
that was actually kind of fun.
- Yeah, you were amazing.
- Yeah.
Yeah, jet.
- Just wait a second.
- Yeah. Ok.
Guys, I have to stop by the shop
before we go ice skating.
Why?
Just a little work thing.
A little work thing?
Yeah, well,
there's this investor in town
and I have to meet with her.
You guys can play video games
while we wait.
Yay!
I thought you said
today was just about us,
that you weren't going to work.
I did say that,
but this just came up.
Something always just comes up.
Yeah, and how do you think I paid
for all the donations
we just made?
You have to earn your gifts
with hard work and sacrifice.
When will you understand that?
- Oh, I do.
I love my job and I have
sacrificed for my career,
but never at the expense
of my family
and never on christmas eve.
Fine, I won't go.
Maybe one day I'll be able
to forget all of the times
that you chose work over me,
but today is not that day.
I'm trying.
Yeah, well, try harder.
Jet, I'm not gonna make it.
Oh, come on.
I am not giving up.
- there you go. Yep.
Looks really good.
- For you.
- You can just...
you know what... in his pipe
and smoke it.
Do you remember
that music box you gave me
when I was 12?
The one with the clock on it?
- Yeah.
My dad found it at a yard sale.
We fixed it together.
It's a very valuable collectible.
That's why you were so mad
at me when I broke it.
Gosh, I begged you
to fix it for me,
but you never had the time.
I'm sorry.
I got the time now.
I gave it away years ago.
All I ever wanted
was for you to love me.
Oh, honey, I do love you.
I always did.
I wish I could believe that.
It's just too late.
You can't make up for lost time.
What is it gonna take for me
to prove to you that I love you,
that I am ready
to be a good father,
the kind of father who deserves
to be loved again?
Can you go back in time
and fix that clock?
I didn't think so.
We'll just see about that.
Well, that was a surprise.
I didn't want to wait
another minute.
I got it.
I find that clock. I fix it.
I give it to her,
then she knows that I love her.
Then she loves me too.
And then I get to live.
You see, I get it now.
The meaning of christmas,
the meaning of life,
it's love.
My love, her love, harkin's love.
Love is everything.
You're right, it is.
But there's something else
you should know about...
Oh.
Jet, I have
every confidence in you.
You are my number one guy.
Now, this was
a limited edition, and...
I know they made
several of them, though.
So you'll be able to find one,
and buy it,
no matter what the condition
and no matter what the cost.
Are you ok?
This isn't like you.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
Oh, my god, are you dying?
- Not today.
- Ok.
Oh, and I need it
for the carnival tonight.
Chop, chop.
- Yes, sir.
- I'll text it to you.
- Ok.
Ah, there you go.
And this one.
Oh, I have an idea for that one.
We have something very special
for you, young man.
Perfect.
Hi.
- Hi.
Really surprised me this year.
So here you are, young man.
This is great, yes.
- Sure to warm you up.
Let me come around and help you.
Come on. There you go.
Oh, I needed this.
Wow, I don't know why I don't have
one of these in my office.
- Can I have one?
- Sure, why not, kid?
- Oh, no, dad.
She is eight years old.
She doesn't need a massage chair.
Have you watched the news lately?
Climate change, inflation,
supply chain issues
for pokémon cards.
It's a very stressful time
to be a kid these days.
She does have a point.
You still don't need
a massage chair, ok?
I wish this day would never end.
Don't say that.
Because then
christmas wouldn't come,
and you'd miss
all those presents from santa.
- Oh, right.
I've been very good this year.
I'm going to get
a lot of presents.
Oh, you really think so?
It has been
a really wonderful day.
It's been a long time
since I felt part of a family.
I love you.
Surprise!
- Oh, nina. Hi.
What are you doing here?
Well, jet told me you were busy,
but he slipped up and said
you were at the store,
so I thought I'd swing by
so we could talk business.
I've run the numbers and I'm
super interested in investing.
- Who is this?
- This is nina nishi.
She's... she's...
Well, a possible investor.
Gosh, I... I would love
to be in business with you,
but today I promised my
daughter and my granddaughter
that we would spend
the day together.
And I've broken
a lot of promises in the past.
I'm not gonna do that anymore.
So I hope you understand.
- Wow.
From everything I heard about you,
this was not what I was expecting.
You're very lucky to have
a dad that shows up for you.
Yeah, I am.
I'll talk to jet.
We'll schedule something
for after the holidays.
- Great.
- Wait, wait.
Will you just wait...
Wait a second?
Go, meet with her.
- But honey, I...
- Listen, I know
that the business
has been struggling.
And harkin and I can just sit
in the massage chairs.
Are you sure?
Of course.
I don't deserve
a daughter like you.
Yesterday, I would have
agreed with you.
But today... today, maybe you do.
Go. We'll be right here.
- Ok.
Nina?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Thanks for waiting.
Lower back.
Whoa, that...
Yeah, that feels good.
Oh!
You know what I just realized?
This is a christmas carnival,
and there's no games
or prizes, and there's no santa.
You should dress up
as santa, papa.
Yes.
That's never gonna happen.
Please.
A man must hold on
to some dignities,
and not dressing as santa
is one of mine.
Even the grinch
dressed up as santa.
My father dressed as santa
every year.
And I am not my father.
I am no santa.
If you say so.
Want to get some snacks?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Jet, where are you?
If you're not here in ten minutes,
I swear I'm gonna fire you.
No, I don't mean it.
Just hurry!
You know, I'm sick
of that martini.
Just... may I have some gin
on the rocks?
Make it a double.
Merry christmas, brian.
It isn't christmas
until tomorrow, is it?
Sorry, I just wanted to...
and tomorrow never comes, does it?
It's always just today.
Today, over and over again.
And today is my last day.
My last day.
Do you understand?
Are you ok?
No, I'm not.
I... I want more time.
I have to get that clock,
that... that music box clock.
That will get me to tomorrow,
which actually is christmas.
- You're right.
It's not christmas yet.
I hope you find everything
that you're looking for, brian.
Who was that?
It's just a ghost
of christmas past
to remind me
what a horrible man I am.
Why is there no santa
at this party?
Papa has dignities.
Ok.
I've been thinking.
I don't want to invest
in your company.
Of course not.
- I want to buy it.
- Buy it?
Yes, the whole thing.
It's the only thing
that makes sense
for me and for you.
Just think,
you won't have to worry about
money ever again,
and you can spend
more time with your family.
- Ok.
- Really?
- Really.
But, dad, this company,
it's your whole life.
Well, maybe it's time
it wasn't anymore.
- I'm here! I've got it!
Please, don't fire me.
- Jet.
- Finally.
Michelle...
mm-hmm?
I know I was never
the father you deserved.
And you did deserve better.
And I promise I'm going
to be better from now on,
because I'm proud of you,
and I love you,
and I hope this gift
shows you how much I care.
It's a clock.
- Yes, it's...
It's the music box clock
I gave you when you were 12.
Yeah, the one that you wouldn't
help me fix when it broke.
No, no... I know, I... I...
But... but... but it's fixed now.
I mean, I found a new one for you.
I got this for you.
Just open it.
Thanks.
You said that if I fixed it,
we could have a second chance.
You said if I gave you this,
it would prove that I loved you.
I'm just gonna let
you guys talk in private.
I never said that.
Yes, you did, on the balcony.
I've never been on the balcony.
Yes, you were.
I tracked it down today.
And... and jet drove all over
town trying to find it.
Oh, so jet got this for me.
No, we... well, yes, but...
it was a lot of driving,
all those last-minute shoppers.
Well, thank you, jet.
I appreciate your effort.
Come on, honey.
I'm guessing that didn't go
how you had hoped.
I can fix this.
Hey, everyone,
can I have your attention?
Come on in here. Don't be shy.
What is she doing?
Hi. Merry christmas, everyone.
I just wanted to introduce myself.
My name is nina nishi.
And I just wanted to say thank you
to our generous hosts,
brian conway and pc electric,
for all the hard work
they've done.
Come on up here, brian.
Come on up.
Come on. Come on up.
This man has worked so hard
over the years
to build this company up
and to give back to the community,
which is why after all that
hard work and sacrifice,
he's finally gonna reward himself
by selling me the company.
What did she say?
What are you doing?
I know we haven't
discussed the details,
but I'm just so excited,
I couldn't wait.
And don't worry, I will be
a very generous boss,
if and when I fire you
after breaking the company
into pieces
and selling off the parts.
This is not what we discussed.
This is the only thing
that makes business sense.
- Listen, everyone.
- Brian.
There's been a misunderstanding.
- But...
- No one is getting fired.
Please, go back to the party
and enjoy yourselves.
And you, just get out.
Go. Hit the bricks.
Did you ask dr. Angeloni
to take me off the schedule today?
No.
Ok, yes, yes, but only because...
that patient almost died
during the surgery.
If I had done the surgery...
the same thing
would have happened.
Well, thank you for having
faith in me as a surgeon.
No, that patient had
a brain bleed.
It doesn't matter who operated.
What... what are
you talking about?
You know what? I don't care.
I thought you had changed.
You sure fooled me.
- You're right.
I wasn't there for you.
I don't deserve you.
I'm a horrible father.
And I'm a horrible boss.
And I'm a horrible human being.
Oh, you're right.
You're all right.
Oh, my god.
- Whoa. Whoa.
- Dad.
I'm sorry.
- Papa.
Hey, dad. Dad, hey. Hey.
- Papa, papa.
- I'm sorry.
- Are you ok, papa?
- Dad, stay with me, please.
Papa.
It's ok. It's ok. It's ok.
I tried.
I know.
The worst thing isn't that
I won't wake up tomorrow.
It's that everybody else will.
They'll wake up on christmas day
with the wreckage I left behind.
A failing business.
My broken family.
I wish I could have one more day,
not that I could live any longer,
but that they would be ok,
have the better life
I wasted so much time
trying to give them.
I gave you 12 chances.
I know.
Or did you?
You've only given me 11 chances.
It wasn't until
after the first death
that you promised me 12 days
to get it right.
Now, now, now, wait a minute.
Please, give me that day.
One more day.
Please, I can fix this.
I know I can.
I'll make a deal with you.
I'll give you
that one more day, but...
Only to set things right,
not to keep living.
When the day is done,
so is your life.
Deal?
I'll take it.
Merry christmas, brian.
This looks...
Great, jason.
Well, thank you, brian.
You think you could do me
a little favor?
Sure, I... I...
I can try.
- whoa, whoa, whoa, be careful.
Slippery patch.
Bless you, sir.
Oh, please be careful.
There's a slippery patch
right there.
Merry christmas, folks.
- After you.
- Thank you.
Merry christmas.
Good morning, mr. Conway.
- It is, isn't it?
This is for you.
Gingerbread latte
with extra cinnamon.
Your favorite, yes?
How did you know that?
How did he know that?
All that is to say
that even though it may not
have seemed like it,
I have been listening
and learning.
And you were right.
We should change our strategy.
If we... I mean,
if this company is to survive,
then we have to start
thinking about the future.
Dale, that is why I am approving
your new marketing
and branding campaign.
Really?
But how are we gonna
pay for all this?
Well, I know
that nina nishi's in town,
and she's interested in investing.
I've scheduled a meeting
with her this afternoon.
And something else.
I would like to thank
each and every one of you
for your years of devotion
and your hard work
by giving you all a 20% raise
and a month's salary as a bonus.
Oh, my god.
Well done. Thank you, thank you.
Except for you, jet.
You are getting
an even bigger raise
because I'm promoting you to coo.
After all, you've been looking
after me and this company
for years, and if...
If anything were to happen to me,
I know pc electric
would be in good hands.
I won't let you down, sir.
Please, call me brian.
Yes, sir.
I mean, brian, sir.
I mean, brian.
All right.
You should work on that.
Well, what are you all
sitting there for?
It's christmas eve. Get home.
Start celebrating.
Oh, oh, and if you're
interested at all,
please come to the christmas
carnival tonight.
Bring your families.
Bring your friends.
It's gonna be fun.
Merry christmas.
I have just a few last things
I'd like you to do
as my assistant,
if you don't mind.
- Of course not.
- Ok.
Now these, I want you to get
to the carnival for tonight.
And these, I'd like to be
ordered and delivered
to the house asap.
I'm on it, brian.
Thank you.
- Papa!
- Harkin.
What a wonderful way
to start the day.
And how is my favorite
sunshine sparkle unicorn?
Awesome.
I have a surgery scheduled today,
and the nanny just called.
Well, I can take care of her
while you work.
- Really?
- Sure.
I can't think of a better way
to celebrate
this beautiful day
than to spend it
with my awesome granddaughter.
Great, ok.
Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, michelle, I can't
tell you how I know this,
but your patient, the one
you're about to operate on,
has a brain bleed
that no one has noticed.
What are you talking about?
Just trust me.
Go.
Ok.
I'll see you later, honey.
Thank you.
Ok. Bye, honey.
Ok, now, how would you
like to help me
with a very special project?
You bet I can.
And that is gonna work
just like that.
We'll put these screws in gently.
And that will fit
right in there like so.
- Right here.
- There you go.
Now put a little pressure on it.
Nice job.
Ok, I've got
this really quick meeting,
but you... you sit here for a bit.
If you need anything at all,
just come and get me.
You're the best papa ever.
I want to thank you for coming
on such short notice.
I know this seems out of the blue,
but I've realized recently
that time is precious,
and I didn't want to wait.
Well, I have to admit
I was gonna contact you anyway.
I have been following
your business for a long time.
I... I didn't actually ask you
here to talk about business.
Wait, I thought you were
gonna ask me to invest.
I am.
But first, I want to talk
a bit about life.
I know what it's like
to want to be successful,
to want to build something
that lasts.
But our work,
no matter how important it is,
must always be in support
of the life we live
and never in sacrifice to it.
I do want you to invest
in pc electric,
but only if it's part
of a life you want to live
and not an excuse to hide from it.
You're not the person
I thought you would be.
I'm not the person
I thought I was.
Life is beautiful, right?
You learn something new every day.
Yeah.
You were right.
I ran some tests
and found the bleed.
And we fixed it.
The surgery was a success.
Oh, that's wonderful, honey.
I wish you could see
all the things I see
when I look at you.
A brave, strong, smart,
kind, generous woman.
I'm sorry I wasn't around for
you when you were growing up,
at least not the way
I needed to be.
None of that was your fault.
You deserved better.
And I am sorry it took me
this long to figure it out.
It's ok.
You're here now.
That's what matters.
I heard there was free
hot chocolate in the cafeteria.
Is that true?
And why have you been keeping
this from me my entire life?
Because I am a mean,
horrible parent,
just like my dad here.
Why don't we all go get a cup?
You know, I have
a couple of final touches
to put on the carnival
for tonight.
Is it ok if you two meet me there?
- Of course.
- Do we have to go.
It's always so boring.
What?
What are you expecting,
some sort of wild and crazy
christmas extravaganza?
Yes.
Well, then.
I guess that's just what
we're gonna have to have.
- He's so silly, huh?
- Yeah.
Ho, ho, ho!
You came.
I'm so happy you're here.
Merry christmas.
Well, the new boss.
- Papa!
- Oh, honey!
This is the best party ever.
Oh, hi.
It's just getting started.
I thought I would never
see the day.
Well, when you realize that
today is the only day you have,
you have to make sure
it's the best possible day
it can be.
Ok, now I really don't know
what to think.
What has gotten into you?
Love!
And maybe a little bit
of that spiked eggnog.
You should try it.
Honey, I think it's time
you finally showed me
that cartwheel.
Ok.
- Ta-da!
- Yeah! All right, well done!
Let's get this party going.
Come on!
Give me a ho, ho, ho!
All: Ho, ho, ho!
- Oh, hive me that ho!
Give me that ho!
Ho, ho, ho!
Santa needs a cocktail.
Can I get a big can
of whipped cream?
Hi.
- Hi.
Hey, listen,
I have been thinking
about what you said,
about what I want from life.
I was gonna buy your company,
then break it into pieces
and sell off the parts,
but I don't think
I want that anymore.
What do you want?
I want to build a life
worth living.
And I think pc electric would
be a good place to start.
I agree.
And when I'm gone...
When I'm retired,
I know that you'll be there
to look after the company.
Thank you.
Oh.
Of course.
Thank you.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
It's good.
- It's good.
- It's pretty good.
- Yeah.
Merry christmas, brian.
Merry christmas, sara.
Wow!
This is quite the party
you've thrown.
I thought you hated christmas.
A man can change.
How about you?
Are you still
that open-hearted girl
I so foolishly walked out on
all those years ago?
Why don't you dance with me
and find out?
Mm.
Do you remember
that christmas I spent
with you and your father?
He and I got into a big fight,
and I stormed out.
Mm-hmm.
Well,
after you left,
we had a long talk.
He told me that he knew
how he was too hard on you,
that he always just wanted
what was best for you.
He told me how proud of you
he was,
how much he loved you.
He loved you.
I loved you.
You didn't love yourself.
I knew it.
I knew you always loved me,
you just never told me.
You're horrible.
I know.
Oh.
Good evening, everyone.
Thanks again for coming.
Just a few short words before...
It's all over.
Pc electric is a family business.
And honestly, I'd...
I'd forgotten about the family
part for quite some time.
You see, I was so busy
trying to live up
to my father's memory
that I'd forgotten
what really matters
is making new ones.
I see it now,
the true meaning of christmas.
Love.
Love of family,
love of friendship,
love of humanity.
After all, christmas celebrates
the birth of a love so great
that it just might save the world.
Gosh, I... I never got that.
You see, in my life,
there was always one person
I could never love:
Myself.
I didn't think
I was worthy of love.
But if I can't love myself,
then the love I give
is worthless.
Not anymore.
So here's my christmas wish.
I wish that all of you
could love yourselves
as much as I love you.
This has been
the best day of my life.
Merry christmas!
Why you gotta go
and make me cry like that?
Wow, you are just full
of surprises today.
Oh, I've got a few more
for you too.
You ready?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
All right, keep your eyes closed.
- Ok.
- Eyes closed.
- Where are we going?
- Where are we?
- Closed. Closed. Closed.
- Come on.
- Keep them closed.
I'll say when.
All right, now...
- Uh-huh.
Open them.
I had a little help from a friend.
- Dad.
- Too much?
Never.
- all right, come on.
Get on in there. Let's go.
What did you do to the inside?
Is it... did you also
put christmas in there?
Oh, wait till you see that.
Here you go.
Oh, boy, look at these.
- Here are the cookies.
- My goodness.
Whoa, whoa, hey,
those are for santa.
Yeah.
Santa and I go way back.
He's not gonna mind.
Now, I want you two
to open these gifts.
- No, it's christmas eve.
We always wait until morning.
New tradition.
I like this new tradition.
That is my dad's tool belt.
That way you'll know
you'll always have the tools
to fix anything in life.
Thank you, papa.
You're welcome.
Your turn.
Ok. Ok.
You remember that music box
I gave you when you were 12?
Yeah, the one I broke?
The one I wouldn't fix.
I wish I could go back in time
and fix it like you asked me to.
I wish I could go
back in time and fix
a lot of things in my life.
But I can't,
so I made you a new one.
- I helped.
- Yes, she did.
I hope that you'll fill this one
with lots of good memories.
Open it.
Our song.
No matter what happens,
I love you.
I love you too.
Me too.
Oh, come here.
Merry christmas.
- Oh.
Now, you had better get to sleep
or santa won't come.
Ok.
Thanks, dad, for everything.
Good night, honey.
See you in the morning.
Merry christmas.
And to all...
A good night.
You figured it out.
I did.
Took me a while.
Oh, it sure did.
Oh, I was running out
of ways to kill you.
There may not be
such a thing as a good death,
but at least now I can say
I lived a good life.
You ready to go?
I am.
Santa?
Yes?
Thanks.
I'm alive.
It's christmas day.
Oh, my...
It's christmas day!
Ah! I'm alive!
Michelle! Harkin!
It's christmas morning! Wake up!
- Oh, my goodness.
- Let's open presents!
Come on!
You know, I don't know
what's gotten into you,
but I'm loving
this new version of you.
Me too.
Big finish.
That's terrible.
This is the best christmas ever.
It is, indeed.
- Yeah.
- Say, why don't we have
a nice cup of hot cocoa?
Oh.
Maybe put
a little irish whiskey in it.
Oh, yes, incredible. Yes.
- Aye.
- Oh, yes, aye.
Wait,
there's one more present.
I'll get that.
That's interesting.
To brian, from santa.
Ok.
Well, huh.
Uh-huh.
Told you I knew him.
What is it, papa?
It's a gift from an old friend.
Read the card.
Yeah.