Oh, my God!
I don't I've ever had anyone
stuck that long in jail.
I'm sorry, Bubba.
Crazy. 10.
She just got doubles.
- Okay.
- 175.
- Mr. Money Bags over here.
- I land on it every time.
- How much?
- I landed on it twice.
Don't you remember
when you were little
when we used to play,
you'd never want your ones?
You'd be like,
"just keep the change."
Like you were some big spender.
That's why he
always used to play banker.
- Yeah, I know.
- We need to gang up on Sean.
Brody, Brody come here.
Brody, come.
Brody, come here.
Oh, no.
Don't buy it,
no, I wanna buy it!
No.
Which one's it go with?
You know what?
Fine, fine.
I'm gonna, if you ever
wanna buy this one...
Alright, what are you thinking?
Yay!
Eight.
Walk up to a butterfly
with a stick.
I know I said something
interesting happened,
but I never really knew that...
Hey, Chatty Cathy.
- Oh yeah.
- It's your turn.
Okay.
Can't tell Mom, this is
just between me and you.
You're getting the good treats.
Good girl.
Hmm.
Morning.
Oh, hey.
You were looking so cozy,
I just let you sleep.
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
I had a really
weird dream, though.
Yeah?
Yeah.
We were in the middle of
the woods and you were
walking ahead of me and
I couldn't see your face,
and I kept trying to catch
up to you, and I couldn't.
And I was calling out your name,
and you wouldn't turn around.
Then I had this overwhelming
sense of letting go.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, you should be, asshole.
Well, I promise I'll be
nicer to you in your dreams.
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
What?
There was something else.
You stopped at one
point and I was finally
able to catch up to you,
and when I did,
I was really afraid.
And I called your
name one more time
and then you turned around
and you turned around and...
I turned around and what?
I woke up.
That's when I woke up.
I'm making breakfast.
- Box came.
- Yeah, want anything?
No, I'm good.
But you know what?
You guys eat, let me know,
I'll come up and sit with you.
Donovans are still
getting a box.
That's good.
Come on, time to get up.
Hey, come on, sleepy ahead.
It's after 10,
daylight's a-wasting.
Sean, time to get up, breakfast.
- What, what?
- It's time to get up.
I been up for a while.
Yeah, sure you have.
I got up at four.
- Okay.
- I went back to...
Sure you did.
Okay, come on, breakfast.
Any bagels?
There's just two, so
you can each have one.
I don't need a whole one.
No, I'm good, and your
father doesn't want one, so.
Thanks, mom.
Cut this now.
Any cereal?
Oh, no, sorry, bub.
Okay.
Not like we have
any milk anyway.
I don't care.
Here, put that under there.
Be careful.
Stephen!
He cut himself.
How bad is it?
Get me a rag.
You're bleeding, oh, my God.
No.
Let me see, let me
see it, let me see it.
You're okay.
Front.
That's a little deep.
How many times have I
told you to be careful?
Especially when using a knife.
- I'm fine, Mom.
- But what if it wasn't?
What if it was worse?
There are no hospitals to go to.
There is nobody to call.
We're on our own.
Do you know what that means?
- Mom.
- Hey, it's okay.
Yes, Mom.
They get it.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to be sorry,
you just need to be careful.
And keep it elevated.
I'll check on it in a minute.
- He's gonna be fine.
- How many times
have we told them
they have to be careful?
Oh, I don't know, a million.
They have to understand,
Stephen.
They do, they understand.
We never should've come here.
You'd rather be back in Boston?
- In that tiny apartment?
- It wasn't that tiny.
We would've been tripping
all over ourselves.
Thank God we've
got the summer house.
At least there are people there.
It's safer with less people.
Is it?
Really?
What if something happened?
What if something really
happened, Stephen?
We would be on our own!
We are on our own.
We would've been
on our own there too.
Mass General was still
operating before we left.
Yeah, but for how long?
Everything was being
shut down, quarantined.
It's safer here.
The less people, the safer.
- Okay, how's it feel?
- It feels better.
Doesn't hurt that bad.
We got the bleeding to stop, so.
Yeah.
Just tape that right there.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Brody.
What you looking at, girl?
What do you see out there?
What are you all
worried about, huh?
Who's a good girl?
Kisses, thank you.
Okay.
You, you're a mental case.
Yes, maybe I am.
Ingratiating bastard.
Do you always play
kiss-ass with the loonies?
No.
I like you,
Kane, you're regular.
Take the medal.
- I'll take this book.
- What book?
"I Remember Mamma"
by Oedipus Rex.
May I go?
You're gone, you're gone.
So far, so good.
So far, very good.
This okay?
As long as I can turn my pages.
Ah, I don't wanna disturb you.
Oh no, it's fine.
Oh, come on, I'm sorry.
I like when you're close.
You're such a liar.
Mm.
What you reading?
Jack Reacher.
Mm, it's any good?
I've read it before.
Do you want to talk?
No, I'm tired.
You go ahead and read.
We can talk.
I am so sorry
about this morning.
Don't be.
That was scary.
Thank God it wasn't
something more serious.
I really worry
about those two boys.
I know, I do too.
No, not just this morning,
I mean...
Stephen,
they're growing up in isolation.
It's not like they were...
My God, don't you remember
the fights we used to get into
trying to get 'em
off their computers?
Used to yell so much.
But they're not
outdoor creatures.
Sean used to love football.
Maybe he will again someday.
Don't say that.
- Say what?
- Someday.
We've been waiting for
that day for so long,
that word has no
meaning for me anymore.
Hey, we're gonna
get through this.
Can't go on forever.
Donovans are still
getting a box.
Yeah.
And people do recover from it.
Before they shut
the internet down,
how many stories
did we read about people
that were just
raving mad one second
and then totally fine the next,
like nothing had happened?
But how do you know it's real?
Don't you ever think about that?
I could have been
sick this whole time.
You could have been
What if it's just a fever dream?
How would you know?
You wouldn't.
What if you're just
strapped to a bed somewhere
in some induced
coma so you don't
hurt yourself or
rip your face off.
And this whole time,
you could think
you're just lying next to me.
How would you know?
Because this feels real to me.
Doesn't this feel real to you?
Look, I know when the days
all bleed one into the other,
you can feel adrift,
but we're here together.
Hey.
Come here, gimme your hand.
Come here.
You feel that?
Do you feel my heart?
Yeah.
That's real.
I love you.
I love you too.
To get to the
What are you doing?
Let's go!
Hi.
Go, team, let's
go, team, let's go, team!
Come on,
bub, it's time to get up.
Rise and shine, sleepyhead.
Wow.
I know, I didn't think the seeds
from last year
were gonna sprout.
It's crazy.
You wanna help?
Not if we want 'em to live.
Aw, come on, it's easy.
I killed a cactus once.
I can't be trusted.
Well, at least you can
keep me company, right?
I can do that.
They're early.
Go get the boys, I'll get her.
Brody, Brody, Brody.
Brody, come. Brody, come on.
Brody, come on!
Hello?
Hello, hello, yeah, we're here.
Wyatt, Wyatt, it's the call.
Whitton family, M-A-6-3-9-6-4.
Sean?
Sean, it's the call.
Wyatt Whitton,
identification W-W-3-9-4-7-2.
This Anna Whitton,
identification A-W-3-9-4-7-1.
Sean Witten, S-W-3-9-4-7-3.
I didn't get the beep.
I didn't get a beep.
Identification, you didn't say...
Sean Whitton,
identification S-W-3-9-4-7-3.
We've been asking for
shoes for both boys,
size nine and 10.
- Didn't stay on the line.
- It's okay, Dad.
Yeah, it's okay.
We'll get by.
It's been five weeks.
We ask for movies,
they send movies.
Just needs shoes.
It's okay, we'll get 'em.
It's not like we're
going anywhere.
Such bullshit.
Okay, so we are still
on the battle of Gettysburg.
Wyatt, can you read the end of
the Gettysburg Address there?
"We here highly
resolve that these dead
shall not have died in vain,
that this nation under God
shall have a new
birth of freedom,
and that government of
the people, by the people,
for the people shall not
perish from this Earth."
Which makes you
a murderer, don't it?
Palmer now.
This is pure nonsense.
It doesn't prove a thing.
I thought you'd
feel that way, Garry.
You were the only one that
could have got to that blood.
We'll do you last.
That was not funny.
It's a little funny.
Blast him!
There's so much emptiness.
Kill him now.
I don't like...
Kill him.
- Shh, the kids.
- I know.
- Oh, my God. Is that bacon?
- Yes.
- Do you want some?
I'd eat that raw.
It was a really good box.
Yeah?
What else is in there?
Do you wanna know or do
you want me to surprise you?
You know, I actually
have to think about that.
I'll tell you one thing.
One of your favorite
things is in there.
Okay, that's not fair.
I like driving you crazy.
Drove me crazy last night.
You know,
you might as well tell me.
You are anyway, you're
terrible at keeping secrets.
I am not.
- Yes I am.
- Okay.
- Tell me this.
- Mm-hmm.
Is there sushi in that box?
No, there is not
sushi in the box.
'Cause that would
be fucking awesome.
Sushi in a box?
Ben to box.
Okay, you're gonna
be like, what?
But you know what I
would kill for right now?
A fucking Whopper.
- What?
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
An original chicken
sandwich from Burger King.
Yeah.
- That's disgusting.
- Oh, no.
It's like this
laboratory-created perfect disc
of like crunchy,
greasy yumminess
that you just have
to eat right there
in your car in the parking lot.
Drive-throughs.
Hey, why don't you
go get the kids up?
Yeah.
She's getting so old.
She's a good girl.
She's gonna die in this
house before this ends.
Just like Hooper.
And we're already
here to bury her.
There's no work to miss,
no school to skip,
no life to go back to.
It'll just be something
to mark the time.
Some stray detail while we wait.
Hey.
That's my good girl.
Yeah, that's my good girl.
What's the matter?
Wyatt?
- Wyatt?
- Yeah?
How long have you been in there?
About a couple minutes.
Did you set your timer?
'Course I did.
- Five minutes.
- I know.
No, five minutes,
not a minute longer.
Four and a half to be safe.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Fine.
Okay, wait, what is this guy?
Get the milk.
I've never heard you
guys do this one before.
It's not like we can access
it anymore, we're trying.
Hey Wyatt, do you remember the?
Has anyone seen the dog?
- What is he gonna do?
- Stop it.
No.
You guys are being too silly
things that they do.
Has anybody seen the dog?!
- Sorry, I can't find Brody.
- She's not on the deck?
- I don't see her.
- Is the gate closed?
Yeah, gates' closed.
And she's not out there?
Brody!
Come on, girl.
Brody, come!
Brody!
- Ah ha.
- Wow!
How did you beat that?
With that crappy roll.
Dad, Northwest
territory attacks Alberta.
Dad.
It's your turn.
I'm sorry.
We don't have to play
if you don't want to.
No, no, no.
It's fine.
She'll come back.
You're never
gonna love me again?
I don't even wanna look at you.
Why?
I don't like my bread!
- I'm just spinning.
- Oh yeah!
She's gone.
She could come back.
She's had us worried before.
Not like this.
This is different.
It's okay.
Why would she run off?
Because she could.
Holy shit.
And turned the bed around
so the next time
when the alarm went off,
it flew into the wall.
He was so fucking mad.
He was like, "I'll kill
everybody in this room!"
Hey, what are you guys watching?
Oh, oh, oh no, busted.
Definitely,
definitely can't go that way.
Oh my.
What are you guys doing?
- It's called laughing.
- They're drunk.
Wait, how?
Well, sometimes the gods,
they favour the brave,
and they send down
from the heavens...
Actually, we got this.
We got this in the box.
Is that whiskey?
How do you know that?
It's Irish whiskey.
This is your birthright.
Do you want some?
- Yeah.
- No, Stephen.
What?
He's 100% Irish.
He should have
some Irish whiskey.
Okay, he's 92% Irish,
and then he's 8% Viking.
We're part Viking?
Yeah, the parts that
raped and pillaged
their way through Ireland.
- Stephen!
- Jeez, Dad.
What?
- It's history.
- Okay, fine.
Just get two glasses
and I'll pour you...
Wait, so what is it?
It's actually pretty
decent bottle of hooch.
It's booze.
How does it taste?
Well, it tastes a
little bit like heaven
and a little bit like hell.
Okay.
- Mom!
- Mom.
That's plenty.
All right, here goes.
Oh bubba, I'm so sorry.
Can I have some more?
No, thank you.
- You okay?
- I hate whiskey.
It likes you.
It does.
Yep.
I can't pour.
My pour spell is broken.
My God, have I ever
told you guys the story
- about how I met your mom?
- Yes.
Okay, fine.
It's only the story of
how you got to be here.
So, you know, never mind.
Oh, my God, I did not like
you when I first met you.
I didn't even notice you.
You were so full of yourself!
Oh, and he tried
so hard to be noticed.
Oh, my God.
And then you did that thing.
- I did, I did that thing.
- Yes, you did that thing.
Imagine if you hadn't
done that thing.
I would be who knows
where with who knows who.
My God, and I'd be
right there with you,
except totally without you.
Aww.
- Cheers to family, guys.
- Oh, cheers.
Love you guys.
- Cheers.
Yeah.
- It's raining.
- Terrific.
Please tell me there's a
fucking aspirin in there.
Can you go get the kids up?
Yeah.
Come on, Wyatt, time to get up.
- What was that?
- What?
What'd you just
shove under there?
Nothing.
- I'm gonna take a look.
- Dad, it's nothing.
- Wyatt.
- Wait, no, Dad.
- What the fuck was that?
- I can explain.
What the fuck was that?
What is it?
It's okay,
really, I can explain.
- Stop talking!
- Stephen!
- It's okay!
- He was online!
He's fucking chatting
with somebody, right?
- You're online?
- Oh, my God.
- Mom.
- What did he do?
- He's got his phone.
- He has his what?
Mom, come on!
Did you go into the safe?
Did you break into the safe?
- Yes.
- Are you insane?
Mom, it's not that big a deal.
Just let me explain.
My God, will you stop talking?
Who was that?
Who were you just chatting with?
- Well?
- You told me to stop talking.
Don't be a fucking smart ass.
Who was that?
- It was just a friend.
- From where?
She's from Chicago.
- Wyatt.
- Shut up, Sean.
I'm sure
you know all about this.
- I didn't know.
- Oh, tell me the truth.
Do you have your phone too?
- No.
- Don't lie to us.
Yes.
- We're both online.
- Sean!
- They need to know.
- God dammit, shit!
We're talking to people
all over the world.
There's thousands of us.
What, how?
Like network set
up all over the place.
You guys wouldn't
know about that.
That's how it gets in here!
- Dad!
- Shut up.
Do you know what you've done?
Do know what kind of
danger you've put us in?
- It's fine.
- Oh, it's fine.
Yeah, 'cause no one
even thinks it's real.
Oh, it's not real, huh?
Why don't tell that
to your grandfather.
You know what?
Tell it to my friend
Charlie Bishop, okay?
Go tell him.
- 'Cause I watched him die.
- It's different now.
These are like
3G networks at best.
Just so we can
talk to each other.
I can't listen to this anymore.
There's thousands of
people communicating.
They have been for months.
And how long have
you been doing it?
Just a little while.
- How long?
- A week.
- 10 days.
- Why didn't you tell us?
Because of this.
We knew you'd freak out.
There's whole parts
of the country
- back up and running again.
- Don't listen to this.
Jennifer goes to a
school, an actual school.
You can't listen to this.
He could be infected already.
We could all be infected by now!
Have you seen it?
Have you seen the schools
and these cities
back up and running?
My friend Noah video
chatted me the other day
from a coffee shop.
There were people in
the background ordering.
But if you were infected,
how would you know that's real?
That's what this does!
Don't you understand?
It steals reality
right out from under you
and traps you in
this virtual version
that looks and feels
and sounds and smells
just like the real thing,
but it's not!
In reality,
you're some ravaged skeleton
strapped to a
fucking hospital bed.
Dad, we're fine.
You can see I'm fine, right?
But I could already be infected.
You've opened the door.
You've let this in.
Stephen, what if it's true?
- I want your phone.
- Dad, please!
Give it to me!
- And yours too.
- I don't have a phone.
Whatever it is that
you're going online with,
I want it and I want it now.
- Dad, please just listen-
- Go get it!
What about your computers?
- Can you get online with these?
- No.
If you're fucking lying to me.
I'm not lying.
That's it.
My iPad?
Sorry.
What about your computer?
That's it.
- Please listen, Stephen...
- Don't say it.
Don't say it, 'cause I
know what you're gonna say.
Stephen, please. Please.
Stephen.
What if it's true?
Standard monitoring protocol.
It's gonna start with
a rash behind the ears
- and the back of the neck.
- Stephen, please listen to me.
You didn't see how they died!
You didn't see how they
fucking looked at me
before they tried
to rip their eyes
out of their fucking skulls.
Stephen, calm down.
Just take a couple deep breaths.
We both saw that text.
That person was real.
Yeah, but I could be infected.
How long has this been going on?
They say a week, but it
had to be longer, right?
I mean, they've been doing
this behind our back.
- You know what, fuck this.
- No, don't!
Come on, Stephen, we
have talked about this.
We always said that
if the powers that be
wanted to take full control,
that this is how
they would do it.
Maybe, just maybe, this
has been over for months,
and we're stranded out
here, we have no idea
what's going on,
how would we know?
Control of what?
We're just sitting here.
Everything's delivered.
Nothing's asked of us.
I mean, we're not enslaved,
we're just waiting.
We're not enslaved?
Stephen, I have a chip
in the back of my neck.
So do you,
we can't leave this place.
So we stay safe
until they figure out
how to fight this thing.
Nobody's figuring out anything!
Or they already have, and
just like the kids said,
we are just stupid for
going along with this.
Okay, all right, if this
is some big master plan,
what's the point?
I mean,
what are they taking from us?
Everything.
Maybe it's just control.
Maybe that's all they want,
because they can do it.
Or what if they're just
building an infrastructure
that they need and
we're just holding on
until they do it for
some new world order.
God knows,
I don't know what it is,
but please,
Stephen, listen to me.
I have an idea, please.
Please.
Anna.
Please listen to me, listen.
Okay.
We take the devices
and we hide them
where they won't find them.
Okay, and then we'll do
the monitoring protocol
just like you said.
It's a week, six days.
And if none of us show signs,
then you and I go online,
or just one of us so that the
other one can stay safe, okay?
See what's really there.
Find out what the
hell is really going on.
Just one time.
And then we'll do
the monitoring protocol
for the person who went
online, and if we're all okay,
and if we stay safe,
then we'll know, right?
We'll know.
Things are starting
to get back to normal.
We need to know.
Please, Stephen.
Promise.
I won't.
This is so dangerous,
what we're about to do.
You know that, right?
- Oh, my God, that was the...?
- Surprise.
Holy shit.
Now I know it's not an
original chicken sandwich, but.
I do not care.
- Love you guys.
- Love you too.
I love this burger.
Hey, not too late.
Okay.
- Good night.
I love you.
I love you too.
Do you wanna see
what I'm building?
I'm tired, Bub.
You wanna show me tomorrow?
- Sure.
- Okay.
I'm excited to see it.
- Night.
- Night, Mom.
Not too late, okay?
I'm pretty tired.
- Seriously.
- I know.
Dinner was awesome.
I'm glad you liked it.
It was true.
What we said before.
Well, we'll figure it out, okay?
I just don't wanna talk
about it right now.
Yeah.
You sound really good.
Thank you.
- Night.
- Good night.
What day is it today?
- Thursday.
- Do you know the date?
I don't know the date.
I don't know the date either.
Me either.
What did you have
for dinner last night?
Burger and fries.
Can you recall one
detail about the dinner?
You and Dad were smiling.
Who gave the Gettysburg Address?
Lincoln.
Count backwards from 10 to one.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
- What day is it?
- Thursday.
Who gave the Gettysburg Address?
Lincoln.
Count backwards from 10 to one.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
- Six.
- Five.
Four.
Three.
Sorry, two.
One.
Zero.
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
I got this weird ingrown
hair on the back of my neck.
Well, jeez, I hope you live.
Oh, I think I can soldier on.
I'm going up.
You coming?
No, I think I'm
gonna have a drink.
Feel like having a drink.
Do you want one?
No, I'm tired.
We could get drunk, fool around.
I will definitely
take a rain check.
Okay.
I'll be up in a minute.
Come tuck me in.
You know, you won't be asleep
by the time I get up there.
Just a night cap.
All right.
Well, don't be long.
I won't.
Steve?
Shh.
I hear the dog.
I think she's out in the woods.
What, what?
What's happening?
Gotta go check.
Go back to sleep.
You know, I could come
with you, if you like.
No, not yet.
Okay.
Hmm.
Mom?
Hey Bubba.
You okay?
I can't find your father.
Well, it's been a while now.
What?
Don't you remember?
Remember what?
Dad's gone.
He's dead.
It's been six months.
Why would you say that?
Because it's true.
Remember?
That's why we're here.
He started acting
really strange.
He started forgetting things,
he started
wandering around
the apartment at night.
He took apart the
kitchen shelves.
You called the hospital and
they came and took him away.
We haven't seen him since.
You brought us here
because you thought
it was safer than Boston.
- To see if we'd show signs.
- Monitoring protocol.
You remember, right?
Yeah.
Do you know what day it is?
Tuesday.
I'm worried about you.
Do you need anything, Mom?
I need your dad.
What?
I just feel bad.
No, I'm okay, I'm good.
Okay.
Mom?
- Mom?
- Yeah.
47 is the answer, right?
47, that's really good, Wyatt.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm just feeling a
little tired, that's all.
We can do
this later if you want.
Yeah, I think I'll...
Yeah, I think I'm
gonna go take a nap.
You hungry?
Can I make you some lunch?
- I'm okay.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay.
- Don't come any closer.
- I'm not, I'm not.
I'm standing right here.
- Do you have any antibiotics?
- What?
Antibiotics.
No, we don't have
any antibiotics.
I need...
My boy.
I left to get
antibiotics, right?
That's why I left.
No, we don't have anything.
You're the one with the dog?
What?
Yeah, I hear him sometimes,
far off.
I haven't heard him in a while.
I'm sorry.
I can't remember the last time
I've spoken to someone else.
We don't have anything
that we can spare.
How did you get out?
I can set you free too.
Quick, you won't feel anything,
I promise.
Stephen!
- Stephen!
- Hey!
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
God bless.
Stay safe.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on.
Hey, Bub.
- Hey.
Do you wanna see
what I'm building?
Sure.
Okay. Well it's
mostly finished by now,
but this was just some
random thing I came up with.
One thing I'm most proud
of is that the cockpit
comes out, like here,
like you can open this,
and you can slide
the cockpit like this,
and you can get the pilot
out, but you can also...
Stephen!
Stephen?
Stephen.
Stephen!
Hello!
Yes, we are here.
This is the Witten family.
M-A-6-3-9-6-4.
This is Anna Witten,
identification A-W-3-9-4-7-1.
The others are here.
Please, please wait.
Sean.
Sean, it's the call.
Sean?
Wyatt.
Wyatt?
Sean Witten,
identification S-W-3-9-4-7-3.
Where's Wyatt?
Why are you hanging up?
We need to get your
brother and your father.
We're not gonna have
enough food. Hello?
- It's just us.
- Hello?
It's just us, Mom.
Why did you hang up the phone?
They're here in
this house somewhere.
They are somewhere here.
Mom, you're scaring me.
Did you do this?
What?
Just tell me what's going on.
There's nothing going on.
It's just been us for months.
You're lying.
- Why are you lying?
- Mom.
What day is it?
No, I remember.
I remember...
With your father, I was
playing a game, and Wyatt.
Wyatt.
He was showing me his building,
he was building Legos.
If you try to remember,
if you try and fight it,
that helps.
They say that if you try
to hold onto something
that feels real to you,
you can beat it.
Are you real?
Yes, Mom.
And Wyatt and Dad...
You weren't feeling well.
You couldn't tell
if you were stressed
or if you were getting
sick, so we came down
to the summer home.
You made me drive, remember?
I was afraid to, but you
guided me the whole way.
You remember that?
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember.
It's just been us.
I'm so sorry.
Why are you sorry?
Because I...
Have I paid enough
attention to you?
Yeah.
Mom, God, yes.
I'm fine.
I love you.
I love you too.
You okay?
Could watch a movie or
play a game or something.
No...
I'm okay, it's okay.
Okay.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna
go lay down for a minute.
Okay.
I'll cook you dinner soon.
We have a lot of
nice things for dinner.
Okay.
Call you in a bit.
Just leaves us three.
Mr. Clayton, I think
we should take a break
for five minutes.
Tempers seem to be
running a little high.
Aw, come on a minute, I was
just starting to do good.
Hello?
Anybody there?
All right, I'm gonna sign off.
Anna?
Stephen.
Anna, where are you?
- Are you at the hospital?
- No, I'm here.
I'm at the summer house.
Where are you?
The summer house.
We're at the summer house.
Where are you?
I'm here.
I'm at the summer house.
I don't understand. We're here.
Me and the boys, we're here
at the summer house.
Where are you?
Are you okay?
Is this some kind of joke?
Wyatt!
- Wyatt!
- Stephen.
Wyatt, did you do
something to the computer?
Stephen.
- Well, come look at this!
- Stephen!
He's coming,
just hang on one second.
I love you.
This doesn't make any sense.
You're supposed to be...
Where are you calling from?
- I love you.
- No, no, no, wait, wait.
Everything's okay here.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Stephen!
Oh, my God.
What's happening...
Fuck you.
Wyatt.
Wyatt?
Honey, honey.
Wyatt.
Honey?
You're not real.
I remember.
We're right here.
I remember!
Hold on,
gimme a second, I gotta get on.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey, there she is.
How you feel, baby?
Hey Mom.
But yeah, no, so he's gonna say,
I don't know what you're saying.
I can't, Wyatt can
probably explain it better.
- Hey, Wyatt.
- Wyatt!
You look like you're
feeling better.
The doctor said was
gonna be tough to talk
for a couple of days.
Was thinking about
steaks tonight.
What do you think about steaks?