[SCANNER BEEPING]
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
[CLERK] Road trip?
[WOMAN] No, moving.
[CARD MACHINE SQUAWKS]
Your card's been declined.
Okay.
[WOMAN SIGHS]
Let's try this one.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
[EXHALES]
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[EXHALES]
[SOFTLY] Jake, baby, please help me.
Come on. Come on.
Okay.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[HORN HONKS]
Oh, did I scare you?
Text me.
[GIRL] Yeah.
Bye.
Just so you know, you're ruining my life.
Well, thank you for sharing.
Where's your uncle?
I don't know.
The string I tied to him broke.
Chill with the smart mouth, okay?
[LOUD RAP MUSIC PLAYING]
Whoo! Told you.
Right on time. Y'all ready?
Come on. Let's ride.
Let's make some miles.
- What y'all waiting on?
- Where you been?
I was just saying
some last-minute goodbyes.
Really? 'Cause you smell
like you've been smoking weed.
What? You tripping.
That's my new body spray.
- Turn out your pocket.
- Hey!
What is this? TSA?
Come on. I ain't getting on no plane.
And body search is a violation
of my basic human rights.
Reggie, you promised.
No drugs and no weed for the entire trip.
And I intend to honor that pledge.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I do.
You better.
Entire trip?
Entire.
Entire trip.
Good thing the trip ain't started yet.
[GAME SOUND EFFECTS PLAYING]
[BOY] Boo!
Cameron, the train's leaving
the station in two minutes.
- I'm not going.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
I guess you're moving in
with the next family that lives here?
What if they don't like
stinky-head boy smell?
I'll sleep in Dad's bed.
They're picking it up in 20 minutes.
Whatever.
[GAME SOUND EFFECTS PLAYING]
Come on, little man. We got to go.
Yo, Reg.
- Hey.
- Come on, just give me a hit.
Now what kind of uncle shares
a joint with his teenage niece?
The kind sitting right in front of me.
One and done.
Thank you.
Puff and pass.
[REGGIE SIGHS]
I assume you're bringing a back-up supply.
[SCOFFS] No, it's my last jay
until we get to Houston.
Promised your mom.
You, being a man of your word?
Don't be giving me no attitude, okay?
And don't be giving it to your mom.
Why? It's her fault we have to move.
Nah. Nah. Listen, shit happens, Kelly.
Ever since your dad died,
your mom's been doing everything
in her power to hold this family together.
She's paying for all this...
It just got to be too much.
Nothing feels right without him.
I know.
["TELEPORT" PLAYING]
[EXHALES]
♪ Might not be there by your side ♪
♪ Or with you in the morning ♪
[FAINT CHATTER AND LAUGHTER]
♪ I wish that I could drive ♪
♪ 'Cause I'd head straight for you ♪
♪ If I could teleport
Teleport ♪
♪ If I could teleport ♪
♪ I'd be with you tonight ♪
♪ I wish you could touch my skin ♪
[FAINT LAUGHTER]
♪ My body's yearning for your feelings ♪
♪ If I could leave it all
Leave it all ♪
♪ If I could leave it all... ♪
[CELLPHONE BUZZING]
- Hey, Ma.
- Hey, baby. How you doing?
- Y'all on the road yet?
- No, not yet. Just, um...
taking one last look around the house
before we go.
- How long's the drive?
- Three days.
I figured two nights on the road.
Be at your place, uh, probably by Friday.
Call me if you need anything.
- Yeah, I'll call you on the way.
- Travel safe.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I love you.
- Yeah, I love you too.
- Bye, baby.
Bye.
[CAR HONKS]
Cam, come on!
Get your scrawny butt out here.
Now, we not stopping
between here and Arizona.
- So if you got to go, now is the time.
- Mom, can we just leave?
Come on, you know the drill.
Come on, y'all. Come on.
Bring it in, let's get together.
Do we have to?
If you don't act like family,
I will leave you behind.
Promise?
Come on.
Don't. Don't. Don't.
[SIGHS] Heavenly Father...
please bless and protect us on our journey
to our new life.
In your name, we pray. Amen.
- Amen.
Amen. Amen.
Do we have to go?
Yes.
["WHERE DO WE GO FROM HERE" PLAYING]
♪ We're at the crossroads, my dear ♪
♪ Where do we go from here? ♪
♪ Maybe you won't go, maybe you'll stay ♪
♪ Oh, I know ♪
♪ I'm gonna miss you either way ♪
♪ It's such a lonely road ♪
♪ Where do we go from here? ♪
♪ We go ♪
♪ All I can do is ♪
♪ Follow the tracks of my tears ♪
♪ Follow the tracks ♪
♪ Tears ♪
♪ Oh! When I cry your name ♪
♪ Am I callin' in vain? ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Where do we go from here? ♪
♪ Maybe you won't go, maybe you'll stay ♪
♪ All I can do is ♪
♪ Follow the tracks of my tears ♪
♪ Follow either way ♪
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[HELICOPTER APPROACHING]
Please tell Señor Cross
we are grateful for his assistance.
[HELICOPTER TAKES OFF]
[LAUGHING]
Mr. Cross will be happy to see this.
We take all the risk,
Mr. Cross gets to keep all the profit.
Seem fair to you?
You don't like the arrangement,
talk to Mr. Cross.
Otherwise, shut the fuck up, bro.
[LAUGHING]
Whoo!
[GUN COCKS]
You do this and you're a dead man.
Mr. Cross gonna...
Fuck Mr. Cross.
[R&AMP;B SONG PLAYING ON CAR STEREO]
[SNORING]
[GAME SOUND EFFECTS PLAYING]
Yo.
What? Police? Where we at?
- Are we there?
- Mom, what's wrong?
Nobody has said a word
in three and a half hours.
Oh, hell no.
Okay, and?
And I was hoping
we could be like other families
and converse. You know, talk.
- [SCOFFS] No.
- Why?
Because that's what families do
on car trips.
Yeah, I know, right? It's crazy.
But people joke, they sing songs. They...
play car games.
No, that's what they do in the movies.
Yeah, uh, Mom, I think
you've mistaken this for 1983.
That's it. Everybody put
your phones away. I'm serious.
God! Mom...
Really?
Let me explain. That phone?
It's a privilege, Kelly.
Don't give me a reason to take it away.
Fine.
[WOMAN] Okay.
Let's have a conv...
I'm sorry. My bad.
Who wants to go first?
Okay, I'll start.
There you go, my man. All right, go, Cam.
[CLEARS THROAT]
My declarative statement is
moving to Texas sucks.
[LAUGHS] I agree. Look at that!
End of conversation, right?
- That's right.
- [WOMAN] You got that. Whatever.
Bunch of lightweights.
You know how many times
I had to move growing up?
- [CAM, KELLY, REGGIE] 27.
- 27 different military bases in 17 years.
Yes, Mom, we know.
- Your dad was an army colonel.
- [WOMAN] But he was a great dad.
He taught us how to hunt, how to shoot,
how to fight, and when not to.
All facts.
- Especially for you.
- [REGGIE CHUCKLES]
Hey, look. I know how you feel.
Whenever my dad asked us to move,
I got angry too.
Question is,
do any Black people live in Houston
or will it just be us?
Do any Black people live in Houston? What?
You ain't heard of Megan Thee Stallion?
Yes, you have. I know you have.
- How about Destiny's Child?
- Who was they?
- Willie D!
- Scarface.
Scarface, see? Geto Boys.
- I don't know them.
- Come on.
Who are those people?
- You need to study hip-hop. Anyway...
- Too young for that.
There are a lot
of Black people in Houston.
Whoa, hey. Wait, wait, wait.
Sis, sis. Eyes ahead. Eyes ahead.
Slow down. Slow down.
Okay. What is this?
[REGGIE] Looks like a detour.
- Ah, what the hell is this?
- [WORKER] Slow down, please.
"Detour, next 85 miles."
[WORKER] Go over by the shoulder.
This is gonna cost us some time.
[REGGIE] Knew I should a brought my weed.
[R&AMP;B MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
This is some serious Area 51 shit
out here.
Y'all know what happens next, right?
The car's gonna stall out,
then we'll get hit by a tractor beam,
and lifted up in a UFO.
Oh, my God.
Next, we'll be strapped down
on our stomachs
with big-eyed aliens probing our ass.
- They won't do that to you, Uncle Reggie.
- Why not?
'Cause the aliens only want
to study intelligent life-forms.
- Hear what I'm saying?
- Ooh! Burn!
You know what? Because you're my nephew,
I'll let that slide.
Bren, he's too smart for his own good.
- What you gonna do with this brain power?
- Tell me about it.
Intelligence can be
such a burden sometimes.
Yeah. Especially to the people around you.
[REGGIE] Wait, wait, wait.
Is this Throw Shade at Reggie Day?
Y'all ganging up on me.
- No, sir.
- Listen.
That's it.
No more Snickers for none of y'all.
- Hey!
- [CAM] I'm sorry!
- [REGGIE] No. Hell nah.
- [KELLY] Listen.
- No.
- You know we love you. Okay?
- You're our teddy bear.
- Get off. Get off me.
Whatever. I just ain't lived up
to my full potential yet.
One day, I'm going
to surprise every damn body.
[SCOFFS]
Even myself.
[COUNTRY ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNORING]
[CLERK] You get
detoured off the interstate?
- Mmm-hmm.
- [CARD MACHINE BEEPING]
[CLERK] You intend to stop
and stay around here?
[CARD MACHINE SIGNALS]
Why, is that a problem?
No, ma'am, not for me.
[TOILET FLUSHING]
- Hey, Mom, can I have a Red Bull?
- No. We're leaving.
What? Why?
What is the rush?
Mom! How many dead bugs
did I find on the windshield? Guess.
Oh! Just... throw that away.
Go get in the car right now.
[WHISTLES SUGGESTIVELY]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[SPITS]
[R&AMP;B MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
What the hell?
Bitch!
- Reggie, wake up.
- [MAN 1] Open up, I'm right here.
Pull over. Come on, get out.
Sis, what you do
to piss the good old boys off, huh?
Eyes forward, just ignore 'em.
...like you can't see me. I'm right here.
- What do they want?
- I don't know.
[REGGIE] Don't worry.
[HONKING INSISTENTLY]
- [GASPS]
- [CAM] Whoa!
- [KELLY] You're kidding me.
- What the hell?
[LAUGHING]
- It's my fault, I'm sorry.
- What are you talking about?
They were... They were hitting on me
at the gas station and being nasty,
so I gave 'em the finger.
Girl, are you stupid?
Why would you do that?
Didn't you see where we were?
[HONKING]
[REGGIE] Hey!
[KELLY] Ow!
[REGGIE] I swear to God...
[MAN 1] Bitch!
They're gone, it's fine.
Kelly, don't you ever do that again.
- I know.
- It's a different world out here.
Okay, okay, I know.
Sorry.
Oh, hell no.
[BRAKES SQUEALING]
Mom, what's going on?
I don't know,
but we're not waiting to find out.
[REGGIE] Oh, they playing games.
Move, damn it!
Ah, shit. Yeah, we in it now.
Reggie, stay in the car.
Hell, I won't stay in the car and let
these lanky-ass white boys start shit.
- Please, let me handle it.
- Hell no.
There's not a lot I do well,
but this, I do damn well.
No! You explode, then they react?
Then what's gonna happen to my...
Please. I can't take that risk.
Please.
[REVVING ENGINE]
You want me to call 911?
[SIGHS] No. No.
Your mom is going to handle it.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Please move your truck,
and let us go by.
You could a killed us, lady.
You endangered our lives.
- Oh, hell no.
- Reggie.
[SIGHS]
Okay, boys. You've had your fun.
Now what do I have to do
to get you to move that truck?
Apology'd be nice.
Okay, fine.
I apologize.
We good?
You can't just say it.
You got to mean it.
Unless you want us
to make your whole family apologize.
- Don't you come near my family.
- Then say it like you mean it.
I apologize...
for endangering your lives.
Our white lives.
- Your white...
- Louder.
I apologize...
for endangering...
your white lives.
[MAN 1] Apology accepted.
[MAN 2] See how easy that was?
[MEN LAUGHING]
Oh, lady, you know
we was just fucking with you.
[MEN WHOOPING]
[HONKING]
[SIGHS]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[DOOR OPENS]
What, Reggie, you got something to say?
You got a comment now that it's all over?
Nah, I'm good.
Anybody else?
- Uh, Mom...
- What?
We can make it to Tucson by seven o'clock.
Tuscon?
Yeah, it's two hours and ten minutes.
[SIGHS]
I'll find us a motel.
Cheapest one.
We on a budget.
[KELLY] You all right?
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- Mmm.
- Mmm-hmm.
Yeah.
- What you know about this?
- [KELLY] I like this song.
- Mom?
- Mmm-hmm?
Those guys today,
were they going to hurt us?
I don't think so.
They were mean, stupid white boys
doing what mean, stupid white boys do.
Are we homeless people?
What?
'Cause technically, we don't have a home.
[SIGHS] Listen, little man.
It's not your job
to worry about things like that.
It's your job to be a kid
and it's my job to be your mom,
and make sure that you and your sister
are taken care of. Okay?
Will we ever have a home again?
We will.
But, you know, a house ain't a home.
Home is us.
You, Kelly, Reggie, me.
As long as we're together,
none of us are ever homeless.
[VOICE BREAKING] I miss Dad.
Hey, come here.
I know. Come on.
Come here, son.
It's okay, it's all right. I know.
We all miss him too.
It's all right.
[MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING]
[SIGHS] I hate this.
Can I just sleep in the car or something?
No.
Why? Look, this room is ugly
and there's zero privacy.
- She wants to Face Time Zac and be kissy.
- Shut it, pipsqueak.
- Mom, she called me a pipsqueak.
- Yeah, you are.
You're, like, half the size
you should be at your age.
- You too!
- You're smaller than me!
Okay, enough!
- Chubby cheeks.
- No, I'm not!
Y'all are getting on my last nerve.
- [TOILET FLUSHING]
- Whoo!
Family announcement.
Nobody, I mean, nobody go in that bathroom
for at least two hours.
Probably smart to wear a Hazmat suit too.
Just a fair warning.
[SIGHS] Do I look lighter?
You know what?
Everybody just get some sleep.
We got a long day ahead of us
on the road tomorrow.
Yeah, like I'll sleep
when Reggie starts snoring.
- Hey! You know I don't snore.
- And Kim Kardashian's butt is real.
Uncle Reggie, on the Richter scale,
you're an 8.5.
- You know y'all are adopted, right?
- What?
- Okay, enough.
- [SCOFFS]
Get some sleep.
- Good night.
- G'night.
[SNORING DRAMATICALLY]
What the...
- You fools!
- Oh, oh, oh!
- [KELLY] No. No!
- [BRENDA LAUGHS]
Oh, we throwing stuff?
You want some too, sis?
What?
You don't want none of this.
You want some?
Hey, chill.
[LOUD BANGING ON WALL]
[WHISPERS] Shh! Uh-oh.
Okay, let's just go back to sleep.
- [CAM] Okay.
- We don't want to get kicked out.
- Here.
- You gonna get it now.
[CAM SNICKERS]
- Boy, if you don't go to sleep...
- Okay.
[SNORING]
[MUFFLED THUDS]
Mom, what was that?
That sounded like it came from next door.
- [THUD]
- [MUFFLED SHOUTING]
What the hell is going on?
Somebody throwing a party or something?
- It's four in the morning, Reg.
- That's when the best parties get started.
- No, no, no, this sounds like a fight.
- What?
I'm calling the front office.
[LOUD THUD]
- That definitely ain't no party.
- [CAM] I'm scared.
I'm not letting this go on.
- What?
- Mom, please don't go out there.
I'm a ER nurse. For all we know,
some woman is getting beat by a man.
- You gonna get caught in the middle?
- [MUFFLED SHOUTING]
- Mom, no.
- Sis...
[GUNSHOT]
- The fuck?
- [DOOR OPENING NEXT DOOR]
- [CAM] Mom?
- [GASPS]
- Mom, who is that?
- Shh!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[DOORKNOB RATTLING]
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES, ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[SOFTLY] Sounds like he's gone.
I know a gunshot when I hear one.
That was definitely a gunshot.
- Somebody could be dead in there.
- I better check.
Cam, stay here.
- But...
- [KELLY] Stay here.
[SOFT GRUNTING]
[GURGLING]
Damn.
Kelly, call 911. There's a man
with a gunshot wound to the throat.
- What?
- Keep your brother in that room!
Bren, wait! Be careful.
No time, he's gonna bleed out.
Sir? Sir, I'm a nurse.
My name is Brenda, I'm gonna help you.
[WHEEZING]
It's okay. It's okay.
Reg, go to the bathroom,
get me some more towels.
Now!
Just stay calm.
I've called 911.
Help is on the way. I'll take care of you.
- Hurry up, Reggie! Just hold on.
- [GASPING]
All right, just hang on. Hang on. Hang on!
Sir, you're going to be okay.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
Look at me! Look at me, sir.
Come on. Hang on!
Damn.
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFLES]
Jake, please.
Please help me through this.
[SNIFFLES] I need you.
[SIGHS]
[POLICE SIRENS WAILING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR STEREO]
[OFFICER] Captain Hammers, sir.
Son.
We haven't touched anything.
We waited for you.
Okay, then,
let's see what we got.
[OFFICER] The witnesses next door
reported a fight.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
Harvey Ruck.
Enforcer and bag man for Mr. Cross.
An informant of mine says that Ruck
and his partner Pepe Ochoa
were supposed to deliver a payoff
to Mr. Cross from the Sinaloa Cartel.
Looks like Ruck went independent,
canceled Pepe's ticket.
Took off with the loot.
Do you think the cartel caught him?
We didn't find any money.
[HAMMERS] Reasonable assumption,
or Cross did it.
Man's had his hand in every dirty deal
that ever went down
in this part of the world.
I've been chasing
that slippery son of a bitch for years.
I'll bring him down.
Just a matter of time.
Used a nine millimeter.
I want to talk
to the folks staying next door.
Nice family of four. I let them go, sir.
Let 'em go?
Yes, sir, just before you arrived.
But I got their statements.
Son...
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
...how many murders have you investigated?
One.
Ah.
If that family can ID the killer's voice,
then they are in danger.
And you'll have four more murders
on your conscience.
I need to talk to that family.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON POLICE RADIO]
[MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
[KELLY] How come Reggie gets to drive
and I don't?
Because you only have
a learner's permit for California.
Reggie probably doesn't
even have a license.
What? Hold... Hold... Hold on.
I got plenty of licenses.
- [KELLY] Plenty?
- Okay?
- Are they valid?
- Yes. I don't know what you talking about.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Hello.
Brenda Freeman?
[BRENDA] Yes, who's this?
Mrs. Freeman, I'm Capt. JD Hammers
of the Arizona State Troopers.
I'm in command
of the homicide investigation
at the Sunset Motel.
It appears I missed you by a minute.
I need you to come back.
I'm sorry, Captain.
I just want to get my family
as far away from that motel as possible.
Don't blame you, Mrs. Freeman.
It was a gruesome thing you witnessed.
If you pull over, I'll meet you somewhere.
I need to ask you
some follow-up questions.
I told your officers everything.
Yes, ma'am. But...
Look, Captain...
[SOFTLY] ...I can't talk right now.
I have your number. I promise
I'll call you as soon as I can talk.
- Ma'am, you don't... Ma'am!
- Have a good day.
Got a bad feeling about this.
Mom, what was that about?
We're... We're not going back, are we?
Hell no.
No, absolutely not.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
- Hello.
- [DISTORTED VOICE] Hello.
Who is this?
We know what you did.
We know what you took.
- I think you got the wrong number.
- Don't hang up, Brenda.
- How do you know my name?
- Boss man wants his money, Brenda.
Excuse me? What money?
You took his money and he wants it back.
I don't know what you talking about.
Don't call me back anymore.
- What was that?
- Some weird voice.
Talking about how I took her money.
Probably trying to scam me.
[CHUCKLES] I ain't got nothing
for 'em to scam.
[SQUAWKING]
[REGGIE] I mean, think about it,
double-quarter-pound burger.
That's half a pound, right?
How come they ain't got the guts
to call it a half-pounder?
Because it's bad marketing.
[CLICKS TONGUE] No.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
Oh, this asshole again.
Don't answer it.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing's wrong.
Uh-uh.
- I know that look, little brother.
- What look?
Something's going on with you.
You get twitchy and darty.
- My eyes ain't darty.
- You darty right now.
Like when you got a secret
or you about to tell a lie. What's up?
[SIGHS]
Damn.
All right. All right. All right.
I was going to surprise you
once we got to Houston.
All my life, everybody say
I'm the family fuck-up, right?
- No comment.
- This time, Reggie ain't the problem.
Reggie's the solution.
[UPTEMPO MUSIC PLAYING]
Where'd this come from?
The Lord is our savior,
fell out the sky right into our laps.
Peep what's inside.
[EXHALES]
- What the...
- The dead dude.
He stashed it under the bathroom sink.
It's gotta be drug money, right?
I figured this dude is deader than shit.
He can't use this money,
but I know a needy family who can.
Have you lost your damn mind?
Bren, the dude was dead.
I mean, like his heart had stopped.
I'm a nurse! I know what a dead dude is.
You thought you were just gonna take this,
and make our lives better?
- This money could save our lives.
- It can end our lives!
Bren, just say thank you.
Stop looking on the dark side.
[SCOFFS]
We could turn around
and go back to Los Angeles right now.
Save the house and everything.
You stole money from a crime scene, Reg.
The voice on the phone,
he killed that man for this money.
And?
And their boss knows we have it.
He knows who we are!
Bren, you overreacting.
He ain't coming back for this.
What if he does? Huh?
You gonna turn into some street gangster?
Instead of the assistant manager
at Chick-fil-A?
Hey, that's an elite position. Okay?
I had to work my way up to that.
You know how many drug tests
I had to pass? That hurt.
- Okay, we gotta call the police.
- What?
No. You call the police,
they'll arrest the whole damn family.
They'll say we the ones that murdered him
to rip his shit off.
We are not criminals.
[SCOFFS] We the next best thing.
We Black.
You want to risk the lives
of those two kids?
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
Here she is.
- Bren, don't answer!
- No, Reggie.
- Don't pick it up.
- Get... Reggie, get... get off!
[GROANS]
We have your money.
We want to give it back.
Where are you?
I'm not gonna tell you that.
Worried about your family? You should be.
Look, you'll get your money back,
but it'll be on my terms, okay?
I'll call you back.
I thought about what you said.
You're right.
You have every right to be angry.
Let's just keep half the money.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[KELLY] Yeah, in the very next room.
[GAME SOUND EFFECTS PLAYING]
Yeah, Zac, he was murdered.
I mean, there was blood everywhere.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES]
[GRUNTS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[LINE RINGING]
[DISTORTED VOICE]
This is our game, Brenda.
You don't make the rules. Mr. Cross does.
The bag is in room 33
at the Center Star Inn.
It's in the closet on the top shelf.
You're not hearing me.
The key will be under the mat
outside the door.
Get your money.
[DISCONNECTS]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[RETCHES]
[VOMITS]
Let's go.
Yeah, let's hurry up
back on the road to nowhere.
Mom, what were you doing?
I was getting some tourist brochures.
Check it out.
We're not tourists.
We're seeing
a whole new part of the country.
Maybe we should take advantage of it.
You know, soak up some culture.
Seriously? This place has culture?
Look, after last night, I just think
we all need to relax and breathe a little.
Feel like normal people again.
Ain't nothing normal about this place.
[QUIETLY] Shut your ass up.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[ANNOUNCER] Howdy, folks.
Welcome to Old Bravo.
The town where the Wild West never dies!
- [LAUGHING]
- Get him!
Oh, no! You got me.
Come on in.
[SNORING]
[SCREAMS]
- Dork.
- No, I'm not.
- You're in jail.
- What?
- Yeah.
- No.
- You're in jail.
- Oh.
[REGGIE] Brenda, you my big sister,
I love you.
But you definitely just messed up
the best thing that ever happened to us.
That money would've got rid
of all our problems.
All money is not good money, Reg.
Whatever. That's Jake talking.
You damn right that's Jake talking.
You gonna bring up my dead husband?
You know what? Why not?
Jake was a hero, Jake was a god,
'cause Jake always did what was right.
And remind me what good it did Jake
when he needed chemo and radiation,
didn't have the money for it.
I got the money!
You got the money by getting yourself
so far in debt you lost your house.
Let your own kids down!
- You a asshole, you know that?
- Yeah, I know it.
I've known it my whole life.
'Cause people constantly reminding me.
You know what? Maybe I am
just an assistant manager at Chick-fil-A.
That don't mean
I don't have my own dreams too.
You killed those dreams.
I was just trying to make things better.
That's all I was doing.
[KIDS CHATTERING]
[LAUGHS SOFTLY]
You all I got, sis.
I love you and those kids.
You know that.
I wasn't trying to hurt nobody.
I know, Reg.
I loved Jake too.
I know.
Seems like every day
the man upstairs is testing us.
[CREAKING]
[ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- This is really peaceful.
- Yeah.
[CAM GROANS]
I gotta use the restroom.
Uh, Reg, go with him.
Mom, I'm not a little kid anymore.
Okay. Come straight back.
Okay. Okay.
Hurry up.
[BELL TOLLING]
[ANNOUNCER] Hey, folks. You hear that?
It's high noon.
And there's a duel happening.
Come on down!
[APPLAUSE]
- Feels kind of real.
- Who you got?
- My man right there.
- Yep.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
What?
[DISTORTED VOICE] Last person
who took Mr. Cross for a fool is dead.
We want our money.
The money is there. It's in the room.
Then go get it.
I'm not going back there.
You have something of his, Brenda.
- And now Mr. Cross has something of yours.
- [MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[GUNSHOT]
Bren?
He's here. Cross is here. Go find Cameron.
Bring him straight to the car.
- Come on, we gotta go.
- Whoa!
- What is wrong?
- Don't ask questions, just do as I say.
Cam! Cam, you in there, little buddy?
Come on.
Come on, little man, let's boogie.
We gotta roll.
My bad.
I'm sorry.
You drop this?
Oh, shit!
Cam!
Cam! Cam?
[ACCORDION MUSIC PLAYING]
[PATRONS CLAPPING RHYTHMICALLY]
- Are you gonna tell me what's going on?
- Just Just get in the car right now.
Oh, my God.
Okay, I'm in. Now what?
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
[LOW VOICE] Hello, Brenda.
This is Mr. Cross.
He's with me.
Please, just don't hurt him, okay?
[CROSS] Call the police,
or fuck with me again,
and I'll grab your daughter next.
Please, for the love of God,
just don't do this.
You have two hours to retrieve my money.
Then bring it back
to Old Bravo and call me.
Or your son is dead.
Mama! Mama!
[SOBS] Help!
- Cam?
- Swear to God, if he hurts that boy...
I gotta get back to that motel
and get the money.
Mom, what's happening? Where's Cam?
- Cam has been abducted.
- Abducted?
Reggie will explain it to you
but right now I gotta go.
Go where? Where are you going?
I got to get Cam,
but I need to leave you here.
No! No, no, no!
He's my brother, I'm coming with you.
Listen to me. I cannot worry about you
and your brother and do this.
Just wait for me, I'll call you.
Mom! Mom! Don't.
- Mom, wait, please.
- [ENGINE STARTS]
- No, no, no. Come on.
- Mom!
I got you. I got you.
- Kelly, trust her.
Mom!
[SOFTLY] I'm sorry, baby.
- Mom!
- [CAR HONKING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CARS HONKING]
- Come on, move!
- [HONKING]
[HONKING]
You better not hurt my baby.
[SIREN SQUAWKS]
In pursuit of a speeding Chevy Suburban.
Headed westbound, east of Old Bravo town.
[WOMAN] Capt. Hammers, we got a hit
on your plate request
coming out of Old Bravo.
Driver is a female, Black.
This is State Trooper Captain Hammers.
She's a witness.
If the cartel or Cross spot you,
they'll kill her. Fall back.
Do not pursue.
I repeat, do not pursue.
Oh, my God.
"Don't worry"?
[CRYING] The last three months of my life
have felt like a bad nightmare
that just keeps getting worse.
I know.
I can still feel him, Reggie.
Like Daddy isn't dead, you know?
I can hear his voice
and I can see his face.
And I don't...
And I don't want to let that go.
[SOBBING] I don't want to lose him.
Your dad is always going to be with you.
You hear me?
Trust that.
And your mom's going
to get Cam back. I promise.
Reggie, come on.
Please tell me what's going on.
I messed up, Kelly.
I messed up big-time.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
No!
What? Okay.
Breathe. Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
Hey!
Stop! No!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
No! No, please! Wait, please!
No!
Stop!
[PANTING]
["START A RIOT" PLAYING]
I see you.
Fuck.
Thieving bitch.
Stop!
Stop that car!
Fuck!
I see you! Where you going?
[RAPPING CONTINUES]
[SOUND DISTORTS]
[SOUND RESUMES]
[SONG ENDS]
- My bag! Give it back.
- [WOMAN SCREAMS]
Kiss my ass!
Give me back my bag, you little thief!
[MAN] Yo!
Drop the bat.
Whoa. Just... Just... put that down.
Shut the hell up.
I'll blow your ass back to Africa.
Mace!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[PEOPLE WHISTLING]
[MACE] Holy shit.
[PEOPLE WHOOPING]
What do we got here?
This woman here, she stole my property,
but I got it back now.
So I'll just go get my car and go now.
I don't want any trouble.
Oh, that's too bad.
It looks like you got it.
Look, I don't have time for this.
Hey, show me what's in the bag.
[BRENDA] No.
[THUNDER CRACKING]
I'm leaving.
[GRUNTS]
[PEOPLE WHISTLING, CHEERING]
[LAUGHING]
Would you look at that?
[LINE RINGING]
Mom, pick up.
This is Brenda,
please leave it at the tone.
[VOICE WAVERING] Mom, uh,
we are at Lucky 13 restaurant,
right outside of Old Bravo, okay?
Can you please call me?
Reggie just told me everything
and I'm really scared.
[FAINT MUSIC PLAYING]
Begging your pardon.
Would you be the Freemans?
Captain Hammers
of the Arizona State Troopers.
I'm looking into the homicide
that took place last night
at the Sunset Motel.
I didn't spot y'all at Old Bravo
so I figured you'd be here.
There's no place else to eat for miles.
- Sir, we already talked to the police.
- I know.
Mind if I join you?
Darling, bring me a big old glass
of iced tea, extra sweet, lots of ice.
- Thanks.
- Sure, Captain.
And, uh...
you'd be Kelly.
And you'd be the uncle.
Reginald Beaumont.
Hmm. Which accounts for two of you.
Now, as to your mom and brother,
your mom was last seen driving
south of here like a bat out of hell.
Where's your brother Cam?
Um, he was with her, sir.
Probably didn't see him
because he's little for his age.
Hmm.
- [WAITRESS] Super sweet.
- Thank you.
Now, how about we cut the bullshit?
There's a fortune in missing drug money.
And if your mom's got it,
she's in a whole world of danger.
Because it either belongs
to the Sinaloa Cartel,
or a Mr. Cross,
a man who's the most dangerous criminal
in the Southwest.
He's murdered at least 50 people.
You want to see
your mom and brother alive again?
You need to tell me where they are.
Or don't.
It's their funeral.
[BREATHES DEEPLY] Reggie.
Sir! Sir, wait.
[PANTING] My brother's been kidnapped.
Can you please help us?
It was Mr. Cross.
Please.
- [LOUD MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PEOPLE CHEERING]
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]
- Not so fast, bitch.
- [BRENDA GROANS]
[GROANS IN PAIN]
Best place to lie low is my ranch.
Mom should have called us by now.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What? What's wrong?
SUV's been trailing us
for the last five miles.
I slow down, he slows down.
I speed up, he speeds up.
You think it's Mr. Cross?
I don't think
he'd get his hands dirty like this.
Might be one of his goons.
Let's not take any chances.
But I'm gonna ask you both
to duck down in your seats.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
- [UNCOCKS GUN]
- You can come up for air.
Sorry to scare you like that,
but I had to be sure.
You think that dude is gonna try
and smoke my sister and nephew?
I'm not gonna let that happen.
[LOUD ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[BRENDA] No! Let me go.
Yo, Mace! Look who's all woke up.
[MAN] Look who's here.
Big Mama wants some action too.
- [BRENDA] Get off of me!
- Well...
you know what they say?
Once you go white,
you ain't ever walking right. [LAUGHING]
[ALL EXCLAIM]
- Oh, you...
- Fuck, get off of me!
- Let me go.
- Bitch broke my nose.
Let me go
or I'll snap her scrawny red neck.
Do it. That's one less slut.
[HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAN SCREAMS]
[MACE] Get the money!
[BRENDA] Get away from that!
Give me back my bag.
You ain't going nowhere.
- [BRENDA] No! No! Please. Please.
- [MAN] Get the bag!
No!
Son of a...
- Here you go, Mace.
- [BRENDA] That's my bag.
[MEN] Whoa!
Easy now.
I need that money to get my son back.
Don't give two shits about your son.
Yeah, fuck her!
Yeah, she won't use that gun.
[SCREAMING]
Oh, God!
Mace, bitch shot off my leg!
I missed! I was aiming for your balls.
I got one more shot in this gun.
Who wants it?
Huh?
You can't shoot us all.
I won't have to.
The money in that bag
belongs to Mr. Cross.
You heard of him?
I wonder what he would do
if he finds out who stole his money.
Put the fucking money back in the bag.
Go on, do it.
- [BRENDA] All of it.
- [MACE] Get it in!
- Hurry up!
- [MAN] Do what he says.
[MACE] Jesus Christ.
Look.
There ain't no reason
to tell him about all this, huh?
No harm, no foul. Right?
I'll think about that
when I'm driving away.
[HAMMERS] If Mr. Cross
or any of his friends decide to show up,
my wife Val is as handy
with a gun as I am.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
[DOG BARKING]
[REGGIE] Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Don't worry about him. He's friendly.
- I do not like dogs.
- Even the teeny-weeny ones freak him out.
Well, it's the teeny-weeny ones
that have the sharpest bite.
Go!
- Hello, woman. [LAUGHS]
- Hello, man.
This is Kelly Freeman
and her uncle Reggie.
They're from California.
- Ma'am.
- Well, how do you do? Nice to meet you.
- Hello, Kelly.
- Hi.
Are you hungry, child?
Oh, no, thank you. We're good.
Reggie, Kelly, lend me a hand, please.
I had to give him a shot to put him out,
so he might be groggy.
- [CAM STRUGGLING]
- Oh, fuck no!
[COCKS GUN]
See? Boy's safe and sound.
- Cam.
- You dead, motherfucker.
Nope. Alive and kicking.
[SHOTGUN COCKS]
Boss man.
You and your surprises.
I know. I couldn't resist.
Now, where's my money?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[KELLY] Mom, uh,
we are at Lucky 13 restaurant,
right outside of Old Bravo, okay?
Can you please call me?
Reggie just told me everything
and I'm really scared.
[PANTING]
Where... Where's my family?
Come on.
[LINE RINGING]
Come on, baby, pick up the phone.
Pick it up. Pick it up, Kelly. Pick it up.
[CELLPHONE BUZZING]
That's her.
Ah, she's probably calling to say
she's got the money and is on her way.
You have had one hell of a 24 hours, JD.
[CHUCKLES] My own damn fault.
I underestimated Harvey Ruck.
He didn't know I put a tracker on his car,
so he wasn't hard to find.
Son of a bitch was feeling brave.
I had no other choice.
[WHEEZING]
Problem was, I had to clear out
before I could find the money.
Figured I'd get it
when I came back in my official capacity.
But now we'll get our money back
from Mrs. Freeman.
Oh.
We will, you will.
You're a good man.
My good man.
Love you to death.
[CAM CRYING]
Listen to me, nothing bad is gonna happen.
I will not let
anything bad happen to y'all.
Once your mom gets here with the money,
they'll let us go.
I promise. You hear me?
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
Where's my family?
[DISTORTED VOICE] We're sending you
a family portrait.
[CELLPHONE CHIMES]
[CROSS] Don't be late.
Or the throat cutting starts without you.
[BRENDA] Oh, shit.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
This is the trap for Mom,
and he's using us as bait.
We have to find a way out of here.
Yeah, how? This place
looks like Jigsaw's basement.
What about that?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, God.
Oh, my God!
- [KELLY] But it's rusted shut.
- Here, Kelly.
- Okay, but what if they hear us upstairs?
- [REGGIE] They won't.
This is housebreaking 101.
Cam, hand me one of those rags over there.
Good. Wrap the rag
around the end of the broom.
All right, take the end of it,
gently press it up against the glass,
directly in the middle,
then give it a fast punch.
Just pop it.
[NERVOUSLY] Okay.
- Go ahead. Go ahead.
- Can you give me a lift?
- [DOG BARKS]
- [KELLY SCREAMS]
Oh, my God!
[GROANS] It bit me.
Oh, God.
Shut the hell up, Cujo,
before I whoop your ass!
- Here.
- [HAMMERS WHISTLES] Here, boy!
Steady. Steady. Steady.
He's coming. He's coming.
- [GROANS]
- Sorry, sorry! Here.
[ENGINE STALLING]
[BRENDA] Come on!
Damn!
All right.
Should have warned you about my alarm dog.
Got some good news though.
Your mama's almost here.
Y'all need to come back upstairs.
Sorry you got caught in the crossfire,
but soon as I get my money,
you're free to go.
- Just gonna let us go on our merry way?
- That's right.
You a goddamn liar.
What did you say?
You heard me, cracker.
You can take this country, "aw, shucks,"
fake Southern hospitality bullshit,
and shove it right up
your tight cowboy ass.
I ain't gonna let you hurt these kids.
You gonna need to learn some respect, boy.
Perfect.
- [SCREAMS]
- Clorox, motherfucker!
[HAMMERS SCREAMING]
JD! JD!
Kelly!
[GROANS]
Damn, I thought she was a nice old lady.
[KELLY PANTING]
[SCREAMS]
Reggie!
[GROANING]
Lose that knife.
I said lose that knife.
Well, look at you, little man.
You ain't gonna shoot me.
You're right.
He won't. But I will.
Drop the knife.
[GROANS]
[VOICE WAVERING]
We wasn't going to hurt you.
Bitch,
get your evil, Martha-Stewart-looking ass
down them steps.
Now!
- Bitch, get your...
- [SCREAMS]
Girl, give me this weapon. Get our phones.
Let's get the fuck out
of this psycho house.
[REGGIE GROANS]
Thanks, little man.
Please don't die.
I got you. I ain't going nowhere, okay?
You hear me?
I promise. I ain't going nowhere.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Now, let's get out of here.
Come on, we got to find your mom.
- JD, they're getting away.
- [HAMMERS GROANING]
- Are you okay?
- The little shit poured bleach in my eyes.
Can you see?
Good enough to hit what I aim at.
[HAMMERS KICKING DOOR]
- [LINE RINGING]
- [KELLY] Mom, come on. Pick up please.
Please. Please, please, please.
- Come on.
- [BRENDA] Kelly!
Mom? Mommy, where are you?
I think I'm almost there,
but my phone is dying.
I think I can hear you
but I can't see you.
Mom, where are you?
- [TWIGS SNAP]
- Mom!
- Cam!
Oh, my God!
- Mama!
- Oh, Kelly!
Oh, Cam, my baby.
[GROANS]
Mom, Reggie, he kept us all safe.
Thank you, Reg.
Thank you for my children.
They're all I got.
You too, big sis.
[KELLY] Okay, Mom, listen to me.
Mr. Cross is an Arizona State Trooper.
He's... He's the captain.
- What?
- Capt. Hammers is Mr. Cross.
And he's corrupt and evil,
and his crazy wife is just as bad.
They were gonna kill all of us.
- He's what? Where are they now?
- Locked in the cellar.
Well, we better move.
Wait, wait, wait! What about the money?
It stays to pay for our escape.
Come on, sis.
Hammers, Cross, whatever his name is,
he's not gonna honor that deal.
You know that.
It stays.
Tell me that's your final offer.
I'll put it where
the schizophrenic asshole can't miss it.
Come on. Let's go.
[LOUD THUMPING]
- Give me my shotgun.
- Here.
Go!
[VAL] Where are they?
[HAMMERS] Look.
They can't be far.
Look what we got.
Time to go hunting.
[BRENDA] Don't start the car until I yell.
You got this, Kelly. You got this.
- All right. Let's get this baby started.
- Okay, Kelly, go.
[ENGINE STALLING]
- Come on.
- [BRENDA] Come on, please.
- Reg, you're gonna have to fix this.
- I'm on it.
[VAL] Which way?
[HAMMERS] Don't know. Lost their tracks.
[CAM] I think it's the fan belt.
- You a smart kid, you know that?
- Thanks.
Become a scientist when you grow up.
Help change the world for the better.
- Make Uncle Reg proud.
- I got you, Uncle Reg.
All right, move back.
Okay, start the engine.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
- Yes!
- [BRENDA] Yes!
Oh! Oh...
[BRENDA] There you go.
- Yes!
- Yeah!
- We did it!
- [ALL LAUGHING]
[LAUGHTER, CHEERING CONTINUES]
Got you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Can we just keep driving
until we get to Grandma's?
Absolutely.
We only stopping for gas.
[SCOFFS] I heard that.
Amen.
- Oh, shit, we got company.
- What?
Hold her steady.
Drive!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- Get down!
- I think I got their attention.
[LAUGHING]
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
- [BRENDA] Oh, my God!
- Take this. It's us or them.
Come on, Mom. Focus and squeeze,
like Grandpa taught you.
Nobody messes with my family.
[HAMMERS] We got a live one.
Damn her! I can't see.
- Yes!
- [REGGIE] Did you get 'em?
- [KIDS] Hell yeah.
- Yeah, but keep driving. Don't slow down.
[GRUNTING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PANTING]
They're back.
[CAM] Oh, God!
- No, no, no!
- No!
- Missed me, motherfucker!
- [BRENDA] Reggie, keep it steady.
[REGGIE] Bren, be careful.
- Mom!
- Oh, no!
I got you now.
[VAL CACKLING]
Hang on, I got this.
[KELLY] Be careful.
Mom, get back! Get back!
Look out!
- Mom!
Stop the car! Reg, stop the car!
- [CAM] Mom!
- [KELLY] No!
This is my game.
You broke the rules.
Bye-bye.
No. No.
No! No! No!
- [KELLY] Mom?
- [CAM] Mama!
[DISTORTED SCREAM]
[LAUGHING AND WHOOPING]
[KELLY] Oh, my God.
All right, enough. Enough! Enough!
You want me? Just take me.
Take me, okay, please?
Please!
- [ENGINE STARTS]
- [WHIMPERS] No, Mom, no.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[PANTING]
Like shooting fish in a barrel.
- Jump, kids! Get out, now!
- [KELLY] Cam, go!
No.
[SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
I make my own rules.
Son of a bitch.
- [KELLY] Hey, Mom?
- [CAM] Mom!
Oh, baby.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
You're okay.
It's over now. It's over now.
All right.
This nightmare's over.
I got you.
I'm never letting go.
- Never.
- Okay.
Come on, bro.
You too.
You know the drill.
Come on.
[REGGIE] Oh, thank God.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you, Jake.
Thank you.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Reggie?
Drive this car
and do not stop until you hit Texas.
Yeah.
[FAINT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Thank you.
Y'all enjoy it.
Listen, uh, y'all ain't got to worry
about the check. I got it covered.
What?
Come on, y'all. Dig in.
And come up off this syrup, Kelly.
You paying?
Yes, Bren. Give me the...
Tell me you didn't.
Didn't what?
No! I see your eyes darting.
What did you do, Reggie?
[SCOFFS]
How much?
[CHUCKLES]
Enough to give us a new start.
That's right, and there's more
where that came from.
[REGGIE GRUNTING]
[KELLY LAUGHING] Oh, my gosh!
Yeah, you know, waffles, they taste best
when you load 'em with lots of syrup.
And butter. Got to have butter.
We gotta give that back.
Give it back to who?
Wait, yeah, Mom. Give it back to who?
We can't exactly take out an ad.
[REGGIE BLOWS RASPBERRY]
No, absolutely not.
Cam, Kelly, do not look at him like that.
He is not a good role model.
Excuse me, I'm a great role model.
We gotta give this money back to...
I don't know.
Somebody.
Right?
Mom, we're keeping it.
Restitution.
Looks to me
like you've been outvoted, big sis.
So eat. Your food's getting cold.
[CAM] Yeah, come on, Mom.
- Join the family.
- [REGGIE] Mmm-hmm.
A celebration.
[CAM] Come on.
Just a family celebration.
["GOOD DAY" PLAYING]
Pass the syrup.
[SIGHS] Thank God.
Let's put this money away.
We don't need no problems.
Texas ain't got nothing on Arizona.
[KIDS] ♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
♪ And all my homies gonna ride today ♪
♪ And all these mommies look fly today ♪
♪ And all we wanna do is get by today
Hey ♪
♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
♪ And ain't nobody gotta cry today ♪
♪ 'Cause ain't nobody gonna die today ♪
♪ Save that drama for another day
Hey ♪
♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
[MAN] ♪ Hairline fresh, new cologne on ♪
♪ Feelin' so good
Changed the color to my phone ♪
♪ Orange Kool-Aid go good with Patron ♪
♪ Oh, nah, hell nah, boy
Still my ringtone ♪
♪ Free car wash
Had to clean up the Dodge ♪
♪ Give back when I can
Just playin' my part ♪
♪ Church folk had a fish fry ♪
♪ Mustard, hot sauce, light bread
And french fries ♪
♪ Love for the big guy ♪
♪ Hit the park
Boys showin' off their hops ♪
♪ Nappy Roots on the radio
And you know it bops ♪
♪ Last night, hit the pick three
Bought some Air Force Ones ♪
♪ Four tall tees
Man, I'm loving B.G. ♪
[KIDS] ♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
♪ And all my homies gonna ride today ♪
♪ And all these mommies look fly today ♪
♪ And all we wanna do is get by today
Hey ♪
♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
♪ And ain't nobody gotta cry today ♪
♪ 'Cause ain't nobody gonna die today ♪
♪ Save that drama for another day
Hey ♪
♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
[MAN] ♪ And I finna worry
'Bout what nobody say ♪
♪ I'm still above ground
That's the reason I pray ♪
♪ Got my car cleaned up now
I'm ready to play ♪
♪ Make a call to the sticks
Say I'm headin' their way ♪
♪ Heard my cousin cookin' out
I gotta get me a plate ♪
♪ Got this new outfit
Ain't even out in the States ♪
♪ So if I ain't speakin' too soon
But this is a hell of a day ♪
♪ And the sticky got me
Sittin' in a hell of a place ♪
♪ Got my stunna shades on
And grin on my face ♪
♪ My grill looks mean
But I swear I'm straight ♪
♪ And the hood showin' love so I'm A-OK ♪
[KIDS] ♪ We're gonna have
We're gonna have a good day ♪
♪ And all my homies gonna ride today ♪
♪ And all these mommies look fly today ♪
♪ And all we wanna do is get by today
Hey ♪
♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
♪ And ain't nobody gotta cry today ♪
♪ 'Cause ain't nobody gonna die today ♪
♪ Save that drama for another day
Hey ♪
♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
[MAN] ♪ We might as well do
Exactly what the children sayin' ♪
♪ Take a day off
Hit the park and just hang ♪
♪ Barbecue, roll a few
And put up your deuce ♪
♪ If it's beef, put the piece down
Throw up your dukes ♪
♪ It's time to change our ways
So we can save the day ♪
♪ For the children's sake
And make a better place to play ♪
♪ And if it's all good
Break out your coop and grip your wood ♪
♪ And if you're ridin' dirty
Light your spliff and blow your... ♪
♪ But do it real big
Exactly like a player should ♪
♪ Enjoy your 24
Do your thing and rep your hood ♪
♪ The world is all yours
But still we all grind ♪
♪ Forever and a day
The choice you make is really fine ♪
♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
♪ And all my homies gonna ride today ♪
♪ And all these mommies look fly today ♪
♪ And all we wanna do is get by today
Hey ♪
♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
♪ And ain't nobody gotta cry today ♪
♪ 'Cause ain't nobody gonna die today ♪
♪ Save that drama for another day
Hey ♪
♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
♪ And all my homies gonna ride today ♪
♪ And all these mommies look fly today ♪
♪ And all we wanna do is get by today
Hey ♪
♪ We're gonna have a good day ♪
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]