Ripped & Edited by physic_nut
Place your empty cartons in the
assigned slots, then sit down.
Our school has been singled out among
middle schools nationwide
as a model to others in the national milk
promotion campaign.
You're approaching the development of secondary
sexual characteristics.
The calcium in the milk
isn't just good for your bones,
but for the nervous system, too.
I confiscated these adult titles from
Mr. Kamiyama last month.
Mr. Watanabe hacked the censorship
at his dad's store,
and Mr. Kamiyama circulated them
among all the boys.
As you're aware, your minds
and bodies are developing.
you really kissed?
It's called "puberty".
I'm unsure of milk's actual effect
on 13 year old bodies and minds,
but April's annual check-up
will surely yield some results.
Not that I'll be here.
I quit teaching at the end of the month.
For real?
Fantastic!
(25th March - 7th Grade, Class B)(End of term)
I've no idea if I was a good teacher or not.
Shut up, teacher's talking.
Thank you, Mr. Hoshino.
By the way, anyone know Dr. Sakuramiya?
He wrote this book. He's amazing.
He's just an incredible person.
Famous as an educator via his books,
TV appearances...
An ex-delinquent, he traveled the globe then
returned to be a teacher, right?
Correct. Last year he found out
he only has a few months left to live
but chose to keep teaching until the very end.
My first placement was at the school he taught.
Really?
"The weak of heart visit hurt
on those weaker still.
"Do they have any choice
beyond endurance or death?
"No, you guys inhabit a world
much wider than that.
"If life is harsh where you are,
why not take refuge elsewhere?"
Take refuge.
She said it. Let's go.
Already, the esteemed teacher's words are working.
What power.
I don't mind.
Compared to him, I find myself
lacking as a teacher.
I set myself just two rules.
I would always address you formally.
I'd try to see things your way
and speak to you politely.
No casual chats nor advice about
anything under the sun...
For those wanting a teacher one sees on TV,
I daresay I came across as cold.
Sorry, Miss Noguchi.
Your midnight texts saying,
"I wish I was slim. I want to die"
didn't get a kindly response.
I just can't bring myself to believe all you say.
But you're our teacher...
There was an incident,
when a young male teacher got a text
from a girl saying she'd lost her will to live.
He raced round to the hotel where she was.
She took his photo, showed her parents,
who stormed over to the school.
It's so ridiculous.
It was just a prank from a girl sore
at being scolded in class.
The teacher was naive not to have suspected her.
You're our teacher. Don't you trust us?
No, because you're all so good at lying.
See you on the rooftop.
Miss, I'm not feeling well.
Can I go to the infirmary?
Sure.
Since that incident, our school policy is,
should a student summon a teacher,
a same-gender teacher responds.
If a boy in this class summons me,
Mr. Tokura of Class A goes instead.
As our teacher, you're avoiding responsibility.
"Avoiding responsibility"
It might seem that way.
But only to a girl as self-obsessed as you,
who worries over her chances of
marrying pop-stars.
Who got so upset one night.
She claimed she'd lost the will to live.
So that you people never again
talk of wishing for death,
I'll talk about something important.
Life
As you know, I'm a single mother.
I was supposed to marry Manami's father.
He was a teacher, too and a man I respect.
Just before our wedding, I got pregnant,
and he discovered he was infected with HIV.
HIV... the Human Immunodeficiency Virus,
the cause of AIDS,
which he apparently got from adventures overseas.
Don't hold your breath.
There's no airborne transmission.
Hand-shakes, coughs, sneezes,
public baths, pools are also not
routes of infection.
Daily life presents no danger
from an infected person.
I myself did not get it.
HIV isn't necessarily transmitted by sex, either.
I didn't believe it and had myself retested.
To have the child but not get married:
that was our conclusion.
Why not get married?
Even if the child wasn't infected,
word of the father's infection would bring
unavoidable discrimination.
Surely that's worse?
This would cause more harm than lack of a father.
That was his decision and I agreed.
The poor kid.
Putting the kid first, made us do what we did.
More than anyone,
he must've longed to hold her.
His pain,
was much greater than mine.
I poured all my affections into Manami.
When Manami turned 1, I returned to work.
She was in day-care until 6pm.
The HR center introduced a Mrs. Takenaka,
who looked after Manami after that.
She kept a dog called, "Mook".
Manami loved that dog.
Feeding him was Manami's special task.
Mrs. Takenaka was hospitalized in the new year.
So I'd have to finish up to be at day-care by 6pm.
On teacher conference days,
I picked Manami up earlier,
and had her wait in the infirmary
until the meeting finished.
Manami loved the Cotton Bunny character.
She had the bag, the handkerchief,
the tissues, the shoes...
Mr. Shimomura you remember this purse?
Please, I want it, I want it!
But I just bought a jacket, right?
Why not, it's just a purse?
Looking back, maybe you were right.
Because in the end...
Manami?
It was her last act of willfulness.
Miss!
February 13th
The police ruled it "accidental death
due to fall into a body of water".
Breadcrumbs were found near the dog,
from the same bread as at Manami's day-care.
Apparently she went to
the pool secretly, each week,
to give Mook his dinner.
She's crying.
Why are you crying?
Manami's no longer with us.
Those little hands,
will no longer touch my skin.
My hands will no longer
stroke that soft face and hair.
As her guardian,
Manami's death must be my responsibility.
However,
I can't leave it at that.
Manami is dead.
But it wasn't accidental.
She was killed,
by students in this class.
You won't believe what Moriguchi just said.
What's your greatest protection?
Is it your parents?
Is it a weapon?
Your most trustworthy ally and protector
is the juvenile legal code.
Under Article 41 of the penal code minors
are not criminally responsible.
You can't be arrested.
Wonderfull, huh?
A girl 13 like yourselves,
calling it "a holy rite",
laced her family dinners with poison.
Then blogged in detail about the symptoms.
The "Lunacy" thing?
Yes, "The Lunacy Incident".
A name she'd used in the blog
which the mass media picked up
and used to fan the flames.
In the end the reason she killed her
entire family with cyanide
remains a total mystery.
Which just served to spawn wild ideas,
and earn her heroine status among her peers.
Tell us who the hell did it.
The science teacher who'd taught her
about the chemicals
was persecuted mercilessly.
The girl herself composing contrite statements
in a juvenile facility,
will return to society, right-as-rain.
You guys can murder
and get clean away.
That's exactly why I did it!
In any case,
murder can't be prevented.
If the mood takes you,
grab a bat from the baseball team,
a knife from home economics,
a jump-rope from the sports locker...
even these bare hands...
...will do the job.
That hurts.
Sorry.
Quickly...
You're all dying to know
the name of the culprit, right?
I do apologize,
but I don't feel like making it public.
That's the important bit!
Manami's father was Dr. Sakuramiya.
The reason we held a private ceremony,
was so he could grieve for her openly.
It was the first time he had held her,
yet her soul had already gone.
He told me that he'd developed AIDS.
He'd only a few months left to live.
I didn't know what to say.
I think...
the day that Manami died,
some important thing inside me
died along with her.
Last week I went to Mrs. Takenaka's house.
to pick up some of Manami's things.
Among them, was this...
the purse she'd begged for but I didn't buy.
Why was it there?
Mrs. Takenaka found it in Mook's kennel.
They roll over here sometimes.
You know how students play catch
when they're cleaning the pool?
I remembered that one of the penalties
for breaking school rules
was poolside cleaning duty
or tidying the sports locker.
Not me.
I know who did it!
On that day...
did Manami go to the pool alone?
There were two killers.
Henceforth, I'll refer to them
as Students A and B.
Student A has excellent grades
and outwardly presents no problem.
Although occasionally,
I heard disturbing rumors about him.
Since elementalry school, he traps cats and dogs,
then tortures them to
death in his "execution machine".
"Execution machine"?
A weird contraption he made.
Then he posts photos on his website.
(Genius Professor's Research Site)
New machine Under Development Watch This Space!
I called his elementalry teacher, just in case.
They just said he wasn't a problem.
Just when I was beginning to
put it out of my mind...
What was your major?
Student A came to my lab.
Chemistry.
Anything electrical?
Your father would be more knowledgable than me.
Open it, there's something nice inside.
Isn't it great?
Am I your guinea-pig?
You made this to kill more animals?
Is that all you can say?
Pop.
What?
You didn't hear it.
The sound of something important
disappearing forever.
National Middle
High School Science Fair
Application Form
"Shocking Anti-Theft Purse"
"Keeping your change away from thieves"
No "execution machine" then?
Whatever. Just put your seal on it.
From the disarm function he'd added,
his stress on its safety
through to his pure and eager
7th grader report style...
...it all filled me with dread.
"A contribution to society"?
If you think it's that dangerous,
leave it for the judges to decide.
I did ask the Principal
but my fears were laughed away.
In the end, his "Shocking Anti-Theft Purse"
earned the award of excellence
in the Middle School finals.
Shuya, Shuya, Shuya...
Conclusion: Shuya Watanabe
I asked him the truth about Manami's death.
Just kidding...
He discussed it quite happily.
As if unaware the mother of
the murdered child was before him.
Student A's motivation for the killing
was laughably simple.
For the world to acknowledge his genius.
He wanted acclaim as a superior person.
However the day his science project
made the papers...
it wasn't him who won the acclaim.
(Middle School Girl Murders 4 Family Members)
but another 13 year old.
You win praise for doing good
but nobody really notices.
That Lunacy thing was no big ideal.
Why is Potassium Cyanide special?
If it were me, every single thing...
I'd create with my own hands.
I want to kill him.
That was exactly how I felt.
Student B began school and started sports.
But it was all strength-building
and he never got to hold a racket.
Die, die, die, die.
Though unhappy, he hadn't the courage to
talk to his course adviser.
He had his mom get him off sports
and started at cram school.
His grades didn't improve and he started to worry
but didn't work any harder.
He made it to a police station and was held there,
but was shocked when Mr. Tokura
came to pick him up.
Why isn't it Miss Moriguchi?
Just shut up, idiot.
Die, die, die...
For breaking the rule against
entering video arcades,
he was given a penalty.
2 weeks cleaning poolside and the changing rooms.
He'd never have the balls to kill.
I heard this a from Student B in his own home.
His mother sat beside him.
Each time he spoke she'd say...
You poor thing...
She said it time and again.
Not about my dead daughter but about him.
Around February, Student A made his approach to B,
to lure him in to his dreadfull plan.
I wonder who it can be?
What?
Is that the thing that won the prize?
It's got more power now, so I want to test it out.
Could be anyone, but the idea was to zap bad guys.
Then let's test it on bad guys.
Student B first suggested Mr. Tokura.
Student A didn't respond.
Then Student B put my name forward.
It was just unforgiveable.
Her own student in a tight spot yet
she sent a different teacher.
She's already been a guinea-pig.
Student A shot down that idea.
How about her daughter?
It'd teach her to put her kid
before the needs of her students.
Student B described Manami's trips
to the pool to feed the dog.
And about the purse she so wanted
but I didn't buy her at the mall.
The one they selected for their target,
was the youngest and the weakest.
It was my daughter.
Your mom didn't buy you this, right?
Or did she, already?
I thought so, because she told us
to get it for you.
She did?
A Valentine Day present from your lovely mom.
Open it up,
there's chocolate inside.
What happened? She's not moving...
She's dead.
He was in a total panic... kicking up such a fuss.
You can tell everyone it was me who did it.
After I said that, I went home.
Then that idiot...
If they realized the purse killed her,
suspicion would fall on me.
So I figured I'd make it look like she fell.
A spur of the moment decision.
This is how Manami died.
As I already told the 2 boys,
If the police ruled it an accident
I won't rehash that verdict.
But there is one thing.
What killed her wasn't the purse.
I had it thoroughly checked out.
It's incapable of stopping
even a 4 year old's heart.
It's a pathetic piece of work.
Want to try it?
Manami had simply fallen unconscious.
She drowned after B threw her in.
That was the indisputable cause of Manami's death.
It's so ironic.
Student A had homicidal intent
but wasn't able to kill.
Student B did not but brought about her death.
Even if arraigned by the authorities,
juvenile law would mandate
simple custodial supervision.
Innocent to all intents and purposes.
I judged that to be insufficient.
Teachers have a responsibility to
guide students back to the right path.
I want them to admit their crime
and appreciate how precious life is.
I want them to realize the gravity of their crime
and live with that burden.
The milk that you all just drank...
Two of them had something extra mixed in.
The HIV-infected blood of Dr. Sakuramiya.
Be quiet!
You were both kind enough to drink it.
Thank you.
Please be sure to get a blood test
in a couple of months.
If it worked, you'll have
a 5-10 year incubation wait.
Plenty of time I should think,
to reflect on things and
appreciate the preciousness of life.
Springtime...
when the flowers, trees,
grass, birds, people, too...
all blossom into life.
Every one of you,
please have a meaningfull spring break.
(Yuko Moriguchi's Confession)
That's the end.
Miss Yuko...
Can you believe it?
After you left and the new term started,
our class could be this full of smilling faces?
(6th April - 8th Grade, Class B)(Start of term)
April... suddenly it's 8th grade
and there's a new homeroom teacher.
Wer-ther has been my nickname since school.
Doesn't mean I spend my days in sorrow!
His jokes aren't funny.
too pally from day one.
Hayakawa?
And Naoki?
Absent again with a cold.
We all knew he wasn't ill at all.
What surprised us more,
was that Shuya was at school at all.
I wasn't a good student back in my schooldays.
But one particular book by
one particular man changed my life.
That wasn't just unfunny,
it was a cruel joke.
"As I wandered the globe
I began to read the Bible. "
"In it, I glimpsed the true nature of education. "
"Though a man might have 100 sheep,"
"should just 1 go astray,"
"in order to save that 1, the man,"
"even though he risk the 99 others... "
Sir, you're the best!
I just want to be totallly open with you all.
They're just a bunch of wimps.
Whatever your problem, come to me.
Everyone was desperate to
escape the truth you thrust at us.
I'll hand whatever you throw at me!
They're all pretending to be idiots.
I want to be an elder brother to you all!
(Mizuki Kitahara's Confession)
(Dr. M. Sakuramiya)
"Miyu"?
"Natsky"?
"Sugi-June"?
"Missa-Pon"?
I'm sorry.
I've been lying.
Naoki's not absent because of illness.
But he's not skipping school.
He wants to come but a mental issue prevents him.
The only person in class who
doesn't know the reason is Werther himself.
Anyone leaks teacher's confession
we'll treat you as "Student C".
We all got that anonymous text
right after the end of the previous term.
How about we try to make a nice
atmosphere for Naoki's return?
Okay, say we take turns making notes,
then once a week, student chair Mizuki and I,
deliver them?
What do you think, Mizuki?
Thank you.
Mizuki, don't you have a nickname?
Me-the-hoe...
I was called that in Elementalry School.
Me-the-hoe!
Me-the-hoe.
Like the name, "Mizuho".
Mizuho huh? I'll call you that from now on.
Me-the-hoe...
Louder, louder!
Me-the-hoe, Me-the-hoe...
Where's Naoki?
If only his other teacher had been
as enthusiastic as you,
maybe Naoki would've escaped
this mental issue he has.
That lady, she was a single mother, right?
Bringing her own child to work,
in the first place...
To avoid talking about the incident,
she kept criticizing Miss Yuko.
She was so caught up in her own child
she'd no time for her students.
- If I might say...
- poor Naoki...
If he puts his mind to it, he can do anything.
Trust me with your son, please.
Thank you very much.
Darling...
Mind your own business!
It's all that woman's fault.
(Yuko Shimomura's Confession)
That my lovely Naoki turned into this...
I'm taking a piss.
He hates us touching anything he's made dirty.
He cleans everything incessantly.
Yet for all that,
he doesn't wash his hair,
nor take a bath.
That bitch...
Why Manami?
Why did she have to die?
What are you suggesting?
As if it were Naoki's fault the daughter died.
He was just tricked into helping by a bad friend.
You poor thing.
Darling...
Get away!
You don't regret a thing, do you?
Shuya Watanabe - Die
Murderer
12 points, 8 points
Die murderer
Maekawa adds 2 points
Rack up "Punish-Him Points"
This text went to everybody.
The murderer's come-uppance measured in points
Of course it was anonymous.
Who'll write some kind words to Naoki?
K is for...
"Keep smilling"!
I is for...
"it's better to share"!
L is for...
"Life can be hard"!
"Let's be happy"!
How's he coming along?
Could I just have a word?
Sir...
Call me Werther.
Even if we keep this up, Naoki's never coming back.
I think this makes it worse.
Mizuho, we're at a crucial point now.
Overcome and we'll see the light.
E is "Everyone's waiting"
R is "Return to us soon"!
Why is it?
My good boy, Naoki...
every time they show up,
he gets so upset.
That stupid teacher,
spouting his fancy words,
yet doing no good at all.
I put a sleeping pill in his lunch.
My husband's always away at work.
My daughter's busy at college in Tokyo.
As the only one here.
I'm all that child has.
I have to protect him.
Mother...
Darling.
Who is this kid?
Why's he smilling?
It's June...
We've had bullying in our class.
The victim is Shuya Watanabe.
I found this message folded in
yesterday's homework.
I don't want a brave student's
warning to be in vain.
It's not bullying but jealousy.
Someone's harassing him out of
envy at his top grades.
But just because he's good that
doesn't make you inferior!
Nobody thinks that for a second.
Being smart is part of Shuya's individuality.
Just like you all have your own individuality.
The individuality to persecute the weak.
The individuality to forget bad things.
I want you all to nurture those identities.
As I keep watch over you.
You snitched, right?
No way.
It wasn't me.
The reason I was suspect was
my Punish-Him Point score
Mizuki - 0 points
Allying yourself with a murderer.
Don't you have any feelings?
Don't you feel sorry for Miss Yuko?
Let me go.
Kiss... kiss...
Miss...
our class is messed up.
Naoki's crying.
He's probably remembering the incident.
He's feeling sorry for that girl who died.
I understand that.
He hasn't changed at all.
Still as gentle as ever.
My dear Naoki.
K... I...
L... L... E... R...
"Killer - Die"
Can you meet at the Koshu bridge?
I'll be there.
So there it is.
I wasn't worried.
I knew you'd be okay.
Want a soda?
You say you knew?
I figured Miss Yuko lied all along.
Mixing AIDS blood into the milk...
People were dumb to believe it.
Why?
Think about it.
If you're serious about revenge,
about killing someone,
you don't say stuff like that.
I wonder...
She'd never do it.
No matter how much she hated you.
There's no way she could.
It was just a way to make you
two think stuff over.
I could just tell.
Aren't you scared?
Of me?
Even though I'm Student A?
Why did you show me your result?
My life's nothing.
But yours is precious.
Sending texts, inciting everyone,
it's obviously you.
Mr. Hoshino
Any more shit from you...
you'll get tongue next time.
Just kidding.
I'll buy everything...
everything he touched.
Best not eat it you might get AIDS.
At the end of last term,
Miss Moriguchi infected my milk...
He then told me the most terrifying thing.
That Moriguchi,
she's the devil incarnate.
Darling, let's go to hospital.
It doesn't matter.
Don't be silly. If you die what about me?
I'm a murderer, you know.
Nonsense.
You just moved the body to help a friend.
It wasn't a body. She was unconscious.
I dropped her in the pool.
But... they said...
Hang on... you didn't know she was alive.
Not true, Mom...
She woke up, right in front of me.
And then...
I just...
July...
No-one harasses Shuya any more.
"... harasses Shuya any more. "
Don't look, it's just a letter.
To who?
I won't send it.
It's just good to write down my feelings.
Amazing...
It's great, Shuya...
That's all I needed.
I just wanted someone to praise me.
I'd been without a mother
for so long,
I'd been so alone...
Everything I'd never been able to talk about,
I opened up to Shuya.
The Lunacy girl...
she's such a kindred spirit.
I revealed the real me, that nobody knew.
Is there anyone you want to kill?
Please go away.
Naoki, if you're there, listen to me!
Withdrawing into yourself solves nothing!
Unload all your problems on me.
I'll solve them all. Believe me, Naoki!
Be at school for the end of term tomorrow.
We're waiting for you!
Thank you for always coming with me.
This Naoki...
is no longer my Naoki.
My gentle Naoki...
he's gone.
Dear Yoshihiko and Mariko,
farewell...
and my apologies.
I'll take Naoki and go on ahead.
We're heading to heaven.
Darling...
Next day, the end of term meeting ended early,
for an afternoon teacher's meeting.
It seemed that Naoki
had killed his mother.
Just tell the police exactly what happened.
Yes.
Miss... Miss Yuko,
I'd like to ask you something.
Is life really that precious?
Really? Everybody's life?
I'm collecting various drugs.
I thought...
maybe I'd use them to kill myself.
But it'd be easy to put in Werther's tea, too.
His life is not important.
You felt the same about Naoki and Shuya.
No, I can't believe that's true.
But it's scary,
to think there's a part of me
that doesn't care if Werther dies.
I told them everything.
Naoki was driven into a corner.
The reason he did what he did...
All of it...
was Werther's fault.
Nobody told me that it was wrong to murder.
Rather than picture books and
dream-filled fairy tales,
my mom read Ohm's Law, Norton's Theorem
always explaining electrical engineering.
She'didismantle all my cute toys
and explain the workings to me.
My mother was a promising researcher in her field.
But she married the dullest of guys
and the kid they made,
was me.
In order to become my mother,
she abandoned her bright future in research.
You're an intelligent boy.
You've got mom's blood in your veins.
But she soon grew to regret it,
and resent the cause,
me...
Why don't you understand?
How come you can't do it?
If only I hadn't had you.
If only she hadn't had me...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
That's enough.
Unable to bear it, my father divorced her.
Mother resolved to restart
her career as a researcher.
Of course, leaving me behind.
All she left for me...
These wonderful books all
had a huge influence on me.
They'll play a big role in your future.
I was a load of books and a parting line.
You've got my blood in your veins.
You've definitely inherited your mother's genius.
See you.
That's when I heard it.
The sound of something important disappearing forever.
(Shuya Watanabe's Confession)
Pop.
Everyone disappears.
You want some?
I'll disappear, too.
As will the world around me.
All of it.
31st August.
I just rigged a bomb at the school.
Its trigger is my cellphone.
An essay of mine entitled "Life"
was selected by the school district.
At tomorrow's opening ceremony,
I'm due to read it in front of the entire school.
"Appreciate how precious life is"!
"I'll never forget Miss Moriguchi's words.
"After losing her only daughter
in an unfortunate accident,
"her words
"and the truth within them... "
I'll trigger the bomb just as I finish.
Blasting myself and the idiots around me,
into smithereens.
Of course the mass media will love it.
However,
I can't abide the trite analysis that'll follow.
So I'm posting my last testament
by myself on this website.
My father remarried the following year.
Per the laws of natural science,
idiots mate with idiots
and idiot offspring result.
I talked it over with your dad.
My idea is to make the stock room
into a study for you.
We don't want baby's cries to upset your studies.
kept reading my mother's books,
feeling our blood bond grow stronger.
I wanted to employ the genius she'd bestowed.
Dreams of useless normal people
bowing down before me,
began to grow monstrously.
What's this?
A reverse alarm clock.
These idiots I'd attracted with pledges
to de-censor porno
could never appreciate the nature of my genius.
(Genius Professor's Research Site)
Firstly, I created a website,
a gathering-place for prodigies
which I linked to my mother's college.
"Engineering genius grade schooler posts
amazing inventions - check it out!"
I thought maybe my mom would take a look.
But...
Comments (0)
Then I got mad,
and posted all sorts of crap...
Execution Machine
Comments (181)
What you did was OK.
Yoshikazu Seguchi.
(National Middle High School Science Fair)
I was delighted to see that
name on the jury panel.
He was a respected scientist and
a great influence on my mother.
To think he might see my creations,
would be a perfect test of my inherited genius.
If selected for a prize,
the news might make its way to her.
I tested the prototype on my teacher.
It passed with flying colors.
I won the national award of excellence.
However...
(Middle School Girl Murders 4 Family Members)
A local middle school girl is helping police
with their inquiries...
A thing like that couldn't get
the world's attention.
Nobody noticed,
especially not my mother.
I needed something bigger
the entire media would cover.
A massive incident.
A murder.
Something that required my inherited talents.
A special murder,
only genius could carry out.
It didn't matter who I killed.
But I did need an accomplice.
Someone who wouldn't guess my real thinking.
Who would do as I say,
then blurt out my crime to the entire world.
A true idiot among idiots.
There he was.
You can tell everyone it was me who did it.
Don't worry, you're not an accomplice.
You were never my equal.
you're a dumb-ass wimp.
It's obvious you're a failure.
I just told him the truth...
Why did he have to do that?
4 Year Old Drowns After Fall Into Pool
Why did he butt in?
I wanted to be your friend.
I just...
with you...
I didn't have anyone.
Want to come watch movies?
I always wanted to talk to you.
To think someone noticed me...
You're different from those jerks.
You seem relaxed... grown-up.
Someone acknowledged me.
So I chose a target, as you asked.
How about her daughter?
Why Manami?
Why did she have to die?
I wonder why?
I've forgotten it now.
I just did as I was told.
I even surveyed the scene first.
But then you...
You can tell everyone it was me who did it.
That jerk...
He so wanted to be a murderer.
But he couldn't do it.
The kid was still alive.
She was breathing properly.
It's obvious you're a failure.
A failure, huh?
He wanted to kill but couldn't.
He's the damn failure.
Look who's talking.
I managed to achieve
what he couldn't.
Why did you butt in?
If you want to tell the world, feel free.
Pop.
After a month that idiot teacher finally twigged.
I don't intend to rehash the police verdict.
Damn it.
What killed her wasn't the purse.
It's incapable of stopping
even a 4 year old's heart.
It sucks.
Two of them had something extra mixed in.
The HIV- infected blood of Dr. Sakuramiya.
That was perfect, Moriguchi!
A deadly disease...
Perfect... if I contract that,
Dad would surely have to tell Mom.
He'd have to let me see her.
Actually, she'd move mountains to come find me.
We're reconciled, she looks after me...
A perfect testament to my genius.
Pop.
After that, I was just killing time.
The smilling...
The tears...
All of it... that, too.
Everything... life itself.
Just meaningless...
...a waste of time.
I saw you by chance that day...
Why did he do that?
The retard.
The one I considered a failure.
It was Moriguchi's fault.
She was trying to kill me.
She even sent a spy to my home.
Yet my mum kept bad-mouthing her to him.
That's why she was killed.
I desperately tried to stop her getting infected.
To prevent her dying.
I was going to be killed, too.
I mean...
Am I even alive?
(Naoki Shimomura's confession)
It certainly doesn't feel like it.
I stink.
But it's proof I'm alive.
This hair, my nails, the dandruff, the stench...
Being hungry... all proof I'm alive.
I'm dying... I'm dying!
I'm dying.
At the age of just 13.
Moriguchi's killing me.
I've never kissed,
or made out,
or done anything.
Why?
You're such a failure.
No, I'm not!
I'm...
Naoki, you're a good boy.
Aren't I, Mom?
Good at sport, at studying...
At killing...
You can succeed if you try.
I'm so sorry, darling...
Why?
'Cause you're a failure.
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
Your poor mom,
she didn't bring you up right.
Failure.
According to his lawyer,
the child apparently received
the court's verdict calmly.
Miss, about "life"...
To think how much he loved his mom...
Silly jerk.
Look who's talking.
Nothing.
What do you mean by that?
You're being scary.
What the hell do you know?
I know everything about you.
You were just a way to kill time.
But I was through.
I'm sick of that "Lunacy" crap.
And your longing to be like her.
Collecting crap like this...
You identify with Lunacy?
You're just a wannabe, dreaming little dreams.
You're an idiot.
Shuya...
You haven't got the courage to kill.
Why not drink this and make a start?
Mother complex.
That's all you are.
Hung up on a mother who abandoned you.
Yet without the balls to go see her.
Scared in case she rejects you, right?
You know full well she abandoned you.
Miss...
I saw you by chance that day...
I did.
You didn't add anything, did you?
I mean put blood in the milk.
You'd never do that.
So I always thought.
Now I don't know anymore.
Now I don't care if Werther dies.
It seems Mr. Terada's taking time off school.
Since Shimomura turned out like that.
But it was Werther's fault...
It was my fault.
I'd meet up with him occasionally.
He was so enthusiastic...
...so pure-hearted...
Such a Sakuramiya devotee.
So I confessed the fact Sakuramiya
was Manami's father.
I reeled him in and used him...
to corner those boys.
Of course I didn't tell him how Manami died.
He listened to my advice so carefully.
About home visits to Shimomura...
"No matter how unpopular keep at it,
at least once a week... "
"If the door's shut in your face, keep calling. "
"Sakuramiya would do no less. "
That's what I kept telling him.
When he asked me about Watanabe's bullying,
I told him to claim a student had reported it,
to help bring it home to them.
Knowing full well it'd promote further bullying.
I said it on purpose.
I was disappointed to hear it'd stopped.
I counted on the cruelty of the class
to result in his death or suicide.
You guys were kinder than I thought.
Miss...
This is for you.
Thank you.
As to blood in their milk...
"Don't repay hatred with hatred. "
"That'll never bring peace of mind. "
"Someday they'll be reformed. "
"Believe in them. "
"That'll bring your salvation, too. "
That's what Sakuramiya said.
To the very end,
he kept saying the right thing.
Whereas I...
went ahead and told them anyway.
But even if I'd actually done it.
the chance of infection's practically zero.
Even if you get AIDS,
it's not a death sentence now.
Drugs can ward off the disease.
With Sakuramiya,
if we'd found the cancer earlier,
he wouldn't have died.
But you all had no idea...
You quaked at the mention of HIV.
So pathetic and clueless...
Miss...
I lost my family.
And Shuya...
I'll never forgive.
So?
Do you think I should die?
You don't understand.
Shuya's just lonely.
He just wants to be noticed...
...by his mother.
Because she left...
'Cause his mom abandoned him...
he just needs recognition and...
Miss...
About life...
It's no big deal.
It's all so stupid.
She was still warm.
It was so creepy, I put the body in the fridge.
It's just a minor committing murder.
The juvenile penal code will protect me.
I won't get the death sentence.
What a let-down.
When I began building,
I wasn't sure how I'd use it.
Three days ago.
Associate Professor Yasaka
It was from my mother,
saying she wanted to meet.
Without a second thought,
I headed for her university.
Department of Science & Engineering,
Electrical Engineering Lab 3...
I saw her, just beyond the door.
If I'd just call out, tears would flow,
and she'd hug me to her.
But...
just then I had a realization.
What I wanted her to embrace,
wasn't this body of mine,
but something bigger,
my talent and...
...the great exploit I'd leave behind.
I walked away from the university.
In order to leave my mark on the world,
I'd found a use for my bomb.
The imminent mass murder,
won't have some idiot like
Shimomura for a witness,
but all of you who gather on this site.
The historical events of tomorrow,
my death too,
must be vouched for,
and my desires recorded,
for the benefit of my mother.
In this world, there are people
who can be forgiven for murder.
For them...
...for me, too.
...to build a better, new world,
there is a right to overstep certain obstacles.
That's what the hero of "Crime and Punishment"
Raskolnikov says before he kills the old woman.
But what I want to say is
that life...
every life... is precious,
every life is beautiful,
and in this world of ours,
every life has equal value!
Just kidding...
Darling, it's Mommy. Sorry you've been so lonely.
Who is this?
Long time, no see.
It's Moriguchi.
I have your bomb.
A simple thing put together by a simple mind.
It was a cinch to disarm.
You blabbered on the website...
Shut up!
No, I won't.
I want to discuss my revenge.
Simply killing you,
won't result in you despising your life.
Rather than murder.
I kept checking your website for a better idea.
Then I saw it, your ode to your mother.
But lying is wrong.
As your former teacher,
I must correct your mistruths.
The e-mail with your mother's address.
Did you think that was from her?
Mother...
You sure hurried over there the next day.
I saw her, just beyond the door.
Actually, you left without seeing her.
In order to leave my mark on the world.
How could you lie like that?
You bitch.
You crept into her research lab,
clutching your crappy inventions
in the hope she'd take a look.
But she wasn't to be found.
Ain't that right, kiddo?
Hey.
What do you want?
This is Associate Professor Yasaka, right?
Do you know her?
The person I admire most in the world.
Yes, but her name's, Seguchi, now.
Seguchi?
These guys are on their honeymoon right now.
Amazing at their age... a shotgun marriage.
You chucked everything and
ran out of there, bawling.
Impressed that I know?
I was watching.
It was me who sent you
the address of her workplace.
Miss Kitahara,
the girl you killed,
she told me your one weakness.
Shuya's just lonely.
He just wants to be noticed,
by his mother.
I did some research.
It was easy to get the whereabouts,
of the woman you'd commit murder
to have notice you.
And to find out who she's with.
Shut up!
I wanted to check the extent of
your feelings with my own eyes.
After acting so cool, you were in a total mess.
Just then I had a realization...
That you'd been abandoned...
Worse, you'd been totally forgotten.
I walked away from the university.
Total despair. Time to die without more ado,
and take as many people with you as possible.
That's the real reason for planting the bomb.
Are you stupid?
You don't have a clue how I feel.
You're the one without a clue.
Why did innocent people have to die?
All you care about is your mother.
Why did Manami and Kitahara have to die?
It doesn't matter who I kill.
Then just kill your beloved mother.
Shut up!
Give that to me.
The police will be there soon.
Should've discovered Kitahara's body about now.
That poor kid...
She was the only one,
who knew what an arrogant weakling you are.
It's just a minor committing murder.
The penal code will protect me.
I won't get the death sentence.
Even if the law protects you,
I will never forgive.
This morning, after dismantling your bomb.
I went to see someone.
Taking with me,
your precious present.
This person that you'd been longing to see,
I was able to meet easily.
Apparently, she'd only just
returned from her honeymoon.
We talked about everything.
I told her how much you loved her.
How many had been sacrificed.
It turns out,
she'd not forgotten you at all.
Stop it.
At the very least, I gave her your present.
I dropped off your invention.
Then quickly said my goodbyes.
Your mother's a lovely woman.
So I prayed you wouldn't push the button.
But in the end...
...you went ahead.
Just kidding.
I heard the sound of
an important thing disappearing, too.
Not so much, "pop"...
...as "Boom!"
Shut up!
Mr. Watanabe,
the bomb was built and was activated
by you.
This is my revenge.
A living hell.
From now on,
your reformation begins, one step at a time.
Just kidding.
Ripped & Edited by physic_nut
Based on a novel by Kanae Minato
Takako Matsu
Yoshino Kimura
Masaki Okada
Written & Directed by Tetsuya Nakashima