[upbeat music]
[Man laughs] Come here.
[Man] Mmm.
[woman pants]
You're so pretty.
[music playing on car]
[Michelle] Unbelievable.
How many times I've...
I wasn't trying to
embarrass you.
I was just giving you a clue.
[Robert] I felt like an idiot
in front of everyone.
How am I supposed to know
who wrote "The Stranger"?
But nobody cares that
you didn't know the answer.
[Robert] I don't know why do
we play that stupid game
every time we go to
their house, anyway.
It gives Vince a chance
to waive his college
degree in my face.
Could've at least
have stayed for dessert.
♪ Something a little
more than time to kill ♪
♪ There's no mistaking the
laws that we're breaking ♪
♪ We'll do what we always do ♪
[man chuckling]
Hey...
you scared
the hell outta me.
Laura, I wanna see you
in the other room. [sighs]
[Laura sighs]
Get dressed and
get out of here.
[Laura] Dad!
[Laura sighs]
We weren't doing anything.
How much have
you had to drink?
A little.
I told you I never wanted
to see him here again.
You completely disobeyed me.
You never got mad
when I was with Danny.
Is it that you don't like Eric?
Because--
Danny would never have
been in there like that.
Oh, you just never caught us.
This is not about which
boyfriend we like better.
This is about trusting
you when we're away.
You're grounded for
two weeks for this.
-Mother, what--?
-[Robert] Go to bed!
Sleep it off!
[Laura sighs]
This is getting out of hand.
I'm too tired to
get into this now.
I'm going to bed.
Right.
Are you coming?
In a while.
[birds chirping]
Well, I'd promised
to be harder, Steve
when business picks up, but
on what if business
doesn't pick up.
Have you seen my briefcase?
Oh, here it is.
Listen Laura, some stupid stuff
like the one you
pulled last night,
have got to stop, do
you understand me?
You know how critical
your senior year
is to getting into
the right college.
Now we have four weeks
to send in those letters
of recommendation.
You're on top of those, right?
Yes.
I'm not gonna do all
this by myself you know.
Tonight we work on
Northwestern's and Wisconsin's,
I'm counting on you young lady.
[sighs]
Maybe we all hold onto them
until the end of the month.
Maybe things will pick up.
I'm showing a house at 5:30
but I should be home
in time to make dinner.
I'm going to work.
This time I promise.
I'll see you later.
Uh-huh
God, I'm late.
So am I.
Don't forget your lunch.
I'll just grab
something at school.
Try not to make
it french fries.
[sighs]
[bell rings]
[chattering]
[Man] Laura, can I speak to you?
You didn't turn in
yesterday's assignments.
You flunked the midterm, Laura.
I don't know if I can
let you make it up.
I mean, you're so far behind.
I understand.
I don't.
You were one of the top
students in my class last year.
Look, I know what your
brother went through
and I just don't wanna see
you start down the same path.
I'm just burnt
out, that's all.
I've talked to Mr. Carlson
about this.
I'm required to tell him
when things slide this far,
you know the policy.
Yeah, whatever. I'm
late for calculus.
[chattering]
[Boy] Hey you.
[Eric] You spilled.
You okay?
You ever wonder what would
be like to be somebody else?
Someone else.
What do you mean?
Somebody else,
somebody different,
different family,
different schools,
different looks.
Everything.
I don't get it, how
could you be someone else?
Forget it.
No, you gotta give
it a rest Laura.
You've been talking
crazy lately.
Really.
Well, maybe I'm crazy.
Hey, isn't that
dad over there?
[Eric] Don't tell me it's
his cousin, right?
-Get outta here.
-[Eric chuckles]
[door opens]
[Michelle on answering machine]
Hi, it looks like
I'm not gonna
make it home after all.
I know, don't say it.
Hmm-- The Northwestern
application is in my desk,
why don't you get started
I'll arrive after dinner...
[Robert] Laura? Is that you?
[Michelle on answering machine]
...lamb chops are defrosting.
-Yeah?
-[answering machine beeps]
[Robert]
Come in here, we need to talk.
So is there something
you wanna tell me?
No. Why?
Well, I got a call from
your guidance counselor,
Mr. Carlson?
He says you're barely
passing any of your classes,
you've been ditching school.
He wants to see your mother
and me Wednesday afternoon.
I--
Dad, don't worry. I'm not
gonna flunk any of my classes.
This is exactly
how David started.
First its the grades,
then its the---
Dad, I'm not stealing
things or doing drugs,
why don't you just lay off?
We have a serious,
serious problem here, Laura.
What are we gonna do about it?
Nothing, just don't worry.
Don't worry.
Well, that's just great.
You tell that to your mother.
She's only been helping
you fill out applications
for college for the last month.
I never asked her to help
me fill out those applications
[sighs]
Laura!
Hey, Laura,
get back here!
[chattering and music
from inside]
[Laura] I couldn't really
get you that much
because mom didn't have time
to go to the store
and I was doing some stuff,
not like lying on the couch.
Cool, I could use those, thanks.
How things in squirrel cage?
Don't ask, I feel like I
can't breathe in that house.
[David] What's up?
I just can't wait
to get out of there.
All mom talks about is, what
college am I gonna go to.
She makes such
a big deal about me
being first and
the family to go.
I guess I kind of left
that on you, didn't I ?
Yeah, I think.
If I hear mom saying she's
counting on me one more time,
I think I'm gonna explode.
I should be so lucky.
What do you mean?
Mom never said
anything like that to me.
When I was about 13,
I guess, Bill Turner and I
broke into dad's liquor
cabinet after school.
We drank a whole
bottle of his bourbon,
it was the first
time I ever drank.
I was so wasted.
[chuckles]
Mom came home early
and busted us.
And after she sent Bill home,
she came up to my room
with this really serious
look on her face.
I was pretty scared.
And she said, "David...
I always knew you were gonna
be the loser in this family.
I don't think she meant it.
Oh yeah, she did.
[clattering]
And that wasn't the last time
I heard that from her either.
And after that,
and I don't know,
I just started getting
in trouble a lot.
Nothing seemed to
matter anymore.
But hey, getting
outta that house
was the best thing I ever did.
Now that I got a
job and everything,
I'm gonna get my own place.
That's what you
said last time.
This time I'm serious.
Besides, Stuart said
I can only stay in
the back of the shop
till the end of the month.
Guess I'm running out
of friends to hit up.
Or you can always
come back home.
Yeah. Right
that'll be the day.
Yeah. I guess this is
not a very good idea.
Real bad idea.
[sighs]
[door closes]
-[Michelle] Where have you been?
-Out
Out where? You're grounded?
You saw David, didn't you?
Ah-- He's my brother, I'm
allowed to see him, aren't I?
How are you planning
to get into college
without finishing
high school first?
I plan on finishing
high school.
Not with F's and
all your classes.
I'm not getting F's
in all my classes.
Don't lie to me!
What the hell has
gotten into you?
Do you wanna end up
like your brother?
Do you wanna throw
your life away?
He hasn't thrown
his life away.
He's got a good job now.
Right, washing dishes?
You're such a snob.
Listen to me.
Is that what you want?
Because that is exactly
how you're gonna end up
if you don't get into
a decent college.
Maybe I won't go
to college next fall.
to college at all.
[Michelle sighs]
You don't even know
what you're saying.
Go to bed.
We'll talk about
this in the morning.
[sighs hard]
[Counselor] Has she been moody,
secretive, depressed lately,
hanging out with
different friends?
Yes. All of those things.
Just to say, we're
very concerned.
Well, I know that we
discussed this option
when you were having
problems with David
and I understood
your reluctance then
but a residential
treatment facility,
such as Meadowbrook has
been having terrific success
in dealing with these types
of behavior disorders.
You might want to reconsider
getting some professional
help this time.
I have to tell you, I feel
very uncomfortable about this.
I still like to
think that we could
handle any problems ourselves.
I understand, but I do
have to be honest with you.
I've seen these types of
sudden behavior changes in kids
and oftentimes it's
a cry for help.
If that cry goes unheard,
it could lead to self
destructive behavior.
Nowadays with teen suicides
at epidemic proportions,
I just think we all
have to look closer
at these types of warning signs.
[dramatic music]
Robert come up here now!
Where'd you find those?
In her desk.
Well what were you
doing in her desk?
Looking for something,
drugs, anything answers.
-Well it's only a poem...
-[Michelle] Read it.
[reading] Feeling so small,
but I know it'd be
better for everyone.
If I just wasn't here at all.
Just a poem huh?
[Michelle sighs heavy]
Well, she couldn't really
be talking about suicide.
[door closes]
I'm going to talk to her.
[footsteps approaching]
Hi.
How was school?
Fine.
Can we talk for a minute?
Sure.
I know we've had
our problems lately
but I want you to know
that you can always come
and talk to me about anything.
No matter how bad it is.
Yeah. I know that.
I know breaking up with
Danny was tough on you
and sometimes it's good
to talk about that stuff.
Eh-- If you feel like talking
about it and you can.
[smiles nervously]
I would like it if you did.
I remember when I broke up
with this guy in high
school, Dev Warner.
I thought I was gonna die.
I'm fine. I really don't
need to talk about it.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Well...
I just wanted
you to know that
I'm always here for you.
I'm not gonna do my homework.
I'm grounded, remember?
Michelle, look at this.
What is it?
It says here that
Laura never took the SAT's?
What?
No, this is a mistake.
I'll call the school.
[Michelle sighs heavy]
Mom, what are you doing?
When were you planning
to tell us about the SATs?
Eh-- I was gonna tell you--
No.
no more excuses,
no more explanations.
I don't wanna see you now,
I don't wanna hear your voice.
Okay. I'm just gonna go--
I don't care
where you're going.
I don't know if I can
ever forgive you for this.
[defiant music]
[car starts]
[car skids]
[TV on]
[Laura] I can't believe
how stupid I am.
I've never seen her like that.
Uh-huh.
I can't go home.
My roommate is not coming
home until Thursday
so you can stay here.
It's late.
Let's go to bed.
Well, why don't I
sleep on the couch.
What's wrong?
[chuckles]
I just told you
that I can't go home.
Uh-huh.
And my life is
totally messed up.
Look, I just need
a friend right now.
Hey, I am your friend.
I'm the best friend
that you've got.
Look, I said no,
just leave me alone.
This is the
perfect opportunity.
We got the whole
place to ourselves.
I can't believe that's
all you're interested in.
[sighs heavy]
You never cared about me.
Oh don't be so selfish.
What I'm doing here.
What about me?
What about you?
[dramatic music]
[passing car honks]
[tires screeching]
[loud crash]
[police radio chatter]
Are you sure you all right?
Dad, I told you I'm fine.
Yeah, the officer said
that your blood alcohol
level was very high.
You probably know that
we've made a decision.
We're gonna get you some help.
We're sending you to a
place called Meadowbrook.
[dramatic music]
[Dr. Winslow] Self esteem,
life management
skills, leadership qualities.
These are the goals
of Meadowbrook.
Now we don't know yet,
the extent of Laura's problem.
The behavior you have seen
may be the tip of the iceberg,
or it may just be growing pains.
But I assure you, our success
rate here is impressive.
Often the two week evaluation
period is more than enough
to take care of the problem.
At Meadowbrook we really
do turn lives around.
[knocks]
[Dr. Winslow] Yes.
Thank you.
Very good.
Your insurance is
more than adequate.
[sighs heavily]
[Robert]
I love you, sweetheart.
I can't believe
you're doing this to me.
I hope you understand we want
what's best for you sweetie.
Don't even try mom.
[steps walking away]
[sad music]
[sighs heavily]
They admitted here
without even talking to her.
What?
They admitted her without
seeing her, without a diagnosis.
How could they do that?
Well, what did they say to
the insurance companies?
It will be all right?
It's just two weeks.
The important thing is
she's getting help.
Dr Winslow, I don't know
what my parents told you,
but I really don't belong here.
You know Laura, I think it best
that the time that you are here
that you try to
make the most of it.
Consider it a break
for you and your parents.
Time to sort things out.
-Okay.
-[Dr. Winslow] Okay.
This is Ms. Collins.
She'll help you settle in.
-All right?
-Okay.
All right.
[door-lock opens]
[door closes loudly]
[Nurse] Sit here.
What's that for?
It's procedure,
everybody gets it.
[Ms. Collins]
It's just something
to relax you.
What are you doing
with my clothes?
They're inappropriate.
We have a dress code here.
No dresses and skirts,
nothing provocative, no shorts,
no makeup, no jewelry.
Only long pants and shirts
with the appropriate
sleeve lengths are allowed.
Now, why don't you get undressed
and we'll finish
getting you settled in.
What do you mean
get undressed?
I mean, take your clothes off.
Excuse me?
Strip search, it's routine.
Nothing to worry about, honest.
Here. Put this off.
We have five status levels
here at Meadowbrook.
With each level you
get more privileges.
You're at level one.
Earn a hundred points and
you move to the next level.
You just earned 10 points
for cooperating back there.
See how easy it is?
If you behave, you
get privileges.
Phone calls privileges,
maybe even off grounds.
Talking with other patients
will be confined with social
hour, from three to four daily.
That's all.
While you're here,
there'll be no TV,
no radio, no mail, no visitors.
I think we better
get a grip on napping
in the middle of the day.
Thank You, Ms. Collins.
I will modify my behavior.
Your dresser.
Your bed.
Now, if you follow the rules,
you and I will get
along just fine, okay?
Group in 15 minutes.
Hey.
Look, I can't
talk to you. Okay?
Why not?
Cause I don't wanna
lose any points.
I'm almost on level four
then I get my own room.
Fine, we don't have to talk.
Did you get
anything past them?
Like what?
You know, cigarettes,
pot, anything ?
[chuckles]
You mean if I
wanted to believe me,
they looked everywhere.
There's ways around
that you'll see.
[chuckles]
At least you gotta little
buzz going there, right?
Yeah. I feel like I've
been run over by a truck.
You're doing the
"thighs-in shuffle", that's all.
Just enough to mellow you out.
If you didn't have a
drug problem coming in,
don't worry you are going out.
[CJ] And we had totally
different taste in music
which was like this big
issue with my old man.
I mean, he thought I was
worshiping devil or something.
He was into all this...
folk music, peace and love crap.
With all of his friends
that wore sandals
and sit far out all the time.
I just couldn't take it anymore.
So one day I took all
of his records out
and busted them up with
a hammer in the garage.
And how did that
make you feel?
Felt great.
[chuckles]
[Marty] Oh.
[Counselor] Yes Marty. You have
something you'd like to share?
Well, I have a
complaint to register.
Fine. What is it?
Well, you know that
that blue water stuff
they have in the toilets here?
The commercial says it's
supposed to last 2000 flushes.
Right? Well, I've been counting.
With one night it can
only last 879 flushes.
That's a difference
of like 1,121 flushes.
That's false advertising.
I mean, I say there
ought to be a law---
[Counselor] Thank you Marty.
Keep it up.
You're gonna be at level two
for the rest of your life.
Does anyone else have
words of wisdom to offer?
All right, we have a
new member of our group
joining us today.
Stand up.
You can introduce yourself to
everyone by stating your name
and admitting that
you're an alcoholic.
Alcoholic, what are
you talking about?
You got into a run-in with
the police the other night.
Crashed your car,
it says right here that
you'd been drinking.
That's a mistake.
[chuckles]
I don't have a drinking problem.
I don't even like
the taste of alcohol.
Group?
Denial.
Denial
[CJ]
You either face up or shut up.
Those are the only two
choices you've got.
[Counselor] CJ's right.
The sooner you admit
that you have a problem,
the sooner we can get
at some of the feelings
that are at the source.
Eh-- I'm not gonna stand here
and say that I'm an
alcoholic when I'm not.
Fine, your choice.
Maybe you'd like to take a
couple of hours and time out,
to think about it.
You had 20 points toward
a level two Laura.
This is going to cost you 10.
-Wait--
-[Nurse] Come on, let's go.
No, this is all a big mistake.
Hey, just don't go
away mad, just go away.
I-- I don't even belong here.
[Laura] Get your hands off me.
[CJ] If I had a dollar for
every time I heard that one.
[Marty] You okay?
They are just trying to put
crap on your head, that's all.
They will let you out by dinner.
[chattering]
[Marty] Same Meadowbrook.
The food is bad
but there's plenty of it.
[Marty] That's just Naomi.
She's weird.
Yeah, I can see that.
[Marty]
It's her nightly routine.
What's wrong with her?
[Marty] I don't know.
She snapped.
Stopped talking
a couple of weeks ago.
They got all upset
about it after meds.
They can't handle it
when you act nuts.
They think she's faking
it to get attention.
[crashing]
[Nurse] Let go of her.
Leave her alone.
I said let her go!
[Nurse] You've got to modify
your behavior.
Are we getting a grip on
not giving our food away?
I told you I didn't
give my food away.
I said, are we getting a grip
on not giving our food away?
Yes. Ms. Collins.
I will modify my behavior?
I will modify my behavior.
Good.
When you've finished this one,
you can go back to your room.
[girls moaning]
These places are all the same.
I've been in and out
of them since I was 13.
What for?
The usual.
fought with my mom a lot.
I wasn't crazy or anything,
although I'm not
so sure anymore.
But I'm out of this place.
I've been working on
it for a few weeks now.
There's this ventilation crate
in the main room,
leads out of the building.
Every time I get a chance,
I loosen one of the screws.
Couple of more days
and I'm mystery.
[Nurse] Up. Face the wall.
What, you think you're special?
Come on, face the wall.
[Rachel]
And after that, I don't know.
I just started throwing
up after every meal
Your mom's cooking must
have been pretty bad, huh?
I just don't want
to get fat that's all.
Marty, that's not level
two behavior now is it?
Huh? Let's try to get a grip
on not making jokes in group.
I'm sorry. I'll get a
grip on not making jokes.
Marty.
Thank you. I'll
modify my behavior.
[Counselor]
Alright, Rachel. Thank you.
How about you, Laura?
Do you feel like
participating today?
Do I have to?
Well, if you wanna get
some of those points back,
you're gonna have to
start participating.
[CJ] Maybe she thinks
she's too good for us.
[Counselor]
Is that true, Laura?
No.
Look at her. You can tell.
I knew girls
like you in school.
Stuck up rich kids.
Maybe she just hasn't
got anything to say.
Give her a couple of
drinks, she'll loosen up.
Laura. Let me
ask you something.
Why do you think you're in here?
I don't know.
Well, I'll tell you why, because
your parents put you here.
Because you're making
their lives miserable,
because your own life
has become unmanageable.
You're an embarrassment to
your friends, your family,
everybody around you.
They may not say that to you,
but believe me, it's true.
I mean, it's bad
enough for your parents
that your brother was a loser.
Now you?
I don't have to
take this crap.
[Security] Where do you
think you're going?
I'm going to see Dr Winslow.
Nobody sees Dr. Winslow.
Believe me, if he
has to come in here,
you're in a lot of trouble.
You can't keep me here,
its against the law.
Not if you're under 18,
but hey, if you want
to call a lawyer.
Then take me to a phone.
Sorry, only level two and up
can use the phone.
[Laura yelling]
No! Let me go!
No!
Get off me.
No...
If you settle down, I
won't have to sedate you,
now its your choice.
Go to hell!
Get off me.
No...
[whimpering]
[faintly] No...
[whimpers fade]
[defiant music]
[chatter]
[whispering]
I wanna escape with you.
Why would I let you do that?
Because with the two
of us loosening screws,
it'll come off faster.
All right, but you
gotta be careful.
They've got these security
cameras everywhere.
What the hell are
you looking at?
You gotta figure out a way
to get yourself into the main
room when nobody's there.
Best way is to get
yourself in trouble
so you get put on deep clean.
How do I get
myself in trouble?
[chuckles]
[door opens]
You better get a grip on
not sleeping in the hall.
Are you gonna answer me, huh?
Or are you gonna play
your usual games?
[whimpering and laughing]
Answer me.
Hey, leave her alone.
She's not gonna hurt anybody.
You just got yourself
two days in deep clean.
[whimpering and laughing]
Are you gonna answer me?
[whimpering]
Get up.
-[Naomi whimpers]
-[Nurse shushing]
Come on.
[Naomi whimpers louder]
[Nurse] Show's over.
Everybody get back to your room.
Come on.
[Naomi whimpers]
I want you to clean
the entire floor.
[dramatic music]
[Security man] Make sure it's
done right or you doing it over.
[kung-fu screams]
Oh man...
I love to give that cheesy weesy
a kung-fu action.
[chuckles]
So...
you keeping it
together alright?
Barely.
You'll get the hang
of it. Don't worry.
-[Laura] What'd you do?
-[Marty shushing]
What's the big deal about
talking in this place?
They don't want you
to make friends.
They want you to
rat on each other.
That's how you get points.
So that's total sex
paranoid in this place.
Like if you're
talking with someone,
they think you're having sex.
Yeah right, that
should be so lucky.
[chuckles]
What did you do
to get deep clean?
Eh...
I don't know.
I found some stupid white out
in one of the four
counselors desks.
What, were you
like sniffing it?
Sniffing it?
No, I was, eh--
I was gonna use it to paint
this little house I built.
What little house?
This house is made
up of an old meal box,
I stole it from the kitchen.
It's for Phoebe here.
[smiles]
Hey.
Hi.
Oh look, she's so cute.
I named her after Holden
Caulfield sister,
you know,
from catcher in the rye?
Oh.
You're really pretty.
You're the prettiest girl here.
It's not lying or anything.
[Laura smiles
I guess it is but I didn't
mean anything by it.
But I meant it not really.
Well, thanks.
[Marty]
Do you wanna be friends?
'Cause, except for Phoebe here,
I really don't have one, and...
it could be our secret.
We wouldn't have to
talk or anything.
We just know that we were there.
You know like...
friends do...
and like eh...
pen-pals or something,
separated by thousands of miles.
What'd you say?
Yeah. I'd like
to be your friend.
[soft music]
Wow.
Hardly recognize a meal
that doesn't come out of
a Styrofoam container.
I guess it has been a while
since we showed
at the dinner table together.
It's so hard for me to get
out of the office before seven,
This looks delicious.
Is it me, or does it
seem too quiet in here?
[both smile backwardly]
Maybe we should turn on some
heavy metal music upstairs
and I guess feel more at home.
I miss the kids.
Well... I mean.
I tried to call Laura today.
Robert, you shouldn't
have done that.
You know what they said?
She needs to be
separated from us.
I know, I couldn't help it.
They said she was fine
but they wouldn't let her
come to the phone, so--
I just hope she's really okay.
Don't do this to
yourself Robert.
We need to give this a chance.
We have no other choice.
It's only 11 more days.
Yeah...
But who's counting, huh?
[radio chatter]
[Laura] What happened to her?
[Rachel] Tried to up herself.
just probably cheeking her meds.
You know, taking the pills
back against her cheek.
When the attendant leaves,
she spits them out.
Then she saves them up and
takes them all at once.
They'll pump her stomach.
She'll be back here in two days.
[ping-pong game on]
That guy's always
looking at me.
[Marty] Who, CJ?
Maybe he likes you.
I don't think so, it's
different than that.
I wouldn't trust him.
As far as I could drop,
kick a range Rover.
Who is he?
Some jerk. Got
here a few weeks ago.
Spent the whole
first week in the SR
for mouthing off too much
and fight with the attendant.
Got him so strung out.
I don't think he knew
what planet he was on.
But now all of a
sudden it's yesterday.
"Anything you say, sir,"
Winslow's poster boy.
So what about you?
What about me?
Why are you in here?
Why'd you do that?
I don't know.
[chuckles nervously]
Some days, I--
Well, some days I get all
wired and I feel great.
I feel like I could
jump out of an airplane
without a parachute and just
fly for days, you know?
And other days...
[laughs nervously]
They call it bipolar.
It's a...
manic depressive, you know.
But I'm much, much
better now really.
I mean, they make me take the
meds here and they help a lot.
So...
Ha... I don't think I could
ever do that to myself.
What about you?
Why are you in here?
For being stupid.
[Rachel] Come on, let's go.
[Laura pants]
Go, go.
[suspenseful music]
Go.
[chair moves]
[Rachel whispering]
You go first.
[Laura] How come you are not?
-[Rachel] You.
-[Laura] Okay.
Rachel, it's a dead end.
[Rachel] There she is.
I followed her out here.
She tried to escape.
[panting]
[Rachel] She tried to escape!
[Security man]
We're not gonna hurt you.
[Security woman]
Come on, stay right there.
[Security man] Calm down,
we're not gonna hurt you.
Calm down!
We won't hurt you!
[Laura] Stay back!
[Security man] Calm down!
You go back to your room.
[Laura panting]
[panting]
[Laura] No! Wait...
[CJ shushing]
I'm on your side.
[Laura] What are you doing?
[Laura panting]
Shut up and listen.
When you get out
to the parking lot,
head for the trees
on your right,
don't stop till
you hit the road.
Call a woman named Nora Fields.
You get the Teen Law Office.
Tell her what you've
seen in here. Everything.
You got that?
Yeah, yeah.
Nora Fields, right.
[CJ] Come on.
[Laura] Wait, wait,
what about the doors?
Just leave that to me.
[Emergency bell rings]
[CJ] Go, Go!
[grunts]
David, hi, its me.
Now I know it's early.
I'm sorry.
But I need
you to come pick me up.
Eh-- It's a long story.
I'll tell you when you get here.
You sure you wanna do this?
You can always stay
with me you know.
No, everybody's
looking for me.
I just want it all to be over.
Hey, I'll call you later.
Bye.
Mum? Dad?
[Michelle] Baby.
You wouldn't believe
the terrible things--
[Robert] Laura?
They strapped us
in chairs and they...
put straight jackets on
us and they drugged us.
What's wrong.
[Dr. Winslow] She won't
participate in group sessions.
She disobeys all the rules.
She takes no interest
in her own recovery.
I can't believe that's Laura.
Needless to say,
the two week evaluation
period was a bit optimistic.
We suggest that her stay be
extended by at least a month.
A month?
I-- I don't know.
Mr. Mills, your daughter's
behavior has become volatile.
She's a danger to herself.
She's a danger to others.
She requires
24-hour supervision.
Are you prepared to watch
her for that long?
Unless you say to me that you
know what is best
for your daughter, then I'll--
No.
She'll be safer there.
How do we get her
to understand...
that she needs this help?
Let me talk to her.
[steps walking away]
[Laura] You're not taking
me back there.
Laura, the way I see
it you have two choices.
You either come
back to Meadowbrook,
without making a scene...
or I call child services
and you go straight to a
juvenile detention center.
And if you were uncomfortable
at Meadowbrook, believe me...
this is it, choice is yours.
[door opens]
I don't understand why
you're doing this to me.
Everything I told you was true.
Hey.
Call a woman named
Nora, the Teen Law Office,
she'll tell you everything.
You're making
the right decision.
Yeah.
[engine revs]
[van door closes]
[sad music]
I'm going to work.
[defiant music]
Wait a second, you're
not putting me in those.
You ran away, you're
going to be strapped.
No, let go of me!
No! No!
No!
You can't do this, let me out.
You better regulate
your moods Laura.
No! Get that away from me.
You'll feel better
in a few minutes.
[panting]
[sighs hard]
You all right?
I couldn't sleep.
I feel like Judas.
Don't think like that,
we did what we had to.
What if she's
telling the truth
about what goes on in there.
You really think
kids are being drugged
and strapped to chairs?
What if it isn't helping,
what if it's making her worse.
It has to work.
It has to. Otherwise
we have lost everything
that we've ever planned
for her, her whole future.
All of her dreams gone.
When did we ever ask
her what her dreams were?
[Dr. Winslow] Laura?
Laura?
Hello Laura.
How are we doing?
I'm strapped to my bed,
how do you think I'm doing?
Please, Laura, it doesn't
have to be this difficult.
You don't have to fight.
Then let me out and I won't.
It doesn't work that way.
You first have to acknowledge
that you have problems
and that you need our help.
I don't need your help.
[panting]
Just let me out!
You give us no choice
but to continue this
course of treatment
Dr. Winslow, this patient
has had over 30 milligrams
of Cyclizine in
the last 24 hours.
All right. Let her rest.
[grunting]
[rapid door knocks]
Hi.
Listen. I know I'm not
supposed to be here, but...
I just came by to see
how Laura was doing.
Alright?
She's not here.
Oh yeah. Where'd she go?
You sent her back
there, didn't you?
I can't believe you, how
could you do that to her?
We were afraid she
was gonna kill herself.
We had no other choice.
What are you babbling about?
Laura would never kill herself.
What are you
doing here, David?
I told you not to set
foot in this house
until you'd paid back--
Don't worry, you don't have
to lock up the silverware,
I'm leaving.
I just came by to see my sister.
Leave Laura alone.
I don't want you around her.
You've done enough.
Ooh, really?
Hey, I hear the mom of
the year award is coming up.
Maybe Laura and
I will nominate you.
Don't look at him.
He never gets his hands dirty.
He's the man of stone--
All right David.
[David] Aren't you pops.
You can leave now.
If you think Laura's just
going to waltz back in here
and forgive you for
what you've done,
you're both insane.
And you wonder why you're
not welcome in this house.
Oh you make sure to remind
me every chance you get.
[bangs door]
Hi.
Eh--
I was just nowhere
near your neighborhood.
And thought I stop in
for a cup of coffee.
[laughs backwardly]
Are you okay?
[Marty shushing]
Come on, don't cry.
[Marty] Hey, do you believe
in reincarnation?
'Cause I do.
I believe I'm gonna
come back after I die.
And I'm coming back
as rock star,
Michael Jordan, something.
Next time, it's gonna be better.
So when it gets real bad,
you know?
you think about that.
Think about next time,
another chance.
Get a grip.
You belong in your own wing.
You know the rules.
Thank you, Dr. Winslow.
I'll modify my behavior.
Laura...
your moods have
become unmanageable.
You need therapeutic
intervention.
You can't handle
this on your own.
You know that now, don't you?
I think you're ready
to start cooperating.
It's time to let go.
You've gotten a grip on
your anger, haven't you?
[whispering] Yes.
I'm proud of you.
You're gonna be just fine.
[chattering]
Hey, they let you out.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't want
any more trouble.
I'm just gonna do my time.
Tell them everything
they wanna hear.
Good. That's good.
It's easier that way.
Yeah. They made me a level
two for promising to cooperate.
[Marty chuckles]
Took me out of Cyclizine.
So then, you'll be
okay in here without me.
What do you mean?
I'm getting out today?
What happened?
I don't know.
They just told me
to go pack my stuff.
[chuckles]
That's great.
Yeah. Yeah, my dad is
going to come pick me up.
We're gonna go to our house
was going to be a big party.
Everyone's going to be there.
You know.
I'll give you my number.
Now that you're in level two.
You call me, right?
Yeah, I will, I promise.
You gonna be okay
out there, aren't you?
Me? Yes, of course.
I told you I'm all better.
Really.
Okay.
Don't forget
to take your meds.
Yes, I will. I promise.
I-- I'm going to miss you.
[sighs]
You're the only
friend I have in here.
We'll still be friends.
We'll always be friends.
[sighs]
-[Robert] Hi.
-[Woman] Yeah?
-[Nora] What do you want?
-[Robert] Are you Nora Fields?
Last time I looked.
I-- I talked to your
secretary earlier.
My name is Robert Mills.
I got your name
from my daughter.
She's a...
patient...
at Meadowbrook,
which is an adolescent
treatment center.
I know what it is. Sit down.
How'd your daughter get my name.
I don't know.
But she told me that you
knew all about these places.
Is that true?
I advocate for kids who
have been wrongly placed
in institutions
like Meadowbrook,
which you might
if you're like most of them.
That's not to say there
aren't some good ones.
There are, but I'm here
for the ones that aren't.
I'm with this little...
David and Goliath thing here,
you know.
Just glad it's me
and my secretary.
for the whole operation,
so, I'm clearly insane.
Herbal... disgusting.
So, what can I do
for you Mr. Mills?
Eh--
My daughter, Laura
tried to tell us that there are
some pretty awful things
that go on in these places.
And...
to be honest with you,
I don't know what to believe.
Well, if half of what you
said was true, is that enough?
Yeah, I guess it would be.
I guess you got your answer.
Well...
let's hope for her sake
that you got a lousy
insurance policy.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
Now you see the length
of stay in these place,
seems to depend on how much
the insurance will cover.
Insurance runs out, presto
change-o, Johnny's cured.
Well, how can they do that?
That's not right.
[scoffs]
Mr. Mills,
would you buy a car
without checking it out first?
I mean, at least
kicking the tires.
No, of course not.
I hate to tell you this,
but you just bought a lemon.
What do you mean?
Did they give you a
tour of Meadowbrook?
[Robert shuffles on his seat]
All right Mr. Mills, I'm
gonna tell you a little bit
about these private
treatment facilities.
[sad music]
[smile]
[sobbing]
[sighs]
[CJ] Hey, they don't like
you to stay in here
after the social hour.
Thanks.
So, did you get in
trouble after the fire alarm?
That? No, a couple of
days in SR, no big deal.
Sorry.
Forget it. You would've done
the same for me, right?
Listen, you have to stop
getting the injections
once they got you hooked
on the big T you're theirs.
I'm not getting
injections anymore.
They're just giving
me a couple pills.
Good. You have to
start cheeking them.
Why do you care
what happens to me?
I just do that sometimes.
Come on.
I went to see someone today,
a woman from the
Teen Law Office.
I think Laura was
telling the truth
about the things that
go on in that place.
Why are you doing this?
She needs to be there to
be watched 24 hours a day.
These places like
Meadowbrook are dumping grounds
for parents looking
for easy answers.
Easy answers?
There's a lot of kids that
don't even belong there.
Th-- This woman, she was telling
me that these hospitals,
they overcharge and
double building insurance
until they bleed them dry.
And then they stamp
cured on the kid's file
and turn them loose.
That's not happening
at Meadowbrook.
We were there.
Honey, I think we gotta
get her out of there
and into some kind
of family counseling.
[Michelle sighs heavily]
You always do this to me.
We take a stand together
and then you fold
and I'm left picking
up the pieces.
If it weren't for me,
nothing would get
done in this family.
Hey, I work my off every day.
-[Michelle] And I don't?
-[Robert] I didn't say that.
You know, if you had been there,
if you had been available
for your children,
if you would've been willing
to take a stand just once,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
I have a responsibility
to my child.
She needs me to
be strong for her
and I'm going to be strong.
Where are you going?
Out.
[door knocks]
-[Robert]
-Hi.
I was wondering
if we could talk.
Yeah. It's late.
I know. I thought maybe
we could get a beer.
Sure.
As long as
it's non-alcoholic.
I heard Stewart's
dad gave you a job.
Yeah, they got a big
contract with the city.
Need an extra hand.
It's nothing much,
it's just got me doing
some groundwork for now.
Mostly sub-metering, three-phase
wiring, stuff like that.
Oh, that's great.
Look...
I know you didn't bring me
here to talk about my job.
I know you brought
Laura home the other day.
But David, I need to know
did she say anything
about what goes
on in that place?
Yeah, she did.
Sound like a concentration
camp in there.
And you believe her?
She wouldn't lie to me.
[sighs hard]
We really trying to do
what we thought was best.
She thought it was best?
Wait til she gets
out of that place.
And she has to go back to school
where everyone knows
she was in a nuthouse.
It's getting late....
No. Wait, wait, Please.
Look, I didn't kind of
just talk about Laura. I--
I came because I
needed to talk to you.
Look, David. I know how
hard this has been for you.
It hasn't been
any easier for me.
Your mother and I, we
haven't said two civil words
to each other since you left.
So it's my fault then?
No, no, no.
I have no one to
blame, but myself,
I know I haven't been
the perfect husband
or the perfect father.
But I'd still like to
think that you and I could...
[chuckles]
It's a little late for
you to try and be my dad.
Don't you think?
I mean, it's not like
we're going to go
in the backyard and chuck
the old football around.
Yeah, you're right.
But I'm still your father
and I love you.
[sighs]
Look, do you want me to
let you off the hook?
Fine. You're off the hook.
I screwed up, I know that.
Living with me was no picnic
either,
but I'm okay now.
I'm not carrying any grudges.
Things just turned out
the way they turned out.
You know, end of story.
So you can just stop feeling
sorry for yourself, okay?
Thanks for the soda.
Hey, come on.
Let's go back to your room.
[Laura] Come on.
everything's gonna be okay.
You all right?
Come on,
let's just lie down.
Come on.
[door creaking]
What are you doing here?
Maybe I should ask
you the same thing.
Listen, don't let
no one come in please.
Fine, tell me what
you're doing in there.
Why don't we just
go back to our rooms
and forget about
everything, okay?
Come on. The attendee
comes by 40 seconds.
Fine.
Thanks.
Now we're even.
Open.
Tongue?
I'm proud of the way
you've been taking
your medication lately.
You've just earned
yourself another 10 points.
[Counselor] It's nice to have
you joining us again Laura.
I don't suppose you're ready
to start participating.
My name's Laura
and I'm an alcoholic.
No, listen.
I've told you a hundred
times, I cannot do it anymore.
That's it.
I know, I know, I
know, I'm sorry.
Look, it's my fault.
I guess I have to
get it together.
I have a family.
I gotta start being
there for my kids.
You know?
No, I'm sorry.
It's over.
That's it.
Oh.
Mr. Mills.
What can I do for you?
Well, I've come to get Laura.
Yes. Is there a problem?
No, no, no, no.
There is no problem.
We just want her at home.
We, is your wife here?
No, she couldn't come.
I see, have a seat.
[Robert clears throat]
No, that's all right.
I think I'll stand.
Mr. Mills, it is not advisable
for you to take
Laura out of here
before her treatment
is complete.
Just show me where to sign.
I'm afraid it's not that easy.
We have been authorized
by you, her legal guardian
and your insurance company
to perform a service.
We have diagnosed her as
being severely depressed.
That's enough to mandate a
stay here for up to six months.
Six months?
What are you talking about?
Let me try to explain
this as simply as I can.
If you take Laura out of
here against medical advice
and she harms herself, you
could be liable for negligence.
You could lose custody
of your daughter.
Look, I-- I'll take my chance.
Please go get my daughter.
I don't know what to tell you.
I'm terribly sorry, Mr. Mills.
I'm afraid I can't
let you take her
without your wife's consent.
Wh-- What are you talking about?
There were two signatures
here on the admissions form.
Under state law, you
to have joint custody.
We'll need her signature.
That's the law.
My hands are tied.
[sighs]
Phone privilege allows
you three calls per week.
All calls must be kept
to under five minutes,
your conversation
will be monitored.
[David's answering machine]
Hi, this is Dave
and I'm not here to take
your call, so please...
I got the machine.
Can I make another call?
Okay.
[Woman] Hello?
Hi is Marty there?
[Woman] Who is this?
I'm a friend of
his from Meadowbrook.
Can I speak to him?
Hello?
What?
[sad music]
[chattering]
Marty's dead.
He killed himself.
Huh-- yeah.
He told me that his father
was gonna pick him up.
Whole family was gonna
have a big party for him.
Marty didn't have a dad.
He lived alone with his
grandmother at the trailer park.
[sobbing]
He told me that everything
was gonna be okay.
He wasn't ready to go.
Listen, whatever
problems he had,
they only got worse in here.
As far as they're concerned,
the only thing he suffered from
was insurance
deficiency syndrome.
They shouldn't
have let him out.
It happens all
the time.
I'm sorry.
[crying]
Michelle. We have
to go get Laura.
They won't release her
without your signature.
I'm busy right now.
We can just come
back some other time.
It's all right, he's leaving.
I have people here,
this is my work.
What is more important?
You work or our daughter?
Will you excuse me.
Michelle.
This is not the time to
talk about Laura's problems.
Well maybe the problem
isn't with Laura.
Oh, it's me, huh? I'm
too demanding a profe--
Maybe you are. Maybe--
I work too much
for my children.
Somebody has to want
something from them.
What do you think I'm doing.
I raised those kids.
I made their life
out of nothing,
where the hell were you?
Fine, why don't you
admit you're married a man
who couldn't live up
to your expectations.
I guess your girlfriends
probably have lower
expectations,
Right? But I deserve a better.
We're just gonna
leave our card.
No, I'm sorry.
[Michelle] Please. I-- I--
[sighs]
Man, Look, the attendant
is going to be by in a minute,
Just go back to your room.
No, I wanna go on with you.
Unless you want me to
go get the attendant.
We can both explain to him
why we're standing out here.
[sighs heavily]
Help me with this.
[door creaks]
Here, don't lose it.
It's the key to this room.
Alright, come on.
[CJ] We're gonna look to all
these files over here.
When you start to take out
those files right up there.
What are we looking for?
Anything with a dollar
amount, the billing records,
stuff like this here.
See this amount here?
$860 is their actual
cost of medication
for one patient from the
weeks 8-6 six to 8-19.
This is what they billed
the insurance company.
$20,600?
Insurance fraud.
Grab those files right there.
Why aren't you trying
to bust them
for all the other stuff
that goes on in here?
The way they torture kids.
Those complaints have to
be filed as malpractice suits
and you're impossible to win.
The way to beat them is
to expose the fraud.
When the insurance
company stopped paying,
this place goes out of business.
This is crazy.
[suspenseful music]
Who are they?
These are names of
people I collected
taking kickback
money for referrals,
school administrators,
counselors, teachers,
they are on the tape.
Dale Carlson is my
guidance counselor.
Not bad, he's nine grand
richer than he was a year ago.
I get this into the right hands,
this place goes out of business.
Who are you, really.
My real name is Jason.
I'm not really 17.
I work for Nora Fields.
She is the one who got me
in here to try to get
enough evidence--
[rattle]
[CJ] Come on.
CJ...
looks like you'll
have some explaining to do.
Why don't you wait outside?
Hmm?
[door creaks and closes]
Well, do you wanna tell me
what you were looking for?
Just looking around
and the door was open.
[suspenseful music]
Peterson...
Colin James, nickname's, CJ.
[CJ]
What are you gonna do with me?
[Dr. Winslow] I don't know.
We'll go to restraint
while I decide it.
It's clear that you've
become a danger,
and not only to
yourself, but to others.
After all,
starting a fire in the records
office is a serious crime.
It's a good thing I
caught it in time.
[phone dialing]
-[Man] Hello.
-[Laura] Hi, it's me.
-[Man] It's late.
-[Laura] I know, I know.
But I need you to do
something for me.
You're leaving?
I was saving this for Laura.
I wanted our beautiful baby
girl to wear this at her wedding
[sobbing]
Oh Robert, what happened?
[crying]
How did I push everybody
away, was I so terrible?
It wasn't just you.
I-- I wanted to be perfect.
Some of us can't be
perfect, I'm sorry.
I am sorry-- I am sorry
for a lot of things, but...
But it's too late.
I don't know.
But we can't let our problems
destroy our kids any longer.
We've got to save our family.
I don't know how to do that.
We've got to start by getting
Laura out of that place.
Alright?
Okay.
[hopeful music]
[phone rings]
What do we have here?
Yeah.
Nora, Hi, its me Laura.
Sorry, Laura?
I'm still stuck
here in Meadowbrook.
Can't wait to get
out of this place.
Laura, right, how are you?
Okay. I guess.
It seems
like ages since we've talked.
Yeah. Ages.
Hey, it's Jason there.
Jason. No.
Jason stepped out.
He's not in
trouble again is he?
No, not trouble.
It's just he went out.
He'll be back in a little while.
I'll tell him that you called.
Great.
Your birthday's coming up.
I haven't forgotten.
I have something for you.
Jason helped me pick it out.
But I guess he won't be
able to get it to you
until I get out.
Eh--
Listen to my time's up.
I have to go.
No, Laura, just
wait a minute. Okay?
No, I really should go.
I'll call you again.
Laura.
Okay.
Gladys, call the
district attorney's office.
I'm getting the police.
How can all of last month's
billing records be gone?
I don't understand this.
I told you, I don't
know where they are.
You're lying.
You've hidden them somewhere.
Even if I did know why.
Why would I tell you now that
I know real scam that goes on
in this place.
Scam?
We provide a service here.
We save lives.
So you need to justify
ripping off insurance companies?
If that's what
it takes to stop.
One more kid from
slitting his wrists.
Yes. That's how I justify it.
All right, that's a winner.
I'd love to be there to see you
explain that one to the D.A.
Listen to me you little punk.
I don't know who
you think you are
but one phone call from me and
there is no more CJ Peterson.
You will spend the rest of
your life in a padded room.
You gonna spend the
rest of yours in jail so.
You're gonna tell
me where files are.
Kiss my--
[CJ grunts]
[panting]
[Alright]
Dr. Winslow, your
telephone's has been waiting
for over half an hour.
I want everyone to
confined to their rooms.
Dr Winslow, Hi I'm Mr.Sanders,
I spoke to you on the
telephone yesterday.
Yes Mr. Sanders, sorry
I kept you waiting. I--
Dr. Winslow, we've
come for Laura.
We want her out of here with
or without your signatures.
Now you lied to me. I checked.
I did not,
it's hospital policy--
Fine, whatever. Where is she?
Forgive me.
Something has come
up, please excuse me.
I'll be back in a few minutes
to start the paperwork.
Hey, don't walk away from me.
We are not gonna
wait any longer.
Mr. Mills. I will
tell Ms. Collins
to start the release forms.
There's nothing in here.
[Security man]
I don't understand.
I heard you talking
to Dr. Winslow.
Is there some kind of
problem with this place
that I should know about?
[Repair man]
I don't get it either.
All I know is we got a signal
down at the switching station
that said the problem was
coming from your cafeteria.
[Nurse] Oh yeah?
It's just ridiculous.
I'm not gonna wait for them.
I want you to go get Laura,
we haven't got all day.
I don't know if I can do that.
Oh, I think you can.
[Ms. Collins] Dr. Winslow...
her parents
won't wait any longer.
All right. Take her out.
I won't be long.
[Nurse]
Dr. Winslow, the ward is clear.
Dr. Winslow.
You dropped this.
[dramatic music]
Ms. Collins!
[grunts]
[Ms. Collins] Come on! Get her!
-[Robert] Come on--
-[Laura] Dad!
Dad! Get off me!
[Robert] Laura!
[Dr. Winslow] Calm down.
[Laura] Let me go!
Let me go.
Laura, don't make a scene.
She doesn't have it!
Let her go or
I'll call the police.
[Dr. Winslow] We have reason to
believe that your daughter
is hiding drugs in her room.
He's lying I don't know
what he's talking about.
We're taking our
daughter over here.
Now this patient has a
borderline personality disorder.
She is a danger to herself
and to everyone around her.
Dr. Winslow, I want to see CJ.
If you take her out of here now
you're going to be liable--
Dr. Winslow!
We have a warrant to
search these premises.
What the hell was that
all about anyway?
It's a long story,
I'll tell you later.
I don't know what to
say, these things happen.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Yes!
You're about ready?
Yeah, almost.
You might wanna leave
some of this stuff.
My place ain't that big.
[Laura chuckles]
[David sighs]
Folks getting along any better?
They're trying.
So what's the verdict
on the college thing?
I just told 'em
that I needed some time
to sort things out.
Maybe I'll go next year.
[grunts]
All right. Let's do it.
[Michelle] You have everything?
Yeah.
Did you want to take your TV?
No need still got the
one I stole from you guys.
Right.
[Robert sighs]
So Laura, just wanna make
sure that you know that...
your father and I
don't want you to go.
Mom, leave it alone,
it's her decision.
I'm telling her how I feel.
[David]
Mom, it's her decision--
[Michelle]
I'm telling her how--
Every time is going to
be like that?
Will you guys please
just stop fighting?
[sighs heavily]
[sighs]
Let's get out of here.
[Robert]
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is ridiculous.
You're right.
I don't want to fight anymore.
We've all made
a lot of mistakes.
We love you.
Um...
Maybe you can come by
for dinner this weekend.
Both of you.
Mom's cooking.
[chuckles]
Could be dangerous.
I think we'd like that.
[smiles]
Bye.