♪♪♪♪[Gimme some lovin' playing]
♪♪ Hey ♪♪
♪♪ well my
temperature's rising ♪♪
♪♪ and my feet
on the floor ♪♪
♪♪ 20 people rockin'
and there wanna go more ♪♪
♪♪ let me in baby,
I don't know
what you've got ♪♪
♪♪ but you'd better
take it easy,
this place is hot ♪♪
♪♪ so glad we made it ♪♪
♪♪ you gotta
gimme some lovin' ♪♪
(Chorus)
♪♪ gimme gimme some lovin' ♪♪
♪♪ gimme some lovin' ♪♪
(Chorus)
♪♪ gimme gimme some lovin' ♪♪
♪♪ gimme some lovin' ♪♪
♪♪ everyday ♪♪
(Photographer)
Linda, just one
more picture, please.
Thank you.
She hates being
on this side of the lens.
[Giggling]
♪♪ Hey ♪♪
♪♪ well I feel so good ♪♪
That old beatle magic
still draws a crowd.
They came here for you,
not for me.
You're the star here.
[Giggling]
I am so proud of you.
Linda, fabulous.
Oh, Danny,
I'm so pleased
that you came.
Sensational, ain't she?
Sensational.
(Photographer #2)
Diane, give US a smile.
(Chorus)
♪♪ gimme gimme some lovin' ♪♪
♪♪ gimme some lovin' ♪♪
♪♪ everyday ♪♪♪♪
This is
incredibly intimate.
(Elton) Paul. Paul,
could I just have
a word for a moment?
Go.
Hey, Elton.
So nice to see you, mate.
Hi.
This is wonderful.
(Photographer #3)
Picture, please.
How lucky to have
a husband with access
to all these
famous people.
[Giggles]
I didn't know
Paul back then.
(Woman) He does make
quite a good subject though.
♪♪♪♪[I want to hold your hand
by the Beatles playing]
♪♪ Oh, yeah, I'll ♪♪
(Linda) I first saw him
at shea stadium, 1965.
I was just another girl
in love with the Beatles
and his music
and his being young.
♪♪ I want to hold
your hand ♪♪
♪♪ oh, please say to me ♪♪♪♪
Are you ready?
(Linda) I was a divorced
single mother
working at a glossy
society magazine,
opening mail
and helping out
around the office.
I was board stiff,
but I made enough
to pay the rent.
The pink Chanel suit
on page 10. Yeah.
You can find it at saks,
and you're welcome.
[People chattering]
I could almost touch
the Beatles
when they walked by.
Weren't they fab?
I couldn't hear them
through the screaming.
I still like
the stones better.
I love them all.
Oh, hey, Rick.
Come here for a sec.
We need your opinion
on something.
Mmm.
Now who do you like better,
the Beatles or the stones?
The who?
That's another group.
The rolling stones.
Now you want to sell
some magazines,
you put them
on your cover.
They are so sexy.
Never heard of 'em.
Anyway, June
is the Deb cover.
Oh, boring, boring, boring.
The Deb of the year
in a long white gown.
Look at US, Rick.
We are young.
We're interested
in pop stars.
We're not interested
in being debs.
It's out of the question.
[Sighing]
[Phone ringing]
He's going to do it.
You just watch.
I know he is gonna do it.
Why would he
listen to you?
He doesn't even
know who they are.
My father's company
owns the magazine.
Daddy's the president
of hearst.
[Chuckling]
Oh, of course.
(Woman) You know
it's such a good idea.
It's so groovy.
Oh, god. Felicia?
Come here.
What?
"Meet the rolling stones
on board the taconite
"in a press conference
to kick off
their u.S. Tour."
[Sighing]
Well, it's addressed
to the magazine.
And there are no names.
Ok, so you go
to Rick's office,
and you remind him
that the cover story
was your idea...
Right.
...and that you insist,
you insist on going.
Ok. All right. Ok.
Hey, I'm going
as your photographer.
[Felicia sighing]
(Male photographer) Excuse me.
You-- you on the left,
can I get a shot here?
(Man) Hey, guys,
move closer.
Hey, which one are you?
[Photographers chattering]
What's the difference
between the stones
and the Beatles?
This.
[Laughing]
(Male photographer #2)
Right-- right here, fellas.
Right-- right here.
(Reporter) You-- you two,
how'd you like america?
Ok, listen up, everybody.
It's time
for the photo shoot.
I need all the photographers
to move along board
right over here.
Let's go.
Uh, sweetheart?
Hello?
You, too.
Right this way.
Linda?
Oh, Linda, hi.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
Rick insisted
he wants a photo.
Oh.
You're wearing that
to meet the stones?
Why not? Let's go.
[People chattering]
Ok. Just-- just one more.
Just one more.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you so much.
I want another drink.
[Felicia exclaiming]
(Felicia)
Thanks.
(Mick) Did you get
what you want?
Is that what you need?
Hi.
[Men chuckling]
Uh-huh. Oh, so nice.
[Giggling]
Beautiful.
Thank you.
Thank you both.
Right.
I am so attracted to her.
I can't quite
figure you out.
You American girls.
Uh-huh.
I want to f...You.
[Whispering]
When?
Now.
Where?
Down below.
So, what's your name?
(Felicia) I told you so.
I think Mick likes me.
Oh, what gives you
that impression?
[Both laughing]
He asked me out,
and I'm going.
Felicia!
Oh, Danny,
where were you?
My stupid photographer
made me late.
Oh, my god.
Did you take pictures?
Do you have any I can buy?
Hi. I'm Linda eastman.
Hi.
This is my friend,
Danny fields.
He's the new editor
for datebook magazine.
Oh.
You'll like Linda.
She hates city and village
almost as much as I do.
And you're in luck, darling,
because she got
some fabulous shots.
(Linda) That one afternoon
set my life
on a new course.
I started hanging around
in clubs with my camera.
I never thought
of it as a job,
although, eventually,
I did earn
my living from it.
[Camera clicking]
Somebody said
there was an amazing
group down at ondines,
♪♪♪♪[music playing]
So I went down there.
[All clamoring]
I had no idea I was
photographing futur e icons.
Although the doors
were huge in L.A.,
no one had
ever heard of them
in New York.
Andy, I love
your movies.
♪♪ You men eat your dinner
eat your pork and beans ♪♪
♪♪ I eat more chicken
than any man ever seen ♪♪
♪♪ yeah, yeah ♪♪
♪♪ I'm a back door man ♪♪
♪♪ the men don't know ♪♪
♪♪ but the little girls
understand ♪♪
[Screaming]
♪♪ I'm a back door man ♪♪
♪♪ I'm a back door man ♪♪♪♪
Hey, gorgeous.
Hi.
How you doing?
Good.
So, listen. There's
this guy coming to town.
His name is Jack auga.
He's signing up
a rock and roll magazine
on the coast,
and he needs pictures.
Honey, you should meet him.
Cool. Good.
Pretty good.
[Crowd cheering]
[People whistling]
Nice, huh?
Hmm.
[People clamoring]
(Linda) My early pictures
came out
of my friendships
with the musicians.
We'd meet, and since
I always had my camera,
I'd take photos
while we hung out.
If things happened later,
well, the '60s was
a very different time.
[Church bells ringing]
(Jim) It's been a while
since I was in church.
I love the light here.
The architecture.
It's like being
in a painting.
It is real peaceful.
So what was
it like for you
before you became
Jim Morrison
of the doors?
I was a fat,
little military brat.
Your dad was military?
Mere admiral.
U.s. Navy.
Hmm.
Oh, I hated everything
he stood for, though.
Tell me.
It's about being tough.
Macho.
Stiff upper lip thing,
you know?
Hmm.
Poetry was for wimps.
You didn't talk
about pain.
[Sighing]
[Phone ringing]
[Exhaling]
Stay right here.
I'll be right back.
(Linda) Hello.
Heather. Hi, baby.
[Birds chirping]
[Dog barking]
(Linda) Heather,
come here.
Let's show grandpa
what you learned.
Ooh. That's terrific,
sweetheart.
Is she taking lessons?
She's too young.
Not too young
to be thinking
about her education.
What about
the Dalton school?
She loves
her nursery school.
Wait too long,
and she won't get in.
Dad, sis,
dinner's ready.
Hey, come on.
Dad, you haven't said
what you think.
I'm not thrilled
my daughter's
hanging around
with a bunch
of long hairs.
Did you like my work?
It's nothing
to hang on the wall.
This magazine's
going to be gone
in 6 months.
Dad, I got a contract
to, uh, take pictures
for a book.
Do you-- do you
want to give me some
free legal advice?
Let's have a look.
Rock and other
4 letter words.
Yeah.
They're paying me
to take pictures
of rock groups.
Well, you didn't sign
this I hope.
This deal is lousy.
Don't tell me
not to do it.
Are you kidding?
A measly $1,000 advance?
Yeah.
It gets me to San Francisco
and Los Angeles and London.
I have to get
the Beatles.
What do you want to go
to London for?
It's a waste
of time and money.
I already bought
the tickets.
♪♪♪♪[Yeh yeh by Georgie fame
and the blue flames playing]
♪♪ That's what I say
I say yeah yeah ♪♪
♪♪ we'll play a melody ♪♪
♪♪ and turn the lights
down low so that
no one can see ♪♪
♪♪ we gotta do that,
we gotta do that ♪♪
♪♪ and there'll be
no one else alive ♪♪
♪♪ in all the world
'cept you and me ♪♪
♪♪ pretty baby,
I never knew
such a thrill ♪♪
♪♪ just thought
I'd tell you because
I'm trembling still ♪♪
♪♪ but pretty baby,
I want you all
for my own ♪♪
♪♪ I think I'm ready
to leave those
others alone ♪♪
♪♪ no need to ask me
if everything's ok ♪♪
♪♪ I got my answer,
the only thing I can say ♪♪
♪♪ I say yeah, yeah ♪♪
♪♪ that's what I say,
I say yeah, yeah ♪♪
yeah, yeah ♪♪
♪♪ We'll play a melody ♪♪
♪♪ and turn the lights
down low so that
no one can see ♪♪
♪♪ we gotta do that,
we gotta do that ♪♪
♪♪ and there'll be
no one else alive ♪♪
♪♪ in all the world
'cept you and me ♪♪
♪♪ pretty baby,
I never knew
such a thrill ♪♪
♪♪ just thought
I'd tell you because
I'm trembling still ♪♪
♪♪ but pretty baby,
I want you all
for my own ♪♪
Oh, sorry.
(Both) Hi.
How you doing?
Good. Good.
I'm Paul McCartney.
[Giggling]
I know.
You and your mates,
you-- are you just leaving?
No. No.
All right. Well,
we were about to go
to another club.
Care to join US?
Yes. Sure.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Great.
You come in our car.
Ok.
Hey, les.
♪♪ We'll play a melody ♪♪
♪♪ and turn the lights
down low so that
no one can see ♪♪♪♪
[People clamoring]
So where did you
come from then?
You wouldn't believe this.
Yes, I will.
I'm a photographer.
Yeah?
Yes.
From New York.
I came to get photos
of the Beatles.
So you knew
where I'd be?
No. No.
I was just out
with my friends.
It was pure coincidence.
Or fate.
Do you believe in fate?
Definitely.
(Linda)
I'd left my portfolio
for Brian Epstein,
the Beatles' manager.
2 days later he called
to say he liked my work
and invited me
to a press launch
for the Beatles' fabulous
new album, sergeant pepper.
Right, hey, girls,
what are you
doing later?
[People chattering]
(Les)
All right, all right,
that's it for now.
(John) No, no,
I'm too tired, mate.
(Les) Let's give the lads
a break, here, ok? Thanks.
(John) Small,
but we did...
Did you get everything
you needed? Nice one.
[People chattering]
Who came up with
sergeant pepper?
It's brilliant.
(Paul) Oh, thanks.
It was my idea.
A bit of a disguise
for the lads.
Change of identity.
[Linda giggling]
Just a bit of fun,
you know?
And the name,
sergeant pepper?
Well, you know
those little packets
you get on airplanes?
Mmm-hmm.
Someone said to me,
"oh, could you
pass me the salt
and pepper?"
And I thought,
salt and pepper.
Sergeant pepper.
Just a bit of a pun.
That's all.
Playing with words.
What a mind.
And, uh, lonely hearts
club band just seemed
to flow.
Traveling band. Gypsies.
And are you
a lonely heart?
Well, that depends,
doesn't it?
How long are
you staying?
I have to get back.
I have a little daughter,
Heather. She's 4.
So you're a mother?
Mmm-hmm.
I miss her when I'm away.
Oh, kids are great.
I love 'em.
I envy blokes
who have 'em.
I plan to have a family
of my own some day.
[Motorcycle engine rumbling]
Heather!
[Laughing] Where are
your clothes, monkey?
I took 'em off.
Can I take your picture?
Come here.
Oh, you look perfect.
Put your arms right here.
(Man) Hi, how are you?
[Clicks]
That's good.
Danny, I'm in love.
Yeah, so what's he like?
Did you sleep with him?
None of your business.
Well, did you?
Why does it matter?
Linda.
Danny.
No, I didn't.
We are talking
about Paul McCartney
of the Beatles?
Heartthrob of millions?
Ok, so you didn't have
sex with him.
You've spent no time alone.
You don't know when
you'll see him again.
And you were together
for what, like, an hour?
Mmm.
Do you want
something to drink?
Yeah.
Danny, when have
I ever said that
I was in love?
Honey, what about
this actress,
uh, what's her name?
Jane something.
He's been living with her
for 5 years.
He'll never marry her.
Has he asked you?
He doesn't know
my number.
(Linda) I didn't see Paul
for a whole year,
but from the moment
we met, I somehow knew
we'd meet again.
[Male announcer chattering
on TV.]
In 1968, he and John
came to New York
to announce
their new company,
apple records.
(Male reporter)
The contract dispute.
(Male reporter #2)
Are you planning to leave
your old label, boys?
Was there a falling out?
It's all about
the music, lads.
Teamwork, integrity,
working together as a band.
(Paul) Artistic freedom.
It's the, uh,
it's the Beatles answer
to men in suits.
You know,
controlled weirdness,
'cause the, uh,
the bosses aren't in it
for the profits.
Yeah. A kind
of western communism.
(Female reporter)
Are you a socialist?
(Male reporter #3)
When are you going
to cut your hair?
[People laughing]
That's all. Thank you.
[Reporters clamoring]
(Linda) There.
Now he has my number.
[Giggling]
Cool.
Hi, it's Linda eastman.
Are there any messages?
(Woman) Yeah.
Paul McCartney
from London.
He did-- did-- he did?
Did--did he leave a number?
No. He's on his way
to Los Angeles
and would like you
to meet him there
at the Beverly Hills hotel.
Is that it?
Isn't that enough?
[Birds chirping]
Hello?
Paul?
Hi.
You're here.
Yeah. Of course.
[Moaning]
[Giggling]
Want some more?
Yeah.
[Giggling]
[Birds chirping]
[Exhaling]
Good morning.
Hey.
What are you doing?
The light here
reminds me of Tucson.
Tucson.
Is that a real place?
Mmm-hmm. In Arizona.
I always dream
of a little house there,
an adobe,
and a-- and a horse.
Is that where you grew up?
No. It's where I got free.
Got free?
(Linda) Yeah.
Society. Husband.
Family.
It's so beautiful there.
Desert.
It's nature
all around you.
When I was growing up
in liverpool...
Mmm.
...i used to go
into the woods
looking for frogs.
Frogs?
Mmm, frogs.
With me,
it was salamanders.
Salamanders, eh?
Mmm.
That's nice.
Mmm-hmm.
(Paul) She was a nurse.
Midwife.
I remember one night,
her riding off in the dark
on her bike 'cause a baby
was on the way.
[Crickets chirping]
Very kind
and loving, me mum.
She used to say to me--
she used to say,
"hey, just let it be, son."
If I was upset
or something,
just let it be.
Mmm, what was her name?
Mary.
Hmm.
Mary McCartney.
Oh, she never said
a word to the doctors
or any of the nurses
about the lump
in her breast
or the pain.
Typical nurse perhaps.
Took care of everybody else
but not herself, you know?
By the time they did
the mastectomy,
it was too late.
How old were you?
14.
Me brother was 12.
And one terrible night,
US boys went down
the hospital.
Oh, they must have known
she was dying,
but we didn't really know
what was happening.
It turned out to be
our last visit.
(Linda) I had never
forgotten that story
Paul told me 27 years ago.
I felt his pain,
and I never wanted him
to feel that way again.
Hey, good morning.
Oh.
Oh, I overslept?
Stay in bed. I'm off.
I'll phone you
from the studio.
Mmm.
Isn't chrissie
coming today?
[Yawning] Uh-huh.
A lump?
What kind of lump?
It's nothing. It's like
this little swollen gland
or something.
The doctor said
it was a virus
or a flu or something,
and he's having me
take antibiotics
and rest and...
Does Paul know?
Do you want
to try my chili?
(Both) It's vegetarian.
Whoa. That's hot.
Thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
When's the last time
you had a mammogram?
Mmm.
It's been a while.
It is good and hot--
if ever.
Uh, look, McCartney,
you got to get
this checked out.
[Mumbling]
Yeah. Yeah. I know.
Typical chrissie hynde.
Hey, I don't want
to lose you.
Promise you'll go
up to London
and see a specialist.
I promise.
And tell your husband,
for god's sakes.
I don't want him to worry.
(Man on intercom)
There's a phone call
for you, Mr. McCartney.
[Piano stops playing]
Hello.
(Linda) Hi, it's me.
[Sniffing]
I got the results
of the test.
And?
It's not good.
Mmm-hmm.
It's all right, baby.
It's all right.
[Crying] So sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, it is not
your fault, ok?
There are so many
things I can do,
and I can beat this.
I know I can.
It's not like mum.
They've got
all these new drugs
and treatments now.
Besides, you caught it
early, didn't you?
You caught it early.
You didn't even know
it was there.
I think, maybe--
[Shushing] Listen.
We'll go anywhere
in the world.
We'll find the best
specialist there is.
We'll beat it.
You'll see.
[Whispering] I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, baby.
(Mason) We'll treat
it aggressively.
First radiation,
then chemotherapy.
No mastectomy.
No.
The cancer's moved
beyond the breast
into the lymph nodes.
Chemo is systemic.
It attacks the cancer
wherever it's hiding
in the body.
Now, it won't be a picnic.
You'll probably
be tired, nauseous,
very weak.
You may lose your hair.
It's a good idea
to be fitted
for a wig now,
so they can match
your hair color.
How soon do you start?
The sooner the better.
Right away then.
[Birds chirping]
[Scissors snipping]
You've never looked
more beautiful, darling.
(Heather)
How do I look, mummy?
You are going to look
so beautiful.
Your grandpa will be
so proud.
[Phone ringing]
Hold on. Hang on.
Hello.
Hello, Linda.
It's-- it's Paul.
Hi.
(Paul) Hi.
Listen, uh,
how'd you fancy
spending some time
with me in London?
When?
As soon as you can.
We're in the studio
working on an album.
Just come.
It might not be
so easy to get away.
I want to see you.
♪♪ Oh, yeah, I'll ♪♪
♪♪ tell you something ♪♪
♪♪ I think you'll understand ♪♪
♪♪ when I say
that something ♪♪
♪♪ I want to hold
your hand ♪♪
[Clamoring]
I'll bet
they're friendly,
this one.
She looks like a tart,
doesn't she?
Yeah.
♪♪ Now let me
hold your hand ♪♪
Hello, love. I'm Maggie.
I'm the housekeeper.
I'll just be off
then, love.
He said to make
yourself at home.
See you later.
Ok.
♪♪ I feel happy inside ♪♪
What's going on, Maggie?
Who's the new girl?
(Maggie) She's an American,
don't you know? A divorcee.
♪♪ I can't hide ♪♪
♪♪ yeah, you've got
that something ♪♪
♪♪ I think
you'll understand ♪♪
♪♪ when I say
that somethin' ♪♪
♪♪ I want to hold
your hand ♪♪
♪♪ I want to hold y
our hand ♪♪
♪♪ and when I touch you
I feel happy ♪♪
♪♪ inside ♪♪
♪♪ it's such a feelin'
that my love ♪♪
♪♪ I can't hide,
I can't hide ♪♪
♪♪ I can't hide ♪♪
♪♪ yeah, you've got
that something ♪♪
♪♪ I think
you'll understand ♪♪
♪♪ when I say
that something ♪♪♪♪
[Squealing]
Hi.
How are you?
Well, at least
you're friendly.
[Laughing]
[Girls clamoring]
Girls,
just give US a break.
Give US a break.
[Girls screaming]
Paul, we love you!
[Crickets chirping]
[Panting]
(Girl) I'm saving myself
for you, Paul!
[Squealing]
[Girl yelling]
I really wasn't sure
you'd come.
Of course.
Who are those girls?
Oh, the girls.
Apple scruffs,
we call them.
The eyes and ears
of the world.
Do they stay all night?
Oh, yeah.
They've been camped
out there for months.
Years, some of them.
What a drag.
Don't worry.
They're harmless.
Hmm.
Bitch.
Sure is.
Yeah.
♪♪♪♪[Playing piano]
[Both whispering]
[John and yoko giggling]
That's so much better
than Paul's intro.
You have to use it.
[Paul tapping Mike]
All right. That's enough.
Can we go, please?
Could we just go?
Obladi oblada.
I hate your stinking song.
Pure rubbish.
Oh, right.
Is that your opinion,
John, or hers?
I can speak for myself.
Oh, is that so?
I hadn't noticed.
(Ringo)
The vocals done yet?
Yeah. Come on.
Come on.
Playback please.
(Technician)
From the top.
Got to use the loo.
(John) Come on.
He needs her
in the loo with him?
It's the junk, man.
He's messed up.
Is it always like this?
[Sighing]
Not when it's just
the 4 of US.
But since yoko came
on the scene,
it's been bloody hell.
I'm losing me best mate,
and there's nothing
I can do about it.
You can use a day off.
(Paul) I'm sorry.
I'm really tired,
that's all.
Hey, it's allowed.
♪♪♪♪[Please please me
by the Beatles playing]
See, the thing is,
to top it off,
apple's a bus without brakes
since Brian died.
Mmm-hmm.
The accountant's quit.
Bleeding red ink
all over the place.
If this keeps up,
we'll be broke in 6 months.
Hey, I have an idea.
Let's get lost.
[Linda laughing]
What are you
talking about?
Let's get lost.
Darling, when
you're driving,
that's the last thing
you want to do.
Just try it.
I can't.
I'll navigate.
Turn off here. Turn.
No.
Turn.
♪♪ Why do I always have
to say love ♪♪
♪♪ come on, come on,
come on, come on ♪♪
♪♪ please please me,
whoa, yeah ♪♪
♪♪ like I please you ♪♪
♪♪ I don't wanna
sound complainin' ♪♪
♪♪ but you know there's
always rain in my heart ♪♪
♪♪ in my heart ♪♪
♪♪ I'll do all the pleasin'
with you ♪♪
♪♪ it's so hard to reason
♪♪ whoa yeah ♪♪
Well, for heaven's sake.
♪♪ Last night I said
these words to my girl ♪♪♪♪
[Birds chirping]
Are you hungry?
I brought food.
Oh, yeah.
Do you do this often?
When real life
starts pressing on me,
I just let go.
Oh, I'm the opposite.
I tell myself
I have to cope.
Oh, I hate that word.
Life's too short.
I wish you didn't have
to leave tomorrow.
Me, too.
I miss Heather.
Yeah, I know, but
I just wish you could
stay a bit longer.
Why don't you come
to New York with me?
Lin, a beatle
can't just go anywhere
without it turning
into a circus.
No. No. No.
You'll go in disguise.
It's perfect. New York is
the perfect place to get lost.
♪♪♪♪[Happy together
by the turtles playing]
♪♪ Imagine me and you I do ♪♪
There you go.
You look like
just another down and out
vet home from Vietnam.
Oh, let's go downtown.
♪♪ If I should call you up,
invest a dime ♪♪
♪♪ and you say
you belong to me ♪♪
♪♪ and ease my mind ♪♪
♪♪ imagine how
the world could be ♪♪
♪♪ so very fine ♪♪
♪♪ so happy together ♪♪
♪♪ I can see me lovin'
nobody but you ♪♪
♪♪ for all my life ♪♪
♪♪ when you're with me, baby,
the skies'll be blue ♪♪
♪♪ for all my life ♪♪
♪♪ me and you
and you and me ♪♪
♪♪ no matter how
they toss the dice ♪♪
♪♪ it had to be ♪♪
♪♪ the only one
for me is you
and you for me ♪♪
Hey, Linda, look, look.
Come here.
Yeah, it's very nice.
♪♪ I can see me lovin'
nobody but you ♪♪♪♪
Let's get married.
No way.
Hey, I'm not joking.
Neither am I.
I've worked too hard
for my independence.
You don't want
to get married?
No. No.
I've done it.
Besides, my father
doesn't approve
of long hairs.
All right. Well,
I'll have to talk
to him then.
Yes. Yes, you should.
You should talk to him
about apple.
He's a lawyer.
He's absolutely brilliant.
So I was tracking
some investments,
but I hear
britain's sinking.
I hear america
isn't doing so well, either.
Paul loves painting.
I was thinking
he should meet
William decoony.
What a good idea.
William's a client
and a good friend.
Oh, thanks.
Speaking of clients,
we're in a bit of a mess
since Brian,
our manager died.
He kept track of
the money, the contracts,
all that stuff.
Well, it's a bit dodgy now.
Linda was saying
that you might help
sort US out,
that you're brilliant
at that stuff.
She's my biggest fan.
I said it
because it's true.
The man for the job
is my son here,
also my partner.
I'll advise you,
of course,
but John will figure out
what's needed.
You let me know.
Anything you need.
Right. Well, uh,
I'll keep it in mind.
(Linda) A week later,
Paul, Heather, and I
took off for Scotland.
Paul owned
a little farm there
in the middle of nowhere.
[Birds chirping]
(Paul) Come on, Martha,
come on.
[Sheep bleating]
It's a little bit rough.
You own this?
Yeah. Just me
and the sheep.
Do you like it?
I love it.
Yeah?
I absolutely love it.
Really?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
She likes it.
I can stay here
for the rest of my life.
We'll fix it up.
We'll put in paint
and-- and-- and--
and curtains
and-- and
a roof possibly.
And then we can--
[exclaiming]
[Goats bleating]
And a floor
would-- would be good.
[Sighing]
It's almost perfect.
Almost?
Yes. You know
what it needs?
What?
A horse.
Ok.
♪♪♪♪[Never my love playing]
Good.
Hey, you two want
to watch me
fall on me arse?
[Linda and Heather giggling]
No. It's easy.
Yeah?
He's bigger,
but you're smarter.
You just have to
remind him of that.
I don't think
he understands
me accent.
[Girls giggling]
♪♪ You wonder
if this heart of mine ♪♪
♪♪ will lose
its desire for you ♪♪
♪♪ never my love ♪♪
[Chuckling]
♪♪ When you know
that my whole
life depends ♪♪
You keep building.
I want to adopt her
when we get married.
Why can't
we just live together?
I want to settle down,
have some kids of me own.
Can a beatle ever
really settle down?
I'm finished
sowing wild oats.
I had all the girls I fancy.
It's you I want.
I love you, lin.
I love you, too.
Fine. What are you
afraid of then?
Let's get married.
I don't want to ruin
what we have.
Oh, let's not talk
about it, ok?
Let's just do it.
♪♪ Never my love ♪♪
♪♪ never my love ♪♪
(Male reporter #4)
Beatle fans
have gathered
outside marylebone
registry office
on this
12th day of march, 1969,
after official confirmation
Paul McCartney is to marry
American photographer
Linda eastman today.
[People cheering]
[Church bells ringing]
Comment, Mrs. McCartney!
Just write that the bride
wore a big smile.
Heather?
(Heather)
I'm ok, mummy.
Oh, come on, girls.
I had to get married
sometime.
♪♪ Never my love ♪♪
♪♪ never my love ♪♪
♪♪ never my love,
never my love ♪♪
♪♪ how can you think
love will end ♪♪
♪♪ when I've asked you
to spend your whole life ♪♪
♪♪ with me ♪♪
♪♪ with me ♪♪♪♪
No, I never agreed
to Bruce Grossman
as our manager.
I don't trust him.
The guy is just a--
he got the stones
over a million dollar
advance at a Decker.
We never got any advance.
Yeah, he also got
all the hot rock songs
off them, too, John.
Look, why don't we have
Lee and John eastman
handle our affairs?
No one knows
the music business
better than they do.
Press announcement
already went out
naming Grossman
as our manager.
Well, get it back.
He's-- he's got problems
with the u.S.
Tax authorities.
Just exactly
what we don't need.
Yoko and I want him.
He's blunt, he's funny,
he knows every one
of our songs.
And none of US are
married to his sister.
Got to sign now, mate.
He's flying back
to New York tomorrow.
Needs a signed contract
to give back to his board.
Oh, now wait.
Wait a second.
Board? What board?
Oh, great.
Wonderful.
What am I gonna tell
the eastmans, eh?
They can still be
our lawyers.
We want Bruce
to handle the money.
Yeah, well,
screw 20% for a start.
He'll take 15.
He's got to have 20.
It can wait
till Monday then.
I want my lawyer
to have a look at it.
You're just stalling.
Did you sign, Ringo?
We all signed.
It's up to you, mate.
So I'm outvoted.
That's it.
All right, fine.
You don't need
my bloody signature
then, do you?
Hey, man.
We'll do it without you.
(Linda) Those days
at Abby road were
frustrating for everybody.
Weeks went by without
anything getting done.
He's not coming.
We're never going
to finish.
Right.
Let's pack it in.
What is it
with you and John?
What's the game?
(Pianist) What do you
want me to do?
We're mates.
We're supposed
to hang together.
We'll, uh, we'll try
and sort it out.
We'll get it soon.
It's ok.
(Linda) Things didn't
get any better
between Paul and John.
But for US,
life was wonderful.
Our child was born
just before
our 2nd anniversary.
Her name was Mary
after Paul's mother.
♪♪♪♪[Music box playing]
Good. Good girl.
Oh, that's beautiful, baby.
Go help your father.
[Banging on door]
John.
Where is he?
McCartney!
What the bloody hell
are you playing at?
We booked a session,
didn't we?
[Baby crying]
Ringo, George and I have
been cooling our arses
for two bloody hours
in the studio,
and you don't have
the bleeding decency
to show up.
Oh, like you've
never kept me waiting.
What about US
out there, eh?
What about US?
Why didn't you tell US
you couldn't make it?
So I'm sorry, all right!
Lin and I were celebrating
our anniversary!
[Glass shattering]
[Baby crying]
Hey! John.
Happy anniversary, mate.
[Door slamming]
(Mason) The cancer
has shown up in
your other breast here.
So, what, it's spreading?
Not necessarily.
It's possibly
a new cancer.
So what now?
More radiation?
More chemo?
I'm sorry.
Oh.
So what do I tell people?
I've been saying that
eating veggie reduces
your risk of cancer.
Don't worry about that now.
They'll feel deceived.
Lin, the most important
thing right now is
to get you better.
Now, we, uh,
we read about
this experimental
bone marrow treatment
in California.
50% remission
rates, right?
Unconfirmed statistics.
The procedure
needs more testing
before we know.
But you could do it here?
Only if you take part
in randomized
clinical trials.
It's our policy.
Randomized, meaning?
You're assigned either
to a control group
getting standard chemo
or to the experimental
treatment group.
Like a Guinea pig.
So we have
no choice about it?
It has to be random.
But if it's lin's best shot,
can't we just pay for it
if we want
the experimental
treatment?
There are other places
that do it, yes.
Not here.
Not until we know
it works.
There are serious risks.
The dosage is lethal.
It kills off
your bone marrow
which must be replaced.
It's a long
difficult ordeal, and
there's no guarantee
it's any better than
what we're already doing.
(Receptionist)
Dr. Mason's office.
Dr. Mason,
they're ready for you.
Think it over
and let me know.
Right. Thanks.
Oh, it's a bloody
crap shoot
is what it is.
No.
We'll go. We'll go to la.
We'll get the treatment.
What have we
got to lose?
Everything.
(Paul) So are we gonna
continue as
a group or not?
Listen, lads.
We've got to get back
to performing.
It's been three years
since we were
last on the stage.
I can't see US doing
massive big shows again.
Ok. So, so we'll go
back to small clubs.
(George) The Beatles.
Impossible.
Right. We could
go unannounced.
We-- we could go in disguise.
Change your name.
[Chuckling]
There's a thought.
What a trip.
I think you're daft.
I'm not supposed
to tell you,
but I'm leaving
the group.
Come on, yoko.
John.
(Paul) It's the end
of the Beatles.
Without John,
there's no group.
But it's not
the end of apple.
It's the only job
I've ever had.
We got to find a way
to cut you loose.
Under the contract
you signed,
apple owns
everything you make,
every song you write
for the next seven years.
Even if the band
breaks up?
And Grossman gets 20%.
Oh, you know
I never even signed
with the bastard.
Oh, we can sue
to break the contract.
They'll never let you
out of it voluntarily.
[Sighing] All right, fine.
Great. Let's do it.
Yeah, stick it to him.
You can't sue Grossman.
He wasn't party
to the apple agreement.
You have to sue
to dissolve
the partnership.
Sue John, George, Ringo?
No, I can't do that. No.
It's the only way, Paul.
(Judge) In view of
the tangled state
of the Beatles
financial affairs,
the unconvincing testimony
of Mr. Bruce Grossman,
and the absence of staff
capable of giving
necessary direction,
the court grants
the petition of
Mr. Paul McCartney
and appoints a receiver
to take over the running
of the partnership
until a full trail
can be held to determine
the long-term disposition
of the Beatles company.
[Dog barking]
McCartney, who the hell
do you think you are?
(Woman)
Dr. Hunter to radiology.
Ok, now,
you ready for this?
All right, hang on.
Anyone we know?
Oh, look.
Here's trouble.
Hello, love.
How you doing?
Hello, beautiful.
Something I made for you.
Presies. Great.
Oh.
Oh, Heather.
It's beautiful.
It's a medicine jar.
A hopi design.
Mmm-hmm.
This is amazing.
Look at the detailing.
Look at this, Paul.
Yeah, it's amazing.
Come here.
Give me a kiss,
talented girl.
Heather, I just want
you to know that
if anything goes wrong--
it won't, will it?
You said not to worry.
Yes, I did,
and-- and I meant that.
(Linda) But with high doses
of chemo,
there's always a risk.
I just want you to know
that I will always,
always be there.
Oh, mama, I love you.
I love you, too.
Come here. Hug me.
Good, sweet girl.
[Girl laughing]
(Linda)
After the breakup
of the Beatles,
Paul was depressed
for some time.
I was beginning to wonder
if things would
ever be the same.
Whee!
Be careful.
(Heather)
Ok.
Paul, you should see this.
It's so cute.
Mary and Heather
are riding in a little
wheel barrow.
Do you wanna go up
with them to, uh,
to see the lambs?
Do you want me
to run you a bath?
How about I fix you
something to eat?
I'll make you anything
that you want.
I meant food.
Just leave me alone.
No. No, no,
I will not leave you alone.
It's been way
too long for this.
You need to get
out of that shirt.
You need to go outside!
Oh, what's the point, eh?
I'm on the bloody scrap heap.
Can't you see that?
I'm no use to anyone.
You are a brilliant
songwriter, Paul.
No, not without John.
He was right, you know.
On me own, I'm just
a sentimental turd.
No. That is not true.
You're not
Engelbert Humperdinck
or whatever the hell
that he said,
and you do not
need those guys.
You are a grown man,
and you do not need John.
[Glass shattering]
Just leave it, will ya?
Just leave it, lin.
You don't know
what you're talking about!
Oh, where are you going?
Out!
[Sobbing]
I'm scared.
I'm scared, lin.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I know.
[Sighing]
You have to pull
yourself out of this,
because I can't.
And you have to stop
blaming yourself
because it is not
your fault,
and it is definitely
not mine.
Oh, Linda,
I don't think I can.
You can.
I know you can.
You have your work.
You have your music.
I feel empty.
That's how I feel.
Just like when mum died.
That's what it's like.
[Sighs]
All alone.
I loved John,
you know,
I really loved him.
You are not alone.
No, the way things are going,
you'll leave me, too.
[Sobs]
Are you kidding?
I am crazy in love with you.
Darling, I will never,
ever leave you.
You can count on it.
[People chattering]
Hi.
Hello, darling.
How you feeling?
Hot.
Hot?
How do I look?
Oh, you look very sexy.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You look gorgeous,
like a Buddhist nun.
Hmm.
Well, sort of.
Holy.
Holy like Swiss cheese.
Like Swiss cheese.
Hey.
What?
This kissing, I believe,
is not allowed.
Oh, I don't see why not.
[Knocking on door]
I don't think so.
Oh, hang, on.
Dr. Bone marrow.
Hey. How we doing?
Look, it's gonna get
rough for a while.
It's a slow
recovery process.
Your body needs time to
build itself back up, ok?
Ok.
I'll check back
with you in a while.
I'm gonna sleep
for a while.
Yeah, you sleep, darling.
You sleep.
(Paul)
Are you in pain?
[People chattering]
Hi.
Baby's fine.
She's in the nursery.
She?
Yes.
So it's Stella.
Stella.
[Moaning]
Oh, I'm so sorry
it had to be a cesarean.
I might have
lost you both.
Rough life for daddy.
Rough life for me.
You have no idea.
I was standing outside,
standing outside waiting.
[Linda laughing]
A sort of vision
came to me.
A bit of a prayer.
You know, like angel wings
and I thought,
"hey, that'll be good
for the band."
Wings.
I like it.
Lin, I've decided
what I wanted to do.
I want US to form
a band together.
You and me.
Go on stage together.
But I'm not a musician,
Paul. Remember?
So what. Neither was I
to start out.
What did we know?
We were just 4 kids
banging away in a garage.
Yes. But you're
Paul McCartney,
and I would be
the first to tell you
that you don't need
a total amateur
on stage with you.
I mean it.
Listen, the best thing
about the Beatles
was being up there
with your best friends.
Well, you're me best friend.
I want you on stage
with me.
I love you so.
I want you with me
every second.
Darling.
Of every minute.
Darling. Darling.
Of every hour.
I don't play an instrument.
♪♪♪♪[Piano playing]
(Paul) Now you make a chord.
3 fingers like this.
(Linda) Oh.
Now, pay attention.
Watch.
Ok.
Mmm-hmm.
Here or you can play
them one at a time.
See, and that's
an arpeggio.
Very good.
[Linda giggling]
So then, from there
you make other cords,
or you can play around
like little melodies.
That's beautiful.
You see? That's really--
that's really all it is.
Yes.
Just messing around
till you find
something you fancy.
Mmm-hmm.
I always hated
piano lessons.
Oh, it's the yawn.
Look. Look, you.
I'm a bit nervous, too,
you know?
It's been five years
since I played in front
of a live audience.
Hardly ever without John.
So we'll keep
it simple, ok?
Ok.
Start at square one.
Ok. Little "c."
[People chattering]
Yeah. Yeah, I'm serious.
Paul McCartney.
Yeah, Paul McCartney,
the beatle.
I'm not joking.
He just walked in,
and he said he wanted
to perform for US.
(Paul) Hello,
I'm Paul McCartney.
[Crowd cheering]
Thank you. Nice.
Oh, it's great to be here.
It's lovely to be here
at Leeds university.
I'd like to introduce
you now to
the new band, wings.
[Band playing off key]
One, two.
I-- i--
[Microphone feedback]
[Crowd muttering]
What's up, love?
I forgot the chord.
What?
All right. Ok.
Don't worry.
There we go.
All right.
Ok.
And this is
me better half, lin.
[Crowd applauding]
Is it, uh, is it all right
if we start now, love?
Yeah?
Ok, thanks.
One, two, three.
♪♪♪♪[Kansas City playing]
♪♪ Ah, Kansas City ♪♪
♪♪ going to get
my baby back home ♪♪
♪♪ yeah, yeah ♪♪
♪♪ I'm going to Kansas City ♪♪
♪♪ going to get
my baby back home ♪♪
♪♪ yeah, yeah ♪♪
♪♪ well, it's a long,
long time too ♪♪
♪♪ my baby's been gone ♪♪♪♪
(Linda) We started off
small by
crisscrossing england
and eventually Scotland.
Crowds everywhere
loved Paul and the critics
had a lot to say.
(Linda) "The former beatle
has gone from Lennon
and McCartney
"to McCartney and Mrs.
"Her colorless,
amateurish singing
makes me wonder
"what Paul could be
thinking to let
his untalented wife
"elbow her way
onto his stage."
It's me who wants
you on stage.
I'll have me bloody cat
on stage if I want.
I did not ask for this.
I do not want this.
Mick Jagger said
that he would never
have his old lady
on stage with him.
Yeah, well, screw him.
I already have.
You're not quitting,
you know? You're not.
[Crowd cheering]
(Paul)
♪♪ yeah, yeah, yeah ♪♪
♪♪ oh, yeah, yeah ♪♪
♪♪ yeah, yeah ♪♪
♪♪ nah, nah, nah,
nah, nah ♪♪
♪♪ nah, nah, nah, nah, nah,
yeah, yeah ♪♪
[Whooping]
♪♪ Oh, nah, nah, nah, nah ♪♪
♪♪ oh, yeah ♪♪
♪♪ yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪♪♪♪
[Crowd cheering]
(Paul) Thank you.
[Whooping]
Thank you.
Oh, it's great to be here.
We love you.
No, no, we do.
Now, the woman
who inspires
all my silly love songs,
my lovely wife, lin.
Without you,
none of this
would be possible.
[Crowd cheering]
♪♪ We wish you
a merry Christmas ♪♪
♪♪ we wish you
[Knocking on door]
♪♪ and a happy new year ♪♪♪♪
Hello, John.
McCartney.
How did you get in here?
It's like the Pentagon
down there.
It's Christmas, man.
We wanted to see you.
We missed you.
How are you?
Great. Come on.
Come in, man.
You look great.
Linda.
Hi, John?
Fabulous.
Thank you.
This is--
this is fabulous.
(Yoko) We love Tokyo.
Okura hotel. Fabulous.
Our home away from home.
Yeah, we're dying
to go to Japan,
[clearing throat]
But they won't let US
in the country.
At least not yet.
Denied US visas
because of
my criminal record.
[Laughing]
Because of this.
Can you believe it?
We were in la
two months ago,
and we got stopped,
and they found
two joints in my purse,
two lousy joints.
Hey, man, they're trying
to kick me out of the u.S.
Same thing.
You ever coming
home then?
They're always on me
about US getting back
together, you know?
I know. It's a drag.
Too much pressure.
I prefer New York.
Come see US again, eh?
Yeah.
(Yoko) And bring
the kids next time.
Yeah, of course.
We will.
And, uh,
bring the old guitar.
Yeah, soon.
Promise.
Merry Christmas, John.
Merry Christmas.
(Linda) Being mobbed
by fans and journalists
in Tokyo
at the start of
the wings world tour
was a nightmare.
We had our kids with US
including baby James
and thought a quiet
vip. Entrance
had been arranged.
[People chattering]
(Man) Mr. McCartney,
picture.
Hey, you take him. Here.
[Photographers clamoring]
How's it going?
(Paul) Hey, big guy.
Oh, great.
Wonderful.
Mr. McCartney.
Hang on. Listen,
this is a mistake.
[Speaking in Japanese]
Hang on. Listen.
Listen, mate.
This is a-- it's a mistake.
It's just a mistake.
Mr. McCartney.
Mr. McCartney,
you're under arrest.
(Linda) Where are
you taking him? No. Paul.
Hey, come on.
Lin, just keep an eye
on the kids.
You come with me both.
The hotel, please.
It's fine. It's fine.
[Speaking in Japanese]
(Stella) Mummy,
it's on again.
[James whimpering]
(Linda) It's ok.
What's going to
happen to him?
I don't know, darling.
They'll probably
keep him overnight.
Release him with a fine.
Keep him where?
I don't know.
[Cell door opening]
[Speaking in Japanese]
Mr. McCartney.
Dolan Warren knott,
British vice council.
Very pleased to meet you.
Linda must be
frantic, eh?
Look, we haven't spent
a single night apart,
you know?
So, uh, how long before
you can get me out of here?
I'm afraid it's not
quite so easy,
Mr. McCartney.
The Japanese are
a rather
conservative lot
on matters
such as drugs.
By violating their laws,
you've shown disrespect
to Japan is
the way they see it.
No. No. No.
No disrespect.
I just--
I just didn't think,
that's all.
Well, there's a chap
in here
who was caught
with much less
marijuana than you,
and he's been locked up
for 3 months already.
They could give
you eight years.
Eight-- eight years?
Oh.
That's barbaric.
Yes. But there it is.
Look, it's past midnight.
I'll visit with your wife
in the morning.
Rest assured,
Mr. McCartney,
we shall do
everything we can.
[Cell door opening]
Lin. Lin.
Hi.
[Sighing]
Six days feels
more like six months.
Oh, how are the kids?
Worried, but we're ok.
The band left
once they realized
that there was no way
to save the tour, but...
Well, they're not happy.
Oh, it was
so incredibly dumb.
[Laughing]
I know.
[Reporter speaking
in Japanese]
[Crowd cheering]
[Chattering]
(Linda) I've had it
with touring.
10 years of packing
and unpacking.
Hauling the kids
all around the world.
Living out of hotels.
I'm tired.
Tokyo was rough.
It was tougher on you
than on me.
I promise it won't
happen again.
No. No more touring.
Promise me that.
Lin, I can't.
Stepping up in front
of an audience is my life.
What about my life?
All right. I'm sorry.
Our life.
There are other things
that I want to do.
Like your photography
book. Great.
My photography book.
My vegetarian cookbook.
We're always saying
that people
in our position
should make a difference,
so let's do more
for animal rights.
And we should
spend more time at home
with our family.
[Chuckling]
Be safe. Be warm.
Love you.
Thank you so much.
Bye, mummy.
Bye, baby.
[Bird squawking]
What's wrong?
John's dead.
(Male reporter) The news
of John Lennon's death
has stunned the world.
Fans keep
a constant vigil
outside the Dakota apartments
in New York City
where he was
shot last night.
Whenever-- whenever anyone
I love dies,
I never get a chance
to say goodbye.
...as soon as the word
was made public.
Most say they just want
to be near the place
where this icon...
Mum.
...was gunned down.
Now John.
Poor yoko and Sean.
Will he even remember
his daddy?
Oh, he'll never
forget John.
No one will ever
Oh, god.
[Dog barking]
[Creaking]
[Moans]
Oh, sorry, love.
Did I wake you?
No.
I had another nightmare.
Oh.
[Sighing]
It's the nights
that are worse, eh?
That's when all the fears
come creeping in.
I just wish
I could see
more progress.
[Sighing]
Come here, you.
They warned US it'd be
a slow process.
At least they haven't
used the word "aggressive."
You know it's bad
when they say that.
I haven't heard
that word.
If I die, it'll be a family
without a mother.
Lin, please don't.
Sometimes it's so hard.
Sometimes I just
wanna give up.
Please.
Don't.
Your tests look fine.
No sign of cancer
in either breast.
Yeah?
It's gone.
So that trip in la
was worth it.
Well, I wish I could say
that but it's
too soon to tell.
The cancer's in remission,
not gone.
So far we can only
hope to contain it,
not cure it.
But it's good news.
Contain it?
For how long?
That's impossible to tell.
You'll need to be monitored
in London every
two weeks to make sure.
So I can do
whatever I want?
Quality of life
is essential.
[Sobbing]
Hey. Hey.
It's wonderful.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
(Linda) Ok, hold that.
What do you think?
That could be a great
album cover, babe.
Mum, it says parsley.
Are you sure
you don't mean basil?
Hmm.
Oh. Oh, no.
You're right.
It-- it is basil.
Call the editor.
(Linda) I want to include
the flowers that I took
in the photo show,
and let's include
these ferns.
I took them
at kew garden.
Ok.
(Mary)
The florist is cool.
The invitations will be
ready Friday,
and Stella's working
on my dress.
Oh, I hope she has
something for me.
Nothing seems to fit,
and I've got her
Paris fashion show
coming up.
Mum, you're beautiful
as always.
(Paul) We can do that.
Of course, we can.
Yeah, but we'll have
to pick it up a bit
'cause the tide's coming in.
I want shells.
What?
It's shells,
it's shells you like.
Oh, Paul.
Oh, you like that,
do you?
Yeah.
Well, let's see.
Hang on.
There's more over there.
I'm sure there are.
[Seagulls cawing]
(Paul) Hey,
there's lots of 'em.
You have to wash
them though.
That's it, see?
Hey, are you all right,
darling?
Mmm-hmm.
What's up?
I just got so tired.
Oh, look. Come on. Come on.
Let's get you home.
You're all right.
Come on.
You'll be all right.
Come on. Let's go.
Here. Let me take that.
[Camera clicking]
Wonderful.
Thank you.
It's so peaceful here.
So beautiful.
How are your wedding plans
coming, darling?
Everything's going so well.
Mary,
do you think that
it might be possible
to move up the date?
Why, mum?
Because I wanna be there.
And things aren't
going well.
I talked to a doctor,
and it's in my liver.
Mary, will you
promise me something?
If anything should
happen to me,
will you take care
of your father?
Of course, I will.
We all will.
[People chattering]
To our lovely star,
Stella, whose
fashion's successful.
You liked it?
[Chuckling]
We loved it.
I am so proud of you.
Never in a million years
would I have thought
that I would produce
a Paris fashion whiz.
You either.
Oh, I don't know.
[Chuckling]
Brilliant.
Thank you.
(Woman)
Hello, again.
Hello.
Great show, Stella.
It was so good.
Thank you.
When did you replace
Karl lagerfeld?
(Both) November.
[All laughing]
Don't mind US.
We're just the silly,
proud parents.
Do you mind
if I steal her?
There some people
who really
wanna meet her.
Hey, she's all yours.
Come on.
Love you.
How about some
more champagne?
[Sighing]
You all right, mum?
Listen, if you're tired,
we can run you back
to the hotel, you know?
Where I really
wanna go
is Arizona.
[Birds chirping]
We're so lucky, Paul.
It's so beautiful here,
and it's been here
for hundreds of years,
and it will be here
long after we're gone.
(James)
You all right, dad?
Can I get you something?
No. No.
You get off to bed.
[Dog barking]
[Birds chirping]
Morning, mum.
Good morning, beautiful.
Brought you
some breakfast.
Oh, baby,
I'm not hungry.
I'll just leave it
here then.
Mmm.
We have an idea.
Why don't I bring
the horses down,
get them ready?
We can go
for another ride.
Yeah?
I don't really
fancy a ride today.
No?
Well, would you
rather go and sit down
by the pool?
I'm so tired.
You just fancy
a bit of a lie in, yeah?
You and me both.
[Birds chirping]
[Moaning]
[Gasping]
[Panting]
Hey, lin.
[Moaning]
Can you hear me, eh?
Can you hear me?
I love you, lin.
I'll love you
forever and ever.
[Line ringing]
Hi, it's Paul McCartney.
I think you should
send a nurse.
No. Right now.
(Mary) What is it, dad?
Go wake up
the other kids.
[Birds chirping]
You're on your favorite
place on earth.
You're up on your beautiful
appaloosa stallion, lin.
It's a fine spring day.
The bluebells are out.
The sky is just clear blue.
Clear blue.
[Sobbing]
(Paul) Linda died
in the early hours
of April 17, 1998.
She fought
a courageous battle
to conquer a disease,
but it wasn't meant to be.
As a mother,
she was the best.
We always said
that all we wanted
for the kids
was that they
would grow up
and have good hearts,
and they have.
She lives on
in all of them.
I'm privileged to have been
her lover for 30 years,
and in all that time,
except for one absence,
we never spent
a single night apart.
She was the kindest woman
I ever met.
She was unique.
And the world
is a better place
for having known her.
Her message of love
will live in
our hearts forever.
I love you, Linda.
♪♪ Two will be like one ♪♪
♪♪ brighter than the sun ♪♪
♪♪ and will always
have each other ♪♪
♪♪ and I love you ♪♪
♪♪ and adore you ♪♪
♪♪ you're the one
I always knew ♪♪
♪♪ I'd find ♪♪
♪♪ will you be mine ♪♪
♪♪ forever more? ♪♪
♪♪ I'll always be there
by your side ♪♪
♪♪ ooh ♪♪♪♪