[film ticking]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[breathing heavily]
[phone ringing]
[upbeat music]
[woman laughs]
[singing in foreign language]
[door chiming]
[speaking foreign language]
[groaning]
Oh, god.
[exhales sharply]
Okay.
[silverware clatters]
- Morning.
- Hi.
Hey.
- Room service?
- Yeah.
I um, I was just surprised
that you were still here.
Oh.
I'm happy.
I was pleasantly surprised.
Here I am.
Um, do you mind if I use your bathroom?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's one at the other
end of the living room,
or there's a second master if
you want some more privacy.
[sighs]
I uh, I hope that you don't
mind a large breakfast.
I'm uh, I'm one of those annoying people
that wakes up early and eats.
Like some kind of rooster.
[woman coughs]
Um, I'm gonna go.
What?
There's breakfast.
Oh, that's really sweet,
but I gotta get going.
Right.
Uh, yeah, back to uh,
English?
- English lit, right?
- Huh?
Back to Arizona University
to study English lit?
[Woman] Yeah.
[Man] Arizona, not Arizona State.
Classy not trashy.
That's right.
- Clarissa.
- Yeah.
- It's Irish?
- Uh, I don't know.
I'd have to ask my mom.
Um, okay, I'm gonna run.
Uh, next time you're in
town, uh, give me a ring.
Three grand.
Three grand to stay the rest of the day.
Oh, I, I have to get
back to my roommate.
Three-five?
Um.
I'm sorry.
Am I being offensive?
I haven't done this before.
I just, I like you.
And I thought with last night,
you seemed pretty...
[chuckles]
Um, let me start again.
Are you around today?
Because I would really like to spend
the rest of the day with you.
And I know that you're probably busy,
so I could give you
something for your time.
$4,000 be enough?
Um.
I don't know, it still
feels kind of weird.
You know what I do with my paintings?
I um, I detach myself from them.
I...
I don't know, I think of
them as a lump of coal,
or, or a barrel of oil,
the furthest thing from which they are.
And I give them a price
and then I let the market do its dance,
free and unfettered from
any emotional reaction.
But what if it was
you and not a painting?
[Man] Let me get what I can get.
Everything has a number
and that number is its price.
[Man] Simple.
What if there is no number?
[scoffs] Then it's known as worthless.
Or priceless.
[Man laughs]
You don't think things
are priceless, do you?
I don't.
- Everything has a price?
- Yeah.
What about God?
What uh, what number
would you give for God?
[Man laughs]
Um.
Okay, uh, just so I can
play correctly here,
God in this scenario
is you, or God is God?
God is God.
Zero.
- God is worthless.
- There is no God.
I'm talking in the market, right?
In the real world.
God has no bearing on the price of things,
therefore, God has no value.
But what if I say there is a God,
and honoring him costs money.
Well, then God has a number for you,
but to me, God is a zero.
So everyone has their own numbers
and can make up their own numbers.
And thus a market is created.
And those with more numbers to spend
can make up higher numbers
and take whatever they want.
Yes, and those with
lower numbers must adapt
and make higher numbers and acquire power.
- Except for God?
- Except for God,
who doesn't exist.
5,000.
And your real name.
Clarissa is my real
name, and no anal sex.
[Man] Make up another name then.
Why?
Because Clarissa's not your real name.
It was engineered to sound
vaguely like a part of your sexual anatomy
and kickstart my subconscious libido.
It's a brilliant piece
of subliminal marketing,
if you knew it or not.
[Clarissa laughs]
What do you really do for a living?
I really am a painter.
A painter?
In the penthouse suite
with a bunch of bros
at a club with eight
bottles of Grey Goose?
I'm a really good painter,
here for my brother's bachelor party,
and those were his friends.
Uncomplicated savages
from the province of Orange County, yuck.
Doctors and dentists and the like.
Very grotesque sort.
So you're a painter in L.A.
No, New York City.
You said L.A. last night.
[Man] I said I used to live in L.A.
and now I live in New York City,
and you don't trust me.
Why do you care what my name is?
'Cause I want the real thing.
Mm.
You wanna play make-believe.
[safe beeping]
[safe chiming]
Five grand and your real name.
Jennifer.
♪ Do you think you could love me ♪
♪ And be true ♪
♪ Am I asking too much of you ♪
♪ Do you think you could want me ♪
♪ 'Cause I need a partner in crime ♪
♪ Do you think you could love me ♪
♪ Love me, love me ♪
♪ Have you been in love lately ♪
♪ Were you hurt ♪
♪ Are you sure it's over with her ♪
♪ Are you looking for someone ♪
♪ On the side ♪
♪ Should I call before I come by ♪
♪ Don't tell me you want me ♪
[Jennifer humming]
♪ If you know ♪
♪ Those words ♪
♪ Are only a show ♪
♪ Are you ready to show me ♪
♪ What's inside ♪
♪ Are you scared of what I will find ♪
♪ If you're looking for mystery ♪
♪ Here's a clue ♪
♪ I got secrets that
I'm keeping from you ♪
[door creaking]
♪ Do you think you could love me ♪
Oh.
Ow.
Party's starting early, huh?
Can't slow down, won't slow down.
[Man sighs]
Mm.
[kissing]
[chuckles] Okay, hold on.
I just need a minute to recover my chi.
Ugh.
It's not you, it's me.
I'm not as young as you are.
It's okay.
I can just
close my eyes for a minute,
lay here and just float.
Where's your brother?
Hmm, no idea.
If they need me, they'll call.
On your smashed phone?
[chuckles] On the room phone.
♪ If you need to call me ♪
♪ On my smashed phone ♪
♪ I probably won't be able ♪
♪ To answer it at all ♪
Where are your clothes?
You ordered clothes?
Travel light.
Free as a bird, light as a feather.
What could you do right now?
What?
What could you do right
now that's gonna help you?
With what?
Your anxiety.
What anxiety?
[Man chuckles]
The double vodka at 11
in the morning anxiety.
Oh.
You know so much, don't you?
Um, some would say
the exact opposite, but-
- Like who?
- Don't dodge.
What was the answer?
What could you do right now?
Sleep.
Drink.
Fuck.
Good.
What else?
[laughs] Um.
I could go to the pool and sit in a cabana
and drink something cold.
Good.
What else?
I could get on a spaceship
and fly to the moon.
- No you couldn't.
- Why not?
You don't have a spaceship.
You don't have the proper training,
and you probably couldn't
handle prolonged zero gravity
with all the toxins
you've got in your system.
- Oh, all right.
- Yeah.
All right.
Really killing my vibe, you know?
Now you're getting it.
Kill your vibe, kill your dream.
The game...
The game is, what could you do right now?
And what's the point of this game?
I'll tell you once you
give me something good.
Not gonna happen.
[Jennifer groans]
I wish we could just fuck.
- No you don't.
- Yes I do.
What could you do right now?
Um.
[sighs] Gamble in the casino,
drive back to Arizona.
Clean my bedroom, go grocery shopping.
Fly to Paris, wash my car.
Okay, back up one, back up one.
How would you fly to Paris?
On a plane.
And how would you get on the plane?
I, [groans]
I would book my ticket on Expedia.
Okay, and then what?
[laughs] Then,
then I would book my hotel.
- Which one?
- I don't know.
The Plaza.
Okay, the Plaza for
five nights in Paris.
Could you really do that?
Yeah, sure.
- Then why haven't you?
- Really?
Why not?
- You know why.
- I don't.
I.
I don't.
I don't have a passport.
You can get one tomorrow at the Embassy.
All you need is $200 and two forms of ID.
Okay, fuck off.
You could do it tomorrow.
Spend all of my money flying to Paris
and come back dead broke?
- You could.
- I can't.
Why not?
I'll give you 15 grand to
stay the rest of the weekend.
You can go to Paris on Monday.
[Jennifer laughs]
Are you serious?
Yeah, uh, can you
tell me what the rate is
for a flight to Paris on Monday morning?
2,000.
And also the Plaza Hotel
on the Champs-Elysees?
600 euro.
Yeah, my friend would like to book that,
both of them, leaving on
Monday and returning on Sunday.
Name?
Hang up.
Name, miss?
Miss?
Name.
Can you hold that for me
until tomorrow morning?
Thank you.
What could you do right now?
- Punch you.
- True.
My therapist used to make
me do that every week.
She said that it improves your IQ.
The more that you believe you can do,
the happier and the smarter you'll be.
Uh, or it just makes you crazy.
Hmm.
It's all imaginary.
The box that you put yourself in,
the rules that you let
other people give you.
All the fears and the hopes
and the dreams, all of it.
Fake.
Money's real.
Maybe.
- Were you serious?
- Hmm?
About the weekend.
Yeah, I was.
I am.
20.
17.5.
18.
20.
And you book the flight right now.
[Picks Up Phone]
17.5,
and no anal sex.
[Phone Hangs Up]
Think of what you can
do with all that money.
Now can I go to the moon?
Mm, no, just Paris.
- But I want the moon.
- Sorry.
- What about all that money?
- What about it?
How do you travel with so much money?
Mm.
It's a very complex system that I have.
Oh yeah?
I swipe my credit card
with the casino concierge
and he opens up a line of credit,
and then when I want
cash, he brings it to me.
It's very, very complex.
[Jennifer laughs]
Did you get any of that?
Don't be an asshole. [laughs]
I can't help it.
[Jennifer groans]
What are you doing? [laughs]
[slow music]
You know, you lied, old man.
[inhales]
Are you hungry?
I'm always hungry.
Pick up the phone,
order whatever you want.
Oh, hello?
There's a guy just there.
- That's the butler.
- Fancy.
Yes, hi.
Um, can I have two cheeseburgers,
onion rings, and two chocolate shakes?
Thank you.
Did you want something?
[laughing]
maybe this is heaven.
Eden.
[Jennifer] What's the difference?
One you're dead, and the
other you're alive, I think.
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
♪ That saved ♪
♪ A wretch ♪
♪ Like me ♪
[Man] You're really into God, huh?
Well, where I'm from
the church is one of the
few things still there.
Business of God.
I bet God's worth a lot
more than zero out there.
- Yeah.
- Clouds,
the gates, the whole shebang.
It's a hell of a business model.
When you realize you've
been ripped off, too late.
Are you a Jew?
You ever made love to a Jew before?
What do you think happens when you die?
You're gone?
That's sad.
Mm.
[groans] Is it?
Isn't it all just a metaphor anyway?
Some self-help book to deal
with oppressive Romans.
You shut down your mind and its desires
and its greed and its doubt,
and you go towards the light,
and you go towards the truth,
and then ye shall be set free
and heaven shall be a place on earth.
RIP, Belinda Carlisle.
Who?
Exactly. [laughs]
- Belinda Carlisle?
- Yeah.
- Oh, she's not dead.
- What?
Yeah, it says here she lives
on the Upper West Side of Manhattan.
Oh, tomato tomato.
Say something really mean to me.
Why?
Just indulge me.
- Mean?
- Mean.
Why can't I say something really nice?
You know the origin of the word nice?
Simple.
Nice is always a lie.
- Mean, always the truth.
- That's not true.
Okay, okay.
Nice then.
You are a
wonderful kisser.
[laughs] That's a lie.
No, that's true.
- Wonderful?
- Mm-hmm.
Good, maybe.
Acceptable more likely, serviceable
for sure, but wonderful?
Mm.
Now you just want out of this game
and you just decided to
overdo the compliment
in hopes of flattery
and retreat on my part.
Come on.
I think you might
actually be good at this.
Just cut to the core.
Tell me something I can't
see from the inside.
I thought that this
was supposed to be Eden?
What, Eden can't be mean?
I'm happy right now, all right? [laughs]
I am.
So just go with me on this.
Okay.
[clears throat]
[both clearing throat]
You're going gray.
That's an observation
I make every morning.
Mm.
You don't have enough hair on your chest.
Okay, I like it that way.
You have bags under your eyes.
Next.
You're hiding something.
- Okay.
- Mm.
You aren't that slick, charming, or smart.
- You're acting at it.
- Good.
You're going off a picture
you saw in a magazine.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
You're a wannabe.
Okay, go.
You took your idea of Ben Affleck,
and you smashed him together with...
Fuck, I don't know who, but somebody who,
[groans] who thinks that
they're better than they are.
Good, keep going.
I haven't really been orgasming.
Sorry, I didn't mean.
No.
[laughs] No.
No, no, um.
You're better at this than I thought,
and I thought you were
gonna be pretty good.
So.
I feel pretty good right now.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Like you just got rid of something?
Yeah.
Well, I'm glad I could help.
Was this from your therapist too?
No.
No, no, this was from my dad.
You ever play this game with your dad?
That'll end your childhood real quick.
What's the point?
He thought that the only point to life
was self-improvement.
And in order to keep improving,
you had to keep ripping yourself apart,
to build something stronger.
If you're not growing, you're shrinking.
You wanna be a winner, or
do you wanna be a loser?
Mm, wanna watch me?
[Man] Watch you?
Orgasm.
[upbeat music]
[water running]
[bright music]
♪ People asked Elizabeth ♪
♪ Why she wasn't big time yet ♪
♪ They meant well ♪
♪ But they had no idea ♪
♪ Putting herself out there ♪
♪ Ever since she could remember ♪
♪ Singing songs to anyone who'd hear ♪
♪ She felt patronized ♪
♪ Wanted to cry ♪
♪ But kept her head held high ♪
♪ Told herself ♪
♪ Best, dear ♪
♪ You've tried your best, dear ♪
♪ All the rest, yeah ♪
♪ What do they know ♪
♪ You've put ♪
♪ Up a good fight, so ♪
♪ Get through the night ♪
♪ Oh, let it go ♪
♪ Getting a bit older ♪
♪ But her dreams aren't growing colder ♪
♪ Singing's still the
thing she has to do ♪
[chopping rapidly]
♪ The men, they like to sit and stare ♪
♪ Comment on her hips and hair ♪
♪ While she sings to anyone who cares ♪
[Man] Pretty awesome, huh?
The shower?
Yeah, amazing.
There's like, two shower heads.
You'd think that Las Vegas
was floating on the Colorado River.
[Jennifer] Why?
Because all that water.
Sorry, that was a bad water joke.
Uh, oh, I got you some
stuff for the day's events.
- Events?
- Yeah.
Pool and then dinner.
Oh, um, I thought that we
would just be staying in.
Tempting, but I thought
we would get some fresh air
and let the lady clean
the room, and, you know.
Where's dinner?
The Academy Awards?
[chuckles] Good one.
I just rented that.
Turns out they will let you rent anything
when you play $5,000 a hand blackjack.
- You wanna rent a turtle?
- What?
That's the most ridiculous thing
I could think of off the top of my head.
Don't worry, we can rent normal stuff too,
like sex toys, or whatever.
What about your brother?
We are meeting them at the pool.
I got a cabana.
What?
Your brother and his friends?
You're here visiting your father
and you wanted to hang out
with a fellow artist while you were here.
- A fellow artist?
- Yeah,
because you, studying sculpture.
- You told them all that?
- No.
But I can if you want me to.
You worry too much.
Oh, well, are you gonna fix that too?
[Man] Maybe.
I'm gonna be a scientist,
studying the brain.
Sure you don't wanna be an astronaut?
I mean, if you're gonna do it
you may as well go for broke.
- No, the brain.
- Okay.
Brain researcher from Arizona University
here to study one of the finest
minds of this generation.
Yeah?
Now, shape up and let's
have a nice, normal day.
And on that note,
I am going to um...
You know what?
I'm paying partly for the pleasure
of saying everything right,
I'm gonna take a nice morning deuce,
and when I come back, light as a feather,
to the pool, Jane.
Aye aye, captain.
[Man] Why aren't you dressed?
Just daydreaming.
[Man] Well, less dreaming,
more action. [claps]
What about Buenos Aires?
Huh?
Paris is so cliche.
Buenos Aires is, it's romantic.
It's like the Paris of South America
but without all the tourists.
I don't know, just a
suggestion, just riffing here.
Thanks, but it's uh,
Paris or bust for me.
- Why?
- It's a secret.
[Man] Mm.
You're feeling better.
I am.
[Jennifer] From when we
first met you're happier.
Maybe.
Good.
- What about you?
- Well, it's no Paris,
but it'll do.
Do you mind if I skip the pool?
- Why?
- I'm just,
I'm not feeling it.
I don't really do so
well around other people.
- Want a Klonopin?
- What's it do?
One is like having two glasses of wine.
[Jennifer] Why don't you
just have two glasses of wine?
Because then I'd be an alcoholic.
I'll pass.
Uh, I should give you that back.
Oh, [scoffs] please.
Don't embarrass me.
What?
[Man] You are a curious case.
You're a person that deals
with people but hates people.
Well, I don't hate people,
I hate more than three people
together at any one place.
I am, by the way.
Happier.
I like you, even though you're weird.
I think I actually like
you because you're weird.
Thank you.
So, [claps]
what now?
[upbeat dance music]
[laughing]
♪ Wake up, check the mirror ♪
♪ Kiss the mirror ♪
♪ Keep it movin' ♪
♪ Gears tight, shoes clean ♪
♪ Friggy fresh ♪
♪ Neck bling ♪
♪ Damn, it feel good to be me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ She lives life like ♪
♪ A big party, you're invited ♪
♪ Let's get wasted, start a riot ♪
♪ Trouble music, rebel music ♪
♪ Hit your ass with a shovel music ♪
♪ She look good when she diggy do it ♪
♪ And I look good when I diggy do it ♪
♪ I make this look good ♪
♪ She make this look good ♪
♪ We make this look good ♪
♪ Bet you wish you could ♪
♪ I make this look good ♪
♪ She make this look good ♪
♪ We make this look good ♪
♪ Bet you wish you could ♪
♪ I love music, drives me crazy ♪
♪ My weakness might be your lady ♪
♪ Keep her yonder ♪
♪ Far away from me ♪
- It's good not to be alone.
- Mm.
[inhaling sharply]
Mm, [exhales] to God and to country.
Mm, bad luck not to drink on a toast.
Mm, and I only look at champagne.
- Why?
- The bubbles.
They don' bring out the devil
and make me feel somethin'
awful in the mornin'.
Wow.
No champagne and no anal sex.
You are uh, you're missing
out on all the fun.
We should go to dinner.
It's midnight.
Oh fuck, really?
Bonzai!
[inhaling sharply]
Bonzai, Daniel-San, banzai.
No?
"Karate Kid"? No?
Oh, vaguely.
Fuck.
Okay.
- Do you have a pimp?
- Yeah.
He has as scar and a cane,
and uh, well, he beats me when I'm short.
His name's Bobcat.
[laughs] I think that
maybe I should become a pimp.
Well, I'm not hiring.
I'm a sole proprietorship.
- That's smart.
- Very.
I think you would be
an excellent investment
opportunity, though.
There's very little
overhead, it's all cash,
and there's no taxes, and you just,
you hire the best and you
let them do their thing,
you just let it rip.
It, it's, it's the oldest profession
but it's also the oldest
investment opportunity.
Mm.
- Baker.
- What?
Uh, [clears throat]
were there prostitutes or
bakers first? [sniffles]
[Man] People were having
sex before they invented fire.
Yeah, but were they selling it?
Undoubtedly.
But I think [sniffles] now,
never have you been, like,
more vital than you are
at the present moment?
- Vital?
- Vital.
[sniffles] What does that mean?
Vital?
- It means-
- No, no, no,
yeah, I know what vital means.
Please do not explain it to me
like I'm some desert bunny trash.
I wouldn't think of it, that was-
- Why am I vital?
Every guy should
feel, I don't know, as
free as I feel right now.
I can say whatever I wanna say,
I can be who I am, who I really am.
Nobody loves anybody and nobody's trying
to manipulate anybody's emotions,
and I don't know, there's no like,
buried resentments or hidden maneuvers
and tactics and shit.
I think the French have this right,
and that's probably the only
time I'll ever say that.
But I think that sex should be
separate from a relationship.
If I wanna fuck my wife, great.
But if I fuck somebody else
then I can just be with my wife
instead of being miserable
trying to bag the old
ball and chain for like,
the 2,000th time.
I think it's, it's more natural...
No, scratch that, it's more
monogamous than monogamy.
Seeing a prostitute's like,
the first class of monogamy.
- You're married?
- Fuck no.
No, this is in theory.
In theory.
What about you not in theory?
Wow, okay.
Jesus, doctor.
Um.
It's not just I who is frustrated,
it's the whole current epoch
of my male brethren, right?
These, these are
confusing times right now.
- Are you always like this?
- Like what?
Controlling.
Just bad genes.
Well, I don't mind it.
Ugh, sorry.
Okay, I'm taking notes.
Um. [groans]
Where was I?
Prostitute, monogamy,
first class. [sniffles]
Uh, okay.
How, what I...
I think that...
Okay.
I'm a nice guy,
and I think that I'm pretty
fairly well adjusted,
et cetera, et cetera, all that.
And on some level, I wanna fall in love.
That knock you down, pound you out,
wake up in Paris kinda love,
but let's face it, that's not real.
Not really.
And more on that later.
The point is that that idea
makes me what some people would call
as like, a bit of a playboy.
But the problem is, I have taste, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- I like and enjoy
a very particular type of woman.
I like somebody who's beautiful
and intelligent and ambitious.
...and...
Those type of women require
energy and attention and money,
and they wanna know
that there's an endgame
to the whole thing.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, yeah, sex is more than sex
or else it's empty and shallow
and brings out the worst,
animalistic part of ourselves.
- You are very quick.
- Oh, for a woman?
Wow.
And next we're gonna talk
about your defensiveness.
Well you know, I run
in very smart circles
and memorize a few things.
Now back to your modern
male bullshit, whatever.
Um,
okay.
I... it's...
There's probably a...
No, there's like,
probably 100 million in this
very country alone, right?
Like poor, just nice guys,
nice guys who wanna get
laid on a regular basis
but who don't...
want to engage
in the dark arts of like,
emotional forgery and passive sociopathy.
What happens is, porn,
masturbation, aloneness,
and it's a closed loop that
begins to cave in on itself
and it's like a journey to
the center of your mind.
And my entire generation are
a bunch of frustrated dudes
that are just jerking off
and talking to themselves
and we need you.
We need you.
We need you to tell us that
it's okay to pay for sex.
That, that, that it's just sex,
and that you're happy to take the payment.
Don't feel guilty, it's
only supply and demand.
But the demand side needs
to know that it's moral
in order for it to thrive in this country.
It's a very Christian nation,
and so we need, we need, you know, like a,
we need an ad campaign, we need, um...
We need, we need George Clooney staring
straight down the barrel of the camera
in black and white, very
serious, very classy,
saying, "I would argue at this point
that seeing a prostitute is
more moral than burning coal,
and it's definitely more moral
than buying anything from China.
And it's definitely, certainly more moral
than our first-world bourgeois
addiction to the cocaine."
Get George Clooney
to single handedly legalize prostitution.
[Man] Mm, set us free, my brother.
Let the market decide.
Let your heart decide.
Let yourself loose, and,
and, and love, you know?
Love yourself.
Love yourself and love your wife
and love your prostitute.
God bless America.
God fucking bless America.
♪ O beautiful for spacious skies ♪
♪ For amber waves of grain ♪
♪ For purple mountain majesties ♪
♪ Above the fruited plain ♪
♪ America ♪
♪ God shed His grace on thee ♪
[vomiting]
[breathing heavily]
Don't overdo it. [chuckles]
Oh, my dad used to say that.
Don't overdo it.
Sorry, Pop.
I think I overdid it.
[vomiting]
Okay.
[breathing heavily]
Hi.
Yeah, can we get um, two
scoops of vanilla ice cream?
Thank you.
[phone beeps]
It'll help settle your stomach.
They give it to people after chemo.
We just nuked your body,
have some ice cream.
How do you know that?
I go to school for it.
Really?
Pediatrics.
[Man groans]
That must be tough, all the sick kids.
[water running]
[spitting]
Okay.
[Man chuckles]
What?
[exhales]
Do you have any friends?
[Jennifer] Sure.
What are their, what
are their middle names?
[Jennifer] Why?
Because real friends know
each other's middle names.
Grace.
Beth Grace Johnson.
Amy Grace Trudeau.
I believe you.
[Jennifer] What about you?
Kevin Benjamin Meredith.
[laughs] I don't believe you.
Good.
Very good.
Kevin Benjamin Meredith.
All right.
I haven't seen him in
20 years.
Since you were 10?
[Man] Thank you.
You haven't made a friend in 20 years?
- Not a real one.
- Why?
[Man] Work, money.
I don't believe you.
What a weird thing friends are.
Just the word, friends.
Friends.
So then why don't
you forget about money?
[Man] I can't.
Why?
I don't know.
I blame my father.
Sure, take the easy way out.
That's what fathers are for.
What's your middle name?
How much money do you
have in your pocket?
Good.
Very good.
[door chiming]
[door opening]
[door closing]
[spoon clanking]
Mm-mm.
Leigh.
What do you see?
The truth?
[Man] If not now, when?
Sadness.
- All men my age are sad.
- Why?
'Cause their dreams are done.
[Jennifer] Says who?
What do you really see though,
when you look at me?
Um, I see a man
surrounded by things.
Uh, a man who's made the
acquisition of these things
his main goal.
And I think he's just starting to realize
that these things are only making it worse
because now he's tricked himself
into thinking that these
things are a part of him,
the same as his kidneys
or his liver or his heart.
And I think it's his heart
that he's almost convinced
himself that he's forgotten.
But he can still feel it, hear it.
Like a faint echo in
the back of a dark cave,
not quite sure where it's coming from.
And I think that this is
really the root of his sadness.
That he decided long ago
to go against his heart,
against what God has given him,
in order to force himself into a system
whose sole goal is the acquisition
of more and more things.
[Man] Why does he do it?
Because he fears death.
What's gonna happen to him?
[Jennifer] It's easy.
He dies the same as everyone else.
And what about all my things?
Mm, they die.
That's impossible.
No, even your paintings in the end die.
Gone in the next great flood when this
sand turns back into ocean floor.
[Man] Well, then what
hope is there for any of us?
Now.
[silverware clanking]
Oh.
Hey, are you still alive in there?
[Man] Barely.
Hey, when's your birthday?
[Man] January 9th.
- What year?
- '80.
[safe beeping]
[water running]
You're a Capricorn, huh?
Figures.
Mm.
Mm, mm, mm, mm.
[Jennifer sighs]
Remind me never to put
anything up my nose again.
Jesus.
Oh, no.
You gotta get up.
[Man] Why?
Because if you stay down,
you'll think you belong there.
We'll never get out of here.
My dad used to say that.
Come on.
[Man] Did he ever consume
massive amounts of cocaine and champagne?
Well, then you just gotta get higher.
Let's go.
[groans] I don't wanna do any drugs.
I know what you need.
- How do you have-
- Excitement.
Adventure.
How do you, how do you
have all this energy?
[Jennifer] I don't know.
[silverware clanking]
Don't you just wanna
stay in the bed all day?
[Jennifer] Do you trust me?
Do you trust me?
With what?
With your life.
Yeah.
- Fuckin', yes.
- Right answer.
Okay, come on.
- Let's go.
- Mm.
[Jennifer] I have to
get out of here, please.
Mm.
[Jennifer sighs]
- Come on.
- It's Sunday?
Yeah.
- The 22nd?
- Sure.
[Man] You wanna have some real fun?
Please!
Please, please, please, please, please.
Okay.
All right, move.
[indistinct]
[safe beeping]
[safe whirring]
[safe chiming]
[safe beeping]
[safe whirring]
[safe chiming]
There.
What's this?
10 grand.
And in return?
We watch a movie tonight.
No deal.
I fucking hate movies.
You didn't let me finish.
After we have an afternoon full of action,
adventure, and international intrigue,
and I double your money.
Okay, I'm listening.
[Man] We are gonna day trade the yen.
What the what?
- It's the Japanese currency.
- How?
- Broker in Hong Kong.
- But it's Sunday.
It's Monday in Tokyo.
Are you ready?
What do I have to do?
How many of those can you take?
37.
And these little guys, two
of those and a cocktail
and it is lights out, bucko.
- A regular pharmacist.
- Mm, call me doctor.
And don't try to control me.
Okay.
Take out your phone and type in
"The value of the yen versus the dollar."
- 120 to one.
- Okay.
So if you think it's going to go up,
meaning that you think one dollar
is gonna buy more than 120 yen,
then you wanna buy long.
Or the call, if you
think it's gonna go down
then you wanna buy short.
What's the price of the call option?
I'm completely lost.
Okay, the call will buy you
100 yen for the price of one.
So if you buy at 120
and it goes down to 118,
how much did you just lose?
- Two cents?
- Two dollars.
What?
How does two cents become two dollars?
[Man] Because you just bought
100 but only paid for one.
That's...
- That's fucked.
- Not if you win.
Are you ready?
For what?
Okay, grab the phone.
You wanna get in at the open
before everything goes to shit.
Are you ready?
[water running]
What's the worst that could happen?
You lose my 10 grand.
Mm, I'd have to watch a movie for free.
Well, there are risks in this life.
Time's a wastin'.
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
Ask for an outside international line.
Can I have an outside
international line?
Okay.
3, 679, 2284.
- 679?
- 2284.
Okay, it's ringing.
Hello.
- It's a bank?
- Okay.
Ask for Maxwell Kane, and when
he picks up call him Max-Max.
Maxwell Kane, please.
Okay, it's ringing.
Hi, Max-Max?
Uh-
- Tell him that you're with The Monk
and that we wanna trade
options on the yen.
Um, I'm with The Monk
and we wanna trade
options on the yen today.
How much.
- How much?
- You tell me.
Call or short?
One second, Max-Max.
Okay, please stop fucking around.
- What should I do?
- Pick a color.
Red or black.
This isn't roulette, it's math.
No, no, no, no, no,
this is roulette disguised
as math, all right?
Up or down, long or short, red or black.
I want call options, Max-Max.
Can you give me some call options?
How much?
Um,
10,000.
He's laughing.
It's because 10,000 will
only get you a couple hundred
if it goes up two cents.
You gotta bet big to win big.
Ask him, ask him what
the credit line is at?
Um, what's his credit line at?
20 million?
Okay, your call.
But market is gonna
jump off, so chop chop.
Shit.
Uh.
500?
[Man] That only gets
you a couple thousand.
Uh, 1 million?
Mm, only gets you about 10 grand.
2 million?
Why don't we win big?
Uh. [laughs]
um, 3 million.
I want 3 million on call options, Max-Max.
Give me 3 million.
Thank you.
- Ooh-wee.
- Oh my god!
Oh my god!
Oh fuck, oh my god.
Where's my phone? Where is my phone?
Nope, I can't watch, actually.
Nope, I can't, uh-uh.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Holy shit!
- What's it doing?
- I'm not watching.
- What? Why?
- It's your bet.
There's 3 million dollars riding here!
No, it's, it's not moving.
That's probably not gonna
move for a little while.
The markets don't really
start to move until 10.
Well, [stammers] what about
all that jumping off shit?
That was dramatic tension.
- What time is it there?
- Six.
Oh, Jiminy Christmas.
It is bath time.
[upbeat rock music]
No, I can't, I can't.
Oh my god, I can't, I can't, I can't.
I just can't.
Oh.
No, I can't.
Sell right now and you win.
Oh my god, it's up!
I'm up five points!
I'm at 125!
[screams] No, 123!
No, no, no!
Oh my god I'm back up to 125!
[Man] Sell right now, you win.
No, what if it goes higher?
[laughs] More, more, more!
♪ Found myself in another dimension ♪
♪ No one really shows who they are ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, go and rip it up ♪
♪ Girls will have to talk ♪
♪ We are over talkers ♪
♪ Don't need drama queen ♪
♪ Throw your tricks ♪
♪ Make some punches and kicks ♪
♪ No pressures in between ♪
♪ Obsession ♪
♪ Conspiracy ♪
♪ Mama, where you at ♪
♪ Obsession ♪
♪ Conspiracy ♪
♪ Crash ♪
[moaning]
Tighter.
[groaning]
[breathing heavily]
Let's go to Paris.
When?
Tomorrow.
[bright music on television]
[crying]
[Tiny Tim] God bless us, everyone.
[cheering]
[sirens wailing]
[humming "Jingle Bells"]
Hey, what's your favorite
restaurant in Paris?
[Man] Uh, Cafe Julians on the River.
I wanna sit at Cafe
Julians and drink champagne.
[Man] I thought you
didn't drink champagne?
Well, when in Paris.
[Man] Can you check and see
what time the flight boards?
I don't have the tickets.
[Man] They're on my phone.
I thought you threw your
phone over the balcony?
[Man] They sent up a new one.
It should be on the nightstand.
[humming "Jingle Bells"]
Ow.
It's locked.
[Man] 2323.
Okay, it says the flights are.
[beeping]
[safe whirring]
[safe chiming]
I asked what time the flight boards
Oh.
Uh.
Um.
- 4:30.
- Great.
Pre-flight cocktail.
- You want one?
- Sure.
[Man] Super.
Okay.
My name's Rebecca Moore.
My mother has stage 3 stomach cancer
and we live in Reno.
No.
This will help pay for her chemo.
Don't!
What's your real name?
Rebecca Moore.
I live in Reno.
You know the interesting
thing about these suites?
Is that there's actually two safes.
There's the smaller
everyday safe in the closet,
but then there's the heavy hitter.
It's a little bit tricky to find, though,
'cause it's a floor safe.
[safe beeping]
Your real name.
What's your real name?
Hello.
Can I get you to send 100 grand cash up?
Thanks very much.
[Rebecca] Who are you?
- David Carthridge.
- Where do you live?
Doorman building on Central Park.
[Rebecca] What do you really do?
Commodities broker for a
large private equity firm
specializing in energy,
specifically crude.
- Oil?
- Black gold.
[Rebecca] Was?
My father died.
This is his funeral.
[Rebecca] What about your
brother's bachelor party.
Those guys you met work for me.
I brought them out here to celebrate.
- Your father's death?
- The execution of his estate.
[Rebecca] Meaning?
Meaning a Caribbean bank
deposited $100 million
into my bank account.
[door chiming]
It's funny how one minute 50 grand
can seem like a fortune, and the next.
My name's Melissa Price.
Where are you from, Melissa Price?
Jean.
One of those little desert towns
you pass on your way from L.A.
[David] How old are you?
25.
It was nice.
How much longer can you do this?
10 years.
- And then what?
- And then I'll own
two apartments in Phoenix
and live off the rent.
What is that?
50 grand a year?
My dad didn't own a fund.
You know, the day that my father died,
there were screams of joy
in his office building.
And I just sat there,
having just learned
that my father's atrial wall had exploded,
and I listened to adults scream with joy.
One day he ruled over 1,000
people and the next he didn't,
because it wasn't real.
I mean, how could something real
fall apart in just one second?
His whole life was just some hologram
that was created by lots and lots of cash,
and the only thing real
that he might've experienced
in his whole life was dying.
That's a good story.
But the truth is, that while he was alive
he did everything he wanted to,
because he could,
because he had more money
and more power than anyone.
They'll hate you for it,
but who cares what they think?
Because at the end of
the day, everyone's dead,
and the only thing that
matters is how you live.
Your father won and they lost.
Jesus died penniless
and he still gets top billing
in every drawer in this town.
Jesus died hung by nails for days.
The rest is a fairytale they tell the poor
to keep them happy and poor
and away from the rich.
Melissa Price,
25,
there is no God,
there is no love, there is
no joy, just cold hard cash.
David Carthridge, poor little rich kid
who gives a hooker 50k so he
can pretend he has a soul,
pretend like this whole
weekend wasn't about one thing.
Fucking me.
That's not true.
I didn't ask for any of
this money, I just have it.
And it attracts people,
they're obsessed with it.
All around me are people that
will devote their entire lives
to making as much money as I was given.
They'll destroy themselves,
they'll destroy each other,
they'll destroy anything to get it.
I didn't have to destroy myself
for it, I already had it,
so I got to keep my soul.
It's unfair, but it's true.
How long have you been up here?
What?
You've been up here thinking
long before I arrived.
20 days.
Why?
- Because my dad died.
- And?
I realized that my life is
the same hologram that his was.
Oh.
So this was a spiritual journey.
Holed up above Las Vegas
to find something real
with a woman you paid.
This was a consume everything,
I came to ease the pain the
only way I know how for 20 days,
but the pain was still there
so you had to consume something else, me.
But you fucked up.
You decided to feel something
rather than consume something.
Tell me your story.
I'm paying for it.
You were what, 23
when we went into Iraq?
- Yeah.
- Working for your father?
[David] Mm-hmm.
Just out of some fancy school.
[David] Yeah.
You wore $2,000 suits, had a secretary,
ate stake dinners twice a week.
But deep down you felt like
an artist, a painter. [laughs]
Maybe.
What happened to the price
of oil after we went in?
- It tripled.
- Did you celebrate?
- I was 25.
- Be brave.
If not now, when?
I bought a...
Bought an apartment,
uh, in South Beach.
Did you wait a week?
Or was it the very day we invaded?
You had the guys down for the weekend,
sun, cocaine, women.
Hundreds of thousands of people
were gonna die and you knew it.
But not you, and not any of your friends.
Just the poor fuckers living
on the wrong kind of sand.
I was 10 when my dad died in Iraq.
I was 16 when my mom finally gave in.
I never was very good at school.
I met a man, came to Vegas with him.
I wanted to be a singer,
I was gonna have my own show at Caesars
and then a record contract in L.A.
But things get hard.
And someone gives you $300
one night and away you go.
[breathing heavily]
Up here you get to make up your own story.
But down there, your
story gets branded on you
the moment you're born.
There is no power in that,
only struggle.
[breathing heavily]
Was it real?
♪ O beautiful ♪
♪ For spacious skies ♪
♪ For amber waves of grain ♪
♪ For purple mountain majesty ♪
♪ Above the fruited plain ♪
♪ America ♪
♪ God shed his grace on thee ♪
♪ And crown thy good ♪
♪ With brotherhood ♪
♪ From sea to shining sea ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ From sea to ♪
♪ Shining ♪
♪ Sea ♪