Is the bloom off the Ivy Rose?
What's up, guys?
It's me, Dan Buford, here
with your Celebrity Gossip.
Pop sensation, Ivy Rose,
may seem to have it all.
Legions of adoring fans,
an up-and-coming social
media megastar boyfriend
in Becker Daniels, and
her most recent album,
"Party Nights...
[It's Party Time]"
has been at the top of
the charts for 16 weeks
with no sign of slowing down.
But the situation is
a little more thorny
than Ivy's public
image may suggest.
The Celebrity Gossip
Minute has obtained
exclusive information
from sources close
to the pop star that Ivy's
life is drama-city right now.
Word is she's battling her
manager-extraordinaire,
Naomi Klein, and
her record label
on the creative
direction of her career.
Things with her and
Becker are wilting fast.
Peter Pan complex much?
And, apparently, Ivy wants
to avoid the one thing
pop stars desperately
crave: the spotlight.
Drama.
But, look out, it's
not all bad news.
We also have it on authority
that Ivy will soon be performing
songs from her album at a very
small, very intimate venue,
very exclusive.
You heard it here first, folks.
And remember what we always say,
"They're just rumors,
so you can't sue us."
And that's all for this edition
of Celebrity Gossip Minute.
We'll see you next time.
Wow, Becker, this place
is really romantic.
Only the best for you, babe.
Excuse me, you can't
just walk in here!
[camera shutter clicking]
Hey, guys, we're just trying to
have a quiet dinner in peace.
How about cutting us some slack?
Wow, that's new.
I thought you loved
the spotlight.
Yeah, well, I thought about
what you said the other night.
See? I listen.
And I also needed a private
moment to be able to do this.
Okay.
Woman: Oh my God, wow.
Ivy...
[chuckles nervously]
You make me want
to be a better man.
I want nothing more than to
buy a house, to get married,
fill it with kids and grow
old and gray together.
Will you do me the favor
of looking over there
and saying, "I've
just been skunked!"
Wait, wait, what?
What is this?
It's a prank. We're
gonna be on "Skunked".
This is awesome, right?
No! No, this is not awesome.
Why would you do this?
Come on.
You said you wanted
to feel normal.
I was like I will show
her what normal is.
Normal sucks.
No.
I thought it was really
sweet and romantic.
We're two of the most
famous people in the world.
When I propose to you,
it's gonna be insane.
I don't want insane.
I wanted the real
version of that.
I can't do this anymore.
Look, you're mad.
I'm sorry.
No. I've been feeling like
this for a really long time.
But tonight, it
just solidified it.
We're on two different pages.
It's not fair to
either one of us
to pretend that we're not, okay?
I'm sorry. It's over.
It's over?
First off, we just wanted to
start by saying how excited
we are to be in the
Ivy Rose business.
International pop star,
Ivy Rose. So excited.
Thank you.
You know, what about
when I'm not working,
I could take the wig off.
And that way, I can move
around the world undetected
and kind of have some privacy.
No, the wig stays.
Ivy Rose isn't just about music.
It's a vibe.
And maintaining that
vibe is so, so important.
I mean, would people even know
who you are without the wig?
That's kind of the point.
So we all know that your
last album was a hit.
But we feel it's time
Ivy Rose grew up.
I'm so glad to
hear you say that.
I was thinking maybe I
could write my own music
for my next album.
Right. Well, we'd love if
that were possible, Ivy.
The thing is, Sean and I kind
of have this down to a science.
Trust the experts, Ivy.
But I actually became a musician
so that I could perform
my own music, you know.
Kind of like Taylor
Swift's "Folklore."
I want my own "Folklore!"
We actually feel like "Party
Night [It's Party Time]"
is your "Folklore."
Your next album would
actually be your "Evermore".
Oh, I just got the chills.
Right?
If your song ain't in
the club, it's a flub.
As I like to say.
But it's true. It's true.
[bell rings]
Oh!
Just the man I was looking for.
Hi, Cameron.
Darren, I have scored two
extremely exclusive tickets
for a intimate
small launch party
with five-time Grammy
winner, Ivy Rose!
Cameron, that's
awesome, it really is.
I just have so much to
get done around the store.
Well, how about this?
You can give me a
list of things to do.
And then I'll go and do them
so that you two can
go and have some fun.
Oh, thank you. Perfect.
Darren, what do you say?
Yeah, all right. I'll go.
Yay.
This is great!
See you later.
- Bye.
- Bye!
Enjoy the show.
I'll get you back for this.
Ah!
Front row.
Front row! Oh, my, yes.
- Amazing.
- Cool.
Oh, this is so incredible.
Yeah.
So, what? What kind of
music does she sing?
Darren, really?
Naomi?
What if I played some of my
own music just for tonight?
Since the audience is so small.
I mean, I wish, Ivy...
I really, really wish.
It's just that this
promo is for your album,
and you know the fans.
They only really want
to hear the hits.
- You get it.
- Yeah.
Don't make my own choices.
Just do what I'm told.
You got it.
Does she have purple
hair or is that a thing?
Is that her thing?
Yes, Darren, she
has purple hair.
Okay. How come you don't
have a purple wig on?
Oh, I... I just thought
my hair looked nice.
Oh, no, it does.
It's show time.
Ladies and gentlemen, we
are so excited to host
this one-time unplugged event
with five-time Grammy
winner, Ivy Rose!
[cheering]
[ pop music plays ]
♪ Every day is summer
♪ So cue the band
♪ Get settled down
♪ So close I can feel it now
♪ Tonight's the night
♪ The lights turn off
♪ So I pull up and
bring my A-game, baby ♪
♪ Out in the city
♪ Our music
♪ Out 'til morning
♪ Out to party
♪ Almost party time
♪ Four, three, two, one
♪ Every day since
I've been born ♪
♪ I'm bring the
heat to the party ♪
♪ And now that you're warm
♪ I turn it up
♪ And I can't stop
♪ It goes on and on and on
until the last one drops ♪
♪ Bright lights
that pop a city ♪
♪ Can't fit the script
♪ Oh, what a pity
♪ I turn it up,
then I can't stop ♪
♪ It goes on and on and on
until the last one drops ♪
♪ Party
♪ I just want to party now
♪ Go until the lights go down
♪ Wanna party
♪ Please just let me party now
♪ Party
[applause]
[cheering]
Becker? What are
you doing here?
[gasping]
- Oh my God!
- Hey, it's Becker.
Ivy...
Oh!
I have been so sad
since you dumped me.
We belong together, Ivy.
I'm begging you...
Please, give me another chance.
So you thought the
way to get me back
was to ambush me
in my performance?
That's an insult to
me and the audience.
We love it!
Cameron, stop!
Are you kidding me?
BE-VY! BE-VY! BE-VY!
Cameron, stop!
She's uncomfortable.
Oh my! BE-VY! BE-VY!
- Come on, Darren.
- No.
[chanting continues]
She doesn't...
Aw... Babe, this
is our couple name.
Come here.
I know this is
gonna sound crazy.
Can you kiss me... right now?
I mean, if you want to.
How's this for spontaneous?
What?
Nothing.
[camera shutters clicking]
- That's cold.
- What's going on?
I said we were over
and I meant it.
Poison Ivy!
Who are you?
Darren.
[scoffs]
Cameron?
Can someone tell me what the
heck is going on with you?
I don't know.
I guess I'm starting
to make my own choices.
Well, your "choice"
tonight made things
a lot harder for you,
for me, for both of us!
You're being painted as
cruel and coldhearted.
#poisonivy is
trending right now!
Oh, uh...
Hey, remember me?
Crazy lady who made
you kiss them onstage?
Oh, yeah.
I vaguely remember that.
You didn't make me.
You gave me an out.
Well, how kind of me.
I just want to
say that I'm sorry
for roping you into
all of that back there.
You were really a
good sport about it.
Hey, that is the most excitement
I've had in a very long time.
Though I can't say
the same for my date.
Hence why I'm waiting
for a rideshare.
Oh, thanks. I'm
sorry about that.
Nah, it wasn't meant
to be, I guess.
I really enjoyed it, by the way.
I'm sorry?
Um, the performance.
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
Yeah, I thought you were
talking about something else.
Thanks.
They don't let me write
my own music, so...
Oh, thank... those lyrics.
Oh, nice!
Oh, too honest?
I mean, it's refreshing,
but a little mean.
Okay, I'm sorry.
You said you didn't
write them, though?
Yes, but I'm allowed
to say that, not you.
What makes you the
musical expert anyway?
Well, I do own a record
store in Deer Falls, so...
Huh.
I will say this.
You sure do know how
to make a statement.
Oh, how rude of me to kiss you
without introducing
myself first.
I'm Ivy Rose.
Nice to meet you, Ivy
Rose. I'm Darren Howard.
Nice to meet you, Darren Howard.
[phone chimes]
Crazy night, huh?
Crazy life.
Sometimes I wish I
could just disappear
and leave it all behind.
And live a quiet, normal life
with a quiet, normal job.
Well, if you want
a quiet, normal job
in a quiet, normal town,
I know just the place.
Trust me. It's not all
it's cracked up to be.
I'm sure it's great.
[phone rings]
This is me.
Goodnight.
Hey, I hope you find
what you're looking for.
Thank you.
[sighs]
[phone chiming]
[phone rings]
[phone chimes]
Deer Falls.
Wall of Sound Records.
A place to find myself.
This is my "Folklore."
[chuckles]
Wow, this is even better
than the pictures.
A place to find myself.
Perfect.
You know, they have computers
that can pay bills now.
Yeah, well, you know me.
I'm more of an analog guy.
Hmm, yeah.
Well, the digital
world loves you.
I mean, the sheer number of
angles they got of that kiss?
- Mwa!
- Aw, geez.
Okay, back on the
floor. Let's go.
- And show me. One.
- It's beautiful.
One picture.
- Yeah, it's beautiful.
- Show me.
Pull out your
snapchat or whatever.
What picture do you want
to start off with first?
The closeup or the full angle?
The best one.
Okay.
- Well, then there's this one.
- Oh, God.
This is an "Oh!"
Okay, I've seen
enough, thank you.
Your face!
Wait! What...
Aw, come on.
This is like the biggest
celebrity story like ever.
Maybe you're not as
lame as I thought.
Okay, I'm still
your boss, you know.
That was a compliment!
Well, now that the
excitement is over,
we still have the store to run.
So let's get back to work.
Oh, hi.
Welcome to Wall
of Sound Records.
Can I help you?
Hi.
Oh, my gosh, Darren?
Darren Howard?
I'm sorry. Do we
know each other?
[gasps]
That's your real hair?
Ivy Rose?
Yeah. Bingo!
So what brings you
here, stranger?
Well, this, you know,
is my record store,
the one that I told
you about last night.
What brings you here, stranger?
Well, you said that
if I was ever in town
that I should stop by, so...
So here you are, less
than 24 hours later.
Yeah, what a coincidence, right?
Right.
Okay. I know this
must seem crazy.
I feel crazy.
I just... last night,
you were so nice to me.
And I can't remember
the last time
someone was just
genuinely nice to me
without wanting
something in return.
So I just thought...
I'm gonna stop talking now.
Hold on, hold on. It's okay.
I liked talking to
you too last night.
Talking.
- Hi.
I'm Karina. Big fan.
And Karina was just getting
back to work, wasn't she?
Ugh. Not fair.
Anyway, I thought this would
be a perfect place for me
to kind of decompress and
reconnect with my work.
So I rented a house
and I'm just gonna kind of
see where it all takes me.
Okay. Well, cool.
I guess I'll see
you around then.
What if I like worked here?
- Worked here?
- Yeah.
Remember quiet, normal job?
I mean, I don't know. It...
I think what he means to say is
that he doesn't know why
you didn't ask sooner.
Oh, is that what I meant?
Yeah, I get it, and you don't
even have to pay me anything.
I'll blend right in.
You didn't even recognize
me without the wig, right?
And, more importantly,
I didn't recognize you.
Did I mention I'm a big fan?
And, look, I'll
be here, you know.
Like I'll help you.
There's not a lot to do anyway.
My loyal employee.
I'm not getting out of this
without saying yes, am I?
[both] No.
Okay.
Well, Ivy Rose, welcome
to Wall of Sound Records.
You're hired-ish!
Oh, my gosh! Yes! Thank you!
Do I get a badge?
A badge.
I can make you a badge.
No, we don't wear badges.
What are you up to, Ivy Rose?
Morning, Ivy.
Welcome.
Well, if you don't want
any unwanted attention,
I can't go by Ivy, right?
So I am Jamie
reporting for duty.
Why Jamie?
It's my real name.
I haven't gone by it
since high school.
So what are my duties, boss?
Oh, please don't call me boss.
Makes me feel old.
You are old.
Choosing to ignore that.
Let's get to work!
- Okay.
- Great!
Show me what I do.
- Here's the records.
- Ooh, okay.
So what do we do?
We have a pretty purple one...
[chattering]
[clears throat]
Hi!
Welcome to the Wall
of Sound Records.
I am Jamie, and you are...
Oh, I'm Paige.
Wow, not used to be
asked that in a store.
Well, that's the kind
of customer service
we provide here at
Wall of Sound Records.
So formal.
So is there anything
I can help you with?
Yeah.
I'm looking for "Party Night
[It's Party Time]" by Ivy Rose.
Right, yeah.
That's... we could find that.
If I was Ivy Rose...
which I'm not...
What section would I be in?
- You put the price on the...
- You know what?
Can you give me a minute while
I ask my associate something?
- Yeah.
- Okay, thanks.
Um, oddly, she is looking
for one of my albums.
Awkward.
We don't actually
carry your music here.
Okay.
I don't hate that, but
maybe you can just point me
to the pop section so
we can save the sale?
There is no pop section,
modern pop anyway.
See, Darren doesn't
believe in pop music.
Okay, it's not like
I don't believe it,
like it's a ghost or something.
I just happen to believe
that pop peaked around 1983.
Before you were born?
My dad brought me
up on the classics.
What can I say?
Okay.
I'm so sorry, Paige. We
don't carry that here.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
I'm sorry.
Are you...
No, sorry.
I thought you were somebody
I went to high school with.
Yeah, I guess I have one
of those familiar faces.
Well, thank you anyway.
I'll just have to
go somewhere else.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Bye. Sorry.
Well, the disguise works,
I'll give you that.
Yeah, I told you it would.
But, more importantly,
we lost a sale.
Ah, yes. Welcome to every
day of Wall of Sound Records.
Hey, I'm sitting right here.
So? Okay.
I understand that you
already gave me an extension.
I just... gotta go.
A customer just came in.
Hey, is everything okay?
Can I help you with anything?
Nope. Just business stuff.
Nothing to worry about.
Nothing to worry about?
Sir, this is my
place of employment.
Okay, not in the mood for jokes.
Sorry. Just... long day.
[phone rings]
Can I make an observation
about the store?
One day working
in a record store
and she's already an expert.
I don't have to be an expert
to see what's wrong in
your business model.
With music streaming, it's
a miracle anyone would want
to walk into a record store
and buy physical music at all.
So at least when they do,
you can have what they want.
So what's the deal?
For me, it was always
about operating a store
that was a collector's dream.
Audiophile's paradise.
How about a truce?
How about I take you to dinner?
- I don't know. I...
- Come on.
It's the least I can do
after I made you kiss me
in front of my ex-boyfriend.
I rented a house in your town
and I came to your store
and made you give me a job.
Wow.
When you list it all out like
that, it's kind of a lot.
Yeah, it is.
All right, you got
me. Dinner it is.
Great! Okay.
So where do people
eat around here?
Nice place, huh?
Yes, this is very... uh.
- Thank you.
Very French.
Best Deer Falls has to offer.
So you come here often?
Oh, yeah, all the time.
My favorite dish is the, um...
Con-fit de co... canard.
Your favorite, huh?
Get it all the time.
You've clearly never
been here before.
Figured it'd be nothing but
the finest things in life
for our VIP guest.
Well, I'm Jamie, remember?
No VIP status here.
Okay.
Okay, and is Jamie saying
she doesn't want to eat here?
Jamie doesn't want to eat here.
Jamie wants real food.
Thank God. I think I
could accommodate that.
This house is incredible.
I love it here.
It's so peaceful.
Your, uh, cheeseburger, Miss.
Now this is more like it.
Mm!
- Good?
- This burger is next level.
Sorry they didn't have any
of your Con-fit co-nard.
Right.
I'm still so insulted
that you took me there.
Well, I guess it's fair that
you have something on me
since I already
have so much on you.
Should I go over
that list again?
No, I think we're good.
Yeah.
So what about the "why"?
Why?
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I love music with
all of my heart.
But I just... I didn't know
it was gonna be what it is.
And what is it?
My life doesn't belong to me.
My image, my relationship...
just everything is about
preserving ticket
and record sales.
So it's just pressure, pressure,
pressure building all the time.
So here I am, Deer Fall's
number one unpaid intern.
It probably didn't
hurt that I was, like,
you know, super handsome.
Moderately handsome...
from a distance.
Okay. You couldn't
even give me that?
Well, thank you for gracing
us with your presence,
runaway pop star.
So what about you?
I'm divorced.
Oh. I'm sorry.
No, no, don't be.
No, we were just kids, you know.
We figured that's what
you do after college.
But as we grew up together,
we realized that we were both
heading in different directions.
Well, that's a pretty
mature outlook you have.
I can say that now with
years of hindsight.
So, yeah, I took out way
too big of a loan, you know.
And I didn't know
the first thing about
running a record store.
But when my marriage dissolved,
I still had the store.
And what a great store
it is, very old school.
Yeah, that's what
I was going for.
When I was a kid, our
basement looked like that.
You know, the shag carpeting,
wood paneling, all that.
Super dated, but also awesome.
My dad and I used to
hang out down there
and listen to old records.
Oh.
So that explains the "my
music peaked in 1983" stance.
Yeah. I figured, you know,
when you get in one of those
audiophile blogs and
you turn it all around,
if somebody like Miles Enderman
gives your store a good review,
you got it made.
I wrote him once a week
the first two years
the store was open,
never replied.
So finally I just
threw in the towel.
Guess maybe I should do
that with the store, too.
What if we can help
save the store?
Consider it an
exchange for letting me
hide out from my problems.
Don't say that.
It's okay.
I know what I'm doing and I
want to help you save the store.
We just need to
make a few changes.
What kind of changes?
Sale?
Yeah.
Are we having a sale?
Well, yes.
Actually, can you hand
me that box down there?
You can help me put it
up here? Go through it?
- Ivy?
- Yes?
The whole idea is to make
more money, not less.
Since you have no
customers to begin with,
it's just called marketing.
Also, there are baked goods.
We can pass these
out to our customers.
I made them myself.
- Oh...
- Go on.
Try one.
Fine. A little bite here.
What recipe did you use?
I didn't. I just
did it from scratch.
Well, it's a good thing that
we don't have any customers,
because these can't
give these to anyone.
I'm closing the door.
No! Then people won't
know it's a sale!
There is no sale... or
non-sale sale, whatever it is!
I think he's just on a diet.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Come one, come all!
You won't be laughing when
you see this collection!
Absolutely not! This
is not a carnival!
Yes, yes, yes! Go, go, go, go!
Please don't do that.
Okay, guys, guys,
please be careful.
No, no, no, no.
- Please don't...
- What?
That is our last
copy of that one.
Remember, folks!
Inside one very special record
is a golden ticket for
a very special prize!
Nope! Shut it down!
Shut it down.
[sighs]
I can't believe he shut down
every single one of my ideas.
Hey, Ivy?
- Yeah?
- Can I ask you something?
Sure.
What made you change your style?
I used to watch your videos
you put out on the internet,
and it was just you in
your bedroom with a guitar.
It felt like you
were just like me.
And then you got famous and
then everything changed.
I mean, I know
your life changed,
but the songs just didn't
sound like you anymore.
I know what you mean.
It's because they really
aren't me anymore.
They want Ivy Rose, the look
and Ivy Rose, the voice.
But not Ivy Rose, the mind.
I mean, have you
tried songwriting?
Yeah. I was just so
stressed out all the time,
everything I would write
felt forced and lame.
And then I was gonna write ere.
But I was in such a
rush getting out of town
that I forgot my guitar, so...
I have one. Two, in fact!
I keep one in the
back of the store.
- You want to borrow it?
- No, no, Karina. It's okay.
You don't have to do that.
I don't wanna
borrow your guitar.
No! Are you kidding?
The fact that I'll
be able to say
that Ivy Rose
played my guitar...
I mean, if you really mean it,
I'd actually really like that.
I do. Forget it.
You came here to disconnect.
And it's an opportunity
to... I don't know.
Reconnect with yourself?
I mean, that's what this whole
thing is about anyway, right?
Yeah.
Reconnect with myself
because myself is awesome.
I know you were just
trying to help earlier.
I guess I have a hard
time with change.
That's the understatement
of the century.
[phone rings]
[leaf blower]
[knocking]
Hi! What's up? Wanna hang out?
Ivy?
You're here... at my house.
Plus, I got you
coffee and a muffin.
Aren't you supposed to be
reconnecting with yourself?
Yeah, I tried that.
It's a work in
progress, baby steps.
Come on. Let's go.
Fine. I'll take that.
So I didn't pack many
clothes before coming here.
Know of any good thrift stores?
Oh, my gosh! Look
at this store!
So cute!
I never figured you
for a vintage girl.
Oh, my gosh.
In high school, that's
pretty much all I would wear.
None of that fast
fake vintage stuff,
you get the real deal.
Kind of like your store.
I see your point.
Yeah.
Nowadays, I really never get
to decide what I'm gonna wear.
But today is a new
dawn and a new me.
Look at this hat!
Isn't that cute?
It's a statement.
A statement, yes.
I like this statement.
Yeah.
[chuckles] Yes.
Ta-da!
Yes.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
But how do you feel?
I feel amazing.
- Then I'm glad you got them.
- Thank you.
Yeah, I feel like I struck gold.
You want me to
take that for you?
Yeah.
Thanks for spending
Sunday with me.
I can think of worse
ways to spend a Sunday.
Shall we?
You've got to be kidding me!
Hey, it's okay.
I told them that I was working
on getting the money...
Or a buyer.
Guess I didn't realize
it was that bad.
Well, if something
doesn't happen soon,
then I'm gonna lose the store
before I can even sell it.
I'm really sorry.
Yeah, well, not everything works
out the way it's supposed to.
Hey, is that your dad?
Yeah.
He was my hero.
We lost him my senior
year of high school.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I... I didn't know.
No, don't worry.
How would you know?
Having his picture there,
it kind of grounds me.
This place, the vibe,
the whole aesthetic,
it actually feels like it's
keeping his memory alive.
That makes sense.
I actually lost my
mom a few years ago.
It was really hard.
I'm sorry, too.
She was my best friend,
and she was so supportive
of my career in music.
Sometimes I feel like
I'm letting her down.
Letting her down?
Like what if I'm not
really that good?
Ivy, if you're not that good,
then we're all in trouble.
And yeah everyone has
imposter syndrome sometimes.
You know the number
of times I thought
I wasn't fit to
run a record store?
Although that one
might actually be true.
Okay, stop.
Okay, this store, it's great.
It's just your marketing...
Yeah, well, we might
not have to worry
about that for much longer.
Hey, I said I was gonna help
you with the store, didn't I?
Ivy, we tried your ideas.
I'm talking about
something bigger.
Why do I have a feeling
I'm gonna regret this?
Are you with me?
I'm with you.
- Let's do this!
- All right!
- Let's do it.
- Yeah!
Okay, ready for your surprise?
I feel like an idiot.
Okay.
One, two, three...
In addition to the lights,
I added a new music section,
some apparel and a
stage for local artists.
- Oh, and...
- Darren's Basement?
Yeah.
I mean, you said you didn't have
a real connection with the name.
And so there's just so
much of you in the store.
So I figured the name
should reflect that.
If you hate it, we can
just change it back.
I don't hate it.
No?
No.
No, it's actually really cool.
Goodbye Wall of Sound,
Hello Darren's Basement.
Great! Because I already
had all of this made.
Merch.
Ivy, thank you for
doing all this.
Thanks for letting me help.
Hello?
Are you guys gonna keep
staring at each other?
Or are you gonna help
me unpack these boxes?
- Right. Sorry.
- No, that's fine.
Well, let's go, sport.
Hope you brought a
change of clothes.
It's soft relaunch time!
[laughing]
Come one, come all!
Darren's Basement!
We have a brand new remodel!
You have good style,
I have good style.
That has good style.
You should go in!
Got a lot of classic
records in there.
Let me tell you,
got amazing finds.
- Guys, come in, come on!
- You're gonna love it.
Woo!
[chattering]
- Welcome to Darren's Basement!
- Welcome!
Darren's Basement, yep.
Buy everything!
Okay, two customers won't save
the store, but it's a start.
Relax.
Rome wasn't built in a day.
Was Rome for sale while
they were building it?
Ha-ha.
Anyway, I trust you
can hold down the fort.
Karina here is
gonna go grab lunch.
And I'm gonna be in the back
doing some paperwork
if you need me.
Okay. Yes, sir, boss, sir.
Don't call me that, please.
All right. Show time.
Hi, there.
Welcome to Darren's
Basement Records.
I'm Jamie.
Can I help you find anything?
Is all this wood
original? And the carpet?
Yes.
Our owner, Darren Howard,
actually restored it himself.
Impressive.
It's decidedly retro
without trying too hard.
Yes. That is exactly
how I would describe it.
Oh, wow, an Allman
Brothers 1973 bootleg?
Original pressing of The
Beatles "Revolver" album.
And a 1950 Charlie Parker
"Live at Birdland".
Impressive selection.
Yes, well, our
owner Darren Howard,
he is quite the audiophile.
Yeah, I can see.
Yes. And over here, we
have our new releases.
And over here is a list of our
live in-store performances.
And over here, we have our
brand spanking new merch.
Seems like you've
got everything.
Yeah, pretty much.
Everything except customers.
That's a shame.
Oh, no. You should have
seen us this morning.
Naturally.
So is there anything I can
help package up for you?
No. Okay, thanks. I
think I'll get on my way.
Thank you. You've
been very helpful.
You know, it's funny.
You look quite familiar.
I can't quite pit it, but...
Okay, good day.
What a jerk!
What are you always
writing in there anyway?
Oh, it's nothing.
Miss Karina here is
quite the writer.
Come on. Let's see.
What are you writing?
Okay, it's just lyrics
that I'm writing for
some of my songs.
Lyrics? So you've been
holding out on me.
Can I read?
No way!
That's so embarrassing!
Okay. You want to talk
about embarrassing?
My last album was called
"Party Night [It's Party Time]."
Yeah, like, why say party twice?
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
Yes. Thank you.
Let's see.
Oh, God...
Wow!
- Karina...
- Don't be scared.
These are amazing!
Yeah, they're so personal,
and raw and authentic.
I told you so.
No way. Ivy Rose just
complimented my lyrics?
No. Jamie did.
Whoops. Right. Sorry.
All right.
I want you to check out mine.
But, honestly, I've been
struggling, so just be honest.
Okay.
Well?
Okay, so spill it,
what do you think?
Meh.
Meh? Ouch.
Ouch, indeed.
Okay, I appreciate the honesty.
That's what I wanted,
but just elaborate.
Tell me what you think.
I mean, they just feel
like they're written
by someone who's trying
to seem authentic.
I mean, these lyrics
are very similar
to the ones that you used
to put out on YouTube.
But isn't that a good thing?
Isn't that what you liked?
Well, yeah, but you're not
that person anymore, are you?
I mean, what about all the
life you've lived in between?
I mean, all the
life experiences.
Even the ones that you don't
like should inform your art.
Hey, I get what she's saying.
I mean, you were Jamie long
before you were Ivy Rose, right?
So what does Jamie feel
about Ivy Rose's career?
Wow.
I feel like I should know the
answer to that, but I don't.
Then I guess you
need to figure it out
to break down those walls.
She's a smart one, isn't she?
You both are pretty smart.
Oh, really?
So you know what
this means, right?
You have to help me.
Help you? How?
Well, I'm not that
teenage girl writing songs
in my room anymore, but you are.
You mean, write with... you?
Yes.
Oh, my gosh, you're kidding!
I'm gonna get to
write with Ivy Rose.
Yeah. Sounds like
a Dream Team.
♪ I took the quick
road out of town ♪
♪ Don't know when I've
ever been this down ♪
♪ If I could just
find my sound ♪
No, that is not good at all.
Wait. What?
Well, why are you
giving up so easily?
I just feel so stuck.
Well, let's get you unstuck.
Now come on, what do
you wanna write about?
I don't know.
Everything felt so much
easier when I was younger.
Life is so complicated now.
You know, adults say
that all the time.
But I don't think that's true.
I mean, you guys have
more stuff to do.
But you swap boys for
men and school for work
but the emotions are
still at the root of it.
Hmm, I guess that's true.
Yeah.
So should I be
writing about a man?
I mean, if you want to.
A man like Darren?
- Karina!
- What?
You like him, don't you?
I am not gonna talk
to you about this.
Why not?
I mean, he likes you,
you know. I can tell.
And he hasn't liked
someone for a long time.
Well, I enjoy our
professional friendship.
- Your professional friendship.
- Yes.
Please!
Oh, my gosh!
Guys! Guys!
What?
The store! It's famous!
Look at what my friend
just sent to me!
We're on Popular Audiophile!
Popular Audiophile?
Wait. Isn't that the blog
you were telling me about?
Yes, it's the premier blog
for vinyl record enthusiasts.
This is huge, but how?
Oh, my! That guy!
That's the guy! He was here!
Miles Enderman? He
was in my store?
Yes! That's the jerk I
was telling you about.
Why didn't you come get me?
I can't believe you got to meet
Miles Enderman and I didn't!
Wait, no. I didn't know
that was him, obviously.
Do you guys wanna read it or...
All right, yeah. Oh, okay.
Let's see.
"Boasting a wood panel aesthetic
"that evokes being in your
buddy's basement in the 1970s,
"Darren's Basement Records
boasts a wide selection
"of new releases, as
well as an eclectic mix
of classical and
hard-to-find vinyl."
Oh, my!
"The owner and
proprietor, Darren Howard,
"has clearly put a
lot of love and care
"into the store,
so be sure to put
Darren's Basement Records
on your itinerary."
- Darren! This is huge!
- This is incredible!
Miles Enderman knows my name!
Darren, I've never
seen you this excited.
Ivy, you were right.
Excuse me?
Can you please say that again,
louder so everyone can hear?
I said, you were
right. You happy now?
- Yes.
- And get this.
Our numbers in social media have
basically tripled overnight!
- Wow.
Now if only our customers
would triple overnight.
Oh, I don't think that's
gonna be a problem.
[chattering]
This is my favorite album.
You guys take checks?
Yeah, we handle
checks, anything.
Thank you.
What?
Deer Falls?
Naomi?
Yeah, I found her.
You seem extra happy tonight.
I am.
Or maybe that cheeseburger
was tasting extra good.
No, really, I...
really wanted to thank you
for everything you've done.
You know, you don't have
to keep thanking me.
I basically had to torture
you into letting me help you.
Seriously, I got an
offer on the store today.
That's really good, right?
A week ago, I would
have said yes.
But if business
keeps up like this,
it's gonna feel even better
to tell that person no.
I am so glad to
hear you say that.
And I know Karina will be too.
Good, because I'm a
little bit afraid of her.
I am too,
but she seems to really care
about you and the store.
Yep, and she really
seems to want us to date.
Yes, she does.
Very subtle, yes.
Nah, she's a good kid.
Yeah.
Her parents, they work a lot.
She hangs around the
store, picks my brain.
Eventually, she started helping
customers pick out music.
So I figured she might
as well get paid for it.
That's really sweet of you.
So the proverbial
elephant in the room.
What's next for Ivy Rose?
Next? Hmm.
Being here is the first time
I've really, truly
felt like myself.
I've really, truly felt happy.
Well, you could always stay.
I mean, you know it
would keep me from having
to hire a new employee,
especially since
I don't pay you.
Is that the only reason?
I guess I do have a house here.
Yeah.
Yeah, you could commute.
I could commute, yeah.
Ivy Rose, the commuter.
Yeah, listening to podcasts.
Right. The glamorous
world of us normies.
[laughing]
Well, I guess I should
probably get going.
Yeah. Okay.
Hey, I had a really
good time tonight.
I did, too.
We should do it again sometime.
Yeah, I'd like that, boss.
I said don't call me that.
Goodnight, Ivy Rose.
Goodnight, Darren Howard.
[guitar music plays]
[harmonizes]
♪ The days were always blurred
♪ My voice was never heard
♪ A quiet place
to find myself ♪
♪ Who could ask for more?
♪ Oh I'm smiling
more frequently ♪
♪ Knowing that I am here
♪ I'm beginning to understand
♪ Myself again
- Mornin'.
- Morning.
- How's it coming?
- It's good.
Actually, the lyrics yesterday,
they just poured out of me.
Yeah, it felt really good.
Can I read?
Yeah.
Really? Okay.
Ivy, I love these.
Really?
Yeah.
It feels like you really
found your voice again.
I mean, there's
some sad in here,
but also a lot of happy.
Ivy...
Yeah, I mean, ever since
I've been in Deer Falls,
this is the happiest I've
been in a really long time.
And you're channeling
your happy.
Yes! Channeling my happy!
Yeah, I like that.
All right.
So what about a
songwriting session
at my house tomorrow after work?
Absolutely.
Okay.
What are you doing? It's
the middle of the day.
Yeah, and I just don't really
feel like working right now.
You don't feel like working?
Shocking, huh?
I'm feeling spontaneous.
How about a barbecue?
Yeah, a company barbecue.
Yeah, I'd love a good barbecue.
How about we do it in my
back yard by the pool?
Love it! Let's do this!
- Yeah!
- Okay!
Come on.
No work.
Ah, now this is more like it.
What has gotten into you?
What? Can't I be
in a good mood?
No.
Fine. Today is a celebration.
Because Darren's
Basement has passed
over 10,000 followers
on social media,
which I'm told by Ms.
Karina is a good thing.
Yes! That is amazing!
- Sparkling cider?
- Oh, yes!
That is so fancy!
Ooh, the fanciest.
Thank you.
But that is not
the biggest news.
Spoke to my realtor today.
And as of tomorrow,
Darren's Basement is
officially off the market.
Wait. You're not selling?
I'm not selling.
You're not selling!
[laughing]
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Woo-hoo!
Okay, wait.
I have also something special
that I've been
waiting for these,
but I can't think of anything
more special than this.
Ta-da!
More muffins.
Uh-oh.
You guys are really mean.
Look. They're not
crumbly like last time.
Yeah. I mean, these kind
of actually look edible.
Yes, edible.
Progress, all right?
I feel like it's almost there.
Almost, but I really
wanna stick the landing.
Well, maybe we need to test
it somewhere, you know.
It'll help us feel
what's missing.
What? Like an open mic?
Something a little
more intimate.
Presenting...
A work in progress
by Ivy Rose...
- And Karina.
- Oh.
Yeah!
Okay. Don't laugh.
I would never.
Know what? This
doesn't feel right.
You have to play with me.
- What? Me?
- Mm-hm.
- No.
- Yeah, you helped me write it.
So you have to play.
I need your harmonies.
Well, I...
I have stage fright.
What? You?
No way.
Yes, way.
See? Yep.
I talk a big game.
But once I'm onstage,
I just freeze.
You know what?
I used to have
stage fright, too.
So how'd you overcome it?
Time, experience
and it really helped me to
play with my best friend, Sage.
I keep trying to tell
her it'll get better.
Yeah, but what do you
know? You're a boy.
I'm Ivy Rose.
So, what do you say?
Wanna play with me?
Well, I'll give it a shot.
All right, come on.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah.
♪ Thirty nights
♪ Camera lights
catching silly flights ♪
♪ And endless streams
of promotions ♪
♪ The days were always blurred
♪ My voice was never heard
♪ And I'd just been going
through the motions ♪
♪ And I saw you
♪ Mumbling every word like
you'd never heard them before ♪
♪ But I knew you saw me
♪ Like you really see me
♪ And I realized that I
wanted something more ♪
♪ Is this the start
of something new ♪
♪ Have all my
struggles lead to you ♪
♪ In this quiet lonely town
♪ Have I really found
♪ My voice again
♪ Now my heart can mend
♪ I'm beginning to understand
♪ Myself again
♪ A runaway pop star
♪ A grump with a record store
♪ A quiet place
to find myself ♪
♪ Who could ask for more?
♪ A new friend to sing along
♪ Call me out when I am wrong
♪ And help me write all
sorts of brand new songs ♪
♪ Oh, I'm finding it
♪ Easier to be myself
♪ When you are near
♪ Oh I'm smiling
more frequently ♪
♪ Knowing that I am here
♪ Knowing if I speak
someone will hear ♪
Wow!
That was... You're right.
That felt pretty good.
Any notes?
[phone rings]
Mr. Howard?
To what do I owe this pleasure?
Ooh, so formal.
I just called to see
if maybe you wanted
to go to dinner tonight?
Oh, is another burger
picnic calling your name?
I was thinking of something
a little more indoors.
Feeling good.
Oh, that place, that Chez Maman?
Is this revenge for the muffins?
Hey, you do know there are
food options in Deer Falls
that fall somewhere between the
burger joint and Chez Maman?
Oh, this place is downright
cosmopolitan then.
Oh, yeah. True center
of high art and culture.
Pick you up at seven?
Yes, I will be ready.
It's a date.
[sighs]
Whoa.
Becker?
What are you doing here?
Look, look.
I was just worried about you.
Okay, well, I'm fine, so
there's nothing to worry about.
How did you find me anyway?
I saw a picture of
you on social media.
You can change your hair, but
I would know you anywhere.
Okay. So now you found me.
What do you want?
Why are you so hostile?
I thought you'd be
happy to see me.
Okay. One, we broke up.
Two, you humiliated me twice.
Okay, okay.
Look, I wanted to talk.
Talk about what?
I wanted to apologize
for everything.
The fake proposal, ambushing
you at the concert,
all of it. I was wrong.
I appreciate that.
Come home, Ivy.
Beck, I can't.
You deserve to be with
someone who's just as excited
about you as you are them...
and someone who loves pranks.
This is really not
how I saw this going.
I'm sorry, but it's really
the best for both of us.
I respect your decision
and the least I can do
is accept that it's over.
Third time's a charm, I guess.
Thanks, Beck.
Take care of yourself, Ivy Rose.
See, when you said you were
gonna pick me up at seven,
I didn't exactly
expect to be stood up.
Yeah, well, you seemed
otherwise engaged
so I figured I'd give
you your privacy.
What are you talking about?
I saw you and Becker
outside your house, Ivy.
Oh, my.
Darren, it...
It's really not
what it looked like.
It doesn't matter what it was.
What does matter is
what it made me realize.
And what's that?
That it was crazy
for me to think that
there was a world in
which you stay here.
What are you talking about?
I just told you
I wanted to stay.
Yeah, and it seemed impulsive!
You weren't thinking
about the future.
What's to stop you from
making another decision
to just run away again?
I would hope that you would
know me better than that.
I don't know what I know.
Come on, it's time for
both of us to admit
that this was nothing more
than a vacation for you.
That's not what this was!
Of course, it was!
And that's okay!
You're allowed to have a
vacation from your life!
This isn't a vacation for me.
Okay, this is my life.
Darren, you have no idea
what these past few
weeks have meant to me.
They meant a lot to
me too, believe me.
I've been falling for Jamie...
but you're not Jamie.
You're Ivy.
So what are you saying?
I'm taking the offer, Ivy.
I'm selling the store.
Wait! I just... I
don't understand!
You're always talking
about not selling out
but that is exactly
what you're doing.
Yeah, cause I was
being an idiot!
You said it yourself!
It's a miracle anyone walks
into a record store these days.
And I can't keep
counting on miracles.
That is not what
I meant by that.
I need to focus on a
future I can count on.
I don't think you should
come by the store anymore.
Goodbye, Ivy.
Darren?
[knocking]
Come in!
Ivy, I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Oh, thank goodness.
I saw a picture of
you in some outfit
and I thought you'd
lost your mind.
Well, looks like you still
have some sense in you.
Great. As if this day
couldn't get any worse.
Hey, is that any way to
greet your loyal manager?
I've been so worried about you.
Well, there's clearly
nothing to worry about.
I'm fine.
Running off in the
middle of the night?
No calls, no texts?
I wouldn't call that fine.
Listen, if there's something
that I've done wrong...
I told you that I
wanted more control
over my career, over my life.
You're right, and I
owe you an apology.
It's just that I always
want the best for you.
And this business does take
a certain amount of hustle.
I know what hustle is, Naomi.
I know you do.
Listen, we can work things out.
We just have to
reevaluate your schedule
and find a way that you can
have a life on top of the life.
- You mean it?
- Of course I do.
Now there's a world
of people out there
who miss you very much.
Your people, Ivy.
So can we get out of here now
and have things
get back to normal?
Yeah.
Guess I'm not
wanted here anyway.
Attagirl.
- Oh...
- Hi.
Can I help you?
Um, yeah... sorry.
I'm looking for my
friend, uh... Jamie.
She lives here.
Jamie, yeah. I'm Addison.
I'm the owner of
this vacation rental.
Yes, she checked
out early in a rush.
I'm not sure what happened.
Oh... uh... okay.
Sorry to bother you.
Wait!
You wouldn't happen to
be Karina, would you?
Yeah, that's me.
I think I have something
for you, something she left.
Oh.
There you go.
Thank you.
Yeah.
"To the most talented,
"refreshingly honest
lyricist I know.
"Thanks for trying to help
me connect with myself again.
"Take care of this for me.
Jamie."
Darren, what happened with Ivy?
She won't be coming
by the store anymore.
Well, yeah. That
much is obvious.
She left town.
Well, we knew that
would happen eventually.
Listen to you!
Are you even gonna miss her?
Karina, of course I am.
I'm gonna miss her a lot.
Then why let her leave?
It's called being realistic.
Just because you want something
doesn't mean you get it.
I mean, sure, yeah,
these last couple of
weeks were a lot of fun.
- Fun?
- Yeah, fun.
But Ivy needed to go for
a sure thing, and so do I.
So that's it, then?
You're just gonna sell the
store and call it quits.
I'm not calling it quits.
I'm moving on with my life.
Don't worry.
I'm sure there'll
be a job for you
at the new pop-up with a much
younger, hipper crowd too.
No! I don't wanna work there!
I wanna work here at a real
record store with you and Ivy!
- Ivy's gone, Karina.
- And you let her go!
Darren, I saw a different
you ever since Ivy showed up.
You were in a better mood.
The store was doing
better than ever.
And you were letting good
things into your life.
Yeah, I know.
But then you always fall back
on this idea of responsibility.
You always have to have a
backup plan or a safety net.
It's called being
an adult, Karina!
The good things that happened
to you only happened to you
because you took a chance.
She left this for you.
"Thanks for helping me find
exactly what I was looking for.
"Sorry I didn't get
to say so in person.
Jamie."
[cheering]
Okay, these fans have
been waiting hours
for a chance to get to meet you.
So remember, big smiles,
make eye contact.
Sign a few albums and you
make them feel special.
Yeah. You've got it.
I am so glad things are back
to normal, back in the swing.
Hey, what's going on?
Nothing. I'm fine.
You're not still thinking
about that boy, are you?
His name is Darren.
Oh, sorry. Darren.
Well, you don't have
to worry about him.
He's gonna be just fine.
What are you talking about?
Well, a little birdie told me
he was having money problems.
So I decided to take
care of those for him.
Wait. What?
Are you the one who's
buying the record store?
Am buying. The sale
is still pending.
But we do have a
verbal agreement.
He'd be an idiot to
pass up that much cash.
It's way above asking price.
But why would you do that?
It's an investment opportunity.
And it didn't hurt
that it eliminated...
certain distractions.
You did this on purpose to
get back at me for leaving.
Oh, don't be ridiculous, Ivy.
I didn't do this
to get back at you.
I did it to get you back.
It's a win-win situation
for everybody involved.
Oh, it's go time!
Remember, big smiles!
[crowd cheering]
[chanting] Ivy! Ivy! Ivy!
Jamie! Jamie!
Karina?
- Karina!
- Sorry, sorry.
What are you doing here?
Well, I came to get
my album signed. Duh!
But, no, you left
without saying goodbye.
Yeah, I did. I
screwed everything up.
I... I just needed
to leave town.
You didn't screw anything
up! Are you kidding me?
You made our lives
so much better!
You made my life better too.
And Darren misses you, you know.
- Really?
- He misses you a lot.
Is that why you came here?
Uh, sort of.
But, mostly, because you
didn't finish the song.
And it is bad luck
not to finish a song
on the instrument
you started it on.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
Just finish it.
Jamie needs to finish it.
It's not my song.
It's our song.
And I can't finish
it without you.
So, here, take this.
Get in. Get in the car.
Ivy!
What is this? Where
are you going?
You don't have to
worry about it anymore.
You can't just take the limo!
Why can't I? I paid
for it, didn't I?
Ivy, why are you doing this?
Because I make my own
decisions now, okay?
And, Naomi, you're fired!
Driver? Take us to Deer Falls!
[Radio] More bizarre behavior
from pop star, Ivy Rose,
who left last
night's album signing
without even making
it in the door.
Double cheeseburger, cheesy
fries and a cola, right?
It's really good
to see you, Ivy.
Thank goodness. I thought
you were going to be mad.
No.
Look, what happened
to you wasn't fair.
I came in here and I forced
my way into your life
because I wasn't
happy with my own.
I'm really glad you did.
It was fun and unpredictable
and it gave me hope.
I think that I was just
so used to being let down
that I just panicked and
snapped myself out of it.
I get it. I really do.
And I am ready to do everything
that I can not to let you down.
You won't have to do that.
I want to.
For starters, I fired
my manager, Naomi.
- What?
- Yeah.
It turns out she was the one
that was buying your store.
Yet another way I was
screwing up your life.
I can't let you sell
the store, Darren.
Look, I know it can be scary,
but that's the amazing
thing about taking chances.
Like you said, the store,
it's a part of you.
It's time to stop giving
pieces of ourselves away
to people who
don't deserve them.
You're right.
I have made three very impulsive
decisions as of late, but...
all of them have led
me straight to you.
Oh, when you say it like that,
it sounds downright consistent.
But nothing about what I'm
about to say is impulsive.
Darren...
I want to be here... with you.
I want you to be here with me.
That's even better
than our first kiss.
If that was even possible.
♪ Thirty nights
♪ Camera lights
catching silly flights ♪
♪ Endless streams
of promotions ♪
♪ The days were always blurred
♪ My voice was never heard
♪ And I'd just been going
through the motions ♪
♪ When I saw you
♪ Mumbling every word like
you'd never heard them before ♪
♪ But I knew you saw me
♪ Like you really see me
♪ And I realized that I
wanted something more ♪
♪ Is this the start
of something new ♪
♪ Have all my
struggles lead to you ♪
♪ In this quiet lonely town
♪ Have I really found
♪ My voice again
♪ Now my heart can mend
♪ I'm beginning to understand
♪ Myself again