THAT'S A
BEAUTIFUL ANIMAL.
AN APPALOOSA.
HUMMM.
COSMO'S GREAT!!
YEAH?
YEAH.
ME AND MY OLD GIRLFRIEND
USED TO FIGHT OVER
WHO TOOK
THE QUIZ FIRST.
WILL THERE BE
ANYTHING ELSE?
YEAH,
SOME GUM.
DON'T MOVE!
RICHARD CHILTON.
YOU HAVE A BIRTHDAY
IN A FEW MONTHS.
DOESN'T EVERYBODY?
YOU'LL BE 18
IN AUGUST.
YOU'RE ALMOST TOO
OLD FOR JUVIE HALL.
WHERE I'M HEADED
MAKES JUVIE LOOK LIKE
A WALK IN THE PARK.
I'VE HEARD IT.
I HOPE YOU NEVER
HAVE TO SEE IT.
CHILTON,
NO SIESTAS
ON MY TIME.
I GREW UP
ON A RANCH.
MY OLD MAN WAS
A HORSE TRAINER.
I KNOW MORE ABOUT HORSES
THAN I DO ABOUT PEOPLE.
I KNOW HOW TO
GIVE THEM SHOTS,
SHOE 'EM,
BREAK 'EM.
LET'S TALK ABOUT
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN
DOING RECENTLY.
YOU'VE RUN AWAY
FROM 3 FOSTER HOMES,
YOU HAVE 4 COUNTS
OF VANDALISM,
AND NOW, THIS
CONVENIENCE STORE FIASCO.
THE WORK
RELEASE PROGRAM
IS FOR SOMEONE WHO'S
PROVEN THEMSELVES RESPONSIBLE.
THAT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE YOU, DOES IT?
I JUST WANT
A CHANCE.
WHY?
SO YOU CAN
GET TO KIDDIE
CAMP AND BAIL?
ALL RIGHT.
NICE TRY....,
FOR AN OLD GUY.
YOU'RE A SHRINK.
SHOULDN'T YOU SAY,
"MATURITY CHALLENGED?"
I'M POLITICALLY INCORRECT
AND PROUD OF IT.
YEAH.
COME ON,
LET'S WARM THE BENCH.
HEY.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
I'M DOING FINE, ANNIE,
HOW ARE YOU?
AH, WELL,
I'M IN TROUBLE.
I NEED
A NEW STABLE HAND.
WHAT ABOUT
THAT WORK RELEASE PROGRAM?
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE
SOMEBODY FOR ME.
WELL, THERE
IS ONE KID...
YEAH...
BUT, HE'S
NOT RIGHT.
TWENTY MINUTES
AT YOUR CAMP
AND HE'D HIT
THE PAVEMENT.
YOU CAN'T SAY THAT
AND I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
KIDS LIVE UP
TO THE EXPECTATIONS
OTHER PEOPLE
HAVE OF THEM.
HERE IT COMES.
HOW IS HE EVER
GOING TO MAKE A DECENT
LIFE FOR HIMSELF
IF YOU TELL HIM
HE DOESN'T DESERVE ONE?
YOUR POLITICAL INCORRECTNESS
IS FADING.
DOES HE HAVE
EXPERIENCE WITH HORSES?
YEAH.
OH,
COME ON, THEN.
BUT, YOU DON'T
WANT THIS GUY
AROUND YOUR KIDS.
WE'LL HIRE HIM
ON A TRIAL BASIS.
IF HE SCREWS UP,
HE'S OUTTA THERE.
THE UNSINKABLE IDEALIST.
INSTEAD OF TEARING
PEOPLE DOWN,
TRY TO BUILD
THEM UP.
IT GETS
BETTER RESULTS.
ALL RIGHT,
LETS GO OVER THE RULES.
RULE NUMBER ONE:
[ mumbles ]
WHAT?
NO DRINKING.
RULE NUMBER TWO:
NO SMOKING.
RULE NUMBER THREE:
NO LEAVING CAMP
WITHOUT PERMISSION.
WHAT HAPPENS ONCE A WEEK?
DINNER AND A MOVIE?
WEEKLY REVIEW.
[ horse whinnies ]
EXCELLENT!
COOL SHADES, MAN.
CAN I TRY THEM ON?
SUNLIGHT HURTS
HIS EYES, SOMETIMES.
AHH,
TIED ONE ON LAST NIGHT?
I UNDERSTAND.
ANNIE, HI.
HEY!
MEET THE NEW
STABLE HAND.
HI.
I'M ANNIE.
IT'S GREAT
TO HAVE YOU HERE.
THANKS.
THIS IS
THE NEW STABLE HAND?
ONE OF
YOUR GUYS?
YEAH.
RICK CHILTON,
THIS IS CLAY NELSON.
CLAY'S OUR
HEAD COUNSELOR.
RICK GREW
UP ON HORSES.
HIS DAD
WAS A TRAINER.
REALLY? FOR WHOM?
THESE KIDS HERE...
THEY'RE ALL...
THEY'RE ALL BLIND.
THANKS
FOR TELLING HIM.
[ bell rings ]
THAT'S LUNCH.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
GOOD LUCK.
I GOTTA GET GOING, TOO.
I'LL SEE YOU IN A WEEK,
WON'T I?
SURE THING,
MACK.
BYE, MACK.
BYE.
COME ON,
I'LL SHOW YOU
WHERE YOU'LL STAY.
DOING GOOD, STEPH!
WHAT IS THAT,
A METAL DETECTOR?
THAT'S WHAT
IT LOOKS LIKE.
THAT IS A
MOWACS SENSOR.
IT PUTS OUT SOUND ULTRA WAVES,
THEY BOUNCE OFF OBJECTS,
AND THE SENSOR VIBRATES.
SORTA LIKE
AN UPDATED VERSION
OF THE WALKING CANE.
EXACTLY.
WE WANT THE KIDS
TO BE AS INDEPENDENT
AND UP TO DATE
AS POSSIBLE.
OUR TACK SEEMS
TO HAVE DISAPPEARED
INTO THE LAND OF LOST SOCKS,
BUT, FORTUNATELY
WE'LL BE GETTING MORE
FROM THE MORRIS
RANCH SOON.
OKAY,
HERE'S
WHERE YOU'LL STAY.
LINENS ARE IN THE CLOSET
YOUR BATHROOM IS
ALL THE WAY DOWNSTAIRS. SORRY.
IT'S NOT THE RITZ
BUT...
NO, IT'S GREAT.
I HAVEN'T HAD MY OWN ROOM
SINCE I WAS A KID.
WELL,
I'LL LET YOU SETTLE IN.
DON'T YOU WANT ME
TO RECITE THE RULES
OR SOMETHING?
I'D RATHER
SEE YOU FOLLOW THEM.
CONSIDER THEM FOLLOWED.
[ music playing ]
[ horse galloping ]
UHHHH!
I'M RIGHT HERE,
LILLIAN.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
PUT HIM DOWN.
SHE SLIPPED THE STIRRUP,
MR. MORRIS, THAT'S ALL.
I SAID
PUT HIM DOWN.
AND DO IT
BEFORE I GET BACK!
CAL, WOULD YOU PLEASE
FIND SOMETHING TO DO?
BUSTER!
I PUT GHOST IN THE BACK,
MR. MORRIS.
I THOUGHT YOU NEEDED
A FEW DAYS TO COOL OFF.
FROM NOW ON,
I'LL DEAL
WITH THAT HORSE.
[ car pulls up ]
IT'S BEAUTIFUL HERE.
GET OUT
AND SMELL THE AIR.
I CAN SMELL FINE
FROM IN HERE.
LINDSAY,
GET OUT OF THE CAR.
I DON'T WANT
TO GO.
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO SIT AND MOPE
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
IT'S MY LIFE.
LINDSAY, THIS CAMP
HAS THE BEST MOBILITY
TRAINING AROUND.
THAT'S SWELL, MOM.
I HOPE YOU HAVE
A REALLY GREAT TIME.
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T
PUSH HER.
THEN SHE'LL NEVER
LEARN TO COPE.
IS THAT
WHAT YOU WANT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LET GO OF ME!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
HEY, SAY HELLO
TO LINDSAY KURTZ, EVERYONE.
[ Together: ]
HI, LINDSAY.
YOU CAN SIT
RIGHT HERE.
YOUR MILK'S
AT TEN O'CLOCK.
BILLY, YOU'RE
REALLY BECOMING A WHIZ
AT THAT OPTICON.
THAT WHAT?
BILLY'S OPTICON.
IT'S A READING DEVICE.
WHEN BILLY'S PASSES
THE OPTICON OVER PAGES,
IT TRANSPOSES THE WORDS
ONTO A RUBBER PAD.
THEN HE READS
THE RAISED LETTERS
LIKE BRAILLE.
OH.
NOW,
IF WE COULD GET HIM
TO TALK TO US SOMEDAY
INSTEAD OF HIDING
BEHIND THAT OPTICON.
OH! I'M SORRY.
LINDSAY, IT'S OKAY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT HAPPENS
ALL THE TIME.
WHY DON'T YOU
GET SPILL PROOF GLASSES?
BECAUSE YOU HAVE
TO LEARN TO GET ALONG
IN THE REAL WORLD.
WE'RE COMING UP
ON THE CORRAL...
...ASPEN TREES
IN THE DISTANCE,
AND THIS IS OUR
STABLE MANAGER, RICK.
RICK,
THIS IS LINDSAY.
HELLO, LINDSAY.
IT SMELLS HERE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU DON'T
LIKE "ODE DE APPALOOSA?"
COME ON.
SEE YA.
THESE ARE THE DIRECTIONS
TO CAL MORRIS' RANCH.
HE'S DONATING SOME TACK.
WHEN YOU GET THERE,
ASK FOR BUSTER.
HE'S EXPECTING YOU.
YOU CAN LOAD
IT UP IN THE BACK.
[ horse whinnies ]
WHAT THE...
HEY, THERE!
YOU THE BOY
FROM THE BLIND CAMP?
YEAH, YOU THE OWNER?
I'M THE CARETAKER.
BUSTER HIGGINS.
WHO DID
THIS TO HIM?
MRS. MORRIS WAS
RIDING GHOST TOO
HARD AND FELL.
SHE WAS HURT PRETTY BAD.
SO, MR. MORRIS
STUCK HIM IN HERE
TO STARVE
HIM TO DEATH?
IF HE WEREN'T
SUCH A GENTLEMAN,
HE WOULD HAVE KICKED
HIS WAY OUT OF HIS STALL
A LONG TIME AGO.
WELL, BETTER
LOAD UP THIS TACK.
YOU GONNA HELP ME
WITH THIS?
OH,
YEAH.
I THINK YOU
GOT EVERYTHING.
OKAY, THANKS.
YOU KNOW,
MAYBE GHOST ISN'T AS MUCH
OF A GENTLEMAN, AS YOU THINK.
I GUESS IT'S POSSIBLE
GHOST COULD ESCAPE.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GET YOU CLEANED UP.
RICK?
HE...,HE....
CAME WITH THE TACK.
CAL IS GIVING
US THIS HORSE?
YEAH, YOU CAN SEE
THE CONDITION HE'S IN.
THE ONLY THING
HE'S GOOD FOR
IS RIDING KIDS
IN THE CORRAL.
CAN HE EVEN DO THAT?
IN A COUPLE WEEKS,
GHOST WILL BE AS GOOD AS NEW.
GOOD WORK.
HEY, YOU CAN'T SNEAK UP
ON HORSES LIKE THAT.
YOU'RE GONNA SPOOK 'EM.
HEY, HEY, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO LEAVE.
YOU WANNA PET
THE NEW HORSE?
áá
OKAY.
COME OVER HERE.
WALK SLOWLY.
BE CAREFUL.
STEP DOWN HERE.
WALK UP TO HIM, SLOW.
STICK YOUR HAND OUT
AND TOUCH HIM.
LET HIM KNOW
YOU'RE THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
LET ME SEE
YOUR HAND.
STICK IT OUT.
I'M GONNA LET
YOU FEED HIM.
THAT SPECIAL MIX
IS PUTTING MEAT
ON HIS BONES.
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU DON'T LIKE
BEING A COWBOY?
HORSES ARE FUN
TO RIDE.
YOU USE YOUR HANDS
AND KNEES AND LEGS
TO TELL THEM
WHERE TO GO.
BILLY, YOU CAN'T
LEAVE THE GROUP
LIKE THAT.
LISTEN, WE NEED 5 HORSES
TACKED UP BY THIS AFTERNOON.
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
HANDLE THAT?
YEAH.
MAYBE THE KIDS
WOULD WANT TO
LEARN TO TACK UP.
I COULD TEACH THEM.
I DON'T THINK
THAT WOULD BE
SUCH A GOOD IDEA,
CONSIDERING...
WHAT, I MIGHT RUB
OFF ON THEM?
TEN MINUTES WITH ME
AND THEY'RE GONNA BE
STEALING CARS, HUH?
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT
WAS YOUR SPECIALTY,
GRAND THEFT.
COME ON, BILLY.
GRAB A HOLD.
THAT A BOY.
JUST HAVE THEM
READY, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
HOP ON DOWN.
...A STEP HERE.
[ Mimicking: ]
JUST HAVE THEM READY, OKAY?
♪♪
[ Knocking ]
YEAH.
YEAH?
HI!
THAT'S FOR BLOWING
ME AND JOEY OFF.
HOW'D YOU
GET IN HERE?
I DROVE,
HOW DO YOU THINK?
IT'S NOT LIKE
THERE ARE A LOT OF EYE
WITNESSES AROUND HERE.
LET'S SEE.
OH, NASTY!
SORRY,
I HAD TO GET THAT
OUT OF MY SYSTEM.
I HOPE YOU
FEEL BETTER.
SO, HOW'S JOEY?
OH, MAN.
IS HE...
THEY DIDN'T TELL YOU?
WHAT?
PSYCH...
HE'S FINE.
WHEN HE GETS BETTER-
HE HAS TO GO TO JUVIE
BUT I'M GOING
TO SPRING HIM OUT.
HOW YOU GONNA
DO THAT?
I GOT MY SOURCES.
YEAH, YOU AND
YOUR MANY FRIENDS.
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOUR PROBLEM IS?
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW
TO PROPERLY MAINTAIN
YOUR FRIENDSHIPS.
LISTEN,
I'M GOING TO BE 18
IN A COUPLE MONTHS.
IF I DON'T WORK
OUT HERE,
THEY'RE GOING TO SEND ME
TO THE BIG HOUSE.
IT AIN'T GOING
TO HAPPEN, MAN
'CUZ JOEY AND I
ARE GONNA GET YOU
OUTTA HERE.
REALLY, MAN?
DUDE...
I OWE YOU ONE.
YEAH,
YOU DO.
I'M TELLING YOU,
HE'S CHANGED.
HE'S A LITTLE CON MAN.
LOOK AT THIS.
THIS PLACE WAS
A DISASTER BEFORE
HE GOT HERE.
COME ON.
HEY, MACK!
RICK.
COULD YOU HAND ME
THAT OTHER SNAP?
THIS?
YEAH, PUT IT
ON HIS HALTER.
COME ON,
HE'S NOT GOING
TO HURT YOU.
HE'S GENTLE
AS A LAMB.
A BIG LAMB.
YOU SHOULD
HAVE SEEN THIS GUY
A FEW WEEKS AGO.
RICK'S NURSED HIM
BACK TO HEALTH.
YEAH?
HE'S READY TO RIDE.
HE'S REALLY GENTLE.
HE'D BE PERFECT
FOR THE MORE TIMID KIDS,
LIKE BILLY.
I THINK YOU'D
MAKE A GOOD TEACHER.
A TEACHER?
WE NEED TO BREAK UP
THE RIDING GROUPS.
CLAY COULD TAKE OUT
THE MORE ADVANCED KIDS
AND YOU COULD WORK
WITH THE LESS CONFIDENT ONES.
I'VE NEVER REALLY
TAUGHT BEFORE.
ANNIE,
COULD I SPEAK TO YOU
A MINUTE, PLEASE.
RICK IS NOT
LIKE YOUR KIDS.
OH, REALLY?
HE'S ALIENATED,
HE HAS NO SELF ESTEEM,
HE MISSED THE ADVANTAGES
THAT NORMAL KIDS HAD.
HE CAN'T HANDLE
THAT KIND OF RESPONSIBILITY.
THAT'S FUNNY.
PEOPLE SAY
THAT SAME THING
ABOUT THE BLIND.
ALL RIGHT BILLY,
THIS IS THE LAST STEP.
PUT YOUR LEFT FOOT
THROUGH THE STIRRUP.
THERE YOU GO--
JUST LIKE THAT!
SWING YOUR
RIGHT ONE OVER.
ALL RIGHT COWBOY,
GET YOU RIDIN'.
STAY HERE AND PET GHOST
LIKE I SHOWED YOU.
I'LL GO DOWN
AND PUT LINDSAY
ON HER HORSE.
WOW LINDSAY,
YOU LOOK LIKE A RIDER.
WEAR BOOTS
NEXT TIME.
I'M NOT RIDING.
I ONLY CAME
BECAUSE ANNIE MADE ME.
RIDE WITH US,
LINDSAY, IT'S EASY.
BILLY DID IT,
HE'S NOT SCARED.
I'M NOT SCARED.
I'M JUST A LITTLE OLD
FOR YOUR PONY RIDES.
AT LEAST TALK
TO YOUR HORSE.
WILL YOU GIVE IT UP!
WOULD YOU GET
IN THE SADDLE?
DON'T PUSH ME!
FINE. DO
WHAT YOU WANT.
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR SPOILED BRATS.
ALL RIGHT
GUYS, COME ON.
WE'RE GOING
DOWN BY THE CREEK.
BRING IT FORWARD.
ALL RIGHT.
LOOKING AWFUL
SERIOUS, COWBOY.
YOU DOING OKAY?
GOOD, WE'RE HERE
TO HAVE SOME FUN.
SIT UP STRAIGHT
IN YOUR SADDLE.
HOLD YOUR PALOMINO'S
HEAD UP.
OKAY.
OH, WHOA,
HOLD UP EVERYBODY.
YES, TIM?
WHAT COLOR
IS MY HORSE?
WELL, HE'S A BUCKSKIN.
SO HE'S BROWN WITH
A BLACK MANE AND TAIL.
WHAT'S BROWN LIKE?
BROWN?
UH,..
BROWN IS...
AHHH...
GOOD RIDIN',
BILLY.
COOL OFF, BOY.
WHAT'S GOTTEN
INTO HIM?
THIS HORSE
IS GOING CRAZY.
WOW, HE'S ON
HIS HIND LEGS.
BEAUTIFUL!
WHOA, GHOST
JUST CLEARED
FIVE FEET EASY!
BILLY, WE'VE
GOT OURSELVES
A JUMPER.
HEY, STABLE BOY!
ANNIE WOULD LIKE TO SEE
YOU IN HER OFFICE.
PRONTO!
[ Knocking ]
COME IN.
HI.
I GOT A PHONE CALL
FROM LINDSAY'S FATHER.
HE SAID YOU CALLED
HER A SPOILED BRAT
AND TRIED TO
FORCE HER TO RIDE.
[ Sigh ]
YOU WANT TO TELL ME
YOUR SIDE OF THE STORY?
SHE WAS THROWING
A TANTRUM.
SHE WOULDN'T
GET IN THE SADDLE.
SHE IS A SPOILED BRAT!
SIT DOWN.
I WANT TO SHOW
YOU SOMETHING.
[ Announcer: ]
We're in the final rotation.
This is Lindsay Kurtz.
THAT'S LINDSAY!
...here at the national
qualifying meet.
This is an excellent
event for Lindsay.
[ Annie: ]
SHE WAS RANKED
NUMBER ONE GOING
INTO THE REGIONALS.
THIS VIDEO WAS SHOT
DURING THE PRE-OLYMPIC TRIALS.
She's upgraded
the level of difficulty...
Here's her most difficult
pass...beautifully done.
NOT BAD.
All she needs to do is
stick the dismount
and she can qualify for
the national championship.
This is a
new dismount for her.
Very difficult.
A round-off double twist.
OH, MY.
Oh...she was way off
from the end of the beam.
Oh, that's a terrible fall.
We can only hope she's okay.
Look how far she
is off the end of the beam
and yet she hit...
THAT'S HOW
SHE BECAME BLIND?
FLASH PHOTOS
AREN'T ALLOWED
AT GYMNASTIC EVENTS.
BUT, SOMETIMES PEOPLE
DON'T FOLLOW THE RULES.
SHE GOT DISTRACTED
AND SHE FELL.
I JUST FIGURED
SHE HAD BEEN BLIND
HER WHOLE LIFE.
ONLY A FEW MONTHS.
THE OTHER KIDS
HAVE HAD YEARS
TO WORK THROUGH THEIR
ANGER AND ADJUST.
LOOK, I KNOW THAT
WORKING WITH LINDSAY
REQUIRES A LOT
OF PATIENCE.
MAYBE YOU'LL DECIDE
SHE'S WORTH IT.
[ clapping ]
WHO'S THERE?
RICK.
HOW LONG HAVE
YOU BEEN WATCHING?
LONG ENOUGH TO
SEE THAT WHIRLY-JUMP-THING.
FULL TWISTING
BACK LAYOUT.
EXACTLY!
WHY ARE YOU
ALWAYS BACKING
AWAY FROM PEOPLE?
I DON'T.
YOU WERE CROWDING
MY SPACE.
THEN I WON'T
COME ANY CLOSER.
GOOD.
I'M GOING
TO BE HONEST.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO ACT
AROUND GIRLS LIKE YOU
....BEAUTIFUL, CLASSY.
I'M SORRY
WE GOT STARTED OFF
ON THE WRONG FOOT.
SOMETIMES I CAN BE
A LITTLE HOT HEADED.
I REALLY WANT
TO TEACH YOU TO RIDE.
I KNOW ABOUT
YOUR ACCIDENT.
I JUST WANT
TO HELP.
YOU WANT TO HELP?
YEAH.
HELP SOMEONE ELSE.
I WOULDN'T
GO RIDING WITH YOU
IF YOU PAID ME.
ON YOUR MARKS...
GET SET...GO!
GO BILLY!
WE'RE GONNA WIN!
YEAH!
[ Bell rings ]
RICK HAS REALLY
GOTTEN TO BILLY.
IT MUST BE ALL THAT RIDING
THEY'VE BEEN DOING.
YEAH, HE'S QUITE
SOME ROLE MODEL.
CLAY, WHAT'S
YOUR PROBLEM
WITH HIM, ANYWAY?
HE'S A CRIMINAL!
HE'S JUST
WALTZES IN HERE
AND ACTS LIKE HE
OWNS THE PLACE.
OH, HE GUESS
HE FORGOT THAT
WAS YOUR JOB.
I TOLD YA YOU
COULD BE A COWBOY.
YOU READY
TO CANTER?
KICK HIM FORWARD
WITH YOUR HEELS.
LOOKING GOOD.
HANDS HIGHER.
PARTNER, I WANT
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
SOMETHING, MAN TO MAN.
GOOD.
SEE, I THINK
LINDSAY'S PRETTY NEAT.
I WANT TO
TAKE HER RIDING
BUT SHE'S AFRAID
OF THESE HORSES.
I'LL NEVER
GET HER OUT TO THE
CORRAL BY MYSELF.
SHE MIGHT COME
IF YOU TAKE HER.
MAYBE BETWEEN
THE TWO OF US
WE CAN CONVINCE
HER TO RIDE.
TAKE YOU ON YOUR
OWN PERSONAL
TRAIL RIDE.
I PROMISE.
ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S MY MAN.
HORSES?
BILLY...,
I TOLD YOU,
I DON'T WANT TO RIDE.
WHY CAN'T
ANYBODY GET THAT.
COME ON, WHERE'S
YOUR SENSE OF ADVENTURE?
IT'S OKAY.
SHE'S JUST PLAYING
HARD TO GET.
LINDSAY,
IT'S BROOK.
I SUPPOSE YOU
WANT ME TO JOIN
IN SOMETHING, TOO.
DON'T WORRY,
NOT THE DREADED
GROUP ACTIVITY.
I JUST WISH
PEOPLE WOULDN'T
PUSH ME SO MUCH.
I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU MEAN.
AT SCHOOL, I USED TO
GET REALLY NERVOUS
TAKING EXAMS.
I WAS IN A PACKED
LECTURE HALL
WITH THE TEACHER
STARING RIGHT AT ME.
MY DAD SAID
TO PRETEND
I WAS THE ONLY
PERSON TAKING
THE TEST.
THAT NO ONE ELSE
WAS AROUND.
THAT WORKED?
IT SOUNDS STUPID,
BUT YEAH,
ACTUALLY IT DID.
IT TOOK THE
PRESSURE OFF.
LISTEN LINDSAY,
WE ALL COPE WITH
THINGS DIFFERENTLY.
I'LL FOLLOW
MY DAD'S ADVICE
AND LEAVE
YOU ALONE.
THANKS.
HELLO?
[ Wings beating ]
I THOUGHT
YOU DIDN'T LIKE
MY STUPID HORSE?
I JUST DON'T LIKE
TO BE FORCED TO DO
SOMETHING.
OBVIOUSLY.
LISTEN,
IF YOU WANT
TO RIDE,
NEXT TIME,
TELL ME,
ALTHOUGH YOU
MIGHT BE A LITTLE
ADVANCED FOR ME.
I STILL HAVE TO USE
SADDLE AND STIRRUPS.
HEY, WAIT!
AREN'T YOU GOING
TO HELP ME DOWN?
YOU DIDN'T NEED
ANY HELP GETTING UP.
[ Horse whinnies ]
WE'RE JUST GOING
ON A TRAIL RIDE,
IT'S NOT SWAN LAKE.
[ Rick: ]
WHY'D YOU ACT LIKE
YOU'VE NEVER RIDDEN?
[ Lindsay: ]
BECAUSE THINGS THAT
USED TO BE FAMILIAR,
JUST AREN'T ANYMORE.
I FELT THE SAME WAY
WHEN MY DAD DIED.
I REMEMBER RIDING
MY BIKE INTO TOWN
AND NOT HAVING
A CLUE HOW
TO GET BACK.
I'VE NEVER
UNDERSTOOD THAT.
EVERYTHING HAD CHANGED.
YOU STILL KNEW
HOW TO GET
TO YOUR HOUSE.
YOU JUST DIDN'T
HAVE A "HOME" ANYMORE.
YEAH.
HI, LINDSAY.
HI, BROOK.
COME ON, GUYS.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING OUT HERE?
YOU WANT TO RIDE?
I WANT YOU
TO TEACH ME TO JUMP.
JUMP?
YOU MEAN
LIKE WITH HORSES?
YES!
WHAT?
STADIUM JUMPING?
LINDSAY, COME ON,
THOSE RIDERS HAVE HAD
YEARS OF EXPERIENCE.
SO HAVE I,
IN GYMNASTICS.
IT'S NOT
THE SAME.
THE SKILLS
ARE THE SAME.
YOU NEED BALANCE,
COORDINATION,
AGILITY...
AND SIGHT.
LINDSAY,
I NEVER EVEN HEARD OF
A BLIND RIDER COMPETING.
BESIDES, YOU DON'T
EVEN HAVE A JUMPER.
GHOST IS A JUMPER.
I HEARD YOU SAY
HE CLEARED 5 FEET, EASY.
YOU KNOW HOW
HIGH 5 FEET IS?
LINDSAY...,
YOU COULD
REALLY GET HURT.
I'VE ALREADY
BEEN HURT.
LOOK...,
I KNOW THAT
I'LL NEVER HAVE
MY OLD LIFE BACK
BUT I WANT SOMETHING
BETTER THAN THIS.
I JUST WANT YOU
TO GET THE FEEL
OF THE MOVEMENT.
[ Laughing ]
THIS IS EASY.
DON'T WORRY
IT GETS HARDER.
LOOKIN' GOOD!
LEAN IN,
HUG WITH YOUR KNEES.
GOOD, NICE!
LINDSAY, LOOKING GOOD!
HEELS DOWN,
LEAN FORWARD.
AHHH...
NOT THAT FAR
FORWARD.
AHH... IT'S
TOO MUDDY.
GHOST SLIPPED!
YOU LEANED TOO
FAR FORWARD.
YOU THREW HIM
OFF BALANCE.
GIVE ME
YOUR HAND.
AHHHH.
[ Laughing]
STAY IN YOUR CIRCLE.
COUNT YOUR
STRIDES.
THREE-TWO-ONE,
SQUEEZE AND JUMP.
I GUESS HE DIDN'T
WANT TO JUMP.
NO KIDDING!
LINDSAY, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO COME RIDING WITH US?
MAYBE LATER.
OKAY.
[ Whistle blows ]
COME ON BILLY,
FASTER, FASTER!
WAY TO GO,
IT'S A REALLY CLOSE RACE!
WE'RE ALMOST THERE!
COME ON BILLY!
THAT'S THE WAY TO PADDLE!
WE'RE ALMOST THERE!
GOOD JOB, BILLY!
HEY, YOU TRYING
TO GET ME BUSTED?
RIGHT, LIKE,
WHO'S GONNA SEE?
[ Bell rings ]
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
GOOD QUESTION,
NEVER MIND!
HEY, LOOK.
C'MON BLITZ,
YOU KNOW I'M
GLAD TO SEE YOU.
GOOD. COME PARTY
WITH US, TONIGHT.
I CAN'T.
MAN, WHAT
IS IT WITH YOU?
YOU LIKE HANGING
OUT WITH THE BLIND?
OH, EXCUSE ME,
"THE VISUALLY IMPAIRED."
GIVE IT A REST,
WILL YOU?
YOU KNOW
I'VE GOTTA LAY LOW
FOR A WHILE.
BESIDES, DO YOU EVEN
HAVE US A PLACE
TO STAY YET...
SOME JOBS MAYBE?
GOT A PROSPECT
ON THE EAST COAST.
I'M WORKING ON IT.
DON'T SCREW THIS UP.
[ Clay: ]
THE WINNER? BILLY!
[ Applause ]
WAY TO GO, BILLY!
WAY TO GO!
THAT LAST JUMP
FELT SO GREAT.
REALLY SMOOTH.
I THINK GHOST AND
I HAVE GOOD CHEMISTRY.
ARE YOU LOOKING
AT ME?
HOW CAN
YOU TELL?
I CAN FEEL
YOUR EYES ON ME.
THEY WERE.
WHAT WERE
YOU THINKING?
I WAS THINKING
ABOUT HOW MUCH YOUR
JUMPING HAS IMPROVED
AND THAT
WE SHOULD CELEBRATE.
A CLASSY GIRL
LIKE ME
OUT WITH A NEANDERTHAL
LIKE YOU?
WHAT DID YOU
HAVE IN MIND?
[ Knocking ]
YEAH!
WAS OUR TRAIL
RIDE TONIGHT?
CAN YOU KEEP
A BIG SECRET?
I'VE GOT
A DATE TONIGHT,
WITH LINDSAY.
OH, COME ON.
YOU KNOW HOW
HARD I'VE WORKED
TO WIN HER OVER.
YOU AND ME CAN GO
RIDING ANYTIME, OKAY?
PARTNER?
HEY, HOP IN.
RIGHT ON TIME.
WHAT DID YOU
SAY HER NAME WAS
AGAIN? LOU-LOU?
LOU-LOU?
NO, IT'S LINDSAY.
OH, RIGHT.
SORRY.
GET OUTTA HERE.
[ Music from inside ]
HEY, GUYS!
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
[ Loud music playing ]
IT SOUNDS
REALLY CROWDED IN HERE.
THAT'S BECAUSE IT IS.
WE'LL GET YOU OUT
ON THIS DANCE FLOOR.
I DON'T THINK SO.
HEY, DESPERADO,
WELCOME TO THE PARTY.
RICK, TOM HALLS.
HI.
WANT A DRINK?
NO, THANKS.
YOU SURE KNOW HOW
TO PICK 'EM.
SEE YOU LATER.
IS SHE BLIND?
YEAH...BE COOL.
YOU KNOW, I'M
A REALLY BIG FAN
OF STEVIE WONDER.
WHAT?
OUCH, WATCH IT!
I'M SORRY.
LINDSAY. LINDSAY!
I'M SO SORRY.
YOUR FRIEND IS...
SUCH A DIPLOMAT.
SCHAEF'S ALL RIGHT.
HE JUST DOESN'T
KNOW HOW TO ACT
AROUND GIRLS LIKE YOU.
YOU MEAN
A BLIND GIRL?
NO, I MEAN
A COOL GIRL.
HUMMM?...COME ON.
[ Horse whinnies ]
[ Slow music playing ]
♪ IN THE SKY ♪
♪ I SEE SOMETHIN' OPENIN' ♪
♪ AND THIS FEELIN' ♪
♪ FEELS FROM HEAVEN ♪
♪ TODAY... ♪
IT FEELS SO CRISP.
HERE'S MY JACKET.
THANKS.
CAN YOU
SEE ORION?
IS THAT
LIKE SCORPIO
OR SOMETHING?
RICK, YOU'RE NOT
SERIOUS, ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU
WANT FROM ME?
THEY ALL LOOK
THE SAME.
HERE,
LET'S SIT DOWN.
THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S BETTER.
LOOK UP
IN THE SKY.
OKAY?
ALL RIGHT,
I'M LOOKING.
ORION IS SHAPED
LIKE A WARRIOR.
THERE ARE TWO STARS
STRAIGHT ACROSS
FOR HIS SHOULDERS,
AND THREE
AT AN ANGLE
FOR HIS BELT,
AND TWO HANGING
FROM HIS BELT
FOR THE SWORD,
AND THEN TWO MORE
AT THE BOTTOM
FOR HIS FEET.
DO YOU SEEM THEM?
YEAH.
JUST LIKE YOU
DESCRIBED IT.
[ Horse whinnies ]
[ Owl hoots ]
YOU KNOW,
I'VE ONLY BEEN
BLIND 3 MONTHS
BUT I'VE ALREADY
STARTED TO FORGET
WHAT SOME THINGS
LOOK LIKE.
YOU REMEMBERED
ORION PRETTY GOOD.
YEAH, BUT WHEN I
WAS ON THE PHONE
WITH MY DAD,
I TRIED TO SEE
HIM IN MY MIND,
IT...
IT WAS LIKE LOOKING
AT A BLURRED PICTURE.
I TRIED TO MAKE
OUT HIS JAW LINE
AND HIS EYES,
BUT I COULDN'T.
MY OLD MAN WAS
REALLY STRICT.
MOST WEEKENDS HE MADE ME
MUCK OUT STABLES.
EXCEPT FOR
THIS ONE SUNDAY.
I MUST HAVE
BEEN BILLY'S AGE.
HE TOOK ME
TO THE TRACK.
WE SAT IN THE STANDS
AND ATE HOTDOGS.
MY DAD LOST MONEY,
BUT I WON.
I BET ON "YOUNG AND RESTLESS."
A 10:1 SHOT.
HE PUT ME
ON HIS SHOULDERS
AND STARTED YELLING
TO EVERYONE,
"MY BOY'S A WINNER,"
"MY BOY'S A WINNER!"
IT'S THE ONLY TIME
I REMEMBER HIM
BEING PROUD OF ME.
I THINK IF YOUR DAD
COULD SEE YOU NOW,
HE'D BE
PROUD OF YOU.
AFTER A GIRL SAYS
SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
HE SHOULD
PROBABLY KISS HER.
[ Horse whinnies ]
[ Wolf growls ]
[ Growling ]
[ Crying ]
I WILL DEAL
WITH YOU LATER.
RIGHT NOW
WE NEED YOUR HELP.
BILLY AND GHOST
ARE MISSING.
YEAH, OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
THANKS FOR THE HELP.
I'LL LET THEM KNOW.
THE SHERIFF'S ROUNDED
UP SOME RANCHERS.
THEY'RE SEARCHING
THE SOUTH SIDE
OF THE MOUNTAIN.
WE'LL FOLLOW THE
RIVER TO RED ROCK TRAIL.
I HAVE A HUNCH
THAT'S WHERE HE WENT.
BILLY WOULDN'T TAKE
THAT TRAIL BY HIMSELF.
LISTEN, I KNOW HIM
BETTER THAN YOU DO.
YEAH, WELL
THANKS TO YOU,
BILLY THINKS
HE'S JOHN WAYNE.
KNOCK IT OFF!
YOU TWO ARE WORKING
AS A TEAM NOW.
CLAY, I'M PUTTING
YOU IN CHARGE.
EVERYBODY FOLLOW ME.
MR. MORRIS?
NOT A THING THIS SIDE
OF INDIAN SUMMIT, CAL.
WE JUST COVERED THE
SYCAMORE GROVE SECTION.
NOTHING.
LET'S FAN OUT
ALONG DEER PASS.
WE'LL MEET BACK HERE
IN AN HOUR.
COME ON! YEAH!
[ Wolf howls ]
[ Steph: ]
LISTEN, IT SOUNDS
LIKE A WOLF
OR SOMETHING.
[ Lindsay: ]
BILLY'S HAS
GOTTA BE TERRIFIED
HEARING THESE
NOISES ALL ALONE.
OH, NO!
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S BILLY'S
COWBOY HAT.
WELL, WE KNOW
HE CAME THIS WAY.
WE GOTTA BE
CLOSING IN ON HIM.
[ Wolf howls ]
[ Birds chirping ]
BIRDS ARE UP.
IS IT DAWN ALREADY?
YEAH.
IT'S NOT
LOOKING GOOD.
WE'RE GONNA
FIND HIM!
YOUD BETTER
HOPE SO.
COME ON, COME ON.
[ Horse whinnies ]
AHHH!
LOOK YOU GUYS,
IT'S GHOST!
WHERE'S BILLY?
I DON'T SEE
HIM ANYWHERE.
HE'S GOTTA BE NEARBY.
TAKE THESE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OKAY.
BILLY!
BILLY, HANG ON!
BILLY STAY CALM.
YOU'RE
GONNA BE FINE.
JUST STAY CALM.
HERE,
WELL MAKE A LOOP.
WE CAN HOIST HIM UP.
HE CAN SLIP
OUT OF IT.
I'M CALLING THE
SHOTS HERE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
WE'RE TRYING
TO SAVE HIS LIFE.
HOLD ON
TO MY FEET.
BE CAREFUL!
ALL RIGHT BILLY.
GET ON
YOUR KNEES.
YOU'RE ON THE
EDGE OF A CLIFF.
REACH YOUR ARMS UP.
COME ON,
STRETCH AS HIGH
AS YOU CAN.
DON'T LEAN BACK!
AHHH.
CAN YOU
REACH HIM?
NO, I GOTTA SLIDE
OUT FARTHER.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS!
I HAVE TO!
[ Grunts ]
OKAY, COME
ON, BILLY.
STAND UP,
DON'T STEP BACK.
COME ON PARTNER,
I'M NOT GOING
TO LET YOU GO.
PLEASE, BILLY!
[ Cries ]
[ Clay: ]
REACH FOR
HIS HANDS BILLY.
HIS VOICE.
WE GOT YOU,
RICK.
HOLD ON AS TIGHT
AT YOU CAN.
WE GOT YOU.
WE'LL PULL
YOU BACK UP.
OKAY, HERE WE GO!
READY?
AHHHH!
[ Grunting ]
RICK, YOU
DID IT!
YOU OKAY,
BUDDY? HUH?
RICK?
YEAH, IT'S ME.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M OKAY.
HOW'S BILLY?
HE'S OKAY.
YOU DROPPED
SOMETHING, COWBOY.
LOOKS LIKE
BILLY'S TIRED
OF BEING A COWBOY.
BILLY, HONEY,
YOU SCARED US.
WHY DID YOU RUN
OFF LIKE THAT?
[ Clay: ]
COME ON, BROOK,
LET'S TAKE BILLY BACK.
COME ON. OKAY.
MY HORSE WILL
FOLLOW YOU.
GHOST IS
TOO TIRED.
WE'LL HAVE TO WALK
HIM BACK TO THE CAMP.
DON'T TAKE
TOO LONG.
ANNIE'S DYING
TO TALK TO YOU.
[ Rick: ]
SORRY ABOUT THIS.
WATCH YOUR STEP.
I'M GOING
TO SET YOU DOWN.
IS IT
BEHIND ME?
YEAH,
THERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S GOING
TO BE OKAY.
THAT'S A STUPID THING
TO SAY.
WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
HOW ABOUT,
"RICK, YOU'RE A LOSER,"
OR "RICK YOU'RE A.."
IT WASN'T
YOUR FAULT.
BILLY DECIDED
TO GO RIDING
ALL BY HIMSELF.
BECAUSE I DITCHED HIM
FOR YOU.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO
TAKE HIM RIDING,
LAST NIGHT.
THE DAY MY DAD
HAD A HEART ATTACK
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
CLEANING THE BARN.
TYPICAL RICK,
WENT AND PLAYED BALL.
FOUND HIM
IN THE STABLES
WITH HIS FACE DOWN
AND ARMS
STRETCHED OUT
LIKE HE WAS
GOING FOR HELP.
HE ALWAYS SAID
I COULDN'T
BE RELIED ON.
EVEN IF YOU'D
BEEN THERE,
WHO KNOWS IF YOU
COULD HAVE DONE ANYTHING.
THAT'S THE
WHOLE POINT.
I DON'T KNOW
AND I NEVER WILL
BECAUSE I
WASN'T THERE.
I DID THE SAME
THING WITH BILLY.
IF I WOULD HAVE
JUST TAKEN HIM
RIDING LAST NIGHT
NONE OF THIS
WOULD EVER HAPPENED.
IT'S DIFFERENT
THIS TIME.
BILLY'S OKAY
BECAUSE OF YOU.
I WISH ANNIE
BELIEVED THAT.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
THE MOST OBEDIENT,
DOCILE LITTLE BOY
TAKING OUT A HORSE
ALONE AT NIGHT.
IT'S JUST
NOT LIKE HIM.
I KNOW WHO
IT'S LIKE.
HAVE YOU CALLED
LINDSAY'S PARENTS?
HOW DO I EXPLAIN
THAT THE NICE
CRIMINAL I HIRED
SNUCK THEIR DAUGHTER OUT
FOR A MIDNIGHT TRYST?
DON'T SAY IT.
WHAT, DON'T SAY,
"I TOLD YOU SO?"
RIGHT!
[ Knocking ]
COME IN.
HEY, CAL.
EXCUSE ME.
I HEARD THE
BOY'S DOING OKAY.
YEAH,
AND SO IS GHOST...
THE HORSE YOU DONATED.
ANNIE, I NEVER
DONATED ANY HORSE.
OH, GREAT.
MR. MORRIS WOULD
LIKE HIS HORSE BACK.
BUT GHOST BELONGS
TO THE CAMP.
NO, HE DOESN'T.
MAYBE YOU COULD EXPLAIN
HOW GHOST GOT HERE, RICK.
WHAT ARE THEY
TALKING ABOUT?
WELL,
I TOOK HIM.
AND MADE IT LOOK
LIKE HE ESCAPED.
I HAD TO.
[ Clay: ]
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
GOSH JUDGE,
JUST SAW THAT
CHAMPIONSHIP HORSE
AND JUST HAD
TO HAVE HIM.
COME ON,
YOU ALL SAW WHAT
HE LOOKED LIKE
WHEN I BROUGHT HIM HERE.
MY WIFE PRACTICALLY
BROKE HER NECK
BECAUSE OF THAT HORSE.
YOU GOT A BUNCH
OF BLIND KIDS
RIDING ON HIM.
I'M ONE OF THEM
AND I CAN TELL YOU
GHOST WOULD
NEVER HURT ANYONE.
HE'S REALLY GREAT
WITH THE KIDS.
WELL, HE'S NOT
THEIR HORSE.
COME ON.
WHERE ARE
YOU TAKING HIM?
RICK?
RICK'S GOTTA GO BACK
TO JUVENILE HALL.
NO!
LINDSAY,
I'M SORRY.
ANNIE, LOOK.
OH, MY GOSH!
MACK.
MACK!
STOP! COME BACK!
WAIT!
YAAA! YAAA!
[ Gunshot ]
MACK, HOLD ON!
I'M TURNING
YOU IN!
FOR WHAT,
TRYING TO GET BACK
MY OWN HORSE?
HOW ABOUT ASSAULT
WITH A DEADLY WEAPON
ON A MINOR, NO LESS?
CAL, I'M SURE MACK
WOULD DROP THE CHARGES...
WHAT?
IF, YOU DONATE GHOST
TO THE CAMP.
RIGHT, MACK?
WHAT DO YOU SAY, CAL?
IS IT A DEAL?
[ Laughs ]
COME ON,
I'LL MAKE YOU
SOME OF MY FAMOUS
BANANA PANCAKES.
I'LL SETTLE FOR
A BUCKET OF ICE.
ANNIE,
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
AT LEAST YOU
SAVED GHOST.
PUT YOUR STUFF IN
THE BACK, RICK.
BILLY?
WHAT IS IT, SON?
HONEY, WHAT'S
GOING ON?
I GOTTA GO.
MACK,
MAYBE WE SHOULD
CHECK IT OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU WANT ME
TO JUST WAIT HERE?
OH, YEAH,
WHY DON'T I JUST
LEAVE YOU MY KEYS.
COME ON!
BILLY, I HOPE
YOU'RE NOT WASTING
MACK'S TIME.
WHAT'S THIS
ALL ABOUT?
MACK, ARE YOU HERE?
YEAH,
ANNIE TOO.
OH, GOOD.
I WANTED TO GIVE
YOU BOTH A PREVIEW.
THANKS TO RICK'S COACHING,
I'M READY TO COMPETE
IN THE STADIUM JUMPING
COMPETITION NEXT WEEK.
LINDSAY, WE SHOULD
TALK ABOUT THIS.
ACTUALLY, I'D PREFER
TO SHOW YOU.
WAIT A MINUTE,
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO LET HER DO THIS.
SHE CAN DO IT!
ANNIE!
MACK,
LET'S JUST...WATCH.
RICK TAUGHT ME
HOW TO PACE OFF
THE AREA BETWEEN JUMPS.
WHEN I HEAR
THESE LEAVES RUSTLING,
I KNOW
I HAVE 8 PACES
FROM THE FIRST TURN.
3, 2, 1...
SQUEEZE AND...
JUMP!
YEAH, BEAUTIFUL,
LINDSAY, BEAUTIFUL!
AGAIN!
3-2-1...
SQUEEZE...JUMP!
WHOA!
BEAUTIFUL,
LINDSAY!
WHOA!
YOU TAUGHT HER
TO DO THAT?
YEAH, BUT SHE'S
A NATURAL ATHLETE.
DON'T SELL
YOURSELF SHORT.
LINDSAY WAS
CATATONIC WHEN
SHE ARRIVED.
RICK WAS THE
ONLY ONE THAT GOT
THROUGH TO HER.
I NEED MY COACH
FOR THE COMPETITION, MACK.
CAN'T YOU LET HIM
STAY ON UNTIL THEN?
RICK KNEW THE RULES.
HE BROKE THEM.
HE'S NOT
A GOOD INFLUENCE.
SHE COULD NEVER
HAVE DONE THIS
WITHOUT HIM.
SURE SHE COULD.
YOU HEARD HIM,
HE SAID SHE'S A
NATURAL ATHLETE.
COME ON.
YOU CAN DO IT
WITHOUT ME.
YOU'LL BE GREAT,
LINDSAY.
DON'T GO!
PLEASE, MACK,
HE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
IF THAT'S NOT
A GOOD INFLUENCE,
I DON'T
KNOW WHAT IS.
WHAT IF HE COMES HERE
DURING THE DAY
JUST TO TRAIN LINDSAY
AND NOTHING ELSE?
ALL RIGHT.
BUT AS SOON AS THE
COMPETITION IS OVER
YOU GO BACK
TO JUVIE FULL TIME,
YOU GOT IT?
I GOT IT...
[ Rick: ]
THANKS MACK.
OH, MACK.
AND DON'T, "OH, MACK!"
PLEASE, ANNIE.
THANKS, PARTNER.
YOU'RE WELCOME...,
PARTNER.
LET'S GET LINDSAY.
COME ON, GIRL.
OKAY, THIS IS WHERE
YOU ENTER.
THE FENCES ARE SET UP
JUST LIKE THE CAMP.
COME ON, BILLY.
I'M GOING
TO PUT YOU UP HERE
ON THIS FENCE.
DON'T WORRY
CAUSE YOU'RE
IN GOOD COMPANY.
YOU FEEL THE RUT?
UM-HUMM.
KEEP HIM THERE.
UP TO THE LEFT
IS THE JUDGES BOOTH.
YOU'LL HEAR THE ANNOUNCER
OVER THE LOUD SPEAKER.
MAYBE SOME STATIC.
OKAY.
PUT HIM
INTO A CANTER.
GOOD.
FOUR PACES LATER YOU'RE
INTO YOUR FIRST TURN.
OKAY.
NOW YOU'VE
CIRCLED AROUND.
1-2-3-4 STOP.
4 STRIDES
AND YOU'RE AT
THE FIRST JUMP.
NOW, IF YOU GET
GHOST ANYWHERE
NEAR HERE
HE'LL TAKE
YOU OVER.
IT'S
A DOUBLE.
YUP.
YOU HUNGRY, BOY?
2 AND 3...
OH, THIS ONE'S
A BREEZE.
1, 2, 3,
OH, NOT THIS ONE.
WHY, WHAT IS IT?
IT'S A
BRICK WALL
BUT DON'T
WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S FOR
THE MEDAL CLASS.
OH, BILLY!
[ Announcer: ]
Welcome folks,
to the annual
All English
Rocky Mountain horse fair.
The competitors
are ready and waiting
at the entry gates
so let's get started.
Rider number 14,
now approaching jump number 3.
There will
be a warning call
for competitors
in the class
to gather
at the entry
prior to
the competition.
THANK YOU.
SEE YOU IN A LITTLE BIT.
The first class will be
regular warm up hunters
with fences
set at two and a half feet.
Riders, prepare
to enter the ring.
In accordance with
standard jumping guidelines,
all rules
will be in effect.
BRUSH HIS MANE
REALLY GOOD, OKAY?
I'M BRUSHIN',
I'M BRUSHIN'.
[ horse whinnies ]
HOW DO I LOOK?
LIKE A RIDER.
RICK, YOU ARE
SUCH A POET.
YOU LOOK ABSOLUTELY
STUNNING, LINDSAY!
THANK YOU.
COME ON, LET ME
HELP YOU REGISTER.
OKAY.
Cleared all fences.
No faults.
IS THIS
SEAT TAKEN?
NO.
WHAT?
NOTHING.
The next class.
The Rocky Mountain
Medal Class.
[ Crowd: ]
OHH!
SOMEONE FELL?
It's okay, folks,
she's on her feet.
YEAH. BUT YOU WON'T.
The last rider...
number 28.
please enter the ring.
WHY ARE THEY CALLING
YOUR NUMBER?
YOU'RE NOT
IN THE MEDAL CLASS.
YES, I AM.
LINDSAY,
YOU DIDN'T?
THE COURSE
IS THE SAME.
THE MEDAL CLASS IS
FOR EXPERIENCED RIDERS.
THE JUMPS ARE HIGHER
AND THERE'S THE BRICK WALL.
YOU HEARD THE LAST
RIDER KISS THE DIRT.
RICK,
I MISS COMPETING.
I MISS THE
SPOTLIGHT.
THE ENERGY
FROM THE CROWD.
THE SICK
FEELING I GET
IN MY STOMACH.
WHY DOES
IT HAVE TO
BE THIS CLASS?
BECAUSE IT'S
THE TOUGHEST.
I NEED TO KNOW
IF CAN DO IT
AND KNOW
YOU'RE WITH ME.
Second call
for number 28,
please enter the ring.
THEN, I'M WITH YOU.
ALL THE WAY.
COME ON BUDDY.
On course is number 28,
Lindsay Kurtz, riding Ghost.
LINDSAY'S JUMPING
OVER THAT?
SHE'LL BE
FINE, GEORGE.
[ Crowd: ]
OH...
BEAUTIFUL!
[ Whistle ]
HEY, WHO'S
YOUR FRIEND?
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD,
JOEY.
OH, MAN, THAT'S HUGE.
YEAH.
LET'S BAIL.
WE GOT US
AN APARTMENT...
IN NEW YORK CITY.
REALLY?
NO MORE JUVIE.
NO MORE
PROBATION OFFICERS.
JUST THE
THREE OF US
IN MANHATTAN.
COME ON, MAN,
WE'RE OUTTA HERE.
3...
2...
1...
[ Crowd: ]
OHHHH.
GHOST.
GHOST?
GHOST!
WHAT HAPPENED?
LINDSAY FELL.
LINDSAY,
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH,
HOW'S GHOST?
HE LOOKS FINE.
I SCREWED UP.
IT'S OKAY.
NO, IT'S NOT.
I DID THE
SAME THING
ON THE BEAM.
THAT WASN'T
YOUR FAULT.
I SAW THE TAPE.
IT WAS THE
CAMERA FLASHES.
NO, IT WASN'T.
I JUST LET PEOPLE
THINK THAT.
I TOOK MY EYE
OFF THE BEAM.
I LOST MY
CONCENTRATION.
JUST LIKE
I LET MY FOOT SLIP
FROM THE STIRRUP.
The judge
is entering the ring.
We'll wait
for an official ruling.
I WANTED TO KNOW
IF I COULD DO IT.
I GUESS,
NOW, I KNOW.
NO, YOU DON'T KNOW.
YOU HAVEN'T FINISHED.
MISS KURTZ,
DO YOU NEED ANY ASSISTANCE
LEAVING THE ARENA?
SHE WANTS TO
DO THE JUMP AGAIN.
BUT SHE'S...
BLIND?
SHE SORTA
KNOWS THAT.
IS THERE
A LAW AGAINST BLIND
RIDERS COMPETING?
TECHNICALLY, NO.
BUT SHE'S ALREADY
BEEN DISQUALIFIED
FOR MISSING THE JUMP.
THAT'S OKAY.
SHE JUST WANTS
TO FINISH.
THIS IS HIGHLY UNUSUAL.
THAT'S OKAY.
SO AM I.
OKAY.
LOOKS LIKE SHE'S
GONNA GET BACK ON GHOST.
ALL RIGHT!
ARE YOU STILL
WITH ME?
YEAH.
[ Applause and cheering ]
YOU CAN DO IT!
Number 28 is disqualified,
however,
the judge will allow her
to complete the jump.
C'MON, MAN,
LET'S NOT STICK AROUND.
WHAT'S TO
THINK ABOUT?
YOU KNOW MACK'S
GOING TO TAKE YOU
BACK TO JUVIE
AFTER THE SHOW.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I'M NOT GOING.
WHAT?
YOU'RE GONNA
THROW AWAY OUR PLANS,
THROW AWAY
YOUR FREEDOM,
TO WATCH
SOME BLIND GIRL
RIDE A PONY?
IF THAT'S THE WAY
YOU WANT TO PUT IT, YEAH.
YOUR PRIORITIES
ARE WAY SCREWED UP, MAN.
COME ON, BLITZ,
FORGET ABOUT HIM.
I DON'T KNOW
YOU, MAN.
ALL RIGHT COWBOY,
HERE SHE GOES.
CROSS YOUR FINGERS.
[ Crowd cheers ]
ALL RIGHT, LINDSAY!
YEE HAW!
Number 28
has cleared the jump.
How about a hand
for Lindsay Kurtz on Ghost.
HEY, WE DIDN'T DO
NOTHING, MAN.
YOU GUYS UNDERESTIMATE
YOURSELVES.
YOUR ESCAPE WAS
DEFINITELY SOMETHING.
COME ON.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU FINISHED.
NEXT YEAR,
I'LL PLACE FIRST.
YOU JUST MIGHT, TOO.
We'd like
to thanks our sponsors
for their generosity
in the individual prizes
awarded today.
I HEARD YOU WERE
PLANNING A TRIP
TO NEW YORK.
GOOD THING YOU
DECIDED NOT TO GO.
YOUR PALS ARE TAKING
A LITTLE DETOUR.
[ Annie: ]
I JUST TALKED
TO BUSTER.
HE SAID
HE COULDN'T STAND
TO LET CAL TORTURE GHOST
SO HE LET RICK
HAVE THE HORSE.
HE DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING BEFORE
BECAUSE HE THOUGHT
HE'D LOSE HIS JOB.
GO ON,
TAKE YOUR LAP, COACH.
THANK YOU, MACK.
YOU KNOW,
I COULD USE A
PERMANENT STABLE BOY.
MAYBE WE COULD
DISCUSS THIS OVER DINNER.
MAYBE.
DO YOU COOK
ANYTHING OTHER
THAN BANANA PANCAKES?
NO.
BUT I DO
A MEAN TAKE OUT.
[ Applause ]
Captions by CaptionHouse