[clapping]
[whooshing]
[ambient music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[distant children playing]
[ambient music]
[exciting techno beat music]
[sombre techno beat music]
[heavy breathing]
[muffled beat music]
[distant birds chirping]
[water trickling]
[Woman] Are you up yet?
Coming.
[door opening]
I need my hair done.
Do you think?
Hello.
Can you give me
your address, please?
What time will you be back?
I'm not sure.
Will you be late?
No, shouldn't be.
I'll make something
nice for dinner.
[children playing]
[car engine rumbling]
♪ I lost my heart
♪ Under the bridge
♪ To that little girl
♪ So much to me
♪ And now I'm old
♪ And now I holler
♪ She'll never know
♪ Just what I found
♪ That blue-eyed girl
♪ She said no more
♪ And that blue-eyed girl
♪ Became blue-eyed whore
♪ Down by the water
♪ I took her hand
♪ Just like my daughter
♪ I'll see her again ♪
[ominous music]
[distant children playing]
[Woman] We've been
trying to get hold of you
all morning, Una.
I know, I'm sorry.
[Woman] Will you be in
this afternoon?
I'm taking mum to
the doctor now.
I'll let you know.
[Woman] I hope she
feels better.
See you later.
You will be asked a
number of questions
by the solicitor who's in
the courtroom upstairs.
After each question, you
must answer into the camera.
Is that all clear?
Can you give him a message?
[Clerk] Who?
Ray.
Can you give him a
message from me?
[Clerk] That's completely
out of the question.
Ray,
where did you go?
Why did you leave me?
Ray, can you hear me?
[machinery buzzing]
Cheers, mate.
See you, man.
Drive safe.
[machinery beeping]
[machinery humming]
[car door slamming]
[men laughing]
[ominous music]
[sputtering]
[spitting]
[women laughing]
[women chatting]
[machinery humming]
[knocking]
You spying on us?
- [giggling]
- Are you lost?
I'm looking for Ray.
Do you know him?
No. What's he look like?
What, is he about my height?
Young, good-looking, yeah?
He's this man.
That's Pete.
Pete?
Yeah, my boss.
Should be around here somewhere.
[machinery pumping]
Pete.
Peter!
Yeah?
[ominous music]
Will you take over, please?
[Worker] Yeah.
Come this way, please.
[machinery pumping]
[ominous music]
Okay. In here.
Can you close the door?
I don't want the door closed.
Close the door.
[door slamming]
[ominous music]
How'd you find me?
- How'd you get here?
- I drove from where I live.
Where I still live.
What do you want?
To see you.
I can't fucking believe you
drove here because of a photo.
Why don't we just
go outside, okay?
You can say whatever
you wanna say outside.
What?
Are you allergic to me?
Okay, fuck this.
- Don't go.
- Fuck this.
You stay away from me, you hear?
Stay away. You need help.
Ray.
Ray!
[machinery buzzing]
I don't even know if it's you.
If you're her.
I am. Of course I am.
No, I don't know that.
- Yes you did.
- I didn't recognise you.
Your face went white.
You could be anyone.
Couldn't you?
I mean, you could be anyone.
You could be a journalist.
Your hair's different.
Reporter.
Could be anyone.
How many other 13 years
olds have you had sex with?
None.
Do you want to
see my birthmark?
You kissed it.
And what you promised
on the beach?
A life together,
just you and me.
None?
Are you sure?
[grass rustling]
[seagulls calling]
[car engine rumbling]
- Hi.
- [Ray] Hello.
[Woman] Where are you headed?
We're going to Europe.
Just me and dad.
And then we're
gonna catch a ferry.
[Ray] Dover to Calais
and then who knows.
Have a lovely time.
Thanks.
None.
Just me.
In that room.
[seagulls calling]
[ocean waves splashing]
[muffled machinery banging]
You're smiling.
You've forgotten.
Yeah.
Yes, I had.
What did you expect?
If it had been
six months later,
you'd be on the
Sex Offenders Register.
Ray would be on it.
You wouldn't be
allowed to forget.
You wouldn't have a new life.
I served my time.
Four years for what
you did to me.
My dad couldn't believe it.
He was never the same again.
He died a few years after.
How?
He fell.
Tripped on some steps.
He thought you were his friend.
He tried to find you.
He knew where I was
for the first four years.
He wanted to hunt you
down and kill you.
Hey! Give me that!
Jesus.
You thought I'd
come to kill you?
[ambient music]
Borrowed this from your dad.
Can you give it back to him?
You changed your name.
Is that difficult?
Random.
Picked it out of a phone book.
Peter?
Peter, what?
I can ask outside.
Trevelyan.
- [laughing]
- Trevelyan?
Peter Trevelyan.
Where the hell did
you get that from?
Under T.
Peter Trevelyan?
Are you fucking serious?
Does that command respect?
Okay.
What about the photos you
took of me in your house?
I got rid of them.
I burned them all.
I've seen those
websites, those poor kids.
Never.
- 10, 11, 12.
- [Ray] Never.
On beds, sofas.
Those sick bastards.
I was never one of them.
[knocking]
Everything all right, Pete?
Yeah, it's all good, mate.
Peter and I are just talking.
Leave you to it.
I was never one of them.
You know I wasn't.
- Do I?
- They all called me that.
The other prisoners. The guards.
I've been spat on.
I've been beaten up.
Had human shit put in my face.
You know!
I don't know anything
about you
except that you
abused me.
Didn't you?
- Didn't you?
- Yes, but.
There's no but.
I was never one of them.
You were my neighbour's
daughter, not a target.
[sombre music]
You were looking at me.
[ambient music]
I always used to wonder if I
hadn't argued with my friend,
it could have been
her you chose.
Could've all happened
to her, not me.
If you don't know
what you did,
then I'm not gonna tell you.
All right?
[people laughing]
Where's Leah?
She went home.
Una, I didn't choose you.
It's a beautiful day.
A smile wouldn't kill you.
Should we call the fire brigade?
[giggling]
You'll be bored out
your mind here.
I've got boredom protection.
I want one.
Give me one.
- Go on.
- [chuckling]
You'll get me in trouble.
How many people were
at that barbecue?
There were 10 or 15
people there, right?
Why?
Because I had shorts
on that day.
[Una giggling]
Yeah, they laughed about
this in court as well.
You wore shorts?
In court that was your defence?
If I'd been aroused,
[laughing]
if I had an erection,
if I'd been turned...
Can you hear yourself?
I stood there next to you,
drinking my beer,
in those shorts.
I would've walked away.
I would've sat down.
A person knows if they're
aroused by children
because they're always
looking to be near them,
to lure them, deceive them.
The greater the risk,
the bigger the thrill.
You seem to know
a lot about it.
I had to talk
to psychologists.
There are patterns of behaviour.
Cycles of abuse.
Were you abused as a child?
For God's sake.
No.
This is the exact same
thing the lawyer asked me.
He claimed the courts
would be more lenient
if I had been abused.
But I haven't.
I'm not one of them.
[door clicking]
[Woman] Mark is
waiting for you.
I've got a meeting.
I have to go.
It's important.
Go.
Why don't you
wait in your car?
[Woman] Peter!
Okay!
[door slamming]
[ominous music]
[wind blowing]
[ocean waves rolling]
[ominous music]
You know this is
a big deal, yes?
Just don't fuck it up, okay?
We want you moving ahead
into the future with us.
Yeah?
Okay?
Peter, you okay?
Good.
Okay, let's get in there.
What're you doing here?
You're a good swimmer.
You wanna race?
[chuckling]
You'll beat me.
[water bubbling]
[ominous music]
[water trickling]
What are you doing
this weekend?
Nothing much, really.
Who was that guy?
Yeah, who was he?
Just someone I know.
Where did you meet him?
Around.
[Girls] Tell us.
Come on.
He's the neighbour.
Friend of my dad's.
Let's go.
[garage door buzzing]
[ambient music]
Want a cup of tea?
No, thank you.
Coffee?
No.
We got champagne,
ice cream, caviar.
[laughing]
[dramatic music]
Thank you.
Listen, why don't we go
through to the meeting?
Or at least to reception.
You shouldn't be here alone.
I'm waiting for Peter.
[sombre music]
[Prosecutor] State your full
name to the court, please.
Ray?
Where did you go?
What happened?
Why did you leave me?
[courtroom commotion]
Ray, can you hear me?
I love you.
[people gasping]
[courtroom commotion]
That does mean we'll need
to consolidate
several positions.
[meeting room commotion]
Here at Ethgon, we believe in
investing not just in ideas
but in people.
[banging]
I'll pass you over to Peter now.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Right, okay.
So it's like Jen said.
We're gonna be moving to
working more with north-west
and consolidating our
futures together.
New beginning.
[audience commotion]
[ominous music]
I can't do this.
Look, they want me to...
give you 6 names.
They want 6 names of people.
- Peter.
- Excuse me.
I'm doing this.
Daryl.
Mate, I'm sorry.
[meeting room commotion]
[people yelling]
Peter!
I'm gonna fucking kill him.
He's fucking dead.
[ominous music]
Peter!
Scott.
What the fuck is up with Peter?
Nothing.
Hey.
You think he's your friend?
You're on his list.
Yeah.
You should empty
out your locker.
Get up.
How long have you
been married?
I don't have time for this.
Let's go.
Four years.
Do you have children?
No.
That poor woman. No
idea who she's married to.
No idea what you did...
She knows.
She knows?
I have to go.
How does she know?
Because I told her.
She was fine with it?
Of course not,
but I told her what my
life was like then.
What was your life like then?
I had problems.
Did you? Did you really?
What kind of problems?
I made the biggest,
most stupid, mistake
of my entire life.
Did you tell her it was
a 3 month stupid mistake?
That you ran away with me?
I told her everything
because she loves me.
Well what's wrong with her?
There must be something
wrong with her.
Don't talk about
her like that.
Why not? What the fuck's
wrong with her?
Pete!
[door slamming]
This is my life.
I had to fight for this.
I lost everything.
Did you ever think about me?
What was happening to me?
You got out after four years.
I've been living this
for 15 years!
Every fucking day!
We never moved from that house.
I was talked about,
pointed at, stared at.
I was attacked by
your girlfriend.
I lost my life.
The only thing I didn't
lose was my name.
[Scott] Pete!
I had to keep my name.
[ominous music]
Peter!
Pete!
[door clicking]
She attacked you?
A couple of years later,
I was shopping with my mum.
She slapped me.
Pushed me to the ground.
She used to say
that you glared at her.
That you were after me.
You used to hang
around on the street,
near the car.
Write notes.
You'd put them under
the windshield wiper.
"Your girlfriend's ugly."
"Your girlfriend's
got a glass eye."
[laughing]
I was a shameless stupid
girl with a stupid crush.
You weren't stupid.
I was.
No.
You weren't.
You don't remember
what you were like.
What was I like?
You were headstrong.
Determined.
Wise beyond your years.
- No.
- Yes.
Yes.
You were so impatient,
sick of being treated
like a child.
That's what children say.
What could I have possibly
given you that wasn't my body?
What else could you have wanted?
There was nothing else.
There was.
For me there was.
Do you remember the codes?
[phone dialling]
I used to ring your
parents' house, one ring.
Meant she'd gone out
and you were on your own.
Car parked facing right,
"meet me in the park."
[ominous music]
I could've stopped.
I should've stopped.
But you didn't.
[ominous music]
Whatever it was,
whatever I was thinking,
made me believe
I loved you.
Crawling in to those trees.
And pulling up my top
and touching my breasts.
And unzipping your trousers
and taking out your prick.
Telling me to hold it.
Then on the blanket
you brought...
I thought it was to
make us comfortable
but realised afterwards
it wasn't, was it?
It was so that twigs and earth
wouldn't stick to my clothes
so that no one would suspect.
[leaves rustling]
I didn't want us
to get caught.
Every waking moment
was about how
I could get to be closer to you.
How I could talk to you.
I was so obsessed with you.
I used to leave work early.
I'd come home,
I'd work on my car.
My car didn't need work.
I'd do it just so I
could be near you.
You remember.
We both knew the risks.
Any of you seen Peter?
[ambient music]
[sombre music]
[door closing]
Una.
There were twin beds.
Don't.
Why not?
We both know what happened.
We were both there.
We undressed.
We had sex on one of the beds.
I'm not sure how long for.
I saw how much
pleasure it gave you.
I liked that I could do that.
We did it twice. Fucked.
Twice.
You turned me around
the second time.
We made so much noise.
We lay in each other's arms
afterwards and I cried a bit.
My parents would be
looking for me.
They'd be phoning my friends.
I don't even know if I came.
Did I come?
I thought you did.
[water running]
How could you tell?
Did I make a noise?
What did I do?
Your eyes were closed.
Your face was flushed.
You said you
wanted cigarettes.
You were going to look
for a shop, a pub.
I wanted to go with
you but you said no,
I was to wait there.
Then you touched me and
kissed me between my legs.
You'd be back in five minutes.
I fell asleep and when I woke up
I didn't know what time it was
I was sore between my
legs but I felt wonderful.
I was so happy.
And you'd be back soon and
you'd have chocolate for me.
I didn't even have to
tell you what I wanted.
You'd know what I wanted
and you'd bring it to me.
[ominous music]
[muffled conversation]
I waited for you in that
room but you never came back.
[ominous music]
[door opening]
What are you doing?
This room's private.
What you wanting?
[Una Voiceover] I looked
for you in the town.
Everywhere.
But I couldn't find you.
Did a man come in
here for cigarettes?
[Woman] What?
About an hour ago,
a man for cigarettes?
I'm sorry, my love.
[ominous music]
[Man] Hey, you can't
be in here.
I'm looking for my dad.
What's his name?
Ray.
[Man] A girl looking for
her dad, Ray.
We got Ray in the bar?
When did you last see him, love?
[ominous music]
Oh my god.
[Una Voiceover] I felt
sick. I wanted to die.
I was never going
to see you again.
Ray!
I didn't say anything
to anyone.
I didn't say a word.
I told them you hadn't
touched me.
That I had run away.
[thudding]
[car engine puttering]
[car door slamming]
They asked me what
you'd done to me.
When I wouldn't say, they
told me what you'd done to me.
They drugged me and
held me down,
opened my legs and
took out your come.
They said you were
only after one thing
and when you got
what you wanted,
that's why you disappeared.
I hate the life I've had.
You wouldn't know any of that
but I wanted you to know that.
[ambient music]
Peter?
Could you leave the
bathroom, please?
[Mark] Oh, I'm sorry.
[door closing]
I came back.
- What?
- I didn't leave you.
I came back.
Thank you.
2-85, thanks so much.
- Thank you.
- Lovely.
Take care.
Thanks.
- Have a good one.
- Bye.
I needed a drink.
I needed courage.
Because we were really doing it.
We're getting on the ferry.
We were running away.
[ominous music]
Same again, mate?
So, yeah.
I just needed to clear my head.
So I went for a walk
around the streets
and then...
and then I came back.
[foreboding music]
She told me you had gone.
Just run off.
I went to the car,
yelled out for you.
I thought maybe you were hiding.
But nothing.
I started to fucking panic.
Where would you go?
Why would you go?
I didn't know what the
fuck was going on.
It didn't make any
fucking sense.
And then I thought maybe
someone had got you,
that you were being hurt.
That I hadn't protected you.
[bar commotion]
Can I get a whisky,
mate, a double?
You got a daughter?
Yeah, I do, yeah.
Why, have you seen her?
Have you lost her?
Yeah.
So what are you
in here for, then?
Did she say where
she was going?
What's your name?
Hey, what's your name, mate?
Come back here!
[ominous music]
I didn't leave you.
That's what the lawyer said
because he said it might
sound better in court,
that I was disgusted with
myself so I ran away.
It's not true.
I didn't.
I came back for you.
I'd like to report
a missing person.
Pardon me?
A missing person.
Leaving me there, coming back,
there's no difference.
Yes there is.
For me there is.
Pete!
Peter!
Cunt.
[thudding]
[Una] What's going on?
[Ray] They're locking
up for the day.
[Ray sighing]
[sombre music]
We can't stay here.
Are you expected home?
Yeah.
I am.
Did you tell your wife?
That you were coming
back for me?
That you wouldn't
have left me there?
No.
You haven't told her, have you?
Anything.
How could I?
You don't think she
should be told?
I don't think we
should talk about it.
- Can I meet her?
- [Ray] Don't be stupid.
How old is she?
She is a year older than me.
Is she sexy?
Does she turn you on?
All that sagging skin.
What does she like best?
You're unwell, you know that?
You need help.
Sick.
- I am not.
- [Ray] You are fucking ill.
I'm not.
You are fucking...
I'm not sick!
[groaning]
[shushing]
[crying]
I started at 6:30
this morning.
What do you do?
Have you got a job?
Just office work.
It's nothing earth-shattering.
It's not what I wanted to do.
What did you wanna do?
I don't know.
Something else.
You still live at home?
With your mum?
[laughing]
If she knew I was here.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
[garbage rustling]
[rustling]
[Una laughing]
I did think about
you growing up.
What you'd be like.
I never wanted to hurt you.
[ambient music]
Do you think about me then?
It's all I have of you.
Holding you.
Touching you.
And fucking me.
Do you masturbate?
Do you come?
Yeah.
[ambient music]
[heavy breathing]
[Ray moaning]
[groaning]
I can't.
I want you to.
No.
Why not?
I can't be with you.
Am I too old?
[sombre music]
Pete?
Oh, shit.
Pete, what the
fuck, man?
What?
What the fuck?
Huh?
What d'you mean "what"?
What the fuck, eh? You
fucking gave them my name!
You got me fired.
What?
No, hold on, who told you that?
Fucking Mark.
He's lying.
- He's lying.
- He told me.
He's a liar!
Look! Look!
Look!
Your name's not on that.
That's the list.
Mark's a liar.
Please, just get her.
Get her out of here.
Lock up, please.
Can you do that?
Just get her out of here.
[sombre music]
[stomping]
Right, we've gotta go.
You can't stay here.
Where is he?
Ray!
He's gone. He's just left.
He's gone. I've just seen him.
You've gotta go,
I need to lock up.
Do you wanna go for a drink?
I could really do with one.
I don't know.
Just one drink.
Come on.
Just one.
Is this you?
[Ray tapping]
There it is.
Do you see it?
That's our new life.
Yeah.
[seagulls calling]
Why do you call him Ray?
It's a long story.
Is there something
going on between you two?
Have you got anything
to drink at your place?
[ominous music]
Hello.
Hello, girl.
Peter?
Long day?
I must have dozed off.
Thanks for doing
all that downstairs.
Come here and lie with me.
I've gotta get ready.
Come on.
[moaning]
Peter.
[exciting beat music]
That's not full.
Oh, shit.
Sorry.
How's that?
That's good?
[exciting beat music]
You have a little.
Yeah.
[heavy breathing]
[groaning]
[Una crying]
You all right?
Una?
[crying]
Hey.
It's okay.
[Una sobbing]
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Don't be silly.
Hey.
It's all right.
I wanna go home.
Will you take me?
I don't think I can drive.
Yeah, of course.
Where's home?
Peter's.
I'm staying at Peter's.
You're staying at Peter's?
He's my dad.
Are you serious?
I need to go home.
They'll be expecting me.
Fuck.
There's that party tonight.
I forgot.
You okay?
I just haven't eaten anything.
I'll make you something.
I'm fine, it's okay.
No, no, it's fine.
I'll just heat something
up for you.
Then we'll get you home.
Yeah?
[food sizzling]
[phone ringing]
Una, where are you?
I'm fine.
I was on the point
of calling the police.
You have no idea at all.
[Mother] About what?
[Una] You were so
desperate to hush it all up.
[sombre music]
Una.
Please come home.
Let me know where you are.
Please, darling.
Una?
Wow.
That's my girlfriend's.
Until a week ago.
You look amazing.
Will you come with me?
He's my boss.
Please, come with me.
[doorbell ringing]
[people laughing]
[ominous music]
Hi, Scott.
Hello, I'm Una.
Hi, Yvonne.
Glad you could come.
- [Scott] How's it going?
- [Yvonne] Good. How are You?
Hello, hello.
Here comes trouble.
Ah, this is
Sterling and Hattie.
Gorgeous thing.
Stop licking.
You'll drown her, come on.
Come on, girl.
What the fuck?
It's fine.
Let me get you a drink.
Scott, help yourself.
Una?
Gin.
[party commotion]
[ominous music]
So how did you two meet?
Oh, we just met around.
There you go.
Thank you.
Peter's outside.
[intense music]
[Scott] Garden looks great.
[Yvonne] Thanks.
Try to keep on top of it.
[intense music]
This is Una.
Hey.
[Scott] You alright, geezer?
Yeah, I'm good. I'm good.
Hey, there's someone
I want you to meet.
Excuse me, darling.
What the hell is going on?
What?
How did you meet Peter?
Through friends.
You been together long?
Four years now.
Happy?
Sorry, is that the
wrong thing to ask?
[ominous music]
We just got here.
Are you fucking serious?
Just get her out of this house.
You're not her dad?
What'd you say?
[ominous music]
Is tonight something special?
Just drinks with some friends.
That's nice.
Hey, let's get out of here.
Yvonne, I'm so sorry,
we've got to go.
You just got here.
I know, I just, just
got a text. We've gotta...
No, I'm talking to Yvonne.
Sweetheart,
we've gotta get back.
Love, don't do this to me,
we gotta go.
No.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
[intense music]
[ambient music]
[children laughing]
[riders screaming]
We could be stuck
up here forever.
I love you.
[ambient music]
What you doing in my room?
I'm a friend of Peter's.
From work?
No.
Do you know my mum?
Not really, no.
What's your name?
Una.
[ominous music]
What's wrong, love?
Una!
Una
[ominous music]
Hey.
Never.
I would never do that.
Please don't.
No, please.
Una.
I look after her.
I take care of her.
You've got to believe me.
I have never desired
anyone that age.
Again.
I promise.
You were the only one.
[ambient music]
[dramatic music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[sombre music]
[ambient music]