[MUSIC - JEREMY CAMP, "MY DESIRE"]
Hi.
Hot dog and a diet soda, now.
OK.
Thanks.
HOT DOG SELLER: What can I get for you?
Uh, hi.
A hot dog-- a-- a 7UP, and a bag of chips.
HOT DOG SELLER: Coming right up.
Here-- just keep the change.
HOT DOG SELLER: Thanks a lot.
Yeah.
Hi.
Hi, I-- I'm sorry, I-- I didn't get
a chance to introduce myself.
I've never done this before, but I'm Dan-- Dan Donahue.
[SIGH]
Look, I know this seems really strange,
not-- not that I am strange.
I don't know how to say what I really want to say
except for just to say it.
Look, I'm really late for work.
Would you like to have dinner?
Excuse me?
Would you like to have dinner with me?
I don't even know you.
Well, what do you mean?
We-- we're having lunch together.
Look, I really have to go.
Look, I know I look like a slob,
not-- not that I am a slob.
These are my work clothes.
I actually look kind of nice in a suit and tie.
Why are you bothering me?
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to bother you.
I just-- I just want to have dinner with you.
No, thank you.
Look, we can meet at the restaurant of your choice,
have dinner, and then you can leave.
And-- and that's it-- nothing else.
I said, no.
You can invite your parents.
I'll hire a cop to stand by the table.
What did I do to deserve all this?
I mean, why me?
I don't know.
I-- I just saw you buying a hot dog, and I thought to myself,
this is the pretties lady I've ever seen.
And I thought, if I don't talk to her now,
I'll never see her again as long as I live.
Is that what you say to all the girls?
No, I told you I'd never done this before.
We'll meet for dinner, and that's it?
That's it.
And if I want to leave, you won't stop me.
I won't stop, I promise.
OK.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Great.
[MUSIC - ADIE, "DON'T WAIT"]
[WHISPERING]
DAN: I promise you, we won't get caught.
You promise?
Come on, I promise.
OK.
Come right here.
Come on.
[PHOTO SNAP]
Go, go, go.
Hurry.
Come on.
[LAUGHTER]
These are really good.
Eat one.
I'll choose an animal for you.
[LAUGHTER]
Cow-- no
Oh.
-Here you go. -What is it?
You're a tiger.
Oh, I like that.
Thank you.
Here-- I'll share.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Now close your eyes for a minute.
SUE: What for?
DAN: Just close your eyes until I tell you to open them, OK?
SUE: OK.
DAN: Don't open them.
SUE: (LAUGHING) All right, OK.
Don't open them.
What are you doing?
DAN: Don't open your eyes until I tell you to.
Oh.
DAN: OK, open your eyes.
They're beautiful.
Not as beautiful as you.
You always know the right things to do.
What do you mean?
Romantic dinners, walks in the park,
now this-- I bet you're this way with all the girls.
No.
Why me?
I was waiting for the right woman.
And you think I'm the right woman?
Yes.
What makes you think so?
Remember that first day at the hot dog stand?
Yeah.
Well, when I saw you, I got this wonderful feeling I
haven't felt since I was a kid.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
SUE: What are you thinking about?
Dan?
Pardon?
What are you thinking about?
Oh, I was just daydreaming.
About what?
Nothing really.
You OK?
Yeah, yeah.
A rhino--
[LAUGHTER]
Thanks.
You're welcome.
All right everybody, that was good.
Now, let's have another rehearsal.
Gene, they're gonna love it in New York.
Let's take it from the top.
One, two, three-- kick it.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi.
[INAUDIBLE]
Honey, there's a major fan of yours.
And he wants your picture, or your autograph, or something.
I don't know.
OK, OK, OK. All right, listen up, everybody.
Keep playing.
Right after this, we're gonna go right back to Jamaica.
I can handle this.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Ya man, Jamaica.
Well, you know how everybody-- hey,
how do you like my sheets, man? I got them at a white sale.
[LAUGHTER] -They look good.
I'm really proud of you.
The band, and that you're lady's pregnant-- I
think that's great. -For the second time.
Oh.
Yeah, I'm a dad, and I love it.
What a responsibility. -It's great.
You just try to be a little better than what you got, and--
Yeah.
And you remember the time you thought was Superman.
We got your ego, and you jumped off of that stand?
It's amazing I didn't break my neck that night.
Yeah, I'm surprised we all survived it.
We all didn't.
All right, now-- tell me-- tell me about Sue.
[SIGH]
What can I say?
She's-- the greatest woman I've ever met, everything
I've ever dreamed of, yeah.
She's great.
She's-- she's all that?
Yeah.
So I wanna know how long you've known her?
Six months.
And you gonna ask her the question?
Yeah, I-- I was going gonna ask her--
-Come on, man. - --this week, yeah.
-Really? -Yeah.
All right, now see this paper towel stuff?
It's nice.
Imagine-- imagine I get a suit on, fix
up the dreads and everything.
You know, but the dreads are kind of heavy, right?
I like them.
Can I be the best man?
You always have been, Norman.
[LAUGHTER] -I'm excited for you.
Come on.
So you like reggae music.
-Yeah, I like, I think. -All right.
I mean, I just a few-- [INTERPOSING VOICES]
All right, I'm gonna teach you the song.
-OK. -OK.
I know there are ladies present,
but I was feeling kind of--
Dad, I can't believe you told that joke.
[LAUGHTER]
I promised her I wouldn't.
-Can we have some cake? -Yes.
I finished my lamb.
That lamb was great, by the way. MRS. PALMER: Thank you.
It was, Mom. [INTERPOSING VOICES]
--guests more often.
MRS. PALMER: Thank you so much.
The rosemary was very good on it.
So Dan, how's your apartment building coming?
Oh, just great.
I've only-- thank you.
I've only got one more unit to rent.
Hey, that's terrific.
-Do you want some more coffee? -Please.
You, uh, do all the repair work yourself, right?
Yeah.
My dad's real handy, so I kind of picked it up from him.
Hey--
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
Oh, great.
-Dad-- -Thank you.
MRS. PALMER: The biggest one for you, my dear.
Yay.
You know, I'd like to meet your dad.
Sure, that'd be great.
How's the, um, golf game coming?
Great.
MRS. PALMER: Oh, sure.
[LAUGHTER]
I've been practicing the last two months
for a grudge match with my son.
Now, the cake is very special, because Sue made it herself.
DAN: Really?
Yeah, really.
So, um, how long have you two been dating now, hm?
Tonight is our six month anniversary.
Good night, Mr. Palmer.
Good night, Dan.
Good night, Mrs. Palmer.
Thank you for dinner.
Oh, you're more than welcome, Dan.
I'll walk you out.
OK.
Good night. Bye.
I'll be back, Mom.
OK?
Oh, they're a wonderful couple.
Mm, just like us.
Dan, what's wrong?
I know something's wrong.
What is it?
I can't see you anymore.
What are you talking about?
We can be together.
What do you mean we can't be together?
Dan, what's wrong?
I don't know.
You can't just say we can't be together and-- and not why.
I want to get married, and have children with you,
and be a family.
There's nothing I want more than
to marry you, raise a family together,
and live happily ever after.
But it just doesn't happen that way.
(CRYING) It will with us.
We love each other, for--
It's not about us.
It's about me.
There's too much anger inside, and I just can't seem to get
rid of it no matter how hard I try,
I thought if I buried myself in my work
that it would eventually go away, but it doesn't
[CRYING]
It's funny.
I worked so hard not to be like my father,
and I find I'm just like him.
You're nothing like him.
Oh, yes I am.
You just don't see it.
No.
What I see is a warm, sensitive, compassionate man.
[COUGHING]
Oh, God.
Why'd I break the heart of the one I love?
What do I have to do to be free to love?
[MUSIC - THOUSAND FOOT CRUTCH, "WISH YOU WELL"]
DAN (VOICEOVER): Dear Dad, I have
now been alive for 27 years.
It seems like only yesterday I was
a little boy going to school.
I thought anyone 27 was really old.
And now I find I am 27.
In no time at all, I'll find myself being 51,
an age I'm sure you find hard to believe you are.
I'm writing you this letter, because I
feel you should know me.
And the only way you can fully understand who I am
is you must know what I've gone through.
I don't believe you know me.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MIKE: Bob, get Bill another one, would you?
Well, thank you, Mike.
I appreciate it very much.
Catch you tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Mommy, Mommy, when's Daddy coming home?
Soon, honey.
MOM: Any second, sweetheart.
Daddy's home.
Hey, bud, how you doing?
Daddy, let's play horsey.
OK, come on.
Jump on.
Wee--
Faster Daddy, faster.
OK, buckin' broncos.
Wee-- buckin' broncos.
[LAUGHTER]
Hi, honey.
Look, Mommy.
We're playing horsey.
Oh boy, horsey.
[LAUGHTER]
DAN (VOICEOVER): "Remember those days, Dad?
Nice memories, aren't they?"
CHILDHOOD DAN: One, two, three, four, five--
DAN (VOICEOVER): And then something strange happened.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[TELEVISION]
DAN (VOICEOVER): All I could do is accept the facts of life.
I had no control over my destiny.
I had to make the best of it.
Put on a good show.
Be a good boy.
After all, boys aren't supposed to cry.
But inside, I was dying.
I wanted my family back, that's all--
no new toys, no new house, no new friends, no new school.
I just wanted my family back.
[TELEVISION]
[GLASS BREAKING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah, I know, Tony.
Yeah.
Oh, Danny really-- he loved the pizza the other night.
I think he's really beginning to warm up to you.
Uh-- oh, and thanks so much for offering to help us move.
Oh, it's going to be such a big help.
Yeah, I really appreciate it.
Oh, oh no.
I can't tonight.
I promised Danny I'd take him to a movie.
Daddy's home.
Uh, my-- uh, Tony.
Uh, look, I'm gonna have to-- Yeah, I gotta go.
I think Mike's here.
Oh- OK.
Yeah, bye.
Hi, Dad.
Hi, bud.
What are you doing here?
I came by to pick up a few things.
Is that all right with you?
Danny, just stay here and watch TV.
But Mom, I wanna see Dad.
Don't-- just do what you're told.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MOM: What are you doing?
Where's all my things?
MOM: Mike, I'd really appreciate if you'd
call before you come by.
(YELLING) Where are they?
MOM: I put them in the garage.
Mike--
You put my things in the garage.
I tried to call you to-- to ask you what
you wanted me to do with them.
This is my house.
I built it, remember?
MOM: I know that.
It's just that-- that it would be--
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
I want my things back where they belong.
(YELLING) Mike, they don't belong here.
You don't decide where they belong.
I do.
I'm still a man in this house.
MOM: Mike, you don't live here anymore.
I would appreciate it if you would just leave.
Don't I work hard to support this family?
Didn't I give you my paycheck every Friday?
Don't I spend time with Danny-- huh?
Don't I?
That's not the problem. It's--
Then why are you punishing me?
MOM: I'm not punishing you.
Yes you are.
You don't love me anymore.
You're always down at the bar drinking with all your buddies.
Big deal, so I stop after work and have a couple
of beers with the guys.
It's not like I'm out chasing women.
Why cant you just come home and spend time with your family?
I come home every night and have dinner with my family,
don't I?
You come home every night, and you're drunk,
just like you are right now.
I work my butt off to support you and Danny.
I deserve to do anything I want to do.
You're the reason for all this, not my drinking.
You're the problem.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[HONKING]
Daddy, Daddy.
Hey, bud.
How you doing?
Hi, Dad.
What's up, bud?
Hey, bud, um, I'm gonna go to the club for a few minutes, OK?
Uh, There's soda and chips in the fridge.
OK?
OK, Dad.
OK.
[DOOR CLOSING]
[GUNSHOTS ON TV]
[CAR]
Hey, bud.
Wake up.
Hi, Dad.
How you doing?
OK.
Everything go all right?
Yeah, but--
Good.
What do you say you get ready for bed, huh?
OK.
Dad, how come we never do anything anymore?
What do you mean?
We spend every other weekend together.
I know, but we don't do anything.
Like what?
What do you to do?
I don't know-- like go bike riding,
or play ball, or something like that.
Well, we could do a lot more if your mother hadn't
moved you 150 miles away.
It's her fault. If she hadn't run off with Tony,
we could spend every day together.
Do you still love Mom?
I wish it wasn't like this, bud.
If your mother hadn't run off with Tony,
things would be a whole lot better.
Mm-- can I get, um, into Channel 5?
I think a "Big Valley" rerun is on.
Mm-- [LAUGHTER]
DAN (VOICEOVER): You would hug me, and kiss me,
tell me you love me, and then say,
see ya in two weeks, buddy.
[LAUGHTER]
My sweet heart, oh.
[HORN HONKING]
What's on after this-- Matt Dillon?
I have no clue.
I gotta see some Westerns tonight.
I'm in a cowboy mood, honey.
[LAUGHTER]
Hi, sweetie. How about a big hug?
Danny, honey, what's wrong?
Danny-- Danny?
Danny, Danny, what's wrong, honey?
DAN (VOICEOVER): I couldn't go to Mom, because you said she
was the cause of the problem.
She was the enemy.
Sweetheart, let mommy in.
I couldn't go to you, because you wouldn't listen.
So I turned inward.
I'll be out here if you need me, OK?
DAN (VOICEOVER): I asked God why he was doing this to me.
[CRYING]
I'm really worried about Danny.
Oh, don't worry about Danny.
Danny will be fine, you know?
He just need to get his bum kicked a few times.
Oh, stop.
He's just always so depressed when he comes home from Mike's.
Well, would you be?
[CRYING]
Hi, honey.
Hi, Mom.
Can I lick the spoon?
Sure.
Now don't eat all of that.
I don't want you to spoil your appetite, OK?
OK.
[PHONE RINGING]
Can you get that for me?
Yeah.
OK.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hi, Dad.
How you doing?
Yeah, she's home.
Mom, it's for you.
Oh.
Hello.
Oh, hi Mike.
How are you?
Fine.
Oh, Mike, I don't know.
Do you think he's old enough?
Do you think it's safe to put him on the bus?
Will you be there waiting to pick him up?
OK.
All right. -Yes.
Yes.
Make sure you sit next to the bus driver.
OK, Mom.
All right?
And remember what I said-- no talking to strangers.
Yeah, Mom.
When you get there, you stay in the station
until your dad picks you up, OK?
OK, Mom.
OK.
Did you pack your toothbrush?
March.
OK bud?
Yeah, Dad.
DAN (VOICEOVER): Although I felt cut out of your life,
I still deeply treasured the times we spent together,
just you and me.
The whole world could be crumbling
around me, but so what?
I was with my dad, my hero.
Uh, Tony-- Tony, could I just have this and--
What are you doing? What are you doing--
-I'm just-- -(YELLING) What are you doing?
I'm just changing the bed.
(YELLING) Well, why are you changing this bed?
I've been sitting here alone for 20 minutes
for the first time in two weeks having a little privacy,
working on my puzzle.
Suddenly you're in here changing the bed.
There's a lot of other beds.
Go change another bed. -Tony--
Give me a little time to myself.
Why is everything such a big argument with you?
Why can't we just work things out?
Why is it so hard?
Why did you go downstairs and just do it on the sofa?
Why can't you take your privacy there?
Why does it have to always be here?
They're arguing at each other again.
MIKE (ON PHONE): Well, that's their problem, bud.
[ARGUING]
Yeah, but they argue every day.
MIKE (ON PHONE): Look, there's nothing I can do about that.
Look, bud, I gotta go.
I'll-- I'll see ya this weekend.
Bye.
MOM: Why is everything always an Argument with you?
Why-- why can't we just work it out?
There is no privacy downstairs.
And there is no working anything out with, you know,
because it always ends up getting you to be your way.
My way?
Yeah, that's right.
Everything I do is for you.
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, come on.
Come on-- that's a hunk of snot in some big old bloodhound's
nose.
Everything you do is for that little wimp downstairs.
He's about this high.
You know who I'm talking about?
That's what you do for-- him, not me.
He's a prince.
You keep Danny out of this.
He's not the problem.
Everything is one big fight with you.
Everything is a great big show.
The problem is him.
He's coming between us.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
I mean, wha-- why is everything such a big deal with you?
Keep him out of this.
He's not the problem, you are.
Oh, I'm the problem.
MOM: Yes, you-- you make a big deal out of everything.
Like what?
Like the other day when I bought
hamburger buns with poppy seeds.
Wait-- wha-- oh-- one second.
Now how many times have I asked you not to bring
poppy seeds into this house?
I forgot.
No, no, no, no, no, no-- you didn't forget.
I have told you a thousand times,
do not bring poppy seeds.
I can't eat poppy seeds.
They get in my teeth. -I forgot.
TONY: No, you didn't.
You know I can't eat poppy seeds.
But you bring the poppy seeds here anyway, don't you?
Now you know why you bring the poppy seeds?
Because the runt likes poppy seeds.
So here we got poppy seeds in the house.
I can't eat poppy seeds, honey.
You know I can't eat poppy seeds.
But your bring them in anyway, because you
don't care about me.
All you care about is him, and that's a fact.
And everything revolves around this kid00 Danny
this, Danny that.
I'm tired of hearing his name.
I just can't take this anymore.
Well, you're gonna have a-- a lot--
lot bigger problem when that kid gets older, believe me.
What you ought to do is throw him
out in the dirt with those Italian kids down the street.
Let him get some mud on his face and get into fist fighting.
Believe me, he's an evil kid.
He's gonna grow up to be Dracula, you watch.
[SIGH]
Oh, mm, this is so good.
You know-- you'd like to have one, wouldn't you?
All you'd have to do, young man, is get out there
and pull those weeds like I told you,
and I'd be happy to give you one.
Hey-- hey-- what are you looking for?
Why are you being such a jerk?
Now listen, your little wise mouth punk, this is my house.
You understand?
This is not your house.
It's not your mother's house.
It's my house.
Not the sooner you get that through your head,
the better off you're gonna be.
Now why don't you just go out and play in some traffic?
Kids don't wanna work for nothing these days.
Boy, it's amazing-- everything handed
to them on a silver platter.
OK, I got a silver platter right with the 10-speed bike
in the hot shop where it's gonna stay.
Bet you he'll learn to be a worthless, shiftless
bum like his old man.
When's Tony gonna give me back my 10-speed?
Don't worry about it, honey.
Come on, stop playing with it your food,
just eat it, all right?
Eat your dinner.
But he's had it for three months.
Look, if he doesn't give it back soon,
I'll buy you a new one.
How's that?
He's being such a jerk.
I-- I know, honey.
I'm sorry.
I'm really tired of eating TV dinners in my room.
Look, it's not gonna be much longer, OK?
I, um-- Tony's gonna be moving out soon.
I filed for a divorce.
I can't wait till he's gone.
Let's just make the best of it until he leaves, OK?
OK.
Can we have Salisbury steak for dinner tomorrow?
Mhm.
And how about hot fudge sundaes?
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
DAN (VOICEOVER): The photo I've enclosed explains the truth
about our relationship.
[PHOTO FLASH]
OK, just one more, Dad, OK?
OK.
Hey, what's with the arm?
[PHOTO FLASH]
DAN (VOICEOVER): That was the day it all ended.
That was the day you killed your son.
[LOUD ROCK MUSIC]
I want you to wait, wait, on the count of three-- OK?
One, two, three--
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(YELLING) Yeah, let's get him.
Yeah--
Woo--
[SIRENS]
What are we gonna do?
(YELLING) Get out of the car-- now.
Cathy, want a ride?
No thanks.
Why not?
I'd rather walk.
DAN: Well, you're gonna be late.
I don't care.
Yeah, me neither.
Feel like going to school?
Not really.
Nah, me neither.
Hop in.
So what happened?
My dad wasn't happy about what happened last night.
And he was drunk, as usual.
I hate him.
I wish he were dead.
You are so lucky your dad doesn't live with you.
Yeah.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[YELLING]
Who's the woman?
[INAUDIBLE]
Come on, Dan.
Be a warrior.
Wimp-- come on, wimp.
If I did it, you can do it.
OK, I'm gonna do it.
OK, one, two, three--
[CHEERING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Ha, I wish my old man would go out of town permanently.
I don't even have a dad.
You could say I have a coach for a dad.
You can say I have that, OK?
Through my whole life, I had to sit and watch my brother
and my father come in and worship their trophies.
My brother is more like the son the he wanted, you know?
Can't do nothing about it.
Makes me so mad.
You know, it's-- to you, I could see--
at least your dad hits you.
My dad doesn't do anything.
You get some kind of attention.
You know, my dad just doesn't hit me for attention.
I don't know what you're talking about.
My dad loves me.
What are you laughing at?
No, I'm serious.
My daddy has a hard time, you know.
He works long hours.
And he comes home, and he expects me to be there.
And when I'm not there, he gets mad.
And he's always drinking.
He really loves me.
I don't why you'd say something like that.
Sorry.
There's nothing with my father.
It's me.
I come home, and I'm late.
And I don't get the grades that I want to get.
I get a B+, and he gets angry, and that's all.
NORMAN: That's not all.
Yes, it is all.
And I don't appreciate you talking to me like that.
My father loves me, and he's a good man.
And he really tries to-- take care of me.
And he's always taken care of me,
because there's no one else to take care of him.
Because my mother died, OK?
[CAR]
[SHOUT]
It's Annie.
[COUGHING]
OK.
Annie--
Annie, hey.
You're here.
Oh, man.
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
I need to talk to you guys.
Ah, come on.
Happy birthday-- we need to sing happy birthday.
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
I need to talk you guys.
I made this for you.
I-- I need to talk to you guys.
I really do. -Here.
Are you all right?
[INAUDIBLE]
Yeah, I'm fine now.
[LAUGHTER]
OK, sorry Dad.
Dad--
Shh-- shh.
I-- I need to talk to you guys.
Sipping Dad's beer.
I--I lied to you guys about some stuff.
And-- well, I feel kind of-- kind of crummy about it.
And all those times I got flowers
at school and everything, and-- and I told you,
you know, they were from my dad, well, I lied.
Truth is, I didn't really know my dad.
I met him one time.
I just found out where he's living again.
I wrote this poem.
I wanted you guys to hear it.
I'm gonna send it to my dad.
Was it something I said?
Was something I did?
Having a fatherless life as a kid.
When I was a little girl, my father gone away.
And although it's many years ago, it seems like yesterday.
The fantasy of what he'd be was a beautiful dream.
He's a handsome knight in shining armor.
His chivalry makes me beam.
But another father steps in.
And another day gone by.
And the months turn to years.
More heartache builds up inside.
But that handsome knight in shining
armor-- he's gonna come riding up one day.
And he's gonna rescue me from a father figure that
brings me nothing but misery.
One day, my fantasy father stepped in.
All I could ask him was where have you been?
15 years old and coming face to face
with a father who'd been nothing but the family disgrace.
Should I hug him, kiss him, run from him, or say I love you?
Now the pain of meeting the real you-- you're
no handsome knight in shining armor,
just a pitiful, self indulgent fool.
Go away, Dad.
Please, please, please go away.
Come back little fantasy.
I want to live my yesterday.
[LAUGHTER]
CATHY: We should've put her birthday present on.
Guys--
DAN: What's wrong?
CATHY: I don't know.
I don't know-- oh no, oh-- no, no, no.
Annie, Annie, Annie, Annie--
[SCREAMING]
CATHY: Why is this happening?
Why is this--
[SCREAMING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
What's up, Dan?
Hey, man.
Yo, Dan, where you going?
Yo Dan-- Dan, wait up.
Dan-- Dan--
Dan--
-Danny-- -Norman--
Norman--
Wait up.
What's wrong, man?
You're not even hanging out with us anymore.
-I've been busy. -Busy?
You've been busy for the past two months.
Dan, what's wrong?
I want to work.
I want to do something with my life.
Life?
We're just kids, Dan.
Don't be so serious.
I just want to do something with the future.
All work and no play makes Dan a dull boy.
I'm a man.
Sorry-- make Dan a dull man.
Look I just-- I wanna be somebody, somebody important,
you know, somebody that my-- you know,
that people will be proud of.
I don't wanna end up like Annie.
Come on, man.
Annie's death was not your fault.
There's nothing you can do to change that.
And there's nothing you can do to change the world.
Yeah, but I can change myself.
And that's what I'm gonna do.
I don't know what's gotten into you, Dan.
I gotta go.
NORMAN: Well, I'll catch you later, man.
DAN (VOICEOVER): We were never a church
going family-- full of weak-minded hypocrites,
you said.
But Mom somehow managed to sneak off to Sunday service.
She never stopped praying for you or for me.
Those prayers finally took hold, and I
went to meet with the pastor.
They were no hypocrites, Dad-- just people like you and me
trying to find their way.
And I learned there was someone who loved me unconditionally,
who gave his life for me and would always be there for me.
I knew it was time to make a change.
Dearest Mom, wile growing up, it was
very difficult to understand and appreciate all you did for me.
It's only now as an adult that I am able to reflect back
on my life and begin to understand the loving
influence you had on me.
Thank you for picking me up during the difficult years
and for believing in me.
It is only because of your unfailing,
self-sacrificing love that I have become who I am.
Without your encouragement, I would be nowhere.
Without your prayers, I dread the thought.
Train up a child in the way he should go, and when he is old,
he will not turn from it.
I see your face whenever I read that verse.
And I pray that someday, I can give my child the same gifts
you have given me.
Happy Mother's Day-- your son Dan.
[GROAN]
[LAUGHTER]
Woo-- huh, looks a lot better now that we own it.
Sure does.
Oh--
Ah, well, we don't need this thing anymore.
You've taken on quite a responsibility.
It's quite a project.
I'm ready for it.
A lot of sacrifice for a young man.
I know, but I want to do it.
I'm very proud of you.
Thanks, Mom.
Yeah?
Hi, I'm Dan, the new landlord.
You mean you're the landlord's son.
Nope, I'm the landlord.
Yeah, well, you're a kid.
You're the landlord?
Uh, I know, but, uh, I'm him.
Uh, so what seems to be the problem?
The problem?
Well, everything-- the, uh, roof leaks.
The ceiling is caving in.
That faucet in the kitchen keeps me awake all night.
And the heat only works when it wants to, usually if it's hot.
Wow.
Looks like I better get started.
Um, can I come in?
Be my guest.
Excuse me.
So, um, where's the leak at?
Kitchen.
DAN (VOICEOVER): When I was a child, I spoke like a child.
I-- understood like a child.
I thought like a child.
When I became a man, I put away my childish things.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, bud.
Hey, Dad.
How you doing?
Good-- you?
Fine.
So, what's this letter about?
Didn't you read it?
Look, I'm not the cause for your messed up family life.
Your mother is.
Looks like nothing has changed in 18 years, has it?
What's that supposed to mean?
You're still blaming other people for your problems.
She divorced me, remember?
I wanted my family.
I wanted things to stay the way they were.
You know, when I was a kid, all I
ever wanted was to grow up to be just like my dad, my hero.
You should be proud to be like me.
Proud of what-- being bitter over my past?
I'm not bitter.
That's exactly what you are.
Look, I know, because I'm just like you.
I used to be angry with you, but as you get older,
the anger just turns to bitterness.
Look, I worked every day to support you and your mother.
I built a house for you both to live in
and taught you all the skills to make a good living.
And what did I get out it?
What did I get, Dad-- a life of pain,
and life of watching my father living with another family?
She divorced me.
No.
You divorced her by failing to live up
to your marriage commitments.
She wanted to change me.
No, Dad.
No.
She wanted you to love and respect her.
Was that asking too much?
She didn't know what she wanted.
And what she had was never enough.
That's why she divorced Tony.
No.
She divorced Tony because he was as abusive as you were.
It was a tough time she went through
after she divorced Tony.
That's what's-- that's what's causing all this pain.
He's caused the problem, not me.
Stop blaming other people.
Well, if your mother had run off with Tony,
we'd have still been together.
She didn't run off with Tony.
That's another lie.
What about all the nights I cried myself to sleep?
What about me?
You don't think I ever cried myself to sleep?
I have feelings too, you know.
After 13 years of marriage, a family, a house I
built with my own hands, what did I have to show for it?
Huh?
Nothing-- no house, no family, no marriage.
Well, you sure found another family quick.
And when you did, you forgot all about me.
I have a life too, you know.
Didn't I spend every other weekend with you
and send your mother child support?
Oh, that's real supportive.
You blamed my mother for the divorce
and made me suffer for your anger.
That's not true.
You make her out to be the enemy
then send me on like a wind up time
bomb to explode in her face.
You know what that does to a 9-year-old child?
I just got a divorce.
I was angry.
When you're angry, you just-- say things.
Look, I called you to tell you what I thought.
I was fighting to hold back the tears,
because boys aren't supposed to cry.
And I asked you why you never called me.
You remember that call?
Yeah, I remember.
Why didn't you ever call me?
Hey, I'm not a phone person.
And what was with that picture, huh?
That was the day I killed my son.
That was the way I felt.
Just because I didn't want you to put
your arms around my neck?
You backed away and said, what's with the arm?
I just don't like anybody to put their arms around my neck.
I'm not just anybody, Dad.
I'm your son.
I love you.
Don't you see what this is all about, Dad?
Loving each other, growing together as a family,
teaching your children right from wrong,
being there for them when they need you-- that's life, Dad.
What you want from me?
Your respect.
It's always been there.
I've never felt it.
I can only go by--by what you do and say.
Look, I can't live my life with bitterness.
I need to be free to love and to be loved.
I think it's time for me to hit the road.
OK.
Thanks for coming.
Mhm.
Look, I want you to understand that I
don't blame you for anything that's happened,
and that I love you.
And I forgive you.
And my door is always open.
Guess we don't have much in common.
We're related.
That we are.
My father, your old dad-- shaking hands
was always the manly thing to do.
He worked very hard, then he died.
That's life.
I gotta go, bud.
I love you, Dad.
[MUSIC - JEREMY CAMP, "NOTHING ELSE I NEED"]
[KNOCKING]
DAN: Hi.
I've never done this before, but will you spend
the rest of your life with me?
[MUSIC - JEREMY CAMP, "NOTHING ELSE I NEED"]
DAN (VOICEOVER): One thing I've learned over the years is
that miracles still happen every day--
a prayer answered, finding true love, the birth of a child.
My miracle was the day my father knocked on my door
and asked to be a part of my life again-- my family's life.
All right, Mikey-- now I'm gonna fake a hand off to you,
and you go along-- OK?
OK.
Ready?
Hut-- Yeah-- Good toss.
Go.
[MUSIC - JEREMY CAMP, "EVEN WHEN"]