(foreboding music)
(traffic whooshing)
(tires screeching)
(crash banging)
(glass shattering)
(fire crackling)
(distant siren alarming)
(pleasant flute music)
- There was a car
wreck last night.
Your mom's in the hospital.
(gentle piano music)
Do you understand, Lily?
(dramatic tempo music)
(footsteps thumping)
Did you get a nap?
Well, should we
get you cleaned up
and in some fresh clothes?
- I'm fine.
- Okay.
Was Grandma Beth still napping?
- Can we go to the hospital?
I want to see her.
- I know but we can't right now.
- [Lily] I want
to stay with her.
- You can't.
- Why not?
- Because hospitals have rules.
This is gonna take
patience, okay?
You can help with Grandma Beth.
- I don't want to
help with Grandma,
I wanna stay with Mom.
- A routine is gonna
be good for all of us.
(birds chirping)
(atmosphere whooshing)
(chimes clinking)
(birds chirping)
(eerie music)
(unsettling music)
(thunder rumbling)
(dramatic tempo music)
- You're leaving?
- Yeah, I gotta go to work.
I'm sorry that you have
to stay here all day
but I haven't been
able to figure out
any of the arrangements.
If you have any issues,
you just call me, okay?
The number's on the fridge.
There's plenty of sandwich
stuff if you get hungry
and we'll talk when
I get home, okay?
(piano keys clinking)
(birds chirping)
- We should go to
the hospital anyway.
I don't know.
Hitch hick?
Of course I don't
wanna be kidnapped.
Why would you even ask that?
- [Man] Little bird.
(somber string music)
- Lily?
Well hello, sweetheart!
- Hi.
Why don't you guys have a TV?
- We have books.
You aren't going to tell me
that you prefer TV
to books, are you?
- TV is fun.
(Beth chuckling)
- If fun is having someone just
zap things into your brain.
Here.
- Thanks.
- There's nothing real about TV.
It's not like the
stories in books.
- There's nothing
real about stories.
- Nothing real?
Come on.
I have trouble remembering
things, did you know that?
- Aunt Martha told me.
- Just little things, really.
Ah, here it is.
These are some sketches
from the last thing
I was working on,
"The Farmer and the Fire Elf."
- The Fire Elf
isn't a real thing.
- So you say.
Do you wanna hear it?
- Where are the words?
- All up here.
Once there was a goodly farmer
who lives with his lovely wife
right on this land, in fact.
(pleasant flute music)
One day, when he was
tending his field,
there was an earthquake that
shook the ground under his feet
and rattled him to his bones.
(dramatic music)
The earth split and a great
hole opened next to the farmer,
who walked to the edge
and peered inside.
(ominous music)
- What was inside?
- I'm note sure you're
ready for this story yet.
As the farmer was
looking into the hole,
a small man, caked in ash and
cinders, was crawling out.
The farmer was scared
something fierce
as he watched the small man
shake the cinders from his coat.
- Was the man magic?
- [Beth] There was magic in
him but it was a dark magic,
for it was not a man who
crawled out of the hole
but a fire elf.
(sinister music)
The elf told the farmer that
he had come to grant him
whatever he wished if only
the farmer would allow him
passage across his land
and out into the world.
Well, the farmer
quickly surmised
that there was evil
in this creature.
So he told the elf that
he wanted nothing from him
and that he would not allow
him to pass across his land
but that rather he
should go back down
the hole from which he came.
Well the elf was furious
that the farmer would not
let him pass across his land.
He vowed to do whatever he
could to hurt the farmer.
(ominous music)
So one night, he stole
into the farmer's house...
(eerie music)
and took the very
heart from his world.
(sinister music)
- [Lily] Heart?
- All those things we
love and hold most dear.
In this case, it was the
health of the farmer's wife,
who soon became ill and
was confined to her bed.
The elf took the heart and
broke it into three pieces
which he placed with
three bewitched subjects
in three other worlds.
He gave one piece to a maiden
and cast a spell
of vanity on her.
He gave a second
piece to a writer,
and cast a spell of
melancholy on him.
The third piece he
gave to an astronomer,
then cast him out, lost
into a starless void.
The farmer was heartbroken.
The next evening,
he left his wife in
the care of a neighbor
and set out to seek
the pieces of the heart
and save his wife.
- How did the
farmer go traveling?
To the other worlds, I mean.
- Just after sundown, when the
worlds are closest together,
that's when you can travel.
You must close your eyes and
picture where you want to go
because you want the
place you are seeking
to also be seeking you.
When you open your eyes,
you must be very quiet
and keep a keen eye.
- Have you gone?
- Oh no, it takes a lot
of courage to travel
and he waits out
there, bitter as ever,
looking for a way
out into our world.
- What happened to the farmer?
- Oh, he went looking
for the pieces.
Perhaps the Fire
Elf captured him.
- I thought it was true.
- It is true.
I just have to
remember all the parts.
- Can the heart
make people better?
- Certainly.
If you know where to
look for the pieces.
And if you have the right
things to go traveling with.
- What things?
(lively tempo music)
- A whole bag of tricks.
- [Lily] The farmer
took a sewing bag?
- Oh, I doubt it.
But all travelers must
have their own things.
- That's not a true story.
- I don't tell tall tales.
- What happened next?
- I'll give it some thought
and see if I can remember.
You can hang on to
them if you like.
(pleasant flute music)
(somber music)
- [Man] Little bird.
(Lily gasping)
Little bird.
(ominous music)
(birds chirping)
Little bird.
(somber flute music)
(somber horn music)
(ominous music)
(steam sizzling)
Little bird.
(lively tempo music)
(doors thudding)
- Help!
Help!
(fire rumbling)
(ominous music)
- What do we have here?
A little traveler?
- Let me out.
- Perhaps we can be of some...
use to each other.
- What?
- You're searching for a
way to save someone, yes?
Your poor mother.
I'm...
very sorry, indeed.
I could help her if you like.
- You can?
- Oh yes.
I could heal her.
Good as new.
But in turn,
you...
must do one simple thing...
for me.
- What?
- All you need to do...
is invite me...
to pass out of this land.
- I can't.
- Of course you can.
- I know what you are.
(elf hissing)
- You place your
hopes in the heart.
You shall never find it.
- Maybe I will.
- No, child.
I'm your only hope.
- No.
- Your mother may
not live much longer.
- That's not true.
- I know death,
little one.
I know grief and misery
and I doubt you're brave
enough, little bird.
(elf laughing)
(fire rumbling)
Good luck.
(sinister music)
(suspenseful music)
(bird cooing)
- Mom will get better.
We don't need him.
(crickets chirping)
- [Beth] I don't want to
wear this dress, it's old.
- [Martha] It's just
a nightgown, Mother.
- [Beth] I told the little
girl we need to leave,
that he won't stop
until she's dead.
- [Martha] Who?
- [Beth] That
woman, the sick one.
He'll come for her soon
too, mark my words.
I told the child all about it.
- Sleep well, mother.
You know she confuses
things, right?
Why don't you go ahead
and get ready for bed?
I'll start you a bath.
- I can do it.
She doesn't tell tall tales.
- They're only stores, Lily.
(water faucet spraying)
(gentle string music)
- [Beth] Just after sundown,
when the worlds are
closest together,
that's when you can travel.
(unsettling music)
(atmosphere whooshing)
(water bubbling)
(suspenseful music)
(thunder rumbling)
(music intensifying)
(dramatic music)
(water bubbling)
(suspenseful music)
(cannons booming)
(foreboding music)
(gentle music)
(pleasant instrumental music)
- What in God's...
Have you been in the
bath this whole time?
Look at this mess.
- It just happened.
- Get to bed.
(Martha sighing)
- Don't worry, I
won't try that again.
- It's got some
cracks in the paint
but I'll take care of it.
- [Martha] How much
more is that gonna cost?
- [Man] Ah, it's easy,
don't worry about it.
- Thanks.
- [Man] Sam, bring
me a paint scraper.
- Hey.
- You living here?
- Just visiting my
aunt and grandma.
- Your aunt used to babysit me.
When I was younger, I mean.
- I bet that was fun.
- How'd the tub flood?
- I did it.
But...
I fell asleep.
- Oh.
My dad said your grandma's
having memory things.
- She still remembers
a lot though.
- She used to tell me all kinds
of stories about traveling
in other worlds and stuff.
- That's what I
was dreaming about,
a story she told me when
I fell asleep in the tub.
It's stupid.
- No.
I love her stories,
there were cool.
- Yeah, like almost real.
- Yeah.
I mean, they aren't but,
well, you never know.
- [Man] Sam, paint scraper!
- Here you go.
If you go traveling.
My dad said to check it
but it still kinda works.
- Thanks.
No problem.
(truck engine rumbling)
- I'll be back as
soon as I'm off.
(Lily crunching)
(foreboding music)
(Lily gasping)
(Beth crying)
- Oh.
- What's wrong, Grandma?
- Jane.
- Mom is in the hospital.
- I don't understand how.
(dramatic music) (Beth crying)
- We're going to find the
pieces of the heart for Mom.
That's what we're going to do.
(pleasant flute music)
Stop being such a worry wart.
Yes, I know I almost drowned.
You have to picture
where you want to go.
I didn't do that.
Yes, I do know where
to picture going.
Well, how am I supposed to know
what all this stuff is for?
Well, are you coming or not?
(Lily sighing)
The Maiden.
(lively chiming music)
(exciting music)
(gentle flute music)
(somber music)
(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
(somber music)
Well, it's better than ending
up underwater, I guess.
(somber instrumental music)
(gentle string music)
(eerie music)
(suspenseful music)
That was close.
Did he look familiar to you?
(somber horn music)
(birds chirping)
Hello?
- One moment while I get ready.
No, this won't do.
No, this won't do at all.
(pleasant harp music)
- I think it's lovely.
- Yes, it is.
But what would a
little girl know?
(birds chirping)
- Those birds sound beautiful.
- Birds?
Be a good girl and
stop distracting me.
I won't be long.
(somber music)
- Can you help me?
- Ah, I may have something
that will fit you.
- No, I'm looking for...
for a heart.
- Let's try this one.
- It's very pretty.
- Here.
(birds chirping)
A few more touches.
- It's nice but...
- How beautiful
that looks on you.
- It looks pretty?
- Oh, indeed, and there is
no substitute for beauty.
Beauty is the outward shine
of a happy and righteous soul.
- I don't know.
- There's no injury too
deep and no pain too great
that beauty cannot reconcile.
- Really?
- Oh, yes.
To be beautiful is to have
the sun shining upon you
for all others to see.
- What about someone who
is pretty but isn't nice?
- Simply impossible, dear.
How we look is who we are.
(gentle music)
There.
See?
Do you not feel happy?
(gentle string music)
- Nicole said I was ugly.
- What?
Of course you're not ugly.
Nicole must be blind as a bat.
(Jane chuckling)
You are very pretty.
- Nicole is prettier.
- That's not true.
And that's not what's important.
It's not about what's
on the surface.
I mean, that's all
that mirror shows,
not what's underneath and
that's where the real beauty is,
the kind of person you are.
So don't you go
getting stuck in there.
(Jane chuckling)
(pleasant music)
(birds chirping)
(ominous music)
(glass shattering)
- What have you done?
(dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
What is that sweet sound?
- The birds outside.
- Maybe a short
moment to listen?
(pleasant music)
Perhaps more feathers.
(lively instrumental music)
(drum cymbals crashing)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(birds chirping)
(pleasant music)
I've forgotten how lovely
the nights are here.
- Can you help me?
- [Maiden] Of course, child.
- I'm looking for a
heart or part of one.
- A heart.
Oh, yes.
(atmosphere whooshing)
(birds chirping)
- Thank...
(sinister music)
I knew that man in
rags looked familiar.
The Fire Elf
must've trapped him.
Ow.
- Morning.
What in the world?
Why didn't you come get me?
Well, it's just a small
cut, thank goodness.
How did you cut yourself?
- I don't know.
- All right, well come on.
All right.
Is there anything you wanna
tell me, to talk about?
Why don't you go
ahead and get dressed?
I'll go make breakfast.
Lily, I need you to
come down here, please!
You may not wanna
talk about things
but I need you to explain this.
- I'm just trying to help Mom.
I went through there,
into a mansion,
and there was a man in rags
and there was a maiden too.
She was trying on
al these dresses
and there were tons of mirrors.
- Please stop.
I know that you're confused
but lying to me will only
make this entire thing worse.
What? (gentle string music)
- Why do you hate me?
- I don't.
Not at all.
(Martha sighing)
Honey,
you know that there is a chance
that your mom won't
wake up, right?
- She will!
- It was a very back
wreck and you know that...
- You're horrible!
I wish you never
brought me here!
- Lily, come back!
(gentle music)
(flashlight clicking)
(door knocking)
- Can you tell me
more of the story?
- You mean the story
about the rabbit
who accidentally
learned to speak French?
- I'd like to hear
that one day but...
- How about a snack?
(birds chirping)
- Talked to the doctors today.
Your mom's still in a coma
but they say the pressure
on her brain's reduced.
So that's good news.
- Can we go see her, please?
- We can go on Saturday.
It's the next time I'm off.
(crickets chirping)
- [Beth] You're just so
sweet to an old lady.
- [Martha] Thank you, Mom.
- [Beth] I do hope they
give you a raise soon.
- Goodnight.
(crickets chirping)
(lively tempo music)
We can't sissy out now.
You heard, we're helping Mom.
I know Aunt Martha's mad.
You'd think for a bird that
could fly away anytime,
you'd be a little bit more bold.
(lively horn music)
The Writer.
(exciting instrumental music)
(wind howling)
(gentle music)
Yes, I know that's
Aunt Martha's room.
(gentle flute music)
(somber string music)
(Martha snoring)
(Martha groaning)
(lively tempo music)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(books clattering)
(Martha gasping)
(Martha groaning)
(somber flute music)
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me.
(lively tempo music)
(somber instrumental music)
(ominous music)
(mystical music)
(eerie music)
(suspenseful music)
- [Writer] No, nope.
Nope, no, no, no.
No,
No. (somber horn music)
(writer groaning)
(paper ruffling)
- Hello?
(writer groaning)
I'm looking for a piece
of a wooden heart.
Have you seen one lying around?
- No!
- You sure?
- What's that?
- Are you the writer?
- Well, I don't know
about "the" writer
but I am a writer.
At least, that's what
I believed I was.
- What're you writing about?
- Well that's the
thing, isn't it?
That's the very thing.
Well, see, it's supposed
to be something light,
something guaranteed
to bring smiles
to the faces of the guests
but I can't seem to
strike the right chord.
They start light enough and
then devolve into gloom,
misery.
- People like sad
stories sometimes.
- Well, yes,
but this request comes
from the King, himself,
for the Princess' birthday.
- Want some help?
(writer chuckling)
- You know, that might
be just the thing.
Perhaps you could help me,
being as how you are a child
with innocent intentions.
You do have innocent
intentions, correct?
What I mean to say is you're
not a wild phantom beast
with a transmorphing spell
cast upon you, are you?
That would be just my luck.
- Uh, no.
- Good!
It would be extremely
inconvenient to be eaten alive
at this particular juncture.
Come!
Here, come.
Come, sit.
(upbeat flute music)
Give me a subject.
- How about...
a unicorn?
- I had a pet unicorn once.
- Really?
- Really.
Glorious magical beasts.
No one mentions the
flatulence, however.
(writer chuckling)
Okay, go on.
- What if it was
ridden by a prince?
- Yes.
Ah.
- And he's on a quest.
- Quest, yes.
- To save his entire kingdom
from an army that wants
to take over his people.
- All right!
The prince gathers
an army of his own.
The army is proud
and determined.
(army men shouting)
The prince leads them
forth to a glorious battle.
(writer neighing)
During which,
the prince is knocked
from his steed.
(writer yelping)
As the battle rages around him,
the prince struggles to
get his feet under him.
Just as he stands, a giant
stone from a cannonball
smashes him flat.
(prince screaming)
The army flees in terror.
(writer screaming)
(army men screaming)
Another stone smashes
his one-horned steed.
- What?
You can't kill the
prince, he's the hero.
- Oh.
Did I just kill the hero?
- Yes, and a unicorn.
- Oh no!
No!
Could you imagine what
the children would think?
- They probably wouldn't
like it very much.
- The King would probably
separate me from my head.
- Sounds like you'd
pretty much hate it.
They should live forever.
- No one lives forever.
(somber music)
- They can in a
story, can't they?
- Perhaps.
But will that be true to life?
- We'll just have to start over.
- What's the use?
They all end the same way.
I should've been a mason
or a baker.
One is unlikely to lose one's
head over yeast and rolls.
I am worthless!
Worthless!
(writer screaming)
- What a drama queen.
Well, there's no time
for wallowing in sorrow.
(writer groaning)
You need to think about something
else or do something fun.
- What's the use?
- My mom and I dance in
the kitchen sometimes.
I bet it would make
you feel better.
- I wrote a story about
a dancer earlier today.
It ended in a
gruesome house fire.
(radio buzzing)
- Come on. (upbeat
radio music)
- Oh well, I suppose
there's nothing to lose.
- That's the spirit.
- I'll probably get a cramp.
(upbeat violin radio music)
(upbeat band music)
Ugh.
Well, you were certainly
right about the dancing.
Thank you for your help.
You know, this place
is awfully dramatic.
I think I'll find a
more suitable place
to write this lighthearted fare.
Be sure to write me
whenever you wish.
I would love to hear from you.
Goodbye.
- Wait!
Can you tell me where to
find the wooden heart?
- You mean that one?
(chiming music)
- Thanks.
(gentle music)
We have to be quiet.
(Lily sighing)
Aunt Martha's house.
(ominous music)
(ominous tempo music)
- How clever you must feel.
(elf laughing)
Two pieces.
Well done.
I know a secret.
I know you're not brave
enough to save her!
Not when you can't
even admit the truth!
I'll have her soon!
Very soon!
(elf hissing)
(gentle music)
- Ha, we're too quick for him.
(somber flute music)
Oh no.
- Come here.
Why would you do this?
- I didn't do it.
- Lily, why would
you tear up my books?
- I told you, it wasn't me!
- Then who?
- You don't know everything.
You think that Mom's going
to die but she's not!
- I don't think that.
- Yes you do!
You just want me to
forget about her.
- Of course I don't
want you to forget her.
I want you to talk about...
- Then why won't
you let me see her?
- That is not what I'm doing.
You have to understand
that things are really
tight right now.
We will go see your
mom as soon as we can.
I do think it would
help if we could talk.
If we could talk about, if
we could talk about people,
if we could talk
about people dying.
- Why?
She's going to get better.
- Lily, that's not what I...
(dramatic music)
That's not what I meant.
Uh-huh.
No, extra hours
are fine next week.
Yeah, thank you again.
Thanks.
(Martha crying)
(dramatic string music)
(Martha knocking)
Let's go see your mom.
We have to be quick, okay,
I only have half a day.
(pleasant flute music)
(gentle piano music)
Come on, Mom.
It's Jane.
- That's not...
- Yeah.
(gentle piano music)
Mom,
do you wanna sit down?
Okay.
- I'm gonna fix it all.
- I told you, that's why.
That's why we...
- It's okay.
It's okay.
You know,
sometimes we want
things to be real
or things not to have happened.
We can want them so much
that we ignore the truth.
(Lily sighing)
- We have to find the
last piece tonight.
We have to.
How does the story end?
- The story?
- The Farmer and the Fire Elf.
- [Beth] A twist.
- [Lily] Huh?
- The story has a twist.
They all do.
The farmer searched and searched
but the Fire Elf had one more
trick up his dark sleeve.
- What happened?
Did the farmer win
against the Fire Elf?
- I don't quite remember.
But if he did win,
one thing is certain,
the solution came from a
place we didn't expect.
Usually from right here.
- [Martha] You should
eat some dinner, Mom.
- I don't like this.
- You like pasta.
- What else do they have here?
- I think that's all
that's on the menu tonight.
- What kind of a place
only serves one thing?
- They were so busy that
they ran out of everything.
- Oh.
(gentle flute music)
Well.
- Can I be excused?
- Mm-hmm.
(somber music)
(lively music)
- If you don't wanna
come, you don't have to.
Of course you do.
The Astronomer.
(exciting instrumental music)
(somber orchestral choir music)
(somber instrumental music)
(wall crackling)
Whoa.
You gotta see this place.
(ominous tempo music)
(clocks ticking)
What do you mean, which way?
There's nothing.
(machinery clanking)
(dramatic orchestral
choir music)
(clocks ticking)
Hello?
Hold on tight.
(somber orchestral choir music)
(steam hissing)
(pleasant orchestral
choir music)
Excuse me?
I was hoping you could help me.
- How have you come here?
- From...
There was a rope.
You speak English?
- I speak many languages.
You've been imprisoned as well?
- No, I asked to come here.
- So you can take us away.
- I can try.
(gentle instrumental music)
Aunt Martha's house.
It's easier to go
than to get back.
I'm sorry.
What are you looking at?
- I'm looking for a
point of reference.
- A what?
- Something that can
show me where here is.
- You don't know where we are?
- No.
- And there's nothing out there?
- See for yourself.
(wheel creaking)
(gentle vocalization music)
- No stars.
- None.
(gentle vocalization music)
- If there's nothing up there,
why do you keep looking?
- Does your kind like
the company of others?
- We like being
with our families.
- The same is true for my kind.
If we're separated or alone,
we're very unhappy.
- So everyone is gone?
- No.
Most likely, we're just
beyond the edge of the stars,
very far away.
- Same thing, I guess.
- Untrue.
Existing and not existing
are very different things.
Everything came
from the same speck.
The stars, the planets,
the atoms in your skin,
and everything can feel
the pull of everything else
and one day all those things
will pull each other
together again,
back to the same bright point.
Eventually, we will
all be one again.
(crickets chirping)
- [Lily] How many are there?
- More than grains
of sand on the beach.
- And they are very far away?
- Yes but they all came
from the same place.
(pleasant music)
(lively tempo music)
- We just need something
else out there.
- That's precisely what
I've been looking for.
(pleasant flute music)
What are those?
- They're stars.
- I've seen many stars
but none like those.
- Everything came from
the same place, right?
(pleasant instrumental music)
- Very curious!
(suspenseful music)
What have you done?
- I don't know.
(gentle music)
(spacecraft whooshing)
(dramatic tempo music)
(insects chirping)
- Will you join us?
- I have to get back home,
to my people.
- Thank you, little traveler.
(spacecraft humming)
(atmosphere whooshing)
(crickets chirping)
(music chiming)
(pleasant flute music)
- [Beth] I told you, I am
not ready to go to bed yet!
This is my house
and you work here
and I'd like you
to remember that!
- Can you please?
- Will, don't touch!
Get your filthy hands off me.
- Look...
- You can't just go around
touching people like that!
- I just...
- And you can't bring people
into my house without
my permission.
I won't allow it!
Shoo, get!
Who is that?
Who is this child that you
have brought into my house
without even asking me about it?
You've never asked
for my permission,
you never even told me
it was going to happen.
- [Martha] Mom,
please, just calm...
- [Beth] Oh, just
leave me alone!
(door thudding)
(eerie music)
(fire crackling)
- Did you misplace
something, little bird?
- Give it back.
- Why would I give back
something that belongs to me?
- It's not yours.
- Do you think the true heart
would be made of simple wood?
You think a heart can be mended
by simply putting the
pieces back together?
- What?
(sinister music)
No!
(fire whooshing)
(sinister music)
No!
- I told you you're not strong
enough to find what you seek!
Now,
allow me into this
world and I'll save her.
- I don't believe you.
- Come now, child.
You can believe me.
- No.
- So be it.
(ominous music)
Your mother...
will soon drift...
away.
- No.
(dramatic music)
(gentle flute music)
(birds chirping)
(somber tempo music)
(glass clinking)
Grandma?
(birds chirping)
- [Sam] Hi.
- Hey.
- What're you up to?
- Nothing.
- Where are you going?
- None of your business.
- Sorry.
I'm going to the
hospital to see my mom.
- Isn't that a long way away?
- Yeah.
- Hey, that flashlight
come in handy?
- Yeah.
- My dad told me about
the wreck, about your mom.
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- Okay.
My mom died like two
years ago from cancer.
- I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
It was like so unfair.
- I bet you miss her a lot.
I mean, I'm sure you do.
- Yeah.
Your grandma watched me
when my dad had to work.
She kinda always knew what to
say when I was feeling bad.
- Do you think about
your mom a lot?
- Yeah.
I mean, I would've done anything
to save her but, you know.
- Anything?
- Yeah.
You want me to come with you?
- It's probably too far away.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
- Where are you?
Where are you?
- [Elf] Over here.
- I'll do it.
I'll let you pass
into this world
but I want more time
to find the heart.
(ominous music)
- [Elf] No more
time, little bird.
- Then I won't let you in.
(elf chuckling)
- [Elf] Because
this is so very fun,
I'll give you one more night.
- That's not enough time.
- [Elf] That is my offer.
(ominous music)
(gentle music)
- I bet the Fire Elf
has the heart with him.
That's what Grandma
meant by a twist.
We have to go if we're
going to find the real one.
(lively tempo music)
- [Beth] And he waits out
there, bitter as ever,
looking for a way
out into our world.
- The Fire Elf.
(dramatic music)
(lively tempo music)
(somber music)
Holy Moly.
(foreboding music)
(fire crackling)
(ominous music)
No!
There's that man in rags.
(gentle music)
(somber tempo music)
(fire crackling)
(water trickling)
(uplifting music)
(foreboding music)
(Lily sighing)
(elf slurping)
(eerie music)
(uplifting music)
(lively tempo music)
(ominous music)
- What do we have here?
(intense music)
(suspenseful music)
Run, run, run.
(dramatic music)
(fire rumbling)
- Aunt Martha's house!
Aunt Martha's house!
(atmosphere whooshing)
(liquid bubbling)
(fire crackling)
- You like your cage?
- No.
- [Elf] Aw.
- I have it and now
she'll get better.
- What did you
find, little bird?
(elf laughing)
- The real heart, I found it.
- Silly little bird.
Trapped in a cage.
You found nothing!
- I did, I...
No!
- The only lies are those
you've been telling yourself!
There's one thing
that remains true.
Across all worlds.
Everyone is eager
to bury their pain.
They're not strong
enough to face it.
The sun will soon
rise in your world
and your mother will
die while you're here.
Here in your cage.
(elf laughing) (ominous music)
- No!
Grandma, finish the
story, please, Grandma!
(dramatic music)
- [Beth] Little bird?
- Grandma?
Grandma, finish the
story, please, Grandma!
- Only you can do that.
- But I don't know
where to find the heart.
- You do but you
must be oh so brave.
- I'll try.
- Sometimes we must face things
that are full of
pain and sorrow.
That is the way of the world.
- I can't!
- You can.
Be a brave little bird.
- No, don't go!
(dramatic tempo music)
The man in rags.
(atmosphere whooshing)
(liquid trickling)
(dramatic music)
(sinister music)
- Your mom's in the hospital.
Your dad was driving
and the other car hit
the driver's side.
He didn't make it.
Do you understand, Lily?
Your dad died.
I am so sorry, honey.
Lily!
(dramatic instrumental music)
(gentle piano music)
- Everything came
from one point,
so we're all one thing.
(pleasant music)
- All the memories,
even the bad ones.
(uplifting music)
- [Elf] Give that to me!
(suspenseful music)
- Aunt Martha's...
(gentle flute music)
- [Elf] That belongs to me!
- No it doesn't.
- I'll have you all in cages!
Every...
last...
one of you.
- Come on then.
(sparks fizzling)
(Elf groaning)
You're the one who's
scared and weak.
- You live on people's
fears but I'm not scared.
- You...
should be...
(dramatic music)
(sparks fizzling)
(dramatic choir music)
(lively tempo music)
(fire crackling)
(Lily crying)
- Aunt Martha.
Aunt Martha.
Dad.
- It's okay.
(gentle piano music)
It's okay. (Lily crying)
It'll be.
(heart monitor beeping)
(pleasant tempo music)
(birds chirping)
- [Lily] No one lives forever.
Not even in stories.
But if you remember them,
maybe they're still kinda there.
I think so.
(gentle music)
- You missing her?
Me too.
- Do you guys
wanna hear a story?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
- You know, your Grandma,
she could tell great stories.
- The best.
- I know.
Once upon a time, there
was a happy little family.
They loved to dance
in the kitchen
and go watch the stars
outside at night together.
There was a mom,
a dad, their kid,
an aunt, (women laughing)
and a grandma.
One day, the little girl went
traveling to three worlds.
In the first world,
there was a maiden
and she had a spell
of vanity on her.
The second world,
in the second world,
there was a writer.
He had a spell...
(pleasant instrumental music)
(lively instrumental music)
(somber music)
(dramatic instrumental music)
(pleasant instrumental music)
(lively tempo music)
(ominous music)
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic instrumental music)