[dramatic music playing]
[speaking indistinctly]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
- [David] Hey, Jessica.
- Oh, hey! He has arrived.
- Okay, love you too. Bye. Hi!
- Hi!
- Are you Mr. Ashland, I guess?
- Yes.
- Uh, David, please call me David.
- Okay, David.
Sorry, I'm a little nervous
because I didn't know,
you're going to have a camera.
Well, I always keep my camera
with me because I never know
when I'm going
to catch the next big star.
Oh! Well, hopefully I'm it.
Ha, ha.
Well, you look absolutely great.
You mind if I just get a shot
of you here?
[Jessica] Well, okay.
Stunning! Wow, you look awesome.
[somber music playing]
[music fades]
[David breathes heavily]
[knocking on door, lock clicks]
[David] Well, hello there.
Welcome to Dallas.
Hi!
- How are you?
- I'm well. How are you?
- You found it all right?
- I did, yeah.
It was, uh, a little tricky on
the back roads, but it's fine.
Well, I hope you don't mind that
I've got this camera going on,
but, um, it's all part
of my audition process.
So, if you would tell me
your name.
[chuckles]
Laci Lee Bateman.
Laci Lee Bateman,
isn't that something.
You are a hundred million times
prettier than your pictures,
- I have to tell you that.
- [laughs]
- Thank you.
- Look at you!
- Oh.
- Oh, wow! My, my!
All right, um, would you like
to have a seat over here?
[Laci] Um, thank you so much,
yeah. Uh, Mr. Ashland, right?
- [David] David.
- David.
Call me David, please and, yes,
I'm glad you remembered my name.
David, hi!
So, um, well,
I hope you don't mind me
filming you like this right
now but the whole point...
No, natural in front
of the camera.
[David laughs]
Uh, good, good.
I'm glad to hear that.
Um, the whole point
of me doing this is now, um...
I'm, uh, auditioning
for the first reality
feature film.
Wow!
So, um, it's important
that I keep my, uh,
actors on film
as long as I can, you know,
and I'm trying to see
how they interact
with people all day long
with a camera on them all day.
Oh, okay. Yeah,
it's absolutely understandable.
- So, um... So how old are you?
- I am 19.
- 19 years old, wow!
- Yeah.
Well, uh,
you don't look 19 but...
I know, everyone tells me.
I get one of two reactions.
I either get you look
15 or you look 24.
So I'm kind of wondering
where I place in that range.
Wow, you are just stunning.
- Thank you.
- I'm sorry. I just, uh...
You make me blush.
[David laughs]
Well, I didn't expect you
to be so damn beautiful, God!
[laughs]
Thank you.
- So, uh...
- Yeah.
Tell me a little bit
about yourself right now.
Um, okay. Uh, my name
is Laci Lee Bateman...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...and I'm from Oklahoma.
- And, um...
- Let me guess.
- What?
- Durant.
Yeah, actually.
How did you know that?
Oh, just, uh, inkling suspicion.
I guess us Durantians, you know,
have a tendency to...
to display, uh, certain qualities.
So, okay, and are you still
living in Durant now?
Um, I actually, I'm trying right
now to move, uh, out to Los Angeles
but it's so expensive.
I mean,
I've been working for a while.
I've just been trying
to do all that so, you know.
- So, let me guess, Los Angeles.
- Yeah.
- To pursue your acting career?
- Acting career, yeah.
Um, I... You know, I...
I did a lot of the plays in high school
and I took all the
drama classes, and it was, um...
It was a really, really,
good experience and I absolutely loved it.
So, um, I would be really happy
if I could be an actress.
That's why I responded to your,
uh... your lovely, um...
- I'm sorry, I'm so nervous.
- That's okay.
- My ad in the paper.
- Yeah, your ad in the paper.
Well, I'm certainly happy
that you answered it.
Thank you.
So, um, anything else
you want to tell me
about yourself right now?
Like what?
Well, are you the only sibling
in your family?
Oh, no,
I have a younger brother.
Oh, you do.
And his name is Hunter
and he's ten.
- Wow.
- So he's... he's... he's cool.
And then I...
I had an older sister.
Um, but...
I hope you don't mind me,
you know,
- walking around you and such.
- No, it's fine.
I just, um,
want to get all angles of you.
So, let me tell you
what I had in mind.
I'd love that.
I'm auditioning for a feature film of...
A reality feature film.
Kind of like a reality
TV show but a movie.
Um...
I would like to follow you
around during the day
or part of the day
and, um, with the camera on you,
and to see how you interact
with people,
and things and me with a camera
on you the whole time.
I think, I'll be
very comfortable with that.
That...
that sounds really quite nice.
So, what do you say
we get going.
Okay.
And, um, you know, let's just
have a leisure afternoon
and we'll get to know
each other better, okay?
- That sounds wonderful.
- All right.
Okay, let's go. So, yeah,
I'm just parked up there so.
I'm parked on the street.
I hope that's okay.
- Yeah, that's fine.
- Oh. Um...
- [David] Here, I got it.
- Okay.
[lock clicks]
- [Laci] Great.
- After you.
[Laci]
Thank you so much.
Steep stairs.
- [David] Be careful, now.
- It's all right. I'm a dancer.
[somber music playing]
[David] Thank you so much
for being here.
[Katie] Thank you.
[David] So just have a seat
there while I shut the door.
- Perfect, perfect.
- [Katie] Okay.
All right, wow!
[laughs]
Do you mind
taking your hair down for me?
Um, sure. It's...
it's a little bit messy.
- Is that okay?
- I doubt that.
Wow!
Wow! Okay. All right.
So, you know,
I'm really, really, happy
you answered my...
posting for my audition.
Yeah, yeah.
You said something about, um,
a reality movie or reality show.
Yeah, a reality film.
You know,
I'm booking natural girls
being as natural as possible,
you know.
And to let their beauty shine
through, you know.
That's what's important.
Everything's real, all right?
Natural acting will scratch
that not actual acting.
Just beautiful girls
being themselves, okay?
Well, is there a plot or is...
is it...?
Well, yeah.
That's the neat thing.
I'm letting the girls
tell the story.
- Okay.
- All right?
That's a really good idea
Mr. Ashland. Ha, ha.
- David, please call me David.
- Okay, David.
All right. Okay.
So, let's get started.
Okay,
so if you can just hold that
just right under
your chin there.
[giggles]
And if you could
state your name.
I'm Katie Summers.
- And, uh, how old are you, Katie?
- I'm 20 years old.
- I just turned 20.
- 20 years old, wow!
One more year and I can drink.
Oh, I doubt that.
I'm sure you've been drinking.
[laughs]
Okay. All right.
So, um, now I know I told you
there was not a script here.
- Mm-hmm.
- All right?
But
it's really, really, important
that I see how my actors
respond to the script
that I'm going to give you.
- Okay?
- Okay.
So, I don't want you
to look at it now
because I want to...
want it to be spontaneous.
- Okay.
- All right.
So, I want you to read it
as if you were
a demented serial killer.
- Ha, ha, okay.
- Okay?
And you are taunting the media.
You're taunting cops.
You're taunting everybody
and, uh, you're making sort of
a game out of it, okay?
That's really important.
You're making a game out of it.
- Okay.
- All right?
Okay, so, uh, just be, a darker,
hot, demented version of yourself.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Like, you're a serial killer.
- Okay.
So, when I say go,
I want you to go, all right?
- Okay.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay go.
Do you like to watch?
Do you like to play?
Then get ready
for my little game.
I'll audition each girl.
For now, there will be five
and if you pay attention
to the clues
they just might get out alive,
or not.
[laughs]
Is that... is that okay?
You want me...
I can do it again.
- That was great.
- Okay.
You know, I couldn't have said
it better myself.
[somber music playing]
Now, don't forget, um,
I have to open the door for you
because it doesn't work, so.
- [David laughs]
- [car alarm buzzes]
- [David] Okay.
- Sorry.
[David laughs]
What was that?
[Laci] Oh, it just...
It makes that noise.
I don't know.
[car alarm chirps]
[Laci] Why is it doing that?
[door thudding]
It just doesn't work at all.
[David laughs]
- [David] That's all right. Let me just...
- I'm sorry.
Oh, you can sit...
Oh, what's that?
[David] Oh.
- It's a surprise for later.
- A surprise?
Yeah.
[car alarm wailing]
Sorry.
I told you, it's just...
It just...
[both laugh]
Sorry.
- It's all right.
- It just, um... Yeah, so.
- A temperamental car.
- It's temperamental.
[reverse alarm beeping]
- All right, then. Ready?
- Yeah.
- Great.
- So, where are we going?
Um, well, I actually have to run
and get an outfit
because I have a thing I have
to go to tonight, so, yeah.
Okay. Right on.
- I'm headed up.
- What?
- It's all right.
- It's the dangerous car.
It is. It's very...
- It'll kill ya.
- It'll kill ya!
You know, watch out!
- Yes, I know. It's hot, right?
- It sure is.
You can turn the air
conditioning on if you'd like.
[David] Okay.
Uh...
- How's that?
- Oh, that's perfect.
Thank you.
Yeah, I don't want, you know,
you don't want to get yourself
all sweaty and...
Of course.
- Like I am.
- Seat belt, David.
Oh, right.
- Seat belt.
- Whoa.
Okay.
[Laci] David, is it on yet?
- Is it on, is it on?
- We're on.
[chuckles]
Okay,
so this is the Oklahoma sign.
Um...
Basically I've always wanted
to have my picture taken here
because
when I'm a big, famous star, uh,
I don't know, I just think it
would be nice for people to know
where I came from, you know.
Like... I want them to know
that I'm really
just a corn fed girl.
[both laugh]
And that you are.
All right, let's go.
[Laci] Okay, come on.
It's so hot.
[speaking indistinctly]
[wind blowing]
No.
So...
This is Oklahoma.
[David laughs]
Hometown brand, you know.
You want to stay here
your whole life?
No.
I like to see stuff.
It's kind of loud.
I don't know, I'd like
to see things, you know.
Like what?
- Like Italy.
- All right.
I don't know.
[both laugh]
Look, don't be shy.
I don't know, I just...
I think it'd be nice to, like,
see everything out there,
you know, just something
different from...
Ooh.
- [David] You doing okay?
- Oh, yeah.
I just stepped on this
broken something.
- [David] Well, uh...
- Anyways...
- Thanks for showing me that.
- Of course.
I'm going to turn this off
because we got a big afternoon
ahead of us.
Yes, we do.
- Bye.
- Bye!
Essentially what we're going
to be doing right now
is we're just driving.
Um, there's this really great, uh,
vintage shop that I really like.
- Um...
- Uh-huh.
It's probably one
of my favorites.
So we're just going to drive
there and, uh... Yeah.
- It'd be cool.
- Great.
So I just... I hate...
This street freaks me out
a little bit.
It's right there.
This is it. It's interesting.
Kind of a scary little monkey.
I love antique stores.
[David] Wow!
You know, especially because...
it's just so much history
and everything that's here
as opposed
to something brand new.
- Oh, hi!
- Hi.
[Laci] I think,
this is the children's section.
Oh, look at that!
That's so gorgeous.
A little tutu up there.
- Wow.
- This place is amazing.
[Laci] Isn't it, though?
[somber music playing]
- [David] Oh.
- Hi.
- [David] I'm just, uh...
- It's all right.
[David] Looking at all the...
all the interesting stuff.
Yeah, it is really interesting.
[David sighs]
Isn't it wonderful?
I know, Isn't it wonderful?
Oh, she's scary.
[jarring indication]
- David.
- Yeah.
Why are you so interested
in all these mannequins?
Oh, I'm just looking at the...
the design of them.
I mean,
they're so intricate and old.
I mean...
[jarring indication]
- Sure.
- There you are.
[Laci] I love the clothes.
[jarring indication]
- [David] What's that?
- A shirt.
- What does that say?
- Rockstar.
- I'm going to a concert tonight.
It seems appropriate.
- [David] You are?
- Yeah.
It's outside, so, it's going
to be kind of hot I'm guessing.
I probably should get some
shorts while I'm here.
Oh, [inaudible].
They're cute.
[jarring indication]
Oh, these are better.
Look at these.
- Look at that.
- Yeah.
[somber music playing]
- Hey, David!
- Yeah.
- [Laci] You okay?
- I'm fine.
[Laci] You're awfully quiet.
[David] I just find
this very interesting.
[Laci] Well, that's good.
I'm going to try these on.
I'll be out in a minute, okay?
[David] Okay.
You gonna come out
and show me your new outfit?
- [Laci] I'll be out in a minute.
- Okay.
[Laci] See.
- Wow.
- I like it.
Yeah, let me see you,
let me see you.
Come on out here. Wow!
I like it. It's cute.
Looks great.
- Don't hurt yourself.
- I won't.
- You should see yourself.
- God, I look fat.
- [David] What'd you say?
- Nothing. I'm just being silly.
Well, I thought I said you...
I thought I heard you say you
were fat or something like that.
[Laci] No.
I love this dress. Look at this.
Round up.
[chuckles]
[David sighs]
[Laci]
Um, this dress is wonderful.
Oh, my gosh!
Look at this.
[David] Oh!
All right, David. I'm going to
change back into my clothes, so...
- Okay. Yeah.
- You okay?
I'll be, uh, waiting out here.
So, uh, what's this, um,
thing you're going to tonight?
[Laci] Oh, it's a concert.
Uh, who is it?
[Laci]
Oh, I don't know actually.
I was just invited, so, I didn't
buy the tickets or anything.
[David] Huh.
- Who are you going with?
- A really nice boy.
His name's Andy.
- [David] Andy.
- Boy, he's not a boy, he's 26.
He's a man. Or is he 25?
I don't really remember.
[David] He's much older
than you, isn't he?
[Laci] Not that much older,
six years.
My mom and daddy
are ten years apart.
Does that mean
that you're into older men?
It's not like,
I'm into older men.
I'm just, you know,
not age discriminatory.
[David laughs]
Well, I guess,
that's good to know.
[David] Uh, Ashley.
Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- [Josh] This... this is the camera guy.
[inaudible]. She said that
you've been at her job and stuff.
I'm her boyfriend, Josh.
Who are you
and what is up with the camera?
- I am David and I'm a director.
- Well, David the director,
she said that
she is not doing a movie.
She said she already
told you take the...
You're going to know
who I am when I take the camera
and bust you across
the head with...
[David]
Excuse me, excuse me.
- Josh, that was your name?
- Come on.
Hey, listen. Listen, I'm really,
really, sorry about that, okay?
I... That...
I didn't mean to do that.
- What? What?
- Actually, I apologize.
David, can we just
talk about this later?
I'll talk about it
with him tonight
and then I'll talk
about it with you later.
- [Josh] All right, there, there, there.
- [David] I appreciate that.
See there's even fireworks
in the background.
- It was meant to be.
- [Josh] Yeah.
[David]
Josh, listen, I'm a director.
I've worked so hard on this film
and she's my best girl.
I understand. I understand.
And she's...
she's serious about this
but... but you're following
her around, it's weird.
I'm not... I don't know.
I'm not in it.
I'm not an actor like her.
I don't know this stuff, but it's...
it's weird to me, okay?
We'll talk about this later,
okay? How about that?
Yeah, we'll talk...
we'll talk about it later.
[David] I appreciate it.
Thank you, Ashley.
[fireworks]
[David] It's all meant to be.
[somber music playing]
[David]
So, where are you taking us now?
Um, well, actually, I have
a couple of things I have to do
but I was thinking maybe I might
show you my old high school
only because I haven't been
there in a while and, you know,
you said
you wanted to get to know me.
So, I figured
maybe you might enjoy seeing it.
- Well, that sounds like fun.
- Ah, here it is.
I like it. It's a good school.
If you... Actually if you look at it...
Uh, I hate this seat belt.
Oh, there we go. Okay.
This is the high school
and there's the football field.
Go team!
High school is definitely
an interesting little, uh...
- Did you like high school?
- Parts of it.
[David chuckles]
Did you ever ditch?
Huh, no. I was a good girl.
I don't call it ditching. I...
I call it, uh, deciding
to not attend for the day.
[David laughs]
I think, I did that quite a bit
when I was younger too.
Only in my senior year. I never
really missed other than that.
I liked school. It was, uh...
So did you have
a best friend in school?
- A girl you palled out with?
- Oh, yeah.
Her name is
Julia Anderson actually.
- She's not my friend anymore.
- How come?
It's a long story.
- Here we are.
- Okay.
This is...
Durant High School.
Spent four years of my life here
and I must say it was
very interesting four years.
[David] And why is that?
Just, um...
you know, you have friends
you've had forever
and some friends get pregnant,
and some friends don't.
Some friends go to college
and the friends you thought
would go to college get pregnant,
and then the friends you think who are
going to end up ruining their lives
actually go to Harvard, so.
Well, no one went to Harvard,
but you know what I mean.
So, did you date
one of your football players?
- Of course, I did.
- What was his name?
His name is Skip
and that's not a joke either.
[David] Skip.
Bleachers.
[Laci] Yeah, bleachers.
[David] There must be
a story about that.
- Lots of stories about that.
- Oh, really?
[Laci] Mm-hmm.
Like what?
Nothing much.
Just, you know, standard, uh...
games that are won
and, you know,
getting drunk, things like that.
Sneaking out of the house at 14
stealing your parents car.
Stupid stuff really.
[David] I thought you said,
you were a good girl.
Good girls are bad girls
who don't get caught, David.
So, this is a football field.
[Laci] Yeah,
this is the football field.
[David] I bet you've seen
many a game here.
[Laci] I have. I was a
cheerleader, so, I saw every game.
- No! You were a cheerleader?
- I was a cheerleader.
Really?
Yeah. Sadly.
And, uh...
would you feel
like doing a cheer for me?
- No, no.
- Oh, come on.
- No.
- Why not?
[Laci]
Because I can't cheer anymore.
- I bet you can.
- No, I can't.
I don't do that anymore, David.
I haven't done a cheer
since I was about 17 years old.
So, you never forget it.
That's not true.
You can forget everything.
I bet you,
you can do a cheer right now.
I don't know.
Lot of...
It's a lot of energy, David.
Ah, I'll kill myself.
[David] No, we don't want that.
- [Laci] No.
- So, how does it go?
Just tell me the lines then.
- Come on.
- All right, hold these.
[David laughs]
A-T-T-A-C-K, the lions are back!
A-T-T-A-C-K,
we're leading the pack.
attack, attack, attack!
[David laughs]
That was great.
Oh,
look at that I broke my watch.
- [David] Oh, no!
- My sister gave that to me.
Can you help me
find the other piece, please?
- Sure.
- This is terribly important.
You don't understand.
She's passed away
and this is like the only thing
I have left of her.
[David] Oh, no.
You were really close?
She was my best friend,
but I don't want to talk
about it right now.
I just want to find it.
Look, this is
really, really, important.
[both sigh]
[David] What part broke of it?
Let me see.
- Oh, the strap came off.
- Oh, just kidding.
This is how blonde I am.
[Laci laughs]
I can't... It's fine.
I'll fix it later.
- [David] I can fix it for you.
- Are you sure?
- [David] Yeah.
- Thank you.
[David] I'll just, uh... I'll do it
at the end of the interview, okay?
[Laci] Okay great, thanks.
- Don't lose it.
- I won't.
[somber music playing]
[knocking on door]
- Hi, Mr. Ashland.
- You made it.
- David remember, call me David.
- Oh, that's right, David.
I'm sorry.
Wow, you certainly are a dancer
and you brought the red shoes.
- Yeah, I got the red shoes.
- Well, come on in.
Um, actually, uh,
so where are the other girls?
Oh, you know, you're the first one here.
You're right on time
and the other girls
are on their way actually.
Okay.
Well, um, you know, as...
I can wait in the lobby.
There's...
there's no problem actually.
Well, no.
Certainly you can come in.
I mean one of them called
and said they were getting gas.
They're running a little late
and the other is actually
parking their car right now.
So, you're just first.
Um...
- Okay.
- All right, come on in.
- You certainly look great.
- Thanks.
[door closes]
- [David] I'm filming you all real.
- [Megan] No, no, no.
[David] You're all real.
Well, this is what
we're doing together.
- [Megan] No, why would you do this. No!
- You're doing this.
- You're doing it.
- No, no, you're doing this.
Why are you doing this?
- No.
- [Megan crying]
[David] Oh.
That's real.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- I'm great.
I've never been better actually.
Good.
[reverse alarm beeping]
So, David, you know
all this stuff about me.
What about you?
Where'd you go to high school?
Well, I traveled a lot
as a, uh, kid and a teenager.
You see my, uh,
my father was a pilot.
That's cool.
What kind of planes did he fly?
- He, uh, designed and built his own.
- Really?
Yeah, small planes and...
we'd fly from little airport
to little airport having lunches
and I mean
I wanted to be a pilot myself
- but I just, uh...
- What happened?
I, um... I don't have as you can
see I have to wear these glasses.
- Oh, right.
- So, my eyesight isn't that great
and, um, I just have trouble
seeing things far away and...
Actually one time I me
and my dad were flying and...
he asked me to look around
for planes.
And I looked and I looked
and I thought
I had seen something
that was right under us,
and I told him
and he didn't believe me.
He thought
I was kidding and, uh...
And it was just a near miss
in the air
not less than 200 feet,
a plane flew right under us.
- Oh, my!
- And so it was kind of scary.
And so, at any rate
that scared me
and I just don't like
to fly anymore.
Oh, well, that makes sense
and do you... Are you still
close with your father?
No.
I'm sorry.
So, this is the park.
I used to play here
all the time.
- Oh, yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
What was your favorite game?
Mm, I liked the swings but...
Um, I also liked to draw
with chalk and, you know,
slides, really everything.
Oh, my God!
- Look at that.
- What's that?
[David laughs]
[Laci] Becca, ones only. Sarah.
Look at that.
I used to do stuff like this
all the time.
Except mine would be Laci Lee.
Oh, my God! This is one
of my favorite things, David.
Look over here.
This...
this was my first boyfriend.
[David laughs]
[Laci] Just kidding.
- Um, this was...
- I see.
This was just, uh...
It was the tire swing.
I didn't practically hit my head
on the ceiling when I used to.
It was like the tire swing, you know.
It's something every kid just loved.
It... it was the rocket ship.
With a pole around the center.
You know...
it's fun.
It was, um... was good.
♪ Hey, hey, oh, playmate
Come out and play with me ♪
♪ And bring your dollies three
Climb up my apple tree ♪
♪ Slide down my rain barrel
Into my cellar door ♪
♪ And we'll be jolly friends
Forevermore ♪
- Don't look up my dress now, David.
- Oh, now!
What kind of man
do you think I am?
[Laci]
No, you're a man at the most.
[David laughs]
- [David] Where are you going?
- Down the slide.
Ah!
[David] Whoa!
[both laugh]
Are you okay?
[Laci laughing]
[Laci] I'm fine.
I forgot,
how fast those things can be.
[David] Oh, man, that was...
- Wow!
- You sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
[continues laughing]
You are just something else,
you know that.
When we're done
you'll be cutting that.
[laughs]
You know that was...
I guess that was as real
as they get, you know.
That is as real as they get.
Oh, look. That was me.
[David]
You used to swing on here?
Hey, can I swing with you?
Thank you.
That's my friend David.
- [David] Hi, what's your name?
- Sarah.
Hi, Sarah.
- You live around here?
- I live over there.
[Laci] The brick house?
It's beautiful.
- How old are you, Sarah?
- [Sarah] 11.
[Laci] 11.
Oh, so that means
you're in sixth grade.
- Yeah.
- Wow!
[swings squeaking]
Who can swing the highest?
I bet I can.
Let's see.
[swings continue squeaking]
[David]
Who's winning, who's winning?
[Laci giggles]
Well, Sarah, I definitely think,
that you won this one.
[David] Now, be careful now.
You can't film here.
So did you used to come here
every day?
Every day.
Well, it's Durant what else
are you going to do?
Right?
[David] That looks like fun.
Stopping.
Sarah, thank you so much
for letting me swing with you.
Your welcome.
[Laci]
It was lovely meeting you.
Bye, Sarah.
[David] Bye, Sarah.
[Laci] David.
[David] I'm right here, missy.
I am right here.
[somber music playing]
[Amy breathing heavily]
[Amy screams]
What are you...
what are you doing?
What are you doing?
[David] Oh, God!
You are...
perfect.
[whimpering]
[David] Did you and your
boyfriend used to hang out here?
No, no.
Skip, was that his name?
Skip, yeah. That was Skip.
We did more of the, uh...
We started dating high school
freshman year
and then we dated
until senior year,
but, um, essentially
what happened was,
is, uh, we would do more things
like we go to parties together
and, you know, we'd hang out
after the football game and...
I mean we never really did
anything playful
or fun like this.
He was a real serious guy.
You know, he... he was always
trying to be the best.
Hmm...
Did that bother you?
It's not my life.
I sense that maybe you...
you might miss him a little bit?
No, no.
I don't miss him.
I don't miss him at all.
Hmm. Was it a bad breakup?
I don't want to talk
about this with you, David.
I don't mean to be rude or
anything, but it's very personal.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I really don't mean to be rude.
It's just...
It's okay. It's okay.
You know, I just...
I'm just trying to find the
realism in everything, you know.
- Of course.
- It's... it's... it's important to me
that each one
of my actors are real
and... and...
but I'll tell you again.
- Hey!
- What?
- You're doing a great job.
- Thanks.
I lied to you.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
About what?
I said, I didn't hang out here
with Skip but I did.
I hung out here
with him quite a bit.
We pretended we were married.
[jarring indication]
Silly, right?
Well, not silly.
- H.
- Harris.
Laci Lee Harris.
- And...
- Skip Harris.
[David scoffs]
[scoffs]
I guess you pretty much
didn't make it real, didn't you?
We made it real.
I mean it was, uh...
it was first love, you know.
You know how that works.
You think,
you're going to get married
and you're going
to be together forever,
and you're going to have babies,
and life's going to be perfect,
and...
it doesn't work out that way.
I mean it does for some,
but then, you know,
ten years down the road,
he's fat
and you're living in a trailer.
[David chuckles]
Humor is my defense mechanism.
[David] You know, why didn't you,
uh, carve your name on this tree?
[Laci] Um, that's new I guess.
I mean the tree's not new,
but the...
the, uh,
bark missing from it is...
and I don't like destroying
things of nature.
- What? How sweet of you!
- Hmm, yeah, well.
So...
I take it you and Skip...
did he get you in trouble?
How do you mean?
You know, like, uh...
was he your first?
It's kind of a personal
question, don't you think?
Well, a simple yes
or no would do, don't you think?
Yeah, he was.
[David] Hmm.
I don't mean
to make you uncomfortable.
It's okay.
Do you think,
that you were his first?
Yes. I like to think so.
- But how do you know?
- You don't. You never know.
[David] Hmm.
He really hurt you, didn't he?
Yeah, he did.
Do you still see him
now and then?
No.
No, I don't.
You know where he is?
Yeah, I know
where he lives and everything
but., mm..
doesn't matter.
You know...
I was in love once.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
What happened?
Well...
she wanted a...
she wanted to have a big family
and...
I couldn't give it to her.
Why not?
I am... Just have
a little bit of a problem.
[chuckles]
I'm sorry.
It's all right, you know.
I mean, some people
can have kids some people can't.
That's got to be
really hard though.
Yeah.
My... my father
always wanted grandchildren.
[sighs]
So...
I can... I couldn't do it. I...
It's okay.
Hey, hey, hey, it's okay.
You know...
being around someone like you...
you know,
and you look the way you do...
and you act the way you do...
I'm sorry,
you're making me tear up.
I just feel so bad for you.
I mean,
that's going to be really hard.
[David] Do you., um..
do you ever think
that someone like you...
would ever be interested
into someone like me?
[chuckles]
Of course.
You're so sweet.
[jarring indication]
God!
You're...
you're just something else.
I just... I'm blown away by
your presence, your attitude...
you're just so grown up
for your age.
I get that a lot.
[chuckles]
I'm an old soul.
You could say that again.
I like it here.
I like with you here.
I like being here with you.
It's fun.
- You do?
- I do, yeah.
Why?
Something different about you,
David.
Well, like what?
Tell me what?
I don't know. It's just...
I haven't figured it out yet.
Give me a minute.
It's just different. That's all.
- You ever met anybody like me?
- Definitely not.
No one like you in Durant,
that's for damn sure.
- Hey, uh...
- Yeah.
Do you mind if I hold your hand
while we walk a little bit?
Okay, sure.
[chuckles]
You're silly, David.
- [David] Why am I silly?
- I have no idea.
- You're beautiful.
- Thank you.
You're not so bad yourself.
Thank you.
That's awfully close.
[chuckles]
[David chuckles]
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking...
is that...
Oh! Wayne!
Get your ass over here.
Laci! Oh, my God!
It's so good to see you.
[Laci] It's so good to see you.
How are you?
[David] Um...
[indistinct conversation]
Um...
Oh, my God!
Are you still with Paula?
[David] I'm...
conducting an...
important interview.
You look amazing! Look at that.
[David] I said that I was...
- [Laci] Wow!
- [David] ...conducting a
really important interview.
[jarring indication]
[David]
Did you hear what I'm saying?
Did you?
[Laci] What are you doing now?
[David] Did you hear?
Did you hear what I said?
I am conducting an important
interview with her.
[Laci]
David, hey! Calm down, okay?
[David] What part did you not
understand, hillbilly mother fucker?
- Listen.
- [David] Why don't you fucking go?
- I don't give a flying fuck.
- I'm a really good friend...
[David] Did you hear
what I fucking said?
Get the fuck out of here! Go!
Just get out of here!
I said get the fuck out of here.
- Fine, I'll leave.
- [David] A piece of shit. Yeah.
- Yeah, that's right.
- [David] You don't forget it.
I won't forget it.
[somber music playing]
[David] You turn around and walk
the other way now, you understand?
- [Wayne] Okay.
- [David] Right now.
I will
because I don't want to...
[David] Right now!
I've heard enough from you.
- Yeah, fine.
- [Laci] David, come here.
- I'm out of here.
- [Laci] Get your...
- [David] What are you waiting for?
- [Wayne] Whatever, man!
Forget you, man.
You're not worth it.
[Laci]
What the hell is wrong with you?
Get the camera out of my face.
No,
get the camera out of my face.
- What are you..
- Listen, listen to me.
What do you think
that you're doing?
I just...
You can't treat people
like that.
- [David] Laci, listen to me.
- Don't talk to me.
- [David] Listen to me.
- No!
- Let go.
[David]
I wanted this reaction from you.
Do you understand?
I told you,
it was important for me to see
how you acted
in front of others.
Would you listen?
Stop and listen to me, please.
[Laci] No,
I don't want to listen to you.
Just listen. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
I didn't mean it at all, at all.
You go over there
and you apologize to him.
You want me to do this,
you apologize.
- Listen, I'm sorry.
- No.
You... not to me.
You apologize to him.
I'm not the one
who needs apologizing to.
Stop it.
What is wrong with you? Stop it.
[David]
Okay, okay, okay, listen to me.
I'll go apologize.
Will that make you feel better?
[Laci] Yes, it will.
Go walk your ass over there
and apologize
and get the camera out of my...
[David] Come on,
where are you, Monica? Oh, God!
There you are.
David.
Monica.
- What are you doing here?
- Hi.
- How you doing?
How do you know where I live?
Oh, well, you know, you... you, uh...
you signed your contract already
and your address was on it,
and I was in the neighborhood
and I thought, "I wonder,
if Monica was around to, um,
- you know, get her on film."
- Right.
You know, since I'm doing
the reality film and all.
Um, I... I thought we weren't going
to start this until next Saturday.
Right. But, you know,
I was in the neighborhood
and it's just a beautiful day,
and all and I thought...
- Yeah, but I mean...
- ..."Oh, God!
I hope she's around."
And here you are.
Yeah, I didn't know you were
going to be filming me though.
Is this going to be like
a regular thing now?
- You're just going to film me wherever?
- No.
- You certainly look great.
- Um, thank you.
Uh, I didn't think,
I was going to be... be filmed.
I just thought maybe if she was around
this would be great research for me
and... and good practice
for you to be on film.
Okay. Uh, well, I would
appreciate the heads up next time.
Sure.
You know, I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean, to make
you uncomfortable or any.
[car engine starts]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Monica] All right. Well,
I'm going to take a shower now,
so I'll talk to you later.
Love you. Love you too. Bye.
[somber music playing]
[water running]
- Monica.
- Oh, my God!
[somber music playing]
[Monica screams]
No!
[Monica crying]
[screams]
Help!
No! No!
No, no.
No, please stop this! Please!
Let me out!
[somber music playing]
[David] Hey.
Hi.
[David sighs]
- I said I was sorry to him.
- Mm-hmm.
- I told him what I was doing.
- Okay.
I still don't understand why you
think you have the right to do that
to people regardless of if
you're making a movie or not?
I mean, the things you said,
were absolutely horrible.
It wasn't even funny,
nor was it remotely appropriate.
[David sighs]
Listen.
I just don't want you
to get hurt like you have been.
You just
don't want me to get hurt?
How do you know he's...
I went to high school with him.
He's a friend.
He... he was dating one of my...
the girls on my cheerleading squad, Paula.
I mean...
He...
Laci.
I would be really grateful if I
could just take you home right now
and we could be done with
all of this because I'm sorry.
I don't think,
that you're for me.
Well, that really, really,
makes me sad, that you say that.
It really, really, does
because you know why?
Why?
Because I wanted... I want to
give you this part in this film.
You have shown me exactly
what an actress
should be and is.
I mean,
you're... you're amazing.
You're an amazing,
amazing woman,
not a girl.
and I'm sorry that I reacted
the way that I did.
I just... I'm sorry but I mean you... you
showed me exactly what I... what I needed.
And it's really important
for what I'm doing.
You know, there are so many
films out there that are bad.
There are so many actors out
there that are bad...
and you showed me what was real.
- I don't know, Mr. Ashland.
- Please.
I don't know.
Do you want to be an actress?
Yeah.
It's not that. I just...
you freaked me out, okay?
Like, you really freaked me out.
I'm...
[sighs]
please accept my apology.
And when we're shooting that won't happen.
I just had to make sure.
I had to be sure
that you were the one.
And listen to me, you're the one,
you're going to make this film.
I promise you.
And you're going to be a bright shining
star and everybody's going to see you.
Everybody is going to see you
the way that I really see you.
I'm going to make sure they do.
Okay?
Okay. Okay.
Forgive me?
Maybe.
[David chuckles]
Well, how about this?
How about I treat you to some...
some nice ice cream?
I do like ice cream.
Okay, we'll go.
- There's a Dairy Queen up the street.
- Perfect.
Come on.
I can't wait to show you some of the
footage that I've already shot of this.
- Oh, you've already shot footage?
- Oh, yeah!
- Oh, my God! I would love to see it.
- Oh, yeah.
You're the icing on the cake.
[laughs]
[car alarm chirps, buzzes]
We got to get that door fixed
for you sometime.
We got to do something.
[somber music playing]
[Jade] Somebody help me!
Somebody!
Someone!
Help me!
Help! Help me!
What do you want from me?
Help me!
Oh, my God!
Someone.
What do you want from me?
Let me out of here. Let me go!
Let me go!
[David] You know, I'm real excited
that you're taking this part.
I'm real excited
I'm taking this part too.
- I am honored.
- Oh, I'm honored!
Are you kidding me? Thank you so much
for giving me this opportunity, David.
Oh, you are so welcome.
- It's going to be real fun.
- It's going to be real fun, yeah.
What is this asshole in front of us doing?
Oh, my God! I mean, I'm sorry.
I don't mean to... And that is
why I don't drive. Oh, my God!
We're going to die.
Okay. I'm sorry.
[laughs]
- Okay and...
- That was close, wasn't it?
Well, you know what they say,
"Live for the moment", right?
'Cause you never know
when you're just going to die.
[both laugh]
Woo! Scared me a little bit.
Hello.
[woman speaking indistinctly
over radio]
Hi, can I just have one, um,
dip... chocolate dipped cone
and vanilla ice cream, please.
- And what would you like?
- Nothing.
- Are you sure?
- I'm positive, thank you.
Well, all right. Okay.
Thank you.
- Yeah, let me get this.
- Oh, no. You don't have to do that.
[David] Oh, no, no, certainly.
[Laci] Thank you.
[woman speaks indistinctly]
Oh, a small please. Thanks.
Sorry about that. Pardon me?
Thank you.
That happens, right?
So...
if you were to play any type of
role in a movie, what would it be?
Somewhere I get to wear
big, poofy dresses.
- Like period piece, maybe?
- Yeah, period piece. I'd love to do that.
Like my favorite movie was...
actually I really liked Titanic...
Oh, yeah.
...with Kate Winslet
and Leonardo DiCaprio.
Wouldn't you love to do a movie
with Leonardo?
Hmm, he's not really my type personally.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
He's really adorable and cute,
but I think, he likes the taller
model-y looking types.
So, when you say he's not your
type, do you mean as an actor
- or is it if you were to date him?
- No, no, he's a wonderful actor.
I think, that he actually...
he's one of the best actors out there.
But as for, um...
- Just checking your angles, you know.
- Sorry.
But as for like him and I, uh,
dating,
I... I prefer men like, uh,
Julian McMahon.
He's pretty.
[chuckles]
I don't think,
I know who that is.
Oh, he's just...
he's on Nip Tuck and a couple other shows.
And, you know, of course Orlando
Bloom, can't go wrong with him.
[David] Mm-hmm.
[somber music playing]
[humming]
So, how about you?
If you can date anybody,
who would you date?
- [woman] It's $1.14.
- Thank you.
[David]
Date anybody, who would I date?
Yeah, Catherine Zeta Jones,
Julia Roberts, uh, Kate Moss?
Well...
if you were a big actress, well,
you really wouldn't have to be one,
I might be interested
in dating you.
[laughs]
That's very sweet, David.
Thank you.
- [woman] Hope you have a nice day!
- You as well. Here you go.
[David] Thank you.
- [Laci] Oh, I'm sorry.
- Oh, that's all right. That's all right.
- It's just change.
- [Laci] I'm so sorry.
- [David] No worries.
- I'll get it in a minute.
Oh!
[David laughs]
I can't eat and drive at the same time.
I'm not that talented.
Thank you. It's very good.
Would you like some?
Oh, no. Thanks.
Knock yourself out.
Is it good?
- It's very good, yeah.
- It looks good.
- Can't go wrong with Dairy Queen, right?
- Mm-hmm, not at all.
[Laci chuckles]
So...
you were saying.
- You can't choose me. That's not fair.
- Why?
Because it has to be somebody
like Orlando Bloom or...
I... I am not attracted
to Orlando Bloom.
[chuckles]
- Sure?
- Yeah. I'm very sure.
Oh, well it has to be
someone like, you know,
someone big and famous,
not somebody...
[David sighs]
Natalie Portman.
[Laci] Mm.
- I'd date her too.
- Ha, ha. You would?
No, no, but she's very good
actress and she's very pretty.
Are you into girls at all?
That's a random question.
Well, you're the one that just
said, "I would date her too."
- Are you sure?
- No, I don't do the girl thing.
I'm sorry.
Uh...
Like, you know, it's just kind of like,
I don't eat human beings, so, uh...
Okay.
That's a very good analogy.
Well, you know what I mean,
don't eat your own kind.
[David laughs]
[laughs]
- Hey.
- Hi.
Well, you know, since we're headed
back to my neck of the woods,
I wanted to take you here
and show you this great,
big old star because, you know what?
- What?
- That's what you're going to be.
[laughs]
- You think so?
- I know so.
- Isn't it awesome?
- It's great.
[David]
You go stand right by it now.
Great big star that you are.
[laughs]
- So, uh, hey.
- What?
Speaking of neck of the woods,
um, since we're headed back
to my neck of the woods, um,
there's this... kind of this
special place I'd like to show you.
- Really?
- Would you like to see it?
Well, yeah.
I mean, if it's special to you,
I mean, yeah.
- I'd love to show you it.
- I'd love to see it.
- All right.
- Great.
- Come on.
- Okay, come on.
[both chuckle]
Thank you by the way, again,
for the part.
- Well, you know.
- I'm so excited.
You're perfect for it and
you're just precious, you know.
Aw!
- I'm going to save this battery again.
- Okay, bye again.
[somber music playing]
[David] Please...
call me David.
So, why do you like coming here?
Just helps me think, you know, with us
getting ready to do a movie and all.
Yeah.
And I'm really glad
that you came here with me.
- I really appreciate it.
- Of course. I mean, yeah.
You know, I've been meaning
to ask you something
and I don't mean to pry
or anything but...
Well, yeah.
What was your...
what was your sister's name?
[jarring indication]
[scoffs]
Why do you care?
I was just wondering because you
seem very standoffish with that.
It's just none of your business.
I'm sorry.
I...
- I'm really sorry.
- It's okay.
No, Laci Lee, listen,
I'm very excited for today.
Thank you so much
for allowing me to film you
and I'm so glad
that you've taken this part.
And... Well, thank you so much
for coming here with me today.
Look, I'm... I'm sorry. No.
- You ready to go?
- Her name was Jessica.
She was great.
I'm sorry I overreacted but...
That's okay.
No, that's, you know, no...
Really I'm... That's okay.
I'm...
Thanks for opening up to me.
Sure. Well, why don't we...
Let's go. Come on.
Sure.
[Laci] Don't want to step on...
[suspenseful music playing]
[chuckles]
I certainly enjoyed my day
with you.
I had a really nice day
with you too, thanks.
And, you know,
thank you so much for this role.
I've... I really appreciate it
and I'm really excited, so...
- You're not as excited as I am.
- Oh, you can go.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, it's so bright
and so hot in the summer.
- It's, um, right here, right?
- Yeah.
- Great.
- All right.
Well, I really look forward
to working with you
and, um, I mean you have all
my contact information, so...
Well, aren't you going to come
see some of the footage?
Well, um, you know,
it's just I have that concert and
because I have that date, you know.
And, um, I just...
It's... it's getting late.
Well, I... I understand and all,
but, uh, I'd really like
for you to see the footage.
I think, it'd be really
important research for you.
I mean,
it'll really only take a second.
Yeah, well...
Laci, listen,
it'll really only take a second.
- Okay.
- Great.
[David singing]
♪ Come out and play with me ♪
[Megan]
Why are you doing this?
♪ If you don't play with me
I'll be your enemy ♪
♪ I'll scratch your eyes out ♪
[Monica] Oh, my God!
♪ I'll stab you with a knife ♪
♪ And that will be
The end of your life ♪
Who's been the bad boy?
[Laci] This place is a lot
further than you said it was.
I'm sorry, Laci,
but places like these need a lot of space.
- Come on in.
- Well, what is it?
This is my very own soundstage.
Is that code for like
your den of sex?
[both laugh]
Well, you'll be the first
to find out, won't you?
With my luck, probably.
[David laughs]
I mean, that in the nicest way
by the way.
Of course.
I mean, I wasn't saying that you
weren't attractive or anything.
- I was just saying that, um...
- That's okay.
[laughs]
Laci, there isn't anything
you can say that'd upset me.
- Not one little thing?
- Not one thing.
What if I told you
I wasn't going to go in there?
What if I told you I was just
going to walk back to my car
and get in and drive away?
Well, I would tell you that you
wouldn't be up for that Oscar
that I know that you're going
to win after this.
What if I told you
I didn't want to win an Oscar?
But I know you do.
I know you want that award.
I know you want best actress
because that's what you are
and that's what I see,
and that's what you're going to be.
- You're a manipulative little shit.
- Am I now?
Come on and show me
your fucking sound stage.
I got to go.
Okay, but you know, I've been
working here since the beginning.
How long has that been?
It's quite a long time. You know,
my work has taken me years to perfect.
[Laci] I bet it has.
- How old are you anyway?
- Old enough.
Just like anything...
you have to stick to it.
- Of course, understandably.
- Wow, you still look great.
Oh. Um...
[chuckles]
It sure is dark in here.
Yeah.
I could, uh... I'll change that.
So...
You were going to show me some
footage or something, right?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Laci.
I'm just so excited that you're here
because with you accepting
this final role in my film...
I'm on my way to best picture.
[chuckles]
- So you ready?
- Yeah, sure.
Okay, I'm going to...
But look, I really got to go
after this, okay?
You know, because I have that date
and everything, so I got to...
Sure, I remember.
So, if you can just, uh,
hold on to this camera.
- [Laci] Yeah.
- Just be careful.
I'm going to go turn on
the overhead light for us, okay?
[Laci] Okay.
Oh, that's all right.
[Laci humming]
David?
David!
I thought you were
turning the lights on.
David, this isn't funny.
Not laughing.
David!
I'm going to go if the lights
don't come on right now. I mean it.
David, I really have to go.
[door thudding]
David, the door is locked.
The door is locked.
David, why is the door locked?
Okay, just breathe,
just breathe.
David! David, where are you?
[door thudding]
Please, please, please, please.
All right. Okay.
All right, just breathe.
Just breathe, just breathe.
[suspenseful music playing]
David?
- [thudding]
- [screams]
David, is that you?
David.
David, this isn't funny.
I'm not laughing.
David.
Oh, my God!
[breathing heavily]
Shh! Shh!
My God!
David. David!
Oh, my God! No. Okay.
Keep it under...
keep it under control.
Keep it under control. Okay.
[shuddering]
David.
My God!
God!
[breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music playing]
[switches clicking]
[gasping]
David, was that you?
[whimpering]
[screaming]
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh!
Ow! Ow! Stop!
Ow, shit!
[screams]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [Jessica on recording] Hi.
- [David on recording] How are you?
[Jessica] I'm good.
What was your name again?
[David]
David, please call me David.
- [Jessica] Okay, hi David.
- It's very nice to meet you.
[Jessica]
Hi. Nice to meet you too.
[David] Wow, I hope you don't mind
that I have this camera rolling.
I keep it with me all the time
because you never know when
I'm gonna meet the next star.
Wow, you look great
and you look great on film too.
- [Jessica] Well, thank you. Thank you.
- Just getting you here.
- So, how are you doing?
- I'm doing very well, thanks.
- Thanks for answering my ad.
- I'm really excited.
[Laci] Oh, my God!
I hope to,
um, do really well for you.
[Laci] Jessica?
[David] Well, so far you look great and...
and thank you for meeting me here.
Did you have a long way to come?
[Laci] Oh, my God, no!
Oh, no I... I just recently
moved here to Dallas from Durant,
over a full month from back home
where my family lives.
[David] Oh, oh, wow! Okay.
That's a nice scarf
you're wearing by the way.
Oh, thanks.
This is my lucky scarf,
my sister Laci, uh,
knitted it for me for Christmas.
- [David] You have a sister?
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, she's, uh... The two of us we
want to be, um, famous actresses,
so... I'm sorry, I'm a little
nervous so I'm acting silly but...
[David] No, that's okay.
[Laci] Oh, my God! Somebody help me!
Somebody help me!
[screaming] Somebody help me!
Can anybody hear me?
[Jessica]
Um, she's younger, sorry.
[Laci crying]
[suspenseful music
continues playing]
- [Jessica] Sorry, I'm...
- [David] It's okay.
[Jessica] A little bit.
[David] That's the last thing I want to
do, so just be yourself, you know.
This is exactly
what I'm looking for.
I'm looking for natural girls
to be natural.
[Jessica] So, what are you...
[Laci shuddering]
[suspenseful music
continues playing]
[screams]
[Laci continues screaming]
[dramatic music playing]
[knocking on door]
- Hi, Mr. Ashland.
- [David] David, please call me David.
[dramatic music continues]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull