SOMEWHERE IN THE ATLANTIC OCEAN
MAY 12TH, 1918
There it is.
It's ready for firing.
To battle stations!
- Captain!
- Yes, my boy?
Good job, Hans.
Alarm!
Prepare torpedoes one and two for firing!
- Captain?!
- Fire at will!
Fire at will!
The ship is coming directly towards us.
Yes.
Hurry up.
Get off the boat.
US NAVY ATLANTIC FLEET COMMAND
NORFOLK, VIRGINIA APRIL 27TH, 1945
TRONDHEIM, NORWAY
...however,
we have now completed an armament,
as the world has not seen before.
I have...
...after he rejected that...
...I have equipped Germany
in these five years.
I have spent billions on it,
the German nation
has to know that now. I have...
We have created the best air
and tank defense in the world.
Through tireless work, day and night.
I approached all
the seemingly impossible problems
with the firm will...
MILITARY NAVY
COMMAND POST NORWAY
In unprecedented
demonstrations of millions
the entire German nation has united today
to work, to their values,
their moral ethos
and to their national solidarity.
This evening, across national,
and denominational differences,
the whole German nation comes together,
to finally...
THE UNITED STATES 10TH FLEET CAPTAIN
SAMUEL L. GRAVELY JR. THE USS PC-1264
Don't be like that, you wimp.
- Do you guys have anything for me?
- No, shut up.
What I'd give for a good beer right now.
Are you ready for battle,
my fellow soldiers?
- Yes.
- We will defeat them.
I have a bag of potatoes here.
And I also have chocolate.
- No, no.
- Great.
- All right?
- Yes, well done.
Yes.
They're coming!
Fire at will!
The report from
the Führer's headquarters is,
that our "Führer", Adolf Hitler -
in his command post
at the Reich Chancellery -
has been fighting to the last breath
against Bolshevism
and has been killed in action for Germany.
On the thirtieth...