[BUBBLING SOUNDS]
♪♪
[SPLASH]
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
♪♪
Good citizens of Pacifica,
never before has the ceremony
of the Mermaid Moon
been more critical to the future
of our world.
The Golden Pearl has chosen
eight special mermaids
who will compete to be
the Power Keeper.
The only one who can ensure
our civilization's safety
for the next 100 years.
If the Golden Pearl shines
her light upon you,
step forth.
Huh, wow!
[GASPS]
Oh, oh, no.
[CHUCKLES]
Alright!
[GASPS]
- What's going on?
- Who's missing?
- Where are the other two?
- Oh, no!
[GASPS]
- Where are the other two?
- Who could it be...?
Where are the other
two mermaids?
[UPBEAT HOLIDAY MUSIC]
♪ Let's go make it happen ♪
♪ Ooo, oo, oo ♪
♪ We gonna have the time
Of our lives ♪
♪ Ooo, oo, oo, oo ♪
♪ Let's go make it happen ♪
♪ Ooo, oo, oo ♪
♪ Make it happen
Feel alright ♪
♪ Ooo, oo, oo, oo ♪
♪ Let's go make it ♪
♪ Let 'em know that
I'm livin' my life ♪
♪ No coming down 'cause
I'm up so high ♪
♪ Bad vibes, I'll be
Waving goodbye ♪
♪ Come along to this party
Of mine ♪
♪ Don't be shy
Let's live it up ♪
♪ I don't think I could
get enough ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm feeling great ♪
♪ Straight from the jump ♪
♪ I'm so A-plus
and two thumbs up ♪
♪ Don't hesitate, don't worry ♪
♪ Come and take it all in ♪
♪ These good feelings
ain't never ever gonna end ♪
♪ Let's go make it happen ♪
♪ Ooo, oo, oo ♪
♪ We gonna have the time
of our lives ♪
♪ Ooo, oo, oo, oo ♪
♪ Let's go make it happen ♪
♪ Ooo, oo, oo ♪
♪ Make it happen,
feel alright ♪
♪ Ooo, oo, oo, oo ♪
♪ We gonna have the time
of our life ♪
♪ Ooo, oo, oo ♪
♪ Let's go make it happen ♪
♪ Make it happen,
feel alright ♪
♪ Ooo, oo, oo, oo ♪
♪♪
Whoops!
[LAUGHING]
Skipper!
We're here to pick up trash,
not seaweed.
[CHUCKLES]
My bad.
I love spending time
with you and your sisters.
It reminds me why being
an only child is so great.
You're a Roberts.
Barbie Brooklyn Roberts,
to be exact.
That makes us
practically sisters.
Not the same,
but still cool,
Barbie Malibu Roberts.
I got one!
I got a whole bunch.
[CHUCKLING]
That's great, Chelsea.
Hunh.
[SIGHS] This is such a big job.
It's kind of overwhelming.
Every little bit helps, right?
It would be nice
if we could just snap
our fingers and "poof."
Too bad magic's not real.
Um, Barbie?
[BOTH] Which one, Stacie?
My sister one.
Your bag is glowing.
Oh.
Whoa!
Oh, I can explain...
sort of.
Um, it was a gift...
from a mermaid.
So...
A mermaid?
You know that sounds crazy,
right?
Probably the reason
I never told you.
But it's totally true.
We met her on vacation one time.
She needed my help
to save some dolphins.
Then we got mixed up with this
crazy scientist named Marlo...
Anyway, it was a thing,
so, um...
And the glowing necklace?
The mermaid, Isla,
gave it to me as a thanks
and as a way to connect if she
ever needed my help again.
Looks like she needs
your help again.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey there.
Pretty.
But what are we waiting for?
We have to go help Isla!
Oh, you want to come too?
I'm seven, and I'm obsessed
with mermaids.
Do you even have to ask?
I want to be a mermaid.
We do get to be mermaids, right?
How cool would that be?
You promised Mom and Dad
we'd all stick together.
They're not going
to be too happy
if you put an entire ocean
between us.
[CHUCKLING]
You win.
We'll all go see Isla.
[CHEERING]
Yay!
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're all down with this?
What am I missing?
I know. This is weird and crazy
and seems impossible.
But, sometimes, to see
the impossible
you just have to make the leap.
- [BIRD CHIRPING]
- Whoa!
What do you think?
I've never even seen a bird
like you before.
I'll take it as a sign.
[BIRD CHIRPING]
I'm in.
Alright!
Okay, how does this work?
[LAUGHING]
[ALL] One, two, three!
[GASPS]
Amazing!
Oh, wow!
[LAUGHS]
Whoa!
- Whoa!
- Wow!
Beautiful!
Yeah!
Isn't this awesome?
Whoa! Oh!
Woo-hoo!
Look at this tail!
Whoa.
Whoa!
[LAUGHING]
[GASPS]
Hi!
[LAUGHING]
Girl, we have gone on a lot
of adventures together,
but this one takes the cake,
the crab cake.
[CHUCKLING]
Do not be fooled by their
whimsical appearance
in legends and fairy tales.
Brace yourselves for this,
people.
Are you braced?
Mermaids are real.
[CROWD MURMURING]
Mermaids?
[CHUCKLING]
Is she for real?
Is this serious?
With all due respect, Marlo,
you've been trying to
convince us of this for years.
We're scientists.
We need proof.
Where is your proof?
I'm glad you asked,
Dr. Tang.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Whoa, whoa!
This shell tiara was found
on a tiny rock
out in the middle of the sea.
I believe it once belonged
to a mermaid.
[SCIENTIST] Is this a joke?
That rock is the epicenter of
a well-documented phenomena
known as "The Mermaid Moon".
It appears once
every hundred years.
I have it on very good authority
that when the first ray
of the Mermaid Moon
hits this specific location,
all mermaids come to
the surface of the sea
to soak in the moon's energy.
And what is the source of this
good authority?
Well, um, it's...
My granny told me about it
when I was a little girl.
- [SCIENTIST] Absurd!
- [SCIENTISTS LAUGHING]
[SCIENTISTS] Right.
- What a waste of my time.
- Is this in the budget?
This is ridiculous.
This lecture is over.
Wait! Don't go!
I'm not finished.
Yes, you are, Marlo.
We are officially revoking
your funding.
But, but...
Please, Marlo, come on.
Our oceans have far more
pressing issues to address.
Stop wasting our time with your
frivolous fairy-tale witch-hunt.
It's not a witch hunt.
They're mermaids.
It's a... mermaid hunt.
[GROANS]
Get over here or you're fired.
Oh, oh!
Well, it was a good gig
while it lasted.
Hm.
Here's an interesting job
I can apply for.
Tropical beverage taster.
I wonder if they'll let me
work from home.
Ah!
Funding or no funding,
I will continue my mission.
A real live mermaid in captivity
will bring a pretty penny
on stages across the world.
Then we'll see who has
the last laugh.
[DIABOLICAL LAUGHING]
I should probably get
a new ringtone.
Whoa! Uh, that's a shark.
It's okay. She's as afraid
of you as we are of her.
Afraid? No, I'm just so...
thrown.
Everything I thought I knew
just... isn't.
But, um, is it different
under water
or do we not still have
a mission to start?
And where exactly are we going?
- Wow!
- Whoa!
Being a mermaid is the best.
Fins up!
This'll take us to Isla.
Ahh!
♪ Ya, ya, ya, ya, ya ♪
♪ I've been stuck
In a place ♪
♪ Living life by
My own rules ♪
♪ Never went face
To face with ♪
♪ A song I don't know
The words to ♪
♪ Before I was
Just cruisin' ♪
♪ Let the days
Pass me by ♪
♪ Didn't know
What I was losin' ♪
♪ Never knew
I was so blind ♪
♪ Sometimes I find the things
On my mind ♪
♪ Can run far ahead
But I'm still behind ♪
♪ Barely believing
In what I'm seeing ♪
♪ I gotta let go
To all that I know ♪
♪ 'Cause some things in
Life you have no control ♪
♪ And then I wonder
What I've discovered ♪
♪ Beneath the surface ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ I'm seeing clearly
For the first time ♪
♪ I'm finally looking ♪
♪ Beneath the surface ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ It's so exciting
All that I'm finding ♪
♪ Beneath the surface ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Ay ay ay
ay ay ay ay ♪
♪ Beneath the surface ♪
Isla!
I knew you'd come.
And you brought the guppies!
- Hi!
- Isla!
This is my friend, Barbie.
So, what's going on?
Oh, there are two Barbies.
Now it all makes sense.
What makes sense?
Well, I don't even know
where to start,
because with
the Mermaid Moon so soon,
we've got the ceremony
to prepare for,
but without the right powers
we can't.
So, the golden pearl picked
but left two people out
and I knew where
to look for one,
but I wasn't sure until...
Oh.
Maybe it'd be easier
if I show you.
♪♪
I hope, I hope, I hope, I hope
I'm an earth mermaid.
Why?
Duh, Finn, because I like
making things grow.
- How cool would that be?
- Cool, sure.
But who wants cool when
you can have fire power?
Being able to heat water
and control volcanoes.
It's literally hot.
Whatever, Finn.
What power do you want,
Talleigha?
I really don't care
which one power I get.
- What?
I plan to have them all.
Why am I not surprised?
You want to be the Power Keeper.
The one mermaid who
can control every power.
The one at the center
of the ceremony.
All eyes on her as she lifts
Mermaid Rock to the sky.
- Whoa.
- Look at Talleigha!
[CHUCKLING]
Look who's already getting
her air power.
And water and earth.
Once I get fire,
no one will be able to rival me
for Power Keeper.
That's not how it works,
you know.
We all get a little
of every power.
But the one we're supposed
to have
is the only one that sticks.
Unless you're the Power Keeper.
You think it's you, Aquaryah?
It could be.
Look, I'm already getting
water power.
Mm!
Whoa!
[CRASHING SOUNDS]
You're way too young to swim
with us big fish, Aquaryah.
But don't worry,
it'll only be another 100 years
until the next Mermaid Moon.
Good one, Talleigha.
[LAUGHING]
Baby sis, what are you
doing here?
Talleigha's right.
You'll never have your powers
by this Mermaid Moon.
[SIGHS]
How do you know?
I just know, okay?
[PUFFERFISH SQUEALS]
Wait for me!
♪♪
So many mermaids!
It's like Merchella.
[CHUCKLES]
This place is amazing, Isla,
but you still haven't told us.
Why are we here?
To get your powers, of course.
Powers?
As in "superpowers"?
Kinda.
I'm a mermaid of air.
It's why I can breathe air,
like you.
Do we all get powers?
Oh, I need a good mermaid
hero name.
I could be... Gill-Girl!
Hi-ya!
- Hi-ya!
- [PUFFY SQUEALS]
Hey, you scared Puffy.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- [SPUTTERING]
Sorry.
[CORALIA] So, you've brought us
not just one,
but two humans to compete
in the games?
Coralia, yes.
Meet Barbie and Barbie.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Isla believes humans are
the answer to our problems.
Many of us see you only
as the cause of them.
I look forward to you
proving Isla right.
[CHITTERS]
Who's this?
[CHUCKLING]
That's Viva.
She's a vaquita.
[CHITTERS]
[GIGGLING] Hi, Viva.
It's great to meet you too.
Aw, what a cool pet.
We don't have pets here.
We treat all creatures equally.
Oh, excuse me.
You're definitely cool
and totally not a pet.
Attention, everyone.
There are now eight candidates
for Power Keeper.
The final two have come to us
all the way from the surface.
Psh. Land dwellers?
No way.
They don't belong here.
They'll never be as powerful
as we are.
They're the reason
we need powers.
They seem cool to me.
For the benefit of our guests,
let me remind everyone
what's at stake.
The future of our world
is in your hands.
My bet's on Talleigha!
None of us knows who will be
chosen Power Keeper.
No matter who they are,
we must show every creature
dignity and respect...
equally.
I will see you all at the feast.
Until then, behave.
Get in some practice.
Tomorrow, we begin.
[SCOFFS]
I think they really like us.
[GIGGLING]
Look at me!
Zero gravity!
You can't do that on land?
- Ah! Whoa!
- Whoa, whoa!
[THUD]
Not here either, apparently.
[GIGGLES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hi, I'm Skipper.
This is Stacie
and that's Chelsea.
- Hi.
Hi. I'm Aquaryah.
I always wanted sisters.
Wow!
Whoa, you're good.
My special tail
helps me balance.
How come your tail is different?
I was born without one,
so my dad made me this one.
It's pretty.
Thanks.
There are four challenges.
One for each power.
Let's start with air.
[STRUGGLING GRUNTS]
Ha!
A-ha!
Aw.
[STRUGGLING GRUNTS]
Ha! Ah!
Uh, ah, ah.
Oh, Whoa!
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Uh, let's try moving on
to earth power.
[CALLING]
Oh dear, Isla.
Coralia needs you
in the Grand Hall.
Why?
Uh, why not?
I mean, anything would be
a better use of your time
than this whole situation.
Don't be rude, Sareena.
She just means it's obvious
that no land dweller
will ever be the Power Keeper.
It just wouldn't be natural.
Land dwellers have more power
than you think.
Oh, I know what
you're capable of.
Protecting our world
isn't something you do well.
We're here because
we want to help.
That would be a welcome first.
[ISLA] Ignore them.
Are you coming, Isla?
I'll catch up with you later.
Well, let's get practicing.
It would be a lot easier
if we knew where to start.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hello!
♪♪
We really appreciate this,
Aquaryah.
You're helping me too,
'cause the more I practice,
the sooner I'll find my powers.
How will you know
when you found them?
It's more like the power
finds you.
It's just this feeling
you get inside.
♪ We all got a song inside ♪
♪ Waiting to be discovered ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Melody to be amplified ♪
♪ A straight up bop
just like no other ♪
♪ If you ever feel aimless ♪
♪ Scrollin' through
that playlist ♪
♪ Trust that you're inner
greatness ain't far away ♪
♪ Promise soon
as ya find it ♪
♪ You'll wanna rewind it ♪
♪ Again and again
on replay ♪
♪ Turn it up ♪
♪ Let out your music ♪
♪ Like only you can do it ♪
♪ If somebody says
be quiet ♪
♪ Just let yourself
be inspired ♪
♪ Twist that dial like
you can't get loud enough ♪
♪ Turn it up ♪
♪ Won't know
until I try it out ♪
♪ Take a chance and take
some action ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Remember to forget
my doubts ♪
♪ Dig deep
to find my passion ♪
♪ To find my passion ♪
♪ If you ever feel aimless ♪
♪ Scrollin' through
that playlist ♪
♪ Trust that you're
inner greatness ♪
♪ Ain't far away ♪
♪ Promise soon as
ya find it ♪
♪ You'll wanna rewind it ♪
♪ Again and again on replay ♪
♪ Turn it up ♪
♪ Let out your music ♪
♪ Like only you can do it ♪
♪ If somebody says
be quiet ♪
♪ Just let yourself
be inspired ♪
♪ Twist that dial like you
can't get loud enough ♪
♪ Turn it up ♪
♪ Turn it up, turn it up,
turn it up, yeah ♪
♪ Turn it up ♪
♪ Turn it up, turn it up,
turn it up, yeah ♪
♪ Turn it up ♪
Whoa!
Wow, Brooklyn, that was
the coolest thing ever.
Does this mean I've found
my power?
Not yet.
When you really get it,
you'll know.
But it sure seems like you're
gonna be a mermaid of fire.
Huh. Not bad for someone who
just learned mermaids are real.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hot, hot! Woo!
Whoa!
Whoops.
[CHUCKLES]
Sorry.
Aquaryah, what are you doing?
Helping.
And she's doing a great job.
Firing mishap aside.
Look, I know you aren't
from around here
so it's easy not to understand
our ways.
Finn, I can take care of myself.
I know you think you can,
but it's my job to protect you.
You shouldn't be
around strangers.
Especially ones who are,
you know, strange.
Strange?
Uh, I'll show you strange.
- Ahhhh!
- Whoa!
Did I do that?
Whoa! What is going on?!
- Wow!
- Whoa.
♪♪
Whoa.
You got your powers!
You're a mermaid of air!
[ALL] Wow!
Congratulations, Skip.
Wow, I got something
before you did.
That never happens.
Told you she was a good teacher.
Aw.
[GIGGLES]
Come on, Aquaryah.
The feast is about to start.
Whatever, 'cause I got
my powers.
♪ Oooh, I got my powers. ♪
[DOLPHIN CHITTERS]
[BEEPING]
I know I left it right here.
I don't think so.
My bad, there it is.
- Ugh.
- Yikes.
Looking a little rusty,
don't you think?
Wouldn't it be better to get
maybe a tune-up first?
We don't have the budget
for that.
Let alone the time.
That Mermaid Moon is going
to rise soon and when it does,
I am going to be there
and nothing can stop me.
[CRASHING SOUNDS]
[ALARM WAILING]
Except for that.
Fix it!
[ALARM CONTINUES TO WAIL]
♪♪
- Wow!
- Oh!
Whoa.
Who knew that mermaids
could throw a party like this?
Not me. I didn't even know
they existed.
Wait, do you here that?
[GASPS] I've never heard
anything like it.
[LAUGHS] Oh! The music
is killer.
Okay, I gotta check
that thing out.
[SNIFFING]
Care for an appetizer?
Looks delicious.
What is it?
Seaweed, of course.
That's all we eat.
Oh!
Right. Tasty.
Mmmm.
[BARBIES COUGH GAG]
Did they have to leave
the roots on?
Blegh! Sandy.
So, ack, ack, sandy!
[GIGGLING]
Next time try the seaweed
cupcakes.
They're super sweet
with way less sand.
[CHITTERS]
I gotta go.
I'll catch up with you later.
- Sure!
- Later.
Are you really from the land?
Uh-huh.
That must be so cool.
What's it like to breathe air?
I never thought about it before.
Comes pretty naturally.
Oh. I hope I'm a mermaid
of air.
I really want to visit land.
I think that would be scary.
I mean, legs?
So awkward.
That's how we feel here
with tails.
Like fish out of water.
But, you're in water.
And you're not fish.
Are you?
[LAUGHING] No, definitely
not a fish.
It's just a saying
we have on land.
It means, like, you're totally
out of your element.
We all feel like we don't
belong sometimes.
But no matter how different
we feel...
we just gotta remember
that inside,
we are all the same.
♪♪
♪ You know we living
in a big ol' world ♪
♪ Everything's not diamonds
and pearls ♪
♪ Kinda like walking
through the dark ♪
♪ Tryna find your light ♪
♪ It can be a little scary
but I gotta fight ♪
♪ Through my fears,
and my tears ♪
♪ Through it all
I persevere ♪
♪ Standing tall,
head up high ♪
♪ Might be hard but
I still know I gotta ♪
♪ Try ♪
- ♪ Stay true to who I am ♪
- ♪ Inside ♪
♪ Forget about
Our differences ♪
♪ Let it leave your mind ♪
♪ Because you and I ♪
- ♪ We're actually more ♪
- ♪ Alike ♪
♪ Than it seems ♪
♪ Won't let the small stuff
get the best of me ♪
- ♪ So instead ♪
- ♪ Let's rise above it ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ No stopping us, yeah ♪
- ♪ Nowhere else to go but up ♪
♪ And shine the light
inside of us ♪
♪ Let's rise above it ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ No stopping us, yeah ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Keep on climbing up and up ♪
♪ Until our light
is bright enough ♪
♪ Let's rise above it ♪
♪ Gotta keep moving on ♪
♪ Even when it
seems impossible ♪
♪ I'm in bloom
like a flower ♪
♪ Need both the sunshine
and rain to grow ♪
♪ This life is not a race ♪
♪ Even though it can feel
that way ♪
♪ Win by going
your own pace ♪
♪ And rise above
and do your thing ♪
♪ Really no point
In stressing ♪
♪ Right or wrong
Imma learn my lesson ♪
♪ Far from perfect
No one on the earth is ♪
♪ But on myself, yeah,
Imma keep working ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪ We're actually more
alike than it seems ♪
♪ Won't let the small
stuff get the best of me ♪
♪ So instead let's rise
above it ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ No stopping us, yeah ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Nowhere else
to go up but up ♪
♪ And shine the light
inside of us ♪
♪ Let's rise above it ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ No stopping us, yeah ♪
- ♪ People climbing up and up ♪
♪ Until our light
Is bright enough ♪
♪ Let's rise above ♪
[CLAPPING]
Oh, what excellent advice.
I never would have
thought of it.
We're happy to be of service.
We can learn a lot just
by helping each other.
[CHUCKLING]
That's what the sisterhood
of the sea is all about.
And I feel terrible that
I didn't help you earlier.
So, let's fix that.
What do you say to
a little power off?
[BOTH] A what?
A power off is a friendly game
where we test each other,
to see if we can make
our powers appear.
Oh!
Talleigha, be nice.
I am being nice.
Very nice.
What could be nicer than
helping these fish out of water
learn our ways here in the deep?
[WATER GUSHING]
First team to knock
the other team
into our little whirlpool wins.
Little... whirlpool?
More like a huge vortex of doom!
[LOUD THUNDEROUS SOUNDS]
What's down there?
No idea.
No one's ever made it out
to tell us.
We'll take turns trying to
summon whatever power we can.
We'll even let our guests
go first.
[DEEP BREATH]
- You got this!
- Come on, Barbie!
Come on, you're almost there.
[STRUGGLING GRUNTS]
[OUT OF BREATH]
Is anything happening?
Um, your power stance
looks amazing?
But maybe try...
My turn.
Ah!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Brooklyn, what's happening?
Ah! Not good!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
[OUT OF BREATH]
And that's how it's done.
I think we proved our point.
I thought the point was to make
all of our powers appear.
But when one side is
so clearly superior...
[GROWLING]
Brooklyn, you're glowing!
[GASPS]
Yes!
♪♪
[CHEERING]
I knew it!
A mermaid of fire.
Huh?
Yo!
Wow!
- Congratulations, Barbie.
- That was so cool.
A fire mermaid? Seriously?
No land dweller's
gonna show me up.
Fire power?
We're cooked.
Talleigha! You got fire power.
I'll show you fire power.
Unghh!
Whoa, oh, ohh!
[PANTING]
No! Ahh!
Barbie!
Ahh!
[PANTING]
Come on, Barbie.
[STRAINING GRUNTS]
[OUT OF BREATH]
Whoa!
[GASPS] Barbie!
- Are you alright?
- Are you okay?
- Are you hurt?
- That was scary.
I'm fine.
Thank you, Stacie.
Way to move a mountain
for your sis.
I'm an earth mermaid?
How cool is that?
Whatever.
Ready for round two?
This game is officially over.
Hmph.
You've had enough fun
for one night.
Go home.
Now you're on their side?
What are you? Traitors?
Would it really be so bad
if one of them
is supposed to be
the Power Keeper?
We need to do everything
in our power
to be sure it isn't one of them.
That's not the mermaid way.
We're supposed to live in
harmony with all creatures.
Stay out of this, Aquaryah.
What do you know about
being powerful?
You'll never be...
Never be what?
She's too young to understand.
I don't need you
to fight my battles.
But...
♪♪
I can't believe Sareena
and Talleigha did that to you.
I gotta talk to Coralia
about them.
Please don't. We will find
a way to get along.
Okay, I'll stay out of it.
For now.
You all must be exhausted.
Get some rest, I'll see you
in the morning.
- Good night!
Amazing!
Am I right?
- Ooh.
- Woo!
Whoa!
[GIGGLING]
- Woo!
- Whoa!
- Wee!
- Fun!
[LAUGHING]
[SIGHS]
Whoa!
[LAUGHING]
Are you really okay, Barbie?
Why wouldn't I be?
They were picking on you
because you don't have
your powers.
Talleigha is nothing
but a bully.
When have I ever let a bully
get in my way?
Argh! Ugh!
Oslo! Don't scare them.
They're delicate creatures
and they have an important
job to do.
Sniff.
[SNIFFING]
Yeah! They smell a mermaid!
Follow it, my fishy friends.
Lead me right to them.
♪♪
I wonder where Aquaryah is?
She was supposed to meet us.
The first contest is air power.
Use your bubbles to catch
the floating pearls.
The one with the most pearls
when the shell sounds
is the winner.
And, begin!
Woo-hoo!
[LAUGHING]
[GRUNTS]
Alright!
Hah!
Whoa!
Wah!
Aw.
I got your back, B!
- Alright!
- Yes!
Come on, Barbies!
- Woohoo!
- Yay!
I got this.
[LAUGHS]
[STRAINING GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
[LAUGHING]
Oh, no, he didn't.
♪♪
[CLAPPING]
Ha!
[GIGGLES]
For your earth power challenge,
you must built a structure
out of sand
to test your ability
to control terrain.
Bonus points to anyone
who can grow a garden in it!
Ready?
Commence!
♪♪
Alright!
Uh-huh! Yeah!
[SIGHS]
[CHUCKLING]
Yes!
Wow, Finn's doing great.
♪♪
- Good job.
- Nice work.
Thanks!
I never thought
it'd be earth power.
It feels good.
Care for an appetizer?
Blelch!
Still no sign of Aquaryah?
Mm-mm.
It's not like her to just
go off without telling me.
I need to find her.
But if you're not back in time
for the challenge,
won't you be out of the running
for Power Keeper?
Finding my sister
is more important.
Wait up!
I'll help you look.
Hello!
[GIGGLING]
Want to hit up the snack bar?
I hear they have deep-fried
seaweed on a stick. Yum!
It's okay. I'll stay and play
with Viva.
Suit yourself.
Hi, Viva!
What have you been up to today?
Aquaryah?
- You know where she is?
- [CHITTER]
- Could you take me to her?
- [CHITTERS]
Mm. I'll show them
who's powerful.
[STRUGGLING GRUNTS]
Yes!
Aw.
Aquaryah!
There you are.
What are you doing out here?
What does it matter?
Everyone misses you.
Not Talleigha.
If I had my power,
I'd show her who's
the strongest mermaid.
You don't need any power.
I just met you and I can
already tell
you're one of the strongest
people I know.
Really? Thanks.
Hi there.
Viva! I told you.
We can play when we get back.
You understand her?
Yeah. Doesn't everyone?
Uh-uh. Only if you have
water powers.
[GASPS]
- Chelsea! Look!
- [GASPS]
♪♪
Check it out, Puffy!
You're a water mermaid!
This is amazing!
I have to tell my sisters.
I mean, if you're okay
with going back.
Yeah, I'm kind of hungry anyway.
[SNIFFING]
Where's Finn?
Not here.
Too bad for him.
One down, seven more to go.
As you all know,
it is vital that we of
the mermaid world get along
with all living creatures
below and above the water.
You will each need to connect
with a new friend
and then guide them through
the obstacle course.
The first one to the gold ring
wins the water challenge.
Ready?
Find your friend.
Hey there, cutie.
Want to play?
[CHITTERS]
Nice shark, this way.
[STRAINING GRUNTS]
Hey!
I love your horn.
You're a narwhal, aren't you?
In my world we'd call you
a unicorn of the sea.
Whoa!
[LAUGHING]
Oh!
[GASPS]
Okay, let's go!
Yeah! Yes!
This is great.
Go, Barbie!
There!
Woo-hoo!
[LAUGHING]
Ugh!
I love making waves.
Ah!
[LAUGHS]
This is so much fun.
You are such a good partner.
Woo!
Hi, Sareena.
You're so good at this!
Get out of my way, land lover.
Yeah, come on, we're gonna win!
We're gonna win!
Yes! We won!
- I win, I win, I win!
- [CHITTERS]
I mean, we win.
Thank you.
[CHITTERS]
♪♪
- I'm a water mermaid!
- [EXCITED SQUEALS]
Congrats.
Great race, Sareena.
Thanks.
[WAITER]
Appetizer?
Bleh!
[CHITTERS]
Yeah, that was pretty nice
of them.
Why were you talking
to the land dwellers?
Don't tell me you're turning
traitor, too.
I saw how you treated
that shark.
Who's the real traitor here?
Let's go.
- [WHINES]
- Tsk. Rude.
[GASPS]
Hey!
Aquaryah?
Sis? Are you out here?
Uh, where is here, by the way?
Mystic Kelp Forest.
Aquaryah and I used to play
right over there.
You really look out for her.
Just really protective
when it comes to my sister.
Especially since
we lost our parents.
Wow. Sorry.
I can't even imagine
how hard that must be.
Yeah, we're super close.
Plus, with her fin difference,
you know.
Know what?
She just needs extra attention.
She seems pretty capable to me.
I don't remember coming
this way.
It's a shortcut...
I think.
♪♪
What is that?
I don't know,
but it's getting really close
to Mermaid Rock.
We need to tell Coralia.
Come on.
- [SCREAMS] Help!
- Aquaryah! What's happening?
I don't know!
[SCREAMING]
Ah! Whoa!
- Ah!
- Whoa.
Where are we?
[SCREAMING]
Two! I can't believe
I actually got two.
Where there's two...
No, no, we're the only ones.
Don't try and trick me.
I know all about
the Mermaid Moon.
Soon the entire scientific
community will know
how I discovered the secret
world of the mermaids.
Is that enough proof for you,
Dr. Tang?
[BOTH]
Who's Dr. Tang?
[CHITTERS]
Viva, what's wrong?
Is it Aquaryah?
Is she in trouble?
[CHITTERS]
We need to find a water mermaid
to translate.
I need someone
who speaks Vaquita!
[CHITTERS]
She says Aquaryah is in trouble!
[GASPS]
Chelsea too!
Wait, Malibu,
are you understanding
what the vaquita is saying?
What's happening?
She wants us to follow her.
So, what are we waiting for?
Let's go.
Some sisterhood.
You'll miss the fire challenge
and be out of the competition.
I knew you didn't have
what it takes to be here.
You know what being
a real sister means?
It means we stick together.
I'm glad to hear you say that,
Barbie.
Because we have a terrible
crisis on our hands
that needs all the help
we can get.
We have to help the girls.
I understand.
But my sentries have informed
me that there is
another threat approaching.
One that could destroy
all of the mermaid world.
I need all mermaids with powers
to follow me immediately.
I can't leave without my sister!
Go, they need your powers.
I'll get the girls back.
I promise.
Oooooh! We're getting close!
People like her
give humans a bad name.
And are the reason we keep
our world hidden.
We need to escape.
[STRUGGLING GRUNTS]
Hi, fishy. Wow, are you
cool looking.
Do you know how to get
out of here?
I don't think they like me.
But they understand you!
Keep talking to them.
Do you like living
in this aquarium?
I bet when you lived in the sea
it was a lot more fun.
And being bossed around,
that can't be very nice.
If you help us escape,
we'll take you with us!
You'll be free to do
whatever you want.
What is that?
A floating island.
A man-made floating island
of trash.
Sadly, yes.
If it gets any closer
to Pacifica,
it will block the moon's rays
and we won't be able
to perform our ceremony.
We have to stop it.
If the Power Keeper is among us,
we have a chance.
Whoa. The girls are in there?
[CHITTERS]
You've got your prize,
so can we set sail for home?
Now? Please?
With only two mermaids?
When the moon rises I'll be able
to catch even more.
Then, all the world
will know my name.
[BARBIE] Marlo!
[GASPS] Barbie!
This is a really strange place
to run into an old friend.
We're not friends,
but Marlo once tried to capture
one of mine.
Of course you're the one
behind this!
Where are the little girls?
Ha! Wouldn't you like
to know?
- Uh, Marlo?
- Not now, Oslo.
I need to explain to our guest
here why these little mermaids,
why all mermaids, in fact,
are so important to me.
- Yeah, but, uh, the thing is...
- You see, Barbie,
when my grandmother gave me
this tiara,
she told me the power
belongs to the sea.
She knew mermaids were real
because she was one.
Of course I never saw her tail,
but I knew it was true.
That makes me part mermaid too.
It explains everything to me.
Why I always was drawn
to the sea,
why I never quite fit in
on land.
Why it became my life's work
to prove mermaids are real.
Marlo, you really need
to see this.
What is it?
[GASPS]
They're gone!
- What? Where are they?
- [CRASHING SOUNDS]
- Whoa!
- Ohhhh!
What's going on?
I knew we should have gotten
that tune up.
[GLASS SHATTERING SOUNDS]
Oh, no, oh, no!
We're taking on water!
[STRUGGLING GRUNTS]
Come on, Oslo!
Do something!
Ah!
It's no use! We've got
to abandon ship!
Not without my mermaids!
Whatever. I'm out of here!
[MARLO] Oslo!
Oh, no! I can't get it out.
Ah-ha!
[LOUD CRASHING SOUNDS]
[BARBIE GASPS]
- Whoa!
- Oh, no!
What? I'm a mermaid!
Oh, no! My tiara!
[STRAINING GRUNTS]
Ah!
Marlo! Listen, there is more
to being a mermaid
than just swimming around.
A huge battle is going on.
Help me get out of here.
Help us.
[STRAINING GRUNTS]
Please, Marlo.
You know the right thing to do.
[MARLO'S GRANDMOTHER]
Its power belongs to the sea.
♪♪
Whoa!
Thank you, Marlo.
Let's go.
Ya!
Ahhhhh!
Hi-ya!
[GRUNTING]
♪♪
Barbie!
You're a water mermaid!
What's she doing here?
Helping.
No one can help us now.
We need the Power Keeper.
[CHITTERS]
She's here.
- Chelsea! You're okay.
- Aquaryah, you're okay.
She's more than okay.
She's the Power Keeper.
♪♪
Wait, me?
I've been watching you
this entire adventure.
No one is braver, stronger
or more caring.
I can feel it.
You have the power within you.
♪♪
It is her.
Aquaryah's the Power Keeper.
Everyone, aim your powers
at Aquaryah!
♪♪
We did it!
[CHEERING]
Aquaryah! You are amazing!
And you were right.
You don't need my protection.
I probably need yours.
This was the best
underwater adventure ever.
You're the best
underwater friend ever.
You never treated
me differently,
even when I didn't have powers.
Back home, no one
has superpowers.
We have to solve our problems
without them.
That sounds awful.
Not when we all work together.
[GIGGLING]
I knew you had it in you.
Helping people is
your real superpower.
It wasn't just me.
Marlo stepped up.
I feel so invigorated!
What else can I do to help?
The best way to help is to go
back to your life on land
and spread the word.
Respect our world by treating
yours better.
Look!
It's time.
♪♪
♪ Feeling something
In the air ♪
♪ You know that it's electric ♪
♪ Rocking this new energy ♪
♪ Igniting like a spark ♪
♪ It's a burst of magic
Changing your world ♪
♪ If you let it ♪
♪ Look around and open
Up your heart ♪
♪ 'Cause when ya come
Together, yeah ♪
♪ Turn the bad
To better, yeah ♪
♪ Never sayin' never ♪
♪ When you find your
Power, power ♪
♪ Your power, power ♪
♪ Doin' things you never
Thought you'd do ♪
♪ When you find
Your power, power ♪
♪ Your power, power ♪
♪ Look at how the world
Can open up to you ♪
- ♪ When you find your ♪
- ♪ Power, power ♪
♪ Ohhhhhh ♪
♪ Power, power ♪
♪ If you ever thought the skies
Are less blue ♪
♪ Then you're dreaming ♪
♪ Count on your friends ♪
♪ And watch the sunshine
Reappear ♪
♪ It can take
A hand or two ♪
♪ To break right
Through that ceiling ♪
♪ Remember that united
We are fierce ♪
♪ 'Cause, when you come
Together, yeah ♪
♪ Turn the bad to better
Yeah ♪
♪ Never sayin' never ♪
♪ When you find your
power, power ♪
♪ Your power, power ♪
♪ Doin' things you never
Thought you'd do ♪
♪ When you find your
Power, power ♪
♪ Your power, power ♪
♪ Look at how the world
Can open up to you ♪
♪ When you find your
Power, power ♪
♪ Your power, power ♪
♪ Doin' things you never
Thought you'd do ♪
♪ When you find your
Power, power ♪
♪ Your power, power ♪
♪ Look at how the world
Can open up to you ♪
- ♪ When you find your ♪
- ♪ Power, power ♪
♪ Ohhhhhh ♪
♪ Power, power ♪
♪ When you find
Your power ♪
♪♪
♪ Ya, ya, ya, ya, ya ♪
♪ I've been stuck
In a place ♪
♪ Living life by
My own rules ♪
♪ Never went face
To face with ♪
♪ A song I don't know
The words to ♪
♪ Before I was
Just cruisin' ♪
♪ Let the days
Pass me by ♪
♪ Didn't know
What I was losin' ♪
♪ Never knew
I was so blind ♪
♪ Sometimes I find the things
On my mind ♪
♪ Can run far ahead
But I'm still behind ♪
♪ Barely believing
In what I'm seeing ♪
♪ I gotta let go
To all that I know ♪
♪ 'Cause some things in
Life you have no control ♪
♪ And then I wonder
What I've discovered ♪
- ♪ Beneath the surface ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ I'm seeing clearly
For the first time ♪
♪ I'm finally looking ♪
- ♪ Beneath the surface ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ It's so exciting
All that I'm finding ♪
♪ Beneath the surface ♪