Corey!
Corey Gorey!
Get out here right now!
Just don't sit there, get your skinny ass
out now!
You heard her, get moving, donkey dick.
Shut your mouth. Come on.
Get moving.
Come on!
Damn!
Corey!
Where the hell is my TV remote?
Have you seen the TV remote?
Why don't you try the third dimension,
bone head?
Corey! — okay, just a minute.
You know, if
you don't find that TV remote,
mom's gonna sit on you.
Corey, get your ass in here right
now!
Okay, okay.
uh!
Have a nice trip this fall?
We interrupt this program
for this newsflash update, have you seen
this man?
Charles M. Bruno, convicted mass
murderer
has escaped from prison, he killed two...
Well, where is it?
I—I don't know.
"I don't know," I don't think you know
anything,
but I'll tell you what I know, I know my
remote is missing
and I know I'm missing my soaps
and I know you're in big trouble.
Belt or the curling iron, ma.
It's just a remote, a stupid TV
remote, there.
What did you say?
He called it stupid, ma.
Don't you ever talk to me like that
again.
Get the belt.
No.
It hurts.
Ah!
What, ah, ah!
Comfy?
Who the hell can that be?
Probably one of them nigger
neighbors.
Well?
I, my mama wanted me to...
God!
What—what's that?
Get.
Now get him down from there, he has
unpacking to do.
What do you mean? We haven't had any
fun with him yet.
There's your fun, go and get him down.
What do you say, Corey?
Thank you, stepmother.
Well?
Thank you, stepbrother.
Corey, you have the rest of that
truck to unpack
and don't forget that all the dishes and
pots
have to be washed and put away
and you'd better not break a dish
and remember, you can't go to bed,
'til all your chores are done
and I don't care if it takes you all night
and you'd better find my TV remote.
Shall I bake a cake or something
to take to the new neighbors?
You'd better bake two or three,
did you see the size of that woman?
That's not a very nice thing to say,
Harry,
I'm sure she's very nice. I— Corey,
I hope you don't think you're done.
I'm sure she's gonna be trouble.
In fact, the whole family's gonna be
trouble.
Do you hear me?
Why did you guys have to die?
Hey, dipshit, you in there, you
wanna play?
Ah, later.
I need a hall pass.
Have a seat, miss Freeman.
Thanks, Larry.
Larry, the vice principal will see you
now.
What the fuck are you looking at?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean,
I didn't mean to look at your legs.
So what happened to your face?
Um, I was in a car accident.
I mean, my father was killed in a car
accident
and my stepmother was driving
and my stepbrother was in the car and my
brother, biff...
Okay, spare me the gory details,
I didn't wanna hear your life story.
Corey Gorey.
You're all registered, Corey,
take this hall pass and report to room
112.
Thanks, um, where is room 112?
Jackie.
Will you show this nice young man to his
homeroom?
I need a hall pass.
Thanks.
Cool, you like Ozzy Osbourne too.
Yeah, so?
You know he's playing at the
forum this week?
No shit, everybody knows that.
Maybe I could get us tickets.
Yeah, maybe,
but I wouldn't be caught dead with a ninth
grader.
112 is down the hall and up the stairs.
Okay, thanks. Oh, by the way, what's
your name?
What's it to you?
So I know who to give the Ozzy tickets
to.
Marilyn Monroe.
Hey, I know you, you're the new kid
next door, I saw you.
Which way you going?
Um, I'm heading to room 112.
Oh, I'm heading that way too,
gotta pick up my little sister, she's sick
again.
Did your mama do that to you?
Yeah, sorta.
My brother gave me this,
got me with a iron for burning his best
shirt.
Did it hurt?
Yeah, mama threw him out for doing it.
This your room right here.
Yeah, this is just it, anyway,
it was good talking to you.
Yeah, maybe we can walk to school
together?
Yeah, we'll do that.— okay.
Alright, take care.— okay, you too.
Bye bye. — bye bye.
♪ she's got an evil kiss ♪
♪ she's got an evil mouth ♪
thank you.
♪ she's got an evil kiss ♪
can I help you?— yeah,
how much are the Ozzy Osbourne tickets?
Depends on where you sit.
I gotta have the best seats in the house,
man.
Watch, you're over the counter.
I'm sorry.
♪ she's got an evil kiss ♪
18 bucks apiece, go on sale tomorrow at
10 o'clock.
$18? I'll be back.
♪ whoa ♪
♪ whoa, evil kiss ♪
Yo, Sabino, open up!
Yo, Sabino, open up, it's me!
Who the fuck's me?
Biff Gorey, remember?
Ah, biff, my man, hold on a second,
buddy.
hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hold on, I'm not dressed.
Hey, wait a minute, honey, this won't
take long.
Keep your clothes off.
Hey, what's happening, buddy?
Sabino, good seeing you.
The usual?
Yeah, but I need to try some first.
Alright, step into my office.
This is it.
This is some killer shit, man.
Dig it.
Hey, just one, snorkel queen.
Thanks, honey.
Told you this shit was killer, man.
So, ah, same price?
Yeah.
Listen, I need you to front it to me,
okay?
You know I'm good for it.
As usual, huh?
Hey, five days, okay, five days.
You know where I'll be, right?
Okay, man, thanks, dude.
Get the fuck outta here, man.
Get outta here, ha ha!
I see you out there,
get the hell in here right now.
Where the hell have you been?— I had to
stay after.
School's been over for an hour.
— ow, I'm sorry!
Don't you lie to me, you little
shit!
— ow!
When I tell you to come right
home after school,
I don't mean an hour later, do you
understand me?
Yes, stepmother. — well?
I won't be late, I promise.
Now get to your chores
and you'd better not be late again
tomorrow.
Hey, is this
the line for the Ozzy tickets?
Yeah, but we're here all day, computer's
fucked.
I
Mom?
Corey.
Ssh, what, what are you doing here?
Where were you today?
I was out doing some things.
You cut school.
I know, I had some things to do.
I heard your mom yelling at you last
night.
The whole neighborhood heard.
You get eek?
No, but if I don't go back inside, I'm
gonna get eek.
Listen, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Hey, you wanna walk to school together
tomorrow?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I promise we'll walk
to school, okay.
Okay, bye.
You'd better be there this time.
Alright, ssh!
Corey, I hear you sneaking in
back there!
Where the hell have you been all day?
Your school called, you've been playing
hooky,
you little bastard!
Ow, I didn't! — don't tell me your lies,
you little fuck, I told you yesterday,
I didn't want no trouble from you.
Do you hear me? — ow!
Get outta here, do you hear me?
Y—yes! — the curling iron, ma?
Yeah, when you're done,
make sure his chores are done too
and I don't care if it takes the little
asshole all night.
Corey, you forgot that the floors have to
be scrubbed
and the laundry has to be put away
and if you think this bathroom is finished.
♪ too many girls looking at you ♪
♪ do it now, do it too ♪
♪ do it now, it's taking its toll ♪
♪ do it now, I'm losing control ♪
♪ I'm losing control ♪
nice looking jugs on this chick.
♪ I lose most every time ♪
♪ 'cause there's always a girl ♪
what the hell?
♪ that do it right ♪
damn!
♪ I leave broken hearts ♪
Damn, where the hell is it?
♪ too many girls ♪
hey, what's this?
♪ too many girls, I'm losing control ♪
hm.
Ooh!
Where'd the little dweeb get this?
Ha, finders keepers.
Ah, my centerfold.
Hm.
Oh, well.
♪ yeah ♪
♪ too many girls ♪
Don't drop that pizza.
What are you staring at?don't you have
chores to do?
I'm all finished.
Um, can I go out this Friday night?
No.
Please, the school's having a dance
and it's chaperoned.
You have your nerve, you little shit.
Do you think I've forgotten all the times,
that you've come home late and playing
hooky?
But the school's having a dance?
So?
Your school is run by shit—faced
communist liberals,
so if you think I'm gonna let you go out
and get a bimbo slut pregnant,
you'd better think about it again.
Please, I won't be late.
I just have to go out this Friday night
please.
I said no and don't make me say it
again.
Besides, who wants to go out with that?
Go to your room, I don't wanna see your
ugly face again.
♪ no way out ♪
Corey, you little shit, where's dinner?
Well, do you hear me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, alright.
Don't ever not hear you.
♪ no way out ♪
♪ the kids are going to party hell ♪
♪ I wanna go home ♪
And now this newsflash update,
escaped mass murderer, Charles M. Bruno
has struck again.
Liquor store attendant, armen Abdul was
shot in the head
by Bruno at 10 A.M. this morning.
Bruno got away with $13 and a full tank
of gas.
Police believe that the fugitive
is headed towards Los Angeles.
If you see this man, do not approach him,
call 911.
This has been a newsflash update, now
back to our program.
Stuffing, my favorite.
Hey, where are the clean towels, Corey?
Corey, get me a towel and my jeans
better be dry,
I got a hot date tonight.
What's the matter, what
happened?
Hey, watch where you're aiming, will you?
We'll be right back
to our nine o'clock movie, but first these
important mes...
Fat drunk.
Okay, I'm outta here.
Alright, yeah!
All mine.
Fuck!
Goddammit!
Biff!
You asshole!
Goddammit, motherfucker! I
I'm gonna kick your fucking ass!
Damn!
Fucking asshole!
God, fuck, uh!
Damn!
Hey, ma, ma.— uh!
Come on, it's time to go to bed.
Fat slob, who cares about you anyways?
Jesus!
Fucking little shit.
Psst, Corey.
Huh?— come on,
wake up, you little dweeb, get the fuck
outta my bed.
Oh yeah, thanks a lot for the great seat
at the Ozzy concert, that's right, man.
Thanks for the ticket, sucker.
You know Jackie, she sure was hot.
I got her so stoned and turned on by the
concert, man,
she let me feel her all over.
What?
And after the concert I plowed the shit
out of her
in a gas station toilet until she screamed.
You know, she sure was a little slut, but I
enjoyed myself.
The Ozzy Osbourne tickets, you piece of
shit.
Sit back down.
You know, I fucked you and your little
girlfriend.
Now I'm going downstairs to get myself a
been
you get this place cleaned up by the time
I get back,
you hear me?
Fucking son of a bitch!
Fuck!
Oh, oh!
Shit! — hey, let me go!
I'm gonna kill you, you little shit!
Let go of me, biff! I— come here, you
motherfucker!
Come here, come here!
Get the fuck away from me!
Come here, motherfucker! — fuckhead,
no!
— come here!
I open up,
you little, fucking turd!
Fuck you!
Oh, you're gonna get it, motherfucker.
Holy shit, not a scratch.
I'm sorry, biff, I'm sorry.
Corey, give me your hand.
Okay.
Oh, my god!
My arm, help me!
Please, I cut my arm. — I'm really sorry!
You little asshole, you killed me.
He's gonna die!
I'm gonna kill you in the head.
I ma!
I'm dying! You did this, you!
Oh, biff, biff, don't die, don't
die, biff!
Get him for me, ma.
Ma, it's Corey's fault, ma.
Oh, biff, oh!
Hello, police department.
Hello, anyone there?
This is the 911 police emergency number.
If you have an emergency,
you'll have to tell me your address,
because our machine is broke.
For once, I think
biff's right, she's gonna kill me.
Okay, need time.
Need to think, need a plan,
have to clean up.
Fuck it.
Yeah.
Hey, get outta my purse.
Who tied me up?
Corey, untie me right now.
Hm!
I've got some good news, stepmother
and I've got some bad news.
The good news first, okay,
you're going on a really strict diet.
The bad news is biff won't be coming
around here anymore
and he left me in charge.
Don't worry, I'll make sure your lifestyle
remains the same.
See, now you can watch all your favorite
TV shows
and do what you do every day,
only no food, not that you need any.
Now look, I'm exhausted and l've had a
very long night
and I need to get some sleep, okay.
Fatso.
I
God, I'm hungry.
Are you?
Mm—hm, mm—hm.
Too bad.
Bye bye.
♪ I was walking down Hollywood ♪
♪ on my guard, on my guard ♪
♪ you see everything on show ♪
♪ love in paradise ♪
♪ well, is love a sin ♪
♪ not tonight, not tonight ♪
♪ believe it, believe it ♪
♪ when love comes down ♪
♪ when love comes down, comes down ♪
♪ I see right now and I know her name ♪
♪ believe it, believe it ♪
Wow, I've been wanting to tie up my
mom for years.
Biff home?
Nevermind, I can see you're all tied up.
♪ when love comes down ♪
♪ when love comes down, down, down ♪
♪ late at night ♪
♪ I'll be there ♪
hey, hey!
Where's biff? I — huh?
— how did you get in here?
The door, it was unlocked.
Where's biff?
Biff, um, he's out.
Wait, so what you're saying is he's not
here?
Yeah.
Impossible, nobody stands me up.
When's he back?— he's not coming back.
Now listen, my mother doesn't allow
people up here.
Would you just please go, please just go?
I can't have anybody up here,
if she finds out anybody's up here,
I'm gonna be in major trouble, please go.
I have some business to do with biff.
Wait a minute, haven't I seen you at
school?
You're that creepy Gorey kid, aren't you?
I'm not creepy.
Biff didn't tell me
he had a creepy, little brother.
I am not little, I am not biff's brother
anymore.
Now look, you gotta go.
What? Wait a minute, I'm not going
anywhere,
until you tell me what's going on here,
where's biff
and who's that tied up to the couch?
Would you just please go?
Not until I talk to biff, we have an
appointment.
I told you he's gone, he's not coming
back.
Will you just go?
Look, if you won't tell me what's going
on here,
maybe fatso will.
No. I
stop!
Please just stop, please don't untie her,
okay?
First time I ever
double—crossed a governor.
What can I do for you?— why, what's the
matter now?
Hey, what's wrong?
No, I jumped out that
window a long time ago.
If I tell you, you promise not to say
anything to anybody?
Please.
How can I promise not to tell anyone
anything,
if I don't even know what's going on?
Now why don't you just tell me where biff
is?
I can't, not until you promise
and not here, she'll hear us.
— well, let's see.
I don't believe it.
It was an accident, I didn't mean for it
happen.
So is the, where's he now?
I put him in the freezer.
Oh, oh god, sitting next to the steaks.
Well, I didn't want him to go
bad.
So what are you gonna do now?
I don't know about thinking, but I don't
know.
You could call the cops,
you know, it was an accident.
No, no way, I'm not
calling the cops, if I call the cops,
they let fatso go, then I'm really dead.
Okay, you have two choices.
You can either call the cops or run away.
Run away? I don't know where I
could go.
Hawaii, Rio, The Bahamas.
The Bahamas?
All I've got is $33, no way I could go to
The Bahamas.
I know, I would've left home years ago,
but I don't even have bus fare to Burbank.
♪ mine, mine ♪
you want another beer?
No, um, beer has calories.
Biff and I did some really good stuff after
the concert.
Where's his stash?
Stash?
Drugs, weed, coke, you know.
Oh, I think I have a stash.
Ta-da!
dude, this is just a little weed, where's
the coke?
I don't know, I found it here.
Smells good, could be the same stuff,
that biff and me did at the concert.
But I remember he said he had a pound
of cocaine,
I remember he said a pound.
♪ wrap me in real tight ♪
if we can find it, we're rich.
Seriously?
Serious as a heart attack.
At...
100...
No, wait, well, 120 gram
and 20, no 16 ounces in a pound.
You got a calculator?
Yeah, I've got one downstairs.
Get it.
Okay.— and a mirror.
Alright.
And a razor blade!
Looked all day and didn't find Jack.
Jack?
Jack diddly.
Wasn't that funny.
are you alright?
Oh, oh, god.
Ninth graders.
I haven't laughed this hard since my dad
died.
First time you smoked pot?
I have to go home.
Oh, oh, god.
I'll be back tomorrow to help you look.
Jackie, wait.
Don't let me interrupt.
You come back here, you come back
here right now.
I'll take care of her.
♪ whoa ♪
Come on, open up, hun, it's me.
Beat it, creep.
Hey, we gotta talk, you know, we both
live here now.
Not so fast, since when do you live
here?
Since last night, cozy, huh?
You make me wanna puke.
Hey, you should try and be a little more
friendly, okay.
Maybe you and I could get kind of close,
huh,
what do you think?
I wouldn't wanna catch anything and if
you live here,
I'm moving out.
Give it up, bitch.
Hi, Corey.
This is Jackie.
I have a little problem.
Sure you can come over.
You can stay as long as you wanna stay.
Great, we can be partners.
We'll run away together, but you have to
find that pound.
Alright, I'll see you tomorrow
and I promise I'll keep looking for you
know what.
Alright, bye. I
Yeah!
— ow!
Oh, my god.
Thank god. — what happened?
I've been tied here for two days.
Please get me something to eat, drink,
please, something.
Sure.
Please hurry, get me a beer, a beer,
that's what I need is a beer.
I think he's gone crazy, that bastard
stepson of mine.
I'm gonna kill him, I'm gonna kill him.
Hurry. — your refrigerator's empty.
Huh?
Let me try your freezer.
The little shit tied me here
and left me to starve, I could've died
here.
He's really going crazy,
I really think he's going crazy.
Oh, hurry, hurry, please, I'm so thirsty,
please.
There could be some beer somewhere.
Corey, Corey, is that, hey,
what's going on out there?
Hey, tell me what's happening.
Oh my god.
What are you doing?
You,
did you do this?
Come here.
Come here, you're in a heap of trouble
now.
I said come here.
Goddammit, what's happening?
Help, help!
Stop, what are you doing?
I'm gonna get you, come here.
get out from under there.
Come on, get out of there, you're not
getting away from me.
Okay, okay.
Where did you go?
Help.
help.
Stop!
stop!
I can't breathe.
Oh! — oh, Jesus!
Oh, shit!
Jesus, what's the car doing?
Hold on, hold on, I can't stop it!
Corey!
Corey, is that you?
Corey, get back in here!
Hey, my beer!
Please, Corey, help me.
I'm so thirsty and hungry.
Please, Corey.
I'm so sorry I was mean to you really,
I won't hurt you again, I promise.
Just one beer, please.
I'll get rid of the
belt and the curling iron.
I know you're out there, I know you can
hear me.
Corey!
Help me, I need, please, I'm hungry, I'm
thirsty,
I want a beer.
Corey, get me a beer.
Please, Corey.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry, please, Corey.
Water, something to eat, anything.
Do me a favor and shut up!
Help!— I said shut up!
Now I have to go clean up,
Jackie's gonna be here in a little while.
Eat shit, bitch.
It doesn't mean anything
nowadays, hildy,
just a few words seen over by a judge.
We interrupt this program
with a newsflash update, have you seen
this man?
He's convicted mass murderer, Charles m.
Bruno
and he was last seen
heading towards the greater Los Angeles
area.
Bruno was driving a late model, gray
BMW, license plate...
Promise not to yell and I'ii let you have
this.
Agreed?— mm—hm, mm—hm.
Good. I— if you have any information
on Bruno, call 911 immediately.
He has been convicted of the brutal killing
of 23 men, women and children and police
advise,
that he should be considered armed and
dangerous.
This has been a newsflash update,
now back to our regularly scheduled
program.
Good?
It tastes funny.
It's just leftovers. Wanna drink?
No, can't I have a beer?
Just drink.
Fine.
I gotta get dressed anyway, Jackie’s on
her way over.
You'll be honest I hear?— all I know
is instead of two weeks at Atlantic city
with my bride,
I spent two weeks in the cold.
You don't deny that, Mr. Warner?
Deny it, I'm proud of it.
We beat the whole country on that score.
Course we did,
that isn't what I got married for.
Hi.
Hey, thanks for letting me stay here.
Things have been really tough at home.
You just wouldn't understand.
I—I need to use your phone.— I don't care!
Sure, I'll just take your stuff up.
— we interrupt our program
with a newsflash update.— hi.
— this man, Charles m. Bruno...
There must be something better on than
this.
In Los Angeles.
Since Bruno's escape from
prison,
he has killed six convenience market
employees.
♪ that proves the nastiest of them all ♪
♪ a darkened creature dressed in black ♪
♪ they know you're here to attack ♪
um, I'll be up in a minute.
I just need to give a few people the new
number.
♪ she may be hot, I am in hell ♪
Hi Leah.
Yeah, it's me.
Okay, are you ready?
The new number is 555
7520.
Hey, I know he's just
a creepy, little ninth grader.
He has a place to himself
and he'll do anything I say.
And another thing, the mail didn't come
today.
Hey, great, no bills today.
I'm telling you, Harry,
I saw the mail lady coming down the
block,
but she never got past the Gorey’s.
I
Good morning.
Hm.
Ah.
Ah, I don't eat breakfast in the morning.
You got a beer or something?
No, but I have orange juice.
Give me a break.
Ugh!
I've gotta take a shower and then we
gotta find that pound.
What about breakfast?— you eat it.
It's not in here! I'll check outside.
I
Corey.
You crazy or something?don't ever do
that.
Was that miss stuck up?
No.
Well, I saw her moving in, is she biff's
new girlfriend?
Kinda.
What does your mom have to
say about that?
Nothing.
I guess so, I haven't heard
her yelling in days.
Is she sick?
No, she's been kind of tied up.
Too drunk to know what's going on, huh?
Yeah, you could say that. I— anyway,
I'm going to shoot some hoops, you
wanna come along?
No, I kind of got some important
business to take care of
and besides, that's kids' stuff.
Are you out here looking for the stuff
or do I have to do all the work myself?
I gotta go.
You're out here flirting
with that flat—chested,
little nigger girl,
while I'm looking through your scuzzy
house.
Hm.
yeah.
Hey, beautiful, is biff around?
Sorry, you just missed him.
Hey, not so fast, babe, I need to talk to
biff today.
He owes me money.
Well, babe, he's not here.
Comprende?
Hey, bitch, I ain't some stupid beaner
wetback, alright?
I know what's going on here.
Now get that asshole right now
or my hand, your face, got it?
Corey, there's someone here who needs
to talk to you!
You're into bondage too, tubby?
Who are you?— you ain't biff.
Biff, you shithead, get down here!
Hey, calm down, biff's not here, okay.
Now can I help you?
Look, man, this ain't no fucking game,
alright?
Now give me my 125 and I'm gone, man.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Look, biff's not here
and we don't have any money.
Yeah, well, what the hell's going on
here?
Why's the porker tied up and where's biff?
I fronted him an eight ball and now I want
my cash.
You hear that?
I'll tell you what, you
tell biff I'll be back Saturday
and if he doesn't have my cash, you're all
history.
That's all, scarface and especially you,
babe.
You hear that, biff, Saturday night!
And if no one's here, I'll burn the place
to the fucking ground, man, you got that?
What are we gonna do now?
I don't know, but biff told me he had a
pound of cocaine,
not just a measly eight ball.
That lying, little prick, if he
wasn't dead, I'd just, uh!
Damn.
♪ she's gonna be mine ♪
♪ can't you see, oh, what you're doing to
me ♪
♪ can't you see ♪
what a rush.
maybe we shouldn't be doing drugs.
Suit yourself.
How are we gonna get $120,we don't
even have jobs.
We don't have a pound of coke either.
Should've guessed that biff was a lying
sack of shit.
What are we gonna do?
Well, I don't wanna go home.
There's gotta be a way to raise some
cash.
We could have a yard sale.
No, where did your mom get all this junk,
the goodwill?
No, she just wore it all out.
Hey, maybe we could get a paper route?
No way, too slow.
What we need is quick money.
I went to this frat party last summer,
they charged admission, it was BYOB.
By what?
Bring your own bottle.
If we charged just five bucks a head,
100 people came, that would be $500.
No way, if we have a party,
my stepmother would be untied and then
I'm really dead.
Well then, you think of
something better.
We can really make $500?
Easy and probably a lot more,
enough to pay off that Sabino creep
and have a few 100 dollars left to run
away on.
Yeah, but what of my stepmother?
Get real, Corey, none of my friends are
gonna let her go.
We'll tell them she's on
a diet, they'll think it's cool
or we tied her up, so we could have the
party.
No one's gonna wanna ruin the party by
letting her go.
You sure they won't untie her?
Trust me, what other choices do you
have?
$500.
♪ what you're doing to me ♪
♪ oh, what you're doing ♪
What are you doing?
Hi.
Corey, I can't do this.
Why not, don't you like me?
Yes, it's just, I can't do this.
Why not?
Because I want my first time to
be special.
But what about biff?
What about biff?
He told me you and him after the
concert.
He told me he had a pound of coke.
So you and him never?
I never ever.
Then you're a, I'm sorry, I didn't know.
That's okay, I just want my first time to
be special,
you know what I mean?
Yeah, me too.
Do you think you can wait?
Yeah.
We'll take the money and we'll run away.
We'll go somewhere romantic like a hotel
room,
just you and me, okay.
Okay.
Goodnight, Corey.
Goodnight, Jackie.
God, I love her.
I
Did you just hear somebody knocking?
Hm—hm.
I must be hearing things.
Stop!
Corey, hi.
Don't!
Why is there a padlock on the freezer?
W—what are you doing here?
I came about the party.
Party, how'd you know about the party?
These, they're all over town.
Jesus!
Can I come?
No, you can't come.
What's the matter with you?
You, get outta here before I kill you.
Hey, that hurts.
I said get outta here, get out of here
and never come back, alright, never come
back!
I don't need some stupid, skinny, little
nigger as a friend.
I said get out of here! — I thought you
liked me?
Get out of here, get out of here and
never come back!
Stupid, little nigger!
Fuck!
Hello.
— this is a newsflash update.
Corey, are you home?— Charles m.
Bruno,
escaped mass murderer—— hi, chubby.
Continues his killing spree
in Los Angeles.
Another convenience store was hit this
morning.
employee and two customers,
all were immigrants from Sri Lanka.
♪ hell, I can't stop,
I'm not the first male ♪
what are these?
Yeah, they're bitching, me and Marcy
handed them out.
You can put some of them up. — you put
them out?
These things are all over town.
Hey, it pays to advertise, we'll make a
fortune.
But you told me all your friends would
come,
not the whole damn town.
What if the police see these things?
Don't worry about it, sweetie, it'll be
cool.
But Jackie.— drop it.
What are we having for dinner?
Dinner, how can you think about dinner?
I mean, my life is ruined here, the police
are gonna come in
before I tie her and she's gonna, she,
she's gonna kill me.
Don't you have any real food?
That'll be a dollar, thank you.
One buck, please.
Thank you.
♪ oh, baby ♪
Hi!
Hi.— so look at you.
♪ be my baby ♪
thank you, excellent.
You must be Jackie.
So, you must be Greg.
Are you gonna be working the door all
night
or are you gonna have a little time to get
away there?
Um, I'll make sure there's time.
Great.
Well, I can see you're busy here,
so I guess I'll head into the party.
See you later.
Is that a promise?
Promise.
♪ and the promises we're breaking ♪
♪ everybody says you're a real bad girl ♪
♪ prove it, I'll never
let you take me on a whirl ♪
♪ a vacation ♪
excellent.
Hm.
It's going great.
Wow, hey, you don't mind if I hold that
onto this?
♪ I don't ask all that much ♪
♪ all I want, only your love ♪
what the hell's going on here?
Hi, that'll be a buck.
You gotta be outta your fucking mind.
Hey! I— get the fuck outta here.
You need any help?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Muah! Money, money, money, money,
money.
That'll be one buck.
That'll be 125 bucks.
Um, here's one on the house.
Look, I'll go see if she's collected
the rest of the money,
okay, I'll be right back, I promise.
Hey.— I'll be right back.
Is this for me?
Yeah, you got it, you got it, babe.
Yeah.
What, who is it?
Jackie, it's Corey.
Listen, the guy's downstairs about the
money.
Oh, I'll be with you in just a minute.
Hold on.
I'll be back.
Shit.
How about this?
Not here, someone will see us.
So?
So you'll have to wait until tomorrow.
Another customer.
You keep it quiet
or I'm calling the cops.
Who was that asshole?
That was my neighbor.
Everybody, shut the music down, please.
Hey, I like that fucking song, man
and where's my cash, fucker, huh?
We'll collect it, I promise,
we'll collect it right now.
Yeah, fucking pronto, man.
You think we should let her go?
Sign says we shouldn't.
She looks so miserable though,
maybe we could do something to cheer
her up.
How?— I don't know,
a new makeover always cheers me up.
Yeah, she does look a little bit drab.
Yeah, let's do it.
Get out my makeup.— okay.
You do her nails. — yeah.
Yeah, and I've got these fake
eyelashes here too.
Ooh, what a job this is gonna be, look at
her.
What is that on her chin?— ooh, it's a
big mole.
Do you have that cover up stuff?
Yeah, get that out. — yeah.
Oh, I've got these hot pink eyelashes,
they're gonna be so perfect.
This is gonna be a big job,
but this is gonna be so much fun.
I've had it.
Hello, police?
There, what do you think?
I know, watch.
Oh, yeah, that's perfect.
Yeah, it matches the eyes.
I think she likes it.
Hey dude, what are you doing?
What the fuck do you want, asshole?
Hey!
It looks like you have a nice party going
on here.
We're gonna have to break this up,
the neighbors are complaining.
You all have 15 minutes to vacate these
premises!
This party is over, 15 minutes,
then we're going to arrest everyone who
is still here
and we're gonna confiscate all the drugs.
You all have a nice party now, you hear?
Hey, wait a minute, hold on, stop, stop!
Jackie, Jackie!
Jackie, get here now, everybody's leaving!
They're taking all the stuff!
Hey, quit pushing me, man!
Jackie, get down here!
Hey, stop that, man, leave it alone!
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop, stop!
Jackie! Hey, wait a minute, what are you
doing?
Hey, no, Jackie!
Where are you going?— with him.
But you're my date tonight.
Oh, Corey, get back to reality.
What makes you think you stand a chance
with me?
You wimpy, goddamn freshman.
But what about the money?
What about the money?
Jackie, come back, you promised, now get
back here!
What about the money? Come back here!
How do I get the money?
Geez!
What about the money?
God!
What am I gonna do now? She's gone off
with some other guy.
We were gonna spend the rest of our lives
together
and now she's gone off, she's gone off
with some other guy.
I don't know what to do.
You're gonna pay me my money.
Oh god, not you.
That's what you're gonna do, fucker.
Look, man, Jackie ran off with the
money,
I don't have any money. — who the fuck is
Jackie, man?
I told you, she ran out, she's
not here, man.
I don't where the money's at.
uh!
Where's my fucking money?— I don't
have it!
I don't have it!
I don't have it! — motherfucker,
where's my fucking money?
Where's my fucking money?— in the
freezer!
It's in the freezer, man!
Where, fucker?
It's in a freezer back here.
Come on, motherfucker.
Open it, motherfucker.
Come on! — okay.
— hurry up.
Get the fuck outta the way, motherfucker.
oh, Jesus!
You fucking asshole.
Damn it!
oh, god!
He just ran out in front of me.
Is he dead?
Yeah. Hey, this is that Bruno guy.
Better call headquarters
and have them send out the meat wagon,
because of your crazy driving, we're
heroes.
He just ran out in front of me.
Hello, this Jackie?
This is Corey, how you doing?
Listen, ah, biff was right, I found the
pound.
Yeah, it was in the kitchen in the coffee
can.
Why would I lie about something like that?
Okay, sure, come on over.
Alright, okay, I'll see when you get here.
Okay, bye bye.
♪ had every day ♪
♪ she makes me drink 'til I can't see ♪
♪ then digs her nails deep in my back ♪
♪ put shackle here, I'll shackle there ♪
♪ her eyes elated to the end ♪
♪ I can't stop, I'm not the first male ♪
What happened to your face?
Ah, he hit me with the coffee jar,
that's when I found a cocaine.
Oh, really? So where is it?
It's in the kitchen, come on, I'll show
you.
What about last night?
Well, what about it?
Don't you think we need to talk about
last night?
I mean, the guy you left with and
everything
and the money and what went on last
night.
I mean, don't you think you owe me an
explanation at least?
No, I don't think I owe you anything.
You don't think you owe me anything?
No, you're right.
You don't owe me anything, I owe you
something.
Hey, what are you doing?
Getting what you deserve.
Fucking bitch, I love you, I love you!
I love you, I love you, I love you.
— oh, my god!
I love you, I love you!— no!
— I love you!
Stop!
I love you! Let me hear you, bitch, let
me hear!
Uh, yeah, yeah!
God!
Stop, stop!
Stop, stop, stop.
I love you.
I love you, I love you, I love you!
I love you, I love you!
I love you, I love you,
I love you!
Ah, ah, ah, I love you, ah.
♪ where's it at ♪
♪ drop me in pain ♪
♪ where's it at, ah—huh ♪
♪ whoa ♪
♪ she likes it too ♪
♪ my babe ♪
I love you.
♪ she wore a creature's pain ♪
♪ whoo hoo ♪
j'owj'
Something's going on over there.
Sounds like somebody was getting killed
or something.
No, it's stopped now.
Yeah, 12204
oakwood drive.
Thank you. I
They're on their way.
Shit.
Die, you fucker! — what?
Uh, get away!
Somebody help me!
Die, die, come back here now!
You can't get away from me, come back
here!
Please get away from me!
Get away from me now! Somebody help
me!
Help me!— I will find you!
Get away from me! I
I
Oh, god!
oh, get away from me, ah!
I'm gonna kill you!— help me, help,
help!
Get away from me!
get away from me now!
Stop!
Oh, oh, oh!
Bastard.
Thanks, man, she was gonna kill me.
She was gonna kill me just like she did all
the others.
♪ see at the mirror on the wall ♪
♪ that proves the nastiest of them all ♪
♪ a darkened creature dressed in black ♪
♪ they know you're here to attack ♪
♪ my goddamn charm starts to rise ♪
♪ as I look into her eyes ♪
♪ she may be hot, I am in hell ♪
♪ I can't stop, I'm not the first male ♪
♪ wicked witch ♪
♪ her poison brew had every day ♪
♪ she makes me drink 'til I can't see ♪
♪ then digs her nails deep in my back ♪
♪ lets me crawl onto the rack ♪
♪ you shackle here, I'll shackle there ♪
♪ her eyes elated to the end ♪
♪ she may be hot, I am in hell ♪
♪ I can't stop, I'm not the first male ♪
♪ wicked witch ♪