Okay.
do you
want a drink?
No.
Nice watch.
Yup.
Going to be a cold.
A few minutes, you're
going to feel so warm.
You think he was dead?
Who are you?
The man on the board.
Who was it?
We're all here for the same purpose.
Get some sleep.
He looks tired, thinks she looked tired.
Why don't you get some shots?
What's your name?
My name.
Farley dates, um, Morrison
where you're headed deeds.
Okay.
Well, I'm, I'm headed.
Uh, I'm headed East to Jacksonville.
Where do you want to go there for?
Well, I'm married.
My wife's there.
What was your wife?
Visiting Jacksonville.
It's a family matter.
What kind of family matters?
My mother is ill.
I would ask you what's wrong
with the lady, but I can see
you not too deeply into it.
Didn't conversation.
You know, if you would answer my
question, maybe I would be more
concerned about answering yours.
Besides weren't you the one
who said to stop talking and
go to sleep and sound advice.
It was too.
Alright.
Good night.
Good and cold.
It can get mighty cold.
There's a lot of people don't
know just how cold it can get.
Then I can tell you
I was all over Missouri.
Wave.
Well, this fellow thinks scalp
on her hospitable fellow things
were passing through town.
And my first week out, you asked me if
I'd ever spent the night in these parks.
No.
Why?
I said he suggested that I get a
blanket or two, I will address.
Okay,
nice.
One day to like this one,
you at Walmart, your DS.
Okay.
So I'm sitting up on the Mesa inside
of Cherokee territory near Fort lane.
No cover at all.
No trees, nothing.
Knights started to creep in and
the temperature drop fell like
a stone below zero further.
So I commenced jumping around like
a beat, let a square dance got
scared, real scared what a died too.
But.
You got lucky.
This Buffalo came by and I
dropped it with my shops.
Carved them up.
Call right inside is gutted hide.
Yes.
Very nice and warm.
So if you get cold and you need
a blanket, you let me know.
Am I supposed to believe
that don't believe it.
I don't care.
I have plenty of blankets and I thank you.
it's a long way to travel for a woman.
You must imagine she's pretty special.
Yes, I do got a picture of her.
My mother's ill.
I'm going East to meet my wife.
She's visiting my mother.
We didn't know if she'd make it to
Christmas when we usually visit her.
So we're visiting her now.
Can I have that back please?
Well, that is worth something please.
I've been everywhere.
Have you worked inside
the big river, Kentucky?
I ain't never been there approximately.
I live in the desert this past year, but
so you're married.
Yes,
very much.
I don't think I'd like it.
What's that supposed to mean,
but it wouldn't like it deeds.
I don't take offense at that too.
Well, how can you be so cracked?
Sure.
Maybe your nights wouldn't
be so cold and lonely.
If you had a white Mallard.
I see.
You're probably right tonight.
I like to think of myself as
a lender and what that means.
Yes.
That's what I am.
Oh my my mind.
What a surprise.
Well, I don't doubt that it would be to
you and there's a number of other things.
I'm a city boy.
Like you would not guess
that I am while sunny.
I thought I'd be happy to see
another person after a year
to myself, but I was wrong.
Don't think I'm so stupid.
I didn't see that copying.
You got stuck on you bedroom pistol, and
it's a fine one to got stuck on a pillow.
I moved those to a safe place.
If I was, you allowed me to
blow your head on a nut, stop
playing with yourself tonight.
Listen, you talk beyond father.
I did not invite you into this
camp to listen to the spew.
Just who the hell do you think you are?
What about the Darren up your
greasy sleeve and the shotgun in
the sharps you have on that city?
Five farm you call the horse,
correct me if I'm wrong, Gramps.
But isn't that a pistol, not
20 inches from your big mouth,
a Remington judging from it.
Sloppy bulge.
If you wish to plant yourself
elsewhere, please go.
But if you are going to squat
there at least keep quiet.
Well, I think you might be
good for around the two yet.
I don't care what you think.
You want to hear a story
city?
Boy,
what kind of a story?
Something city boy,
I asked to know what kind of story
Oh, one that'll make that splatter
your ears and your tongue blades.
Like a metal cache pig.
Not that we caught his soda,
your deeds story or not.
Don't get smart.
I won't tell it.
Ah,
A few years ago, and there
was millions of Indians.
See, they covered this land like
buffaloes living there, Indian ways
and practicing a strange tribal
rights tribes varied as they will do.
But one hard and fast rule known to
damn near every white man was that
you don't go kick it around the
cemeteries because that's sacred ground.
Not so important today.
See, as we killed most of them
off, we're gonna lose all with a
few of their customs since none of
them had never been written down.
But one, I can tell you a right
and a white man's encounter with it
and old goat name, uh, Lee Colby.
No, he knew better and across the sacred
soil, but he'd lost a half a day already.
And there was nothing
better than to make it up.
Let's see nothing, but
a lot of nonsense I'm ashamed.
I'm ashamed to admit it back there.
I read it, believed all this.
Stupid plain stupid.
It was on his Patrick
Duchess gave up, quit,
lying down and died.
Peaceable.
Let myself decompose.
You you'll give up.
Look what happens.
Come on, boy.
you're done.
Well, your dad
was that company.
You, you, you achieved or some major.
Why didn't you buy one?
Get up.
Look at me.
I'm older than you.
And what does he mean when I
talk?
I wish you
great.
Self can choose to drive away.
Aye.
Hi,
how you doing?
I think I should temp up then.
I guess you Timbo him.
He was just letting me know.
Okay.
Ooh, you didn't have to bite
my head off to prove the point.
You
raised him?
Peace.
I got to get out.
Oh,
Hey.
Ah,
Morrison.
That's almost beautiful.
I mean, it's bizarre, certainly
bizarre, but so much more there.
You didn't make it.
I loved it, but I want to know what
you thought of when you told it.
I mean, it seemed to me about so much
more than, uh, the man being punished for
passing through an Indian burial ground.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Well, why did you make Lee?
An old man, but he was an old man.
Exactly.
So why did she end the story on an image
of children burying the solid man deeds?
It's a story you tell it.
And there it is, but it
wasn't that terrifying.
Gotcha liked it.
I did, but it seemed more about
dying or an old man's fear of death
and about breaking an Indian taboo.
How much did you add the ritual?
It's the body and then
what can be put on that?
And it's what been true or not.
I told him exactly as I remembered it.
Word for word.
Come on Morrison.
I mean, you remember a lot, but there
were so many details to your story.
So many, I'm not saying that you're
lying, but I'm suggesting that some
of it might've been prevarication.
Let me put this another way.
Don't you think it's incredible
that Indians would go so far
out of their way to put a man.
So gruesomely to death, simply on a
County, went through a stupid graveyard.
Oh sure.
The dog let it around you.
The minute I saw your
campfire, what did you or not?
What is incredible deans
that you made it this far?
Not knowing two spits and
half a fart about the very
controllable with your friends.
Okay.
I have a lot to learn.
I admitted, but I wish you'd be honest
enough to admit that your story.
Wasn't all true.
Word, horse shit.
Oh, I pick it by that remark.
You don't want to hear another
two, another cup of coffee?
No, I don't.
Well, well, what you got to tell another?
I've got them.
Don't have him
give me another cup.
This story is about a young
fella, not unlike yourself.
The store clerk namer, um,
would be on himself, traveling
alone by the great divide.
Those grassy Hills, that
roll on just a ball forever.
He was a modest city worker,
hat and coat, not like yours.
And he was slogging along, but
in the sunset did thoughts.
It was pretty wife.
He was going to see
Whoa.
Whoa, Whoa.
Pardon?
Ma'am don't be afraid.
I ain't going to hurt you.
Tom would be, man.
Tom would be
only wondered if you might
be lost or something.
I didn't mean to frighten you
are you alone?
I'll be a pitching camp real soon.
You're more than welcome to join me.
If you like
be my pleasure.
If you've joined me.
Can I help you get somewhere?
No, I'm alone.
do that.
I'm fine.
Looking for a place to
camp, not paying attention.
You don't think it's too far.
There's a flat spot.
Just up ahead.
Pardon me?
Sorry.
I was just saying if it doesn't look too
far, there's a little spot right here.
It looks like a good camper.
That'd be fine.
Ma'am
I stopped calling you man.
I'm sorry,
Jenny Tuberville.
My name is Jenny.
You warm enough?
I didn't know.
I got this cold at night.
no, I couldn't.
No, I couldn't.
You're good, man.
Tom, can't imagine how
Frito was out there.
I was so afraid about who is
going to come across me or who
I was going to come across.
I'm very lucky that you found me and
took care of me the way you've done.
I guess you probably figured
while I'm out here by myself.
Thank you, Jenny.
But you don't have to tell
me any, I was thrown out.
I was thrown out of the
town that I lived in.
Look.
I'll take you to the nearest town and
I'll see to it that you're taken care
of and that you've got a place to stay.
No, I'm gonna tell you
anyone will do the same.
I'm just concerned, like anyone
it's beautiful to have a baby
and anyone who can see beyond
that ritual of marriage.
Not
everything's going to be all right.
Try not to think about it.
You're a good man, Tom,
thank you for everything.
I'm sorry.
I lied.
I had to lie.
I couldn't tell whether
I could trust you or not.
Whether or not you were a good
man, but you're different, Tom.
You are a good man.
Yeah.
You're not pregnant.
I felt safer that way.
When people see you're pregnant,
they treat you differently.
I did it because of the men that
came before you put your different,
I don't want to pretend, would
you tell me you're good, man.
You're a decent man.
Please don't do anything to me.
You're not going to hurt me.
Tell me, I know you're
not going to hurt me.
You're not like them.
Please stop, please, please.
Don't do anything to me.
Journey or fresh.
Pregnant again is before
coffee deeds.
That's terrible.
Sick.
You're disturbed.
What was wrong with it?
What it's disgusting.
It's just sick.
Where did you, Treach
up a story like that?
You were listening to it pretty
good here, but I had no idea
what was going to happen next.
Well, it'd be a pretty
solid story if you did.
Wouldn't it.
You liked it.
He like just went to my South runt.
Admitted you city folks are a strange lot.
You say shocked me.
And then when I do you come crying?
Oh, why did well, if you're
such a godsend, no, at all.
Why do you think I liked it?
Same as anybody likes it.
It excites you.
It never Rouses yet.
And if it did.
So what that doesn't mean?
I liked it.
I mean, did it ever occur to you
that different people have different
tastes and that it might, in
fact it made me feel ill at ease.
Um, the first sign of humanity you
offered me were the story stories.
Why stories?
Well, it's a good way to
get to know a person then.
Yeah, I guess so stories
are entertainment.
Even drive it as something
beads, get to it.
It's not ready yet.
Would you let me finish?
Supposing I were to go to bed right now
as if I had heard no stories at all.
Could I, when you put up a fight,
don't the stories as you call the main
something beyond just entertainment.
Yeah, well, no.
Yeah, that means something more
than just entertainment to me.
Now that you put it to me in that way,
don't play.
Tell me why the hell should
I just got them game to you?
Not important if it's not important,
my story is not important.
If my story is not important and
why the hell should I tell him?
I know a story.
The reason why I asked you all
those questions was because I know
a much better story than either
one of the stories you told me.
I know a story that will make.
That's fly out through
your ears and your tongue.
Right?
All right.
The North went up and made me deve.
Would you set yourself a muddy task?
Would that handsome meant to sprint?
Okay.
as, you know, the war displaced a
good many hardworking families, some
on account of fear of retribution
and some, because, uh, Their homes
were destroyed by the noble North.
Each family had its own reasons,
but many of them, West new land
dealing with the land, they could
rebuild their homes and maybe enjoy
the good life that was once theirs.
Now, these early farmers were willing to
work hard for their trucks because trains
were all they had left besides the clothes
on their back and the people they love.
This story is about the
hidden, it's just such a fan.
First day they spent in town shopping
and meeting their new neighbors,
getting acquainted with the local
policy, take some towns from the South.
Was it comfort after journey?
Almost like coming home.
Take a good long look.
Ain't nobody gonna say nothing.
You too, but I'm going to get down
and I'm going to put my feet on it.
that's right, honey.
Come here.
You see this post here
from this post here.
Clear onto the next one.
Way over there.
Clear onto the next one, one mile East,
we got one square mile of God's country.
Or is the house
puts much too much.
Louis Docker, Mike Finchley
and Bobby Jeffries.
They all said they'd help us out.
And I figure when they
need us, we'll help them.
Other people will help us too.
You're not going to be alone.
Him Marine.
There's going to be a whole
community of people here.
it is beautiful.
So big.
And just like the garden of Eden.
I normally put the house.
Oh, no.
Dare ask you, Paul.
Well, I tell you the truth.
I hadn't thought about that long.
I mean, you ask your mother,
she has all the ideas.
Uh, what about over there?
On that Hill?
I thought wouldn't that be nice.
Overlooking everything.
Put it there under those trees.
That would be so pretty in the
morning to look out the window and
have trees right outside the window.
Just like the rich people do it.
Doesn't matter to me.
What's in your head.
I don't know.
I just think that things
are pretty quick right now.
It's good.
I've been through the log salt
coffee, and I don't think there's
as much as we guess there'd be.
I don't think there's
half pound of coffee.
And I know there's not two spoons of salt.
You know what I want to do when
I have my own room, my own bed.
I want to paint the walls, sky
blue and over my bed, a breastfed,
maybe I'm getting a picture
of you both right over my bed.
Arthur, how are we going to make
other payments after we make the first
author?
Lean data.
It's not that like it is happening.
I think you better rethink my deal.
One woman, ain't going to call me now.
She never told her
you're beautiful.
And you are shameless as what
you are and finessed with a dish.
I love, man.
What kind of shape will not put
you in in the morning and shit?
I knew it.
I knew it was too good to be true.
Oh no, he was top of your bed.
I don't know.
I don't have a clock long passed that day.
I suspect you're Paul's right,
but I don't want to go to bed now.
It's all first night I
should get to stay up.
What is it?
I don't know.
Papa.
He's in an Arthur.
We've got a business problem West of town.
Wonder if you could help us with him?
Wait until the morning,
evening.
Ma'am.
Uh, orient Hunter.
You remember our friends from town?
Michael, just give me a minute.
He said it was late till they now,
can you gentlemen do without, just
for tonight, give me a minute.
You have a honey lunch.
You're going to go up in the morning.
I'll give you that book.
I promise you right.
Oh, so you're not going.
I'm just going to be a couple hours now.
I won't let you do this to me again.
Tell you what we'll do our third.
Uh, we'll go on ahead.
You'll be able to find it.
All right.
Not all right.
No.
You said that before this happened
again, like it is now that we could
talk it over before you did anything.
There were times I said, if there was
time, how much time do you need it?
Before we can discuss it?
You know, wrong for me.
I said, for me, it ain't wrong.
That's a blind, stupid apartment
liking to say it's for what I said.
Hold on log.
You have no idea what's
going on in the world.
No, it's wrong.
All right.
What have you been,
where are your bed?
You're scaring me or I just take it easy.
Did you see, I saw you hitting that, man.
No, no, either Huntingdale Eva, a bed,
people in the world are people so bad.
And so he will, the only thing you
can do is you'll have to cover him.
I was protecting your Eva, but
there was a woman and a grown up.
He's a grown up to be just as
bad and didn't want to hurt.
You want to take all that?
I had good reasons.
That's not marker.
They're not men.
They're not fine.
He, honey, please.
You don't understand.
Please.
Oh, wait from her.
You go inside, ours, her go inside.
I'll talk to her.
it's not what you think.
It's not at all what you're
thinking your paws, not like
those other men out there tonight.
He senses that it's wrong.
Some folks just hate.
Paul knows it is not that simple
and working on him, working on him.
And I believe he'll stop.
We can get him to stop.
He's a good man.
Really.
How can you go to him?
How can you go back tonight?
Ever if my husband, you knew, how am I
supposed to understand anything anymore?
He will stop.
Well, look at what you're saying.
How can you possibly say
anything to defend him?
He chills people.
You act as if it's all going to go away.
Like it's some simple thing, but to tell
you everything I saw tonight, don't,
you know, no, there's a young girl.
No.
Does she know about giving everything
you have to your neighbors when you have
nothing because they have less than you.
She know that that man, that killer.
Who married me anyway, when most men have
turned, their backstage did walked away.
No conscience, nothing at all.
Hi belly full of baby.
That's our work.
Anyway, I wasn't a woman.
I wasn't a wife.
I, I wouldn't have kept you.
my daughter and I will
always, you, you all right?
He doesn't do all things, evil things.
Arthur and I love, and you
can ask Pete not to love.
If that's what it takes
to get him to stop.
I can't do it.
I just can't.
It'll clear,
I'm going into town to get some supplies.
Do you want to come along?
I have so much to do here.
Why don't you ask Kiva Eva?
Yeah, mom, on your pod to town.
I love you, Paul.
And as they roll off down the road,
it's neighboring field broadened,
inviting free arm around her.
I love you Eva.
He says, I love you too.
And we're going to make
this a beautiful hall.
So that's it.
You know what this means?
I like it.
Maybe not as scary as mine, but
that's not what your story is about.
Right.
I, uh, my God, I'm pleased.
And me to please, you put me on
the spot harden and to see again,
did you tell him the last story?
It being such a good one,
you know, Oh, come on.
Morrison.
Yours was every bit as good.
Mine was good, but your
is, yours was a ripe one.
Got me thinking about it.
Got me thinking it did.
And I won't have it said that
a store Krug businessman.
I didn't me.
I won't have it said, I'm going to
tell you a story that will stick to
you like an eyeball to a cactus needle.
And we won't get any sleep and whatever,
would it help if I told you that I'd
written a little and you should expect me
to be a good storyteller, I'm telling you
I can do better when I have a set mine.
Wasn't that good?
Here's was more terrifying,
more, more exciting.
Sit down.
Morrison is not that important.
Shut up thousands stories.
I know 2000 stories.
It's a matter of picking the right one
as all, like you told a good story.
I'm going to tell a better one.
There's no large amount of just,
just, don't try to talk me out of it.
I'm not telling you it's
going to be a long night.
Yes, he did.
I'll split concentrate course work.
Yep.
Got a story
better than mine.
It's better.
Tell me not to drink this stuff when
you deeds don't drink it Morrison, but
it helps me to tell stories better.
Don't drink it.
Tell one better than yours.
Can't take any chances.
Imagine four men, actually
six, two of them are dead.
The four alive men looks to straw for
the three of the dead, the patient.
The distraught fellow, Dr.
Francis Letterman doctor and
the sheriff at the time, bill
horn on the circle H ranch.
It was rainy.
This little get together.
It's a contest to pick a
hired gun to be his next top.
Man, big go cautious as one.
The first two rounds, not many
people attend this too many losers.
You got one left, but
he's the paper, his name.
It was Martin laugh and
Martin's mind a killer.
Is that filthier brutish beasts in
bed, no resemblance to himself after
all he feeds well, dresses fine.
He knows how to treat
the ladies in his work.
He is an artist gristle gesture, the arm,
clever thunder, one bullet clean distance.
And that is why he is invincible.
That is how he stays alive.
The idea is that he's a
killer, never crossed his mind.
Okay.
bill.
You didn't tell me there was
going to be three fights.
What difference does it make Francis?
Oh man, the shoulders to fly.
They didn't choose to die.
I'm supposed to prevent this.
We shouldn't arrest you.
Right.
Oh, Francis, we'll be done
here in less than an hour and
I promise you be a on is fine.
You've forgotten a couple of words.
Horn stupid deadly.
Mr.
Horn, Mark.
It is a place it was before and it
remains, he didn't Martin law, the
best gun in the territory those years.
My second batch.
see.
Yeah, you should do
something about your eyes.
Second thought.
Don't worry.
Going to bed early tonight.
Oh, no, I don't think so.
I got plans.
One bullet six.
You'll just have one bullet.
All right.
Funny man.
the winner of this match
becomes my next gun.
No better paying job exist.
To my knowledge, you'll
be a King in your own tie.
Oh yeah.
Women property power, or if you choose a
little savings to help buy your freedom.
And with those other gentlemen,
I'll make sure whoever loses
got a good Christian batteries.
Goodbye.
you got the job.
All right, Martin.
You're the best.
Miguel put up a good fight.
You must've been and
I'll see you very proud.
I'm going to need you by
sign up to sign the contract.
If you want, you can stay with me tonight.
No, no, I got plans.
I'll be there.
Martin.
Bring the clean water and leave it outside
the door by no means am I to be disturbed?
Sorry.
Yeah, blood blood on a, on everything.
It's my curse.
I can't sleep in this.
Uh, get up.
We gotta get this cleaned up.
Why won't it hurt you?
This is doing, I don't want
to argue about this, Sarah.
I want it cleaned up.
All right.
Cleaning up.
We'll get out.
Okay.
No, just get out.
You get out.
I said.
Get out,
get out.
Why don't you just pay me first then?
What did I do?
blowy where you been, you're supposed
to run out the horns place this
morning to firm up the contract.
Blow you up.
Sorry.
I'm late.
Just give me a minute.
Rough night.
I got ya.
But you better hurry up.
Well, Horn's not used
to being kept waiting.
I'll just be another second.
Martin, just a second.
Bluey
Martin.
I said, yes.
Hey Martin.
This time somebody else
would have to clean up.
I liked of nets.
That was fun.
Oh God, what have I done?
Oh, you did this to me.
Or stick around, man.
Fellow be a fool to go out in the
desert heat without proper rest and
sleep the day and head out tonight.
Charlie, we'll keep one more day, Charlie.
His name is Charlie.
No, I just pulled up on that.
I got to get moving.
I don't want to make it
to Jacksonville in a week.
I got to draw almost
a hundred miles a day.
You leave it?
Yes, I'm leaving.
Once it comes South, we'll go by the
Laramie and stop off at Kansas city.
Well, I will show you two
of the finest sin palaces.
This country has to offer great
time going East Morrison, where
you got it all whole damn wig on.
It takes four days to get to
wherever it is you're going.
What was it?
Jacksonville?
Yeah, four days.
How do you know you've never been there?
No, but I've been there for, well,
in this great country of ours,
I'll have, you know, while I've
even been back in like a Montana
stop, stop.
Don't make me laugh.
No, just too much.
Where are you going?
More Sandino.
Sure.
I'm here to solve where you off to.
Oh, I remember don't look
at me like that a bit fine.
Without you, your city ship, you.
I was thinking of you see.
See what marriage does to you?
You can't spend a day, not
a single day on yourself.
Oh man.
What's the rush.
Picture I showed you at the beginning
of the evening, I'm going East Morrison.
I have to be there in a week.
I love storytelling.
I love writing, but the only thing that
would stop me from going East is someone
I love as much as Elaine and I like you.
I greatly enjoyed your
stories and I'm going East.
You're lucky, man.
Deeds.
There are a few fragile moments.
I'll see.
Y'all sure
you ever make it to Seattle.
You're welcome to spend a night
or two, be a warm bed and warmer.
No sleep at all.
True.
Yeah.
Were you still a city boy,
nothing will change that.
Good story.
Won't change that.
I know
I'm going to be a wealthy man.
Spent a year looking with this
bastard slung over my saddle
will be eight days left.
Now I'm not a professional.
Then I'm not been hunting.
When they first came off the wire Alvin
Dudley, Raymer six counts of murder.
And two counts of armed robbery,
$2,000 reward, dead or alive,
five feet 10 on in 50 pounds,
coal, black hair and mustache.
The statements use marks
missing fingers, scarred face,
or he got a honey right away.
The left eye.
You say it was missing fingers.
no, I didn't say that.
Good.
Hi, Georgia stories.
Come on.
You ain't going to last eight days.