[♪♪]
[birds chirping]
[train chugging]
[indistinct chatter]
RIDER:
Yo, that's my bike!
[♪♪]
Yo, I like that bike, nigger.
Try and get it, bitch.
[♪♪]
Hey.
[TV chatter in background]
What?
Dude, are you fucking serious?
FRANKIE:
What?
It's my birthday today, man.
No shit. It is?
How old are you?
15.
Oh, come on.
FRANKIE: I want to show
you something. Come on.
Yo, no way, dude.
FRANKIE:
Happy birthday, man.
SEAN:
Hey.
FRANKIE:
You like it?
So sick, I love it.
[chuckles]
[horn honks]
Hold your horses.
PATTY: Hey Sean, can you
come down and give me a hand?
Be careful, okay?
[horn honks]
What the fuck is your problem?
Hey, did you pay the rent?
Yeah, yesterday.
Cat food?
FRANKIE:
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey mom.
Hmm.
Care if I go ride the bike
Uncle Frank got me?
PATTY:
Sure, sure.
Can you just put cat food
out back?
Yeah.
Thanks.
[TV chatter in background]
You know it's Sean's birthday,
right?
Of course, I'm his mother.
Just checking.
I got him a cake from ACME.
You know where
that picture of Mom is?
I want to get it framed.
PATTY:
Uh, yeah, I think
it's in my bedroom in the...
In the side table.
[TV chatter in background]
[♪♪]
Oh my God, I'm riding.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck yeah.
[laughs]
[♪♪]
FRANKIE:
I'll be right back.
FRANKIE AND PATTY:
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Seanie ♪
[♪♪]
PATTY:
Make a wish.
MICHAEL:
Frankie, my boy.
How have you been?
Where did you just come from?
What do you mean?
I was in the bathroom.
Did you just get high in there?
No, I didn't get...
I had a cheese steak
on the way over.
I was taking a shit.
You ate cheese steak
before our weekly lunch?
Dude, I told you.
I don't want to hang out
with you when you're high.
I'm not high.
Here, use this to investigate.
FRANKIE:
What are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
[sniffing]
Get that fucking hand
away from me,
you're fucking gross.
No, you can compare it
to the stink in the bathroom.
Come on, just...
Michael!
Go wash your hands,
you freaking pig.
MICHEAL:
Hi Rosie.
You're grossing everyone out.
MICHAEL:
There's no one in here.
Yeah, well I threw up
in my fucking mouth, all right?
Go wash your damn hands.
Okay, okay.
She's pissed.
FRANKIE:
You're fucking disgusting.
No, I think she still
has the hots for me.
FRANKIE:
Okay, I doubt it.
MICHAEL:
Oh yeah? Why is that?
Well, for one,
you look like shit.
MICHAEL:
Oh.
Yeah, well, get used to it,
'cause you're gonna look
just like me
when you are this age.
Fuck that.
Yeah, when I was in my 20s
I looked just like you.
Yeah, and then what happened?
MICHAEL:
What do you mean what happened?
FRANKIE:
You partied too much.
No. No.
I had your sister.
And by the way, how is Patricia?
She's still into
banging black dudes?
FRANKIE: See, dude, I
know you're fucking high.
You think you're a comedian
when you're high.
No. I'm always funny.
I'm gonna go.
No, don't go.
Frank, don't go.
Frankie, please.
Please don't.
I mean, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I can't help it, okay?
But I mean,
what's the difference
between the two of us anyway?
Frankie, you sell it,
and I smoke it.
But it's like no difference.
No, just don't go, son.
Come on, it's...
FRANKIE:
Stop.
Okay, bye Frankie.
MICHEAL:
I'll see you next week, son.
[♪♪]
Hey.
PATTY:
Hey, honey.
SEAN:
Hey mom.
PATTY: Can you go down to the
corner and trade this for some cash?
There's probably $200 on it.
Don't take less than $125.
Okay.
PATTY:
Thank you.
FRANKIE:
You really shouldn't do that.
Do what?
Make him trade your EBT card
for cash.
You know it's illegal?
You want me asking you for money
all the time?
FRANKIE: No, I just don't
want Sean getting a record.
Calm down.
He's a minor.
And anyway, I'm giving 25 bucks
of it to him for his birthday.
Come on, Patty.
FRANKIE: Also, you should
see who he's hanging out with.
Some of those friends
are already trapping.
Hmm.
How am I supposed
to keep up with
who Sean is running around with?
I don't know. Maybe ask him.
I'll do my best.
[♪♪]
[cell phone vibrates]
♪ Look ♪
♪ Eh, right back ♪
♪ Back in this bitch ♪
[indistinct lyrics]
♪ Pick a fence, backyard,
dig a ditch 6 feet ♪
[indistinct lyrics]
♪ What you mean, nigger? ♪
[laughs]
JIMMY:
What up, boy?
WILLY:
Good.
So how did that go?
Piece of cake.
WILLY:
You got that blunt?
JIMMY:
You know it.
WILLY:
Ah, mine, nigger.
JIMMY: Yo, I still can't
believe you got locked up
on some bullshit like that.
No doubt.
JIMMY: Frankie, this nigger
followed an Amazon delivery dude
all around the neighborhood
and grabbed a box off a stoop.
WILLY: You never know
what you gonna get, man.
Man, it ain't worth it
unless you're stealin'
a whole fucking van
with all the shit in it.
I don't care.
Just get me
to a goddamn toilet, man.
I ain't shit all day.
They ain't got no stalls
in there and shit.
Just toilets all in the open
with all them niggers to share.
FRANKIE:
Yeah, man.
The last time I was in
over the weekend,
I didn't shit for days.
Oh man. Fuck that.
If I want to take a shit,
JIMMY: I'ma just go
ahead and take a shit.
Bullshit, nigger.
How are you going to take a shit
with 50 eyes on you?
The same way I always do,
nigger.
By taking a shit.
Yeah, I ain't nigger.
Let's get the fuck outta here.
[♪♪]
[indistinct lyrics]
[car horn]
WILLY:
Motherfucker's tweaking.
[indistinct lyrics]
Yo, check that out.
[♪♪]
WILLY:
Ah, ah.
What the fuck.
WILLY:
Give me your fucking license.
What?
WILLY: Give me your
fucking license, man.
DEALER:
All right. All right.
And what the fuck are you doing?
DEALER:
I... I ain't doing nothing, man.
Yo don't make me
kill you today, bro?
I'm doing you a solid here,
homie.
DEALER:
All right.
Columbus is off limits.
WILLY: Everything from
Fishtown to Port Richmond,
that's all taken.
You feel me?
I got you.
All right, cool.
Now, run that shit.
All of it, motherfucker.
DEALER:
All right, all right.
That's all I got.
Yeah, we know where
you live now, too.
[indistinct lyrics]
[♪♪]
FRANKIE:
Hey.
Um, were you at
the park the other day?
I'm... I'm Frankie.
What's your name?
Jane?
Are you... are you deaf?
Can I... can I walk with you?
I... I know that's weird.
I just... I just I think
you're really beautiful
and I want to know more
about you.
[laughs]
[♪♪]
This is you?
Can I see you tomorrow?
[♪♪]
[laughs]
FRANKIE: Have you um,
have you always been deaf?
[♪♪]
FRANKIE:
Do you hear anything right now?
[♪♪]
FRANKIE:
Damn, that's crazy.
Not... not the deaf part.
Just the whole thing.
[♪♪]
Do you remember sounds?
[typing on phone]
What sound do you miss the most?
Damn.
How do you say ear?
Just like that?
That's it?
What about eye?
Okay, I get it.
What about sunset?
How do you say, kiss me?
[♪♪]
♪ When we wake
♪ Hear the birds
and see the sun ♪
♪ Side by side
our fears are done ♪
♪ Oh, the good time's
just begun ♪
♪ Oh, we know what we have,
let's hold on tight ♪
♪ And found what we're
looking for in life ♪
♪ Call us crazy but
things are finally right ♪
♪ With you and I
the future is bright ♪
♪ Oh, we don't need no more
♪ Oh, even in the hard times
[♪♪]
Yo.
Hey.
What are you all excited about?
Nothing.
MICHAEL: Well, you had a
little extra pep in your step.
Get out of here.
ROSIE:
What can I get you, hun?
FRANKIE: Uh, can I get a
coffee, two eggs scrambled
and some white toast?
You want a refill?
Yes, please, Rosie.
What happened?
You know, a little
work-related incident.
FRANKIE:
Work-related?
Still busting people's
car windows out?
Yeah.
Why are you acting
all high and mighty?
What are you getting
out of those cars anyways?
Like, loose change?
Whatever, you know.
Tools, clothes, random stuff.
Wait, wait, wait.
Check these out.
These are sweet.
These are prescription.
What do you do with these?
MICHAEL: I'm gonna sell
the frames. They're big...
Who's gonna buy those?
I can get 5 bucks from somebody.
ROSIE: You know, one of
you assholes broke into my car
and busted out the window
the other day.
For, I don't know what,
80 cents in change?
Really?
What kind of car is it?
ROSIE:
Oh, aren't you hilarious?
You know, it cost me a couple
of hundred bucks
to get it fixed?
Cocksucker.
Just remember that the next time
you're busting out
people's windows.
Thank you, Rosie.
I told you.
Dude, she's not into you.
She's just being polite.
Please.
Rosie's not polite.
Oh, by the way,
if you find any Birds tickets
when you're scavenging,
please don't sell them.
Let me know.
Come on,
even I wouldn't sell those.
But I'm not gonna take you.
Who the fuck else
are you gonna take?
One of your crackhead buddies?
I have friends.
And maybe Rosie.
Sure.
All right.
What's going on with you?
What do you mean?
MICHAEL: You're just not
your normal pissed-off self today,
that's all.
I met a girl.
Ah, there we go.
Great.
FRANKIE:
What?
Just don't get her pregnant,
okay?
I haven't even hooked up
with her yet.
What the fuck are you
talking about?
All I know is I met your mother,
I got her pregnant
with your sister Patricia,
and I did what
I'm supposed to do, okay?
I manned up.
I did the right thing.
And boy, was that
a fucking mistake.
I mean, marrying your mother.
I don't mean you kids.
That wasn't a mistake.
I love you kids, all right?
And come on, man, I just
don't want you to make
the same fucking mistakes
I made, that's all.
Don't worry about me, all right?
Well, then, so what?
Is she cute?
Yeah, cute?
Yeah, she's dope.
She's deaf.
Wait, wait, wait
what do you mean deaf?
Is this like some kind of
cool lingo?
No, like she can't hear, deaf.
MICHAEL:
Really?
Yeah, but I mean, it's cool.
How the fuck do you
communicate with her?
She reads lips and then
replies with text.
Well, I don't know,
maybe that's good.
She can't nag at you
all the time.
FRANKIE:
Jesus, man.
You really are just
a miserable person, aren't you?
[laughing]
What? What's so funny?
[chuckling]
MICHAEL: You remember
my friend Sal from high school,
the one that owns
that painting company?
Yeah.
Sal banged a deaf chick
back in the day.
Yeah, but she was butt ugly,
right?
She wasn't cute at all.
But Sal didn't care, 'cause
he would fuck anything, right?
Just so...
Anyway, so what was I saying?
Sal.
So Sal, he's banging this...
This... this girl, right?
And the neighbors called
the fucking cops,
because she was deaf, right,
so she couldn't tell
the volume of her voice
and you know, just
look at this face.
Just be prepared for that.
That's all.
I'm just trying to help.
Thanks for the great advice,
man.
As always.
That's why I'm here, kid.
You remember when I was 6,
you'd take me to the ball game
after you'd take me to get
water ice?
Yeah, of course.
Best time of my life.
FRANKIE:
That's what I'm saying.
I mean, back then
you were sober.
At least, I think you were.
I mean, you weren't a mess
like you are now.
What's your point, Frankie?
What are you worried about?
What am I worried about?
Look at you.
Look at me what?
You got to eat something.
MICHAEL:
I'm not hungry, Frank.
It's on me.
Okay, Mr. Fucking Money Bags.
I don't give a shit
who pays for it.
If I'm not hungry,
I'm not gonna eat anything.
I just want...
I want you to
meet my kids one day, you know?
I don't want to have to
tell them that
you died a crackhead.
Oh, what did I tell you?
I told you no kids.
Wear a condom.
[chuckles]
You...
You're just like your mother.
You got no fucking
sense of humor.
I'm... I'm kidding, okay?
I'm fine.
Here, look, look.
You want to see this here.
[munching]
Okay, you happy now?
Delicious.
[chewing]
All right, don't leave me
in the dark now.
Tell me about this girl.
Is she from the neighborhood?
What's her name?
Jane.
MICHAEL:
All right, Jane is a nice name.
Is she from the neighborhood?
No, Fairmont.
Yeah, that's fancy.
FRANKIE:
Not really.
Bullshit, Frankie. That's fancy.
So this fancy Jane
from Fairmont,
she has you thinking
about having kids?
Maybe.
Interesting.
I mean,
I'm not saying she's the one.
But I think about my future
sometimes.
What, as a pusher?
What is that supposed to mean?
You know, I know the deal, okay?
I know that I'm fucked up.
I know I'm no good.
I admit it.
You can't.
You can't admit
that you're no good.
You ruin people's lives
for a living, Frankie.
You know that, right?
For 10 bucks a pop,
you ruin people's lives
and for what?
I don't fucking make them do it,
all right?
Oh.
That doesn't matter, son.
It's still on you.
[♪♪]
All right, look,
what the fuck do I know?
Ah, you listen to me?
You're gonna finish this?
[♪♪]
JARVIS:
Make sure to take care.
[indistinct speech]
FRANKIE:
Why are you talking to Stefan?
JARVIS:
You don't like Stefan?
No, man.
That little motherfucker
is always setting me up.
FRANKIE: He's already
selling out of his house.
Really?
Well, he's definitely
a motherfucker that will
pull on anybody I tell him to.
He'll sling, he'll collect,
and he'll pop someone.
You can fucking use him.
Just keep him out of
my business.
Like this business?
Is this your business?
Hey!
JARVIS:
Hey, you little shit.
CHRIS:
What up?
Do you know who I am?
Yeah.
Do you know what's gonna
happen to you
if I catch you
out on this corner again?
Yeah.
You want to work?
Text me.
But don't let me catch you
out on my corner again.
You dig?
Yeah.
JARVIS:
That's a good guy.
What the fuck.
Keep an eye on that.
I will.
JARVIS:
You better.
I keep driving around here
and I see rival trappers
on my corner.
And I know you ain't gonna pull.
You ain't about that.
But I want you to know this.
Stefan is ready to go.
[phone vibrates]
Yo, I got to bounce.
Hey. Hold it down.
Yeah.
[engine starts]
[♪♪]
NANCY: So, Frank, Jane
mentions you have a little brother.
[♪♪]
Oh, yeah, uh Sean.
He's my nephew though.
Um, he's like a little brother.
But yeah, just re... really smart
and a good kid all round.
She also mentions
you live with him
and your mother?
Um, no, it's my sister,
it's Sean's mother.
My mum passed 10 years ago.
What do you do for work, Frank?
FRANKIE: Uh, odd-end
jobs, whenever they come up
and a friend of mine
owns his own business,
so I do... I help him with
pick-ups and deliveries.
Uh, what about a career?
Are you in school
or do you plan to go to school?
FRANKIE:
Um, I'd like to. I'm not.
Just for as long as
I can remember
I've been taking care of
my sister and my nephew,
so I just haven't really
had a chance.
But if I were to go back,
I think I'd want to be
a juvenile probation officer.
Why is that, Frank?
I just... I think I can relate
with them
and hopefully, push them
in the right direction.
Well, I hope you follow through
with that, Frank.
What about you guys?
What do you guys do?
I'm a professional
stay-at-home mom.
She was a lawyer,
but wanted to raise Jane.
NANCY:
Yes.
And I have no desire to go back.
We know.
What... what about you,
Mr. Stafford?
Um, more or less security.
Like outside of a nightclub
security?
No.
It's basically cameras.
I help develop the systems
that enable you to move cameras
and view them on laptops
and computers.
That... that was you?
MARK:
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, well, I was one of
the developers.
The software was
originally designed
for buildings,
commercial applications.
But with the ever-evolving
tech boom,
the software has now
moved into homes
and for personal use.
It's really not
that interesting.
But um, my company
provides services to
a lot of the
government buildings
around the city and some
high-end retailers, too.
Oh, that's... I mean,
that's really, really cool.
Jane, what about you?
Jane always wanted
to be a doctor.
FRANKIE:
Really? I didn't know that.
Well, did Jane tell you
she's off to Michigan
in the fall?
No.
No, I mean, that's awesome.
I've heard of Michigan.
I know that's a great school.
It's an excellent school.
NANCY:
Well, she got into Penn as well.
Why Michigan over Penn?
MARK: Well, it really
wasn't an easy decision.
Michigan has a medical professor
that's also deaf.
And we thought that would
give Jane the proper support
that she may need.
[♪♪]
I'm sorry.
FRANKIE:
It's okay.
[♪♪]
You know, you could have
told me about Michigan.
[♪♪]
[typing on phone]
You don't...
You don't have to be sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
[typing on phone]
[♪♪]
FRANKIE:
Yo.
Hello?
Fuck. Shit.
Patty.
Sean! Sean!
Get in here.
[indistinct speech]
[♪♪]
[ambulance siren in distance]
[splashing]
[♪♪]
All right.
Your mom?
SEAN:
Yeah.
FRANKIE:
What did she say?
Nothing, dude.
She... she says I'm ungrateful.
Ungrateful of what?
I don't know, man.
And that you're a bad influence.
That I'm a bad influence?
Dude, your mom had me
on the corner when I was 15.
[♪♪]
Listen, I mean you know how
we're like brothers, you know,
we don't have that
uncle-nephew vibe.
FRANKIE: Just, you know,
learn from my mistakes
and I'll be the first one
to tell you
to finish high school,
go to college.
Just follow your dreams,
all right?
Yeah.
FRANKIE: You know, from... from
now on, just try not to worry so much,
you know.
And I know your mom
can be crazy.
But be a kid. Go skate.
Go hang with your friends.
I got you, okay?
I love you.
Love you, too.
[♪♪]
[screams]
♪ I thought that I lost you
♪ Yeah
♪ Thought that I lost
♪ Stop coming around
♪ And I couldn't feel you
♪ You're just so full of it
♪ Now I don't know you
♪ Going through the motions
♪ Now I don't need you
♪ Yeah
♪ Take it back
♪ You don't know what you mean
♪ Throw it back
No doubt.
[music in background]
What's so funny?
Nothing, man.
Yo, I know she said something
about me, man.
So tell me.
She's just wondering
why you say "no doubt"
all the time.
[laughing]
JIMMY: This motherfucker
right here has the smallest vocab
I have ever heard.
[laughing]
Man, fuck you.
[♪♪]
♪ But I lost you
♪ Yeah
♪ Thought that I lost
♪ Stop coming around
♪ And I couldn't feel you
♪ You're just so full of it
♪ Now I don't know you
♪ Going through the motions
♪ Now I don't need you
♪ Yeah
♪ Take it back
♪ You don't know what you mean
♪ Throw it back
♪ Take it slow
♪ Lead the scene
♪ Turn my back,
can't switch up ♪
[indistinct lyrics]
♪ I could see it in her eyes
♪ I could it
♪ We'll skate and shit,
it'll be real cool ♪
♪ Don't try to play me
for a fucking fool ♪
♪ Just like a game
played by rule ♪
♪ Yeah
♪ Trying to act like
you don't know me ♪
♪ Summer came, went away
♪ Please stay
♪ If you'll stay, we can stay
♪ I'm exhausted
♪ Sometimes
I feel like I lost it ♪
[indistinct lyrics]
[♪♪]
♪ Summer came, went away
♪ I'm gonna stay, but I'm...
[door shuts]
FRANKIE:
Hey, thanks, brother.
[sighs]
[T.V. in background]
[door opens and shuts]
How'd you get home?
PATTY:
Suzie got me.
Hey, sweetie.
FRANKIE:
Dumped your stash.
Upstairs, too.
Why would you do that?
Are you serious?
You're such a fucking asshole.
PATTY: You act
like I'm an alcoholic.
FRANKIE:
You are an alcoholic.
PATTY:
No, I'm not.
Sean, do you have that cash
from the other day?
PATTY:
Thank you.
Where did that come from?
I sold my bike.
Yeah, he wouldn't have had to
if you hadn't been
with your girlfriend all week.
Can I not be happy?
PATTY:
Oh my God.
You made a commitment to us
when Mom died.
No, I made a commitment to Sean.
I never said I'd take care
of you.
You know, you should really
be thanking me.
I've already turned you into
a better man than
our father and his father.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm moving out.
[chuckles]
Good riddance.
FRANKIE: You're
gonna keep saying that
when I stop paying your rent?
You do that,
and you'll never see Sean again.
Yo, Sean, could you just
go upstairs for a minute?
You know,
I know what you're doing.
It's not right.
Oh yeah? What's that?
You're doing exactly
what you did to me
when I was his age.
Just let him enjoy being a kid.
Oh my God, I'm so sick of you
making me out to be
a bad parent.
This isn't about you or me,
Patty.
[scoffs]
You have a good kid up there.
I know he's a good kid.
PATTY:
I raised him.
You fucking didn't.
You're not his father, you know.
I don't pretend to be.
[scoffs]
Aw. Sure you don't?
[♪♪]
Here you go, Frank.
FRANKIE:
Thanks, Rosie.
Mike's a no-show, huh?
FRANKIE:
Yeah, I mean...
You mind?
No, go ahead.
You know, the best thing
you can do about Michael
is just really
not worry too much.
I know it's easier
said than done.
FRANKIE:
Yeah, I guess.
I mean, if he's not here
or home,
he's just under a bridge
somewhere.
[indistinct chatter
in background]
I'll find him later.
Remind me not to park
under any of these bridges.
[indistinct chuckling
in background]
FRANKIE: I mean, I don't
even worry about him anymore.
I've just been thinking about
this girl I've been seeing.
Oh yeah?
What about?
What to do?
ROSIE:
What to do with what?
Well, I like her.
Love.
That's good.
[chuckles]
So what are you trying
to figure out?
How to move forward.
Just tell her.
No.
She's too good for me.
You're way too hard on yourself.
I don't get it.
Why is she better than you?
FRANKIE:
I mean, she's going to college.
She's thinking about a career.
I mean, she's gonna be a doctor.
And she comes from
a lot of money.
And I mean, I got no plans.
You know where I come from.
Big deal.
What's important is
how you treat her.
I've dated all kinds of men.
Ones from the neighborhood,
guys from the mainline.
They all treated me like shit.
You know who treated me
the best?
Don't say it.
[scoffs]
ROSIE:
Your father.
My Mom would disagree.
ROSIE: Yeah, well, I don't want
to talk bad about your mother.
I mean,
she... she was great
with you kids, really.
But the way she treated
your father
was a different story.
What was she supposed to do?
I mean, he's a drug addict.
ROSIE:
Back then he wasn't.
I mean, he wasn't a saint.
But he did everything
your mother asked of him
to make that relationship work
and be a good father.
He... he... he put food
on the table
and a roof over your head
and loved you kids.
My Mom always told me he loved
drugs more than us.
That's why he's never around.
ROSIE: I was best friends
with your mother back then.
He wasn't doing drugs
until after she kicked him out.
He...
Maybe he drank a little more
than he should have some nights,
but he was a kid.
Younger than you are now
with two children.
I know he was a good father,
'cause I saw it
with my own eyes.
We shouldn't talk about it.
I'm really happy
you two get along like this
and meet each other every week.
It's really nice you were able
to maintain a relationship.
You ever thought about
maybe not seeing him anymore?
What do you mean?
I'm just saying,
maybe a little tough love
would be good for him, you know.
Like you meeting up with him
every week,
ROSIE: it's like he's not
doing anything wrong.
I think he just needs
a push in the right direction.
Maybe I'm wrong, I don't know.
I know he doesn't say this,
because men have fucked-up egos,
but he loved your mother.
Really.
Like for real.
First love.
Like, you know, like this girl
you're falling in love with.
Yeah, I just, you know,
I just think what if...
What if she's not in love
with me, you know,
like my Mom and my dad?
Oh, Frankie.
Don't be a wimp.
[chuckles]
Life's too short.
Yeah.
ROSIE:
See you.
I'm off.
[♪♪]
FRANKIE:
Yo, dad.
[indistinct music on TV
in background]
FRANKIE:
Dad.
[indistinct music on TV
in background]
[♪♪]
[breaths heavily]
FRANKIE:
Dad?
Frank.
I need your help, son.
FRANKIE:
Are you all right?
Yeah.
MICHEAL: I... I just...
I'm really screwed up.
I just need something
to get my act...
Your hand is all fucked up.
MICHAEL:
I just need you to help me.
I just need something
to clear my head.
Can you just help... help me out?
No.
Why not?
I told you I'd never do that.
Okay, can you just
loan me some money then?
No, I can't.
Just fucking help me, kid.
[breaths heavily]
I'm gonna leave.
MICHAEL:
No, no.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[grunts]
I'm sorry.
I just...
I just need you to help me.
MICHEAL:
Please, just please.
Just let me
take you to the hospital.
They'll get you better.
No hospital, I...
Can you hook me up now...
No, no, no, no, listen.
And I'll go.
I promise that I'll go with you.
I promise.
MICHEAL:
Just, but, just...
Can you hook me up?
[♪♪]
Please?
FRANKIE:
Hang on.
[♪♪]
FRANKIE: Hi, there's
a... there's a crackhead
on Malborough and Columbus.
He's smashing car windows
and stealing shit.
Okay, thank... thank you.
Thank you.
[♪♪]
[police siren]
I'm gonna grab my purse
and let's go.
Hey, can we just chill
and like maybe watch a movie
or something?
I don't want to.
My dad is upset.
Why?
He has a copy of your record.
Oh.
How did he get that?
He just can with his work.
Is it all true?
I don't... I don't know.
What does it say?
Theft. Assault.
Is it all true?
Yeah.
Why?
I mean, it's hard to explain.
Look, I don't come from this.
Like not many people
come from this.
What do you mean this?
Nothing was handed to me either.
Your dad ever try to
trade you for crack?
No.
What are we talking about here?
I want to help you.
Help me with what?
However I can.
You can't.
What if I stayed here?
What do you mean?
I went to college here
instead of Michigan.
We could be together.
We could live together.
You can't stay here.
Why? Penn is better.
No, it doesn't have
the deaf doctor dude.
It's the whole reason
you're going to Michigan.
I'm not gonna be the reason.
Plus, your dad already
hates me enough.
How do you expect this to work?
I'm staying.
No, you're not.
I'm leaving.
JANE:
No. No.
I love you.
You love me?
How do you know?
I can't explain it,
but I love you.
I don't know what
you want me to say.
Come with me then?
I can't come, Jane.
You know that.
I have Sean.
Then I'm staying.
Jane, Jane.
Jane, look at me.
I'm telling my dad tonight.
Why would you do that, Jane?
Because I love you.
And I know you're better than
anything you've donein your past.
Well, I don't love you.
Yes you do.
Frankie.
FRANKIE:
Stop. Stop!
How am I supposed to be
with a fucking deaf girl?
I don't know you.
You don't know me.
You're just
a fucking handicap girl
I fucking took advantage of,
okay?
You're right. I don't know you.
Get out.
Get out!
[♪♪]
No doubt.
You mind if I light up?
FRANKIE:
No, no. Go ahead.
WILLY:
[indistinct speech]
Yo, so uh, what's up with Jane?
You ever work that out?
[sighs]
No.
She leaves for college
in a few days.
WILLY:
Man.
I liked her.
You gonna call her?
No, I kind of said
some rude shit.
So apologize.
We all say shit we don't mean
when we're pissed off.
[breathes in]
What about that GED?
You take that test?
FRANKIE:
No.
[exhales out]
No doubt.
Why not?
FRANKIE:
And why do you care?
WILLY:
Just asking.
[inhale then exhale]
The way I see it,
this here can go two ways.
Either in jail or dead.
"A pessimist sees a difficulty
in every opportunity.
An optimist sees the opportunity
in every difficulty."
[inhales]
Winston Churchill said that.
[exhales]
FRANKIE: How do you know
Winston Churchill quotes?
[chuckles]
I literally watch
History channel all day.
[chuckles]
I love that shit.
[laughing]
You know what?
Why are you still doing this?
I know your grandma
made you graduate.
You know how many times
I tried to get a regular job.
I'm talking McDonald's,
Burger King.
No one would hire me.
WILLY:
I don't know.
You know, shit. I tried.
[inhales]
I got plans, though.
[exhales]
Right now, I'm just trying to
pay my grandma's mortgage
she keeps getting behind on,
'cause social security
ain't shit.
I didn't know she owned that.
Yup.
That house, though?
That's what's gonna be
what build my wealth.
[inhales]
Property, homie.
[exhales]
It took my grandma 50 years
to even have the opportunity
to be able to own.
So, you know I got to
keep that dream alive.
I don't know no other niggers
that own houses.
I didn't know you had it
planned out like that.
WILLY:
You better get that GED, nigger.
[exhales]
[laughs]
[indistinct chatter]
DRIVER (OS):
I appreciate it.
FRANKIE: Hey, what
the fuck are you doing?
Nothing.
FRANKIE: What did you
just put in your pocket?
What the fuck is this?
What the fuck, dude?
Are you dealing now?
Fucking answer me.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
PATTY:
Look in the cupboards, Frank.
There's not a freaking thing
in there.
We got no food, no toilet paper.
What the fuck is that?
Where is it?
In my room.
You forgot the ketchup.
FRANKIE:
That's it?
Yeah.
FRANKIE:
Who gave it to you?
Stefan.
PATTY: Calm down. It's just oxy.
Fuck you, Patty.
FRANKIE:
Yo, Stefan.
STEFAN:
Yo, what's up?
FRANKIE:
Stay away from Sean.
You hear me?
Fuck you, nigger.
I'm Sean's step daddy.
What?
What, you ain't know?
Me and your sister like this.
Yo, stay away from Sean,
all right?
Fuck you gonna do about it?
Like I thought, nigger.
[♪♪]
I love you.
FRANKIE:
I love you, too.
[♪♪]
[indistinct chatter
in background]
[phone vibrates]
[breathing heavily]
What's up?
Woah, okay. All right, man.
Just uh...
Yeah, just tell Jarvis.
We'll handle it.
All right, cool.
All right, peace.
MAN 1: I've been out here.
You know what I mean?
They just try to act like
they know me.
Niggers don't know me, nigger.
That's what I tell them.
You know what I mean?
I'm good at what I am.
[thudding]
[gun shots]
[♪♪]
[knocks the door]
[indistinct music in background]
FRANKIE: Yo, why did
you let Stefan do that?
That kid was probably
Sean's age.
I don't give a shit.
It's money out of my pocket.
FRANKIE:
The dude's a fucking kid.
Plus, I had it handled.
Excuse me?
Stefan handled it.
You see, you're not gonna see
one of those motherfuckers
on one of my corners again.
You feel me?
Stefan made sure of that.
I made sure of that.
[indistinct music in background]
[exhales]
What's all that?
I quit, dude.
JARVIS:
You quit?
Yeah.
I need your whole crew.
It's all Willy, dude.
He'll take care of you.
FRANKIE:
He needs the income, though.
[chuckles]
[indistinct music in background]
I hope so.
We good?
[indistinct music in background]
As long as that money comes in,
we are.
All right, I'll see you around,
man.
I'll see you later.
[shuts the door]
[♪♪]
[knocking the door]
[shuts the door]
MICHAEL:
Hey.
FRANKIE:
Hey, I got you a hoagie.
Oh, nice.
Thanks.
Can I come in?
[scoffs]
MICHAEL: Yeah, yeah. I'm
sorry. Yeah, come on, come on.
Come on.
FRANKIE:
So how are you feeling?
I'm all right, you know.
Good days and bad days.
FRANKIE:
Your 30 days up?
Uh, yesterday. I still got to
go to meetings, I mean...
I mean, that's good.
Are they mandatory?
Yeah, but it's okay.
I would go anyway.
I mean, I'm done with that shit.
I hope so.
I mean, I'd rather not
find you under a 95
crying like a little bitch
again.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I never
thanked you for that.
I appreciate it.
No, I'm...
I'm not fucking around.
You did the right thing.
So, you know, how's the girl?
FRANKIE:
We broke up.
Yeah, I kind of figured.
FRANKIE:
Why is that?
Because you're not
prancing around here
like you're all high and mighty
like you were before.
[chuckles]
At least you still got
your sense of humor.
Yeah.
What can I say?
All right, well,
I'm glad you're good.
I'm gonna head out.
No, no. Hold on, son.
How are you doing?
I mean, about that,
are you all right?
Me? I'm fine.
You sure?
Yeah, why?
Well, you know,
for the last 10 years
every time I saw you,
you were angry about something,
you know, and it was only when
this deaf girl came into
the picture that you were all
positive and smiles.
Look, I know that I fucked up
with you and your sister.
I mean, I had a lot of time
to think about this shit.
I'm fine.
No, just hear me out, all right?
I mean, you know,
your Mom, God rest her soul,
you know, she... she let me back
into her life
when she got diagnosed
with the cancer, you know,
she felt guilty, because
she blamed herself
for my addiction
and for being a fuck-up.
And so she let me back in,
you know, and...
You know, I really loved
your Mom.
You know, I really did,
more than anything.
I don't...
I don't even care anymore.
I mean, I don't.
I don't want to talk about Mom.
Did you know I stole from her
on her death bed?
I'm so ashamed of that.
I mean, I never apologized
for that.
She didn't deserve that.
No, wait. Please.
[breaths heavily]
I'm ashamed of that and
I've done some fucked-up things
in my life.
But the thing
I'm most ashamed of
is how I treated you and Patty.
[scoffs]
What, dad?
You found Jesus now
or something?
No, fuck that, son.
This is not about, you know,
steps and recovery
or making amends.
I'm not even close to that yet.
But I want you to know
that I know
that I was a selfish man
and a horrible father, okay?
And I'm gonna do
everything in my power
and make it up to you
and your sister.
I promise.
All right, look, I forgave you
like years ago.
That's why we still
see each other.
I mean, good luck with Patty,
though.
Maybe you can get through
to her with your bonding
on addiction.
MICHEAL:
Yeah, fuck it.
You got to understand.
Son, alcoholics are just
different, all right?
I mean, it's easy to deny
you're doing something wrong
when everybody you know
has a drink every now and then,
all right?
But for us druggies, I mean,
drugs, they're illegal, right?
So we know right from the start
that we hide when we use.
We know what we're doing
is wrong.
Look, if she wants to
waste her life drinking all day,
I don't care.
But when you manipulate
your 15-year-old brother
to go deal on the street,
and then you do the same thing
to your son,
that's what I don't understand.
Yeah, see, that's my fault too,
kid.
No, seriously, your Mom,
she over... over-compensated
because I wasn't around,
that she just gave Patty
everything she wanted
and it just backfired, you know.
She has this
sense of entitlement.
She thinks everybody
owes her something.
I mean, the only person
who owes her anything is me,
'cause I'm the one
who fucked up the most.
I'm sorry I fucked up
with you guys.
I'm sorry.
And I'm gonna spend
the rest of my life
trying to make it up
to you guys.
I swear to God.
Just stay sober.
It's all I want.
That's the plan.
Come here, you.
Fuck.
MICHEAL:
Oh man, I missed you, kid.
I love you, kid.
FRANKIE:
I love you, too.
MICHAEL:
All right.
Something must have got into
my eye.
So you hear I start working
for Sal this week?
Really?
MICHAEL: Yeah, yeah, he
offered to hire you too, if you want.
He did?
Yeah, don't get too pumped.
It's only 10 bucks an hour.
How am I supposed to
cover anything with that?
Well, you got a million
job offers lined up?
It's a start.
Yeah. All right, fuck it.
What else am I gonna do?
MICHAEL:
Exactly.
This is his number.
Call him.
Get on a crew next week.
You know, maybe uh, maybe
we'll work together.
I'll show you the ropes.
Okay, cool.
The Birds are playing,
you wanna... You want
to watch the game?
Yeah.
Come on, come on.
You got the ham and cheese?
FRANKIE:
Yeah.
MICHAEL:
Attaboy.
Dude, I don't fucking
get this math shit.
SEAN:
What is it?
It just says to
simplify the given expression.
SEAN:
Can I see?
Go ahead.
SEAN:
Okay.
Three plus parenthesis,
three minus eight parenthesis,
squared, minus seven.
Dude, I used to
hate this stuff, too.
But math I like,
'cause if you know how to
attack the formulas,
then you're good.
So all you want to do is start
within the parentheses first.
So it's three minus eight,
which is negative five.
Then negative five
times negative five
is 25.
Squared means it's that number
times that same number.
Oh my God, dude.
I don't get it.
SEAN: Like I said, it's
all about knowing how to
attack the formulas.
Okay, so we have 25,
and now we just go outside
the parentheses
and work the problem
from left to right.
So it's three plus 25
minus seven.
21.
Exactly.
Sean, you're fucking smart,
dude.
[chuckles]
Dude, I just pay attention
in class.
[♪♪]
SAL:
Now, let me tell you something.
A lot of people think
this kind of work is for chumps.
But it's not.
It's... it's my art.
This is painting.
Not that stuff that Van Gogh
and Picasso did.
That stuff's bullshit.
It is what it is.
It stays that way forever.
It never changes.
This is meant for change.
New beginnings.
All right?
You get a roommate,
you rent your room out,
you paint it.
Maybe you're gonna
turn your bedroom
into an office.
You paint it.
Maybe you have a kid on the way.
You turn it into a nursery.
So you paint it.
Each layer of paint
is a new beginning.
A fresh start.
It getting too sentimental
for you?
No.
I just want you to
take pride in what you do, man.
SAL:
This is... this is real art.
This is God's work right here.
[indistinct lyrics]
[♪♪]
♪ How could I know
♪ How my head stayed
♪ Waking up
SEAN: Okay, "the
following are excerpts from
the US Constitution,
Article 1, Section 8.
Congress shall have the power
to raise and support armies,
to provide and maintain a navy,
to provide for organizing,
arming and disciplining
the militia.
Article 2, Section 2.
The President shall be
commander in chief of
the army and navy of the US.
Which of these
fundamental principles
do these excerpts reflect?
A, Federalism.
B, Limited Government.
C, Separation of Powers.
Or D, Judicial Review?"
Easy.
C, Separation of Powers.
Eh.
FRANKIE:
You serious?
SEAN:
Haha, no. I'm just kidding.
You got it right.
Don't play with me like that.
All right, let's do another.
SEAN: Yeah, let's
do a science question.
Go for it.
Okay, true or false.
Most of the nervous system
response inside of your body
is not in your control.
True.
See, Frankie.
You got this, man.
Hey.
[snapping fingers]
Ooh.
That's the one.
[♪♪]
Yo, what's up?
Good.
We're all ready.
Catch you later.
I'll be there.
FRANKIE:
How's your head?
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, you're gonna be late.
SEAN: Hey, don't forget
mom's birthday is tonight.
FRANKIE:
I know.
Meet me at the flower spot
after school.
This is Sean, my little nephew.
That's cool.
He's really good at skating.
Skateboarding.
Yeah.
How old is he?
Only 15.
Oh wow.
So what's he, in high school?
Yeah.
Oh wow, look at that.
I'd break my neck.
[laughing]
Yeah, it was from
when he was 13, too.
I'd climb a 30-foot ladder
before I do that.
You take that test
you want to take?
FRANKIE:
No, I still have two days.
Yeah? You're nervous about it?
Well, I mean, a little bit.
He helped me study, so...
Nice. That's pretty cool.
He's smart as fuck, dude.
Yeah.
Hey, is it still cool
if I cut out early
to meet Sean?
Yeah, yeah, that's fine.
All right. Only like 10 minutes.
That's cool, that's cool.
We only got a little bit to do.
Thanks.
You did good today.
Appreciate it.
[♪♪]
Frankie!
[wind blowind
and water dripping in distance]
PATTY: Why are you
busting in here like that?
What happened to your shirt?
Money, cat food.
Everything you need is in there.
PATTY:
What's that for?
Frank, what the fuck
is going on?
Frank.
[loads the gun]
FRANKIE:
Sean is dead.
What do you mean Sean is...
Sean is fucking dead!
No, no. What happened?
What happened?
What'd you do?
What did I do?
You fucking did this.
Stefan, your fucking boyfriend.
Frank, Frank, no, no, no.
This is what happens.
This is what fucking happens.
This is what you did.
PATTY:
Frank!
Please.
Where are you going?
[glass breaks]
Frank!
[sobbing]
[♪♪]
[phone rings]
JIMMY:
Yo?
All right.
Good, let me know.
Yo, Rashid just told me
they're right on Tioga.
[indistinct chatter]
MAN 2:
What's up, homie?
[indistinct speech]
Definitely.
STEFAN: I'ma come back
up here see if he's gone.
MAN 2: I'm gonna be on
the block waiting for you.
[indistinct speech]
[♪♪]
This is on me. Stay here.
[Willy and Jimmy indistinct
chatter]
Yo, stay in the fucking car.
It's fucking...
FRANKIE:
Stay in the fucking car.
[indistinct speech]
[♪♪]
[loads the gun]
[gun shot]
[♪♪]
[police siren in distance]
JIMMY:
Yo, come on.
We better go.
Frank.
[police siren in distance]
[♪♪]
[water running]
[door knocking]
CHERYL: Hurry up, get
your ass down here. He's here.
Can you get off your phone?
He's here.
Hello. Come on in.
I'm Cheryl.
FRANKIE:
Hi, I'm Frankie.
That's Colin.
Hey, Colin.
How you doing?
Yeah, how about yourself?
Good.
I'm Frankie.
I'm gonna be
your probation officer.
Okay.
FRANKIE: You know, I used
to live in this neighborhood.
All right. Cool.
[♪♪]
♪ Oh, I ain't gonna
live like this no more ♪
♪ Most of my life's
been waging war ♪
♪ I've found peace,
I could have swore ♪
[♪♪]
♪ Oh, I ain't gonna live
like this no more ♪
♪ Hurting as bad
as the years before ♪
♪ Living in a lie
I can't no more ♪
♪ Oh, I had to cut ties
to settle the score ♪
♪ I ain't gonna live like this
no more ♪
[♪♪]
♪ Oh, I ain't gonna live
like this no more ♪
♪ I've been drinking till
my body's sore ♪
♪ Ain't touched my bed
to sleep on ♪
♪ Well, I'm gonna
get on my feet ♪
♪ Get on my chores
♪ Get some things from
the candy store ♪
♪ This old ship's
coming back to shore ♪
♪ 'Cause I ain't gonna live
like this no more ♪
[♪♪]
♪ Let's paint you a garden
where everything grows ♪
♪ Where the wild flowers bloom
from an open window ♪
♪ Now, I'll carry life
with cracks in my hands ♪
♪ Spent my life fretting,
but here I am ♪
♪ Spent my life fretting