(soft music)
(glass shattering)
(water babbling)
(bus engine roaring)
(wind blowing)
- Hey you, Teddy? - Yeah, Leo?
- [Leo] Yeah, you wanna throw your stuff in the trunk?
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
So what are you writing?
- [Teddy] A novel.
I've been stuck at the last third for a long time.
I just need some time to really nail it, you know?
- [Leo] Yeah.
Well, I don't write, but I know what you mean.
- This is amazing. - Yeah.
You'll be out here in the middle of nowhere for a while.
- [Teddy] No kidding.
- [Leo] You'll get a lot of writing done.
- [Teddy] How long have you been acting?
- [Leo] Oh, I've been trying for about four years now.
- How's it going? - It's okay.
I mean mostly small stuff.
No commercials yet or anything.
- Yeah, that must be tough.
God, Leo, this is amazing.
- Wait 'til you see inside.
- Great.
- [Leo] How about a drink?
- [Teddy] What do you like to do here?
- [Leo] Crispin pays me a bit to keep the place in shape.
Lots of great hikes.
Sometimes I play music and I like to dance.
You know, in private.
- [Teddy] Cool.
- [Leo] I don't usually admit that.
(mellow music)
- Jesus.
- [Leo] Yeah.
- It just, you don't see this many stars
in the city.
Kind of puts things in perspective.
(chuckling)
- You must be exhausted.
- I am gonna pass out soon.
- Sorry we got so drunk.
Was kind of my influence.
- [Teddy] I like to drink too.
Good thing I'm not staying.
- You wouldn't get any work done.
- It's be nice if you stopped by though.
It could get lonely otherwise.
- Yeah, I'll see.
(bright music)
♪ Try me, sun's last today
♪ Before it all became
♪ Falling not to get up
♪ Before nothing could change
♪ Balance, ticking, what's there ♪
♪ Trying senseless (indistinct) ♪
- Hi.
- How'd you sleep?
- Great.
I think I have a hangover though.
Hm, what time is it?
- It feels late.
- I need a shower.
- Shower doesn't work.
- What?
- It's busted.
- When I stay here, usually I don't bathe most of the time,
but when I do...
- What do you do?
- You got a bathing suit?
- Um, no.
- Crispin's got one that you can borrow.
(bright music)
♪ Don't try understanding
♪ Fractions of a cloud detailed ♪
♪ Why don't I remember it's a chore ♪
♪ And I'm sending, withholding even more ♪
♪ Something's gotta give up lately ♪
♪ We summarize
♪ Something's gotta measure my memory ♪
♪ Don't worry me, try nothing, I ♪
♪ Do you want my wave
♪ Bound to say I do
- I should get going soon.
- Don't leave right away.
- What about your writing?
- Well, I'm concerned
I might not know everything about this house.
- There's not much else.
- What about the car?
- Car works fine.
- I guess I'm just afraid to get to my writing.
- Yeah, I'm sensing that.
- Thanks.
- Call me anytime.
- I had a lot of fun last night.
- Get some writing done, Teddy.
- Okay.
(engine starting)
(sighing)
The biggest obstacle I have is translating what I actually
feel into words.
I think I know what I'm saying until I read it later,
then it usually sucks.
- [Man] Just takes practice and diligence.
You don't get better until you've done it a lot.
- [Teddy] I wish I had someplace
quiet and away from the city
where I could write this damn thing.
- [Leo] I think I could help you.
(door slamming)
(shouting)
(whining)
- [Teddy] Hello?
- Hey, Leo, Teddy, just checking in on you.
You got in okay?
- [Teddy] Yeah, how's the writing going?
- Great.
Yeah, I've written some pages.
Not as many as I'd like, but.
- [Teddy] Well, it's only your first day.
- Yeah.
So you're going on any auditions or anything?
- [Teddy] No, I gotta work this weekend.
- When's your next day off?
- [Teddy] (laughing) Are you lonely already?
- Well, I mean, it's nice
to have some human contact, you know.
- [Teddy] You inviting me back out there?
- Yeah, of course.
I mean, by the end of this weekend,
I'll have written 20 pages, that's amazing for me.
This place is really inspiring.
- [Teddy] Well, I'll plan on coming up on Monday,
I'm not supposed to work again until Thursday.
- Great.
I mean, that should be cool.
I guess I can handle being alone until then.
- [Teddy] Well, call me if you need anything.
- Okay, man, bye.
- [Teddy] See ya.
(phone beeping)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Crispin, it's Teddy.
- Hello Teddy, how are you coming up?
- God, I just have to tell you your house is amazing.
Thanks so much for letting me stay here.
- [Crispin] I'm glad you're using it, how's the weather?
- Just what you think, hot and sunny.
- Leo drive you?
- He is very nice.
You've known him awhile?
- You know, I knew his parents.
- Oh.
I thought you could have been lovers once.
- [Crispin] Oh no, he's like a little nephew to me.
I could never do that.
- Is he gay?
- [Crispin] He's had girlfriends in the past.
I think he's probably bi.
Who isn't these days?
You have to.
- Yeah, but I shouldn't be telling you that.
- [Crispin] Well, good luck figuring out the puzzle.
- You know your shower doesn't work.
- [Crispin] Changing the subject.
It hasn't worked since the earthquake.
I never bothered to fix it.
I usually take baths when I go out there.
- Where?
- [Crispin] I do it with hot water from the hose.
You stretch the hose out in the sun.
The water's a decent temperature to bathe in.
- Okay.
- [Crispin] But there are thousands of hot springs
you can go to, those are always nice.
- Yeah.
- And the writing?
- Great.
Couldn't be a better place
for me to finish this damn thing.
Thanks again so much.
- Well, keep in touch, my dear.
Anything you need, call Leo.
He knows the house very well.
- Okay.
Talk to you soon, Crispin.
- [Crispin] Bye, now.
(crickets chirping)
- Shit.
(bright music)
(energetic music)
♪ I hear by, give up all that you need to ♪
♪ And since I fell to the station ♪
♪ Open doors to (indistinct)
♪ Happens still far to go
♪ And we don't leave this up for the lonesome days ♪
♪ We talked about
- I really missed you.
- [Leo] You been to town at all?
- Nah, just been writing.
- [Leo] You got bags under your eyes.
- (laughing) Yeah.
I'm on a night schedule now.
- You want a beer? - Sure.
So how was work this week?
- [Leo] Made a lot of tips.
- Ever thought of doing a play?
- Yeah, I've done a few.
Why?
- Just asking,
thought it might be better than waiting for that commercial.
- Well, yeah, usually.
There's no money in it though.
- Ever thought of doing something
where money wasn't the main objective?
- Yeah, all the time.
I'm just getting tired of it.
So what's your book about?
- Basically about a crazy family from the Midwest,
a family who crumbles when their son comes out as gay.
- Autobiographical?
- Yeah, a bit.
So do you have a girlfriend?
- I'm in between?
- What was your last girlfriend like?
- Nothing serious.
- Did you like to dance with her?
- No, she was into rock shows.
- And you don't really dance at a rock show?
- No, you sway.
- (laughing) I like the way you do that.
(both laughing)
(soft music)
How about something stronger?
- Sure.
- So have you only been with women?
- Who wants to know?
I've had my share of diverse experiences.
- You're hard to read.
- I used to think that everyone was bisexual,
but women don't like to hear guys talk like that.
- Yeah, I guess not.
- So I don't talk about it much.
- When you met me, did you think I was gay?
- I don't know.
A little maybe.
- I'm totally gay. (both laughing)
- Totally gay.
- So tell me about your diverse experiences.
- When I was 12, I used to fool around
with this neighborhood kid.
- [Teddy] Really?
What did you do?
- Well, we were talking one day about what do we feel like
if a, if a girl sucked your cock, you know, just,
just wondering about it and, and then he said,
"Hey Leo, oh no, no, no.
"Nevermind, nevermind."
So of course I didn't know what he was gonna say.
I had to pull it out of him and,
and he said that if I wanted that he would suck my cock.
- Where were you, what time of day was it?
It was nighttime and we were right near my garage.
So we went into my garage and he sucked my cock.
(both laughing)
- Did you like it? - Yeah!
That was my first time, so I never forgot it,
but then he wanted me to suck his, and I did,
but I didn't like it.
It was kind of smelly. (Teddy laughing)
- What happened?
Did you guys keep fooling around?
- Here and there, yeah.
- [Teddy] Did you ever go further than blowjobs?
- No.
Just touching and blowjobs.
That's sweet.
- It was what it was.
- [Teddy] Whatever happened?
Did you guys keep in touch?
- Well, he became a total pothead
and then I moved away and I heard
that he got into heavier drugs after that.
- Trying to deal with being gay.
- You think?
- Yeah.
- So what about you?
When did you know you were gay?
- I think I was five.
I was at a gas station with my mom
and the gas station attendant.
He was so beautiful.
He had slick black hair
and his pants were dirty with oil stains.
He was smacking gum.
And I told my mom that I wanted to take home the gas station
man to be my dad. (Leo laughing)
- You wanted to take the gas man home?
- He was probably 20.
- What did your mom say?
- She shushed me and told me not to say things like that.
- Keep it secret.
- Yeah.
For years, unfortunately.
And when I was 19 and tried to come out,
she told me that I wasn't gay.
I've never been with a girl and how can I know for sure?
Fucking a nightmare.
- So what'd you do?
- Went to college and became asexual.
Want another?
- Yeah.
That really sucks, man.
- What's that?
- You know, having to repress yourself like that.
- Yeah.
But eventually it reached a breaking point and that's where
my novel happens, then the aftermath.
- So what happened?
- I don't want to give it away.
- Okay.
- This is a truth serum. (laughing)
- Yeah. (both chuckling)
- So are we just gonna stay here all night and get drunk?
- We should do something else, right?
- Yeah.
(energetic music)
♪ Summertime, don't give it all away ♪
♪ Special lives, I look in your eyes ♪
♪ Were you gonna miss it
♪ Don't turn on a leaf, this is true ♪
♪ Domicile, just pretend there's nothing left to do ♪
♪ Right up to this kiss goodbye, won't you tell me ♪
♪ Do you realize (indistinct) on my way here ♪
♪ I feel all crazy
(both laughing)
♪ Right on through this kiss goodbye, won't you tell me ♪
♪ Do you realize, (indistinct) on my way here ♪
♪ I feel crazy, right on through this kiss goodbye ♪
♪ Won't you tell me
♪ It's been a long time
(tense music)
- Leo, wait!
Get out.
Please don't be mad at me.
- Teddy, it's not your fault.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have. - Don't you see?
You liked it and now you're running away.
- No, Teddy.
I'm not gay.
- Leo, I think you might be.
- Teddy, I'm sorry.
- Leo, please.
I've been waiting to see you all week
and now you're leaving.
- Teddy, let go.
- Leo. - Let go.
- Come on please.
I'm sorry.
I'm just a lonely, melodramatic fag.
- I'll be back, all right?
- All right.
- Ow, ow, ow, Jesus!
Just great.
(engine starting)
(discordant music)
(gasping)
(tense music)
- Teddy.
Teddy?
(tense music)
Teddy, Teddy!
I've been searching, I know (indistinct).
He finished writing a novel.
I read it, and...
- [Crispin] What do you think?
- [Leo] It was beautiful.
- [Crispin] Is there any way you can send me the manuscript?
- [Leo] Crispin, he's missing and you want me to send it?
- [Crispin] Leo, send it to me, that's all I ask.
- [Leo] Okay, I'll do it.
- [Crispin] And for god's sake, call the police.
- [Leo] Yeah, I'll do that too.
(siren wailing) (soft tense music)
- Honey.
Leo.
- Yeah?
- Could you put some stuff on my shoulders?
- Sure.
(rapid tense music)
♪ Watch the mouse carefully
♪ With delicate descriptions I used to know ♪
♪ In a small, like a rescue
♪ In slow motion
♪ The river falls
♪ The river falls onto
♪ Disadvantage and so cross where the bend is ♪
♪ We get lost
♪ Watch the mouse
(indistinct)
(muffled voice speaking)
- Hi.
- Good morning. - Good afternoon.
- Was that Crispin on the phone?
- Yeah.
He wanted to tell you that the book made the New York Times
bestseller list.
- Incredible.
- Hey, now can we go on a little vacation?
- Isn't that what we've been doing?
- I know.
I mean, actually go somewhere instead of staying put.
- Where do you want to go?
- I don't know.
- Maybe a boat cruise or something silly like that.
- Who are you again?
- That's no way to speak to your wife.
(dramatic music)
♪ Afraid I don't have to
- [Cheryl] At the party the other night, I noticed
that young guy was looking right at you.
What'd you say to him?
- [Leo] Told him that I was married.
- [Cheryl] What did you say to that?
- [Leo] He told me that he thought I was cute.
(indistinct)
You know how gay men are, they speak their minds.
- [Cheryl] Like when a woman knows what she wants.
- [Leo] Like you.
(wife chuckling)
- [Cheryl] Like me.
I know I want you, (indistinct).
- [Leo] Yeah.
♪ Shall I demonstrate
♪ With you
♪ What I promised to
- Where were you?
- Just out.
- What's happening to you?
- I don't know
- You're fucking someone, aren't you?
- I don't know.
- I don't even know you.
That's all I am to you, right?
The place to live.
- Cheryl, what are you talking about?
- Just get the fuck out of here, you monster!
(grunting and crying)
- Okay, okay.
Ow!
You bitch!
(Cheryl laughing)
Jesus!
- So you're gonna hit me now.
Just get the fuck out of here, Leo.
(soft sobbing)
(water running) (soft music)
(soft music)
- Been waiting for you.
- I'm sorry about before.
- Do you think I'd turn you away?
- I don't know.
How's your writing going?
- Okay.
I think I've written about 10 pages since I last saw you.
- What's your book called? (soft music)
- I don't know.
I'll wait until the end and get a feeling from it.
- What about Goodbye?
- Goodbye.
Why Goodbye?
- Oh, I guess that's what you said to your family.
- Yeah, I guess.
- We all say goodbye at some point.
- Stay a while this time.
- How long are you staying?
- Two months.
- I want to finish before then.
What?
- Hm?
Nothing. - Is something wrong?
- I just see these images sometimes.
- What did you just see?
- It's always something terrible.
Something awful.
- [Teddy] Like what, someone dead?
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Scary.
- No, it's nothing.
- Have you ever been in love?
- I used to be married.
- Wow, really?
- Was a while ago.
- How old were you?
- 20.
- [Teddy] So young.
How did you know her?
- We worked together.
- Any kids? - No.
- [Teddy] You still in touch?
- She's dead now.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- What did she die from?
- She was found murdered outside our house.
- Was it ever solved?
- No.
- Are you trying to terrify me?
- Well, you asked.
- Fuck.
What was she like?
- She was really pretty.
- Who did she look like?
- [Leo] You ask a lot of questions.
- It's just, I've never
felt that strongly about someone else.
- It was just natural.
- Do you miss her?
- [Leo] Sometimes.
- Like when?
- Every day.
- So you still love her.
- I guess.
- Is it weird to be with me?
- No.
I missed you.
Been thinking about you.
- [Teddy] Hey.
- How's it going? - All right.
Taking care of business?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, me too.
Do you want to go somewhere?
- Why?
- Just want to get away.
- You're giving up on your writing?
- No, just taking a break.
- Don't stop.
Keep going.
- What's that?
- Jesus.
(panting)
(sobbing)
- Leo, what's wrong?
What are you crying about?
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- You should eat.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- When do you work next?
- I don't. - You quit?
- You could say that.
- You okay with money?
- You ask a lot of questions.
- Well, you're not very talkative.
- I'm going through some shit, sorry.
- That's apparent.
- I'm trying to spare you the gory details.
- You can talk to me, Leo.
Otherwise what's the point?
You want to be buried or cremated?
- I want to be buried at sea.
You? - Cremated.
Just seems easier.
- You think about death a lot.
- Sort of.
Just think about how long I'll have to write and whether
what I write'll mean anything to anyone.
- I'm pretty sure life is meaningless.
- Why?
- I just don't understand how it's so unfair to some people
like my wife.
Why would someone want to kill her?
- Yeah.
Fucked up things happening in the world.
But I think everything happens for a reason.
- You think that she was killed for a reason?
- I don't think that she deserved to die,
but it was just her time.
- Her time.
- Yeah.
I mean, we all have to die.
Sometimes it's by accident, car crash or something.
- Struck by lightning.
- Yeah.
- Do you think that there's always a reason?
- I think that we need to be good to each other
while we're on the planet.
After that there's a whole other set of circumstances
we have to deal with.
- Think so?
- I don't believe in God, but I believe in life energy,
like natural resource.
- Like water?
- Exactly.
- Are you taking the bus back to Ohio?
- Yeah, when it's time.
- You should get back to your writing, Teddy.
- Would you slice some watermelon?
It's in the fridge.
- Sure.
- Then I'll get back to work.
(tense music)
(eerie humming)
- Don't leave me.
(eerie music) (water trickling)
(crickets chirping)
- What scared you as a kid?
- Getting up in the middle of the night,
because I always thought that something like a big,
giant hand with sharp nails was gonna grab my ankle
and not let go. (laughing)
- Yeah, me too.
- Did that ever happen to you?
- No, did it happen to you?
- Oh yeah.
All the time, still does.
(fierce gobbling)
- Shit, you're scaring me.
Active imagination, huh?
- Yeah.
- You should do some writing.
- Maybe I will.
- Trust me, Leo.
We'll work on it.
(energetic music)
♪ Too much time by the river
♪ So this ghost don't lose me
♪ Saturation
♪ So went down the other day
♪ Mistaking something you're not to say ♪
♪ Affection was a landslide
♪ And that is all I got to give ♪
♪ I wake up stalling, that emotion ♪
♪ We come by when you say that
♪ We come by, we come by, we come by when you say that ♪
♪ We come by, we come by
(Leo panting) (eerie music)
God, the water's cold.
What did you touch?
- Nothing.
(crickets chirping)
- Leo.
I was thinking maybe tomorrow you should head back home.
- Really?
- It's just, I need some time alone to do some writing.
I like having you here, but you're distracting me.
- Yeah.
- You seem moody lately.
Maybe you need some time alone too.
- Yeah.
- Or maybe you need to look for another job
or acting, you know?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
- No, that's okay, I'll go.
- Come back though.
In a few days.
- Okay, sure.
- You're not angry?
- No, of course not.
(crickets chirping)
(birds singing)
- How'd you sleep last night?
You were acting strange.
- Okay.
(phone ringing)
- Hello? - How are you, Cheryl?
- [Cheryl] Hi.
Hold on.
Leo, it's Crispin.
- Hello?
- [Crispin] Leo, I have a favor to ask.
I have a friend, a former student of mine who I'm letting
stay at my house in the desert.
- What's his name?
- [Crispin] It'd Teddy, Teddy Rapaport.
- Do I know him?
- [Crispin] I don't think you've met.
He's arriving in a few days and since you have keys
I was hoping you could pick him up
and bring him to the house.
Open it up, show him the premises.
- What would you do if I couldn't pick them up?
- [Crispin] I have some other friends who stay there.
They might help, I just thought since you stay there
so often you know the place better than me.
- Okay, yeah, yeah, I can pick him up.
- [Crispin] You're a doll.
He arrives on the 4:00 PM bus Tuesday.
- Okay, I'll be there.
- Where are you going?
- Crispin's.
- [Cheryl] So you'll stay there overnight.
- Yeah.
- You're always going out of town.
Do you want to do something with me?
- You want to go to the zoo?
- That's sweet.
- Yeah.
It should be fun.
- We haven't been in a while.
- Yeah.
(crackling) (eerie music)
Cheryl, I...
- Hm?
- Nothing.
- What are you thinking?
(eerie crackling)
- [Leo] About the elephants.
- [Cheryl] You and those elephants.
- [Leo] You don't like them?
- [Cheryl] I like all the animals, just not snakes.
(eerie music)
♪ So let go, whisper slowly and I mention ♪
♪ Listen to what we can't believe ♪
♪ Down on the corner, sleepers so adore a counter ♪
♪ The last time forever
♪ Happily chasing the nights away ♪
♪ Nothing more to give up
♪ This morning, honestly
- More recently it's been argued that schizophrenia
is just one end of the spectrum
of human experience and behavior.
Not a mental illness
and everybody in society may have some
such experience in their life.
This is known as the continuum model of psychosis
or the dimensional approach and is most notably argued by
psychologist Simon Rodel and psychiatrist Peter van Kerr.
Hey, gorgeous.
(waves crashing)
- [Leo] You want to do something with me?
- Come here.
- [Leo] I love you.
- I love you too, my darling.
- [Leo] Sun's out.
- You work on that tan, my love.
(waves crashing)
(dramatic music)
- I missed you so much.
- I missed you too.
- So what do you think of our situation?
- What do you mean?
- You know, us?
- I don't know.
- I'm falling in, Leo.
- Don't fall, Teddy.
- I'm serious.
- I'm not...
You shouldn't be in love with me.
- You don't want me to?
- I'm just not thinking about that.
- I wish you'd live in the present.
- You don't know me, Teddy.
I don't think I can know you.
How can I love you if I don't even know you?
- I don't know.
I want to know you better.
I want to love you, Leo.
I want to spend all of my time with you
for more than a few weeks.
- Is that love?
Maybe you're just lonely and I'm filling the void.
- Yeah, maybe.
Maybe that's all love is, filling the void.
You're probably right.
- That's what I think.
- Well, now you know how I feel.
(soft sobbing)
- Teddy, I'm not...
I'm sorry.
(Teddy softly sobbing)
It's not you, it's me.
It's me.
(water babbling)
- You're not gay, Leo.
- You haven't been with a woman.
How can you tell if you're a, a homosexual?
You have to find yourself.
You're still searching, aren't you?
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
I love you, son.
(Leo softly sobbing)
(water trickling)
(rapid music)
- I'm done.
- You finished the book?
Sit down.
- Will you read it?
- Yeah, of course.
That would be an honor.
- Will you really read it, Leo?
- Yeah, I will.
(warm music)
(eerie music)
- Don't leave me.
- I'm sorry.
(indistinct)
(Leo panting)
- Leo, baby, please stop!
(water babbling)
(heartbeat pounding)
(rapid music)
♪ There's much to know why I'm here ♪
♪ Don't (indistinct)
♪ And I hope that you're wrong for the last time ♪
♪ I'll take it one more flight
♪ It's only still, so we might
♪ And I know it's the living of just a few ♪
♪ What could we do, my enemy
♪ Well, I can't stop trusting me ♪
♪ And I hope that you're wrong for the last time ♪
(energetic music)
(singer vocalizing)
(waves crashing)