- Oh.
(horns honking)
(tires screeching)
Come on.
(horn blaring)
Fuck you, you complete moron!
- [Office Worker] Can
you hold the door please?
- Awe.
- What are you looking at?
- Uh, nothing.
- It's beautiful.
- Just an anniversary
card my wife gave me.
- Oh.
- If you live to be a hundred,
I want to live to be a
hundred minus one day
so I never have to
live without you.
- Do you and your wife
share a birthdate?
- I'm two and a half
years older than she is.
- If you die when you're
100 and your wife dies a day
before she turns 100, that's
30 months after your death.
If she doesn't want
to live without you,
the card should say
that she wants to live
to roughly 97 and six months
old, if you die at 100.
- [Caroline] Morning.
- [Office Worker] Thank you.
- Oh, hey, Justin.
Hi.
- [Office Worker] Hi.
- Hey.
Hi, how are you?
- [Office Worker] Okay.
- Morning.
- So it's still considered
sexual harassment,
even if I say just
kidding afterwards?
- Yes, George, it is.
Mint?
- How did it go
with our new client?
- Barry, would it be
possible for me to take on
different types of clients?
- Sexual harassment is
our bread and butter.
- I have lots of ideas
for methods to help people
in more profound ways.
- People don't want to be
helped in profound ways.
They just want to sign a
document and not get sued.
If we get any sort
of special projects,
you will be my first call.
- Last night's relative
abundance was still 23%.
- Shit.
Charts.
This is the most stubborn
bacterium I've ever seen.
It won't die.
We need a larger sample size.
- I hear that Pearson's
announcing the Adler grant
at the faculty meeting.
- Morning, Dr Stern.
- Congratulations, Dr Stern!
- Thank you.
-Congratulations.
- Speaking of things
that won't die.
- Her leukemia vaccine just got
approved for clinical trial.
- Thank you everyone.
But the real victors
are the children.
I do it all for the children.
- Cancer researchers
are the worst.
What do you want, Laura?
- Just saying hi.
I haven't seen anyone
since my book tour.
How are things going with
your new, uh, hand sanitizer?
- Sanitizer is only one
potential application
of my research, which
is going swimmingly.
- If you need any extra
supplies, just visit my new lab.
They keep giving me
stuff I don't even need.
Bye guys!
- [Lab Workers] Have a good day!
- Bye!
- Congratulations!
- Alright, I am happy to report
that one of our own has won
the Margaret Adler Grant
for Women in Science.
Her work has made this
department very proud.
Congratulations, Laura!
(group clapping)
Your leukemia
vaccine has brought
a lot of media attention
to the University.
- Well, I do it all
for the children.
- Well, we'll hold a press
conference about this tomorrow.
Keep up the great
work, everyone.
- I'm sure you'll
get the next one.
It's just honest competition
between colleagues.
It's not personal.
- The only reason you won is
because you spend more time
posing for photo ops
than in a laboratory.
- I need to be an
advocate for the work.
I speak for those
who have no voice.
- Hearing you speak makes
me want to hurl myself
in front of a moving vehicle.
I don't respect you as
a scientist or human.
You're a complete fraud.
You probably stole your vaccine
idea from some grad student,
and I am pretty sure
those children hate you.
I need to speak for
those who have no voice.
(quirky music)
- [Actor] What is the hoopla?
Isn't this like your
primary military specialty--
- [Moviegoer] That guy's fat.
- [Moviegoer] And gay.
- Shh!
- [Moviegoer] No,
mommy shushed us.
What do we do?
- [Moviegoer] Let's
go cry about it.
- Were you born this
way or did you suffer
some sort of major
trauma to the head?
- [Moviegoer] Hey!
- [Moviegoer] Shh!
- [Moviegoer] Keep it down!
- I pity everyone
you've ever met.
- [Moviegoer] Quiet!
- [Usher] Ma'am, I'm going
to have to ask you to leave.
You can't keep
harassing our customers.
This is the third
time this month.
- Maybe you shouldn't
allow total sub-humans
into your theater.
- [Usher] Ma'am, please.
- Okay, fine.
I'll go.
- [Moviegoer] Outta here!
(crowd clapping)
(door slamming shut)
(playful music)
- I think we have pretty good
chemistry between you and I.
- Between you and me.
- [Jake] Hmm?
- You said between you and I.
It's the object
of a preposition.
You wouldn't say she comes to I.
It's she comes to me.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Nobody is coming tonight.
- What so I'm just
supposed to be wrong?
What's going on?
- Laura Stern killed
herself last night.
- So they're giving
me the Adler Grant?
- Dr Wolfe...
- They're not giving
me the Adler Grant?
What?
People think it's my fault?
- How could you speak
to her like that?
We women in science are
supposed to support one another.
- You didn't even like her.
- At least I didn't kill her.
(door slamming shut)
- Did you or did you
not tell Dr Stern
that she was a complete
fraud hated by children?
And did you mention something
about throwing oneself
in front of a moving vehicle?
- Is that how she did it?
I was just saying what
everyone else was thinking.
- Serena, you're a
gifted microbiologist.
Nobody kills pathogenic
antibiotic-resistant bacteria
like you, but you have
become a liability.
- Don.
- I've got the
University to hold off
on doing anything with you yet.
- Thanks.
- On one condition.
You are to undergo intensive
sensitivity training,
starting immediately.
- Sensitivity what?
- You'll meet with
a sensitivity coach
and she will decide the
proper course of action.
(quirky music)
- Fuck me.
- You must be Dr Wolfe.
I'm Caroline Sanders.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
- Why are you touching me?
- The woman who passed away,
Dr Stern, was your colleague.
- Oh, right.
- This is a safe space.
You can cry if you'd like.
- I do not cry.
Ever.
- Why don't we have a seat?
- I have a lot of
work to do so--
- Serena.
May I call you, Serena?
From what I've been told, you
do have a lot of work to do.
On yourself.
So, why don't you
sit and tell me
a little bit about your job.
- I am the principal
investigator of my lab.
I specialize in the
Bacillus genus of bacteria.
There is a new species
of Bacillus I discovered
that's resistant to
antibacterial agents.
- Antibacterial agents
like hand sanitizer?
- Hand sanitizer is
one form it could take.
I study the bacterium itself,
its behavior, where it's from,
its pathogenic properties,
and yes, how to kill it.
- And how would you
describe your relationship
with the people in your lab?
- I would describe it as fine.
- We're naming him Hunter.
- The miracle of life.
- Why am I looking at
your wife's uterus?
- Would you like to
have lunch together?
My mom visited and
I have leftovers.
- Eww.
What is this, a church
potluck in Dayton, Ohio?
(Joan crying)
- Her adopted
mother passed away.
- Cancer.
- At least you don't
have her genes.
Not that you know whose
genes you do have.
Those were taken out of context.
- Can you admit
you have a problem?
- I have a strong personality,
I don't think it's a problem.
It's inconvenient, maybe.
- That's all?
- Science isn't
about personalities.
It's about ideas.
It's about constant,
vigilant work
to turn those ideas into facts.
I consistently have good ideas.
That's how I got to be where
I am today, not by being nice.
So what do you have, an MSW?
- I have a dual
doctorate in Sociology
and Behavioral Psychology.
You're not the only scientist
in the room, Dr Wolfe.
- Well, you're in
the soft sciences.
So, what's the protocol?
Do I need to read a
pamphlet and sign something?
Take a test?
- If you want to
keep your job here,
the administration will,
I suspect, need to see
a real transformation
from within.
- So I have to hug someone?
- The only one who can sign off
on whether your
sensitivity training
has been a success is I.
- Nice grammar.
- Thank you, Serena.
Now, I have a number of
criteria I'll use to determine
whether you have made a
genuine transformation.
I'm going to shadow you closely.
- Shadow me?
- Why don't you show
me around your lab?
- Put these on.
- What?
- Remember this is my lab.
You're a guest here.
- You won't even know I'm here.
- Okay, so over here we
have isolated samples
of Bacillus Virilis, the
species I'm studying,
in different dilutions.
- Hi, would anyone like a mint?
- Thank you.
- Hi.
- I'm Caroline.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Caroline.
You'll be seeing a
lot of me around here.
Anybody else?
- And over here, we have samples
taken from human subjects,
to study the relative
abundance of Bacillus Virilis
among more commonly
found bacteria.
- So this new hard-to-kill
bacteria is found on humans?
- It's not dangerous
in the concentrations
that we find it in, but
if it continues to grow,
it could be a problem.
- Would you like
the latest results?
- Hi, I'm Caroline.
Mint?
- There's no eating
in the lab.
- What do you do here?
- I'm Dr Wolfe's grad student.
- Oh, so how long have you
been mentored by Dr Wolfe?
- Ellen, results?
- 21.5% relative abundance.
- Shit.
Increase the triclocarbon
by two percent.
- Ellen, how does
it make you feel
when Dr Wolfe is short with you?
- How does it what?
- Swab her.
- What's happening?
- I'm including you in my study.
- I'm sensing some hostility.
I know that I may seem
like an intrusion,
but I am here to help you.
- What's going on?
- Some sort of extreme
behavior modification therapy.
- And we get to watch?
(soft guitar music)
- Hi.
- Wow, interesting day.
- Mommy!
- Okay, Mommy has a project.
So let's go make
dinner while she works.
- [Maggie] What's going on?
- I met a woman who
really needs my help.
(soft guitar music)
- [Serena] She started it!
(knocking on door)
- Uh!
- Morning!
Coffee?
- Did someone else die?
- Nice PJs.
- Did I die?
Is this hell?
- Lovely home.
I wanted to get our day
off to a good start.
- How did you get
into my building?
- I buzzed and buzzed,
but you didn't answer.
Carl let me in.
- Who the hell is Carl?
- Your building manager.
He is a sweet guy.
- I don't understand
why you're in my home.
Is this legal?
- When I mentioned that
I would be shadowing you,
I didn't just mean at work.
(phone ringing)
- [Operator] 911, what
is your emergency?
- Yes, I'd like to
report an intruder.
Her name is...
What's your name again?
Caroline Sanders, PhD.
She's in the soft
sciences, though.
- [Operator] You
know the intruder?
- May I?
Hi!
I promise to help her
become the kind of person
who respects your time.
Thank you so much for
your brave service
to the people of Los Angeles.
Why don't you get ready and
we'll drive to work together?
Thank you for showing
me your apartment
and giving me a ride.
- You showed up unannounced
and insisted I drive you.
- When a colleague
says thank you,
a simple, you're
welcome, goes a long way.
- I called the police on you.
That's the definition
of not welcome.
- You're very concerned
with being right.
- Is that a bad overall
goal? (phone ringing)
- It makes it difficult to form
deeper relationships
with people.
- [Don] Serena?
- Don, I woke up with a
malignant parasitic cyst
called a sensitivity coach.
- Hi, Dr Pierson.
- You know how close I
am to a breakthrough.
How am I supposed to
get any work done?
This has thrown me
completely off-kilter.
- [Don] Serena, if you
want to keep your job,
you have to complete
this training.
- Can they really blame
me for Laura's death?
Maybe she had a
chemical imbalance?
Was she on medication?
(phone clicking)
Don?
- You have a lovely apartment.
I noticed you don't have any
photos of family and friends.
- Why are people so
obsessed with photos?
Don't they know what
their children look like?
- This is my partner Sarah
and my daughter Maggie.
Photos help me keep
my loved ones with me.
- I was married once.
In college.
It ended after a year.
- I'm sorry you
went through that.
(tires screeching)
- What the hell?
Did your mother drop you?
- Just kidding!
We're sure you had a perfectly
good reason to do that.
We're going to give you
the benefit of the doubt.
(quirky music)
- People are transferring
to different labs.
They say they don't want
to work for you anymore.
Hey, that's mine!
- [Caroline] That's
a lot to take in.
How's that make you feel?
- Fine.
(drill buzzing)
I have wanted to work
on a project like this
my entire career.
It was not easy
to get my own lab.
(tape snapping)
People belittle my research.
They say I'm making
hand sanitizer,
but antibiotic
resistance is dangerous.
I may not be curing cancer,
but I am helping people.
(drill buzzing) Hey!
Could you just...
Do you have to do
that right now?
- Just doing my job.
- Thank you for taking
such pride in your work.
- You're welcome.
- Serena, you study bacteria.
I study human behavior.
How do you determine how to
kill drug-resistant bacteria?
- Perpetual
observation, hypothesis,
and then methodical testing
until I get a favorable result.
- And I'm going to observe
you in your environment,
generate a hypothesis as to
why you are the way you are,
though I have a few
ideas, and work with you
to mitigate your behavior
and neutralize your effect
on the environment until
I get a favorable result.
- Did you just liken me
to a pathogenic bacterium?
Oh, now you're done.
Thank you, thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- What was so fucking important?
How quickly can you even
get one of these made?
- It's beautifully done.
- Got it.
- Can you succeed in your
research without a staff?
- Okay, so that's definitely
university property.
Okay.
People!
I know I can be a bit abrasive.
And I'm sorry for
the way I've behaved.
I'm receiving help and
learning to be more sensitive.
Please stay.
I...
I believe in the
work that we're doing
and I know you do too.
What now?
- We get to work.
Welcome to our safe space.
Let's start with the basics.
When someone gives you a lab
result that you don't like,
try saying thank you
instead of swearing at them.
- So you want me to
thank someone for
giving me shitty news?
- It's acknowledging
the effort it took
to give you that news.
- Hey, Caroline, your
kitten has feline AIDS.
- I don't have a kitten, but
thank you for that information.
Let's do a quick role-play.
I'll be a colleague you
find really annoying.
- Tough to imagine.
- Dr Wolfe, is it okay if I
leave work early tomorrow?
My boyfriend's taking
me out and I'd rather go
on a date with my boyfriend
than make hand sanitizer.
Now, you respond in
a respectful way.
- I'm not responding to that.
- I feel--
- Why can't I just say
what I want to say?
- If you begin by using, I feel,
the person's less
likely to be offended.
You're simply stating
how you personally feel.
- Okay, I feel that's retarded.
- Many people find
that word offensive.
- But it's what I feel.
- Get it all out.
That's okay.
I have more.
Let's talk about your parents.
- Should I lie on a couch
and recover a memory
of being fondled by my uncle?
- Were you?
That's a joke.
Unless you were.
I'm trying to figure out why
your defenses are so high.
- My defenses?
- Your quick temper,
condescension, your need to say
every insult that
pops into your brain.
- Not every insult.
- These are your
defense mechanisms.
What are you protecting
yourself from?
Let's discuss your triggers.
What gets you really annoyed?
What do you hate?
- I get to talk
about what I hate?
- Of course.
- And I can say whatever I want?
- Please.
- Okay.
I hate being wrong.
I hate it when I'm right
but people think I'm wrong.
I hate when a person is
wrong but they insist,
despite all available
evidence, that they're right.
I hate that it's considered
rude to correct people.
They should just say thank you.
I hate when people get
recognition they don't deserve.
I detest small talk.
I don't want to talk
about the weather.
I don't want to
talk about traffic.
If you think you have some
special, magical route
to get to work, I don't
want to hear about it.
It's probably not that good.
I hate when people inflict
their personal problems onto me.
I hate when people bring their
children or pets into work
or force you to look
at vacation photos.
I also hate when women
put on that voice
when they speak to or
about children or animals.
I don't want to hear about
your hobbies, marriages,
where you bought a particular
item, whether it was on sale.
I hate when people
listen to music so loudly
that you can hear it
through their headphones.
I hate when people make up
abbreviations for things
and use them in regular speech.
I hate emoticons; I never
understand what they mean.
I hate overzealous huggers.
I hate the word bro.
I hate the overuse
of exclamation marks.
I hate when I'm parallel
parking and the car behind me
honks like they have no idea
why I'm not driving forward
as though they've never
parked in their entire life.
I hate the color purple,
not the book or the movie,
just the actual color.
I hate proposal videos.
I hate flash mobs.
I hate the phrase baby bump.
I hate that's what
she said jokes.
I hate when men use erection
metaphors to describe
something that they
really like, for example,
I have a total hard on
for this deep-dish pizza.
I hate deep-dish pizza.
I also hate mini cupcakes.
I hate when people speak
in random foreign accents
like it's inherently funny.
Sounding vaguely
British isn't funny.
- Thank you, Serena.
That was a good start.
- I could keep going.
- No, no.
That was plenty.
Today wasn't so bad was it?
- Yes?
- [Ethan] Serena, it's Ethan.
- Oh.
Hey.
- Who's this?
- None of your business.
- [Ethan] Am I on speaker?
- I'm driving.
- [Ethan] Is someone
else with you?
- Hello!
I'm Caroline, who's this?
- [Ethan] Ethan,
Serena's brother.
- Sorry to interrupt.
- Can I call you back later?
- [Ethan] Sure.
- Great thanks, bye.
- I need to talk to you.
- You have a brother?
- Half-brother.
- Hmm, he sounded
like a teen in crisis.
How old were you
when he was born?
- 17.
I barely know him.
- Your parents are divorced?
- My father left and
then my mother met Glenn.
- That must have
been hard for you.
Where do you go to
unwind after work?
- [Actor] Oh, when
did you get it?
Okay.
So?
- [Moviegoer] You tell him.
- Shh.
- [Moviegoer] She's
too pretty for him.
- [Moviegoer] Mm-hm.
- As much as I love your
brilliant commentary,
do you think you could
keep it to yourself?
- Serena.
- It's fine.
This happens all the time.
- [Moviegoer] I'm just
trying to watch the movie.
- Could you watch it
with your mouth closed?
- [Usher] Ma'am.
- What's happening?
- We have to go now.
- What?
- We're being kicked out.
Come on.
- Why did you engage with her?
- She started it.
She shouldn't have been talking.
- Yes, but you
always have a choice.
Would you rather
be right or not get
kicked out of the theater?
I mean, when was the last time
you saw the end of a movie?
(buzzer buzzing)
Happy second week of
sensitivity training!
Don't do that!
Come on, open it.
Do you like him?
- I don't understand
what's happening.
- [Caroline] Caring
for another creature
is part of your training.
Haven't you ever had a pet?
- This isn't a pet.
This is a cesspool for
pathogenic bacteria.
- But isn't he cute?
- [Serena] Most small
turtles are illegal.
They're smuggled in
from other countries
and they destroy the ecosystems
of our ponds and rivers.
- This isn't the
illegal kind of turtle.
He's the adorable
pet kind of turtle.
- It probably has Salmonella.
- You like bacteria.
It'll give you two
something to talk about.
- [Serena] I really have
to care for this thing?
- You have to give him a
name, give him a nice home.
Think about him when
you're not around.
It's all part of being a person.
- First, I'm going to
test him for Salmonella.
- Okay, remember what we've
practiced about taking a breath
if you don't like what you hear.
And.
Here's your new stress ball.
It's a molecule.
Squeeze it!
- Morning, Ellen.
- Good morning, Dr Wolfe.
- How was your
evening last night?
- It was good, actually, I--
- Wonderful.
Do you have the results
from last night's tests?
- Yeah, it was 26%.
- Shit.
A three percent increase?
I mean, okay, thank you
for that information.
- Dr Wolfe, could you
take a look at this?
- Interesting.
Thanks for pointing this out.
- Dr Wolfe, I had an idea
I wanted to show you.
What if we--
- No, that wouldn't work.
Here, test this for Salmonella.
- Oh.
- I think it's safe to say
that didn't go very well.
- The virilis count should
be decreasing by now.
I don't know what I'm missing.
- We need to discuss how you
just spoke to Ellen out there.
- I'm sorry I didn't play
nice at your tea party,
but I'm trying to prevent
a public health crisis.
This is science,
not little league.
- Positive reinforcement
encourages productivity.
- Are you even a real person
or are you a schizophrenic
hallucination?
Should I be on medication?
- Probably.
(playful music)
- Thanks for letting
me drive today.
(toy squeaking)
- [Maggie] Hello!
- [Caroline] Maggie,
what did I tell you
about throwing your toys?
- Why is there a small
child in the vehicle?
- Serena, this is my
little monster, Maggie.
Maggie, this is Serena.
We work together.
- Not exactly.
- Do you do sex
people her past meat?
- That's how she says
sexual harassment.
- Does she have a
learning disability?
- No, she's just five.
- I'm almost six!
And I'm going to have the
biggest birthday party ever!
- Sarah had an early meeting
so I'm driving Maggie
to school today.
- It's not going to be
a long drive, is it?
- This could be an
opportunity for you
to work on your hostility
toward children.
- You don't like kids?
- Not especially.
- Me neither.
They're mean and stupid.
- Don't say that, honey.
Maggie's having some
trouble at school.
Some of the kids
are picking on her.
- You should just tell
them all to go to hell.
- Uh, no, honey.
You should be the bigger
person like we talked about.
They'll follow your lead.
- She should stand
up for herself.
- [Caroline] She should
turn the other cheek.
- Why are they picking on you?
Is it because your
mothers are lesbians?
- No.
It's because I'm purple.
- What do you mean
you're purple?
You mean you like purple?
- I love purple.
Purple is me.
- Purple is I.
- You're not purple.
You're gray.
- She's going through an
identity assertion phase.
She identifies with
the color purple.
Not the novel, the actual color.
- The other kids say that
purple is dumb, so I'm dumb.
- Purple is dumb.
- Here we are.
Say bye to Serena.
- Bye to Serena.
- The next time someone
says something mean to you,
just tell them this.
(Serena whispering)
- [Caroline] Great,
we'll see you there.
- [Maggie] Bye!
- Ethan.
Hi.
What was it you
wanted to talk about?
You're here?
(upbeat music)
- I'm excited to
meet your brother.
- Half-brother.
(upbeat music)
- Serena!
- You look different.
- I'm Goth now.
- Hi, I'm Caroline.
We spoke on the
phone the other day.
- Nice to meet you.
How long have you
guys been friends?
- We're not.
We work together.
- Cool.
Are you a scientist, too?
- Yes.
As a matter of fact, I am.
So, Ethan, what
brings you to LA?
- Things aren't going so
well back home in Riverside.
- Where are you staying?
- Crashing at my
friend Damian's.
He's got five other roommates
so I'm sleeping in the tub.
- Is Damian in school?
- No, he dropped out
to follow his passion.
- And that is?
- Body art.
- Is that a type of dance?
- He lets me stay
with him if I let him
practice his designs on me.
He's a tattoo genius.
- The genius spelled
despair incorrectly.
- Yeah, that's why
he needs to practice.
- Can't he practice
with a dictionary and
not on your flesh?
- I don't mind the spelling.
It's sort of ironic.
- It's sort of retarded.
- Serena.
- Sorry.
I feel that it's retarded.
So what did you
want to talk about?
- Mom and dad kicked me out.
- Why?
- The same reason
they kicked you out.
- That was different.
- I turned 18 last
week and they told me
I could take care of myself.
- Oh right.
Happy birthday.
- Listen, can I stay with you?
Damian's place is
getting pretty cramped.
- No, that would not work.
- Just for a little while
so I save up some money.
- Believe me, you're better
off at your friend Denny's.
- Damian.
- This should help you out.
Take care.
And get some blood work done,
you've probably been
exposed to hepatitis.
- Thanks.
- Don't you think he should
be with family right now?
- I hardly know him, and I have
the turtle to take care of.
- There must be something
you feel comfortable
doing to help.
- Mm-mm.
Everyone, meet our
new intern, Ethan.
We've been short-staffed
since Laura killed herself
and everyone quit.
And we could use an
extra set of hands.
- He doesn't look
very science-y.
- Joan, please show Ethan
around and find him something
to do that he can't
possibly mess up.
- I'll show you a supply closet.
- Look at you,
being a big sister.
- Half-sister.
- If this works out,
maybe you can invite him
to come stay with you.
- Maybe we can all hold hands
and watch the sun set together.
- I know you're being sarcastic,
but that sounds lovely.
- Fleming's Salmonella
test came back negative.
- You named the turtle Fleming?
That is so cute.
- Alexander Fleming
discovered penicillin.
- It's a distinguished name.
- Did you get a
chance to look at my--
- There were errors
in your report.
- Really?
I checked all--
- [Serena] I made revisions.
- Serena, don't you think
you were harsh with Ellen?
- I treated her
like a professional.
- That report must have
been 40 pages long.
That's a lot of work.
- Yes, it is.
- Where are you going?
- To the bathroom.
Would you like to come
with and supervise
how I treat the toilet?
(door clicking open)
(Ellen sniffling)
(water gushing)
- It's nothing.
- Good job.
- [Caroline] It doesn't
have to be perfect.
- They better not
touch anything.
- Just remember why
you're doing this.
- Because you made me.
- Because it's important
to let people in.
Take an interest
in your colleagues
and let them know
they're appreciated.
- Uh-huh.
(buzzer buzzing)
- Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I want to watch.
Hide the iPad by the table.
- Seriously?
- Put your Bluetooth in.
I can help you during dinner.
- Okay, Cyrano.
(buzzer buzzing)
- Hi!
- Welcome, Joan.
- [Caroline] Invite her in.
- Please, come in.
Uh, actually, I don't allow...
Would you mind taking
off your shoes?
- I wiped them.
- It's just--
- [Caroline] Just let it go.
It is too late to call 911.
- Would you like a drink?
- Sure!
- [Caroline] Try
to bond with her.
- So, we're just a couple
of women scientists.
- Yep.
- [Caroline] Keep it going.
- In such a
male-dominated field.
- Yes.
- Make it more personal.
- When do you menstruate?
Maybe our cycles have
synced due to all the time
we spend together in the lab.
- Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Sorry.
(buzzer buzzing)
- [Caroline] Talk!
Serena!
- Why don't you each tell
me about your hobbies?
- [Caroline] Good.
- Sandra and I like to
leave Hunter with a sitter
and go antiquing
in Palm Springs.
- [Caroline] Nod and smile.
- What about you, Joan?
- I've become prolific
in slam poetry
since discovering I was adopted.
- [Caroline] Are you nodding?
- I recently joined the
Quidditch team on campus.
- Wow!
- [Dr Hamilton] That's great.
- Quidditch?
- The game from Harry Potter.
- [Caroline] I can't
believe they have that.
- Thank you for coming.
- Thanks for having us.
- We should to this again, soon.
- Good night!
- [Caroline] Great job!
- Please just tell me
I don't have to attend
a Quidditch match.
- Baby steps.
I'm really proud of you!
- [Serena] Uh!
- Night!
- [Serena] Mm-hm.
- [Sarah] Did you just coach
her through an entire dinner?
- She says the funniest things.
I mean not a lot of
people could get away
with the stuff she says.
- She can't get away with it.
That's why they
assigned you to her.
And why you're spending
so much time with her.
- I don't know how to explain
it, but I really need this.
(toys crashing)
- [Maggie] Mommy!
- [Sarah] I'll go.
Coming sweetie!
- Dr Wolfe, the last
formula we tried worked.
- It killed 97.3% of the
virilis in the isolated sample.
We're running it
again to make sure.
- Shit, it worked!
- Oh.
- Let's double and triple
check these results.
- [Dr Hamilton]
That was strange.
- [Joan] I don't
know, I liked it.
- [Ellen] Me too.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
- To teamwork.
- We just drank.
- Can you admit that improved
morale may have contributed
to today's victory?
Come on, I really
like cheersing.
- Alright, I admit it.
- To sensitivity!
- Now, you're pushing it.
To Fleming, the
turtle and the man.
How's Maggie?
- She's tougher than I was.
- You were teased in school too?
- Who wasn't?
- Did they pick on you
because you're a lesbian?
- I was fat.
My mom told me to kill
them with kindness
so no matter what they said
to me, I was nice back,
and that took all the
fun out of teasing me
so they left me alone.
By high school, I
was class secretary
and head of the
homecoming committee.
- Didn't you ever just
want to tell them off?
- Why give them the
satisfaction of seeing me upset?
I know you don't like
talking about it,
but your parents, Ethan?
- My mother is retarded
and my stepfather
is a giant asshole.
- Right.
So, your stepfather...
- Glenn.
When my father left, my
mother was destroyed.
Then she met Glenn.
Doesn't that name
sound like someone
you just want to
punch in the face?
- What about John Glenn?
- It's different as a last name.
Glenns would eat vomit and
tell you that they liked it
if you told them it was
a delicacy that required
a refined palate to appreciate.
Glenns walk around in their
boxers and wink at you
if you walk in on him
and your mom having sex.
- That's very specific.
- After Ethan was
born and I turned 18,
they said I could
take care of myself.
I put myself through college.
I didn't visit.
I wasn't welcome.
I barely recognized Ethan.
- Now, poor Ethan is going
through the same thing.
- I don't understand it.
I was like this remnant of
my mother's shitty marriage,
but I can't believe that Glenn
would kick out his own son.
- Your mother kicked
out her own daughter.
Didn't you say you
got married young?
- My biology professor.
I was his favorite student.
- And then what?
- He found another
favorite student.
- So you felt abandoned
by your parents
and the person you turned to
for comfort abandoned you too?
- Well, it taught me
to rely on myself.
- I can see why it's hard
for you to trust people.
- I never thought
of it that way.
Did you just therapy me?
Sneaky.
- You liked it.
This is getting gloomy.
What do you normally
do to celebrate
a major scientific breakthrough?
- Oh, I'm usually just annoyed
that I didn't figure
it out sooner.
- I'm not going to
acknowledge you said that.
(Caroline laughs)
Whiskey.
I have a surprise for you.
You're going to love it.
- Okay.
- This is going to be fun.
Okay.
You know how you never get
to see the end of movies
because of your anger
management problem?
- I'd say it's because of the
completely intolerable nature
of the average moviegoer.
- Right.
So I was thinking,
how many great movies
have you never
seen the ending to?
We are going to watch movies
all the way through to the end!
Where is your TV?
- I don't have a TV.
(soft music)
She had the heart of the
ocean the entire time.
And then she just
threw it back in.
The explorer's search
was completely in vain
and I'm pretty sure if
they'd tried harder,
they both could have fit on
that piece of drift wood.
(soft music)
They had such a
beautiful friendship.
I can't believe they
chose to die like that.
- They ran out of options.
They didn't want to go to jail.
- They finally found their
freedom and would rather die
than let anyone take it away.
- That's deep.
(suspenseful music) Ah!
(Caroline laughing)
Selfie!
- That's not a word.
(energetic music)
Oh my God.
Is this fight club?
Are you really me?
- I'm not you.
- You can't be me!
- You're a really
belligerent drunk.
- Ahhh!
Fight Club!
(upbeat music)
- Staring contest.
- You have pretty eyes.
Did you know that
Bruce Willis is dead
the entire time in
The Sixth Sense?
- Yeah.
- What an amazing twist.
I never would've known if
Caroline hadn't shown me.
(laughing)
- What is it?
- Huh?
Oh nothing.
(laughing)
- Come on, what?
- Just something Caroline said.
(laughing)
- We've done repeat tests
and we've still been
getting good results.
- That's great.
Thanks.
- There are a couple
of human samples
that are still not responding
as quickly to the new formula.
- Dr Wolfe?
- It's probably
just a sensor error.
Let's keep an eye on it.
Thanks for letting me know.
- Are you all right?
- Huh?
- Nevermind.
Thanks.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Oh, knock, knock.
- Have you guys noticed
anything weird about Dr Wolfe?
- The first rule
of Fight Club is?
- It's almost like she's...
- Happy.
- Oh!
Oh!
- Ahh!
- Maybe she had a tiny stroke.
- [Caroline] Oh, ho, ho!
- [Serena] Don!
- Serena, I don't have time
to hear your protestations
about sensitivity training.
- Oh, I'm not here to
complain about that.
- Oh.
- We've gotten a lot of momentum
from our recent breakthrough,
but we could use
some more resources.
I've written a proposal.
I know the department
needs revenue
and you're hoping there
might be commercial use
for my research.
I think we're really close.
We just need some funding.
- I'll look this over.
Let me see if there's
any discretionary
funds I can get you.
- Thanks for your
support, Donald.
- You're welcome.
(upbeat music)
Onward and upward
Ever forward on and on
Hell to be in
the land of heroes
Yours went dead and gone
(upbeat music)
Hey, we know how
to make life go on
On
The afterlife
- Almost.
- No.
- You did.
- Umm.
- What is it, Ethan?
- Serena, I just need your
signature on this supply order.
- Okay sure.
- I'll be right back.
- You don't want to miss
anything, I might lose it.
- Yeah, this looks good.
You can put this order through.
- All right.
Can I ask you something?
- Yeah.
- Is there anything going
on between you and Caroline?
Like a gay thing?
- I'm not gay.
- I know, but she is.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- You just seemed happy.
That's all.
- Surprise!
Open it!
- Is it another turtle?
- A square turtle.
- I had it printed.
Do you like it?
(energetic music)
Remember
When you held my hand
Why don't you dance with me
I'm not no Limburger
Huh
Say, don't that make you
feel a whole lot better
What you say
I'm just asking
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Dance this mess around
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey!
- Hey.
- Should we get tickets?
- I got them already.
- Oh, let me pay you back.
- Uh, no, I...
My treat.
- I'll get popcorn.
(dramatic music)
- [Moviegoer] It's the part
where the guy gets shot.
- [Moviegoer] Oh yeah?
(gun firing)
- [Moviegoer] That's sick.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- [Moviegoer] The son dies too.
- [Moviegoer] Oh,
that's messed up!
(moviegoers whispering)
(dramatic music)
- Just breathe.
See?
You're in control.
- [Moviegoer] That guy's gay!
- We're sorry!
What happened in there?
I thought we had
it under control.
- I'm sorry.
He just got to me.
- We have been
making good progress,
but your temper and road rage
are still big hurdles for you.
- I'm doing a lot better.
I'm sorry.
- I can't pass you until
you can control this.
- Is that what this
is about for you?
- I'm sorry?
- You're right.
I'll work on it.
Do you want to go and
get a drink or something?
On me.
You know, I got us
kicked out and all.
- It's getting a little late.
I should get home before
Maggie goes to sleep.
- Sure, of course.
- I'll pick you up at 8:30?
- Sounds good.
- Great.
Good night.
- Night!
Fuck.
- Are you sure one of the other
coaches couldn't handle it?
I think Amanda.
All right.
I'll be right in.
- What is it?
- Some executive just
called his assistant a fag
in front of the entire company.
So they want me to go in and run
an emergency sensitivity
session all morning.
- And you don't want to?
- I hate sexual harassment.
These guys don't want to change.
They just want to hire me
so they don't get sued.
- Tell Barry that.
- I tried.
And I'm already late
to pick up Serena
and now I have to cancel on her.
- Well, I'm sure
she'll understand.
- She has abandonment issues.
(playful music)
(phone beeping)
(energetic drumming)
- You okay?
- Pretty sure I've contracted
Salmonella poisoning.
Whatever.
- Where's Caroline?
- Caroline isn't here yet?
She was supposed to
help me with a letter
I'm writing to my birth mother.
- She gives you advice?
- Yeah, she's just the greatest.
- Hamilton, does Caroline help
you with personal matters?
- Does she ever.
Thanks to her, my wife
and I are listening
to each other for the first
time since Hunter was born.
It's like a whole new marriage.
(dramatic drumming)
- Miss me?
- Apparently
everybody missed you.
- Is everything okay?
- Dr Wolfe, could
you come here please?
Our formula isn't working
on two of the samples.
- But whose samples are these?
- One is the culture I
took from Dr Hamilton
and the other is from Caroline.
- That's my bacteria?
- What's different
about these samples?
- I believe we've isolated a
new strain of Bacillus virilis.
This strain, which is only
present in these two samples,
is even more
antibiotic-resistant
than the original.
Our formula doesn't kill it.
In fact, its population
is multiplying rapidly.
- Shit, shit.
Shit!
- Serena, don't get discouraged.
- Really?
First, I have to be
nice all the time
and then I can't be upset that
my project is totally fucked?
- I'm just saying that
you'll figure it out.
- How do you know that?
Does your sociology degree
give you that information?
Or is it just your naively
optimistic attitude?
- Serena.
- What?
You want me to calm down, take
a deep breath, be patient?
I've tried all of that.
I've jumped through
hoops for you.
None of it worked.
You clearly have no
idea what you're doing.
You're just a sad, insecure
woman who's compulsively nice
to everyone because
no one ever liked you
when you were younger.
(soft music)
(crying)
(phone ringing)
- Hey!
No, not much, just
watching a movie.
No, I can talk.
(somber music)
- [Serena] Did
Caroline come in today?
- [Ellen] Can I speak with you?
- Yeah.
- I've gotten an
offer at another lab.
I feel like I'm not
really growing here.
Do you think I should take it?
If you need me, I'll stay.
- You should take it.
- Oh okay.
Well, I'll stay on until
you find a replacement.
- If you want to start at
the other lab, you should.
We'll be fine.
- We have meetings
we have to get to
so if we just sign the thingy?
- I'm not sure I understand
what thingy you're referring to.
- Oh right, well,
last month I pinched
a receptionist on the
ass and my boss made me
go to this lady and I
signed a piece of paper
and I could go back to work.
- Yeah, I had to
sign the same thing
after I asked a junior associate
if she was wearing a bra or not.
Turned out she was.
- What was the name of the
lady who we used to go to?
She was hot.
- So you're saying that you
already signed a document
apologizing and promising
not to behave this way again?
- Yes, can we go?
- But you have done it again
and you're probably
aren't sorry.
- We could sign another one.
- Let's discuss the
way we treat people.
Would any of you
gentlemen like a mint?
No, you know what?
You don't get a mint!
You don't deserve a mint!
You're not very good people,
and nothing I can say or do
is going to make
you good people.
I did not get two PhDs to
sit around with men like you
and talk about why you
probably shouldn't touch
a female colleague's
behind or use ethnic slurs.
- So, do we not have to sign--
- Get out!
- Hi, Serena.
- Hey.
I guess I failed
sensitivity training.
What happens now?
- I had to alert
the administration
that you didn't
complete your training.
And, now, it's up to them.
I imagine there will be
a hearing of some kind.
I think they'll be fair.
Don't worry yet.
- Whatever happens, happens.
- So how's your research going?
I heard you hit a snag
with that new strain.
- What does it matter if I
never stop this bacteria?
We're all going to die anyway.
- Excuse me, I'm looking for--
- The biology
classroom is around
the corner and to the right.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Buck up, Serena.
I think you'll figure this out.
- [Maggie] Can I have
a lion at my birthday?
- [Sarah] No.
- [Maggie] What
about a killer whale?
- [Sarah] No.
- Please, Mommy?
- No.
- What about other Mommy?
She always says yes!
- [Sarah] What is it?
- Am I too nice?
- [Sarah] Sweetie, come here.
It's okay.
- I put today's
charts on your desk.
- Thanks.
- I guess that's it unless
there's anything else you need.
- No, thanks.
Best of luck.
- I don't mean to
meddle but I think
Ethan has been sleeping in here.
Just thought you should know.
- Did mom and dad
ever do this thing
where they would just send
you to your room for hours?
- Yeah, they sort of
made a game out of it.
- Yeah like, they'd give
you rewards for how long
you could stay up there
without asking for anything.
- I think that's how I
got my first microscope.
- I started to think that I
liked being alone all the time.
But then I just realized that's
how they wanted me to be.
You know?
(quirky music)
- Nancy, it's for you!
- Hi, mom.
- It's been a while.
How are you?
- How am I?
- We just got back
from Joshua Tree.
Do you want to
see some pictures?
- [Glenn] Take a look at
the bracelet I got your mom.
- Aww, isn't it nice?
Do you want to come in?
- We have plans, babe.
- Oh, Glenn.
Would you just go back inside
so I can catch up with Serena?
Just for a second?
- Aren't you
worried about Ethan?
- No.
He's an adult now.
- He's a kid.
So was I.
Why did you send us away?
- It's nothing personal.
Glenn and I just want
to be alone together.
Don't you have someone that
means the world to you?
Honey, you were
always so emotional.
- I was not.
I never cried.
- Well, you used
to cry all the time
about every little thing.
- That is completely untrue.
- Remember when
your goldfish died?
- Maybe you shouldn't
have given me a pet
with such a short
life expectancy!
- You shouldn't have
got so attached.
- Thanks to you I can never
get attached to anything!
- What's going on out here?
- She's just fine, dear.
- I am not fine!
I am completely fucked
up, thanks to you people.
This turtle is dead
because of you.
Do you know the average
lifespan of a box turtle?
Do you?
- We don't, dear.
- 50 years.
50 fucking years.
I can't even keep
a turtle alive.
It's not even mammalian!
I have zero friends.
My life is empty.
I don't even know
how to like someone.
- Well, what's this
got to do with us?
We are very loving people.
- You treated me like shit
and then you abandoned me
and now you're doing
the same thing to Ethan.
- How is Ethan any
of your business?
- He's my brother.
- Well, he's like
a half-brother.
- Honey, Glenn and I are
just better as a pair.
We're like the two musketeers.
- The two musketeers
is not a thing.
They're called the
three musketeers.
They're a group of three people.
That's not even applicable
to this situation.
- Well, that's just who we are.
(dramatic drumming)
- This is a nice apartment.
- Thanks.
Could you...
Nevermind.
- This is great, thanks.
- Ethan?
Do you think it's
my fault Laura died?
How do you even apologize
for something like that?
- I guess you don't.
- I made you these.
- [Dr Hamilton] A small
improvement, at least.
- This is a great idea
for a new formula.
Good work.
- It was Ellen's idea.
- She never told me.
- You wouldn't listen.
(upbeat music)
(players yelling)
(whistle blowing)
- Dr Wolfe.
- You looked pretty
good out there.
- Really?
- Well, actually, it
all seemed quite strange
and I couldn't comprehend
what was happening.
- Is there something in my
report I should clarify?
Did I forget--
- No, no, your work
is perfect, as usual.
I...
I remember that you
mentioned that you played
and I found out where
your practices took place.
I came to ask if you'd consider
coming back to the lab.
I promise things
will be different.
I'll listen better.
I really want you to
contribute on a deeper level.
- Did my new formula work?
- No.
But it was an
improvement on the last.
We're really close.
Thanks to you.
- I want a promotion
and a raise.
- Okay.
So you'll come back?
- Yeah.
Yes.
- You'll come back now?
- Yeah.
- So, what position do you play?
- I'm a beater.
- That sounds intense.
- I was having trouble
being aggressive enough,
but Caroline helped me.
I'm sure she misses you.
- She doesn't really
care about me.
She was paid to
spend time with me.
It was her job.
- Do you go to the lab every
day just because it's your job?
(energetic music)
- Come on.
I respect you but I
have somewhere to be!
Thank you.
Hi.
I'm...
Caroline's my...
- Serena, you came
for my birthday!
When can we open presents?
- Soon.
- [Maggie] You said
that an hour ago!
Come on, let's go
shake all the boxes.
- So you're Serena.
- This is clearly a bad time.
- Come on in.
The more the merrier.
- Lovely home.
- Caroline went upstairs
a little while ago.
I gotta keep my
eye on these guys.
Feel free to go up
and look for her.
- I don't want to impose.
- You'd actually be
doing me a big favor
if you went up and got her.
- [Toy] Oink, oink, oink.
- Caroline?
Caroline?
(suspenseful music)
Caroline, I'm so sorry.
- Ahh, ahh!
- I...
I thought you had
killed yourself
because of the horrible
things that I said to you.
- Nothing you say could ever
make me want to kill myself.
- I sort of have a track
record in that department.
I saw the empty pill bottle
and you looked unconscious.
- I took my last aspirin.
Can I tell you a secret?
- Uh-huh.
- I'm hiding.
I hate children's
birthday parties.
- But you love children.
- I love Maggie.
I don't necessarily
love other people's kids
and in large quantities in the
proximity of sugary treats.
- I came to tell
you how sorry I am.
I was completely out of line.
- Thank you and you were,
but there was some truth
in what you said.
- No, I was just taking my
frustrations out on you.
- I care too much
about being liked.
It's something I'm working on.
- Well, if you ever need
asshole training, I'm available.
(children chattering)
- [Woman] Look at
you, you're filthy.
Hold still.
(boy sobbing)
(dramatic music)
- It's the children.
It's the children!
- What?
- You and Dr Hamilton
both have young children.
Children must be the carriers
of the resistant
strain of virilis.
That's why your samples
didn't respond to the formula.
Have any of these
children seemed ill?
- I've been vomited on
like three times already,
but that's not
necessarily abnormal
for a kids' birthday party.
- Did you keep any samples?
- No.
- I'll have to swab them all.
It's fun, right?
Next!
Thank you.
- Just a little science project!
Are they in danger?
- Not anymore.
Do you want to come back
to the lab with me after?
I'm sorry, that was dumb, it's
your kid's birthday party.
- You're the poster
child for birth control.
And your IQ matches
your shoe size!
- Did you?
(horns blaring)
- Come on, jerks, we
have lab results to get!
- It's the children.
The children were
the key all along!
- Guys, I'll be back.
Apparently Laura Stern's
research was a fraud.
She'd been embezzling
grant money for five years.
She was about to be audited.
That's why she killed herself.
- Gather everyone.
I have an announcement.
Before I start, why
is this skeleton here?
- I ordered it.
- What for?
- Skeletons are cool.
- Okay.
So these cultures were
taken from children, age?
- Six.
And Hamilton, how old is
that former fetus of yours?
- Hunter?
He's three.
- So if my hunch is correct,
the carriers of the strain
are at least six and under.
Parents can get it
from their children.
It's pathogenic
and drug resistant.
Yet adults don't seem
to be getting sick.
Yes, Ellen?
- No, it's probably dumb.
- Speak up.
- Maybe adults have a natural
antibody to this strain
that we can use to figure
out how to kill it?
- That's a great thought.
I want a full genetic
sequencing of every bacterium
and a close comparison
of the adult samples
to the children's.
If we get to the bottom
of this, we can figure out
how to eradicate it for good.
Ellen.
Good work.
- Serena, I hear you've
made another breakthrough.
- Well, it's all
for the children.
- And Caroline, in light
of what we've just learned
about Laura, the university
has decided that Serena
no longer needs
sensitivity training.
- Yes, I do.
- That's definitely
true, but the university
will no longer
require or pay for it.
- Well, it looks like
my work here is done.
- [Ellen] Dr Wolfe, would you
like to take a look at this?
- Call me after work tonight.
We'll go see a
movie or something.
You're doing great on your own.
- [Ellen] Dr Wolfe!
- I'll see you soon.
- [Ellen] Its defenses
are breaking down.
Do you see it?
- Thanks.
I...
I'll be right back.
Caroline.
(upbeat music)
You left before I
could thank you.
- You don't need to--
- Thank you for making me
a little more of a person.
- My pleasure.
- I don't know
how to say this...
I think I have feelings for you.
I have for a while now.
- Feelings?
Are you attracted to me?
- Possibly.
I've done some interesting
Google searches.
- Serena, can you
describe these feelings?
- I get excited when
I'm about to see you
and sad when I don't.
When you squeeze my hand
or touch my shoulder,
it feels good.
It makes me feel a
little less angry
about whatever it is
that I'm angry about.
When something
important happens,
I want to tell you about it.
I imagine what you'd say or do.
I miss you when I don't see you
and my day always
gets better when I do.
- I feel the same way about you.
- You do?
- That's what it feels
like to have a friend.
- Oh.
So we're friends?
- Very good friends.
- So what do we do now?
- I think we hug.
- Oh.
(gentle music)
- Where do turtles
go when they die?
- Nobody knows.
- Are we going to die?
- Yes.
- Not for a very
long time, honey.
- I'm going to try
not to think about it.
- You know, that's
what most of us do.
- Maggie, what do you
say we go play out front?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- I'm sorry I inadvertently
made your child
aware of her own mortality.
- She'll be okay.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- [Moviegoer] What's he doing?
Doesn't he know she's
waiting for him?
- [Moviegoer] He's not going
in the basement, is he?
He's going in the basement!
- I got this.
Excuse me, we're trying
to watch this movie.
Could you shut the hell up!
Thanks.
- [Moviegoer] Why don't
you shut up, lady?
All the barriers
colliding inside
Always falling to a beat
That you will like
You make me feel like
I don't need to hide
It's getting lonely as
I push you out of my mind
Oh, it's clear
A cure is here
To all our thoughts
That feed our fears
This energy has been saving me
As I take on my worst enemy
This energy is a remedy
To everything
that's killing me
Oh
Never thought
someone would like
Who I am beyond
these sensitive eyes
Looked within and
found this truth
That I like it when
I'm here next to you
This energy is
what's saving me
As I take on my worst enemy
This energy is a remedy
To everything
that's killing me
Oh
We're two molecules
breaking all the rules
Oh what a fool would do
To breathe in
To be near
Somebody like you
We're two molecules
breaking all the rules
Oh what a fool would do
A fool would do
It's a slow, slow growth
But I'm doing all that I know
To be better
Letting my old self go
It's a slow, slow growth
But I'm doing all that I know
To be better
Letting my old self go
It's a slow, slow growth
But I'm doing all that I know
To be better
Letting my old self go
This energy has been saving me
As I take on my worst enemies
This energy is a remedy
To everything
that's killing me
Oh
This energy has been saving me
As I take on my
own worst enemy
This energy is a remedy
To everything
that's killing me
Oh