You forgot
Oh my...
This is horrible.
I'm so sorry
It's okay. I know how much stress
you've been under lately.
No, no... That's no excuse
This is so terrible of me.
On top of that, I'm late... Can you
imagine it? Of all days
Today had to be the one for them
to send that stupid guy to come
So I could be relieved from duty
I'm so sick of this stupid job!
They just want to be stressing you out...
working you like a slave for minimum wage
I mean, what kind of nonsense is that?
Okay... Okay... Okay
It's fine. You're here now, and the day is
not over.
Go and change... let's
get this party started
You make it sound so simple
Okay. You know what I want
for my birthday?
I want us to have a nice romantic dinner
Then, I want us to watch a movie
Then... you got the idea.
But, most importantly, I want us
to not complain about anything
Let's just forget all our problems. Uh?
Will you give me that as my birthday gift?
I feel really bad
Look at that
I should be the one doing all that for you
So, does that mean I'm not
going to get my wish?
Sorry. Okay, what do you want me to wear?
Something a little nicer...
With a better attitude
And... You didn't even complement me.
You don't like what you see?
What?!
You look beautiful. Absolutely stunning!
Alright, go and change.
Come back and bring me Superman!
Don't you mean black panther?
Yes... Sorry. Bring me back the king!
So what happened to the one
I sent you last year?
Oh, is that so?
The latest version has come out
So, the one you have
is not working anymore, right?
Okay
Is there anything else you
want me to buy for you?
Are you sure?
Okay... How about your friends?
Is there anything you want me
to buy for them?
No?
How about your favorite teacher?
No, how about your principal?
Are you sure they don't want
the latest iPod or iPhone?
Sorry?
Sorry for who?
You better be sorry for yourself!
My friend hand over the phone to mama!
I said, hand the phone over!
Mama, what's the matter with that boy?
Does he think I'm plucking money
from trees here or what?
Young is not an excuse for foolishness
He's old enough to use common sense
Ah, ah...
Every time, it's this
one or the other thing
Especially him!
Always asking me for things I don't
even buy for myself... Ah, ah!
Am I their father?
I mean, did I come here to fend for them
Sorry mama
Mama, I don't mean to complain...
I'm just...
It's Just a really hectic season for
me right now... that's all... I have...
I have lots on my plate
Mama, I know and...
I appreciate that
No mama she's not.
Don't worry, you'll be the first to know
Just be a little patient.
It will happen at the right time.
Okay Mama.
I hear you.
Alright.
Okay, Um... Mama, I have to go.
I'm running late for work
Okay.
All right.
Okay...
Alright. Okay, greetings ma.
Okay
Bye bye.
I'm sorry... did I wake you?
No, it's fine
I know I could just say no.
But, they just keep asking for money,
for clothes and things and...
When you say no, it just makes
you look stingy
meanwhile, it's them... I mean, don't
they use common wisdom
Anyway, um... you said you wanted to talk
to me about something last night
Um... Don't worry. We'll
talk about it later
Alright. Well, I'll see
you later after work
Ah, ah. Are you just going to leave
without kissing your wife goodbye?
I haven't brushed my teeth
- So who is infertile? You or him?
- Ah, ah..
Cynthia, what kind of question is that?
How rude?
Girl, we are family!
Who else you gonna keep it real with?
Besides, I'm only echoing what everyone
else has been asking.
Who's everyone else?
Can I get a glass please?
Yes, Queen Cynthia!
Ah
You better recognize.
So, who's everyone else?
You know, I'm really feeling
this mini kitchen
Really? Is that right?
Yeah, it's like a life-sized dollhouse
Well, you know I've always wanted one of
those dollhouses ever since we were kids
Yeah you could practically reach
for anything from one spot
And that's the beauty of
living in a life-sized
But Cynthia, who is everyone else?
So you haven't been receiving
any pressure from your mom?
My mom is everyone else?
Come on
Come on, you know how it is when you've
been married over nine months
with no baby and no belly.
I mean how long have you been
married anyway? five years?
Three!
Well that's well over nine months
Can the nice Cynthia please come
out and play now?
You don't think I'm being nice right now?
Anyway, for your information,
neither one of us is infertile
We're just waiting until the right time
to bring our baby into this world
Okay...
I know whose idea that was...
Oh Cynthia, please...
Seriously though, can I just...
Can I just be honest with
you for one moment?
It's that even possible?
Wow... That was a dirty play. Okay
But I'ma be a good sport.
I'm gonna let it slide this time.
You know I love you, right?
Bro, can I hold something?
Yes... You can hold your own pocket
Bro, there's nothing there to hold.
Just look and see how dry it is...
Man, It feels like harmattan.
Ah...
Ima, wait a minute
yes?
Are we not working the same job, with
overtime hours?
Plus you're the bachelor...
Yes?
Why is it that you're always the
one asking for money.
Bro, Nosa, it's not rocket science
Look, between sending money back home
and money for rent payment,
there's barely any money left for food;
not to mention transportation costs
But I have already told you
You need to cut your coat
according to your size.
I guess you have figured me out.
I guess, I'm a tailor...
Sit there and crack jokes. Ah...
I hope you know comedians in Nigeria
are making some serious money...
Just in case you want to do
this comedy thing
Look, I'm not interested in comedy.
I'm just a very funny person
I hear you.
Exactly
Anyway
yes?
You need to give up that
big apartment and...
move out of that expensive neighborhood.
You can go to a smaller apartment
or even rent like a studio or something
Ah! Studio?!
What's wrong with you?
I am not feeling that studio idea
Why?
I'm not yet married
And?
I intend to marry up in life.
I need that apartment to serve as leverage
for the kind of woman I'm searching for
No top notch woman, with
class and self-respect
would be interested in pulling with a guy
who's unable to pull his own weight
Do you understand what I'm trying to say?
So, she will be marrying your apartment?
Come on bro...
Okay, let's be real!
You are very lucky
Not a lot of women are like Efosa
As a matter of fact, she's one in a million
I've never met any other woman willing
to downgrade inside a marriage
What?!
So, I am a downgrade?
Is this your way of
indirectly insulting me?
Why? why would you say such a thing?
I'm only paying your wife a complement
I was Just hailing her.
Look, you can tell that she's
tasted the good side of life...
At least, before things fell
apart in our country.
Perhaps, it was fate
bringing both of you together
I doubted she'd have seen or considered
you if her father's wealth didn't plummet.
Sometimes, that's a blessing in disguise
Because, I believe it's those humbling
circumstances that formed such a
strong, beautiful character in her.
So yes, I'm reaping the blessing or
rather the blessings
Look, Ima, let me tell you something
There are good women out there
but you'll never find them if you're trying
to be someone or something or not
If a woman follows you
for your possessions,
she'll just end up despising you.
I'm telling you
Yes, Master Sensei
You speak with the knowledge
of the praying mantis
Okay, Mr. Comedian! Ah.
Come on, can"t you take a joke? Sorry
But on a serious note, I hear you
I'll take your advice
really?
Yeah
I'll move out of my apartment and I'll
look for a cheaper solution
As a matter of fact, actually...
I have a great idea...
Really
Yeah
So, I can move in with you guys...
and we can split the rent three ways.
What do you think about that?
You have lost you mind. Are you drunk?
You must have used alcohol
as mouthwash. Idiot!
My friend, you better move into
that little security booth
Chill out, ah...
Don't go find your own apartment
Something is wrong with you...
Look, I have a big house back home,
for your information
Big house? Yet you borrow money
every day... You're not ashamed...
You have to be your brother's keeper.
Why are we friends?
What kind of friends? Do I know you?
We are only coworkers
Don't talk like that
I don't know you like that.
Go and find your own apartments
You're not ashamed? Your
mates are making babies
and you're here borrowing money from me.
Comedian... You better
go sell some tickets...
You keep living the cheap life...
Keep living the cheap life!
But who's is borrowing money now?
Cheap life? Look at your life...
Ain't you a professional borrower?
Okay you win, I agree...
By the way, you still owe me...
Okay, Please calm down... You win
Okay, how about we put
your honesty to test?
Okay, go ahead.
Are you happy?
- Am I happy?
- Ah, ah... It's English I spoke
Yes
My honesty meter is detecting
some conflict with your answer
Your honesty meter is broken
Whatever
Okay, so tell me this
If you could do it all over again,
Would you still
choose Nosa over Desmond?
I can't believe I'm even entertaining this
O please, believe it,
and answer, honestly.
You're basically asking me if
I would still pick love over comfort
I don't mind comfort...
Oh believe me, there are days when
I so wish that money wasn't an issue
But, at the end of the day,
I'd still pick love above all
See, I think in some ways you're wrong
Yeah?
Yeah, you equate Nosa to love
and Desmond to money
That is a faulty equation
I mean, the way I see it,
Nosa is love without money and
Desmond is love with money
I know... I've seen how madly
in love with you he was
The guy was lovesick. No lie!
But I wasn't in love with him
That doesn't matter
he is a young, rich, handsome
prince and in love with you
You know, that is every woman's dream!
Prince?
That's a little bit of a stretch
His father is a chief!
Anyway, he has princely money.
Why don't you go and marry him then.
It's not me he wants.
Anyways, did you see what he bought his
current girlfriend? A new convertible Benz
I saw it on IG
I guess he finally found love after all
That car is fine!
Babe that could have been you.
I'm happy with Nosa
I've told you. Nosa is my soulmate
My best friend! I couldn't imagine going
on this journey called life without him
That is why for richer or for poorer, in
good times and in bad times,
love is what makes life special
You sound like an old
R&amp;B song
Really.
Yes! I am the champion!
You're no champion. That was pure luck!
Luck?! Excuse me! That was pure
mathematical genius!
Is that so?
Yes and if you're looking for an excuse,
blame those oversize fingers of yours
What?!
These? Oversize fingers?
Yeah? You wanna see oversize fingers?
Nosa!
You wanna see oversize fingers?
Nosa! Nosa! No! Nosa! Please
No!
No! Nosa! Nosa!
Stop it!
Nosa! No!
Can you believe the delivery guy just
left Mr. Edward's package on the sidewalk?
Good think this is not our last neighbor.
It would have disappeared by now.
Remember when you ordered
that small camera?
Please don't remind me.
Did you at least ring the doorbell?
I don't need one more person asking
me for anymore money.
You know he can just come downstairs
and knock on the door, right?
You're so sure he's
going to raise the rent.
It's been over two years. Believe me,
he's trying to give us a heads up.
Maybe he's trying to invite you to church
Nah. He already knows the answer to that
Busy, busy, busy! No time for God.
What?! Is that the pot
calling the kettle black?
I am neither a pot or a pothead.
Thank you very much.
In fact, the Bible says I am a saint.
Okay, saint Efosa,
show me where in the Bible it says you
need to go to church to get to heaven
That's not fair. Why don't you go
to the church and ask the pastor?
No need for that.
He can't find it either.
Because it's not there
You know, I really miss the days when we
used to go to church together
Very encouraging
And you were a lot more positive
Well, I guess I'm too negative for
you now, Saint Efosa.
Come and lay down next to me
I want a baby
I think it's time
The pressure is getting to you.
It's not that. My
biological clock is ticking
Seriously?
I thought we had to plan. What's about
nursing school? You still have what...
two years left?
Babe I'll be almost 30 by then
My mother had me at 34...
Her last born in her 40s
Did you seriously just make your
mother the standard?
All I'm saying is, 29 is still pretty young
Even your mother won't give me rest,
if we haven't had a baby in a year
So, it's the pressure from our
parents that's getting to you
It's not!
Babe
We have a plan
Let's just stick to it.
It's not the pressure from our parents
Yes it.
It's not the pressure from our parents!
I hate it when you do that!
What?!
When you try and tell me how I feel.
I just told you it's nothing to do with
our parents and you still insist
Gosh, I hate that!
Sorry
Why don't you just let me tell you
how I feel and listen to me?
I said I'm sorry.
Okay. Go ahead, talk I'm listening
Stop over-reacting.
You see?
You see? there you go again.
Oh come on, what now? Ah...
You know what? I don't
feel like talking anymore.
Seriously? You're just going to
leave me here just like that?
Efosa!
Leave me alone
Now police say a group of men randomly beat
a 39 year old man to the
ground and rubbed him.
How are you doing?
Sorry mammy, I didn't want
to shock you or anything
That's okay
Listen,
I think my mother likes you
I know she can't talk, but I can tell
You know, I like you too.
I didn't like the other Aide. She was too
stuck-up and had an attitude. But you don't
Even if you're far more prettier than her
You know, I don't see a lot of African
women that pretty. What part you're from?
Wakanda?
I know it's not a real place
but check this out; If you were a queen,
what kinda queen you would be?
My kinda Queen!
Get the joke? Wa kinda queen...
Ma kanda queen
I get it.
So wait, is he getting physical with you?
No, it's not that.
So, then like what? Is he asking you out to
dinner, on a date, or something like that?
No, it's just
Constant compliments.
Compliments? Mira please! I wish somebody
would be complimenting me all day
I'ma send my boyfriend to him
Trust me, this is not the sort of man
you want your boyfriend around
He has this weird vibe. He's
just very weird and creepy
My guts just don't agree with him
Well, remember what they said in training...
Sometimes, you gotta trust your gut.
I know. And that's my dilemma
Can I really ask them to transfer me
because my guts don't agree
with the son of my clients?
I don't know.
Plus, you know how long it took them
to give me this reassignment
That'll be like the third one in
less than two months
I don't know.
Anyway
Good afternoon sir
Hello Nosa.
You were just on my mind
Thank you.
I've been meaning to talk with you
It's about your rent
First of all, let me say how pleased I am
to have you guys as my tenants
It honestly feels more like
family living downstairs
And I especially want to thank you for
how you've been voluntarily taking the
garbage out for the house on pickup days.
That has been such a relief for me
That's okay. It's not a problem sir.
So, you know your two-year
lease is ending next month.
And as that, a renewal usually
comes with an increase in rent
However, I have a proposal for
you, if you're interested
okay
I was thinking, if you could help with
the house maintenance, things like
Mowing the lawn regularly or blowing the
leaves. Shoveling the snow during winter
Things of that nature.
I'm thinking, I can knock $150
off your monthly rent
okay I'll knock off $200
Yes, yes! Yes, I'll do it!
Great. We have a deal.
Thank you sir
What are these for?
They're for Cynthia. She left them here.
She came here?
You didn't mention that to me
Is she forbidden from visiting?
Oh come on, you know I feel about her.
Well, she's family, and she happens to
be one of my closest friends.
Yeah. Very arrogant and snobbish friend.
She's human.
We all have flaws.
Well,
don't worry, once we make millions
you won't have to wash
your clothes anymore
We can just hire servants just for that
I don't have a problem
washing my own clothes
Well, if I had my own way, I wouldn't
want my wife to lift a finger
I've been thinking about this baby thing
I know how much it means to you
You don't have to do me any favors
Oh come on, I'm really trying here
Sorry
I'm sorry for not hearing you
I don't know, maybe...
Maybe I'm the one who's not
handling the pressure well
I know you family didn't think you were
making the right choice marrying me
in fact if not for this visa lottery,
I wouldn't have stood a chance
You knew where I stood
Yes, I know but
I don't know if as a man I could have
asked you to make such sacrifice
to marry into such poverty
I will always be grateful to God for
coming through so timely.
So, you know my expectations were very
high leaving Nigeria to come to America
But, sometimes it just feels like
Like God just did me this one big favor
and was like, you're on own from here.
Oh, that's not true.
I'm not saying it is
I'm just saying how I feel.
And you accuse me of
not listening to you
Please Continue, I'm listening.
We've been in this country
for over three years
I expected that by we'll be
doing way better than this
I expected that by now we'll have something
to show for the amount of time spent
And on the other hand, the financial
responsibilities is enough stress
for someone to just want to run
and go back home
I mean, we could be living in a better
and bigger apartment than this
but I've to subject you to this dungeon,
just to save money for dependents
that are not even my own children
It's a sacrifice that I'm gladly making
And please don't call my
house a dungeon again.
My bad
You know, the fact that we're able to
help take care of so many people
is a huge accomplishments
Do you think that if we were back home,
and you had finished school, even if you
had gotten a job as a civil servant,
that you'd be able to do the same thing?
I know there's a lot of pressure
But it's not coming from me
Don't you ever wish for
better circumstances?
Of course
sometimes it gets really hard,
especially in the Winter
But even on the worst days, you're the one
that helps me on... You give me hope.
So let me ask you this
Have you ever wondered what it would
be like if you married Desmond?
Yes
I've wondered.
But, I've never wished it
Did you hear about the
death of my friend, Edun?
Yes. Sorry for the loss. What a tragedy
Isn't it?
Simple illnesses that should be irrelevant,
is just claiming lives over there
What sort of a country is that?
You know what that country needs?
Young, educated minds, with proper vision
Yes
These recycled leaders are old, and have
lost their vision, if they ever had one.
Can you imagine that in this Era,
they still don't have stable electricity?
Ha!
Please give us young innovators!
Look at how our young Artists are
making waves on a global level
That's only parts of the solution
What we really need are
leaders with a heart,
True
with love and compassion for the people
Exactly!
I mean, anyone can get a degree;
even the devil is very educated
Ha! Nosa for president
O please, I'm not at all interested.
I hope you see this? can you see it?
This is one of the major
issues with our citizens
Everybody complains, but nobody
wants to step forward to make change
Go and sit down!
Efe, I'm boiling Eggs. You want some?
No my love, I don't
want to be late for work
I'm leaving
One of these days that'd soon
be a nurse's uniform
Ah! Amen
Listen, I have some plans
I want to run by you
I think you'll actually favor them
Really?
Yes
Later.
I thought they said you're not
allowed to wear jewelry at work
What?
Oh... um, I don't think
they meant wedding rings.
Oh, okay. Alright
enjoy your day
I'm not going back to
that assignment... No way!
What?!
What?! No! That's not true!
He tried to rape me!
He tried to rape me
So, like I said, I've been really thinking
about how to make this baby plan work
So, I've been doing some major research
and I think I have a solid plan
So, just a few days ago I ran into Stanley. He
used to work at Brilliant Security Guards...
Remember the one I used
to work with before?
So we're catching up and I discover he's
no longer working security.
He's now doing taxi
And I can just see cause, funny enough,
the time we were working together,
we used to brainstorm the idea of taxi and,
coincidentally, I run into him on the block
I mean, is that a confirmation or what?
Man...
Listen...
If I put in the time I
put in security into taxi,
Especially if I own my own car,
huh! O girl, my love, this is a major hit!
We can even start shooting for the baby
sooner than planned. I'm thinking like...
October, November, you know,
after a fall semester...
That way we'll be expecting by summer break
See I told you I really put some
serious thought into this
Come on, you're not saying anything
So what do you think?
Um... It sounds interesting
Interest?
Oh... Okay...
Okay, you're worried about the
financial aspect, right? Okay.
Look, this whole taxi plan will run
us a little over... Like $5,000...
That's including the fees, TLC license,
documents, insurance...
And even down payment for
financing a new car
So, how are we going
to get the money? Okay.
Well, already we're saving for the fall
semester... that's not due till, what?
October, right? So, I mean if I
start doing the taxi,
We can raise the money
by like, August ending.
I mean, I'll still be
doing my security hours
Just less hours; not too much, so
I can still - That's only $2,000
Just hold on... wait, wait, wait first.
Just... Hear the whole plan, okay?
Um... Okay so... if I double
up on my hours,
I'll talk to my Supervisor... That
shouldn't be a big problem
You can still maintain your same hours
Overtime is not necessary
Unless you want to... I mean,
that could always help.
But I think,
between both our checks we
can raise like... let's see...
$4,000 by August... And, yeah, hopefully
if this new assignment goes steady
before the end of summer, we can do that.
You don't think it'll work.
Babe, Seriously,
I've been really thinking about this
I mean, even running into Stanley,
isn't... Isn't that like a sign?
It's not that
No?
Then what?
Babe, what's wrong? What's wrong?
What happened?
Babe, what happened?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay... It's okay... What's going on?
Sorry.
I should have told you.
I just didn't want to add more
stress to your plate
Sorry for what?
You have nothing to be sorry about
That bastard is going to
be so sorry... I swear!
That's another reason why I didn't tell you
Just...
Let it go, please. I've already
filed a police report.
I can't believe he also filed
a police report. How dare he?!
Nosa, let it go
The truth will come out
I'm so sorry. This is all my fault.
Nosa, please don't do that
If you didn't have to work, this
would have never happened
No! Stop it! Don't do that to yourself.
This has nothing to do with that
I don't want you to work anymore.
Why?
I'll request more hours.
Don't worry, we'll be fine.
No. I want to work... I'm going to work
Please. Please... Let's not argue over this
I need you to respect my
decision as your husband
It's very important to me. Please
Where is the stupid paper?
What are you looking for?
It's a telephone number I wrote on a
piece of paper and I put it in my wallet.
Oh... I hate when this happens! Ah!
Maybe try checking your wallet.
Okay... Okay... Don't kill me
I'm assuming you think
you left it in your pants.
Okay
Why don't you try checking in the
top drawer of your night stand?
Why don't you just help me look for it...
instead of asking me
a thousand questions?
Boss, please don't be upset.
I'm just trying to help.
Whenever I do laundry, I normally
check your pockets
and take whatever I find out, and put
it in the top drawer of the nightstand.
That's why I'm asking
Boss, please don't be angry... but why
is this number so important anyway?
My field supervisor, Tunde, travelled about
two weeks ago and we have this new guy
covering for him. He's acting really shady.
He doesn't want to give me any hours.
He's acting like it's his father's
company or something.
Anyway, before Tunde left, he
gave me his telephone number
And he's close with the owner. So I want to
reach out to him and see if he can
put in a word for me
You know how much we really need this.
It's not there.
I don't understand
What about safety?
So, you're saying, you can't place me
because he filed a police report?
Really?
Two months
wait...
On another note, I know you've heard
Heard what?
Come on... You know what
I'm talking about
It's trending all over social media
Desmond?
So you have heard.
Isn't that crazy?
First of all, it's not trending...
But you still managed to hear
Do I smell, some sort of interest
in other people's affairs?
You... Shamelessly posted it all over IG
Ah ah... Why do you get so much
pleasure from people's pain?
Oh please... You make it
sound like somebody died
They only broke up, for crying out loud
Or, should I say, he broke up with her
So you don't see any pain there?
What? Of course there's pain.
But, that's a part of life.
She'll get over it
Plus, it's probably best for her anyways
Cynthia you're cold...
Ah come on, you know that's not true.
I have insights. I'm
speaking intelligently.
What kind of insights?
Oh, I thought you were not interested...
Cynthia, if you don't talk right now, I'll
jump over this table and strangle you...
Ah... My sister, violence
is never the answer
Come on, tell me...
He broke up with her because
he doesn't love her
What?!
mmhmm yep.
And I commend him for that
It shows honesty and integrity...
He didn't even asked for the car back
Wow...
So how did you know he
wasn't in love with her?
He told me
He told you?
Exactly what I just said
As in, he spoke to you on the phone?
Why do you sound so surprised? We talk.
Why would he be sharing intimate
aspects of his relationships with you?
Ah ah... Like I said, we talk.
And quite often.
How come you never told me this before?
Efosa, you are a happily married woman
I thought such things wouldn't interest you
Yeah, I know, but still...
Don't forget I knew him before you.
I practically introduced you both
Because I saw this dazzling potential
But you shut it down
Was I supposed to banish him for my
friendship?
So, you guys have been in
touch all this while?
Well, we maintained our friendship
And you talk often?
Well, in different seasons...
Look, I'll put it this way
We may not talk for a while, but when we
do, we just pick up where we left off.
He's that cool.
Now who's got a special interest in him?
Oh no, no, no... and definitely
not on his part
In fact, you would be quite interested
to find out the real reason
why he broke up with his girlfriend. Even
though he did tell me in confidentiality...
real reason?
But you said it was because he
wasn't in love with her anymore.
True...
But that's because he's still in
love with somebody else...
Who?
What?
Stop!
Honest to god.
You're it baby.
No...
Please be serious...
I'm serious... I'm not kidding!
Look, Desmond was in love with
you, that deep. Okay?
He said he will not marry another woman
unless he feels that kind of love.
His exact words.
Cross my heart.
Nosa: Okay, okay. So do you know
anyone that might have his number?
I already asked him.
He said he doesn't have it.
Anyway, do you know when
he's scheduled to come back to work?
What?
That's almost two months from now!
Okay, okay, okay... Bye. Bye. Ah..
What kind of stuff is this now?
Five thousand dollars!
Honey I almost fainted. Ah!
I knew she was going to help us. But I
thought she was going to give us two,
maybe five hundred dollars at most.
When I saw that extra zero on that check?
I couldn't believe it!
Ha!
This is the wildest thing that has
happened to us in a long time!
Wow!
Cynthia! Wow! Ah!
Ah!
Life is so unpredictable at times
I appreciate her thoughtfulness.
This is like a dream
I know!
But...
We can't accept this.
What?
I just wish you
politely refused initially. Now it's just
going to be really awkward
when we have to give it back
What are you talking about?
You're joking...
You almost had me.
I'm not joking. I'm very serious.
Nosa
To be honest, I'm kind of
disappointed in you
Nosa, what... What are you talking about?
Is that what you do?
Going running around, to talk to Cynthia
about our personal struggles?
Nosa,
Ha!
By now, the whole town must have heard
They must be thinking,
Wow, I can't even take care of my wife
Oh they warned you, but you won't listen.
I won't be surprised if there's a song
that comes out in the next few days
about this tragedy!
What a foolish girl! She
chose a beggar over a Prince!
Nosa, what are you talking about?
I don't know what's going on with you,
but you better snap out of it
No! You're the one that
needs to snap out of it!
I will be damned if I allow Cynthia
make a mockery of me
or you, for that matter!
Is that what this is about?
Your pride?
Did you ask her or did she volunteer it?
What?
You heard me!
Nosa, I've already told you. I was Just as
shocked as you are when she gave it to me
So, why would she offer to help you
if you didn't go crying or running to her?
How did she know the exact
amount we talked about?
She didn't put your name on the check.
She wrote mine in bold!
Nosa, I've never known
you to be this Petty
Alright, go ahead. Insult me. disrespect me
I have always given you
the utmost of respect
If that is the case,
respect my decision now!
Henceforth, you cannot discuss our
personal affairs or issues with her.
Call her, first thing in the morning,
and let her know our decision!
I will gladly call her!
In fact, I'll call her tonight
just show me something.
Give me another $5,000 check... or 4000...
You know what, I'll even takes $3,000
Something! Just something that
justifies this pride of yours.
I may not be rich,
but I have self-respect and nobody
will ever take that away from me
Nobody!
No
Not you, and definitely, not Cynthia!
This is not self-respect Nosa
This is pride! Pride! And you want
to kill us with it!
Not with hunger but with pride!
Ah ah!
I know men who have way more money
way more self-respect, that have sunk to
their knees and thanked God for a lot less!
What you need to do, Nosa,
is call her and say, thank you!
How dare you? How dare you take the
gesture from my friend, my dear friend,
and just splits on its like that!
She sacrificed her hard earned
money to lift us up,
and you just trampled it under foot
This is the most hurtful thing you have
done to me Nosa.
You're so wrapped up in
your own self-loathing,
that you can't see who you
are dragging down with you.
Self-loathing
Yes
For months, all you've been
doing is complaining...
whining about this, that and the other!
Nosa, I have tried my
hardest to be patient;
to be encouraging,
but I find myself walking around on
eggshells, when I'm with you
In the last month, everything I
do seems to irritate you
and you seem to find Fault in everybody
I am sorry!
Sorry that I can't come home and fake it!
I am sorry that I decided to
be transparent with my wife!
I am sorry that I'm doing my best
to handle my responsibilities,
in spite of the crappy hand
that life is dealing me!
You make it sound like you're the
only one going through something
Or that we haven't overcome
challenges together
At least in the past,
you used to be hopeful
Now it's just whining, whining, whining!
Oh, I'm sorry, you call that transparency
I can't believe you're
heaping insults on me
Because of Cynthia! Cynthia!
You're so blinded, you can't
even see her motive!
You think she's doing this out of
the goodness of her heart?
She never wanted us to get married!
She never wanted to see us happen!
This is her opportunity to just
gloat over me!
You're still holding on to that?
You're confusing me.
Is this bitterness or pride?
Or maybe it's both.
Here you go, just proving me right
I don't think you've ever,
ever been this disrespect.
No! No way! You don't get to do that!
You don't get to silence me...
I am not being disrespectful!
It is my turn to be transparent with
you.
In the last month, I have found
myself walking on eggshells
to make sure that I'm not stressing you out
to the point that I had to bottle
up the fact that I almost got raped!
I thought I already apologized for that!
I am sorry you have to work!
If I was rich like, what's his name, you
will never have to work a day in your life
so I am sorry, it is my fault
that you almost got raped!
I am traumatized
But somehow it's all about you
If that's not self-loathing,
I don't know what is.
I don't want to continue having this
conversation
The check was written out in my name
So, if you want it that badly, let her
go and write it in your name
and while you're there, She can pay for
your school fees and feed you too!
I thought you said her surgery
is almost a month from now
I'm going earlier.
How long after are you going to be there?
I don't know.
Hello, young man.
Hello Sir.
How are you?
Good Afternoon, Sir. I'm fine, thank you
Well, let me use this opportunity to let you
know you're doing a fine job on this property
Thank you sir.
Mr. Edward, are you...
Are you playing by yourself?
Oh no.
I found this, earlier today, in the Attic.
It used to be one of my
wife and I favorite game
Just staring at it brings back such
pleasant memories
Do you play this?
Um... Yeah. Sometimes with my wife
Wow, that's great!
Speaking of your wife,
I haven't seen her in a while.
Is she on vacation?
Something like that... Yeah
Alone? Without you?
Well, I suppose she won't mind me
challenging you to a game.
Right now?
Why not?
Oh, unless you're scared
Scared? What, me? Ah no, no, no, no.
Mr. Edward, just wait right there.
Let me finish taking the trash bags out
Don't run away.
Oh, I see we have a trash
talker on our hands.
Well I'll be right here
And when I'm done schooling you, you'll
know why they call me, The Professor
Oh, Efosa, that smells so good.
I hope it tastes half as good as it
smells
I hope so too.
Oh my goodness, don't you hate that?
Oh... One day, I was visiting a
colleague of mine
and his mother was cooking in the kitchen
Wait. Male colleague, at home
with his mother...
Alright, carry on.
Oh please it's nothing like
that not even close. Okay?
Anyways, as I was saying,
before I was rudely interrupted
Sorry Madam
Um-hum... As I was saying...
The woman had me salivating
over the smell of the food
It was so obvious, he had to offer me some
And of course,
who was I to be rude and refuse
So I obliged.
Lord, who sent me. Chai!
That bad?
What?!
Let's just say,
the smell was going north while the
taste was going south, at full speed.
I thought I was eating something
different. It tasted so watered-down
Oh my goodness. It was...
It tasted as though someone came
in and poured a gallon of water inside
Wow. That bad?
My sister, I kid you not.
Well, with the way you're dissing the woman's
food, I'm even reconsidering you trying mine.
Oh no. It's too late now,
I must eat that today
Girl, You still haven't learnt your lesson.
Oh my goodness.
I can't believe it.
You're in town? Wow!
Oh my... Efosa, please come. Come!
Please come in.
Wow!
How are you doing Efe?
Hi...
How are you?
I'm well. Thank you. And you?
Good. Um...
Please excuse me for a second.
Ah, you look so nice.
Cynthia!
Have a seat
Look, I promise I didn't know he was coming
I didn't even know he was in town
I'm just as surprised as you are
Why don't I believe you
I swear...
This is so embarrassing!
Don't worry... you don't look that bad
Besides, I thought you didn't
care what he thinks
Cynthia I'm in no mood to be Jolly!
Jolly?
Sorry. Just change now and then
maybe also put on some lip gloss.
But, did he know that I
was staying here with you?
Please let me get back to our guest.
We don't want to be rude.
He's in there, waiting by himself
So, what are you up to these days?
Ah... nothing much. I'm just
working, keeping myself busy
mmm
Yeah... I see your business is doing well
Absolutely, you know, we
just have to keep it going.
Oh here comes the Efosa.
That's Mrs. Efosa Edose.
So, how have you been Efosa?
I have been well, thank you.
My apologies for any
inconvenience, you know.
Popping up here without any notice.
But you didn't have to change
because of me, you know.
I didn't change because of you. I wanted to
Not to seem forward but,
You look as beautiful as earlier.
Desmond, you're such a gem
And you're such a great chef, you know.
This place smells like paradise Kitchen.
Oh, It's not me. that was the
hard work of our chef Efosa
Really?
Um-hum. Yeah.
Efosa, this smells delicious.
And I bet you the taste matches.
Oh would you like to try some?
My pleasure, of course, I would
absolutely love to.
I'm not gonna let you win this time.
Yes, please let me win for
the fifth straight time
Hello, Cynthia, it's Nosa.
How are you?
Um... I've been trying
to reach Efosa and...
It's going to her voicemail and it's not
letting me leave a message.
So, can you call me back?
I want to pay her a visit or something
Anyway, call me back.
Please
Efosa, I'm not the villain, you know.
Why would you say that?
Why are you ignore me?
So you are ignoring me.
I didn't say that!
Then you're not ignoring me?
I didn't say that either.
It feels good to hear your voice. I mean,
more so, that you're talking to me live
Thank God for the privilege to, you know,
travel the world, see a lot
of beautiful things
There are times I just want to shop and just
ship it to you.. I mean, no strings attached
Certain times I buy female jewelry, and...
leave it in my closet
Yeah
Sometime, I get asked like,
hey why're you doing this?
I'm like, um... It keeps me in touch
with my feminine side
And sometimes I say, it's for the future
You're not saying anything
I'm listening
Right.
Do you want to see something?
Sure
Just brace yourself for
this though. Cause, um...
I know you're gonna be
surprised when you see this
Honestly and um... trust me,
I still remember this like it
was a few minutes ago
Yeah
What?!
Yeah... And I remember, on the day
we took this picture, I told my friend
I said, you see this girl?
I will marry her.
Yea... But hey, look, he still
teases me to this day
Me calls me a false prophet... Yeah
False prophet
It's not funny!
I'm sorry but that's funny
No, no, no, no. It's not funny
to be called a false prophet
And more so, it's your fault.
Well it's good to know that I can
still make you laugh though.
What're you two lovebirds chuckling over?
Cynthia!
What?!
Please! I'm just playing
DESMOND: Come on, Cynthia
Alright... I'm sorry
Um... Well, I am...
I probably just, um...
Efosa, I'll... Okay!
Bye
DESMOND: Bye
Oh my god. Oh my god. I just...
I just want to die right now.
What happened?
Oh no...
My goodness, I just want to vanish
Cynthia, will you calm down
and tell me what happened?
Efosa, I am... I'm so sorry
I'm... I... I'm... from the
bottom of my... I'm so sorry
Wait!
What is this got to do with me?
Oh...
I just... I just made the biggest
mistake and I am so...
It was the biggest boo-boo...
I swear it was a mistake
Would you just tell me what it is and
stop beating around the bush!
Okay... Okay... Okay.
So, I text you a picture earlier
or I thought I text you a picture
but...
Anyways, I was wondering
why you hadn't responded.
So I went back to check my phone to see
if it went through and, it did go through
but I...
I sent it to the wrong person.
What did you send? And to
whom did you send it?
I...
I... sent it to Nosa.
What did you send to Nosa?
Oh my God... Oh my God...
I am so, so, so sorry
It's a horrible mistake I promise.
I don't... I don't even know what to say
Cynthia!
Mistake?!
A mistake?! How could you be so careless?
What kind of mistake is that?
Our names are not even close!
I know. It's... It's the
way I saved your names
How did you save?
I saved him... as Efosa's M.
M?
Man.
I sent the text to Efosa's M,
instead of a Efosa.
Why didn't you just save his name as
Nosa?
Come on, you know I know a lot of Nosas
Where is my phone? I need to call...
No! No! No, wait! Wait, wait. Okay?
Don't be in such a rush.
It's my mistake.
I'll fix my mess, okay...
I'll handle it!
Give me my phone
No! Efosa, stop being so desperate!
I mean, come on, girl!
Has he even called yet?
What does that have to do with anything?
If it were you, you would have called.
Because you would have
been so damn concerned.
Listen, I'm trying to stay
out of your private affairs.
But I am so sick of seeing this man
take you for granted like this.
This is exactly what I'm talking about.
You're an enabler.
Good. You want to call him?
Call him!
And then you'll be back to square one
Back to your old mess.
So what am I supposed to do?
Just sit around and wait
Hell yeah!
Efosa, you are the woman
And a gem at that.
Okay?
He is the man. The man is
supposed to chase you
But, I bet you a man will not pursue a
woman that he did not see value in
And with your over-zealousness,
he'll never get the chance to
see how precious you are.
I mean, how many times has
he come by here to see you?
Chai! I can't believe it!
Efosa was my hero.
Ah ah...
Ha! She gave me hope in woman
This really hurts... Ha!
But why would she do something like this?
Wait, what do you mean, why
would she do something like this?
What did she do?
Wait a minute. Aren't you the one who
just showed me a picture on your phone,
saying, see what your Babe did?
So, why are you asking me what she did?
Isn't this something?
It's like, you're confused and you're
also trying to pass it on to me.
Bro
Can I hold something?
Ah ah...
Bros, why?
Where are you going?
Mr. Edwards.
Good morning Nosa,
have you been avoiding me?
No
May I come in?
Yeah, come in.
It's 4 a.m.
4?
Boss, Couldn't this wait?
What was that?
Sorry. I mean, can't this wait till later?
Well, for one, you have been avoiding me.
But more importantly,
I heard the most sound decisions
are made very early in the morning
between 5:00 and 6:00 a.m.
It's 4:00 a.m.!
Well, if we started talking now,
by the time it is 5:00 a.m.
You'll be ready to make a sound decision
Ain't you gonna offer me a seat?
Please have a seat.
That's more like it. Thank you
Do you want something to drink?
Water, juice, coffee...
Nyquil?
I see you're waking up.
Last time we spoke,
you were thanking me for advice
I didn't even know I gave
You were determined to go reconcile
with your wife and bring her home
You even got me so excited when you
shared your plan to
surprise her with a visit
come on...
What happened between then and now?
Look,
I've watched you two guys live
here for two years now
and it's been special
you have something beautiful
So beautiful and special that I'm willing
to put my reputation on the line
coming down here so early in the morning
Even though, I'm sleepwalking now and
will have no recollection of this whole
thing when I wake up later
so what's going on?
That's the man her father
wanted her to marry
I couldn't even meet her parents,
even though were madly in love
It wasn't anything personally
with them, I just...
I wasn't practical
And where we're from, love
submits to practical
I couldn't provide her with
the good things of life that she needed
without her depending on her parents
And then comes in, Prince Charming,
professing his undying love for her
But, she was a rebel
She would not give in to all the pressure
And it wasn't just coming from
her family or her friends
Everyone that knew
her had an opinion of me
But she was determined
She was going to my for
love and that was it
But...
I was poor
My father was poor
His father was poor
And so on.
I had no business falling in love with her
I take it, she's from a wealthy family
No. But...
She comes from a very well
respected and educated family
I see
I wanted it to work out for us so bad
I prayed and prayed and
God answered
If I didn't believe in God before then
I certainly did after
So what happened?
I got a visa lottery to America...
The land of opportunity
Suddenly everything just changed
I had potential
I mean, her parents still preferred
her to marry that other guy. But...
They knew she won't relent.
So, they yielded
So, where did you get the picture?
Her friend...
Cousin... sent it to me
And you think, with all you've told me,
she would just change her mind that
easily?
We've been married for four years.
She has seen all the cards in my hand
Not much of a deal.
Well, love, true love,
always hopes and believe for the best
in spite of the circumstances
Many people claim to marry for love
But, it's in marriage that they find out
what love truly requires of them.
And frankly,
That is the reason for
so many broken marriages
There's no love without sacrifice
No selfishness in love
That's more like lust
And once many find out what
love demands of them,
they want out.
One of the most attractive
attributes of love is humility
Many men count it as weakness,
But the fact,
Not a lot of us possess the strength of
character it requires to bend our knee
Especially, when we feel
justified in our stand
Hear me on this,
You have something very special,
very rare, very precious!
Preserve it. Fight for it!
Don't let pride rob you of it.
I know it's easy to expect her to come
running back into your arms
But sometimes
You have to remind her why she
should come running back
It's not easy.
It all seems to straight
and narrow at times
But, it's the way
Oh my goodness... Ah..
What time is it?
6:37
No, no, no...
The dry cleaner closes at 7:00. I have
to get that dress for tomorrow
Why don't you just go and
get it in the morning?
The event is until the evening.
They're closed on Sundays
Oh! Desmond, come on in... Come on in
Hi
Listen, I'll be right back
I have to go to the dry cleaners, okay...
I'll see you in a second
How are you doing Efosa?
I'm okay.
Ummm...
I got you a little something
What is it?
Well, there's only one way to find out
It's beautiful.
Why don't you try it on?
Desmond, you know I can't do that.
What's wrong is he broken?
Desmond I'm being serious!
Why?
Why do you want to complicate things?
I mean,
there're no strings attached.
I mean, I specifically made sure the...
The price tag was taken off. It's...
It's nothing... It's just a gift.
Where do you see this going?
Wherever love leads, Efosa
Look
I've never gotten over you.
I...
I don't, I don't think I can
My love for you will never die
Maybe it's...
Maybe it's just a crush
No!
It's more than that.
This is true love
Look,
I've been blessed with a lot
Whatever money can buy, I can afford it
But, all of these things don't matter
If they're not shared with
that special someone
Efosa,
no woman,
none has been...
None has been able to come close
to taking your place in my heart
I love you.
Efosa, is everything okay?
Nosa, it's not what it looks like!
♪ Wondering in the dark ♪
♪ Then, I see the Light ♪
Just come home
♪ I draw closer ♪
♪ Living in my head ♪
♪ Dancing on the Edge ♪
♪ You pulled me deeper ♪
♪ And I can't run away ♪
♪ Cause nothing separates ♪
♪ Me from Your love ♪
♪ In spite of who I am ♪
♪ You reach out Your hand ♪
♪ And my heart gives in ♪
♪ Sinking in my shame ♪
♪ You call out my name ♪
♪ You lift me higher ♪
♪ Buried in defeat ♪
♪ Your love rescued me ♪
♪ And held me tighter ♪
♪ And I can't run away ♪
♪ Cause nothing separates ♪
♪ Me from Your love ♪
♪ In spite of who I am ♪
♪ You reach out your hand ♪
♪ And my hearts gives in ♪
EFOSA: How much is he paying you?
What?
How much is Desmond paying you?
What are you talking... Paying me for what?
To wreck my home
First of all, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Secondly, I think you need to calm down
before you say something
that you're gonna regret
You're going a little too far
Oh really?
Yes!
That is what you make out of this?
It's rather obvious!
Oh please Efosa,
don't be ridiculous
Oh am I?
Yes! Very much!
I...
I can't believe that that would even
cross your mind... Obviously,
You don't know me as well
as you think you do
and certainly don't know Desmond at all.
Let me tell you something
about Desmond that you...
Either don't know
or refuse to understand.
Desmond is a great guy!
A great guy!
The most generous person I know, and
that's an understatement.
You stumbling over this?
Please!
That's just chicken change
for people like Desmond
At least, he chooses to help people
Forgive me for my naivete
But $8,000 seems a lot more
like a paycheck, than charity!
That is because your husband is poor!
It probably takes him two months
of hard work, plus overtime,
just to see something like this.
But...
This...
This is a dinner dress.
A birthday gift.
A wristwatch... to people like Desmond!
And he chooses to help people
I didn't know you were in need of charity
Of course...
and you will never know
because even if I needed money
I would never come running to you.
So that's what you think of me?
Every time I have confided in
you with my financial struggles,
you think I'm asking you for money?!
Nosa was right about you.
Thank God we didn't take your money!
Well, that still doesn't change
the fact that he is still broke,
and still putting you through
suffer-head in America
By the way, where did you
think that $5,000 came from?
Cynthia,
not everything in life is about money
There are more important things.
Things like love
Like your character
Like your soul.
Something you've clearly sold
to become a homewrecker in
exchange for his generosity
Wow...
That was low, Efosa.
That hurt.
The truth hurts
That's a nice one. One more...
Change position... More, more.
Move in closer... That's it! Yes! Yes!
That is good! That is good!
Ah, that's nice. That is so nice.
Wow... Wow...
Ah, more, more, more, wait.
One more, one more, one more!