[CHIME]
CHANTING CHILDREN: Don't you
laugh when the hearse goes by,
or you will be the next to die.
The worms crawl in.
The worms crawl out.
The worms play poker on your
snout.
The worms crawl in.
The worms crawl out.
Your eyes fall out.
Your teeth decay.
And that's the end of a
beautiful day.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MELISSA (VOICEOVER): Let me tell
you a story.
My name is Melissa O'Keefe.
When you meet me, you may find
this surprising.
You see, when I was an infant, I
was abandoned in the streets
of New York City.
I was lucky.
Someone found me.
Now I've got a name.
Some say missing persons is a
step down for a cop.
I don't see it that way.
I connect people with names,
names of people.
Some of these people are lucky.
When we find them, they're
alive.
Others aren't so lucky, but we
look for them anyway.
You see, names matter to me.
Unknown, unknown, unidentified,
unknown.
This is it?
This is all you have for me?
We just make the lists,
Sergeant.
All I got on these people is
what you see.
You don't say too much, you
know.
What material are you looking
for?
MELISSA: Material?
Sorry.
Dearly departed.
Three girls, 8 to 10.
They disappeared while skipping
rope.
The Double Dutch Killings,
February last year.
Your people found two of them.
I'm looking for the third.
MAN: Of course you are.
An orphan.
DA needs more evidence.
Well, she could always be on
Hart Island,
along with your skeezer hags,
your ODs,
your bag ladies, your shut-ins,
your homicides, your unknowns.
Unidentifieds always go through
missing
persons database before burial.
So what happened here?
Every once in a while one of
them wiggles through.
Thanks for nothing.
Happy digging.
They got chicks here.
What's wrong with you?
You on speed or something?
Have too much coffee today? -
What?
No. Nothing.
Regular fuckin' death rocker,
aye?
Yeah, that's right.
OK?
I got my own band and
everything, you know?
We got an album. - Oh, yeah?
- Yeah. - Whose basement?
[CHUCKLE]
Hey, you know, I got a name out
there, OK?
People know me.
I got six fucking months in this
dump.
Where the fuck are we, anyway?
You know?
I mean, what is this?
What is in here? - What, in
here?
- Yeah. - It's this.
Fuck!
Oh, hey, hey, hey, relax man,
OK?
Shit, man he's just on burial
duty, man.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not going to any cemetery.
Forget it.
What?
Figure with all this morbid shit
you've got on,
you'd feel right at home.
Yeah, screw you, OK?
I don't go in for this work off
my time shit, right?
I'm an artist, huh?
Artist my ass.
Let's go, boys.
Let's get ready to move.
Can we get a cheeseburger on
the way, Mike?
- Whatever you want. - Fries?
You're shit. Let's go,
double-time.
Move! - Milk shake.
[INAUDIBLE]
TV ANNOUNCER: In other news,
developer
Rupert King and the mayor--
Well, of course the problem
won't go away overnight.
TV ANNOUNCER: King has promised
to solve the city's problems
with the crowded core by
providing low-income housing
on deserted Hart Island.
All those old '60s do-gooder
models were flawed.
I mean, just handing away the
candy store because of what?
The guilt?
TV ANNOUNCER: Little known and
the Big Apple--
Rupert King's plan is more
aggressive.
Sorry.
One second.
Yeah?
Uh, hi Steven.
It's Matthews.
The other side left the table.
Yes, Steve.
Short the stock into the ground.
Orders from on high.
Yep.
[CHUCKLE]
Say uncle.
OK.
Sorry about that.
Where were we?
Well, it's a simple plan--
baseline dignity.
Give them hope, give them work,
get them off the streets.
Ah, it kills them to see them on
the streets.
Yes.
You know, and the other jerk
sitting in the corner
didn't know what the hell was
going on.
Where are we going?
Get to work, pinheads.
CHANTING CHILDREN: Don't you
laugh when the hearse goes by,
for you will be the next to die.
The worms crawl in.
The worms crawl out.
The worms play poker on your
snout.
The worms crawl in.
The worms crawl out.
Your eyes fall out.
Your teeth decay.
And that's the end of a
beautiful day.
Unit 3432, missing person base.
DISPATCHER (ON CB): Copy 3432.
What's your message?
This unit en route to Hart
Island on case 8928.
DISPATCHER (ON CB): Missing
person base acknowledged.
Yeah, one sec.
Hello?
Hi.
Yeah, hang on.
Honey number one.
Can he call you back?
Great.
Hello.
Oh, hi.
Yeah, yeah.
Just a sec.
Honey number two.
Hi, honey.
Yeah.
No, I'm busy right now.
It can't.
Look, I'll call you later, OK?
Yeah.
You, too.
Mm-hm.
Ciao.
We're all proud of you sir.
Project's getting a lot of
positive attention.
Right.
Let's hope it does some good.
RODGER: Markets say it's doing
wonders.
Fucking stench in here is going
to make me sick.
Get a breath of fresh air, man.
Use the opportunity to meet new
people.
What are you talking about?
They're dead people, huh?
I mean, I betcha there isn't
anybody in this whole town's
who's got a goddamn idea what we
got in the back here, huh?
Bring out your dead!
Shut the fuck up, man.
Show some respect.
What are you talking about,
respect?
We're a goddamn funeral
procession
in a fucking dump truck, man.
I'd like to go back to jail,
sir.
One more word out of you is
going to put you in the back.
Better enjoy it, man.
Going to spend most of the next
year inside.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
RODGER: He said he's going for
the plaque idea.
Your name on that island
forever.
RUPERT KING: Can you fathom
forever, Rodger?
RODGER: I'd like to think so,
sir.
RUPERT KING: I'm not talking
about forever
as in long-term investments.
I'm talking forever as in
eternity.
Special price today, man,
$0.50.
Here, matey. Make it last.
A Benjamin Franklin?
Thanks, man.
Hey, [INAUDIBLE] number.
RUPERT KING: Give a man a fish.
RODGER: Reminds me, sir, you
have the mayor's
fundraiser this evening.
RUPERT KING: What are we in for?
RODGER: 7.5.
It's just a damn island.
Who've we got?
Everyone.
The mayor's re-election tie-in
is irresistible,
not to mention the historic
value of your magnanimous
and generous act of--
All right, all right.
I get the point.
De-lint me.
Yes, sir.
Oh.
What have we here?
Oh, yes.
A man of vision.
Yes, sir.
Shame he's a Democrat.
Demublicans, Republicrats.
They're all pink on the inside,
Rodger.
Follow me.
[MUSIC - SHADES OF CULTURE,
"PAYIN RENT II"]
Hey, hey, watch this now.
Standing strong like foundation
making
moves in combination and yo the
one who stresses
I suppress like sedation.
It's the dread, knocking suckers
out like Sudafed.
Crush the opposition cause they
got me seeing red.
They getting me madder than Doc
Danner
when he's in his altered state.
At rapid rates I circulate to
make the fakes disintegrate.
Retaliate with forces from the
subterranean.
In hostile situations I'm aiming
at your cranium.
So heads up, you might get cut
when we erupt.
And when they ask, you can tell
them hard is how I struck.
The demolition team is
demolishing,
so caution is recommended when
you
up against the awesome
individual shining like jewels.
Better pay your rents and dues,
because we sharper than Shinobi
Ninja tools, severing nerve
endings
up inside this hip-hop body.
Do like we do for credit cards,
destroy the carbon copy.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Yo, I'm about to make this
evident.
I'm all up in this so you know I
paid my rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Listen, cut out your spine man
like psycho CAT scan.
Rap skills a man's hand, so
expend your best friends.
I see through you like stencils.
I'm sharpening pencils for all
the battles
that we wage on instruments.
With the vocal chords aided by
the larynx,
it's kind of muffled through the
mic
cause you fucking cuffed it.
Your rights have gotten rotten
before you got shot in,
the dance your fans have all
taken a switch dance.
Perfected an opposite reaction,
tractions needed to grip
and do the class on your mic
trip.
So pay your taxes to the
governor.
And if you didn't pay your dues
the crew's coming
through and roughing you.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Ah yeah.
Hey, there.
Arnie Charon.
I'm the pilot.
Captain said to expect you.
Sergeant O'Keefe.
ARNIE: Big doings today.
I, um, I'm afraid you're going
to have
to leave your vehicle shoreside
on account
of all this razzmatazz.
[SIGH]
Get this.
The Rup there has got this idea
to build some kind of town
on the island.
Between you and me, I think he's
looking
for a medal or something.
Guess it's something he hasn't
already got.
Well, time to get wet.
[HORN]
Yeah. Yeah.
Thank you.
It's about time, you know.
Hey, I know my rights.
I got the right to my dignity
and some decent working
conditions.
You got rights to shit.
Hey, hey!
- Hey, how you doing? - Yeah,
man.
[INAUDIBLE] What's going on,
man?
Had a court date. Well, what
happened?
Oh, man they denied my
complaint.
Fix was in.
Same old shit.
Neely, this is Robbie J.
Hey man.
Uh-huh.
TONY: And Neely likes to stab
holes
in his body to express himself.
NEELY: Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Ain't that like just stabbing
yourself over
and over again in the face?
No, man.
It's like my body is like a
piece of art.
[CHUCKLING]
They're going to make you take
all that all off
when you get to Rikers, though.
You know that, right?
[CHUCKLING]
Anyway.
Ah, shit.
Oh, here goes some art right
here.
Yeah, one of New York's finest.
I don't usually get the
undivided attentions,
so I'll catch up with you
[INAUDIBLE]..
[INAUDIBLE]
You don't get like sinus
problems with shit like that?
[CHURNING ENGINE]
Long Island Sound.
I'm a cop.
No shit.
You look familiar.
Sure.
I'm famous-- especially among
cops.
What's your name?
My name?
Don't matter.
Not anymore.
You and yours took care of that.
Matos.
You're good with names.
Yeah, well they matter to me.
You know, you're that con who's
been spouting all of that
bullshit about being set up.
Mine's not the only claim.
How do you know about it?
Well, maybe you've been yelling
the loudest.
[HORN]
[DOOR CLOSING]
Starting to feel seasick.
Feeling fucking windsick.
This fucking weather is stupid.
Fuck all of it.
Notice how everything around
here is like an island,
you know?
You know, we got Rikers, yeah.
Got Manhattan, huh?
You got Queens.
You got Brooklyn.
You got Staten Island, you know?
You got City Island.
And then we've got this fucking
island.
It's freaky man, you know.
I mean, it's like there ain't
nothing
connected to the mainland
anymore.
You know, it's like that
there's-- there's nothing--
nothing connected to nothing.
I'm going to blow, man.
RODGER: There it is, Mr. King.
Hart Island.
All that land going to waste.
Thank you, Rodger.
Hop in.
I'll give you a ride.
[DOOR SLAM]
Kind of beautiful, huh?
Kind of.
People lived here?
ERNIE: Oh, yeah.
People with yellow fever.
All kinds of contagious
diseases.
Then they put in a lunatic
asylum,
and it was drug addicts and
juvenile delinquents.
Anyone they didn't want around
they brought here.
Cons called it Empty Town.
Will you take a look at this,
Rodger, huh?
[CHUCKLING]
The future site of Hope City.
My grandmother's buried in one
of these pauper graves.
I'm sorry, sir.
Where?
Oh, somewhere back home.
I don't know, really.
Anyway, big change is coming
here, Mackloe--
big changes.
Great changes, sir.
[DOORS CLOSING]
Mm.
Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm!
Look at you.
The captain's importing us the
new and improved tight booty.
Thanks, but you're not my type.
Ooh.
[CHUCKLING]
See, if you move this over
here,
you can just about squeeze in
another 300 units.
I'm a little worried about the
soil reports on this side, sir.
Well, what do we have here?
Turned earth?
Don't worry about that.
[PATTING]
You know, the hardest thing for
a man to move?
Public opinion.
[CHUCKING]
That's a good one!
No.
Earth.
Plain old dirt.
We've got to dig into the soil,
rip it, tear it move it--
hundreds of thousands of tons of
it.
It's like a war, Rodger.
You're not squeamish, are you?
Not at all, sir.
Good.
Stake those points in Potter's
Field for samples.
Better get down to the ceremony.
Can't keep the man waiting.
How do I look?
You look fine, sir.
Yeah, well, give me a little
hug.
Yeah.
Oh, not too much.
Don't want to mess the suit.
That's for your eyes only.
I don't care if you have to eat
the hard drive.
That's only for you.
[APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
[INAUDIBLE] outside.
I'm here for the ID.
Sergeant O'Keefe?
Sorry.
Dwight Truman.
Captain.
Little bit of home.
Hope you're not offended.
Nah, beats the pictures I have
to look at all day.
At least these women are in one
piece.
So you'll be joining us at the
pit?
Yes.
I have the papers for the ID
right here.
OK.
[CHUCKLING]
RUPERT KING: That's always a--
yes.
MAYOR: That's a good one.
RUPERT KING: It is a good one.
[CHUCKLING]
Mr. Mayor.
Are you aware that Mr. King is
under investigation by
the European Health Commission?
That story is unfounded. I--
No, it's true.
My health has never been better.
[CHUCKLING]
So, Mr. King, could you tell us
your views
on the use of prison inmates in
certain countries
for AIDS research?
It's a nice day, dear friend.
I suggest you enjoy it.
Excuse me.
Asshole.
Put your stakes over here.
MELISSA: All those souls.
DWIGHT: Almost a million of
them.
Got a whole city out there.
This might be your girl.
Unknown buried in pit 40.
Date's about right.
I'll get a crew on it in a
couple hours.
Hours?
DWIGHT: Sorry, best I can do.
Make yourself comfortable.
I'll go check out the site.
Chew?
No, thanks.
Hey, Chief.
Missed the morning ride with
you.
Hey, Tony.
Wanted to trade some more fish
tales?
We'll do [INAUDIBLE] when I get
out.
Uh-huh.
Pulled one out last summer the
size of a car.
Oh, yeah?
Two-door, four-door, or
minivan?
[CHUCKLING]
Limo.
All right.
Get your gear and show Neely the
ropes.
That's to see if he's a good
guy.
And so I can think of only one
reason why
this great man would be out here
today, and that reason is hope.
Hope City is the humane solution
to many of our city's problems.
We'll get them off the streets,
clean
them up, put them to work.
Put to work doing what?
Listen, friend.
I'm just giving society's least
fortunate a chance
to make a contribution.
That's the best leg up they'll
ever get.
It is a gift of hope.
And Rupert King is making it
from his heart.
[SQUISHING]
[GRUNTING]
[TAPPING]
[BUZZ]
[GROAN]
Not many people know this about
me, Melanie,
but I myself come from a
hopeless background,
one of poverty and uncertainty.
But I got lucky.
I made a name for myself, and
made a little bit of money
along the way.
So now I think it's time to just
give a little back.
Any questions?
Yes, Mr. King.
Would you be willing to disclose
your stock holdings
in the pharmaceutical sector?
I'm going to bury that asshole.
Heads up.
We've got another customer
coming in.
So what are we doing here?
We're just putting him in here,
and that's it.
TONY: Yeah, real special, aye?
[THUMP]
Oh, man.
Oh, fuck.
OK, that's enough for me.
Oh, Neely, don't worry about
it.
Just grab the other side.
Ah, man.
Come on, guys, put it back
together.
Goddamn cheap coffins.
They do everything half-assed
these days.
TONY: Got it, chief.
We've got some little ones here.
[INAUDIBLE]
Sergeant, we're ready to head
over to your girl.
Tony, Davidson.
Pit 40.
What's that for?
Figure someone should say
something, no?
So on behalf of our needy, our
homeless,
and in thanks for your generous
efforts, Rupert,
I hereby give you the deed to
Hope City, New York.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
[SPADE STRIKING EARTH]
[SEETHING MAGGOTS]
[RUNNING WATER]
[MUSIC - SHADES OF CULTURE,
"PAYIN RENT II"]
Standing strong like foundation,
making moves in combination,
and yo the one who stresses I
suppress like sedation.
It's the dread, knocking suckers
out
like Sudafed, crush the
opposition
cause they got me seeing red.
They getting me madder than Doc
Banner
when he's in his altered state.
At rapid rates I circulate to
make the fakes disintegrate.
Retaliate with forces from the
subterranean
in hostile situations.
I'm aiming at your cranium.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in here so you know we
paid our rent.
Yo, I'm about to make this
evident.
I'm all up in this so you know I
paid my rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Listen, cut out your spine man,
like psycho CAT
scan, rap skills and man's
hands,
so expend your best friends.
I see through you like--
[DOOR OPENING]
--for all the battles that we
wage for instrumentals.
With the vocal chords aided by
larynx,
it's kind of muffled through the
mic
because you fucking cuffed it.
You're about to drop it, rock
it.
Before you got shot it the
dance,
your fans have all taken a
switch dance.
Perfected and opposite reaction
tractions needed to grip,
and do the class on your mic
clip.
So pay your taxes to the
governor.
And if you didn't pay you your
dues
the crew's coming through and
roughin' you.
Yeah, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in here so you know we
paid our rent.
Yeah, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in here so you know we
paid our rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in here so you know we
paid our rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in here so you know we
paid our rent.
Tony.
Search here.
[SPADES BREAKING GROUND]
Well, looks like we found your
girl.
I'm sure the parents will
appreciate the closure.
Best we know, she doesn't have
any parents.
Well, glad to give her a name.
Listen.
You take your time.
I'll go finalize the paperwork.
[SKIPPING]
[COUGHING]
You didn't have to ID that
body.
Regulations.
For regulations you could have
done it from the comfort
of your squad room.
You didn't.
Why?
Why do you say a prayer for an
unknown body?
Somewhere, somebody knows him.
What's your charge?
My charge, assault and
resisting arrest.
Cops on the 39th beat me up for
no reason.
Put me in a hospital for two
weeks.
Left me a souvenir.
Nice, huh?
I was in 39.
Oh, yeah.
What'd you hear?
Nothing.
Yeah.
I'll see you at the ferry.
[GRUNT]
OK.
Hey, look, I played your Casino
in Atlantic City.
Really?
NEELY: Yeah.
You know, I had-- had me some
jacks.
So I went down there.
I played the slots, mostly. You
know, I had--
got one of them buses from Times
Square--
So you had a good time?
NEELY: Yeah.
Yeah.
Hey listen.
You really as rich as they say?
I mean, you got--
you got like a billion?
- People exaggerate. - Yeah?
Oh, well, OK.
So how much you got, then?
I mean, you have more than $10
million.
What do you think?
Yeah, Neely, what do you think?
He's fucking Rupert King.
What do you think?
$100 million.
Bucket's small.
Like fucking [INAUDIBLE],,
Neely.
Just leave it alone, man.
OK, OK.
$300 million. Huh?
You're miles off me.
Miles off.
NEELY: OK, by how much?
I've no idea.
He doesn't even fucking know,
Neely.
That's how much money he got.
He don't even know how much
money he got.
Fuck!
[CHUCKLING]
So you two guys have got a ways
to go, don't you?
[DRAGGING CHAIR]
[CHUCKLING]
No, you better believe it.
Yeah.
Well, it's tremendously
fulfilling.
Of course. Yeah.
Hang on.
Left the cell in the limo.
Do you mind?
Yeah?
What?
No, I'll ask him when he gets
back.
Yeah.
He's in the field somewhere.
All right.
I'll see you tonight. Mm-hm.
Good night.
Where the hell is Mackloe?
He's not on any of the roads.
Well, what do you think we
ought to do?
The mayor and all these folks
need to get back.
Well, you take care of these
people.
I'll stay here and look for him.
OK, it's getting late.
I'm going to need some people.
I'll stay, Captain.
Pretty soon for a missing
persons cop
going home on this one.
[CHUCKLING]
Thanks, Sergeant.
I'm going to need some more.
I'm with you, Captain.
Tony, good.
It's the prisoners manifest.
Get them on the-- on the Rikers
bus.
Arnie.
Get these people on their way.
Come back for us at sunset.
Sure thing, Dwight.
Three more.
All right.
Let's get a move on.
We can take care of this, sir.
He's my man.
I'm staying.
I'd advise you to think of your
own safety.
This island--
This island belongs to me.
Where do we start?
OK, Neely.
Robbie J. Get in the truck.
Whoa, hey.
You can't volunteer me.
No.
I want to go back to jail.
We in jail.
This one place.
[INAUDIBLE]
I'm going to call in.
[CLICKING]
It's dead.
[UNLATCHING DOOR]
[SEETHING MAGGOTS]
[APPROACHING TRUCK]
Started out as a prisoner of
war camp during the Civil War.
Nothing ever survives here.
Nonsense.
They just got it all wrong.
Plenty of room for improvement
here.
Just need some people.
Ah, details.
Tony.
You, Neely, Robbie J, you spread
out across the fields.
I'll take this building.
Sergeant, take Mr. King and
divvy up the hospital.
Everybody meet back here in an
hour.
Look, Sergeant.
Don't you think we could go just
a little bit faster?
I'll take this field over here.
Sorry, Mr. King, you're staying
with me,
for your own safety.
CHANTING CHILDREN: Don't you
laugh when the hearse goes by,
for you will be the next to die.
The worms crawl in, the worms
crawl out.
The worms play poker on your
snout.
RUPERT KING: Mackloe!
[BREAKING WEEDS]
Dammit, Mackloe!
I'm docking you the coat!
Mackloe!
Whoa!
What the fuck is that?
It's a grave, man.
Why don't you watch where you're
going?
Oh, man, don't tell me that.
Don't tell me that.
I can't stand stepping on
graves.
Well you stepping on them
everywhere you go.
It's a graveyard. - Ah, jeez.
Don't say that.
It's fucking gross, man.
It's true.
What happened to Tony?
Hey, man, dig it.
Speaking of gross, I've been
meaning to ask you this, man.
What do you do when you get a
booger?
What?
With the nose rings.
What do you do when you get the
boogers?
What are you talking about,
man?
I take out the ring, and I pick
them out,
just like anybody else does.
What about when they get cold?
You probably get fucked--
you get fucked up headaches and
shit.
Like that with that?
Tony!
Why are you hollering, yo?
Why-- just why don't you just
calm the fuck down?
NEELY: Tony!
Where the fuck you at, dude?
Why you hollering and yelling
and shit?
He's on a fucking island. Why
don't you just chill out?
You see him around?
RUPERT KING: Mackloe!
What do you say we go hang with
the Rup?
Oh, the Rup, huh?
He's your fucking homeboy now.
You got nicknames for him. Yeah,
come on.
Let's go hang with the Rup.
You could trade some more stock
tips with him, man.
He could break you off a piece
of the island and shit.
You could build a hotel.
[CLANK]
Matos.
Why don't take a corridor?
Kiss my ass.
You watch yourself.
What?
Oh, hey, you're a cop?
I owe you respect?
I don't have time for your
bullshit.
You want bullshit.
You were in the 39th.
That either makes you ignorant
or a liar.
You are a convicted criminal.
Yeah, sure, I got a JV file a
mile long.
But I've been clean for years.
And then one day I'm walking
down the wrong side of street,
and I get busted, and it's back
to square fucking one!
This is not the time.
No? When? huh?
They denied my complaint.
Huh?
They had me in handcuffs for the
fucking line-up.
Take it up with the judge.
You know, I'm surprised that
you're still sticking up
for your buddy cops after they
busted your ass down
to missing persons.
Mackloe!
- [SHOUTS] - Jeez!
Fuck!
[LAUGHING]
All right.
That's good shit, man.
Your fucking face was like--
Great fucking joke, mate.
Listen.
I gotta find my guy, so split up
again
and quit yanking my chain, OK?
No.
I ain't going nowhere.
Stay put, and I'll let you
know.
Oh, Rup, I always wanted to ask
you about those Miss
Galaxy contests of yours.
Did you ever-- well, I mean, you
never with the girls there?
Wouldn't you?
Hey, Mr. King.
Mr. King.
Mr. King!
Look!
Back off, mate.
Oh!
Ah!
All right. Right.
Give it back.
Oh, that's top-of-the-line shit
there, Mr. King.
Yeah, yeah, whoa, and it's
mine.
Quit fucking around.
That has sentimental value.
Well, yeah I'm sure it does,
yeah.
Because, well, I just saved your
life.
So this must be a very special
moment for you.
Look, friend.
Cut the crap.
Give it here.
You give me a job in your
casino when I get out.
Huh?
[LAUGHING]
You've got be kidding!
Come on.
Give it here.
That's enough fucking around.
Asshole!
Give that back!
It's mine!
I stole that!
Fucker!
Come here!
Oh, you mad, now?
You mad, now?
You mad, now? You mad?
- Son of a bitch. - Oh, really.
- Come here! - Really?
Don't trip on the fucking
things.
You know what?
Keep it!
Better yet, I'll send you a case
of them.
In your nose.
You were going to wear this in
your nose?
Give me that!
You can't wear this in your
nose.
Son of a bitch!
You can't wear this in your
nose.
What are you going to do? Wear
it in your dick?
What the fuck do you want?
So, so what?
So you can wear it in your nose?
[INAUDIBLE] stick it in your
ass!
Hold on hold on hold on.
Here.
Get the fuck out of here.
Whoa!
Oh, shit!
[SEETHING MAGGOTS]
Ugh.
Bodies don't decompose this
fast.
This doesn't make any sense.
I've gotta call this into
homicide.
Captain, your men.
Hey, these are all short
timers.
They're not murderers.
[SEETHING MAGGOTS]
[GRUNT]
You filthy little punk!
What the fuck is wrong with
you, you crazy bastard?
All right, let's get the hell
out of--
[BUZZING]
Oh fuck.
Get me the fuck out of here.
Tony!
[INAUDIBLE] you stay here till
I get--
[BUZZING]
Captain.
OK. Everybody in the car.
Now. Sergeant, Tony.
[INAUDIBLE]
Everybody in the truck!
[BUZZING]
Come on.
What the hell are you waiting
for?
What was that?
Hold on. Where is--
Where's Neely? [THUMP]
Go!
[REVVING ENGINE]
Fuck!
[BUZZ]
[GRUNTING]
Fuck!
[BUZZ]
[THUMP]
[GASPING]
Do we have mobile?
A walkie talkie?
Anything? - No.
It's only good for the island.
[DOOR CLOSING]
You said this was going to be
an easy duty, man.
And it's been a fucking
nightmare.
It'll be all right.
I'm going to look for Robbie J.
I don't think that's a good
idea.
The boys are my responsibility.
The ferry should have been here
by now.
Boss?
I don't feel so hot.
I gotta get to Rikers.
(DRUNKENLY) Eh, "Lancelot
Link,"
"The Hathaways," and "Mr.
Smith."
Lancelot Link--
"The Hathaways" and "Mr.
Smith."
Oh, I got it.
OK.
Sitcoms with a mother-in-law.
[LAUGHING]
Mother-in-laws?
[BUZZER SOUND]
Wrong!
Sitcoms with monkeys.
Monkeys?
Monkeys.
That's close enough.
[DRUNKEN LAUGHTER]
You don't watch too much
television, do you?
You haven't seen my
mother-in-law.
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, shit.
The sun ran out on me.
Yeah, we-- we better get moving.
[DOOR CLOSING]
Fuck, I feel putrid, man.
It's like I get a fever.
I feel like I'm burning up.
Somebody should find out what
that guy has got.
Mr. King, I'm sorry.
I am so sorry that I took your
watch.
I really didn't mean it, sir.
All right.
Just get a grip.
So Robbie J's got it, and I'm
sure that he's
fine with giving it back.
I'm sure that it wouldn't be a
problem.
Hey can you turn them on?
[SEETHING MAGGOTS]
[HEAVY BREATHS]
[RAPIDLY RECEDING FOOTSTEPS]
[DOOR OPENING]
OK.
Somebody tell me how a body can
decompose in two hours.
I mean, he was just a kid.
Bobbie J.
[CLATTER]
OK, Captain.
I demand you get me off this
island now.
I don't know.
I don't know what to.
The ferry's gotta come.
We'll wait for the ferry.
[FERRY ENGINE]
[INAUDIBLE] Boomer.
Lewtinsky.
Nah, it's too easy.
[SOUNDING HORN]
[FERRY ENGINE]
[BUZZ]
Hey!
[WHISTLING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[HORN]
Listen, friends. Do me a favor.
Don't talk to the press about
this.
It could be very bad for Hope
City.
Fucking Hope City.
[BUZZING]
[SEETHING MAGGOTS]
[ALARMED GROANS]
[HORN]
Hey!
[LOUD BUZZING]
[ENGINE WINDING DOWN]
[GROWING ROAR OF BUZZING]
Back to the truck.
Now. Now!
Back to the truck!
Great.
A fucking rowboat.
Hey, oh, Christ!
Come on, I got him.
Jesus.
OK!
[THUMP]
[LOUD BUZZING]
Jesus.
[REVVING ENGINE]
Oh, god, I don't think I'm
going to make it.
Oh, he's burning up.
Oh, god!
Jesus.
Hey, stop it, will you?
What the hell's the matter with
you?
Neely!
For fuck's sake.
[SHOUTING]
Go, go!
Start up!
Neely!
Who knows what we're going over
now.
TONY: Neely!
Neely!
Get back to the truck.
Save me!
[THUD]
[BUZZ]
[SMACK]
[DOORS SLAMMING]
My god, they're in here.
Get off your ass.
[BUZZING]
[SMACK]
[BUZZ]
I hear a buzzing.
MELISSA: Here it is.
[SMACK]
[BUZZING]
[CLATTERING]
[SMACK]
Hm.
Bravo.
This is personal.
They're after us.
I don't think it's personal.
They're just out there.
No, no.
They're hunting us.
(LAUGHING) Oh, yeah.
There's always been sadness in
those fields.
Mystical bullshit.
Look, tomorrow morning I'll have
this place doused in malathion.
Problem solved.
[STUMBLING]
Sorry.
I'm just feeling a bit dizzy.
I got bit out there.
Just hang in there, OK?
Jesus.
[INAUDIBLE] the fishermen do
when you get out of here, huh?
You do realize that he's
carrying an infectious disease?
What the fuck do you know?
Are you a doctor now?
Come on, look at the facts!
The first one to go down was his
jailbird friend.
Shut up.
There's nothing you can do for
him.
Look.
I don't want to sound cruel, but
I say we put him out.
Anybody leaves, it's you.
Steady, matey.
[THUMP]
[LOUD BUZZING]
[STEADY THUMPS]
OK.
They're hunting us.
But why?
I don't know.
[KEYBOARD CLICKS]
Look at this.
[RATTLING ON KEYBOARD]
Containment?
Custody center?
The poor never been so safe.
Could be Rikers, except for the
lawn ornaments.
MELISSA: Human test subjects?
[SLAM]
What the fuck are you doing?
That's private.
Homeless and stupid.
Not going to go for it.
You'd be amazed at what the
desperate will do for money.
So we get them off the streets.
Well, that's what I promised.
For good.
Come on, now.
You exaggerate.
Anyway, tell me honestly,
Sergeant,
would you really miss them?
You son-of-a-bitch.
[STUMBLING]
I've got it.
I've got the fever.
I'm next.
Do you know why-- do you know
why they call
these places Potter's Field?
There was this place in
Jerusalem.
And nothing grew.
Potters dug their clay there.
Judas betrayed Jesus for 30
pieces of silver.
After Jesus was crucified, they
took that blood money,
and they bought Potter's Field
so that strangers and the poor
could be buried.
Tony?
[GASPING]
I'm going to end up buried--
buried here.
Let's get him out of here.
One more word out of you know,
and I'll shoot you.
[CLATTER]
[GASPING]
[GURGLING]
[LIQUIDY SOUNDS]
Maybe somebody will listen to
me next time.
Come on, Tony.
In the office.
Come on.
[SEETHING MAGGOTS]
[ROAR OF BUZZING]
It's strange.
It's like they're waiting for
something.
They're not moving.
I think we can make a break for
it.
RUPERT KING: Oh, like I say, we
torch the vermin
and obliterate them.
TONY: We've got to bury the
chief.
As soon as this is all over.
Now.
What?
Bury him now.
Potter's Field.
Great.
I'll take care of the flower
arrangements.
Tony, don't do this.
She's the only cop around here
that ever cared.
Give me your coat.
Give me your fucking coat.
[DOOR CLOSING]
It's a terrible shame.
Shut up.
He's a goner.
Shut the fuck up.
Of course, if you ask me, it's
now or never.
So why don't you and I make a
run for it?
Feel free to try.
I might just do that.
[CHUCKLING]
Now look, we have to get our
stories straight, first.
The story is simple.
Nature just kicked her ass.
Oh, kicked our ass.
Right.
Yeah, not exactly the tag line I
had in mind for Hope City.
"Nature just kicked our ass."
Do you ever give up?
Never.
Do you?
Listen.
Here's the proposal.
You help me keep the lid on
things here,
and I'm going to bring you into
Hope City.
I'm not interested.
Eh.
It's going to be more money than
you've ever dreamed.
What the fuck do you know about
my dreams?
All right.
I bring in the jailbird, too--
if he gets back.
With his record, that's the best
offer he's going to get.
No deal.
[DOOR CLOSING]
[GROANING]
Doesn't anyone believe in
teamwork anymore?
[SPADE BREAKING GROUND]
[GROANING]
[CLICKING OF LIGHTER]
[GURGLING]
Sweet dreams you little bastard.
Cry not for him, for he is with
the ether.
No longer does he cast a shadow
upon the earth as we do.
Let's try the boat by the
shore.
OK. Let's get King.
[CRAZY LAUGHTER]
You sons of bitches!
[LAUGHING]
[EXPLOSION]
[ROAR OF BUZZING]
OK.
Into the truck.
Yay, ha-ha, I've got the
bastards!
Go on!
Get in!
[DOORS SLAMMING]
Ah, well, reunited at last.
[ENGINE TURNING OVER]
Go to hell, King.
Make no mistake, friend, we're
there as we speak.
[ENGINE TURNING OVER]
Shit!
Damn thing won't start.
Where are they?
[CHUCKLING]
It's a route.
Quiet.
[INAUDIBLE] They're just sitting
out there.
I'm getting out of here.
Head for the shore.
Come on!
Drop the gun now!
Wait a minute, Sergeant.
Otherwise, your jailbird friend
here gets the chop.
Don't be crazy, King.
We've got to get out of here.
Oh, no.
Nobody leaves this island till
we've sat down
and thrashed out a deal.
TONY: What's wrong with you?
Why don't you forget about this
place?
Listen, friend.
You know, I don't even know your
name.
But anyway, it doesn't matter.
Do you know what makes a great
man?
Hey, hey!
Stop it!
Don't, Sergeant.
Don't do it.
Let me tell you what makes a
great man--
determination, guts, commitment,
work, destiny.
Oh, and luck.
Yeah.
Plain old luck.
A great man has to have luck.
A great man doesn't have six
deals in a row go sour on him.
Hope City's my last card.
I can't let it go.
Please.
Help me breathe life into Hope
City.
I can't.
I'm really truly sorry to hear
that, Sergeant.
[COCKING GUN]
King, don't!
[ROAR OF BUZZING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[SCREAM]
Be careful, Tony.
[GASPING]
[WALKING WITH HEAVY TREAD]
[CRACKLE]
[GASP]
[THUD]
[SEETHING MAGGOTS]
[BUZZING]
[GASPING] - Come on, Tony.
[GRUNTING AND GASPING]
[ROAR OF BUZZING]
[BUZZING RECEDING]
They wanted King.
They got him.
Come on, let's get to that boat.
[TRAFFIC]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Thanks for reopening my case.
You bet.
Come on.
Let's get you out of here.
I was found in the streets of
New York City.
I was lucky.
Others aren't so lucky, but I
look for them anyway.
You see, names matter to me.
[MUSIC - SHADES OF CULTURE,
"PAYIN RENT II"]
Entering your station, the
lyrical devastation.
Whack MC annihilation and
termination.
Hey, hey.
Watch this now.
Standing strong like foundation,
making moves in combination.
And yo the one who stresses I
suppresses like sedation.
It's the dread, knocking suckers
out like Sudafed.
Crush the opposition cause they
got me seeing red.
They getting me madder than Doc
Banner
when he's in his altered state.
At rapid rates I circulate to
make the fakes disintegrate.
Retaliate with reports from the
subterranean.
In hostile situations I'm aiming
at your cranium.
So heads up, you might get cut
when we erupt.
And when they ask, you can tell
them hard was how I struck.
The demolition team is
demolishing,
so caution is recommended when
you up against the awesome.
Individual shining like jewels.
Better pay your rent and dues,
cause we sharper
than Shinobi Ninja tools.
Severing nerve endings up inside
this hip-hop body.
Do like we do for credit cards,
destroy the carbon copy.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this, so you know
we paid our rent.
Yo, I'm about to make this
evident.
I'm all up in this so you know I
paid my rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this, so you know
we paid our rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Why.
You try and find the right lie,
but you're wasting everybody's
time while you're posing.
I'm cool and slow with plenty of
precision.
Immaculate dark vocal box.
I live on the perimeter on the
South Shore, Mount Rushmore.
I'm mad like Zulu language, but
you understand me perfectly.
It's Kandu, supreme fucking
Khan.
I'm all eight grades, my
following-- each one,
teach one.
My name is on their brain and my
name reigns.
Ring the alarm, another fucking
sound done dead.
Romance and finance, the legend.
You go on the job, run the
fucking errands, playa-haters,
snake fakes and devils tonight.
You will be no more.
Yesterday it was the eve of
destruction.
Who next in line for the
crushin'?
Yo, we about to make shit
evident.
We all up in this and you know
we paid our rent.
Yo, we're about to make it
evident.
We all up in this, and you know
we paid our rent.
Yo, we're about to make it
evident.
We all up in this and you know
we paid our rent.
Yo, Scales Empire and Shades of
Culture, you know,
it don't pay the rent.
A shaved head like Telly Savalas
on your tele-vision,
and everything nice I rhyme
proficient.
Check this style, I compile
herbs and verbs with no words
from competition.
Sit back and listen.
Cut out your spine man like
psycho CAT scan.
Rap skills a man's hands, so
expend your best friends.
I see through you like stencils.
I'm sharpening pencils for all
the battles
that we wage upon instrumentals.
With the vocal chords aided by
the larynx,
it's kind of muffled to the mic
cause you fucking cuffed it.
Your rhymes have gotten rotten.
Before you got shot in the
dance,
your fans have all taken a
switch dance.
Perfected an opposite reaction,
traction's
needed to grip, and to the class
on your mic clip.
So pay your taxes to the
governor.
And if you didn't pay your dues
the crew's coming
through and roughing you.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Yo, we about to make this
evident.
We all up in this so you know we
paid our rent.
Yo.
We about to make this evident.
We all up in here so you know we
paid our rent.
Ah yeah.