Sam Snow.
Kit Casey.
The Creature Cases!
The Riddle of the Raging Rhinos.
Hey.
Rita! Rick! Thanks for coming out.
Hey, Reggie.
Love it when we all get together
like this, Reggie.
No fightin', no feudin',
everybody's relaxed, and--
-What's gotten into you?
What a long day.
By long, you must mean amazing.
We cracked the Case of the Cunning Cougar!
We solved
the Secret of the Slimy Salamander.
And I just beat
my all-time high score! Top that!
I'm ready to get a good night's sleep.
-Bedtime will have to wait.
The CLADE crest! The Director's got
a new Creature Case for us!
Director Scratch?
Oh. Hi, agents.
Just brushing my teeth before bed.
-Chickens don't have teeth--
Agents, there's a major mystery
at the Watering Hole Club.
The Mice Squad took this footage earlier.
Whoa. Those rhinos are going wild.
We call it "Rhino Rage."
Your mission
is to figure out what's causing it
before anyone gets hurt.
Looks serious.
We'll investigate!
Good luck, agents.
CLADE is counting on you.
-Well, better turn around.
R.O.N., set course for the Watering Hole.
Now arriving at destination biome,
-African Grasslands.
-Thanks, R.O.N.
Hm. Local wildlife includes zebras,
warthogs, leopards…
Don't see any raging rhinos though.
They must all be inside the club.
We'd better go--
Oh! Uh…
Oops.
A genet!
I'm real sorry.
I was just chasing after that bug.
Genets eat just about anything,
but they love to eat bugs.
Good bugs out tonight?
-They're okay.
I guess.
All the best bugs
are inside the Watering Hole,
but they're only letting
rhinos in tonight.
Oh!
See ya!
Only rhinos?
We'll see about that.
Evening, sir. We're here to--
Sorry, pal.
Private party tonight.
We already had enough trouble.
-But--
-Rhinos only.
Step aside, Sam.
Huh?
You two ain't rhinos,
but you seem all right.
Have a nice time.
Kit, how did you--
Rubbing noses is how rhinos say hello.
Kinda like a secret rhino handshake.
Come on!
Let's see what the trouble's about!
Hm…
Hiya.
Only one entrance, heavily guarded.
Clu-Bots, take a look around.
Ew! So many bugs.
Forget the bugs. Look at all the rhinos.
Don't often see them
all together like this.
They usually hang out alone.
That's why these rhino nights
are so special.
Name's Reggie.
I organized all this.
And trust me,
we were all having a real nice time,
but then folks just started freaking out.
Rest assured, CLADE is on the case.
Agent Sam Snow.
And Kit Casey.
Animal Detectives.
Oh! Get it off!
-Get it off!
-Oh!
Help!
Rhino Rage!
Keep out of her way!
Whoa…
Sam! Over here!
Oh!
Phew!
Clu-Bots, show me
what's going on out there.
It's a 9.7 on the Rhino-Rage meter!
9.7? I've never seen it that high.
Something made her really mad.
The Rhino-Rage meter is dropping.
It's safe again.
Huh?
Oh, phew!
Is it gone?
Is what gone?
I don't know what it was,
but it jumped onto my back outta nowhere.
I was attacked, I tell ya.
Attacked? Maybe that's why
the Rhinos are acting so strange.
But who would attack a full-grown rhino?
Beats me.
And it's only us rhinos here tonight.
Except for you two.
Hm…
Uh, not exactly.
There's also a bunch of bugs in here, and…
An oxpecker bird!
Him?
Aw, that's just Paulie. He keeps me clean.
Yeah. Don't bring me into this.
I didn't start any trouble.
Easy, Paulie.
We just wanna know if you saw anything.
I didn't see nothin'.
It all happened too fast.
And I was distracted by all these bugs.
Come on, Paulie.
I'm thirsty.
Wait!
Check it out.
-Four muddy paw prints!
-Huh?
Whoever jumped
on Rita's back left them behind.
Ha!
Told you it wasn't me.
See? One, two.
Two feet,
no mud.
He's right.
Whoever's causing
all the Rhino Rage has four muddy feet.
-Hm…
Here we go again!
Reggie! Not you too!
Oops.
Whoa!
Whew…
Sorry. My bad.
Everybody okay?
Could be better!
Hm.
Ah-ha!
Kit, how does it feel to be
in the presence of a master detective?
Why? You see one around?
I mean me.
I've noticed another clue.
Look at where we're standing.
Under a tree?
Exactly! All the Rhino Rages
started under trees!
Show her, Clu-Bots.
Well, ain't that something.
So there's a four-pawed critter
on the loose,
jumping out of trees
and scaring the rhinos.
I think I saw it runnin' away.
You did? What'd it look like, Reggie?
Well, it was small, almost like a cat,
with a pointy face and dark spots.
Uh, like this?
Yeah! That's it, but without the go-kart.
Eh, I just like drawing go-karts.
Hm…
A spotted cat creature.
Sounds like a leopard to me.
A leopard?
You better be pulling my horn.
Leopard?!
There's a leopard on the loose?
Not so fast, Sam.
This was no leopard. Look.
The spots don't match, see?
We can't risk it.
If there's even a chance
a leopard is attacking folks,
I gotta shut down the Watering Hole.
Aw…
Hold up, Reggie.
You might be able to keep the party going.
-If we can just figure out…
The bugs!
Whiskers, that's it!
What's it?
Kit, I know who's jumping on the rhinos!
And I know how to catch her too.
Sam, this decoy look pretty real.
There's even bugs buzzing around it.
Just like a real rhino.
But what's the plan here?
Isn't it obvious? We're setting a trap!
Someone with four muddy paws is jumping
out of trees and onto the rhinos
to eat the bugs.
Of course! It must have been--
-The genet we met earlier!
-Uh-oh.
There she goes!
Quick! She's getting away!
Oh no, she's not!
Goin' somewhere?
Hi.
This is who's been sneaking
in here and scaring everybody?
Sure is.
This little genet has four muddy paws,
jumps out of trees,
and she loves to eat bugs.
Oops.
I didn't mean to cause trouble.
There's just so many tasty bugs in here.
And I can reach 'em better
when I jump on your backs.
Sorry. Rhinos only tonight.
You gotta scram.
Oh…
I do?
-Maybe not.
-Hm?
I've got an idea.
Glad things
are back to normal.
And hey, those bugs are gone too.
Yeah. All thanks
to our new official bug-eater.
Do you mind if I hop up?
-Sure thing, doll.
She's gonna go far
in this business.
Great idea, guys.
Don't mention it, Reg.
Just glad to have
another Creature Case closed.
Sam?
Look who's sleepy now.
Hey! That's my job!
Mice Squad Fact File.
Status?
System Settings?
Update. Rhinos.
Rhinos don't really throw parties
in nightclubs.
But sometimes they get together
at watering holes at night.
Rhinos sometimes
rub their snouts together.
It's like a friendly rhino hello.
Animals called genets are known
to hop on rhinos' backs to eat bugs.
Giving the rhinos
a big surprise.
Error. Upload incomplete.
How to fix it?
Move your feet.
The Trouble in the Tundra.
Do you have a mind for animal mysteries?
If so, consider a career with CLADE,
the Covert League
of Animal Detective Experts.
At CLADE,
you'll test your sleuthing skills
in our high-tech training facilities…
…crack cases with the Stinkwell Brothers'
advanced technology,
and you'll work alongside
our ace surveillance team, the Mice Squad.
This is the part! Turn it up!
You were right!
This new Mice Squad song is amazing!
Yeah! I can't get enough of it.
Hey, where are those guys?
Yeah, good question.
We haven't heard
from Bill and Jill in a while.
-Uh, is this part of the video?
Don't think so.
Director Scratch wants to see us.
Hey, Director. Got a new case for us?
I'm afraid not, agents,
and that's the problem.
-Huh?
-I'm not sure I understand,
Director Scratch.
Agents, we've got a mystery
that involves two of our own.
-The Mice Squad are missing.
Bill and Jill!
They were working in the Arctic
when we received this distress call.
Come get us. I repeat, come get us.
Whoa. That didn't sound too good.
No, it doesn't.
That's why I need you to head
to the Arctic and find them fast.
You can count on us, Director.
Now arriving
at destination biome…
…Arctic Tundra.
All right, this is it.
The Mice Squad's last known location.
Kit, would you stop humming
and help me look for them?
I'm only humming to keep warm.
Not all of us
like the cold as much as you.
Including the Mice Squad.
Which is why we better find them fast.
Can't argue with that. Come on!
No sign of them. Or their van.
No sign of much of anything.
What was that?
Over there! A herd of musk oxen!
Maybe they've seen
Bill and Jill. Let's go!
Go, go, go!
-Woo!
-Aa!
What are they doing?
-Don't worry about it, Sam.
Butting heads is what musk oxen do.
Hello, there!
I don't suppose you've seen--
-A wolf!
Protect the children!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy, folks.
I'm not a wolf. I'm a snow leopard.
And I'm a fox.
Well, that isn't much better.
Who are you, and what do you want?
We were just wondering
if you had seen our friends?
No, we haven't.
Unless your friends are wolves…
Wolves?
…then we haven't seen anyone here.
Are you sure?
Maybe you've heard them
playing their music or seen their van?
She said we haven't seen 'em.
We musk oxen keep to our herd,
and we don't mess with outsiders.
We don't have time for anybody else.
If we get
even the slightest bit distracted,
it could put our calves in danger.
But maybe--
You'd better move along,
before we move you along.
Talk about a cold shoulder.
Well, if we can't get any information
out of the musk oxen,
maybe we should track down
the wolves they mentioned.
Good idea, Kit.
Scanning for wolf prints.
Ah-ha! There.
The wolves are heading that way.
I see 'em.
Whoa! They're moving pretty fast.
We've gotta catch up with them. But how?
The Stinkwells!
-Hello, Kit.
-Hello, Sam.
Hey, Stinkwells.
We are so worried about Bill und Jill.
Have you found them yet?
Not yet. But we're tracking some wolves
who might have some clues.
And we need to go fast!
We had a feeling this might happen.
That's why we packed
some special vehicles for you in R.O.N.
We'll send them to you now.
Sorry. He does that when he's worried.
Ah, there they are.
Snow Cycles!
They're beautiful! Thanks, Stinkwells!
You're welcome. Good luck.
Oh…
Woo-hoo!
Come on! Let's catch up with those wolves!
Sam, look out for that ice.
-Oh?
Whoa! Oh!
Whoa! Come on! Come on!
-Whoa!
-Woo-hoo!
Whoa!
-Phew! Huh?
Look! We've almost caught up with them!
Hey, wolves! We need to talk to you!
They can't hear us.
We gotta get closer.
Hey. Where did they go?
Uh-oh.
Why are you following us?
Easy, now.
We're just looking for our friends.
Uh, I don't suppose
you've seen the Mice Squad?
-The Mice Squad?!
The Mice Squad are here?
Oh. You've heard of them.
Heard of 'em?
We're, like, their biggest fans!
Yeah!
I still can't get over
how amazing their new song is!
We haven't seen 'em,
but let us know if you find 'em.
I'd love to get their autograph.
Later, dudes.
-Huh. Well, that was unexpected.
So the wolves haven't seen them either.
I'm afraid this case has gone cold.
I'll say.
The temperature's dropping.
We gotta find Bill and Jill
before they freeze out there.
-All we have is their distress call.
Come get us. I repeat, come get us.
Maybe there's some clue we missed.
Don't think we missed anything. All I hear
is that great beat in the background.
Well, it's good, yes,
but I wouldn't call it great just yet.
Listen. It's offbeat.
-Did ya hear it?
-You're right.
Those drums are all messed up.
They might not be drums at all! Listen!
It almost sounds like…
The musk oxen headbutting!
Bill and Jill must've been near them!
So the musk oxen are mixed up in this!
But how?
We'd better go back and ask 'em,
whether they like it or not. Come on!
-Look! There they are!
-Hey!
Musk oxen! Wait up!
-Whoa!
I thought we already warned you
not to come back here!
Oops.
Uh-oh.
We're standing on a frozen lake!
Get back to the shore!
Oh no! My babies!
This is bad, Sam.
Musk oxen are not good swimmers.
-Come on!
-We've gotta get them back to shore!
Those ice floes…
Maybe…
-If we…
On it, Kit.
Clu-Bot, go!
Wait for it.
Wait for it…
Now!
This way, everybody.
Just one more.
Whoa! Woo!
Uh! There you go.
Our babies! You saved them!
Just doing our jobs, ma'am.
You might wanna consider
getting this little guy a haircut, though.
-He can barely see where he's going.
-Mm?
Not mine.
Uh, did I say something wrong?
This strange-looking fellow
doesn't belong to any of us.
He doesn't?
Actually, I don't think
this is a calf at all.
Is it a wolf in oxen's clothing?
This is no wolf!
-It's the Mice Squad!
They've been here all along!
Oh, hey, guys.
Bill! Jill! We got your distress call.
Come get us. I repeat, come get us.
Are you okay?
Distress call? You mean this?
We're doing undercover work
in the tundra.
No need to come get us.
I repeat, no need to come get us.
The cold weather
must have scrambled it. Weird.
But why were you undercover?
That's why.
We wanted to record
that sound for our new track.
We didn't even see you guys
under all this fur.
We're just glad you're okay.
Everyone at CLADE will be so relieved.
Another Creature Case…
Closed!
So, you were recording our headbutting
to use in your song?
Can we hear it?
All this dancing is warming me up.
Oh yeah? Just wait
till you see my cool moves!
Uh… Whoa…
You're looking pretty cool, all right.
Mice Squad Fact File.
Status?
System Settings?
Update. Musk oxen.
Musk oxen are pretty shy
and mostly stick with their herd.
When threatened,
they form a ring to protect their young.
They live where it's cold.
But watch out for thin ice.
They can't swim well.
Male musk oxen sometimes
ram their heads together. Bam!
It's so loud,
you can hear it from far away.
Error. Upload incomplete.
How to fix it?
Move your feet.