(eerie electronic piano music)
(metal clanking)
(scanner beeps)
(man calls in foreign language)
- Don't move.
(metal creaking)
Well that leg looks pretty bad.
(tense music)
I gotta go.
(peaceful music)
- Wade, what are you doing?
Where's Mandroid?
- Mandroid is here.
- Well this is certainly
keeping out of sight.
- Zanna, I just saved some guy's life.
- Wade, if a security patrol
came along and saw you--
- Security patrol can't
do a damn thing to us.
- Except throw us in prison,
execute us for no reason,
torture us.
- All right.
Fine.
- Hey.
Hey.
I'd rather have you alive than dead.
That's all.
(adventurous orchestral music)
(laughs)
- Tell me, tell me, Carolyn.
- Why?
Are you interested?
- Just curious.
- Curiosity killed the cat. (laughs)
- Okay.
Don't tell me.
(sneaky music)
- You know what to do.
- (grunts) Yes.
- Hurry!
- He used the old line about
being an American lost here
and would I show him the city.
- Did you?
- Sure.
Just enough.
- And?
- And what?
- Did you fall in love with him?
- Right now, I'd drop to the floor
for any man who would take me
who would take me to the US.
- Any man?
- Yes.
(Alexa laughs)
Any old pig would do it. (laughs)
(man grunting)
(men chuckling)
(car engine running)
- Ah!
Let's push it down!
(men grunt and groan)
(car screeches)
(women scream)
(screaming)
(men taunting)
(door creaks)
(creepy music)
- Please.
Don't hurt me.
- I will not hurt you.
I just...
want you to be nice to me.
I want you to dance for me.
- Hm.
(chuckles)
Looks like somebody's been
stockpiling young women.
Ooh la la.
- You think that's funny?
- Hey, take it easy, alright?
- Those girls might be dead right now.
- Wade, it was a joke.
- Just do your job.
Let's get Mandroid fired up.
- Don't be angry at Ryder.
We're all under a lot of pressure.
Ben gets out of the hospital tomorrow
and we're running out of time.
- You got all the time
in the world with me.
I'm not going anywhere.
- Well, I didn't say that.
- Oh, what the hell.
I'm either in the chair or in the tin can.
Let's get this show on the road.
(beeps)
(dark music)
- Ready to rock and roll?
- [Mandroid] Captain
Radiation strikes again.
- Time, Zanna?
- 10 seconds.
Record it all.
(electric buzzing)
(explosion)
- [Wade] Zanna, turn off the unit.
(alarm beeping)
- Don't panic.
Cut the power manually, Wade.
- What the hell's that supposed to mean?
- Break the cone, if we
hit the red we're gonna fry
half the country with this.
- [Wade] We might want to run a check
on Mandroid's delicate touch.
(mysterious music)
(snoring)
- My God.
- [Zanna] Yuck.
Some leftovers.
- Here, catch.
You start on the salad,
I'll improvise the rest.
- Ooh, I didn't know you were a chef too.
- Just an asshole, right?
- You know, I have this stupid idea that
one day I'm gonna pump the Supercon in me
and I'm gonna stand up and walk
away from this chair and...
(sighs)
I'm trying, Zanna.
- I know.
Am I too heavy?
- I couldn't even feel
it even if you were.
- Well.
- I can feel that.
- That's good.
(thunder crashes)
(dramatic music)
(groans)
(rain falling)
(thunder crashing)
(door creaks open)
- You'll look good in this.
(giggling)
- Now Philip, drink this.
Don't you want these scars to disappear?
I can make them go away.
Now, drink this.
Please.
Now!
New tissue should grow almost immediately.
(groaning)
(chuckles)
Take him with the other failures.
(door creaks open)
(gasping)
(men jeering)
- Do whatever he says, whatever it is.
- What?
- [Prisoner] Do it!
- Or he'll give you to
those crazy bastards.
- What crazy bastards?
(spits)
(frantic music)
(cheering)
(yells)
- And what are you going
to do for us tonight?
- I don't understand.
- Dance for us.
- Bam bam.
Bam bam.
(claps)
(exotic music)
(men clapping)
- She's all yours, boys.
(men groaning)
(screaming)
- Oh Ben, this is our
new assistant, Ryder.
- Mr. Knight, this is quite an honor.
- Don't be too sure about that.
I've got quirks.
- Excuse me?
- Zanna didn't tell you.
- Never mind.
Let's go.
(mysterious music)
(computers beeping)
- Hey Ben.
Is that you under there?
- Glad to see you haven't
lost your sense of humor.
- Gotta have it.
- It's good to be home.
- It's very good to have you.
Come on, guys.
(Ben chuckles)
What's so funny?
- I don't want to take my bandages off.
You know, I have thought about
getting undressed with you
I don't know how many times
but I ain't doing it now.
- (laughs) Well, why not?
- Can't be modesty.
- Well, I don't want to not see myself.
If you know what I mean.
Jesus, my eyes!
- That's because there's nothing to stop
the light reflection on the eyes' surface.
Your optics nerves are completely exposed.
- Good diagnosis.
- Hold still.
- [Ben] Ow.
- Next time I tell you to wear your shades
maybe you'll pay attention.
- How long before this stuff takes effect?
- Well, Dad's last notes indicate between
two and three hours.
- So, what do we do until
my guest appearance?
- I'd like to get to work.
- Ryder, do you have everything?
- Yes I do.
Right here.
- Oh, great.
Now I'm getting emphysema.
- The hardest thing for
you to get used to is your
hand-eye coordination.
That's completely changed now
because you can't see them.
You'll have to learn to
do the simplest things
all over again.
- Not if the drug works.
- Ben, this is just the
beginning of the experimentation.
There are no guarantees.
- Well, I've got my fingers crossed.
I mean, who would want to be this way
even for five seconds?
- You know Ben, this invisibility thing
does have it its pluses.
You can skip out on checks in restaurants,
you can check out the
ladies room at the gym.
I mean, the possibility are endless.
- Ben, if you can light this cigarette,
you are my hero.
- [Ryder] That's incredible. (chuckles)
- Doctor Knox,
you must think I'm a fool.
- [Knox] Of course not, sir.
- To come to me with this strange
story about invisible men.
You have seen too much
American television.
- Aren't you the least bit interested
in how your predecessor died?
A CIA agent was killed with him, you know.
- Goodbye, doctor.
- There is many involved here.
And power.
I can help you, sir.
If you have the knowledge,
you have the power.
- Goodbye.
- Virginia,
bring me the files on Colonel Kolczech
and Dr. Karl Zimmer.
(thuds)
(breathing heavily)
- Hold it, Ben.
Let's see.
Okay.
This is steady.
What was his last pressure reading?
- Uh, 160 over 40.
- A regular see through
Arnold Schwarzenegger.
- Yeah, well Arnold, you
better relax for a minute.
I am not sure how all this exercise
is effecting the Supercon treatment.
(yelling)
Ben?
Come on, you have to talk
to me, you have to tell me.
Ryder, I'm gonna need some help here.
Ryder, hold him!
- Hurry!
(yelling)
- Forget it, Zanna, you'll
need a sledgehammer.
- I'll cut you in half
you metal son of a bitch!
(dinking)
- Come on!
- Stay still.
Keep him down, Ryder.
(groaning)
- I guess I lost it, huh?
- (chuckles) You could say that.
- Metal son of a bitch.
- Hey watch out, you know,
I could bring him in here anytime.
Ooh.
- Wade.
How do you deal with it?
- Usually?
Not very well.
- Looks like we both have
a lot to get used to.
(grunts)
(glass shatters)
(screaming)
- If we don't get lucky soon
we may never be able to
reverse Ben's condition.
- Oh.
I'm off to the Supercon
chamber again, huh?
- What's on the schedule?
- Wade and I have a little work to do.
- Then you don't need me tonight, right?
I'll see you in the morning.
- Right, you're the hook again, Ryder.
- Come on, Wade.
- I'm sorry Zanna, that guy
bugs me plain and simple.
- He does good work.
- He's not the only one.
- What's this?
- Well...
(metal stomping)
- This is incredible.
Wade, when did you do this?
- I've been working on it for a while.
The old helmet made me feel
like I was playing for the 49ers.
Now I'll look like
Elvis, the Vegas period.
(Zanna laughs)
- Hm, well, I've seen a better Elvis.
But Wade,
this technology is fantastic.
- Thank you.
(dramatic music)
- The kid, he's here.
- I'm waiting.
Come in, my boy, come in.
- Benjamin Knight's come back.
- In what condition?
- Zanna hasn't found the
formula for a cure yet
and the one that she
tried had side effects.
After an injection he
had some kind of a...
psychotic fit.
(laughs)
- The Zimmer medical talent
is up to its usual standards.
The fits can be controlled,
you know, with drugs.
You concentrate on the Supercon.
And be sure to get the
special set of specs
that Zimmer had always hidden away.
That's priority number one.
- If I do this for you,
you'll release my father?
- I will.
- I need a guarantee.
- I guarantee
he will never leave if I
don't get the Supercon spec.
(laughing)
- [Ryder] Dad.
(laughs)
- I love family reunions.
Move your body.
- [Ben] Is this absolutely necessary?
- It's just a precaution, Ben.
I have to give you a
bigger dosage this time.
- Not that it wasn't fun last time, Ben,
watching you tear apart the lab.
Ooh, Zanna's gonna give
you the big needle.
(Ben gasps)
- Sorry Ben.
So, how are you feeling now?
- Okay.
What's happening?
Get me a mirror.
Boy, do I need a shave.
- To Zanna Zimmer.
If your father were
here he'd be very proud.
- I had help.
- This is permanent.
- What?
- Me.
Being visible.
- I'm sorry Ben.
The radiation you were exposed to
absolutely mutated your body,
to stay visible you will
have to stay on this drug.
I'll figure the dosage
and the frequency next.
- For the rest of my life?
- Probably.
- Can I control this thing?
- As it is now, if you
touch a Supercon crystal
you will become invisible so.
- Speaking of invisible,
where's the perfect little assistant?
(tense music)
Hey.
Zanna doesn't pay overtime.
- Oh, ha.
There were a few things
that needed cleaning, so.
- You've already the efficiency award.
Take a break.
What's wrong?
Hey, you don't look so hot.
- Uh...
I think I'm just gonna go
home and get some sleep.
- Ryder.
You need something?
- No.
No, I'll be fine.
I'll see you in the morning.
Congratulations, by the way.
(tires screeching)
(truck horn blares)
(yells)
(tense music)
(engine hissing)
(explosion)
(gargling)
- I hope you'll be able
to identify Mr. Ryder.
- [Zanna] Is it that bad?
- It's most unusual, doctor.
Most unusual.
Let them see the corpse.
- That's him.
- And you're sure?
There isn't much of him left.
- I'm sure.
- This is the most remarkable thing.
The state physician has
no idea how this condition
could have occurred.
One of my lieutenants thinks
this is a sign from God.
Mr. Ryder worked in your lab.
How do you think this could have happened?
- I don't know.
- Then consider yourself under
arrest for not cooperating.
- [Ben] Jesus, this bench is cold.
- Ben?
Ben?
- Who are you talking to?
- Uh, no one.
No one. (chuckles)
Where are you?
- [Ben] I'm about a foot to the right.
- How did you get here?
- [Ben] I hitched a ride with you guys.
I'm getting you the hell outta here.
- (chuckles) Crazy one.
- Is this the man you talked about?
- No, this one helped
pick up Benjamin Knight
at the hospital.
He worked for Zimmer.
Has she talked yet?
- No, not yet.
But I can assure you she will.
- I have drugs that are quite efficient
if you need some help.
Colonel?
- Yes?
I was just thinking.
Imagine what an army of
invisible men could do.
- Anything, Colonel.
They could do anything.
- Colonel, how long do you
intend to keep us here?
- You are free to go at any time.
(grunts)
- [Ben] Wade, get a head
start towards the truck.
Come on, come on!
- [Zanna] Come on, Ben.
- [Ben] Back to work, ladies.
Move over!
(grunts)
(speaking foreign language)
(thuds)
(grunts)
Come on, guys!
(engine starts)
(alarm beeps)
- Go, go, go!
- Go on, go on!
Come on!
(men muttering)
(wheels skid)
- Woah, hey.
- [Ben] Jesus, it's weird not having
my hands in front of me.
- You're doing great, Ben.
You're doing fine.
(car beeping)
(gun firing)
- Get closer!
Faster!
- Jesus.
(gun firing)
- Oh.
- [Ben] If I get hit, do you think
I'll be able to see my blood?
- Drive, Ben, drive!
(gun firing)
(yelling)
(explosion)
- [Ben] What happened?
Did we lose him?
Well, we got them off our back.
- For about five minutes, Ben.
He won't stay down for long.
(dramatic music)
- Look through these documents
and take as many as you can.
- Alright.
- Zanna, we're never gonna
get all this stuff together.
We've gotta get outta here.
- I know, I know.
- So where are we going?
- Ow!
- There's only one place I can think of.
And that's Dad's hold hunting lodge.
(tense music)
(alarm beeping)
Aw, damn, they're here.
- We're trapped.
- We'll try the backdoor.
- They probably have the house surrounded.
- Come out with your hands up
and no harm will come to you.
- [Wade] Ah, Colonel,
what a nice surprise.
I thought we'd lost you back there.
- Where is Dr. Zimmer and that thing?
- Oh, I'm sorry,
you just missed them.
- Search the house.
How do you operate this machine?
- Well, we're still working on that.
I don't mind telling you
he's a little temperamental.
- Colonel, the house is empty.
- Bring this man.
And this machine too.
(mysterious music)
(tense music)
(blows)
- [Ben] Cigarettes are
bad for your health.
(grunts)
(thuds)
- Ben, you okay?
- [Ben] Piece o' cake.
Let's go.
- Here, get dressed.
(engine starts)
- Incompetent stupid idiot.
(glass shatters)
I told Ryder to be careful!
He wasn't smart enough!
(sobs)
And Zanna has disappeared.
Now where
would that limited intelligence take her?
(birds chirping)
- This is great.
- [Zanna] Yeah, I haven't
been her in a long time.
- You keep it really nice.
- Well, there's cleaning
supplies in the kitchen, Ben.
Join me for cocktails?
- I'd prefer a margarita.
- Sorry, all we've got is Molotov.
- Happy hour, huh?
- I have a feeling we're gonna need it.
- Pretty weird seeing that photo of Drago
and your dad up there.
- It's hard to believe they
were best friends once.
Used to come up here all the time.
They hunted and talked
and when they got back
they always had a new idea.
It was a good time for all of us.
- Yeah.
- Well, they're both gone now.
Top this off, will you?
- [Petroff] Doctor Franklin,
I hope you slept well.
- Like a prince, thank you.
- I have some questions for
you that I hope you can answer.
- [Wade] Well, I'll certainly try.
- First, I would like
to know about the death
of Dr. Karl Zimmer.
- Gee, I dunno anything about that.
- Are you associated with a
CIA agent called Joe Smith?
- Joe Smith?
Sorry.
(groans)
- Now we are on equal footing.
- Go to Hell.
- One of my soldiers present
when Dr. Zimmer was killed
talked about this huge robot,
indestructible.
Unfortunately he was
killed and so were all
the others present.
The only one left was Miss Zimmer.
She claimed that they had been ambushed
but it was never clear by whom and why.
Do you know what I think, Dr. Franklin?
- Ask someone who cares.
- I think that the CIA was
interested in buying this thing.
Something went wrong.
You wound up in a wheelchair
and Dr. Zimmer was killed.
- That's a wild story.
I guess that's why they pay
you the big bucks, right?
- Dr. Franklin.
You and I are going to
have a very, very nice
long talk.
And you, you are going to tell
me everything I want to know.
- Woah, woah.
That cabin should be empty.
Let's have a look.
- Ben, here's some more Supercon
in case you need to
become invisible again.
(gargling)
(whistles)
- What was that?
(groans)
(chuckling)
- We have to come up
with a plan to get Wade.
He's been in there too long already, Ben.
I can count on you, right?
- You can always count on me.
Don't worry, he's gonna be okay.
- Ben...
- Hey.
Don't worry.
I'll just go find myself a
nice invisible girl somewhere.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna get the stuff out of the car.
(grunts)
- Why don't you cooperate
and free yourself from the
misery that you are in?
- Misery?
Are you kiddin'?
I call this character building.
- You're a tough man, Dr. Franklin.
I can see I have to use a
different method with you.
Virginia, get Dr. Knox and
tell him to bring his drugs.
(glass shatters)
(men laughing)
(screams)
(yelling)
(screaming)
(men yelling)
- I wish you hadn't killed my friend!
(Zanna screaming)
- Hey!
(gun firing)
(emotional music)
(breathing)
(footfalls)
(man yells in foreign language)
(slaps)
(yelps)
(woman speaks foreign language)
- You will just feel a little sting
and then we'll talk about everything.
- You're too kind.
(knocking)
- Get on with it.
- What?
(tense music)
- Doctor?
(thuds)
(grunts)
- Ben?
- [Ben] I think I need some help.
- You invisible son of a bitch.
(grunts)
- You wanted to know
how I worked, Colonel?
So study this.
(grunts)
(groans)
- [Ben] Come on, let's
get out of here fast.
- Good idea.
(speaks foreign language)
(thuds)
(clanks)
- Hold it!
(gun firing)
(grunts)
(alarm beeping)
(engine starts)
(guns firing)
- [Drago] Find anything interesting?
(gasps)
- How can you be alive?
- There are so many things
about the human body
you don't understand, Zanna.
And that's why the invisibility
secret keeps escaping you.
- Ryder worked for you, didn't he?
- Very good guess.
I needed the Supercon
formula and now I have it.
- You have nothing.
- Little Zanna, still
trying to be the scientist.
You're a lost girl in need of guidance.
- Let go of me you son of a bitch!
- Ah, a fighting spirit.
I like it.
You know Zanna, I can
think of only one way
you'll be of any use to me.
(mysterious music)
(brakes squeaking)
(screaming)
(dinnerware clanking)
(Drago yells)
- Pump, pump, pump.
(clapping)
Pump, pump, pump.
(exotic music)
(men jeering)
(beeping)
- I can't get up these.
You're gonna have to go it alone, okay?
- Okay.
Let's go.
(men yelling)
(clapping)
- Do you like this, Uncle Ivan?
Don't move or I'll slit his throat!
- Very impressive, Zanna.
- Shut up, you're coming with me.
- Why don't you cut my throat, huh?
Go ahead, do it!
You can't do it, you are too weak, Zanna.
- [Drago] Feed on her!
- No.
No.
No!
- Don't be afraid.
We're here to help you.
We're looking for a blonde
girl they just brought in.
- I don't know.
We're not allowed to talk to each other.
- Okay.
Come on, let's get out of here.
(men yelling)
- Don't run, Zanna.
(screaming)
Don't run, Zanna.
Why not enjoy the time you have left?
(groaning)
- She's not here, Ben.
- [Ben] Okay.
Take the back stairs and get
as far away from this place
as possible.
- Who are you?
- [Ben] Never mind that.
Just get outta here quick.
(tense music)
(screams)
(Drago yells)
- Zanna, dear.
You are exactly where I want you to be.
(high-pitched scream)
- [Ben] What the hell was that?
- I don't know, but I don't like it.
(men jeering)
(Zanna groaning)
- How are you feeling, Zanna?
- Go to Hell.
- Getting a little nervous, my dear?
(laughs)
(thuds)
What are you doing?
Imbeciles!
Don't be afraid, it's only a machine.
Kill the machine!
(men yelling)
Goodbye, Zanna.
- [Ben] Not so fast.
(gasps)
- Oh, Benjamin, my boy,
are you back on your safety pills?
(sword slices)
(grunts)
(yelling)
- I'm gonna break you in two.
(Drago speaks foreign language)
(screams)
Hold on, Zanna.
I got you.
Come on, it's okay.
There you are.
Are you alright?
- Yeah, but Ben is hurt.
Ben.
Ben, can you hear me?
- [Ben] Yeah, he didn't cut of my ears.
- Come on guys, we gotta get outta here.
- Not yet.
I can't let Drago get away a second time.
(dagger unsheathes)
(yelling)
(grunts)
(gun firing)
(glass shatters)
(yells)
(intense music)
- Now Zanna, end of the road.
(gasps)
(exhales) No.
I need some air.
(breathing heavily)
(yells)
(body thuds)
(soothing violin music)
- Okay, enemies of the state, let's go.
The border's half an hour away.
- We haven't decided
where we're going yet.
- Wasn't it the US?
- Ben, it's a big country.
- I always wanted to see
New York or Los Angeles.
- What about Washington?
- Washington.
- (giggles) Yeah, Washington.
I think we'll fit right in.
(glasses beep)
(engine starts)
(epic orchestral music)
(soft violin music)