(silence)
(music)
Hi there.
Hi there, my name's Ted.
Nice to meet ya.
Hi there.
My name's Ted.
Nice to meet you.
Hi there.
My name's Ted.
Nice to meet ya.
Now the sociopath
represents a different set
of problems for the mental
health worker.
For the sociopath does not
suffer from the sort of
repressed impulses that the
neurotic patient needs to
examine and to recognize.
He will lie, he will cheat,
even kill to attain
his ends.
And not even the prospect of
swift and sure punishment
will deter him from his path
to gratification.
Four beers, please.
Want to dance?
Oh, I just got here.
But thanks anyway.
Come on.
Dance with me.
I won't bite, I promise.
You won't regret it.
are you a student?
Uh, huh.
Me too.
Groovy
Urn, thanks.
Sure.
I am so drunk I
am hallucinating.
Aw, hell.
You again?
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Shit! Fuck! Fuck!
(screaming)
(laughing)
This better be
good, Ted.
I just needed to hear
your voice.
It's four in the morning.
I know, Lee.
I've been hitting the books
so hard I lost track
of time.
I haven't heard from you
in nearly a week.
I've been
studying. Lee.
I'm sorry.
Yes, I know you've
been studying.
But, uh, God, I just ... I
hate the way you make me
feel sometimes.
I need to see you.
You only want to see me
when it's convenient
for you.
Why can't you just
be honest?
You don't really love me.
Not really.
If you did, you would call.
Lee, I just ... I just
need to hold you.
Then why don't you come
over right now?
I'll make you something
to eat.
How 'bout tomorrow, Lee?
I'm really tired.
First tell me what I
need to hear.
I love you, Lee.
And I haven't been seeing
anyone else.
Now get some sleep, okay?
You can't hide from
me, Ted.
Ted!
Hey cutie pie.
How are ya?
Whoa.
Oh. No.
No
Look, mommy, it's almost
in outer space.
It sure is, hon.
Hmm...
Make it come back
Well, I can't do that.
Did you ever hear the story
about the little girl who
was holding a balloon and a
gust of wind came along and
carried her away?
That never happened.
You're just being silly.
Yes, it did.
No, I'm not being silly.
Aargh, aargh.
Oh, ho, ho!
Show you silly.
I gotcha.
Be careful.
If I had one-tenth her
energy, school would be
a breeze.
She's just showing off
for you.
Yeah.
I seem to have that effect
on women.
Oh, no, she - she really
adores you, Ted.
So do i.
And I adore you, Lee.
So, one day maybe I
won't have to share you with
so many women
You're so stupid
Yeah.
I may be stupid, but not so
stupid to think you don't
have plenty of
other admirers.
Yeah, Lee.
I have admirers, but just
because someone admires me
doesn't mean I'm sleeping
with them.
Look, look, I don't want
to start an argument, okay?
I was just hoping we could
commit to each other.
Like really commit, Ted.
We are committed.
And I love you, so can we
just focus on that?
Really?
Yeah. Really.
Urn. Urn.
What's that?
What?
Did you steal this, Ted?
(laughs) No.
Ted!
Well, it's not like it's the
first time it's ever
happened, huh?
Just - just keep your
voice down, okay?
Why, you afraid somebody
might find out the wonderful
Ted Bundy's a thief?
You tell anyone that, I
will break your fucking
neck, you hear me?
No. Take
it back!
Give it to one of your
other girls!
I didn't steal the watch, Lee!
Look.
Listen to me.
You have a future.
And you've worked so hard.
What do you think is going
to happen to that future if
you get caught
stealing, huh?
Yeah, right.
Why do you talk
like this?
It's easy, because first I
flunked out of law school
and now I'm flunking
psychology.
Ted, why didn't you
tell me?
I don't know, I just..
Look, there's still two
months left in the semester
and I can still help you.
But if you just
give up. Ted...
Look, I didn't steal
the watch.
I just wanted to get
something nice for my gal.
Show my appreciation.
After all you've done for
me, all the money you've
given me to stay in school,
I figured it was the least I
could do.
It's a beautiful
watch, Ted.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I ever
doubted you.
Is it good?
Yes.
Yeah.
Let's try something else.
What?
Come on.
Flip over.
No! No,
you know I don't
like that.
It's disgusting.
Lee, it's just another way
to make love.
No, it has nothing to do
with love.
It's just, it's dirty.
Lee, sex is only dirty
when you do it right.
Let's just do
it regular.
Okay. Fine.
We'll do it regular.
Okay? 'cause
that's what feels
like love,
right? Yeah?
Yeah.
That feel like love?
Yeah? Good.
How 'bout that?
Ted!
Does that feel like
love? Huh?
Does that feel like love?
Ted!
What about this?
Does that feel like love?
Oh, you're choking me!
That's what love feels
like to me, Lee!
No! Ted!
What, are you nuts?
I gotta go.
No.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's fine, Lee.
It's fine.
Am I going to see
you tomorrow?
Yeah.
I'm at the crisis center
from eleven to three.
I'll call you when I'm done.
I-I remember it was my
birthday that day and
afterwards, when all the
kids went home, he, urn,
came up into my room and
made me put it in my mouth.
He put it in your mouth?
Yeah. I didn't
want him to be all
mad again.
I wanted to make him happy.
Did you tell anyone?
Yeah, my mother.
She didn't believe me.
And if she did, she just
looked the other way.
You must have a lot of
anger towards her.
I don't know.
She's dead now.
You still there, Ted?
Mh-hm, I'm still here.
Well, uh, tell me
one thing.
Why are men such assholes?
Well, I think you just
haven't met the right guy.
You sound like one of
those right kind of guys.
Thank you, Karen.
Look, Karen, one day you'll
find a love that's deeper
and more meaningful than
anything you've ever
imagined.
God. Do you
really think so, Ted?
I know so.
Do you think we could
talk again.
Ted? I gotta
go to work now.
Uh-huh.
Anytime, okay?
Okay.
Take care, Karen.
All right.
And don't do
anything crazy.
All right.
(doorbell rings)
Where have you
been? Huh?
You said you were going to
call and you didn't.
Ted? Ted.
Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
Actually, I'm really hungry
You really were
hungry, huh?
Yep.
Whatcha thinkin' about?
The future.
How I want things to
turn out.
How do you want things
to turn out?
Well, I guess we could
start with the basic premise
that whoever dies with the
most toys, wins.
Okay.
You want a lot of toys.
What else?
Good job.
Nice clothes.
New car.
All the things I didn't have
growing up.
Maybe go into politics.
I still haven't given up
on that.
Mm-hm.
But mostly, I just want
to be normal.
What?
You don't think you're
normal?
I'm trying to be.
Oh, Ted...
I'm really trying to be
Don't make a
sound. Understand?
(whines)
Yes? Okay,
now get up.
Get up.
What do you want?
Shut up and listen.
Cooperate and everything's
going to be okay.
Otherwise, I'm going to
kill you.
Okay.
Do you believe me?
Yeah.
Good. Now, I
just broke into your
apartment. Why
do you want to
believe me?
(music)
A drink?
Oh, yeah.
Whoa.
Nice TV.
Yeah, it's a gift from
my parents.
They're cool, huh?
Yeah.
So when do I get to meet
your folks?
Mmm ... They look like
nice people.
They are nice people.
So what's the problem?
Who said there was
a problem?
What, do
I embarrass
you? Huh?
You're the most paranoid
woman I ever met.
No, well, you've met
my parents.
Yeah, and someday you'll
meet mine.
Someday?
Don't start,
Lee. Jesus.
No, it's just, if
there's a problem, I want to
know about it.
Yes, there's a problem.
But just because there's a
problem doesn't mean that
you're the center of it.
Come on, please, just
tell me.
I don't want there to be any
secrets between
us. Please?
I'm illegitimate.
That's it?
I'm a bastard.
Ooh.
That's an ugly word and it
should be removed from the
english language.
Maybe so, but it's
still true.
Stop saying that.
Don't ever, ever, ever
say that.
Imagine being five years
old and finding out that
your sister is really
your mother.
Okay, and that would be
a little weird.
Yeah, and then being
seventeen and finding out
that your father's not
your father.
Well, they still loved
you, didn't they?
Yes, they loved me.
Of course they loved me.
Yeah.
Who could not love you?
Ah, damn.
Aah.
Whenever I see anybody
carrying that many books,
they're studying to be
a doctor.
Yeah, well, in this case,
it's law school.
Well, those aren't
law books.
No, these are for
everything else.
Is there any chance I can
get you to help me carry
these to my car?
I'm basically helpless with
this cast.
Well, okay.
But if I need any legal
advice, you owe me one
Its a deal.
It's, uh, over here.
Okay.
I hope this isn't going to
make you late for class.
No, I'm fine.
If you could just, uh, put
them on the floor
right there.
Okay.
The killer came in from
the night...
Just what this town
needs, a psycho killer
running around.
Well, don't look at me.
I didn't do it.
I think we can rule you
out as a suspect, Ted.
I can't wait to see what
the son-of-a-bitch
looks like.
You really think it's just
one guy responsible?
You know, what the police
say and what they think are
often two completely
different things.
That's what I think.
I think that they hold a lot
of stuff back so that
there's stuff only the
perpetrator knows.
Do you think those women
could still be alive?
No way.
They're way dead.
Ted, this is a party.
No one wants to talk about
this.
Oh, really, Lee?
What subjects can we
talk about?
Actually, uh, I think
it's fascinating.
Well, I think its sick
and disgusting.
Well, certainly murder is
aberrant behavior, but, I
mean, the psychology that
motivates it is really quite
interesting, don't
you think?
Totally.
I think I need a
refill.
I'm, so sorry.
I'm Betty.
Hi Betty.
I'm Ted.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Lee, right?
That's me.
I'm Beverly from the
crisis center.
You know, I-I work with Ted
at the crisis center.
Oh, great. Hi.
Oh, he is doing
really great.
I- he has an amazing knack
with the callers.
He always knows the exact
right thing to say.
Yep, he sure has a way
with people, all right.
Oh, my God!
Please don't hurt me.
I'm not going to hurt you.
What do you want?
I just want you to listen
to me.
Pay me a little bit
of attention.
See, girls like you, they
don't pay attention to guys
like me.
Guys who don't came from
good families.
Who don't go to top schools,
or drive fancy cars.
(whimpers)
Shut up and
listen! God!
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not some share the
wealth' type of pinko creep
or something.
Don't do this to me.
In fact, I'm a republican.
I worked on a number of
campaigns, and one day, I'm
gonna be governor.
You don't even believe me,
do you?
You probably just think I'm
some kind of loser.
Well, maybe you're right.
Maybe I'm not so important
out there, but here, I'm
in charge.
Here, I'm in control.
Because this is the court
of Ted!
What I say here is law!
You get the
picture?
(screams)
(cries)
Do I have your
attention now?
And Julie's staying with
your parents for how long?
All month.
I was kind of hoping maybe
we could spend some time
together alone before you
went off, back to
law school.
I told you a thousand
times, you can come with me
if you want to.
Your enthusiasm isn't
exactly overwhelming, Ted.
Hey, you gotta make your
own decision.
I mean, if things don't work
out, I don't want it to be
my fault.
I don't want to
argue, okay?
I am just saying, we both
know the reason why I am not
going with you to salt lake.
Mm-hm.
And what is it?
You don't want me to go.
Oh. You know,
you're giving me
a headache.
Is she going with you?
Is who going with me
That woman at the party.
The one you were talking to
that thought murderers were
'oh so fascinating'
You're certifiable, you
know that?
You're a hundred
percent certifiable.
That's right, Ted, just
dismiss it.
Treat me like I'm crazy.
Anybody with the audacity to
disagree with the great Ted
Bundy has to be
crazy, right?
What the hell?
Asshole!
You're such a fucking jerk.
Look, I don't know why
you're so upset.
It was a joke.
Where are my keys?
Don't ask me.
What the hell are these?
I dunno.
I've never seen them before.
Who's a pretty girl?
You are.
You're the pretty girl.
Yeah, you are.
(knock on door)
Who is it?
It's me
Just a minute.
Look, I don't want
to fight.
I just want us to enjoy our
time together before you
have to leave.
Now is that so much to ask?
No. Nothing
would make me
happier.
Mm, what's that
smell? Whew.
I left a bologna sandwich
out on the kitchen counter.
Well, it stinks.
Mm-hm.
Sorry.
Oh, God, I love
kissing you.
Hmm, me, too.
What?
I have an idea.
Oh, no.
What has that little brain
of yours come up with
this time?
It's just something I
want to try.
What?
Have you ever heard of a
thing called 'submission'?
Well, I thought that's
what I was doing every time
I opened my legs.
Is that what it feels
like to you?
Sometimes.
But did you ever think
there might be a little bit
more to sex than just
opening your legs?
I just want to make love.
So, hmm, what could be
more loving than having me
take total control?
Okay.
Just make sure it
doesn't hurt.
It's not going to hurt.
And it doesn't make me
feel degraded, either.
Will you stop worrying?
Oh, God, Ted, I just want
to make you happy.
Goddamnit!
I hope you're having fun,
'cause I'm not.
All right.
All right, don't talk.
Don't move.
Don't even breathe.
What?
What, you can't
pretend that you are dead?
You serious?
Yes, I'm serious!
Just give it a
fucking try, okay?
Okay! I love
you, Ted, and if
that's what you want-
I want it.
Do it.
Okay, open your eyes.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Fuck ... You ... Bitch!
Aah ... Aah ... Aah ...
... Aah ... Aaah ...
Hi. Excuse me.
I'm uh, sorry to bother you,
but, uh, I was wondering if
you could help me out.
Help you out with what?
Uh, with my sailboat I
hate asking, but, uh, I
basically can't do anything
with this cast.
I'll take you for a ride in
it, if you'd like.
Please? Pretty please?
Okay. Okay.
Just don't beg.
Sure. It's,
uh, right over
this way.
I'm Ted.
What's your name?
Shawn.
Hi, shawn.
H-hey!
I thought you needed help
unloading your sailboat.
Yeah, it's at my folk's
place just up the hill.
Didn't I mention that?
No.
Well, is that a problem?
Mm, I guess not.
Great. Hop in.
Don't touch me!
You know what?
I hope you're not going to
act like this all day
If you don't start with
me, I'll be fine.
I, uh, are you on the
rag or something?
Shut up!
Goddamn lemmings.
Look at them all.
They fester like a bunch
of rats.
If they're all rats and
lemmings, then what does
that make us?
I like how you make me do
all the work.
Hey, I brought the
cooler down.
Whatever.
Where is everybody?
They could be anywhere.
Well, shouldn't we go
look far them?
Right now, I just want
to drink my beer.
Fine.
Wh-whoa, where do you
think you're going?
I gotta pee.
Is that okay, your lordship?
Jesus.
Excuse me.
Uh, I'm sorry to bother you,
but is there any chance you
could help me out with
something?
Help you out with what?
Well, with my sailboat.
Urn, see, I'm having
trouble, uh, unloading it
with this stupid cast here,
and I'd really appreciate it
if you'd give me a hand.
(screaming)
Okay, that was a
mistake, bitch.
I'll be right back, kitten.
(screaming)
Hi, again.
Get off!
(screaming)
Are you ready for some
fun, kitten?
Give me that.
Thank you, munchkin.
Well, guess this is it.
Won't be seeing you for a
while, little one.
I don't want you to go.
When you're here, it's like
we're a family.
Yeah, but I gotta go to
college so I can become a
lawyer and buy lots of nice
things for you and mommy.
Will you still come
see us?
Mm-hm.
And you can come visit
me, too.
In Utah?
You got it.
You be good, okay, munchkin?
All right.
This is it.
Call me, okay?
As soon as I get settled.
See you in the funny papers.
We just found a
third body.
What kind of shape's
this one in?
They're all skeletonized.
Nothing good.
Seven heads and
three bodies.
Jesus!
Thanks for the ride.
I really appreciate it.
Sure.
Where're you headed?
Silver canyon.
How 'bout you?
Me, too are you from
around here?
No. Holy shit.
Look at that.
(screams)
Fuck ... You!
Fuck...
Fuck ... You ... Bitch
fuck ... Fuck fuck ... Fuck
Excuse me, ma'am.
Ma'am. I'm
Officer Roseland with
the Murray police department.
I'm sorry to bother you, but
it looks like somebody's
broken into your car.
What?
Yeah, I'm sorry, ma'am,
you're going to have to come
with me.
Do you have any
identification?
I mean...
Ma'am.
I mean, how did you know
it was my car?
Well, what kind of a car
do you drive?
Green imperial.
I'm sorry, but that's
the one.
Fuck!
Mom's gonna kill me if
anything happened to that.
It's still locked.
It hasn't even been touched.
I'm afraid I'm going to
have to ask you to file a
report, ma'am.
But there is nothing to
report. Its fine.
Our sub-station's just
around the corner here.
This is so stupid!
You have, like, the wrong
car or something!
Its for your own
protection, ma'am.
Your station's back here?
Oh, it's a
substation, ma'am.
It's really just an office.
Our headquarters is a few
blocks from here.
Well, I hope it smells
better than this.
I assure you, ma'am,
it does.
We're just to the
right, here.
Damn, it's locked.
My partner must have already
taken the guy in.
What guy?
The one who broke into
your car.
But nobody broke into my
car, so
Sorry, ma'am, I'm going to
have to ask you to accompany
me to the station.
In this?
Its the dumbest looking cop
car I've ever seen.
It's a civilian car,
ma'am. Department
budget only goes
so far.
Oh, great.
The police station's not
over this way.
What the fuck are you
doing? Fuck!
What the fuck are you doing?
You son-of-a-bitch!
Kill you ... The fuck ...
Oh, fuck. Fuck.
I'm gonna fuckin'
kill you!
Don't fucking move or I
will blow your head off!
You hear me?
Yes.
Are you gonna be a good
little girl?
Yes.
Huh?
Yes!
Fuck.
Jesus.
Fucker!
Uuhh!
Fuck.
God!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Ted, don't mess around!
Ted, hit her in the head!
Bye.
See ya later.
Hey.
Oh, my God!
You scared me to death.
Here, let me get that
for you.
Oh, thank you.
That's so sweet.
Don't mention it.
Wow, you're just a kid,
aren't you?
No, I'm actually
almost eighteen.
I didn't mean to insult
you, it's just ... No,
forget it.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to sound like
such a bitch.
I just, you know, I don't
like when people say I'm
like some kind of baby or
anything.
That's okay, kid.
Forget it.
Boy, you're batting a
thousand, aren't you?
Look, I'm sorry.
Don't mean to be a jerk.
It's just that when I first
saw you, I got kinda
turned on.
But now that I can see how
young you are no offense
intended there either, but
well, let's just say that
I'm too old for you and
leave it at that.
Well, you may be too old
for me, but that still
doesn't make me a kid.
Good point.
Another one?
All right.
Oh, boy, look at this!
Oh, is it a boy or girl?
It's a girl.
We know.
You must have been a
really good girl for Santa
to bring you all
these presents.
Uh-huh, I was.
Okay, well, let's see
what's next.
Why don't you try this one?
Oh, my gosh!
We know.
Just what you needed!
Thank you!
You're welcome.
Hello?
Jesus mister. What is
it, your heart or
something?
(siren)
Hey, I'm sorry, officer-
You stop right there
I didn't see you back-
Now!
Put your hands above
your head!
Okay.
No problem.
Turn around!
Put your hands on your head.
All right.
Okay. You don't
need to explain
the law to me.
I-I go to law school.
Yeah we checked that
out, and you sure do.
And I worked on the
"Thompson for governor"
campaign. You
can ask him about me.
A law student active
in politics.
But what's a groovy guy like
you driving around with a
rape kit in his car?
Look, I told you, it's not
a rape kit.
I can explain to you every
single thing you found
in there.
I don't know, Ted.
A nylon stocking mask with
eye slits, a hacksaw, a
crowbar with duct tape
around the handle, a knife,
a rope, handcuffs.
Lock-picking tools?
So far you haven't
explained anything.
I think I've explained
things pretty well.
Well, let me ask you
something else, okay, Ted?
Look, it's your show.
Dig it.
Knock yourself out.
Great.
So, urn, you ever hear of a
girl named Tina Gabler?
No.
Well, that's funny.
She saw your picture and she
insists that you're the guy
that tried to kidnap her
from the mall the couple of
months ago.
Well, she's wrong.
Well, you wouldn't mind
standing in a lineup then,
would you?
You're wasting your time,
but if it'll make you happy,
go ahead.
Look, why don't we get
back to that stuff later?
I'm going to read you a list
of names and see if any of
them ring a bell, okay?
Look-
Just shut up.
Okay, Ted, listen.
Barbara Vincennes, Karen
Stills, Suzanne Welch,
Karen Parks?
Brenda Ball?
Patricia Garber?
Miriam Cutler?
Shawn Randall?
Lucy Lee?
Melissa Smith?
Wendy Fit?
Anita Mintier?
Stephanie Merkson?
Ellen Carter?
Betsy Walter?
Lynn Adams?
You never heard of any of
these women?
Look, I don't like the
tone of your voice.
This interview's over.
My dearest Lee.
I feel my heart is going to
break as I write
this letter.
Here I sit in a cage like
some kind of animal.
So much for the humanity
of mankind.
The so-called authorities
are continuing to persecute
me, even though their case
is a total joke.
They act like I'm supposed
to be remorseful, even
though I've done nothing to
feel remorseful for.
Maybe its all for the better
'cause it makes me
appreciate our love all
the more.
For even if I'm locked in a
cage, I think of the love
that we have and I am able
to be free, if only for
a moment.
I know I haven't always
treated you the way you
deserve, but I'm only a man
and sometimes it's just
so hard.
But all that melts in the
face of the love as strong
as the love I feel for you.
Ever lovin', Ted.
(sobs.)
I want to talk to
you about something.
Sure.
Please don't think that
I'm trying to add to your
problems here okay?
I mean, I know you've got a
lot on your mind lately.
Okay?
And-and the years that we've
been together, I have been
completely faithful to you,
an honor that I know you
haven't always reciprocated.
Even here in prison, I've
been willing to give you the
benefit of the doubt.
But when I hear on TV that
you've got some girlfriend
coming visiting you, that's
when I have to ask myself
what am I doing here?
Is that what this
is about?
Look, Lee, that woman is
working for me.
She's trying to get me
outta here.
I'm in prison, for
Christ's sake.
I can't control what they
say on TV.
Lee, honey-
No!
No more 'Lee, honey'!
Now you tell me right now,
is that woman your
girlfriend?
No. You're
my girlfriend, Lee.
Now there's something I need
to tell you.
Okay.
I'm being charged again.
What?
For some girl's murder.
Some girl?
Yeah, but their case is
totally weak.
They will never get a
conviction.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. No.
Lee...
Lee!
Get me outta here.
Lee.
Theodore Robert Bundy
was taken from his cell in
Colorado state prison and
brought to Aspen, where he
will stand trial for the
murder of Terry Bell whom
authorities claim was
abducted from the Pinewood
ski resort last Christmas.
All right, Ted, las get
these chains off you buddy.
All right, Randy. Thanks.
You seem kind of excited
this morning.
Cooking up something for
your defense, huh?
Yeah, I got a few ideas.
Lets get the legs off
real quick.
Hey, Randy.
Yeah, Ted, what's
goin' on?
Why do women wear makeup
and use perfume?
I don't know.
Why, Ted?
Because they're ugly and
they stink.
For your sake, I sure
hope you've thought this
through.
You know the old saying:
An attorney that represents
himself has a fool for
a client
Yeah, that's what
I've heard.
Thanks, man.
Good luck now buddy.
Thank you
Hey, Ted.
I'm gonna have a smoke in
the hall, okay?
Okay.
Bastard!
Bundy's loose!
I repeat, Bundy's loose!
Bundy jumped out of this
second story window at the
front of the Pitkin County
courthouse this morning.
Witnesses say he left in
a hurry.
However, nobody saw him open
the window.
And he escaped clean
in an unknown direction
(screams)
Oh, my God!
This is so terrible!
It's okay.
Oh, God.
How could I do it?
You didn't know.
How could I have ever
touched him?
Ssh.
It's okay.
Oh, my God!
Hi, Ted.
Welcome back.
Ooh.
Oh, God.
Oh, Ted.
If I didn't have this
visit to look forward to, I
think I'd go insane.
I-I tried to come last
week, but you know, with
Christmas and all, I just
couldn't find the time.
No, it's okay.
Did you get the money
I sent?
yeah. Thanks.
I'm going to pay you back.
I know you will.
Just as soon as we get you
out of this place.
Yeah.
We'll see. They
want to kill me.
What are you
talking about?
Who wants to kill you?
They're moving my trial to
Colorado Springs.
I don't understand
They're asking for the
death penalty.
They don't think they've got
justice unless they
kill somebody.
But their case is
so weak.
They framed me once, they
can frame me again
Okay, Bundy, wrap it up.
Okay.
Look, I'm sorry.
I haven't seen you in two
weeks, and here I am talking
about myself.
How are you?
How was Christmas
Oh, it was good.
I liked seeing my parents.
What they must think
of me.
Don't worry about it.
I'm here and I love
you, buddy.
And soon ... Very soon we're
going to be together, okay?
Yeah
Come on, Bundy.
Let's go
Whatever happens, just
know that I love you.
I love you.
Theodore Robert Bundy,
believed by authorities to
be the worst mass
murderer in U.S.
History, and who some
investigators are saying is
responsible for up to one
hundred and fifty brutal sex
murders throughout
the country.
Has escaped from custody for
the second time.
One detective familiar with
the case is warning the
public that Bundy should be
considered extremely
dangerous and that it's only
a matter of time before he
kills again.
Lord have mercy.
Listen, mister, whatever
you're selling, I
ain't buying.
I'm here about the ad in
the paper.
You still got that room
for rent?
No offense, but you don't
look like you'd know what to
do with a room if n you
had one.
I got money.
Right here.
Mama!
All right!
What the hell are you
carrying on about?
Mama, this here is...
Chris hagen.
Mama, this here's Chris.
And he'd like to rent
a room.
He gives me his word he
can pay
Hell, I'd give a dog the
best room in the house 'he
had the money to pay for
it. Cash.
Yes, ma'am.
You won't regret it.
Yeah.
And don't be botherin'
me anymore.
I couldn't believe it.
I mean, I know we haven't
been dating that long, but
I, at least, expect him to
buy me something
for Christmas.
He didn't give
you anything?
Sure he gave me
something.
The only thing he's been
trying to give me all
year long.
What are you
talking about?
You know what I mean.
No, I don't.
Tell you what, a few more
of those and I will just
tell you all about it, girl.
Good evening, ladies.
How would you like to help
me finish my pitcher
of beer?
We love being helpful
Great.
I'm Chris
Hi, Chris.
I'm Vicky.
This is my sister, Lara.
Sisters, huh?
Sorority sisters.
Right. So.
Obvious question I know,
but, uh ... What are
your majors?
You know, I haven't quite
decided yet.
Mine's pre-law.
Pre-law?
That's a total waste
of time.
What kind of thing is
that to say?
You know what?
I'm outta here.
Where are you going?
See ya.
I don't think your
sister likes me.
No, she's just not really
good in social situations.
She'll be all right.
So, are you a teacher here?
Yeah.
Yeah, I am.
If you'll excuse me.
No excuse.
Wasn't tonight fun?
Yes.
(knock at the door)
Come in!
Hey, what are you
guys doing?
What does it look like
we're doing?
Right.
I met the biggest creep at
the bar tonight.
Ooh.
Anyway, I just came to
say good night.
Okay.
Good night.
Good night, Lara!
See you tomorrow.
Asshole!
Jesus.
(screaming)
Some fucked up shit.
How you doin', Randy?
I tell you what, Chris,
its a crazy world we're
livin' in.
No argument there.
Hear about that psycho
last night?
Went and killed two girls
and then beat two others
half to death.
L-less than a mile
from here.
Yeah, I heard about that.
Why would somebody do a
thing like that for?
I wish I knew.
I mean, goddamn.
I guess some people are
just compelled to kill.
I'm compelled to hit my
mama over the head just
about everyday, but I don't
do it, goddamnit.
But still, you gotta
admire the guy who did it.
Get in there like that, have
his way with those girls,
and then get away.
Takes cunning.
And guts.
I ought to smack you in
the mouth for saying
something like that!
I'm just saying, man-
Aw, fuck you!
You're right, Randy.
Fuck me.
Hey, little girl, what's
your name?
Suzanne.
Suzanne, there's a -
there's been a bit of an
accident.
Your father's been hurt.
My dad?
Yeah.
He asked me to come get you.
Is he okay?
Where is he?
Uh, he's close to here.
Yeah, he's going to be okay.
Well, what happened?
Well, he had a little
accident, and here, why
don't you get in.
Is he okay?
Uh. Uh...Uh..
Fuck...Fuck
Aw... aw...
(yelling continues)
God.
She's dead.
Oh, I'm coming.
Please kill me.
It is further ordered
that on such scheduled date,
that you be put to death by
a current of electricity
sufficient to cause your
immediate death.
And such current of
electricity shall continue
to pass through your body
until you are dead.
I can tell you that
everything's moving ahead
with plans for the execution
at seven A.M.
Bundy was offered a last
meal about forty
minutes ago.
He was offered steak and
eggs, and he refused it.
Prison officials are now
preparing to shave his head
and prepare him for
execution at seven o'clock.
I would like to go right
in there and see him fry.
Burn
Ready for him to die.
Snap, crackle,
pop, buddy.
Justice- justice is
gonna be served at seven
o'clock, bud.
(crowd noise)
I-I don't want to die.
I'm not going to lie to you.
I admit that.
And I'm not asking
for clemency.
I'm not asking
for forgiveness.
I'm not asking for sympathy.
I know they're going to kill
me sooner or later.
Uh, you don't need to worry
about that.
But but there's a lot of
crimes I could solve if the
state could just see fit to
let me live for two or three
years longer.
I-I mean look, I know I'm
not like other people.
I know I can't feel sympathy
for other people.
But I'm still human.
And then I cut her head
off with the hacksaw, and I
took it home with me.
I mean, there's so much
more to me than this guy
that goes around doing those
crazy things.
I, so much more.
Yea, though I walk
through the valley of the
shadow of death, I will fear
no evil, for thou art
with me.
Thy rod and thy staff, they
comfort me.
Thou preparest a table
before me in the presence of
mine enemies.
Thou anointest my head
with oil.
My cup runneth over.
Surely, goodness and mercy
will follow me all the days
of my life, and I will dwell
in the house of the lord
forever and ever.
Amen, Ted.
Amen. Amen, Ted.
Hallelujah.
Hello, Ted.
Now you take it easy
now, Ted.
And just you just keep your
mind on Jesus.
It's time, Ted.
Come on out now.
Got a couple of things to
take care of.
Now, either you come out or
we'll come in and getcha.
Don't make us come in
there, Ted.
Come on.
Take it easy.
Take it easy now.
It's all right.
All right.
What's he doing?
Don't you worry about him.
Ted, listen to me,
okay? Listen.
I want you to stay real
still for me, all right?
Can you do that?
This okay, Uncle Bob?
Goddamnit, how long you
been practicing that?
All right.
You can go, Ted.
You're all done, okay?
You look beautiful.
What's that for?
That's to stuff your butt.
So you don't mess yourself.
What are you
talking about?
Ain't nothin' to be
ashamed of.
They all do it.
You will, too.
Now, drop them pants.
No.
Come on, Ted.
Don't make it any harder
than it is.
Come on, Ted.
No!
Come on.
No.
You relax now.
If you relax, it'll be a lot
easier okay?
Take it easy.
(yells)
Try to breathe.
Just try to breathe.
Is this okay Uncle Bob?
Yeah, that's good, Wesley.
Keep it comin'.
Aaw!
Feels good, doesn't it?
Boy. Oh, got
cotton balls.
Oh, no!
Just relax
More, Uncle Bob
Just like that, boy.
Stop!
Oh, God!
Come on now.
We're gonna stand up now.
Come on.
You're all right.
Just breathe deep.
Breathe deep.
All right now, son.
Come on now.
Stand up.
Hold on.
We got one more little
itty-bitty thing to do now.
It's for your own
good, Ted.
Good.
That's a good boy.
That's a good boy, huh?
Now, you ready?
We don't want to keep your
fans waitin', do we?
Come on.
Theodore Robert Bundy,
do you have a final
statement you'd like to make
before the sentence of the
court is carried out?
Yes.
Tell my family I love them.
Tell them...
Authorities said that
Bundy spent the night
weeping and praying.
Then, at seven A.M., he was
moved to the electric chair.
That's it.
(cheers)
Theodore Bundy was
executed at seven-sixteen
this morning in the electric
chair at
Florida state prison.
He was executed for the
murder of twelve-year-old
Kimberly Leach of
Lake City, Florida.
You know he was also under
sentence of death for the
murder of two young women
in Tallahassee.
Everything was, uh, carried
out according to the book.
What will happen to
the body?
The body will be taken
to a - a funeral home
in Gainesville.
Finally.
I can't believe it.
I was with him for years.
But I never knew him.
I never knew him at all.
Who was that guy?
Who was Ted Bundy?
I'm Ted Bundy.