Wait.
Lucy, what is it?
What happened?
I, I, I can't do it, Grandma.
What?
I'm not good enough to be Clara.
Wait a minute.
You got a callback.
That's just because
of who you are.
Who told you that?
One of the other girls.
Well, that is nonsense.
You got here on your own, okay?
All right. All right.
How long until your group?
They said about
an hour and a half.
Okay. Come on.
I want to show you something.
What is all this?
This is all Rockettes history.
All of these ladies were
superstars; actually,
they still are.
But I want to tell
you something.
I think that the biggest star
in this whole place will be you.
But I know how much
it would mean to you
if I got to be Clara.
- Oh.
- I just,
I just don't want you to be
disappointed if I'm not picked.
The only thing that
would really disappoint me
is if you didn't try.
One of the best things in life
comes when you're really
scared to do something
but you do it anyway.
Were you scared
when you auditioned?
No.
But boy, when they said
yes, I was terrified.
But of course then I, uh,
I had a lot more to lose.
You know what?
I think that you're
old enough now
to hear the entire story.
While my family was
busy getting ready
to host the most lavish
Thanksgiving dinner in Philadelphia,
I turned on the TV and
what I saw changed my life.
It was the first year that
the Rockettes ever performed
at the parade,
and I was absolutely mesmerized.
I wished so badly that
I could be one of them.
I knew my family
would never approve.
Why not?
Well,
my future was already
all mapped out for me,
and it had nothing
to do with dancing.
Is that real gold, Mother?
Oh, don't be
ridiculous, Margaret.
It's gold leaf.
Perhaps we should just
dip the entire invitation
into diamond dust.
Oh, is that an option?
I wasn't serious.
Well, I am serious.
You're our only child,
and we are doing
this to the nines.
I'm sure you could
just do it to the sixes
and be perfectly fine.
What's Maxwell's middle name?
I haven't the
faintest idea, Mother.
I also don't know
his favorite book,
color, food,
what inspires him,
what brings him joy.
You'll learn all
of that in time.
Shouldn't I already know
the man I'm marrying in April?
All you need to know is
that Maxwell is a good man
and he comes from a wonderful
Philadelphia family.
Everyone agrees it's
a perfect match.
Good morning, dear.
As soon as Maxwell
arrives, we'll start brunch.
Oh, there he is!
Hello, my darling.
You look stunning
today as always.
How are the wedding
plans coming along?
Swimmingly.
Is that gold leaf.
Very nice.
My parents send the
regards, by the way.
Father has a polo match at
Brandywine this afternoon.
Oh.
We really should go
and see him play.
Wouldn't that be a
fine time, Margaret?
Maxwell, can I
ask you a question?
Of course.
What brings you true joy?
What really makes you happy?
Margaret,
we were talking about polo.
How about polo then?
Does polo make you happy?
You make me happy.
Thank you.
That's very nice.
What's my middle name?
Maury?
Mary.
It's Marie.
Ah, as in Antoinette.
Maxwell, you must tell us
about your father's new horse.
Didn't you pick it up
at the Devon Horse Show
over the summer?
- Yes, we did.
- A five, six, seven and eight
A one and a two, a three,
a four, a five and a six,
a seven and eight.
A one, two, three, four,
a five, a six, a
seven and eight.
A one and a two, and a three,
a four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, a three, a four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Oh, bravo, ladies!
Bravo!
Margaret, you were in
fantastic form as always.
Thank you.
Oh, before go,
I want to tell you about an
exciting last-minute audition
this afternoon.
Come on.
The Rockettes are all
you've talked about
since last Thanksgiving.
And if I get cast, then what?
I move to New York
for two months?
It's preposterous.
Well, I'm definitely
not going to get cast.
But it's a great way to
get audition experience.
And I don't want
to go on my own.
Just come with me, please.
Okay.
For curiosity's sake, I'll go.
Number 32, number
154, thank you.
Congratulations,
Margaret Bennett.
We've been searching for three
new dancers for this season,
and you got the last spot.
See you November 1st.
Was that a blast or what?
Now you know you
were good enough
even though you
can't actually do it.
Can you imagine
leaving Philadelphia
in the middle of planning
the biggest Main Line wedding
in years?
Not to mention the fact your
family would never allow it.
You are going to tell
them no, aren't you?
Margaret,
where have you been?
I thought your class
ended hours ago.
I've been thinking
about the wedding
and how I still haven't
found the perfect dress,
so I went to the bridal salon
to see if they had anything new.
And did they?
Nothing at all.
So I was thinking,
why don't I go to New York and
meet with Gabriella Monroe?
Margaret,
I have tried every
connection I have in the city
to get an appointment with her.
She is booked
through the summer.
Well, I have another connection.
You do? Who?
Remember my friend Kitty
from summer camp in Maine?
She's Gabriella's niece.
Well, she said her aunt
could see me on November 1st.
That's wonderful.
Oh, and of course
I'll go with you.
No.
I'd like to go on my own.
No, I'm not comfortable
with you being in the city
by yourself, young lady.
I'll stay with Kitty.
Her husband just bought a
penthouse on Central Park.
Oh, she married well.
She must be on cloud nine.
I'm sure she is.
Margaret, you're here!
Kitty!
Oh!
Are you sure you're
okay with this?
Of course.
This is just like "It
Happened One Night."
You're like Claudette Colbert,
running away from
her wealthy family
to follow her dream.
I'm not running away.
I'm having one last
pre-wedding adventure
that no one in my family
can ever know about.
Ooh, I should probably
get to my new apartment.
You're not even staying with me?
The Rockettes have us
in an all women's building
at West 52nd and 8th,
just a few blocks
from Radio City.
How brave?
What do you mean?
I just mean it's a
different lifestyle
than you're used to.
Oh, I'm sure it's lovely.
So that's just south
of here, right?
Is it walking distance?
Not, not with all that luggage.
Let's get you a cab.
Oh.
Remember, if my
parents or Maxwell call-
I'll tell them
they can reach you
at Radio City Music Hall.
Kitty!
Don't worry, Margaret.
I'll tell them you're
wedding shopping,
which we will do
together, won't we?
Of course.
Now, Lillian,
this year please
try to remember,
the 10 o'clock curfew
is not a suggestion,
it's a rule.
A young woman can't be seen
gallivanting around town
at all hours, understood?
Of course, Rose.
You, boys, you're loitering.
Go on now.
Shoo! Shoo!
Could you possibly take
those up to my room for me?
Uh, they're quite heavy and
I'm on the fourth floor.
Ooh, I'll just wait for
the doorman, I suppose.
Oh!
Hey!
Is that a handbag
or a Billy club?
I'm terribly sorry,
I didn't see you there.
Are you hurt?
It takes a lot more than
a weaponized accessory
to hurt a Navy man.
I'm curious.
Why does the Navy have you
taking pictures of a lamppost?
I'm on leave.
And if you really want to know,
I'm taking a shot of the
tinsel on the streetlight.
The little bit there.
I saw it and thought about how
it's probably been up there
the entire year,
just hanging on for dear life,
waiting for the
rest of its friends
to come back for Christmas.
I think my thought
would've been,
"Someone didn't do a very good
job cleaning up in January."
Well, I guess it just
depends on how you look at things.
Can I help you with those?
Oh, no.
I'm just waiting
for the doorman.
We don't have doormen
or any men in this
building, for that matter.
Of course you'll find
more than a few gentlemen
happen upon this
apartment building
looking for romance.
Oh.
Not interested, thank you.
I really
was just taking pictures.
Is that so?
I'm a photographer, ma'am.
I thought you said
you were in the Navy.
Oh, the Navy has photographers.
I take pictures all around
the ship, the bases,
everywhere the Navy goes.
There are no ships
on West 52nd, sailor.
Move on!
Have a nice day, ma'am.
Miss.
I'm Rose, the apartment manager.
Margaret Bennett, I'm new.
No kidding, Maggie.
I'll help with your bags.
Hi.
Excuse me.
What do you think?
This will do just fine.
♪ Santa baby, got
a gift for me ♪
But it isn't very
private, is it?
No, because this
is the common room.
This is your room.
I don't get my own room.
I could pay extra.
How much more would
that be weekly? I...
Oh, I spent most of my cash in
the dining car on the train.
There was the most
gorgeous shrimp cocktail.
Anyway, I'm sure we
could work something out.
Oh, it's nothing to do
with the money, dear.
First years are at the
bottom of the wait list.
- Oh.
- Good luck, dear.
What am I doing?
You're helping me decorate
for Christmas, that's what.
But it's not even
Thanksgiving yet.
Oh, what can I say?
I'm festive.
Here, sit over there.
I'm Sofia Gagliardi, by the way.
And one thing you should know
about me is I talk a lot.
So if we're going to be friends,
you got to tell me if
I'm talking too much
or else I'll just keep talking
and talking and talking.
And I'm doing it right now,
and I can't believe you
didn't say anything.
I'm sorry.
I'm Marg...
Maggie Bennett
from Philadelphia.
Love Philly.
Oh, Liberty Bell, cheese steaks,
Ben Franklin.
Am I forgetting anything?
No, that's pretty much it.
Where are you from?
Bensonhurst.
Brooklyn.
I changed my mind,
I'll finish this later.
You got to change clothes.
We got to be at Radio
City in 20 minutes,
and you're wearing a dress
like we're going to the theater
instead of going to the theater,
if you know what I mean.
Wow, that's some nifty luggage.
Oh, they're just hand-me-downs.
From who? Grace Kelly?
So what bag's your pants in?
Oh, I don't usually wear
pants when I'm going out.
Again, you're not going out.
You're walking to work.
You can borrow a pair from me.
There you go.
Thank you.
And that.
Just go back there.
Chicken parm.
My cousin brought it over
from his restaurant
on Mulberry Street.
It's 10 in the morning.
We rehearse six hours
a day, six days a week.
And then we do two shows a
day for a month straight.
That's a thousand high
kicks a day, Maggie.
You never know when you might
need a late night snack.
Isn't there a dining
room downstairs?
There is, but it's
always good to have backup.
That's better.
Oh good.
You two met.
You must be Margaret.
Maggie's fine.
I'm Alice, resident
advisor for the rookies.
Any problems, any
questions, you come to me.
I'm right here on
the fourth floor.
How many years have
you been a Rockette?
This is my 10th year.
Wow, I hope I
can last that long.
Oh, I'd do it
forever if I could.
So we are missing
one girl. Janet.
She's in 4C.
Oh, let's go say hello.
Come on.
Want to come spruce up our room?
Not particularly.
Righto. Moving on.
I'm Sofia, this is Maggie.
I'm a bit of a talker, so you-
I'm going to stop
you right there.
No need to trade life stories.
Suit yourself.
How come she gets her own room?
There are three new
girls and two rooms.
The early bird catches the worm.
For the record, I believe
I got here before you did.
Did you?
I'm sure I would have heard you.
So, Janet, where are you from.
Cleveland.
Again, don't take
this the wrong way,
but I'm not here
to make friends.
Is there a right
way to take that?
I'm here to make
a name for myself.
First stop, Rockettes;
next stop, Broadway.
You're going to want
to make friends, Janet.
It's one of the best parts
about being a Rockette.
We take care of each other.
We're like sisters.
I already have three sisters,
I don't need anymore.
Well, I think it's wonderful.
I've always wanted a sister.
How about you, Sofia?
You know, we should split.
We don't want to be late for
our first rehearsal, right?
Where is everybody?
There you are.
You were supposed to
come through the back.
Come this way.
We'll just go through here.
Don't be nervous.
Going to be an exciting day. ts
Hi, I'm Lillian.
Welcome to the Rockettes.
I'm Peggy.
And we were all in
your shoes once.
And there are a lot of shoes.
So many shoes.
But don't worry.
After your first season,
they'll be completely broken in.
The shoes or us?
Both.
All right, ladies.
Let's shake some of
that rust off, shall we?
Basic eye-high kick line
starting on your
stage right angle.
And a five, six, seven, eight.
A one, two, three, four,
five, six seven, eight.
A one, two.
Remember, your toe to your eye
every single time.
Six, seven, eight.
That's it.
Effortless.
Yes.
You'll be right there
alongside them soon enough.
Come on, we got to get
you up to wardrobe, hmm?
These are wonderful
and heavy.
Are you okay, Grandma?
Mm.
I don't think it really
hit me until that moment.
I was a Rockette.
And a split second later,
we were more
nervous than before.
Thank goodness we had Alice.
It's okay, ladies.
Drink a lot of
water, stay focused;
and most importantly,
have a ball.
You get to dance with
your best friends.
Day in and day out,
we're here for each other.
That's what makes
what we do so special.
All right.
Remember your spacing.
A one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven and eight.
Then one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Again.
A one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
You can do better.
Again.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven and eight.
A one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Almost.
One more time.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven and eight.
And one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
That's it!
Now, let's do that
100 more times.
Hey, I'm going easy on you
since it's your first day.
That was going easy on us?
Oh, I can't walk anymore.
I need a rest or a sandwich.
I know a good market a couple
blocks down with a deli.
A couple blocks?
Oh, come on.
We can do it.
I'm telling you,
Harriet, it's too early.
Oh, Robert,
it's never too early to
decorate for Christmas.
I think you'd put up
decorations in August
if I said yes.
Hey, knock it off.
We're not paying you
to take pictures.
You're not paying me at all.
Is that why you haven't
been to the barber?
It's called paying
your dues, son.
I did it, you are doing it,
and someday your kids will too.
First he'd ave to find a girl
he loves more than that camera.
Can it, Cuz.
Just calling it like I see it.
Ha! Hello, ladies.
Is there something
we can help you with?
We're just here to
pick up some sandwiches.
Oh, careful,
that one's got a handbag
and she's not afraid to use it.
Oh, it's you?
It is indeed I,
me.
You know each other?
Unofficially.
Then let's fix that.
I, I'm John.
And?
And, and you are?
I'm going to get some fruit.
Uh, can I help
you find anything?
Just the aforementioned fruit.
- Yeah.
- There it is.
Uh, the Jonagold apples are new.
Perfect for hot cider or
cold, uh, your choice.
Duly noted.
Uh, just to clarify,
this is my parents' store.
I, I, I work here.
I'm not just
following you around
trying to show off my
knowledge of seasonal produce.
And what about
Navy photographer?
Oh, oh, that too, until July.
And then a career in
high pressure fruit sales?
And then, uh,
I'm thinking of applying to NYU
to get a visual arts degree
and then start a career
as a photojournalist.
Well, I think that's
a wonderful idea.
NYU is a great-
Anyway, if you have
any more questions
about apples or anything else,
I'm your guy.
I'll keep that in mind.
I think I just might
need a sandwich every day
if it means looking in
those please eyes again.
I thought his eyes were brown.
I was talking about
the guy in a deli.
Who did you think I meant?
Oh, no one.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm spoken for back home.
It took you an entire
day to mention that?
I'm just here to dance,
let's focus on that.
We're still waiting!
Hello?
We're still out here!
That's it, I'm going in.
Woo! Oh!
Oh.
I didn't realize
anyone was waiting.
Woo! Oh!
You used all the hot water!
You can run out of hot water?
Make sure your heads
are back on count five.
And just feel the fabric.
Don't hold onto each other, hmm?
You have exactly 78 seconds
to change from "Wooden Soldier"
costume to "Times Square,"
and that is the transition
that we are going to work
on for the rest of the day.
Positions.
And go.
All right, ladies.
All right.
Right gloves.
Zippers.
I got you.
Janet!
Five seconds!
Well,
almost all of you made it.
Now, just try it without looking
like you were run over
by Santa's sleigh.
To hear you're getting onisd
so well in the city.
Oh yes, I love it.
Kitty has invited me to all
sorts of wonderful lunches
and cocktail parties.
I'm meeting oodles
of important people,
people who could do business
with Father and
Maxwell's family.
Oh, how very
clever of your, dear.
In fact,
it's going so well I think I
should stay on a little longer.
Oh.
How long?
At least two weeks,
if that's all right with you.
Of course it's okay.
You're doing this
for your future.
What are you doing here?
Come with me.
Where are we going?
To get dessert and
talk, in that order.
See the way you're
all looking at me?
That's why I didn't
want to say anything.
I thought maybe
you came from money,
but I didn't think
you came from money
with a capital M.
I need you to
understand, I'm not rich,
my parents are.
And there's no point in
getting everyone all riled up,
I'm only here for one season.
And while I'm here,
I'm on my own.
Sure you are.
Until things get hard, right?
Then you can go right
back to your real life.
This is the most real
thing I've ever done.
I'm just saying it must be
nice to have a safety net.
I have one more
thing to ask you,
it's very important.
Can I borrow that red coat
now that I know
that it's designer?
Of course.
You would have loved this.
Are you okay?
Of course.
You?
You have a sister?
Had.
A twin, actually.
She died a few years ago.
Being a Rockette was
our dream together.
The only thing that
was different about us
was I didn't have
a hole in my heart,
but now I do.
I'm so sorry, Sofia.
It must be so hard
being here without her.
I can't let it be hard, though.
I know if I fall apart,
my whole family will.
And I have to be
strong for everyone.
You don't have to do
that for us, though.
Remember what Mr.
Matthews and Alice said?
We're family now.
So far that's
been the best part.
Now, come on, let me help
you with that laundry.
Something tells me
you had somebody else
do this for you before.
Alice.
What is this?
Your paycheck.
But it's probably
pocket change to you.
Actually, I don't have
any of my own money left,
so this means everything.
I really like that green coat.
I like it when you wear
your green coat red
and I wear my red coat.
And then we just-
And then we look
like Christmas?
We look like Christmas.
After Thanksgiving?
Yeah.
You really have to
stop following me.
Sofia and I were just
doing a little shopping.
Well, if you need me,
I'll be in the shoe department
asking Santa for a pair
of two-tone Chanel pumps.
Looking for something specific?
I'm not sure what
I'm looking for.
Do you want to go inside?
Oh, not again.
I'm terribly sorry.
If it turns out
you're really a hitman,
you're not very good at it.
Excuse me.
Could I see this pin?
♪ And a happy New Year ♪
This is beautiful.
I'll take it.
If you like, you
can put it on layaway
until Christmas Eve.
You put a little
toward it every week
until you've got
enough to buy it.
Oh, layaway.
Of course.
But I'm only here until
Christmas, is that enough time?
It depends on how
much you put in?
You're not staying in New York?
I'm only dancing the one season.
Thank you.
♪ To you and your kin ♪
♪ We wish you a
merry Christmas ♪
Christmas is always perfect
in this little town, isn't it?
Yeah.
But it's pretty close to
perfect right here too.
I should probably tell you.
There's somebody waiting
for me back home.
You don't need to tell me that.
I don't?
I'm leaving soon, too, remember?
And then NYU.
If I had it my way, yes.
I'd be learning from
the best of the best.
Every class is taught
by photographers
who have won Pulitzers
or have their work on the
cover of "National Geographic"
or the front page
at the "Times."
It sounds like the
opportunity of a lifetime.
Not if you ask my folks.
If they knew I
wanted to do anything
other than take over the store,
they'd think I'm
abandoning them.
But you're not.
You're following your dream.
Imagine how much you'll regret
it if you don't even try.
I might not even get in.
Then you take a different path.
It's not always that simple.
What would you have done
if you didn't get
cast in the show?
I'd find a way to keep dancing.
But it wouldn't be like this.
In my wildest dreams
I didn't think my life
could ever be like this.
Yet here you are.
Here I am.
I should probably go find Sofia.
Oh, right.
Of course.
So I'll see you
around the neighborhood?
Just warn me when you're nearby
so I can put on a helmet.
Janet, you have to
rock up on your heels
and make sure you have control
of the girl in front of you.
- I'm trying.
- Good.
Just open your arms so the
girl behind you can follow.
Okay, everyone,
attention please.
The "Christmas Spectacular"
opens in four days.
But before that,
some of you will be dancing
in the Thanksgiving Day parade.
Don't you want
to see who got in?
I know we didn't.
Only half the girls
perform, and we're new.
Actually, a lot of
the veteran dancers
go home for Thanksgiving.
There we are!
Alice, you're not spending
Thanksgiving with your family?
This is my family.
I'm curious.
What does your family
think you're doing?
They think I'm in the
Hamptons with Kitty and her cousins.
What if they see you on TV?
They won't.
I'm the only one who
ever watches the parade.
So everybody won't get along.
Back for
their second year in a row,
here are the world famous
Radio City Music Hall Rockettes
now celebrating
their 33rd season.
That's Sofia.
Man-
The Rockettes
have been high kicking and-
She's something, isn't she?
Since 1925.
She's incredible.
Look at these
talented ladies having a ball.
I still think we
should have insisted
Margaret come home for
Thanksgiving dinner.
Oh, she's hobnobbing with
New York's elite, dear.
She's doing it for the family.
I suppose you're right.
Dessert party, fourth floor.
You coming?
Actually, I think
I'll take a walk.
I want to take in as much
of the city as I can.
Who knows if I'll ever be
here on Thanksgiving again?
- Oh, I'm so sorry, Miss.
- Excuse-
I suppose we're even then.
Well played, sir.
You think I plotted my revenge
on the off chance
you'd be wandering
the Christmas tree lot
three blocks from your
apartment on Thanksgiving night?
Maybe.
Okay, son, were paid up.
Oh, Pops, this is Maggie.
She's one of the new
Rockettes this year.
Oh.
Nice to meet you, young lady.
Nice to meet you.
Let's get this
tree back to market.
Gimme a minute, and I'll help.
What?
You don't think we
can carry a tree.
We're not that old.
You stay.
All right.
So can I help you
pick out a tree?
There's one.
Oh, there's another one.
We don't really have room
for a tree on our floor.
You got to have
a tree somewhere.
We are living and
breathing Christmas
all day at the theater.
I think we're covered.
I was actually just going on a
Christmas-in-New-York stroll.
I want to take in as
much of the city as I can
while I'm still here.
You shouldn't be walking
around the city alone at night.
I'd be happy to take you around,
purely for safety reasons.
That's all?
Well, it can't be
more than that, right?
No.
Just friends.
Then yes.
It's for safety.
Two, please.
Do you have pecans?
I just don't think anyone
actually likes chestnuts, is all.
It's a New York City
Christmas tradition.
Also, the song isn't:
♪ Pecans roasting
on an open fire ♪
Wait, hang on.
You love chestnuts.
You always say
they're your favorite.
Hmm, that's because
of what happened next.
It's so beautiful.
The only thing missing
is a little snow.
I can make that happen.
How in the world
did you do that?
I can always sense
when it's about to snow.
It's a special talent of mine.
Oh.
Mine's knowing when someone's
not telling the truth.
All right, fine.
It was dumb luck.
Oh, by the way,
you were wonderful in
the parade this morning.
Thank you.
I love how people react to
the first few flakes of snow.
It's like they're kids again.
You can see it in their face.
What?
You see things
other people don't,
that's your real special skill.
I think it's what makes
you a great photographer.
Very impressive.
How did you get
him to play that?
I promised him a
pair of my house seats.
Oh.
Already bartering
with the vendors.
You really are
becoming a New Yorker.
Don't you have friends and
family who want to use 'em.
I'm sure they're
so proud of you.
I'd like to think so.
You don't always have
to take pictures.
You can join in the fun.
Ah, no.
I'm not much of a dancer.
Well, I am.
And I don't want to miss
out on any Christmas magic.
Come on.
All right. Okay.
But I apologize in advance
for when I step on your toes.
Oh no.
What time is it?
Oh no, I'm going to miss curfew.
I have to go,
but thank you for the
company and the dance
and everything.
Anytime.
I mean that.
♪ ♪
Wonderful show, ladies.
1 down, 99 to go.
That's so many.
I'm so glad we only had to
do the first two shows today.
We finally have the evening off.
What shall we do?
How about we grab a bite?
Okay. Where?
You know where.
Okay, missy,
it's been a week since
your little evening stroll
with a certain Navy man.
Something happened and
you haven't said a word.
Time to let the
cat out of the bag.
There is no cat.
Please.
It's a lion.
Talk.
We just ran into each other.
We're friends, that's all.
I don't look at my
friends like that.
What are you doing here?
You said you didn't have a tree
so brought you a tree.
Oh, well, uh,
Ben and I.
What's this?
A Christmas tree.
Thanks. But I'm Jewish.
Rose, what do you say?
Can they bring it in?
No men allowed.
What about delivery men?
I can throw in a
sandwich, make it legit.
Corned beef?
Of course.
Extra lean.
I guess a little holiday
spirit never hurt anyone.
Common room, only you two.
No shenanigans.
Oh, that one's really pretty.
- Right?
- Yeah, I like that one.
I like this
one, the texture of it.
Janet, don't you want to help?
I need to rest.
Come on.
It's fine.
Struffoli?
I asked around,
got a recipe from a friend
of a friend in Little Italy.
This is the best Christmas ever.
I'm not sure your fella at
home would like to hear that.
I'm not sure he'd even ask.
What's your favorite color?
Blue, why?
Middle name?
Alan.
And what brings
you the most joy?
Why all the questions?
Just humor me.
Okay.
I'll show you.
I just got these developed.
The last few were my favorite.
This is unlike any
photo I've ever been in.
My family usually
sits posed, formal.
I've never seen myself
like this before.
It's how I saw you from
the second I met you.
You are very talented.
Have your parents seen these?
Not yet.
What are you waiting for?
Then they'll understand
why you want this
to be your future.
You owe it to them, to yourself.
I know, but it's going
to break their hearts.
Just waiting for the right time.
Maybe the right time is now.
Hm.
When I go home after Christmas,
things are going to change.
Haven't they already?
Okay.
We're all set.
Who wants to do the honors?
I think Janet should do it.
Janet!
You've got it.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
Are you okay, Alice?
Yes, I'm fine.
You don't look fine.
You know, I've been
dancing since I could walk.
I thought I'd be able
to do this forever.
And now it's time to start
thinking about what's next.
And I don't know what that is.
Dearest Mother and Father:
All is well on the
Upper East Side.
I've made some
wonderful new friends,
and every night we're dressed
in the most glittering
dresses you can imagine.
I'm really making a mark here.
Did you see me almost fall?
Oh, no one noticed...
We were all mesmerized at
Santa trying to do a high kick.
Margaret, you were wonderful.
Kitty!
Just give a minute.
Margaret?
Ah, I didn't realize
you were coming tonight.
I wanted to surprise you.
I had no idea how
talented you are.
You have to tell your
family about this.
They'll understand once
they see you up there.
No, they won't.
Just please don't say anything
until after the show is over,
then I'll take
care of everything.
It's getting harder
to cover for you.
I'll buy time.
I'll tell Mother your aunt's
still on the design phase.
Oh, for goodness' sake.
You haven't even met
my Aunt Gabriella.
You are still getting
married, aren't you?
Of course I am.
I'll make an appointment
for next week.
Good.
Now, where should we get drinks?
I can't go out, Kitty.
I'm going home and
straight to bed.
We have an early
performance tomorrow.
Well, then I guess
I see you next time
you need to use my phone
or collect your mail
or need help lying to your
fiance and your family.
I'm sorry, Kitty.
It's more complicated than
I thought it would be.
Are you going to say
anything to them?
No.
But you should.
You owe them the truth.
Are you okay?
No.
I don't know why I thought
I could pull this off.
What was I thinking?
This isn't me.
I don't even know
who I am anymore.
Well, one thing's for sure.
You're definitely not Margaret.
- Let's go.
Okay.
Places, ladies.
Yeah!
Wow.
Hey.
Oh, you were incredible, Maggie,
just stunning.
Yeah.
I'm not one for dancing,
but that was pretty great.
Thank you.
I didn't realize you
were coming tonight.
Well, we wanted to surprise you,
but I think you
surprised me even more.
And you were wonderful.
I'm glad you liked it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just have a lot of my mind.
I have another show to do soon
so I have to go back
inside and get ready.
We should get back
to the market, son.
I want to show you how
we close out the books
at the end of the year.
All right.
Congratulations, Maggie.
Thank you.
So you haven't told them?
No, but before you say anything,
I know it's not fair to leave
them in the dark like this.
But if I don't get in NYU,
then there's nothing
to tell them.
I'll be working at the
store just like they wanted.
So that's it?
Either you give in or you
give up on your dream?
If you really wanted this,
you'd find a way
to make it happen.
You're right.
I do.
And seeing you up there
makes me even more determined
to make my dreams come true,
just like you.
You'll never guess
who's on the roll
call list for tonight.
Frankie Avalon.
How'd you know?
Wait.
It really is Frank-
He's coming.
I am going to make
him fall in love with me
from the stage.
Oh, what about your
boyfriend back home?
Hey, until there's
a ring on my finger,
all bets are off.
Good thing you aren't
engaged to Maxwell, huh?
Why do you say that?
You know why?
Actually, no.
I don't know why you keep
pushing this John thing.
Right now I'm focused
on the show, that's all.
Please, I see the
way you look at him.
I look at Ben the same way.
And you never look like that
when you talk about Maxwell,
which, by the way,
is almost never.
That's not love.
I didn't come here for love.
Maybe it's one of the
reasons you should stay.
How are your parents?
They're fine.
You will be home for the
Christmas party, won't you?
It's practically the same
guest list as our wedding.
Oh, and be sure to
stop at Tiffany's first
and pick yourself out
on a nice present.
You mean a present from you?
You know what you like
much more than I do.
I don't want to
disappoint you, darling.
So I'll see you in two weeks.
Of course.
Well, goodbye then.
Goodbye.
Maggie, would you go out
there and talk to your friend?
He's been circling
the block all day
like like Freddy Eynsford-Hill.
I didn't see anyone.
Hello?
Oh, what a coincidence.
I just happened to be walking by
and here you are.
Rose said you've been
hanging around all day.
Yeah, I didn't say how
many times I walked by.
I know this show
is dark tonight.
And you said you hadn't gone
to see the Rockefeller
Center tree yet.
And I wanted to take
some more photos there
before I send off my portfolio,
so I thought maybe
we could go together.
Unless you already went.
No.
Even though it's so
close to the theater,
we always had a show, or curfew,
until tonight.
Then I guess it's fate.
It just might be.
But it's so complicated, John,
for both of us.
The timing-
Is all wrong.
I know.
I'm not asking for anything more
than one more stroll
with a friend.
Are you okay?
I will be.
I suppose you want to
take a picture of me
having this big
emotional moment.
No.
This one's just for us.
You know I can't.
I know.
But whatever happens,
and wherever we end up,
we can always close our eyes
and be right back here.
What if I don't want
to just imagine it?
Then I guess you have
a decision to make.
There you are.
I thought I was going to have
to send down a
knotted sheet for you
in case Rose locked the doors.
Where were you?
I was on a walk with John.
Did John give you that?
Of course not.
Maxwell did.
What? When?
About a year ago.
Wait a minute.
So this whole time
you've been engaged?
Why didn't you tell me
that in the first place
or literally every other
time we talked about Maxwell?
I thought I'd come to New York
and do the show and go
back to my real life.
Maggie, does John
know you're engaged?
No.
But I'm going to tell him
right after I talk to my parents.
I've already decided I'm
calling them in the morning
and telling them everything.
Good.
Anything else you
want to tell me
that you've held
back this whole time?
I don't like chicken parm.
Okay, that's just not funny.
Now let me try on the rock.
Oh my gosh.
Oh.
Oh, a lot of women would
kill for a life like yours.
Are you sure you
want to do this?
Maggie, your friend Kitty's
in the lobby looking for you.
At eight in the morning?
Kitty?
Hi.
I thought our appointment
with your aunt
wasn't until this afternoon.
No matter, I was going
to cancel anyway.
You were right.
It's time for me to tell
my family the truth.
I'm calling them
right after breakfast.
Margaret, stop.
That's why I came here.
You don't have to
call your parents.
Why not?
Because they're on their
way to my apartment right now.
Oh no!
That's exactly what I said.
What did you do?
Let's go back down, and
I'll tell you on the way.
I do hope my Margaret
hasn't been too much
extra work for you.
Margaret's been a dream.
You'd barely know she was here.
Oh, well, the
apartment is stunning.
Kitty, you have made a
wonderful home for you and Stewart.
So where is the young man?
Oh, he's away on
business until Christmas.
That's why it's been so
nice having Margaret here.
Well, ladies, the
coffee was delicious,
but I'm ready to go out for
a big New York breakfast.
So what's good around here?
The hotel has a fine restaurant.
Why don't you get
checked in, eat,
and I'll meet you after that?
Well, why can't
you come with us?
I
Have an appointment
to taste different
flavors of wedding cake.
Margaret,
you know we have a perfectly
wonderful pastry chef
back home.
Of course.
I just thought this way I
could narrow down our options.
Oh, that's an excellent idea.
I'll go with you.
Oh, that's okay!
I know you don't like
sweets in the morning.
I'll tell you what,
you go with Father,
I'll go to the tasting,
and I'll meet you at Gimbels.
Say, 2:00 PM?
Great!
I have to get going.
Taxi!
I know, I have a lot
of explaining to do.
Actually, you don't.
I caught everyone up.
You're my new
favorite soap opera
after "Guiding Light."
I should have told you all
everything from the beginning.
It's just you already
looked at me differently
once you found out I, I
came from money, and...
I was afraid if you
girls knew I was engaged
and not planning on
coming back to the show,
I would be even
more of an outsider.
You're not leaving
the show now, are you?
I don't want to.
But once my family finds out-
Wait, you still
haven't told them?
No, I had to rush right here.
Uffa!
Half hour ladies.
This is your half hour call.
Ready?
To do the show?
Yes.
To talk to my parents?
It doesn't matter if I'm ready,
it's now or never.
Oh good.
I forgot to show you one more
thing with the payroll taxes.
I have something I
want to show you first.
What's this?
It's my application for
NYU's Fine Arts program
for when I get out of the Navy.
You won't have time for college.
You'll be too busy here.
Well, that's the thing.
I, I'm not sure this is
where I'm meant to end up.
So you'd rather take
pictures of Christmas trees
than carry on the
family's legacy?
It's not about Christmas.
It's about me being
a photojournalist,
professionally.
I, I, I got a real
knack for it, Pop.
You have a responsibility
to this family.
Ben is family too.
And he would make you so proud
if you just gave him a chance.
It says Slater
and Son, that's you.
We work night and day to
have this, to give it to you,
and now you want to
just throw it all away?
That's not what I'm doing.
I'm trying to do what's
best for everyone.
Taxi!
Oh, this is so much better.
Now, while your
father is not with us,
I perhaps will buy
his Christmas gift.
And you should get
something from Maxwell.
Maggie.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Matthews.
Something is obviously
going on with you.
You can talk to me.
My parents are here.
They think I'm in New York
to have a wedding dress made,
and they don't know
I'm a Rockette.
They would never approve.
And I'm afraid of
what will happen
if I tell them the truth.
At some point, Maggie,
you're going to
have to just let go
of what other people
expect you to be
and just be who you are.
Take the rest of the day off,
we'll have a swing
cover for you,
and go do what you have
to do for yourself.
Hmm?
Thank you.
I don't know, she's...
Oh, you look much
better now, dear.
Are you ready for dinner?
Yes.
But I've been trying to
reach Maxwell all day.
I've tried him at the
office, the club, his house.
I think you'll be able
to reach him very soon.
Can we ask for a quiet table?
I really need to talk to you
about something important.
Actually, we already have
a table right over there.
Are you surprised, darling?
You have no idea.
Thank you.
Just in time.
Would you like a
cocktail, darling?
Ah, yes.
A double old fashioned, please.
Easy on the water.
Isn't that basically
a straight bourbon?
Is it?
Mother, Father, Maxwell,
I have something to tell you
about my time here in New York.
Wait, before you do, I
have something for you.
An early Christmas gift.
Thank you, Maxwell.
I'll open it right
after we talk.
Open it now.
Don't be rude.
You couldn't stop
talking about them
after you saw them
at the parade.
So as much as I loath going
to any sort of ballet.
I figured I could grin and
bear it for one night, for you.
See, they're for Christmas Eve.
Look at her.
She's so happy.
She's speechless.
Thank you, Maxwell.
It really was very thoughtful.
I can get you something else
if you don't want to go.
Oh no.
I'm definitely going because,
because
I'm in the show.
Uh,
I'm sorry.
I, I don't understand.
That's what I
wanted to tell you.
I didn't come to New York
to have a wedding dress made
or register for gifts
or make connections
or visit Kitty.
I came here because
back in October,
I auditioned for the
Rockettes and they picked me.
I'm sorry.
I think I, I'm
missing the joke here.
This isn't a joke.
I really am a Rockette.
Stop it, Margaret.
We know you'd never
do such a thing.
Just come to the show.
See for yourself.
This isn't something
to be ashamed of,
it's something to be proud of.
Oh, now look what you've done.
You've upset your mother.
Is this all true?
This life we planned,
we didn't plan it for
ourselves, did we?
This was all put
together by our families.
Are you really okay
with marrying someone
you don't even love?
Darling,
I'm not sure anyone in our
position marries for love.
Because if I'm being honest,
I don't believe true
love exists at all.
But it does, Maxwell.
And I think we both deserve
the chance to find it.
I see.
I'm sorry, Max.
Don't be sorry, darling.
You're happy here.
How can I be upset about that?
Thank you.
So are you ever coming home?
I think I am home.
Max?
Where's he going?
Back to Philadelphia, I imagine.
Good.
We'll stop by Kitty's,
pick up your things,
and we can all catch
the last train home.
My things aren't at Kitty's,
they're at a women's
boarding house.
And I'm not going back with you.
I'm staying in New
York, permanently.
But that's preposterous.
You can't make it in
this city by yourself.
Yes, I can.
But you're giving
up your future.
And for what?
To dance?
That's what you don't
understand, Mother.
It's about so much
more than that.
It's about the friendships,
the camaraderie,
the pride we have in what we do.
We make each other better,
not just as dancers
but as strong,
confident women who can make
their own dreams come true.
I've heard enough.
If you're not at the hotel
in two hours, Margaret,
don't bother coming
back home at all.
You would cut me
off from my family
for following my dreams?
I'm trying to save you
from making the biggest
mistake in your life.
My only mistake was
hoping you'd understand.
Elisabeth, let's go.
Elisabeth.
(g-Hi.
How did you-
Ben gave me your address.
Is that your application?
It is.
I was just going to drop it off.
That's wonderful.
When will you find
out if you got in?
While I'm at sea?
So when I get back,
I'll either be doing
Slater and Son or this.
I suppose that means
you told your parents.
I did, but they
don't understand.
I'm not judging their choices,
I just wanted to make my own.
So did I?
And I have.
I have a lot to tell you.
I, I, I need to drop this off.
Do you have time for a walk?
As a matter of fact, I do.
Maybe I should have written
a letter to Santa too.
You think he knows
anyone in admissions?
Well, if he doesn't,
I'm sure my grandfather does.
He's on the Board of Trustees.
You didn't think to
tell me that until now?
There's a few things about
my family I didn't mention.
I already know, Maggie.
You do?
Your family is rich.
Sofia let it slip to Ben.
Yes, it's true.
But I'm on my own
now, completely,
that's what I
wanted to tell you.
I broke off my engagement, John,
and I'm staying in New York.
So when you get back-
Stop, back up.
You were engaged?
Ben didn't tell you that part.
No.
Oh.
Okay.
Uh, I was engaged,
but we're both from
prominent families, you see?
So it was more of a
marriage of convenience,
it wasn't real love, not like,
not like what I
know is possible.
I wish you would have
told me all this before.
But we were just friends.
Isn't that what we said?
I wasn't ready to
tell you everything,
but now I am.
I just needed time to figure
things out for myself.
But I made my choice.
I choose New York and
being a dancer, and,
and you.
I thought you'd be happy.
How can I be happy?
I told you everything
about myself,
and it turns out I
didn't know you at all.
You do know me.
You helped me see who I am.
You told me over and over
I owed it to my family
to tell them the truth,
and this entire time
you were lying to yours.
But I did tell them.
Only when you had
no other choice.
You knew that if
it didn't work out,
you would just go
back to Philadelphia
and pretend like none of
this ever happened; but me,
I'm risking everything.
Well, then let me at least
talk to my grandfather.
Why?
'Cause you don't think I
can make it in on my own.
I'm not saying that at all.
I care about you.
I just want to help you.
Did your grandfather help
you get into the Rockettes?
I did that on my own.
And that's how
I want to do this,
on my own.
The show wasn't
the same without you.
Are you okay?
Never better.
Rose said I could
stay at the apartment
during the off-season
while I look for work.
And I have a lead on a
sales job at Gimble's.
Maggie, did you talk to John?
I did.
It didn't work out.
It's fine.
I came to New York
to be a dancer,
not to fall in love.
I should have just
focused on the job,
that's what matters.
Until you can't do the
job anymore, then what?
What's going on, Alice?
I think it's time I
should listen to my body
and hang up my tap shoes.
So in three days, when
this show is over, so am I.
And I do not know
what to do next.
This show is everything to me,
it made me who I am.
And I, I just don't
want to leave.
We don't want you
to leave either.
But I know one thing for sure,
no matter where any of us are,
we'll always be sisters.
I know mine would have
loved you girls so much.
Really, Janet.
Nothing?
You don't have to do
this alone anymore, Janet.
We're your friends.
But that's just it.
I never let myself have friends.
Everyone I met was
just the competition.
And you girls have stood by me
no matter how hard
I pushed you away.
And I tried hard.
We know.
You helped me
the most, you know?
Your friendship is the
best Christmas present
I ever could have been given.
I just don't want this to end.
None of us do.
Nothing like a piece of
pie after a good cry,
I always say.
I don't have anything to say.
My father built this
business for him then for me,
and I thought someday for you.
It's our legacy.
But don't you see?
You made me into a man
who could see beauty
in the simple things:
in family, in hard
work, in sacrifice.
Don't you see, Pop?
The store isn't your legacy,
I am.
Oh, Robert.
You can really make
a living doing this?
I really can.
And the Slater name will be
under every single picture.
It's good advertising.
Is something
still wrong, Johnny?
Uh, who are you here to see?
- Maggie Bennett.
- Margaret Bennett.
I'm her mother.
Sorry, she already left.
Next show starts in two hours.
I guess we'll have to come back.
I'm sorry.
How do you know my daughter?
Oh, I'm sorry.
How rude of me?
I'm Harriet Slater.
John Slater's my son.
It's sad what happened.
It really seemed that John
had found his perfect match.
I thought that if I
could come talk to Maggie
I could maybe figure
out a way to help.
I'm sorry, I, I, I
didn't know about your son.
You didn't?
No, I just came back
to convince my daughter
to stop this nonsense
and come home.
Have you seen the
show, Mrs. Bennett?
No, I haven't.
If you had, you wouldn't
want to talk her out of that.
It's like when I saw my
son John's photographs,
I knew that that's what
he was meant to do too.
But I think they were
meant to do it together.
John loves her.
Does Margaret love him?
I need to make things right.
We both do.
I can't believe this is it,
our last show.
Hmm.
And my parents never saw it.
Maybe they'll come
around next season.
Speaking of next season.
Alice, can we talk?
I know what you're going
to say, Mr. Matthews.
I know that this is
my last season and-
On-stage, perhaps.
But I've seen how much
you help everyone here,
how selfless you are,
and how much these
girls look up to you.
I think every one of these girls
came into my office this week
to tell me how much they
love you and need you,
one in particular.
The way you stood by Janet
and brought her along,
that's the sort of leadership
we're looking for around here.
So, so what are you saying?
We would like to offer you
the position of dance captain.
You'd make sure the girls
know their choreography,
run rehearsals and maybe
fill in now and then.
Merry Christmas, Alice.
Merry Christmas,
Mr. Matthews.
Ladies, have a good show.
Hmm?
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone,
especially you.
Anything for a friend.
Five minutes, ladies.
Oh.
This just got delivered
for you, Maggie,
from Gimble's.
I didn't order anything.
For Maggie,
who will always be part
of Christmas in New York.
Love, John.
Hmm.
He must have paid for this
before everything happened.
He did love me,
and I loved him.
I'm so sorry, Maggie.
It's fine.
At least now I know for
sure how love feels.
Are you sure you
want to keep it?
You don't think it'll
remind of you what you lost?
No.
It reminds me of
how far I've come.
Places, please, ladies.
And I didn't even know
if it was going to fit.
And then you helped
me zip it up.
You were absolutely wonderful.
I couldn't be more proud.
Look at you.
You're just glowing, Maggie.
You look so happy.
You called me, Maggie.
I know.
I rather like it.
So do I.
I can't believe you're here.
I came back to get
you to change your mind.
Mother-
But I made a new friend
and she changed mine.
I'm so sorry, sweetheart.
I was so busy worrying
about how it looked
to everyone else
that I didn't give you
a chance to be yourself.
And look at you.
You followed your heart.
And look what
you've accomplished.
I'm so proud of you.
Father isn't here, is he?
Oh, he'll come around,
don't worry,
I'll make sure of it.
I only let him think he's
in charge of this family.
And I spoke to John
before the show.
He's wonderful, Maggie.
Don't let him go.
You were wonderful.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
You got the pin?
I can't believe you did this.
I love it.
I'm so sorry about
what happened, John.
I pressured you
to risk everything
without telling you
the truth about myself.
And I need you to know,
I never meant to imply
you couldn't make your
dreams come true on your own.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
No one should have understood
the kind of pressure you
were under from your family
more than me.
But
it seems like you're
working things out.
I think so.
How did our mothers even meet?
Long story short,
they both wanted to
make things right.
And?
So far so good.
You want to see the
view I get every night?
It's beautiful.
Isn't it?
Like Christmas every single day.
Actually, I was
talking about you.
You're not so bad yourself.
I like to dress nice
for important occasions,
like the night a man tells
a woman he loves her.
There's no way I could
leave for six months
without telling you that.
I love you, Maggie.
I love you too.
And when you get back,
I'll be right here waiting.
Even if you don't know
if you're going to end up with
a photographer or a grocer?
I just want to be with you.
This pin always reminds
me of that Christmas
and how I became the
woman I was meant to be.
And I became a lot stronger too.
Lucy, just like you,
you can do this.
Thank you, Grandma.
I should have known this
is where you snuck off to.
Look what Grandma gave me.
Oh, well, I can't think of
a better legacy.
And it all started right here.
The happiest night
of my entire life.