Look at the design of my watch.
Open slit down the middle.
Look at the colour of my shirt:
salmon... open collar...
I will make a point of
pulling out my wallet:
Open it wide, reach inside...
Look at my cuff links:
Open V design pointed back at me.
Think about it.
What do you think all of this
conveys to a woman?
Open your vagina to me.
All right. We use the power
of suggestion all the time.
Why wouldn't I with women?
Why would you say that to me?
What?
Did you know I have
an 18 year old daughter?
- No...
- No, I don't have a daughter.
But you didn't know that. Did you?
So what you actually just showed me
is that you're not aware
of what you're presenting.
I don't care what you do
but maybe you should pay attention
to the actual image you're transmitting.
Hmm...
Now, where's the pussy at?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Keep it inside.
Sorry.
I know who it is.
You look like Jennifer Lawrence.
Hey, don't you think she looks
like Jennifer Lawrence?
Uh, I don't think I know who that is.
You don't know
who Jennifer Lawrence is?
Can I bum one of those?
Yeah I've had that before.
Actually, I was just in a movie
and the director made me
step out of the shot. It's hard...
- How are you for money?
- I'm all right, Dad.
How much can a gig at a dive bar pay?
There's a saying, Denny:
"It's not about finding yourself,
it's about creating yourself"
When I was your age I was so...
Oh, great.
Fucking fantastic.
Very mature.
Hi
Sorry uh, did you just smile at me?
You just smiled at me.
I don't know. We caught eyes.
I had to do something.
I don't know if that's all that it was.
Okay.
No, I'm just saying.
We don't have to apologise
for having a human interaction, do we?
I'm not going to fall
for this schtick. Sorry.
Schtick? No there's no shtick.
I'm not... I don't know
if this looks like schtick,
but actually I'm very anti-schtick.
I don't like the shtick.
- Oh!
- Fuck this schtick.
Okay.
Those your friends?
Uh, yeah. Work friends.
Lawyer?
- Yes.
- Uh huh.
Judging? I buy you a drink?
No.
No. Just one drink.
We don't even have to talk.
We can just drink it in silence.
No, thank you. I'm seeing someone.
So am I. I just...
You probably shouldn't
be hitting on me then.
No, I'm not hitting on you.
I just... You you had
a friendly face and I...
- Honestly I...
- This one?
Yeah, that one. It's very
friendly from across the way.
Now I'm here, I'm a little scared.
And this is not a big thing.
I can buy your boyfriend a drink.
My girlfriend isn't here.
Okay, cool, cool.
Can I be honest with you?
I'm having a weird moment.
I can't explain.
It's like I'm talking
in tongues or something.
I must be having some
kind of religious experience.
- I'd...
- What?
No I just... I... This is innocent.
I saw you.
Um... I don't... I don't...
Okay, hey listen, it's fine.
Um, I know what you mean.
Do you? Because I don't.
I'm going to pretend
I know what you mean.
- Hi!
- Hey!
- Thanks.
- Oh, you work here?
- Play here.
- Cool.
Thank you for not hitting on me.
I wasn't hitting on you.
Okay.
- Hey!
- Hey, Ryan!
Hey, it's your round.
Oh. Sorry.
One more? Thanks.
That was good work on Kleiman.
He's coming later.
Make sure you celebrate with him.
You and me were cut
from the same cloth, Ryan.
I'm going to help you.
But you'll have to work for it.
You're with me starting
tomorrow. New case.
The sexual harassment?
Uh huh.
You know Brian Townsend is? The producer?
Yeah, exac-Kleiman's here.
Let's introduce you.
Hey, good job.
Really good job.
Thanks.
Denny, you looked fantastic tonight.
Really beautiful.
Okay.
Good night.
- Hey.
- Lawyer guy.
That was great.
I mean that was fantastic.
I was going to shout for an encore,
but I thought maybe
it would be frowned upon.
Frowning. I wouldn't want that.
Do you want to stick around
for a little bit? Just… have a drink?
Don't you have a girlfriend?
I had a girlfriend.
Just one drink?
Sorry.
Woo! Encore! Encore! Encore!
Okay, beers are right here.
All you have to do
is just stop, and drink.
That's it.
- You smiled.
- No I didn't.
Okay. I know what it is.
You don't drink, do you?
You don't normally wear lipstick.
Do you like it?
Yes I do.
Close your eyes.
Why?
I like it on you too.
Unfortunately there was
a problem with our accountant,
so I can't right now.
You said it was definitely
going to be today.
Yea, I'll tell you what...
Um, hang out,
and after I lock everything up,
have a drink with me,
and then I'll see what I can do.
Yea. I'm not going to hang out.
I just want my money and then
I'll get out of your hair.
Hey. Don't make this weird.
- Get the fuck off my property.
- Not until I get my money.
Look. You're a pretty
girl, with a pretty voice.
I just wanted some fun songs.
Not a no make up, hair not done...
Fuck you. You fucking asshole!
If you don' like it get the fuck out!
- Hi.
- Who the fuck are you?
What are you doing here?
You're not allowed here!
No, I'm her friend.
- He's my lawyer.
- Lawyer?
Um, what's going on?
He won't pay me three weeks pay.
Oh, why not?
Oh, I don't know. Maybe 'cause
FUCK OFF. That's why not.
When am I going to get my money?
You said you would play covers.
I didn't hear any covers.
Did you hear covers?
You said you would play
Katy Perry 'Fireworks'...
- I was joking.
- I wasn't.
I like Katy Perry Fireworks.
- Hey...
- Fuck off man!
I would like to help resolve this.
I'm just going to be honest with you.
I work with the Department
of Public Health all the time.
I don't give a shit, man.
Listen, just out there I noticed five clear
violations of the food safety code.
Cracked and chipped multi-use food
contact surfaces. Section 11473.
Bathroom inside minimum proximity
of a food preparation area. 11472.
Ew.
Food preparation sink smaller
than minimum requirement.
There's a lot.
You could get shut down.
Did you see the storeroom?
It's a shithole back there.
You need to work something out.
So don't be a dick.
Okay.
You're right.
I just... I get carried away sometimes.
I'll make it up to you.
You think I'm a fucking idiot?
Get the fuck out of here, you fucking...
Motherfucker!
- What a fucking dick.
- Yea, he is.
Don't worry about it.
That fucking piece
of shit's going to pay you.
- I'm going to come back. Fucking...
- Hey, it's... It's okay.
So you're… you're good?
Yea.
Alright. Catch you later.
Hey. Why'd you help me?
- Huh?
- Why'd you help me?
'Cause you want to fuck me?
No.
Okay, why?
I don't know. No reason.
No reason?
Because I'm not a shitty person?
A shitty person would say
they're not a shitty person.
But, you know, if you're not a shitty
person then that's a good thing.
Okay.
So you're cool?
You just… waiting to get picked up.
No.
You're just enjoying the sidewalk ambience?
I'm waiting for someone to do something.
But if they don't want to do something,
then I guess we won't do something.
I want a sandwich.
What?
Okay.
Uh, do you want... ham? Turkey?
I'm a vegetarian.
- Butter?
- No butter.
Okay.
PB&J it is.
Alright.
You know you're an unusual date.
How on earth is this a date?
This is not a date.
Ah 'the Lady doth protesteth
much too much methinks'.
(Okay. A) That is nowhere near the quote.
(B) I have no idea
what you're talking about
(and C) No.
So it's a 'non-date' then.
Friends.
Friends... with a certain chemistry.
- No.
- Friends with no chemistry.
Yes.
Friends with no chemistry who kiss.
We haven't kissed.
- We haven't kissed?
- No.
We weren't just kissing?
Okay.
You know, I can still
taste your lip balm.
How is my sandwich doing?
What? What...
Are you kidding me?
Really, really.
Hey!
Do you have to sit in the exact,
dead center middle of the park?
Huh?
I mean is this like the exact furthest
spot from any access point or...?
Oh my god. Did you have
to walk a little to get to me?
I'm horrified. I'm so sorry.
You should be. Apology not accepted.
Um, Chase called.
Some cosmetics company wants to use
one of my songs in a commercial.
That's amazing.
Yea he wants to use my stuff
to sell make-up to little girls.
Okay.
How's writing going?
I don't know.
I have pieces.
I just can't put the pieces together.
You play what you have?
- No.
- Just play a little bit.
I've seen you play, like, 20 times.
You play for complete strangers.
- Just... Give me a little bit.
- It's different.
Don't. Just stop it. You know
I'm a weirdo about this.
You're not a weirdo.
You just play a tiny bit?
Turn around.
- Turn around?
- Turn around.
- No, I'm serious. Face away.
- You know I can still hear you?
Stop - Shh. I'm going
to pretend that you can't, so…
There you go.
Yea but look away.
- Look away from... Please. Thank you.
- Oh...
Oh, that's it. I don't know.
- Amazing.
- Don't.
- Amazing!
- Stop it.
What's it about?
What's that?
It's a four-leaf clover.
- Oh really?
- Uh hmm.
- I've never seen one before.
- Hey, what are you doing?
I haven't seen one before.
Oh, so you need to pick it because
you haven't seen one before?
It's a clover. I just...
So? You don't need to pick it.
Just leave it.
So we're going to have
an argument about a clover?
Yes.
Fuck you! You're going to squash it!
I'm not going to squash it.
I'm going to squash you.
I think I need you.
Okay.
- Can I show you something?
- What?
Come on.
- Grab your guitar.
- Okay.
What are you doing?
Okay, so that's breaking and entering.
I know a good lawyer.
- Come inside.
- Are you crazy?
Yes.
Watch your head.
Whoa, whoa.
- You good?
- Yes.
I want you to move in with me.
What?
I can get the down payment.
This could be...
I mean this could be our place.
Okay.
If you want this to be your house,
for yourself, then that's amazing.
You're half living
with me anyway. Why not?
Because! Because it's too soon.
And I don't think that I can live up
to the idea you have of who I am.
I don't know who I am.
And you're going to get tired of me.
And I don't want you getting tired of me.
I live with myself 24 hours a day
and trust me, it gets tiring.
I'm not going to get tired of you.
And you don't have to live up
to anything. At all.
And you've moved in with girls before.
- What's the difference?
- It was different.
- How?
- I don't know.
Come here. Check it out.
It's got a little backyard
area where you can write.
Is that fake grass?
We'll replace it.
Sorry to do this, I need you
to take the Townsend meeting.
Um, I'd really rather not
take it unprepared.
I mean... The guy seems fucking crazy.
Well, when you're rich and powerful
you can be crazy too.
Was there something else, Mike? Hm?
No. No…
Well... my secretary is
getting on my nerves.
Oh yeah? Why'd you hire him?
Oh, he basically begged me.
Why'd you hire her?
Why? What's wrong with her?
She's one of the first
people clients see, Ryan,
and her face looks like
it's been hit by a shovel.
That's ridiculous. She's very good.
No. Honestly, I accidentally
looked at her the other day
and gave me a fright.
Okay.
Anyway, you're doing good, okay?
Thank you.
Call me with any questions.
Yea.
Um, there's someone named Denny calling?
Who are you?
I'm Randall. Mike said
I was needed here.
Okay.
So, anyway there's a lady named
Denny says she needs to talk to you.
Okay. Put her through.
- Do you have a minute?
- Not really.
I can't stay here, Ryan.
What?
I don't know, I can't stay here.
What does that mean?
I'm... I'm... I'm telling you that
I tried and I can't do this thing.
But why?
I don't know. It just
isn't me, I can't do it.
What isn't you?
Hey, sorry, can you just
give me one second?
One sec.
- Yea?
- Ah, Mr Townsend has arrived.
Oh f-
Okay. Just give me one minute.
Okay, he'll be-
Can we talk tonight?
- I'm sorry if I interrupted.
- It's okay.
Where's Mike?
- He's going to be with us Friday.
- All right. Update me.
Okay. So...
I want to fucking bury
this little homo.
Okay?
You don't like it?
No, I like it.
I'm just... I'm not used to the idea
of drawing directly onto walls.
Cool dishes.
Were you planning on doing a few,
or is that part of the art installation?
- I just...
- Do you want me to wear an apron, too?
And just be waiting on my knees
for you when you walk in?
Look, you don't have to...
I mean you can just rinse them,
just before the food cakes on.
It doesn't matter.
Regretting having me here?
No.
The best part of my day is seeing you.
Shut up.
You're pretty tough until you
get a compliment, aren't ya?
Then you don't know what to do.
- Shut up, dick head.
- So you insult me.
- I said shut up!
- Oh, I'm so avant-garde.
I don't close cabinet doors.
It's better than being
a chauvinist dick, isn't it?
Alright,.
Do you want me
to play for you or not?
Yes.
This is what I've got.
How about I teach you to play?
- No, I'm good.
- Yea.
I'm going to teach you to play.
- I'm fine, thanks.
- Take the guitar.
I'm fine.
I don't have a I don't have
a musical bone in my body.
- Take the guitar
- I'm good.
Or I will rain down on you
with moderate violence.
Oh my god.
I want to look at you.
You want to look at me?
Yea.
Not yet.
Yep.
Are you sitting down?
No.
Well sit down.
- Are you sitting down?
- Yea.
I've booked you a gig.
Okay.
Yea, someone dropped out
or some shit but wait for it.
You're opening for Jason Mraz.
- And we'll have reps from Universal,
Atlant- - Jason...? Jason Mraz?
That's... weird.
I said I was going to deliver.
I deliver.
I've had a lot of interest
in your demo.
Shouldn't it be Chase,
you are fantastic.
Or maybe a thank you?
Oh, okay, more reserved
than I'd expect.
But, I'm fine with that.
You can save your energy
for the show.
I'll call you back with the deets.
Babe.
Hey. What did you do to... to your hair?
Nothing. I just wanted to cut it.
Okay. What is going on?
Nothing.
- Really? 'Cause I mean it seems like...
- I just wanted to cut it.
Or should I have sent you
an email or something?
Don't do that. I like it. I do. I just...
I don't know. I just... I liked your hair.
I know. I'm sorry.
And we just... We have
the partner dinner coming up.
- This is important.
- I'll wear a wig or something. It's fine.
Alright. But what's going on?
What's going on is
I'm not your typical wifey,
in case you hadn't noticed already.
That's a cop out. I'm just...
I'm asking you to talk to me.
I've got to run. Can we talk tonight?
- Yea.
- Yea?
What's that?
It's a bone. From the wing of a bird.
I'm going to make it into a broach.
Morbid broach.
Only if you consider it so.
Cool.
I've got to go.
Ryan.
I've got this big gig next month, the 26th.
The 26th? That's the night
of the partner dinner.
Yea but I go on at six-thirty
so it's fine, right?
Can you come?
You know what, I'm going to try
and figure something out. Okay?
Okay.
- Oh... Excuse me.
- Sorry.
Didn't mean to surprise you.
Can I help you?
No, I… I knew this place.
Hmm.
It's a mess.
Huh, now it is, yea.
- What's it going to be?
- A bakery.
We're going to specialise
in gourmet bagels.
The whole thing's going
to open up through here.
Glass walls there...
Yea, it's going to be real nice.
You just... walking?
Yep.
- I didn't mean to stop you.
- No, no, of course. No.
I am going to be finishing up soon.
Got a six pack in my truck
if you want to...
Um, I'm okay.
Thanks.
Denny.
You okay?
Yea.
Let's talk.
We should talk.
I'm sleeping.
You're not sleeping.
You're just laying there.
Come on we should talk.
Say something.
- Say something?
- Yea.
Just talk to me.
- You want me to talk?
- Hmm hmm.
I've never said this before.
Okay.
I'm going to need you
to laugh when I tell you this.
You want me to laugh?
Okay, I can laugh.
Sure.
For a long time,
for a very long time I guess...
Yea?
It's really strange to say out loud.
Okay.
I've been having thoughts
about my gender.
Say something.
- Morning.
- Hey.
You want breakfast?
You should have something.
No. I'm okay for now.
Are you okay?
Yea. Yea.
Huh... Shit, I've got to get to work.
Oh, uh, can you wear that black
dress to the partner dinner?
I don't have it anymore.
Oh okay, we'll just buy another one.
Bye.
- Hey.
How was your day?
Was good.
Great, actually.
How was yours?
It was okay.
You know I think they might
give me my first case soon.
Oh wow, that's great.
- Congratulations.
- Yea thanks.
Thanks for doing the dishes.
I got pizza.
Got you your Hawaiian.
- Extra pineapple.
- Great. Thanks.
Hey, can we go to the uh...
Um...
Okay, this one.
- I like it.
- Yea?
- Yep.
- I do too.
Cool, let's do it.
- Alright.
- But wait, which one?
- This or that?
- Um, I like this one.
- Better?
- Yea.
- Okay.
- They're the same, but yea.
Okay, I have one more.
- Okay.
- Alright, I'll be right back.
See anything you like?
No. I don't see anything I like.
Can you just pick something?
Do you need any help?
Yea.
Well that was good.
Good, good, good.
I'll be the belle of the ball.
Hey.
Come.
- You want to play?
- No.
Keep practicing.
Did you ever finish that song?
The one you kept going back to?
Almost. Maybe.
Play it for me.
No.
Keep practicing.
Why are you up?
Because my alarm went off.
I didn't notice.
You should get up too.
We could have breakfast.
No. I want to keep dreaming.
But it's wake up time.
It's wake up time. Wake up time.
Wake up time.
Oh, Fuck!
Hey.
I'm never fucking working with her again.
You didn't tell me you were opening
for Jason Mraz. This is huge.
I did tell you, but…
Yea, but you didn't tell me what it was.
You didn't tell me it was Jason Mraz.
Okay well…
I'm Ryan by the way.
Hi.
Who are you?
I'm Carly, Denny and I have
been friends since high school.
Oh, nice, nice.
Um, I saw Chase.
He looked super fucking pissed.
Yea well couldn't give
a shit about Chase, so...
Okay... Well look,
I'm really sorry I missed it.
Did it go okay?
I didn't play. So, yea.
Why?
Because I just didn't want to.
I didn't feel like going out there
and pretending to be a star
or whatever the fuck I'm supposed to be.
Okay. That's… bizarre.
Oh. Well then I guess
I'm FUCKING BIZARRE.
I don't know if you've
been paying attention?
- Would you mind just…?
- She can stay.
No. It's okay.
I'll just be right outside.
Who is that?
She has nothing to do with this.
I don't deserve this. Okay?
Oh. Oh, you don't deserve this.
Oh, should we have another talk, then?
Hmm?
Is that what you'd like?
I'm waiting, you can go first.
Give me your 'opening address' counselor.
It's going to be a tough crowd
but maybe you can win me over.
You need to fucking stop this! Okay?
Ryan, I cannot fucking stop this!
What do you want me to do?
I don't know.
I'm sorry. We just... we have to get going.
Yea. I'll just... I'll get my bag.
- I'll be...
- Um...
Would you mind…?
I know it's...?
No, it's fine. Yea.
I'll just take a second.
Okay.
Uh, do you want something?
- I'm okay for now.
- Oh excuse me, excuse me.
This must be Denny.
- Oh.
- I've heard so much.
Enchanting as expected.
Thank you for lowering
your standards for our boy here.
- Yes, lovely to meet you, as well.
- Thanks, Mike.
So, senator Vuletic and Jeffrey
have heard all about you.
Kleiman's here and the partners
want to see you.
I set 'em up, you knock 'em down.
- Come on.
- Hang on.
I just met Denny.
You talk business, we'll stay here.
I'll try to entertain our guest.
I'll be right back? Sounds good.
Well, look at this.
- Here you are.
- Here I am.
- Can I get you a drink?
- I'm okay, thanks.
Ryan tells me you're
a musician, painter, and writer?
Oh, it seems he has been telling tales.
He is prone to delusions…
I don't blame him.
The best of us are
sometimes, don't you think?
Reality is not always palatable.
Hmm.
You sure I can't get you a drink?
Yea, I'm good thanks.
Oh, you missed a spot.
Pardon me?
The natural look. Interesting.
Yea, no, I can't fucking do this.
I saw you looking at my body.
Did you like it?
Hey.
I can be crazy too, ya know?
You think I can't be crazy?
What are you talking about?
I could throw this bottle
at the wall right now.
If you want to do it, then do it.
But you wouldn't care, right?
You know, that was my boss
you were talking to tonight.
- Ryan, that guy is a complete-
- No, no, no...
He's my fucking boss.
Okay.
I'm... I'm sorry.
By the way, I don't think
I've ever complimented you
on the brilliant additions
to our living room wall.
I mean I do just have one small thing...
Cabinet doors, generally they're
attached to cabinets, not to walls.
But other than that…
- Why?
- Ryan...
No, no seriously. I want to know why?
Because I like it there.
I thought maybe there's something
or someone BEHIND the door?
What do you think?
I don't know. Let's see.
Hello? Anyone there?
I don't hear anything.
Oh, hang on. Let's ask this guy?
He's kind of like a next door neighbour.
Uh, excuse me sir, can you help us here?
Nope, no news there.
Fuck, I don't know.
Uh, I know.
Maybe there's a surprise
behind... THE DOOR.
I think I'm going to do it.
I'm going to open it.
I'm a little scared.
I'm going to count to three.
Okay ready?
One…
two…
three!
Oh! Wow! Wow!
Nothing but completely blank fucking wall.
What do you know, huh?
Nothing but wall behind the magic door.
What's the point?
What's that?
- Hm?
- What does it look like?
Why wouldn't you tell me?
What was I supposed to tell you?
How?
I tried to talk to you and just…
Ryan, I'm not doing this to ruin your life.
I'm not doing this to ruin our life.
It's not because I think it's fucking cool.
I don't want this either.
It's not that simple for me,
it's not just a choice that I can make.
I wish there was a way that I could
tell you that you would like.
I wish I had the answers
you wanted to fucking hear.
I wish… I wish, Ryan. I wish I did.
Well now it's all out there, huh?
I want you to fuck me.
What are you doing?
I'm wearing your favourite fucking bra.
- What you don't want to fuck me anymore.
- Stop it. Stop it.
Look at me, Ryan.
Yeah.
You afraid it's going to make you gay?
Can't have the partners
at the office find out, right,
Your girlfriend is not
really a fucking girl. Huh?
You're lucky to fuck me.
You know that, right?
Ryan.
We should sleep.
Would play me that song that you
were working on forever?
You know the one that you wouldn't
play for me? You finished it, right?
Ryan, I need to talk to you.
Just a couple of lines. Please.
I have no problem with you
wearing men's clothes or whatever.
I just...
I am not going to stop
taking testosterone.
I didn't know how to tell you.
And I need to consider
my options for my future.
I need to figure it out.
And I'm going to look different.
I'm going to sound different.
I'm going to be different.
I just... I don't… I don't
fucking fit in this box.
I don't fit in this body.
Am I your box?
Hmm?
I mean, is this your box?
Is this…?
I mean, it's a pretty nice box.
Am I your fucking box?
You know we can just break the box.
Hey!
We can just break the box.
Fuck Fuck Fuck Fuck.
Hey.
You look tired.
I'm sorry for…
I was surprised.
That was unacceptable.
I would never normally
do that. Act like that.
I... I just...
This isn't me.
Yeah, okay.
I know.
Thank you. Yea.
Can you talk to me?
- Please.
- Um... I can do my best.
I miss you so much.
Yea, me too.
Come home.
You can talk to somebody?
What does that mean?
Nothing. Just this is a serious thing.
Denny, I am not going to let you
get rid of me that easily.
So what you really came here
to tell me is that I need help?
No. That's not what I meant.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
That's not what the problem is.
I can be there for you.
Ryan, this isn't going to change.
I'm not sick.
You're saying these things but I don't
feel like you're saying them to me.
I mean… do you… do you feel like…
do you want to…
Do you feel like a man?
No...
But, you know, I'm not a man or a woman.
Okay?
And I'm not what you want me to be.
We shouldn't see each other for a bit.
Denny, listen, listen.
Hey Denny, Denny.
Denny don't do that.
Denny.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Hi.
Don't do this. Okay?
Don't make this...
I told you I was going to be here.
I'm here.
- Ryan
- Just... if you want me.
Okay?
You okay?
Yep.
Okay.
It's like I like you so much
that you being around...
I just feel like I can't
do what I need to do.
I love you.
I think I need you.
I know you're here to help.
I can't see you anymore.
What Denny...?
- Hi.
- Hi. Um, Denny Weir.
Please take a seat.
It won't be long.
Are you waiting?
I'm actually here with my brother.
But he said Dr Kali's really nice.
That's a really nice dress.
Thank you.
Oh, there you are. Are you ready?
- Yea.
- Okay, let's go.
Just up on the left.
Okay.
You want a bagel, hun?
Sure.
Do you want it toasted?
Uh, no.
They're from that new gourmet
bagel place down the street.
You want butter?
Uh, no, thanks.
Nothing?
Nope.
You are so weird.
Thank you.
I got to go.
Okay, you parked behind me?
Yea.
You okay?
See ya.
- Bye.
You look like you could use a drink.
Way ahead of you.
I like a man who drinks gin.
It's not me. But it suits you.
You're looking stressed lately, Ryan.
I'm worried about you.
I want to make sure you
take enough time to breathe.
Have some fun.
Are you getting any time out?
- Uh, not really.
- Let's change that.
You know I want to help you?
Yea. Sure.
I like helping you, Ryan.
I want to keep being there for you.
There are not that many people
in this world I deeply respect.
But you... I deeply respect.
Thanks.
We set our own limits, Ryan.
There are no limits,
but the ones we set on ourselves.
What the fuck are you doing?
- I'm asking you...
- What the fuck...
I was going to ask if you think
you can take lead on Townsend!
What do you...
You misunderstood me, Ryan.
I'm trying to give you Townsend.
What do you think I'm talking about?
Jesus, Ryan.
Get some sleep, alright.
Don't lose it on me.
You alright?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You sure?
I'm good.
Alright.
- Yea?
- I've got Mike.
Okay.
Mike?
I'm going to sit in on your meeting
with Townsend. How's it coming?
I think it's fine.
Hey! Never fear.
- You've got me. Okay?
- Okay. Thanks.
Yea?
There's a visitor here for you.
A visitor?
Yes, uh 'Denny' is here to see you.
Okay. Okay, sure.
I went to your house...
and then I thought…
Okay. Yea, maybe I shouldn't have come.
- I understand if...
- No, no, no...
It's good to see you.
I'm sorry for the way things happened.
You don't have to be sorry.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
- Practicing.
- Oh yea.
But you know, I don't have
a musical bone in my body.
Don't do that.
Play something?
No.
I don't.
I haven't played in a while.
You're going to keep
practicing though, right?
Townsend's here. Let's go.
- Oh, uh...
- Come on, let's go.
I'm going to have to miss it.
No. It's okay. Go on.
Yes. Come on, let's go.
No, I'm sorry. I can't.
Ryan...
Tell it to get out of your office
and get to the boardroom, now.
Shut up Mike.
So, are you going to take
another week off, sit in the corner?
Don't be stupid.
Get into the boardroom,
or leave and don't come back.
- Let's go.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Come on. Let's go.
There are critical elements
as you can see.
1. Knock on the door, identify the...
You feel like a beer?
Sure, Denny.
Actually, it's just Den.
Den.