Belva!
Are you checking on Faye?
She didn't walk me to the store yesterday.
I know Mrs. Hamill, you've
already told me twice!
And the smell coming out
of her room can gag a maggot!
I know, I know, just
let me do my job, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Faye!
You in there?
Hey Faye!
The neighbors are complaining!
You gotta start taking
your trash out more often.
Faye!
Faye, I'm starting to get worried.
Nobody's seen you for a couple of days.
Old Mrs. Hamill,
she's driving me nuts
wanting you out here.
Faye!
I'm going to come in now.
Okay?
This living like an animal
has got to stop, Faye!
Jesus Christ!
She is definitely a fighter.
It's amazing she survived at all.
I don't hold out much
hope for her to come out
of the coma though.
Heartbeat is strong.
We'll just keep her on the
iv and keep her comfortable,
for however long it takes
nature to take its course.
Of course, doctor.
Thank you.
Not now, Charlie, mamma's
tired, just five more minutes.
Mrs. King?
Dr. Armstrong, she spoke.
Who?
Mrs. King, the coma patient.
I was just bathing her
and she began to speak.
What did she say?
Was she lucid?
No, I don't think so,
because she called me Charlie.
It was more like muttering in her sleep,
but in case she woke up
I thought it was best
to have you here.
Yeah, it may have been nothing,
just a side effect of her condition.
But in the event she comes around,
I did want to be present, you're right.
Mrs. King, can you hear me?
Hey, what the hell?
Of course I can hear you
Hi,
Mrs. King, my name is-
- who are you people?
Calm down, Mrs. King,
I'm trying to tell you.
My name is Dr. Armstrong,
you're in hospice.
And this is your attending
nurse, Linda dermont.
What am I doing in hospice?
You were in the hospital
for the first few days,
then they transferred you here.
Days?
Yes, you've been here
for the rest of the week.
Oh, god.
Who's been taking care of my cat, Charlie?
What?
Say it!
I'm afraid your animal passed ma'am.
It was the smell of the cat
that caused your landlord
to enter your apartment and find you.
Poor Charlie.
What happened to me?
Why am I here?
You suffered a coma.
From a condition called
alcoholic encephalopathy.
It's a build up of ammoniac in the blood.
Apparently from prolonged,
excessive use of alcohol.
Prolonged, excessive
use of alcohol, yeah,
that's an understatement, doc.
But you're awake now!
That's a good sign.
It's a step in the right direction.
Let's see if we can make
you more comfortable.
Can you try and raise the bed?
Sure.
There you go, that's better.
I'd like to start off by seeing
if we can get a little food into you.
Bring some of your strength back.
Whatever you say, doc.
I'll be back to check on you later.
Linda will handle everything.
I'll see you when I'm on my rounds.
Okay.
God damn, I could use a cigarette.
They're not being
completely honest with you.
You know that, don't you?
What are you, one of the
resident care takers here?
No.
I'm only here when someone
is on their way out,
shall we say.
You see, Faye, these are your final hours.
I've heard of budget cutbacks
before, but this is insane.
I can't be going home
already, I just woke up.
I believe what my coadjutor
is trying to relay, Mrs. King, is that,
you're not going to recover from this,
and unfortunately one of
US will be guiding you
to the afterlife.
What is this?
Some kind of corn ball intervention?
An intervention would
do you little good now,
don't you think, Faye?
This is the end of your mortal life.
All that remains is to determine
where your soul is bound.
Get the hell out of my room!
Just woke up and already
in a mood, Mrs. King?
I'm sorry, but the doctor insists
you try and eat something.
I wasn't talking to you.
I was talking to that pale bastard.
I don't think I know
who you're talking about.
I'm sorry.
I'm not really that hungry but
I could sure use a cigarette.
I'm sorry, Mrs. King, but
there's no smoking at hospice,
not even for the staff.
So, there's no cigarettes
to be found around here.
But please, try and eat something,
it will make the doctor happy.
I'm not making any promises,
but I'll give it a shot.
I appreciate the effort.
Thank you.
So life didn't turn
out the best for you.
Did it, Faye?
I really don't understand the necessity
of these training exercises anyway.
Isn't your primary
concern disaster relief?
Oh, sweetie, come on.
I told you this a million times before.
We've gotta be prepared for anything,
that includes military actions.
Yeah, I know, but,
I just wish you'd be doing
something less dangerous.
I hate the guns.
Oh, you'd have me retire
if you could right now,
wouldn't you?
Well, yeah, maybe you
thought, should think
about staying home and
just doing the one job.
The bottom line right now, sweetie,
is that our son's college
isn't cheap, ya know?
Yeah.
Come here.
Listen, everything is going to be okay.
Enjoy everything and let it happen.
Because I'm in the reserves,
we're doing a lot better
than other people right now.
You're gonna have me all to
yourself, 24/7 soon enough,
and then you're just going to be begging
for a weekend to yourself.
That is never going to happen,
because I'm never going to
get tired of spending time
with you.
You sure?
Yeah, so can you just like
call in sick just this weekend?
And maybe go next month
when you're doing something
less dangerous, like
soup dishing exercises?
Oh, sweetie.
Do you have any idea how many soldiers
are having this same conversation
with their husbands and wives?
If that was the case,
there would be no reserves.
I know, and I can't speak for the rest.
I'll just do my best to try
to convince you to stay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
And how's that?
Shut up.
I'm going to be back, I promise.
Okay?
You better.
I love you.
Disturbing and sad
news out of fort Luke.
Though full details are not released yet,
the military has verified
reports from earlier today
that a soldier has been killed during
routine maneuvers on base.
Oh, no!
The military maintains
this was an unfortunate accident
and not an act of terror.
Full details will be made public,
including the name of the fallen soldier,
once their family has been
notified of the accident.
Our thoughts and our prayers
are with the fallen soldier's family.
No, John no!
Where's my husband, John?
Where is he?
Mrs. King?
Yes, I'm Mrs. King, goddammit!
Where's John?
I'm sorry, Mrs. King.
There's been an accident.
Oh god, no, John!
I'm afraid this doesn't get any easier.
Let's get her inside.
Okay.
I just don't understand
how this could have happened.
John said it was target practice.
If it was just a routine exercise,
how could he get hurt?
Target practice is a
very routine exercise.
But we do use live rounds.
So, we have to be really careful.
Another soldier, he was a new recruit.
His gun jammed.
So John came over to
help him clear it out.
During that process, the gun
malfunctioned and went off.
The bullet ricocheted off
the wall and struck John
in the head.
John was killed instantly.
Mrs. King, if there is anything, anything
at all that we can do
to make this difficult time easier,
just let US know, we
would be glad to help.
What my lieutenant was trying to say-
- my son.
Mrs. King, what do you mean by your son?
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, our son Todd.
He comes home from college in a few days.
And this news is going to destroy him.
If there is any way that
the army could be here,
to help me break the news to him.
It would,
it would let Todd know that his father's
life meant something.
That he was important.
Mrs. King, I understand that
but the military doesn't usually-
- of course, Mrs. King.
Whatever it is you need.
Just let me know when and
where and I'll be there.
Faye.
You had no blame in what happened to John.
Of course not, I know that.
It was an accident.
You had no way of knowing
that he was going off
to die that weekend.
Did you, Faye?
No, how could I have known?
What do you mean?
What do
you think I mean, Faye?
There's no way I could have known.
And yet, you tried so
hard to keep him from going.
Why did you do that?
Because I, because-
- had a feeling?
Maybe an intuition that John shouldn't go
to guard that weekend?
That maybe something bad might happen.
Perhaps if you'd only tried
just a little bit harder.
What the hell do you want from me?
I'm sorry, if you're up
to trying to eat something,
I can take it away.
I just thought maybe you
wanted a straw or something,
that's all.
I'm so sorry.
I could have sworn there
was somebody else there.
I'm sorry, maybe I'm not ready to eat.
I should just get some rest.
Yes, ma'am, you go
try and get some rest.
Thank you.
Oh, come on in, it's open.
Oh, crap!
Good evening, Mrs. King.
Afternoon, Mr. Paul.
What are you doing here?
You know, you can just call me Richard
if you like Mrs. King, and,
isn't today the 22nd?
If you say so, but why are you here?
The funeral is not going to be for-
- Todd, doesn't he come home today?
Oh, crap!
How could I have forgotten that?
I'm sorry, I've been so out of sorts.
I was just napping on the couch
when you rang the doorbell.
It's understandable, Mrs. King.
You've been through a lot
these last couple of days.
Gosh, I'm sorry, I,
I've been splitting my time
between Todd's room and the couch.
I just can't bring myself
to sleep in our bed.
But please, sit down.
Have a seat.
There is sodas in the fridge
if you get thirsty and
I really need to freshen up,
because, yeah, I look bad.
Of course, Mrs. King.
I'd be happy to wait here
and thank you for the offer,
but I'm fine.
Oh, you're very welcome and
if you change your mind, just
go ahead and help yourself.
I'll be right back.
Thank you.
What the heck?
Oh, Mrs. King, you poor woman.
Uh, hello?
Hi, you must be Todd.
Yeah, I'm Todd, that's right.
Who are you?
Where's my parents?
I'm sorry, I'm Richard Paul-
- oh yeah, you're my dad's
lieutenant in the reserves.
Yeah, that's right.
You know what?
You mom just stepped down
to freshen up a little bit.
I guess she thought she had
more time before you got here.
She had been napping on the
couch when I rang the doorbell.
The couch, that's weird.
She'd never let dad or
I get away with that.
So, where's dad?
You know what?
He's not here.
So, why are you here?
No, wait, don't tell me!
Dad is getting some kind of commendation.
He always tells me-
- Todd.
If you work really hard,
the right people will notice.
- And eventually, with time-
- Todd!
You can just move up.
That's what he always says: I do it,
and you should too, son.
Todd!
There's been an accident.
What?
I didn't want to tell you like this.
Your mom thought it would
be better if I was here
and the two of US told you together.
What are you talking about?
Where's my dad?
There was an accident on the base, Todd.
I'm sorry, but-
no!
No!
He's gone, Todd.
Oh, no!
Toddie!
Oh, honey.
Mom, dad is,
dad is dead!
Dad, he's gone!
I know, baby.
Oh my god!
Richie, what are you doing here?
I thought you were out of the country.
I was,
belva called me and told me
that she'd found you unconscious.
And that were in the hospital.
By the time I got home,
they had moved you here.
I swear, that woman
is more of a mother hen,
than an actual landlord.
Well, I'm glad she is.
You're the only family I've got left.
I had to come back.
Thanks for sneaking this in.
Oh, I didn't have to
sneak in, it's plastic.
It's allowed.
Hide it, before the nurse comes back.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Regardless of how you got here,
it's really good to see you.
I was actually just dreaming about you
and how you came into my life.
That is kind of funny.
I was just thinking about that too.
Your dad was good man, Todd.
He was one of the best under my command.
I know he was.
I just can't believe he's
actually gone, you know?
I thought being in the
reserves meant he'd be safe.
That something like this
just couldn't happen.
I know, and I am sorry.
You know, ever since the accident,
every morning I wake up, and I hope
this was all just bad dream.
I've never lost one of my people before.
And losing someone like your dad.
Well, it's been a powerful
blow to all of US who knew him.
I just don't know what I'm
going to do now that he's gone.
And I can expect the world feels the same,
emptiness.
Well, I need to get back to base.
And you get in there and
take care of your mother.
Yeah, you're right.
That's what dad would expect me to do.
You know what?
Here's my card.
I'm going to write my cellphone
number on the back of it.
If you need anything,
you call me.
You got it?
I got it.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Todd.
You're going to be okay.
You're a good man, like your dad.
Say goodnight to your mom for me.
I will.
You take care of yourself too.
Yeah, I will.
Oh, what are you doing, Richard?
You're getting yourself
in deep here, mister.
Captain Daniels is right.
You're just going to make
this harder on yourself.
You know you can't be doing that.
Doing what?
Showing some compassion to a family
that has just lost a loved one?
No.
Showing compassion is an admiral quality.
But you can't get too personally involved.
You're young and-
- sir, I'm 30 and I've made it to the rank
of first lieutenant as well.
Okay, let me finish.
So, you're young and
this is the first time
you've ever lost one of your own.
So,
each time that you have any interaction
with a family member,
it multiplies your grief by every time
that you deal with them.
What are you suggesting?
That I don't follow through?
That I don't keep my word to that woman?
No, of course not.
Do what you said.
But use this as a learning experience.
This is the first time that
you've ever been on one
of these calls with the family.
And if the army has taught me anything,
this will definitely not be your last.
Yeah.
But you have to understand that you need
to distance yourself.
Or the sorrow that you have
will be way too much to bear.
Yeah.
It's all right, lieutenant Paul,
you're one of the good ones.
You'll be all right.
Well, I'm really glad to see you too.
Awake that is.
I've been sitting here
longer than I can say,
watching you sleep.
That's creepy.
It's good to know,
some things don't change.
Bedridden or not, you don't hesitate
to say what you're thinking.
Belva tell you about Charlie?
Yeah, actually I helped her Bury him.
Next to that big tree in the
back of the complex courtyard.
Oh, thank you.
He's gonna like that.
When he was strong enough to go outside,
he used to like sitting up in that tree,
watching those birds.
He wasn't fast enough to catch them,
but he sure liked watching them.
Are you okay?
Do you need me to call the nurse?
No, I'm fine.
I'd feel much better if I had a cigarette.
Uh-uh.
I thought you were giving those up anyway.
And you know.
Speaking of things I
thought you were giving up.
Belva and I cleaned out your apartment.
Oh, crap!
Oh crap is right, ma!
That place looked like a liquor store,
except all the bottles were empty.
What can I say?
It helps me sleep.
Yeah, well, this time your
sleep was almost permanent.
I know.
I tried to quit.
I even cut back a little, but
the clearer my head got, the
clearer the memories of John
and Todd got and it just,
it's unbearable, the heartache.
So,
I couldn't help it.
I just wanted to drown my sorrows.
Numb my feelings in the booze.
You gotta stop this, ma.
I can't keep losing
everyone that I care about.
You can't drink yourself to death.
I just couldn't deal with that,
after the loss of my
parents, and then Todd.
God, that's so awful.
I can barely stand the memory of it.
I know.
Phoenix memorial, third floor.
How can I help you?
One moment, I'll transfer you.
Hello, how can I help you?
Yes, we're
here to see Todd king.
Okay, let me see if he's ready.
Oh no, I'm sorry, the doctor
hasn't yet released him
to see visitors.
So, if you just want to have
a seat right over there,
I'll let you know as
soon as he's available.
This is the only time that we were told
that he would be available to be seen.
And we both took off time to be here.
We don't get to see him that often.
Why do we have to wait?
It's okay.
It won't be that long, right?
No, it won't be but a moment.
He's been in there for quite a while now.
Okay, come on.
Thank you.
I don't understand why we have to wait.
I don't understand either.
But we've got to trust the doctors.
Why?
They don't know anything
they're useless.
He should be at home with US.
Not with a bunch of people who
don't really care about him.
Richie, I know you're upset.
And this shouldn't be happening.
Not to US.
Not after everything we've had to endure.
It's not their fault.
You know if,
if Todd wasn't here,
we would have lost him
to pneumonia weeks ago.
Maybe so, but I'm not sure
this is what's best for him anymore.
Dr bullard, how is he?
Can we see him now?
He's weak, but he can
see visitors for a bit.
What about his lungs?
How are his lungs?
I'm afraid he's still retaining fluids.
We just don't know exactly how
to treat these new drug
resistant strains of aids.
When's the last time you got tested, son?
Just last week.
I've been going to an anonymous clinic
every couple of weeks,
just like you suggested.
This is crap!
You shouldn't have.
You should be able to
go to your own doctor,
you shouldn't have to hide!
I'm sorry!
I hate the military!
I hate it!
I'm sorry, Mrs. King.
I know this is hard,
but we've got to manage
the best we can with the
circumstances we've been given.
Maybe some day, things will be different.
I know, I'm sorry.
But we've got to survive today.
I know, you're right.
This is about Todd.
Why don't you take a
minute, splash some water
on your face and we'll go see him.
Okay, thank you.
I'll be right back.
Hi honey.
Ma?
Richie is here with me.
Hey buddy.
Dad's grave?
We went yesterday and
put fresh flowers on it.
I know how important it is to you.
We won't miss a Sunday, I promise.
I'll be home soon.
Makes me feel better, that
you guys will come visit me
when I'm-
- Don't say that.
You have to hang on.
They are going to figure
out a way to treat this.
You'll see.
Todd, you've got to take it easy.
You are not getting enough oxygen.
Speak a little at a time.
Richie and I were talking,
since your condition is not changing,
we thought maybe we would
get you some in home care
and take you back home with US.
- Faye.
- Sound good?
That's not a good idea.
It's critical that we keep him here
until we can control the pneumonia.
I wanna go home.
I know you do, baby.
And we want you there too.
We'll figure something out.
Todd, I need you to rest some more.
Can I speak to you in
the hall for a minute?
Sure.
We will be right back.
I'm going home!
Soon, Todd,
soon,
you'll see.
Look, I know you two want to comfort him,
but I think it's best
that we keep him here,
so he can get the best possible care.
Yeah, but we could
get him a nurse at home.
Faye.
His condition is so frail right now,
he would not survive that trip.
Look, everybody knows he's
gonna die and there's nothing
anybody can do about it.
Richard!
But at least he can
do it at home with US,
the people who love him.
Not here surrounded by
a bunch of strangers.
We're doing everything we can for him,
but his condition is
gradually getting worse.
If we can get the fluid
off his lungs, I'd be happy
to send him home with you.
But I strongly advise against it.
I wasn't exaggerating when I said
he would not make the trip home.
Dr. Bullard, he is flat-lining again.
Go to the waiting room.
I can't have you in there when
we're trying to do our jobs.
Yeah, but he could
die and we should be in there.
Mrs. King, for Todd's sake!
But he's coming home with US!
Oh god!
Dr. Bullard?
I'm sorry, Faye.
There was nothing we could do.
No.
Toddie!
Oh, no!
I just don't know what I
have to live for anymore.
What is left for me here?
I'm still here.
I know you are.
I'm sorry, Richard.
You just have no idea what
it's like for me to have
to get up every single day
and deal with that pain.
I just want it to be over.
Don't I know, ma?
You know,
there's something I need to tell you.
Something that I've, I've
hung on to, because it was,
well, it was just too
much for me to share.
But, I really think it's you knew.
Shortly after we lost, Todd,
I was gonna end it.
I had a gun in my mouth and everything.
I was gonna pull the trigger.
And then you called, and
then you made me promise
to come over the next day.
Hello?
Hi ya, Richie, honey.
How ya holding up?
Not so good, ma.
How are you doing?
About the same.
I don't know what I would've done
or how I would've gotten
through the day without you.
You know he loved you, right?
Yeah, I know.
It was as mutual as it gets.
So I gotta take care
of you now, all right?
'Cause that's what Todd would've wanted.
Just like you did for
US, when we lost John.
I don't know, ma.
I just,
I don't think I can keep going on.
Sure you can.
Listen to me, you have to!
You're all I've got left
in this world now, Richie.
Without you by my side,
I haven't got a chance.
Can you, uh,
can you come by the
house tomorrow, please?
I've got something I want to show you.
I just, I don't know if I can.
Sure you can.
Listen to me, you have to!
You're all I've got left
in this world now, Richie.
Well, I'll see what I can do.
I gotta go.
No, Richie.
You gotta promise me first!
Promise me you'll be here
tomorrow, it's important.
Okay, okay.
Okay fine.
I promise.
Thank you.
I'll see you in the morning, Richie.
Try and get some sleep.
And remember, I love you.
I love you, ma.
Goodnight.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye.
If you hadn't done that, I-
- you never told me this before.
There was never a point.
And what's the point now?
To let you see how important you are.
If you hadn't stopped me that night,
I wouldn't be here now.
Sounds like some kind of emotional ploy
to get me to stop drinking, right?
Well, uh, let's just call it
motivation to get better.
Have you had a nice visit?
Uh-oh, warden is here to kick me out.
Now, don't be like that, Mr. Paul.
I'm just doing what's best
for Mrs. King's health.
And doctor's orders are 30 minutes Max.
She needs her rest if she's gonna get out
of here any time soon.
I know, Linda, I was just joking.
I will see you tomorrow.
You keep getting better, okay?
And I'll see you then.
Thanks for taking care of her.
She's a lot more special
than you can imagine.
I can imagine.
You have a good night, Mr. Paul,
and we'll see you tomorrow.
You too, Linda.
Goodnight, ma.
Night, Richie.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Now, how are you feeling
after a nap and a visit?
Oh, god, overwhelmed!
Okay, not the answer I was expecting.
I was hoping for hungry.
Well, I could use a cig-
- Cigarette?
Yeah!
Yes, Mrs. King, I know,
but it ain't gonna happen.
How about some warm broth?
It will help you get your strength back.
Well, it's not a smoke,
but I'll give it a try.
Fantastic, I'll be
back in a few minutes.
Thank you.
It was nice of Richard
to come all the way back from Europe
to check in on you.
Oh, god.
You again.
So, where's your fancy friend?
He's never far behind.
I'm here, Faye.
Oh, god.
I was just being sarcastic.
I wasn't really asking for you.
Yeah, I realize that.
But you need to understand,
our business here isn't done.
How does what the soldier
told you make you feel?
Where do you jerks get off
questioning me about my family?
Richie is a good kid.
And Todd?
Was he a good kid as well?
And were you okay with their relationship?
So tell me more about
the movie, was it any good?
Well, good is a relative term, I guess.
Yeah, Todd hated it.
I think hated is a bit harsh.
I just like a little bit
of dialog between explosions, is all.
Okay, if you say so.
Wow, since Todd and I have
pretty much the same taste,
it's probably not a
movie I want to go see.
That would be putting it mildly.
Well, if you don't mind, I'd
like to change the subject.
There's something I
wanted to ask you about.
Yeah, sure, mom.
What's that?
Well, you're graduating
in a couple months.
Have you given any
thought to where you want
to live when you get back?
I hadn't really thought about it.
I was just concentrating on graduating.
And then, I thought I'd come
back home and get settled in
and just go from there.
Well, you know I'd
love to have you here,
but maybe it's time the two of you thought
about moving in together.
Mom!
Well, come on.
It's obvious how you two
feel about each other.
You know what, maybe I should just go.
Richie!
Mom.
Todd.
Okay, now that we've all
established who we are.
Can we just calm down for a second?
Please!
Yeah.
Yes.
I guess so.
Thank you.
Mom, please don't.
Oh, give me a break.
Just hear me out.
Do we really have to do this?
You know, when we lost
John, and we all lost John.
You became a really big part of our lives.
I didn't think I was ever
going to see Todd smile again.
And then when you started
hanging around, the light came
back into his eyes and this place,
oh come on, it actually feels
like a home again, doesn't it?
But ma, it's not like rich
and I can go out and get-
- what?
Married?
Maybe not now.
All I'm saying is you're
my boys and I love you.
You don't have to stand
on ceremony around me.
Life is too precious to not be who you are
and with the one you love.
That's all I'm saying.
I love you, guys.
You're family, that's all that matters.
Wow, I'm totally embarrassed.
I don't know what to say.
You know this is really
hard for me to talk about,
Faye, but-
- call me, ma, like he does.
You're family now.
Okay, ma.
Anyway, like I was saying.
This is really hard for me to talk about.
It's not something my parents
would have approved of.
Rich, you really don't have to do this.
Yeah Todd, I really do think this
is something I need to say.
My parents are gone now.
After I lost them, all
I had was my career.
That is until you guys.
Being in the military
makes it really hard,
but knowing we have your approval,
that really means a lot to me.
Oh, Todd, you can stop
giving me the stink eye
for outing you in front of your boyfriend.
I've known about you
since your first boyfriend
in junior high school.
Mom!
And your father knew, too!
You, my dear, are about
as subtle as an army tank.
Oh my god, mother!
I think John would be
happy for the both of you.
You know he's always liked
you very much, Richie.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Oh, don't worry about Todd.
I'm sorry, he'll be back in a few minutes.
In the meantime,
you want a glass of wine?
Yeah, you know what?
I think I could really use
a drink right about now.
Grab that.
Oh, yeah!
Excellent.
There we go.
I'm making a mess.
Uh, to family!
To family!
Of course I was okay
with their relationship.
Those two boys had a love most
people never get a chance at.
I see.
So you had no problem that their behavior
went against nature?
Against nature, my ass.
To hell with you!
Faye, there is no reason to get upset.
To hell with you too!
Who do you guys think you are,
coming in here and trampling
on the memories of my family?
Calm down, Faye.
I realize you must feel guilty
for failing Todd as a parent.
But this isn't about him, it's about you.
Guilty?
Well, yeah, of course.
That's why you're behaving
like this, isn't it?
If you hadn't condoned
their deviant behavior,
Todd might still be here right now.
Richie didn't give Todd aids
he must have got it when he
was in college or earlier on!
He actually did.
Well, then you know!
You know it wasn't Richie
that ended Todd's life!
That was never a question, Faye.
What we're discussing here
is the guilt that you have over that.
If you and John had put an end
to this early on, this never
would have happened.
Todd's guilt or innocence
was never in question here.
We're just trying to come to
terms with your failure of him
as a parent.
So you can release that guilt and move on.
Good lord, Mrs. King.
I was only gone for a moment.
What happened to you?
I'm sorry, Linda.
I don't think I can eat right now.
I think I'm losing my mind.
Well, that's just too
bad, cause you're going
to have to try.
Thank you.
But, they were just here when I-
- I'm sorry, Mrs. King, I'm
not going to hear of it!
You didn't eat anything yesterday,
and it's my job to make sure you get well.
Mr. Paul is depending on me.
And you told me you were going to try,
so I'm going to hold you to it.
Fine.
That's more like it.
You're not really going to sit there
and watch me eat, are you?
Well, that's not exactly
why I'm staying here.
It just seems that every
time I leave the room,
something happens to get you upset.
So yes, I'm staying here while
you eat, but not necessarily
to keep an eye on you.
You don't think I hallucinate just
because you're sitting there?
Yes, if that's what it
is, that's what I think.
Because it never seems to
happen until I leave the room.
Well, either this is really good broth
or I'm really hungry.
It's probably the latter,
because it's just out of a can.
Okay.
So you want to tell me what
you think you're seeing whenever
I leave the room?
Not really.
It might help.
I doubt it.
Come on, Mrs. King.
Let me guess, you're going
to some kind of night school to
become a psychiatrist, right?
No, that's not it.
I'm very happy in my chosen career field.
I just know that it helps to
talk about things sometimes.
Yeah, I doubt you'd
believe the crazy stuff
that I've been seeing.
Faye, you really think
doing the kind of work I do,
that I would be that easy to surprise?
I suppose.
Come on, humor me, please.
I think we both know, I've
just been hallucinating.
Perhaps.
You do have a pretty good
amount of drugs pouring through
your system right now.
So there's a great chance of that.
What else could it be, right?
Oh, I don't know.
Others have told me things
that have stayed here before.
You mean people that have died here?
Some, and others that
have come pretty close,
but have stayed here for a while.
But regardless, they've told
me that they've seen things.
Yeah, but what kind of things?
I'd like you to tell me what
you're seeing because I don't
want to cloud your memories.
You see, they say near death experiences
can cause our minds to start
seeing things we weren't able
to see before.
And you came pretty close.
Any chance I could get a
cigarette out of this little case
study of yours?
Not one.
I was afraid you'd say that,
but I thought I'd ask anyway.
So what is it you want to know?
So, what is it that you're seeing?
It's not really a what, it's a whom.
So you're seeing someone,
what do they look like?
Two someones.
One is this
touchy-feely hippie kind of guy.
And the other one looks like
a big, black undertaker.
I see.
The hippie guy is
kind of a cross between
a touchy-feely Mr. Rogers and
like a prosecutor.
A criminal prosecutor.
And the undertaker?
Well, the first guy
really gives me the creeps.
The undertaker, he's fine.
He is precise and to the point and
I think we both know
I'm just hallucinating,
so-
- so?
It's not like they are here
to take me to the afterlife
or anything like that.
Is that why they say they're here?
Interesting.
Maybe they are, maybe they're not.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're not holding out
on me, are you, Linda?
No, I'm not holding out on you.
And yes, you're not
completely out of the woods.
But that's not what I was,
that's not what I was talking about.
What I meant to say is that I
think I may know a way that we
can find out.
I don't, what do you mean?
Find out if they are hallucinations.
You mean find out if I'm crazy, right?
No, Mrs. King, we're gonna,
I'm trying to find out if
these are hallucinations.
And how are we gonna do that?
Well,
I just lost my brother recently.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I'm dealing with it.
Do you want me to ask
them about your brother?
Yes.
Seriously?
Yes, if these are just hallucinations,
they won't know anything.
Okay, how did your brother die?
Well, let's see if you can
tell me that in the morning.
Are you all done here?
Yeah, I'm finished with the soup.
But I think there is more than one person
in this room that's crazy.
Well, tonight is
your chance to prove that.
Good night, Mrs. King.
Good night, Linda, thank you.
Well, you just keep turning
up like a bad penny, huh?
'Till my job is done.
I know I'm hallucinating
but this imaginary water
is good and cold.
I know it's hard to wrap
your mind around, Faye,
but we're really here for you.
Yeah, here to put me on
trial for what you view are the
short comings of my life.
I didn't say that.
Good god!
I've had a crap life and I'm
at the end of it and you two
show up and want to pass judgment on me?
Piss off!
We're not judging you, Faye.
Well, it sure feels like it.
We're just reviewing
the events of your life.
So you can let go of any guilt that you
might feel from them.
And move on to where you belong.
Relieve my guilt, for what?
Not trying hard enough to stop my husband
going out on guard, so
he wouldn't get shot?
Or having my gay son pretend he's not,
so he wouldn't die of aids?
Yeah, something like that.
Well, you're wasting your
time there son, because I don't
feel guilty about those things.
Does it kill me, that I lost them both?
Hell yes!
Do I miss them, every single day?
Do I wish things would
have been different?
Yeah, I bet you know the answer now, huh?
But honestly, I don't feel guilty.
If anyone's to blame
for this, it's you two.
You certainly are
spirited when you're angry.
Oh, so you think this is funny, huh?
Well, if you two
supernatural jerks are real,
you must get a real kick out of meddling
in other people's lives.
Oh, Terrence, why did you
choose the life that you did?
You could have been anything
that you wanted to be,
but you had to be a gangster, didn't you?
Terrence dermont.
Hello?
You have a collect call from-
- Terrence dermont.
Will you accept the charges?
I will.
Please hold
and I will connect your call.
Hey, Linda.
Listen I tried to reach
mom, but I got no answer.
I'm down at the county.
What have you been busted
for this time, Terrence?
Possession, but I swear, it wasn't mine.
That cop put it in my pocket
oh, Terrence.
What are we going to do with you?
You really think we'll
believe anything, don't you?
Sis, it's not like that.
I'm keeping it 100 with
you, like I said I would.
But it's my squad.
I think they're after me.
They paid that cop off
to get me locked up,
so they can get at me.
Stop it, Terrence!
You can't reach your mother
because she is in the hospital
having her gallbladder removed.
And if you were any kind of
son, you would know that.
But you don't give a damn
about anyone but yourself.
Sis, don't get mad and hang
up on me, I'm in trouble.
I need you!
I'm not mad, Terrence.
I'm tired.
We're tired!
We're all tired of your lies.
I'm not lying!
I swear on our mother's life, I'm not.
I'm telling you the truth!
Now you've gone too far!
Especially now while she's in
the hospital having surgery.
Or did you forget that already?
I meant no disrespect.
I just need you to believe me.
I'm telling you the truth.
I wish I could too, Terrence.
But I'll tell you what.
Why don't you think of a better
story to tell your mother
when she gets out in a couple of days?
And maybe she'll come down
and bail your sorry ass outta jail.
Bye, Terrence.
No, sis!
Sis!
No, I swear, sis!
Hello?
Is this miss Linda dermont?
Yes, this is she, but let
me stop you right there.
Because I'm on my way out for
work and I don't have time for
a solicitation call.
Mrs. Dermont, this
isn't a solicitation call.
I'm calling from the maricopa county jail,
in regards to your brother Terrence.
We've been unable to reach
your mother this morning.
Do you know how we can contact her?
As I told my bum brother,
Terrence, last night,
our mother is in the hospital
having surgery and isn't
reachable at this time.
Furthermore,
I don't care what crap
Terrence has gotten himself
into this time.
He can wait until she's
available her own damn self!
I don't think you
understand, Mrs. Dermont.
What I don't understand is
how a jackass like Terrence
can have someone calling from
a facility where he is locked
up on his behalf.
Is that good use of my tax dollars?
He can just wait until-
- There was an altercation
last night, Mrs. Dermont
Terrence was stabbed and I'm
afraid he didn't make it.
Oh my god!
Oh my god, Terrence!
If only I had listened to
you that night, Terrence.
If only I wasn't so angry, baby brother.
It might have not changed
what happened to you,
but at least you would've
known that I cared.
Well, looks like somebody
is back on solid food.
Oh, you can blame that on Linda.
She gave me some broth last night.
And I woke up this
morning with an appetite.
Well, I'll have to
remember to thank her.
Where is she anyway?
It's before visiting hours and
she is not guarding the door.
You're safe for now.
The girl that's filling in for
her said she's gonna be late,
she didn't say why though.
So, what are you doing
here so early anyway?
Well, maybe without her bird dogging me,
I can get away with
longer than a 30 minute visit.
I doubt it.
They've got eyes and ears
everywhere around here.
Well, then I guess I
should just get right to it.
There is something I really
need to talk to you about.
This sounds important.
It is actually, you see, um,
well, I've decided to leave the
military and move back here.
So, I will be home full time.
Richie, you can't quit your
career, you love it there.
You're not doing this just for me?
Because if you are, I'm fine.
Well, first off, we know
that's clearly not true and
while that is a contributing
factor, that's not it.
See, since I've been back
I've just, I've been looking
at my life and I just realized it's time.
As long as it's something
that you really want,
and you're not doing this for
anybody else except yourself.
It is, ma.
Actually, my decision goes back
to something we were talking
about yesterday.
Really, how so?
Well, remember how I told you
that making me promise to come
over the next day saved
my life that night?
Yeah, I don't think I
could forget it if I tried.
Well,
it's what happened when
I came over that day
that gave me the strength to go on.
And it's, it's even effecting my decision
to leave the military now.
Oh, come on in.
Hi ya, Richie.
I'm really glad you're here.
I,
I've got something I wanna show you,
but I need to ask you something first.
Okay.
Did, um,
cid Todd ever talk about
John having cancer?
No, he, he never mentioned it.
Well, it was right around
when he was in high school.
Um, John started having groin pain and
we took him to the doctor and
he was diagnosed with testicular cancer.
Oh my god!
That had to be awful for all you guys.
Yeah, it was.
But we got through it together.
But it had a profound effect on Todd.
Why did it effect Todd so much?
Well, we had him
tested, just to be safe.
And he didn't have it, thank god.
But it turned out he was
genetically predisposed to
developing it later in life.
It scared him so bad,
he had trouble sleeping,
poor guy.
Well, that's an awful
thing for someone so young
to have to go through.
Yeah, it was.
This went on for weeks.
Then, all of a sudden, out of the blue,
he was just suddenly over it.
You mean, just like
that, he was just over it?
Yeah.
Did he ever say why?
Well, I asked him about it.
He said he was afraid that he wouldn't
be able to give US grand-kids.
And,
most importantly, one day,
he wanted to be a daddy.
Did you and Todd ever talk
about starting a family?
Oh, honey.
Well,
one day, he was just fine, he got over it.
And I didn't understand
why until yesterday.
I was going through
some of his legal papers
and I came across this.
That's it!
What is this?
It's an account, at a sperm depository.
That's why he wasn't worried
anymore, he knew that he'd be
able to be a father.
Okay,
I don't understand why you
are showing this to me.
I'm not just showing it to
you, I'm giving it to you.
That way, if you ever decided
that later in life you want to
have Todd's baby,
all you have to do is get a surrogate.
This way, you've got an option.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say
anything, you're family.
If you want to have Todd's
baby, this is a choice.
You want to give me grand-kids?
Thank you, ma.
Thank you for coming into our lives
and for making my son so happy.
It's okay, Richie.
Richie!
Are you telling me what I
think you're telling me?
Yup, after that first day
that I visited you here in hospice,
I started screening potential surrogates.
I settled on one last night.
I've already purchased an egg
from a bank and we're going to
do the fertilization procedure next week.
That's great, I can't believe it.
That's fantastic.
I'm going to be a dad
and you're going to be a grandmother.
Wow!
Come here, give me a hug.
I am so happy for you,
this is gonna be fantastic.
What's with all the affection?
Did someone win the lottery or something?
No, this is much better.
Richie just told me he is
going to be a daddy soon.
That's exciting news, congratulations.
What are you hopping for, a boy or a girl?
At this point, I'm
just hoping for healthy.
That's a great outlook and you seem
like you'd make a great dad.
What's the mother like?
Well, thank you!
The mother is fantastic.
She's got a wonderful personality.
She's in great health
and she came with multiple
glowing references.
References?
You didn't buy a wife off the Internet
or something, did you?
No, no, Linda.
He hired a surrogate.
He's actually going to be a single parent.
I see.
Well, you're going to help
me out once in a while when
you're well enough, aren't you?
Of course, you know I
would do anything for you
and your new baby.
Okay, Mr. Paul.
It's time for you to leave now.
But I haven't even
been here 30 minutes yet.
I know that and I won't even
dock you for your time when
visiting hours start.
But they haven't yet and Mrs.
King needs her sponge bath.
Unless you're willing to help with that.
Oh, that is my cue to leave.
That's what I thought.
I'll see you later, ma.
Okay, bye Richie.
I'll see you later and congratulations!
I'm a little confused.
Clearly, Mr. Paul isn't your
son, yet he calls you ma.
And you're gonna help him
raise a child by a surrogate.
What's that all about?
Well, it's a really long
story, but I can give you the
condensed readers digest version.
See, Richie used to be
my son Todd's partner.
And we lost Todd few years ago to aids.
Todd's dad had testicular cancer and
Todd was really afraid
he'd suffer the same fate.
So he put his perm in a bank.
Now Richie is going to be like
the parent of my grandchild.
Oh my god, Mrs. King.
People say I have a complicated life.
You are living a soap opera, girl.
Sometimes it feels like it, Linda.
Sometimes it feels like it.
So I heard you had some
breakfast, I'm pleased.
And I know the doctor will be impressed
when he makes his rounds later.
I'm not surprised you heard.
I was just telling Richie
that you've got eyes and ears
everywhere around here.
You know, I wish they'd
just let me take a shower.
I feel like such an invalid
somebody bathing me.
Me too.
I have real sick people to take care of.
The sooner you get your strength back,
the better for everybody.
So, why did you come
in late today anyway?
Well, it's the third month anniversary
of my brother's death.
And every month on this day,
I go and put fresh cut flowers
on his grave.
Well, I'm sure Terrence
would appreciate that.
Look, I need to ask you guys a question.
We ask the questions here, Faye.
Yeah, well, if you want
any more cooperation from me,
someone's going to give me a damn answer.
Faye,
until you Pierce the veil,
we're not permitted to reveal
what lies there.
All will be revealed in time.
Fine, then you're
wasting your time and mine.
Faye, that is not an option.
Oh, now you're just acting like a child.
We're not permitted to reveal your fate,
but perhaps we can find
some middle ground.
Mr. Ash,
you know our roles in this.
And I know when to bend
the rules, Mr. Church.
Learn to play the game
like a big boy for once.
If I could interrupt your
bickering for a second,
I just wanted to know something
about my nurse's brother.
Terrence.
That's a good start,
tell me about Terrence.
Mr. Ash, this will not be permitted!
Come on, live a little.
Well, now that the cry baby
has gone off to tattle on me,
let me see what I can recall
about Terrence dermont.
He really was quite the
bad boy for a while there.
Then he tried to walk the
straight and narrow for a while
and his past caught up with him
almost immediately, however.
Although he kinda made it in,
just under the wire, if you
know what I mean.
So he made it into heaven?
Let's just say he's having
a much better eternity
than the guy that shanked
him in the showers.
That's all I know.
Was it right?
Did it help?
Yes, very much.
Terrence called me from jail.
He said that he had been framed.
And that his life was in danger.
But I didn't believe him.
And he died.
I was afraid that he was
spending an eternity suffering,
thinking that I didn't care about him.
Now you know he's in heaven.
You know what else this means, don't you?
No, what?
If this proves that they're real
and they told me that I wasn't going
to leave this bed alive,
I won't be going home.
You have to tell Mr. Paul.
No, what good would it do?
None.
Besides, he'd just think I was crazy.
Can we just keep this to ourselves?
And Richard and I can have what
time we have left together.
You've got it, Mrs. King.
Whatever you want.
Thank you.
First of all,
start calling me Faye.
You've got it, Faye.
Second, I need to ask
you a really huge favor.
I certainly owe you one.
Richie is a really good man.
He lost his parents before
he came into our lives,
so he's got no one.
Can you look in on him from time to time
after the baby comes?
I'd be glad to.
With Terrence gone, it's
just me and my mom now.
I would be, it would be nice
to have a man to call on every
once in a while.
And I'll be sure to let him know that he
and your grandchild,
can be as big as part of
our family as he'd like.
Thank you.
You know, it's funny.
Wouldn't it, it'd just
be my rotten luck that
when my life is over, I finally
have a reason to live again.
That's how you ended up here?
Yeah, pretty much.
Because you didn't have
anything to live for?
Yeah, I only left the house
to go to the liquor store or
take my neighbor lady
Mrs. Hamill to the market.
Some punks started hassling her,
they know better than to mess with me.
How is it that they
hassled your neighbor,
but they didn't bother you?
See, they only
made that mistake once.
What do you mean by that?
One of those little
punks tried to mug me.
So I took out my nine millimeter,
aimed it at his jeans,
and told him I was going to
blow his balls out of his ass.
Oh no, you didn't.
I sure as heck did.
What's so funny?
You sound like some cliche
'80s action movie star.
I guess I kinda did.
Well, he must have been a fan
of that genre because no one
ever bothered me after that.
You know what, Faye?
I think this is the first time
I've ever heard you laugh.
To be honest, I don't
laugh very much anymore.
I think Richard is the only one
that's ever seen me laugh in
the last few years, or crack a smile.
I'm going to go grab some
more towels, so we can get this
bathing nonsense over.
And Mr. Paul can come back in, okay?
Sounds good to me.
I thought you'd be gone a
lot longer after the way you
disappeared the last time.
No, we are here for you, Faye.
No matter what, we're
going to keep coming back
until our job is done.
Oh, Christ.
Not exactly.
Ugh, what is it you two want from me?
A decision has to be
made, time is running out.
"A decision has to be
made, time is running out!"
Like I've got some kind of choice, right?
Well, what do you think?
What do I think?
I think I've been beaten.
I think I've been beaten for a long time.
I can't handle anymore heartache
or anymore disappointment.
This feels like the final
kick in the guts, you know?
To find out you're going to
have a grandchild, and you can't
watch it grow up, and you
can't watch it be born.
I just want this to be over.
So tell me what you want
me to say and I'll say it.
So, does that mean that you
believe you are beyond redemption?
Does it matter what I believe?
Is spending the second half
of your life drinking yourself
to death and keeping a
cat with leukemia alive,
worthy of the damnation of hell fire?
Isn't it though?
Who would you like to go with?
Again, what does it matter what I want?
If you had a choice,
who would you choose to
guide you to the afterlife?
Shame on you, Mr. Ash, for
deceiving her and making her
think she had a choice.
She was always intended to come with me.
But you saw her!
She wanted to come with me!
She took my hand!
You suffered greatly in life,
but even when you could no
longer care for yourself,
you still looked out for others.
Faye, you belong in heaven.
You just couldn't see so for yourself.
And as for you demon, you're done here!
Now,
let's go see your husband and your son.
Oh.
We have
but to step into the light
and then you'll be home, Faye.
Do I still have a choice?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Can I choose to stay?
Would you choose to stay,
knowing John and Todd
are waiting for you?
I finally come to realize
how precious life is.
I have a lot more living
to do and now I'm needed.
I think I made it
very clear on how I feel
about bending the rules.
I know you did, I'm sorry.
I don't want to break the rules,
I'm just asking if it's a possibility.
But this is a one time thing
and I cannot say how long
you'll be able to remain.
Life is precious and I know that now.
And you'll
take care of yourself?
I swear.
Then go.
So, you gonna go dancing
with me and the girls tonight?
Oh, thanks, Linda, but I
got toddie junior tonight.
We've gotta give Richie a night
off every once in a while.
Yeah, what she really meant
to say there was grandma's
kidnapping his son
and forcing Richie to go out
and try and have a good time.
So, where you going tonight?
You know, honestly, I have no idea.
I haven't been out in so long,
but I'll figure something out someplace.
If I don't, she's never
going to give me my son back.
Well, I know some good mixed clubs.
Why don't you come out with
me and the girls tonight?
I guarantee you'll have a good time.
And don't be giving me that
I don't dance line neither.
Because I've seen you dancing around here
with this baby of yours.
- Oh, I'm busted.
- She's got your number.
Oops.
Oh, can you take toddie
junior for a second?
Absolutely, give me that handsome baby.
I'll be right back.
Be a good boy.
So, where's the, where's the demon hippie?
Oh, he's only allowed
around when, you know,
a decision has to be made.
It was your pain and regret
that clouded your path to heaven.
So why are you here?
Are you ready to go?
I don't think I'm ever going
to be ready, but I'm prepared
to do what I'm supposed to.
Your time isn't up.
I'm just checking to see if you're as
good as your word.
So what do you think?
How does what I think even matter?
Oh, so now you've developed sarcasm?
I didn't think angels were
allowed to behave that way.
I don't just think you're
alive, Faye, I think,
I think you've finally
come back to life as well.
So, how long do I have?
You have as long as
you need and are needed.
Do you say that to all the
people you bring back to life?
Oh, I didn't bring
you back to life, Faye.
That was all you.
I just helped you see clearly.
You had to figure out and understand
if you had anything to live for.
I think you're about to be paged.
Oh, come here baby.
Did you give me this baby
because you knew he was about to
mess his drawers?
Oh no Linda, it must be
something about you that brings it
out of him.
I change dirty diapers
on adults all day long.
I don't need new experience.
And what were you looking at anyway?
Oh, nothing.
Just appreciating everything around me.
Come on, stinky!