Man:
As scientists
continue to wonder
what caused this
all to happen...
(overlapping dialogue)
Scientist believe
that with proper care
and consideration...
Woman:
...following our exclusive
well-used network...
(overlapping dialogue
continues)
Man:
...what officials fear
is becoming an epidemic.
Woman:
And welcome back to WNN.
I'm joined with my two guests
here in the studio today.
Man #2: You tell me
why he disappeared.
Vision on.
(chime)
Woman: Well, maybe
we were too hard on him.
Too invasive.
Man #2:
He became a celebrity,
for god's sake.
He probably makes
more than all of us combined.
Man #2: Boo-hoo.
Woman: Hold on.
Progress out.
(chime)
Man #2: Come on.
If you were in his shoes,
with the cameras following you
and people always in your face,
don't you think
you'd disappear too?
I mean, think about
all the aggressive fans
and the stalkers
who really affected him.
The man is an exception.
Exceptional.
If you saw
a white tiger in the woods,
you'd follow it, right?
You'd poke him,
try to take a picture.
Woman:
Okay, forgive me.
But you do realize
you're talking about him
like if he was an animal.
Progress out.
(chime)
Woman:
Today, on Star News,
we haven't--
Progress up.
(chime)
Up.
Up. Stop.
(alarm ringing)
(chattering on TV continues)
Computer:
The time is 4:45 am.
(alarm continues)
Vision off.
Computer:
The time is 4:45 am.
Alarm off.
Computer: The time is...
(alarm stops)
All lights,
level two of ten.
♪ ♪
(heavy breathing)
(heavy breathing continues)
(fence rattles)
(beeps)
Woman:
You run, too.
I know who you are.
And now I know
where to find you!
I know where you live!
(car alarm blares)
Hall lights on full.
(knocking)
Woman:
Victor.
(knocking)
My name is Emilina Fox.
And I'm
a "World News" journalist.
Here's the thing;
I just want to talk.
(sighs)
Just give me
a second, okay?
Emilina:
Victor?
Look, I'm by myself.
I'm giving you
a choice here.
Talk now, or I can make this
very public, very quickly.
(sighs)
Emilina.
Fox. Yeah, I got it.
Um, could we go sit?
What do you want?
I just want to talk.
Fox:
This is incredible.
You've been here,
this whole time, alone?
Am I the first person that--
The first woman?
All right, look.
I'm gonna need you
to sit down,
and tell me
what you want.
On the chair.
Talk.
I want to know
where you've been hiding.
What you've been doing,
how you survived.
When you're alone, it doesn't
really matter, does it?
Alone is alone.
Well, self-seclusion
and being alone
aren't exactly
the same thing.
I did not do this to myself!
Where were you
and your dedication
to the story
when there was
two million of us?
A million?
500,000?
When there was 10,000 of us.
You weren't looking for me.
Now that I'm the only one...
why do I suddenly matter?
You're a celebrity, Victor.
Why don't you take
full advantage of that?
If you can't make
the most of this situation,
then how can anybody else?
Why should I care...
about anybody else?
I am one...
of a kind!
What do people do
to people like me, huh?
Stick me in a zoo?
Lock me in a lab?
What are you doing here?
You're locked up here.
I mean, you're no more free
here in this apartment
than if you were
locked behind bars.
It's a choice!
Do you even know
what a choice is?
Oh, fuck!
There has to be a way.
You think I'm stupid?
You don't think
I want to be out there
all the time?
I am literally...
a statistic.
And I don't need
to be confronted
by more people like you,
trying to push their way
into my life.
Please, please.
Hey, hey, hey!
Oh, my--
You don't get it, do you?
Could you stop, please?
No.
Let me go.
You said you came here
for a reason?
Want to see
what it's like
to be me?
(whimpers)
You're not alone.
(cries)
I'm sorry.
It's not something that I--
It's okay, you don't
have to explain.
I--
That was me,
I pushed too hard.
(sighs)
I need to show you something.
That's my son.
He turns ten today.
And I promised him...
I get it.
How could we understand
what it's like to be you?
But you have to understand
that we're not all
the same either.
I'm just a woman
that fell in love
with someone like you
years ago.
A lot like me?
'Cause you, uh...
had a kid with some
black guy?
I just thought that we could
help each other this time.
I don't want
my son to feel alone anymore.
Okay.
I'm gonna go.
Wait.
(sighs)
What's his name?
Xavier.
(News reporter
speaks inaudibly)
Man #1:
But there is
no such thing as race.
Woman:
Well, you tell that
to all of the young black boys
and grown men
who found themselves
disproportionately in jail
15, 20 years ago.
Man #2:
They were actually around.
(chattering)
We're not only talking
about the fact that there was
a racial divide in our culture,
in our world,
that lasted decades.
Centuries.
What we're really
talking about
is that the man we all thought
was the last of his kind
on the face of the earth,
he's reappeared.
Woman:
Once known as potentially
the last living black man
in the world, Victor Jefferson
has been seen again.
(Reporters speaking
foreign languages)
(static)
(music plays)