(laughter)
MOTHER:
You must be so tired.
Okay.
Well, I'll sing the song.
What? No.
(laughing):
Nobody films. Daddy, no.
FATHER: I'm n-not filming.
There's no phone.
MOTHER:
I look ancient. Look at me.
- FATHER: I-I'm not filming.
- MOTHER: Okay.
FATHER:
It's off.
MOTHER:
♪ You are my sunshines ♪
♪ My only sunshines ♪
♪ You make me happy ♪
♪ When skies are gray ♪
♪ You'll never know, dears ♪
♪ How much I love you ♪
♪ Please don't take my sunshines away ♪
♪ The other night, dears ♪
♪ As I lay sleeping ♪
(fading):
♪ I dreamed I held you... ♪
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
You can come say hi if you want.
FATHER:
Yeah, I don't know, bud.
I, uh... I don't think that Mom
wants to see me right now.
But she called and said
she'd be waiting for you
with open arms, so go ahead.
Go, go, go.
Be nice to your mother.
Mommy?
Mom?
LUKAS:
Outside?
(door opens)
LUKAS:
Elias.
Come on.
- Mommy?
- Mom?
(flies buzzing)
MOTHER:
You're early.
I was still getting ready.
(sighs) I know... I know this is weird.
I-I wanted to...
I did try and call ahead of time
to explain things, but...
Um... anyway, it doesn't matter.
You're here now.
And look at you.
So grown up.
You're gaining on me.
Believe me, I...
I hate that you have to see me like this,
but it's nothing to be afraid of.
It's still me under here.
Mommy just had a...
a little procedure.
A surgery.
Are you sick?
No, no, I'm not sick. I promise.
Everything's fine.
It's just...
I don't know, I needed a...
change, fresh start.
You know, like, when a car gets older
and you have to take it in for repairs?
People can be like that, too.
(chuckles):
Sometimes you just need a little tune-up.
Dad didn't say anything.
Well, I was hoping
this could be our little secret.
What do you think?
LUKAS:
Where are my headphones?
I thought I left them here.
(clattering)
What do you think
she looks like under there?
Remember when we saw
that raccoon that got run over
and there was all that,
like, blood and white stuff
- all over the road? (retches)
- Ew. Stop. Stop it.
- Gross. Stop it. That's Mom!
- Probably like that
but all over Mom's face, like... (groans)
- Like, oozing blood...
- I said stop it!
MOTHER:
Is there something wrong?
- Nope.
- No, Mommy.
Okay, good.
I just wanted everything to be perfect.
Anyway, I, um... I got you something,
but you got here
before I had a chance to wrap it.
What is it?
An F-18 Super Hornet.
So you like it?
- So much. Thank you, Mommy.
- Yeah.
Oh, good.
Now, if I can get you to help me
with a few little house rules.
Just while Mommy's healing.
Rules?
Like what?
Easy things.
Like no running or shouting in the house,
and no visitors or play dates.
Just for a while,
just for some peace and quiet.
And the sun,
it's not good for Mommy's skin,
so let's keep the blinds closed.
And my office and my bedroom: off-limits.
So's the barn.
Uh, but what about if...
And no arguing, okay?
What Mommy says goes.
You think you can do that?
Yeah, sure.
Elias, do you hear me?
Yes, Mommy.
Good.
Hey.
Why don't you run outside and play?
- You can unpack later.
- (chuckles)
Mommy?
Yeah?
I made this for you.
Thank you, sweetie.
♪ ♪
(gunfire and indistinct shouting
continue over phone)
Since when do you have a phone?
It's Dad's old phone.
He gave it to us.
Don't want you spending
all your time on that thing.
We could do something together.
It's been a long day, Elias.
But we're not tired.
It's not even 8:00.
- WOMAN (over TV): No, wait!
- (dramatic music playing)
There it is. Yes of course. I see it.
It's something dark and sinister.
You are in grave danger.
MOTHER:
"His yellow skin
"scarcely covered the work
of muscles and arteries beneath;
"his hair was of a lustrous black,
"and flowing;
"his teeth of a pearly whiteness;
"but these only formed
a more horrid contrast
"with his watery eyes,
his shriveled complexion
and straight black lips."
Good night.
You-you didn't sing the song.
MOTHER:
Not tonight, Elias.
But you always sing the song.
(sighs)
You're too old for songs.
Close your eyes.
You'll be asleep before you know it.
(footsteps receding)
LUKAS:
What?
I didn't say anything.
I can hear you thinking.
It's nothing.
(Lukas sighs)
Don't you think something's different?
With Mom?
What if it's been so long
since we saw her...
...that she doesn't like us anymore?
She's our mom. She has to like us.
It's her job.
♪ You are my sunshines ♪
♪ My only sunshines ♪
♪ You make me happy ♪
♪ When skies are gray ♪
BOTH:
♪ You'll never know, dears ♪
♪ How much I love you ♪
♪ Please don't take my sunshines away. ♪
♪ ♪
(breath trembles)
(exhales)
(insects chirping)
♪ ♪
...for the entire tristate area,
a severe thunderstorm warning
beginning tomorrow evening
and lasting until early Friday.
- (BB gun fires)
- (birds chirping)
(BB gun fires)
(birds chirping)
Hide-and-seek in the woods?
You can hide first.
Hey, Elias.
Elias.
What do you call the better-looking twin?
What?
Well, most people just call me Lukas.
(Lukas laughs)
(laughs)
(crows cawing)
Maybe she shut it up last winter.
Mom said not to.
Elias!
♪ ♪
LUKAS:
Elias, what are you doing up there?
(crows cawing)
What were you doing in there?
I gave you specific instructions.
- Stay where I could see you.
- It wasn't my fault.
Oh, 'cause nothing is ever
your fault, is it?
No, Mommy, we only went
in there for a second.
Do not say another word.
- Lukas lost his baseball glove, and...
- Stop talking!
- (thud)
- (Elias groaning)
From now on, you stay inside.
You okay?
I didn't mean to get us in trouble.
You didn't do anything wrong.
♪ ♪
- (Elias groans)
- LUKAS: Sorry.
That spot in the barn...
I think it was blood.
What spot?
The one on the wall.
(Lukas sighs)
Probably just paint or something.
♪ ♪
(gunshot)
(gasps)
MOTHER:
Yeah, that's the problem.
He's never apart from Lukas.
(woman speaking indistinctly over phone)
MOTHER:
I caught him sneaking into the barn today.
I'm telling you,
he knows something's wrong.
♪ ♪
Well, I-I just...
I don't think I can stand
another second in this house.
I need to put an end to it.
I need him gone.
Just how much longer
do I have to keep pretending?
(wood creaks)
Hold on.
(gasping breaths)
♪ ♪
(breath trembling)
(insects chirping)
♪ ♪
LUKAS:
What did she mean, "pretending"?
ELIAS:
I don't know.
But she doesn't like
that we're always together.
Huh.
What?
(footsteps approaching)
MOTHER:
Good morning.
(beeps)
(whirring)
I heard the laundry.
You washing something?
Hello?
What's in the wash?
My sheets.
(cell phone ringing)
MOTHER:
Hello?
- WOMAN (over phone): Is now a good time?
- Just a second.
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter inside)
I can't hear anything.
Me, neither.
(device beeps)
Say something.
(echoes):
Hello?
ANNOUNCER (over TV):
...with no food, no water,
-no clothes,
-(indistinct chatter over TV)
Do they have the skill
and the will to survive?
(man grunting over TV)
Naked and Afraid.
♪ ♪
Where do I put it?
Somewhere she won't look.
Her medicine.
Says "may cause drowsiness."
I hope she took a lot.
Just put it under the bed.
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter over TV)
(whispers):
In there.
(sighs)
("A Girl Like You"
by Edwyn Collins playing)
♪ I've never known a girl
like you before ♪
♪ Now, just like in a song
from days of yore ♪
♪ Here you come a-knocking,
knocking on my door ♪
♪ And I've never met a girl
like you before ♪
♪ ♪
(object clatters softly)
♪ You give me just a taste,
so I want more ♪
♪ Now my hands are bleeding
and my knees are raw ♪
♪ 'Cause now you got me
crawling, crawling ♪
♪ On the floor ♪
♪ And I never known a girl
like you before ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You made me acknowledge
the devil in me ♪
♪ I hope to God
I'm talking metaphorically ♪
♪ Hope that I'm talking allegorically ♪
♪ Know that I'm talking 'bout
the way I feel ♪
♪ And I've never known a girl
like you before ♪
♪ Yeah, it's all right ♪
♪ Yeah, it's all right,
yeah, it's all right ♪
♪ Yeah, it's all right ♪
♪ Yeah, it's all right,
yeah, it's all right ♪
♪ Yeah, it's all right ♪
♪ Yeah, it's all right,
yeah, it's all right ♪
♪ Yeah, it's all right... ♪
(song fades)
♪ ♪
(breath trembling)
(shuddering)
ELIAS:
I told you something was wrong with her.
And why was she smoking?
She hates smoking.
What?
Lukas, what? Tell me.
Remember when Mom said
we were too old for our song?
What if she didn't sing it
because she didn't know the words?
She sang it every bedtime.
Yeah, Mom did.
I don't think that's our mother.
No.
No, that...
No, th-that makes no sense.
She said she's been pretending.
You're just trying to scare me.
- Pretending to be her.
- Stop it.
Tell me you know that's her for sure,
and I'll stop.
LUKAS:
There.
ELIAS:
Wh-What?
Look at her eyes.
Green.
Blue.
You know I'm right.
That's proof.
Try Dad again.
He's not answering.
Then leave a message.
(door rattles)
MOTHER:
Hello?
- Don't come in.
- (door rattles)
MOTHER:
Come on, open up.
You know I don't like
locked doors in this house.
What are you doing in there?
Nothing.
Okay, well, look, I...
I know things between us haven't been...
seamless.
I'd like to start over.
Forgive and forget.
I made dinner.
Chicken nuggets.
Hello?
We're not hungry.
Well, you'll have to come out eventually.
(whispers):
Call Dad.
MOTHER (on video):
You're not filming this.
FATHER:
I'm not filming. Who's filming?
- No one's filming.
- Come on, honey.
I look ancient. Please.
- No, you-you look terrific.
- Please. Turn it off.
She looks beautiful.
- (Mother sighs)
- FATHER: Do the song.
MOTHER:
♪ You are my sunshines ♪
♪ My only sunshines ♪
♪ You make me happy ♪
♪ When skies are gray ♪
♪ You'll never know, dears ♪
- ♪ How much I love you ♪
- (door rattling)
♪ Please don't take my sunshines away. ♪
♪ ♪
MOTHER:
Where is it?
Get up.
What?
Tell me where it is.
- What?
- What are you talking about?
Don't pretend you're stupid.
You're not stupid.
The phone... give it to me.
- But we didn't do anything.
- (Mother sighs)
You're lying.
You lied to me, you disobeyed,
and you called your father.
Now, the last thing I need
is that man up my ass
about whatever stories you're telling him!
- But we aren't lying! We didn't call Da...
- Shut up!
Do not speak.
Just give me the phone.
No.
- Give it. Give...
- LUKAS: Stop it!
- You can't take that! Stop it! Stop!
- It's not yours!
- Wait.
- Where are you going?
Stop!
What are you doing?
Give it back!
You need to learn what lying costs you.
(garbage disposal grinding)
This is what happens
when you don't tell the truth.
(grinding stops)
That's not fair.
Fair?
You think any of this is fair?
You think I wanted this?
You think I'm enjoying this?
(screams)
(footsteps receding)
LUKAS:
I'll take first watch.
You can sleep.
(button beeps)
(walkie-talkie static hissing softly)
(moaning over walkie-talkie)
What is that?
That's her.
♪ ♪
- (button beeps)
- (static hissing)
(toilet flushing)
(relaxing vocal music playing faintly)
(relaxing vocal music continues)
(breath trembling)
♪ ♪
What are you doing?
- Answer me.
- (grunting)
Answer me.
(yells) Fuck!
What is wrong with you?!
Come back here!
(panicked breaths)
What's going on?
I just wanted to know for sure.
(door rattling)
(thunder crashes)
MOTHER:
Elias, we do not lock doors in this house.
(door rattling)
Sweetie, I'm not mad at you.
I just...
I just want to talk.
Go away.
- (banging at door)
- MOTHER: Open the fucking door!
(banging continues)
Okay, I'm counting to three.
One.
Two.
(loud bang)
(yells)
(panting)
Fuck!
(thunder rumbling)
I've tried to be good to you.
I've been understanding.
I've tried playing along.
I've done everything I was supposed to do.
And this is how you treat me.
Your own mother.
You're not our mother.
What did you say?
Elias, don't.
Speak up.
Get up.
Elias.
You're not our mother.
That's a terrible thing to say.
Don't.
Our mother loved us.
Take that back.
We don't love you, either.
We hate you.
Lukas, tell her.
Don't talk to him! Talk to me!
What did you do to our mom? Where is she?
You're lying, Elias.
- You're not telling the truth.
- I'm not lying.
- You are.
- Say it!
- Say I'm your mother!
- Ow! You're hurting me!
- Say it!
- No!
- Stop!
- I have coddled you too much.
Not anymore. Things are gonna change.
- Do you hear me, Elias?
- (yelps)
Let go of me!
- MOTHER: No more talking to your brother.
- ELIAS: Stop it!
- (sobbing): Stop! Stop!
- No more lies.
- Stop it!
- Say it.
- "You are my mother."
- Stop! It's cold!
"You are my mother."
Say it.
- "You are my mother."
- No! Please.
"You are my mother."
Say it. Elias.
You are my mother.
You are my mother. You are my mother.
(Elias sobbing)
(rain falling)
♪ ♪
(scraping)
(gasps softly)
We need to leave.
(thunder crashing)
It's not safe here.
(thunder rumbling)
Come on!
(thunder crashes)
Hello! We need help!
- Open up, please!
- Open up!
Please open the door!
Help us, please!
(panting)
Nobody's here.
Power's out.
(thunder crashes)
Phone's dead, too.
We'll have to stay here
till the storm ends.
(thunder rumbling)
I wonder where Mom is right now.
Do you think she misses us?
Of course she does.
Do you...
Do you think she's okay?
Mom would fight, like,
a hundred million bad guys
just to get to us.
I'm sure she's fine.
(sighs)
It's too quiet.
Talk to me.
LUKAS:
About what?
ELIAS:
I don't care.
Anything.
Tell me a story.
Okay.
Before we were born...
If you're just gonna make fun...
- I'm not.
- 'Cause I'm not in the mood
- for your dumb jokes.
- Elias, shut up.
Before we were born,
when we were still so small
that no one even noticed we were there,
you and me were one person.
Like how everybody is.
And most people stay that way.
But we were smart.
We decided we would split into two.
That way, we would never
have to be alone again.
(insects trilling)
♪ ♪
(wood creaks)
Lukas?
(floorboards creaking)
(breath shuddering)
♪ ♪
(wood creaking)
(gasps)
♪ ♪
(panicked breaths)
(gasping)
Hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, you're all right, little man.
(chuckles)
Don't worry. Not in any trouble.
I'm just here to help, okay?
Hey, San?
Come here and look what I found.
(chuckling)
This person... who is she?
We don't know.
Her face is all covered up.
But she scares you?
Tell her about the cold water.
Hey, Sandy?
(talking quietly)
GARY:
Okay.
Priority number one.
We got to get you out of here.
- Where are we going?
- SANDY: Somewhere safe.
With an actual bed.
I promise...
I won't let anyone hurt you.
♪ ♪
(turn signal ticking)
No.
They're taking us home.
They can't.
- LUKAS: Turn around!
- S-Stop.
Stop the car.
Please.
♪ ♪
GARY:
Okay.
Out we go.
You're angels, both of you.
To be out there on a night like this?
"Thank you" doesn't even cut it.
GARY:
You should thank your neighbor.
Oh.
If not for their motion sensor, uh...
I don't even want to imagine.
(Mother sighs)
Now, are-are you sure
I can't get you coffee or...
SANDY:
Thanks, we're fine.
Cocoa? Tea? Nothing?
I'm sure the gas is still working.
SANDY:
Really, we're okay.
- GARY: There was one thing.
- SANDY: Gary.
GARY:
What?
Now, if you don't mind...
And, uh... (chuckles)
Feel a little embarrassed to ask you this,
- but I was hoping that maybe I could get a selfie.
- Gary.
Oh. (chuckles)
GARY:
Well, I'm a huge fan, so...
Oh. (laughs)
I didn't know there were any left.
- Well, I... (chuckles)
- I'm flattered, honestly.
But, um, I'm gonna have to take
a rain check, because...
I don't have my face on, so...
Oh, of course.
No, that's, uh... I shouldn't have.
MOTHER:
Please, no. I...
You know, I'm gonna send you
some signed head shots
and Blu-rays down to the station.
It's the least I can do.
Well, look at that.
Thank you.
Uh, we do have
a few more things to discuss.
Uh...
Well, you must be freezing.
Why don't you head upstairs,
run a hot bath.
I'll be up in a second, okay?
♪ ♪
(water running)
Anyone can change their face with surgery.
She fooled the cops.
Well, they don't know her.
MOTHER: I mean, I'd be lying
if I said things have been normal,
but to think I'm some impostor?
SANDY:
We're just trying to get a full picture.
MOTHER:
Mm, I know.
GARY:
Purely protocol. Just checking a box.
SANDY:
Um...
Yeah, I can see how that might be
uncomfortable to discuss.
MOTHER:
But I would never lay a hand on my child.
GARY:
No, no, of course not.
- But, uh, we saw the lip, so...
- MOTHER: Yeah.
GARY:
Had to check.
SANDY:
Can I ask how it happened?
Oh, yeah.
He was playing by the pool
and must have slipped on some water.
(Mother sighs)
I told him, what,
a million times to be careful.
I always told them...
I don't know what to do sometimes.
It's, uh... terrifying.
That line between...
reality and fantasy...
it's vanished.
(Mother sniffles)
Thank you.
I just feel really alone here sometimes.
GARY:
Well, children, they imagine things,
and that-that'll pass.
MOTHER:
Oh, God, I hope you're right.
Oh. (sniffles)
GARY:
Well, we'd better get out of your hair.
(Gary and Mother sigh)
MOTHER:
I really have no words.
But I will be sleeping well tonight.
-We all will be,
-(Gary chuckles)
Under the same roof, safe and sound,
thanks to you guys.
(Gary chuckles)
GARY:
Well, take care.
And I'm gonna get you those Blu-rays.
- GARY: Okay. Thank you.
- (Mother chuckles)
- SANDY: Good night.
- MOTHER: Thank you.
(Mother chuckles)
No one's gonna believe two little kids.
Not while she's around.
So what do we do?
In the morning, we try again.
No.
We need to find Mom.
(footsteps approaching)
They're gone now.
No one here but you and me.
Do you have any idea
what you put me through tonight?
I went out there
looking for you in a storm.
Had to take my bandage off
three days early.
You're lucky I'm not disfigured.
I know you're not asleep.
That's fine.
You can ignore me,
be afraid of me if you want to be,
hate me,
but I'm not going anywhere.
You'll learn to love me someday.
♪ ♪
(pills rattling)
(sighs)
(grunts softly)
(sobbing)
♪ ♪
(blinds open)
(soft crinkling)
This some kind of game?
I'm not playing.
Where's Mom?
(grunting)
(Mother panting)
(chuckling)
(sighs):
Okay.
Okay, let's make a deal.
I promise,
if you stop this now...
...I will not be angry with you.
I'll forgive you.
(paper rustling)
Your eyes... they're blue.
Mom's are green.
Is that what this is about?
My eyes?
Oh, my God.
Elias, that's my heads hot.
I wear colored contacts for work.
They're in my purse downstairs.
Look at me.
My eyes are blue.
♪ ♪
LUKAS:
This isn't working.
If we leave now, we can still
make it to Dad before dark.
I'm not giving up on Mom.
Jesus Christ!
Fuck.
Where is she?
Do not to do that to me again.
Do you hear me?
Now get those sciss...
Shit.
I swear to God, when I get up,
you are so...
Where is she?
How many ways do I have to say it?
I'm right here, Elias.
I fed you. I raised you.
I stayed up at night with you.
I did everything to make you happy.
I'm your fucking mother!
(bucket clatters on floor)
Look, w-we're wasting our time.
She's just gonna keep lying
and making up excuses.
Are you even listening to me?
Jesus. What now?
ELIAS:
Our mom doesn't throw away our drawings.
She keeps them all,
- even the bad ones.
- Okay.
She-she saves them in a shoebox
in the back of her closet.
- I get it.
- No!
No, m-moms don't do this.
Moms put Band-Aids on cuts.
Moms play games with their kids.
Moms... moms sing their boys
to sleep at night. Moms...
(sobs)
LUKAS:
Elias, let's just go.
(Mother crying)
(crying):
Please, Elias.
Please let me...
LUKAS:
Let's just get out of here.
You know this is me.
You know it's me.
LUKAS:
She's faking.
She's been faking this entire time.
We can't stay here any longer.
We need to leave.
Elias!
What are you doing?
Looking for her purse.
Why?
ELIAS:
She said her contacts are in there.
LUKAS:
But she's lying.
We can't believe a word she says.
We need to be sure.
LUKAS: Are we seriously gonna
search the whole house?
It-It's here.
I know I saw it somewhere.
I'm telling you, we're wasting our time.
♪ ♪
LUKAS:
It's in here!
No contacts, just like I said.
- Are you sure?
- You don't believe me?
No, I do, but...
You're letting her get between us.
We need to get somewhere safe,
and then the first thing we'll do
is find Mom.
We're gonna find her.
I swear.
(sighs)
LUKAS:
We can't trust anyone.
We just have to call a car
and act like we do it all the time.
We can't leave her there like this.
If we untie her, she'll try to stop us.
Trust me, it's gonna be fine.
I'm just gonna go pack some food.
Grab what you need,
and I'll meet you downstairs, okay?
♪ ♪
MOTHER:
Elias?
Elias, baby, I know you're there.
There's something I need to tell you.
There you are.
My sweet boy.
You know, I've been thinking.
And you...
You're right.
I haven't been myself.
But...
I'll be better.
I promise.
Everything's cramping. Can you...
Could you just cut one loose
just for a moment?
I don't think I should.
Lukas told you that, didn't he?
You're... you're a smart boy, Elias.
You can think for yourself.
You don't always have to listen
to your brother.
Elias.
Oh, thank you. Such a good boy.
♪ ♪
Why did you rip up my drawing?
I shouldn't have done that.
That was a mistake.
Sometimes people just...
...do things they don't mean.
I was upset.
Why were you upset?
LUKAS:
What are you doing?
MOTHER:
Elias?
- You shouldn't be in here.
- ELIAS: She was thirsty.
I just gave her some water.
MOTHER:
Elias, listen to me.
Don't listen to him.
Listen to me.
I'm your mother.
What are you holding in your hand?
MOTHER:
Please.
Elias, stay with me.
Her arms were hurting.
I was just gonna retie them.
You were gonna let her go.
I was just gonna retie it. I swear.
Stay with me, honey.
Get the tape.
ELIAS:
What?
And a sock.
Why?
To keep her from lying.
Elias.
What are you doing?
No, honey.
My... I'm still healing.
Please...
Elias, please don't.
(muffled grunting)
♪ ♪
LUKAS:
You did the right thing.
Together we're strong, right?
All right, we got cookies, Goldfish.
What about Pop-Tarts? You want some?
Elias, Pop-Tarts?
(knocking)
Hi.
Can you open the door, please?
ELIAS:
What should we do?
Don't let them in. Are you crazy?
But they already saw us.
They saw you.
Get rid of them.
(doorbell ringing)
Guess what. You're under arrest.
Just kidding.
Little cop humor. Sorry.
Would you mind
grabbing your mother for me?
(muffled):
Help!
She went out.
You sure? 'Cause her car's in the garage.
She has more than one car.
GARY:
Eh? There you go. Says she's not here.
You want to tell her we came by?
Where'd you say she was again?
(muffled shouting)
(grunts)
- Help!
- (banging)
(grunting)
GARY:
Give the kid a break, okay?
She probably went into town
for a few minutes.
Can we just let him speak
for himself, please?
Do you know where your mom is?
She went into town.
SANDY:
You know what, why don't we just
- give her a quick call, okay?
- Oh, Christ, Sandy.
It'll only take a second, Gary.
It's not a big deal.
GARY:
You wanted to check up, we checked up.
We can come back later.
She's not gonna be happy
- we're harassing the kid.
- It's already dialing.
(line ringing)
- (muffled grunting)
- (vibrating)
Voice mail.
Satisfied?
DISPATCH (over radio):
2320.
2320. Go ahead.
I'll be back.
Elias, is there something
you want to tell me?
You know, I have a kid.
Little girl.
She's a lot younger than you.
Her name's Alma.
And if, God forbid,
she ever needed help with anything...
Any help at all...
I would hope she would know
how to ask for it.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
(muffled grunting)
You won't get into any trouble.
Okay, we got an overturned
tractor trailer off Route 7.
SANDY:
Elias.
Hey. Let's go.
Everything's fine.
Great. I'm going with or without you.
We'll be back tonight
when your mother comes home.
(engine starts)
(muffled grunting)
(muffled grunting continues)
(loud clang in distance)
(horn honks)
(vehicle door opens, closes)
(vehicle departing)
(whimpers)
(breathing heavily)
(sighs) You're such a bad liar.
We're calling an Uber.
Where are they?
I forgot my toothbrush.
- Seriously?
- I'll be quick.
The car's gonna be here soon.
I-I'll be right back.
Just-just tell them to wait.
♪ ♪
LUKAS:
You need to let me explain.
- You lied.
- Elias...
That's her.
You have to listen to me.
Why do you hate her?
I'll tell you, but you can't let her go.
Look, you have to trust me, okay?
- Just let me go!
- Elias, wait!
♪ ♪
(grunting)
I'm just trying to help you!
(grunts)
Elias, please!
Don't listen to her!
- She's gonna hurt you! Stop!
- (banging at door)
Elias, please!
She just wants you to be alone!
(muffled pleading)
Just open this door!
Elias!
Open the door!
(muffled whimpering)
Elias, she's just gonna lie to you!
Elias, please!
(gasping)
(banging at door stops)
(Mother coughs)
Elias?
Mommy?
Oh, baby. Oh, my baby.
(Elias sobbing)
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, it's okay. It's okay.
I didn't want to do those things to you.
- No, it's okay. It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, sweetie.
I'm right here. I'm right here.
- It was Lukas the whole time.
- Shh.
- He lied.
- No. (shushing)
He said you weren't our mom.
He said I had to hurt you,
but I didn't want to.
(sobbing continues)
It's okay. It's okay.
So you're not mad at me?
No. No, I'm not mad.
No.
I'm scared.
I don't know what's going on.
Will you talk to Lukas?
I think something's wrong with him.
I just want things to be back
to how they were before.
(Mother grunts softly)
♪ ♪
Sweetie...
I need you to do something for me.
I need you to come somewhere with me.
Lukas?
Mom?
I can't find Lukas.
It's okay, honey.
Come on.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
(Elias whimpers softly)
It's okay.
It's okay. I got you.
Lukas?
Come on.
♪ ♪
(soft, shuddering breaths)
It's okay, honey. I'm here.
(shuddering breaths)
♪ ♪
(whimpering)
I need you to look at it, honey.
It's okay.
Just tell me what it is.
- Paint.
- No.
(sets lantern down)
I need you to think hard, honey.
- I don't know.
- Yes, you do, Elias.
You know what it is.
Now, I need you to say it.
Please. Please, Elias.
No more pretending.
I can't... I-I tried,
but I just couldn't handle watching you
talking to him all the time
and playing with him. I...
- Please stop. Stop.
- No.
Honey, listen to me.
It wasn't your fault. It was an accident.
You didn't know the gun was loaded.
You were just playing.
You didn't mean to hurt him.
Please stop.
I know this is hard, but listen to me.
We can start over.
- Stop.
- But I need you to see what's real.
- No.
- Please just...
This is real.
And we decided we would split into two.
That way, we would never
have to be alone again.
MOTHER:
Look at it.
- No more pretending.
- No. No, stop.
(laughter)
LUKAS:
You and me are the same.
And that's what makes us lucky.
I can never hurt you,
and you can never hurt me.
MOTHER:
That line between reality and fantasy,
it's vanished.
- This is real.
- Stop.
- No.
- (shudders)
MOTHER:
No more pretending.
- ELIAS: Please stop.
- MOTHER: No...
- No more pretending.
- Stop it!
(Mother screams)
(Elias's breath trembling)
(whimpering)
Mom?
(crackling)
(fire crackling louder)
Mommy?
♪ ♪
(whimpering)
(retching)
(sobbing)
(trembling breaths)
♪ ♪
(gasps)
(shuddering)
You were... you were just...
You didn't do anything wrong, baby.
And you were so strong.
Aw.
(whimpering)
(crying)
♪ ♪
(music ends)