[music playing]
I'm glad you came over.
I wasn't sure where things
stood with us anymore.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, the things you said
to me last time I saw you.
It made me feel like you
didn't believe in me anymore.
Should I believe
in you, Stephen?
Yeah, you should.
Otherwise, what's the point?
You know, don't you?
[gunshots]
And now take a
good look around.
Statistics tell us that of
this class of 22, five of you
will become exemplary
police officers.
Nine more will stick it
out and collect a pension.
The remaining eight will find it
too tough and you'll wash out.
If you want to become
one of the best,
it's your humanity which
will set you apart.
Just remember that you are now
members of a police department
which is 50 years older
than the Constitution
of the United States.
Serve it with pride.
[cheering]
Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- Hey.
Hey, darling.
Look at this stray I found here.
Uh-huh.
Oh, have you seen
the kids around?
Yeah, they're running
around somewhere.
Are they embarrassing me?
Oh, yeah.
So where are your
folks, Stephen?
Probably playing golf.
Stephen's parents
aren't too thrilled
with his career choice.
Here, have something to eat.
She's beautiful
and she can cook.
Ah, don't try to
charm me, Stephen Smith.
STEPHEN: No, ma'am.
So you boys looked
mighty handsome up there.
Honey, you are looking at
two of San Antonio's finest.
You anxious to get started?
So long as I don't have
to patrol the neighborhood
I grew up in.
It wouldn't be so bad.
In Alamo Heights, a
cop is a public servant.
In the South Side, a
cop can be somebody.
Command respect.
Come on.
Look, I told you
I don't know, man.
I already
volunteered, Farrell.
If we're gonna be on
this job for 30 years,
I want it to mean something.
Don't you?
Yeah, but I've got a
family to think about.
Are you with me on this?
[soft music]
Well, it's official now.
My life is one long
string of cops.
Grandaddy and daddy.
Uncle, cousin.
And husband.
And probably one day my son.
Little rookie Jimmy Dean.
So congratulations, Officer.
Well, thank you, ma'am.
Farrell.
FARRELL: Hmm?
What did Stephen
talk you into today?
Well, he didn't
exactly twist my arm.
I don't want to spend my
time patrolling shopping
malls in Alamo Heights.
Doesn't sound so bad to me.
I want something a
little more than that.
You don't have to go
looking for trouble.
Well, if I'm gonna do
it, I want to do it right.
Oh, I see.
And Stephen thinks
doing it right
is doing it on the South Side.
Oh, yeah, sure.
And he's right.
And we're going to
back each other up,
we're going to keep each
other out of trouble,
and we're always going to
be in each other's corner.
Smith and Tucker.
And I'm wanna tell you what,
that sounds like a bad weapon,
doesn't it?
[laughing]
[sirens blaring]
All right, everybody back.
[crying]
They just kept shooting.
Where?
Show me.
[crying]
They just kept shooting.
Shooting each other to pieces!
They wouldn't stop!
Got enough weapons
there, Guerrero?
Mama raised me nervous.
[country music]
Ah.
So I'm off on a horse.
The guy who runs the stable
starts yelling at him.
Boom, I'm off after
this perpetrator.
Lone Ranger
And I'm getting it too.
I'm getting it.
I drew, aimed, ping!
From a gallop, I shot his
horse right in the ass.
I swear, the perpetrator
got thrown 30 feet.
Broke his neck in two places.
Dead all over.
Man, that's the way
you have to do it.
Improvise.
Do what you gotta do
and let God decide.
Were you ever reviewed
for improper use
of your weapon, Captain?
What, are you kidding?
In case you haven't
noticed, Smith,
you're not in the
academy anymore.
Basic rules, my butt.
We are the line of
demarcation between
what happens or doesn't.
The man's right, buddy.
We cruise alone out there.
It's every man for himself.
Ask Joey Miller's wife.
She got his folded
flag last week.
Joey Miller died because
he didn't stay current.
He hardly ever
went to the range.
Oh, right.
The range.
Target practice.
What the hell do you know
about bad guys, Smitty?
Huh?
Alamo Heights, the cocktail
capital of San Antonio.
What crimes do you ever
see except your neighbors
cheating on their taxes?
Lay off, Frank.
Aw.
You want to hear
something, Smitty?
[shouting on tape]
That's me doing sound effects.
FRANK (ON TAPE):
Come on, get up!
MAN (ON TAPE): [yelling]
FRANK (ON TAPE): Don't
make me hurt you!
MAN (ON TAPE):
[yelling] Stop, please!
FRANK (ON TAPE): So talk!
Come on!
And you call that
doing your job.
You call that being
right with your badge,
beating somebody to death.
Well, no one killed no one.
Do I look like an amateur?
Let's say I had.
Trash like that, it'd be
considered misdemeanor murder.
And you know
something else, Smith?
It'd stay on the street.
It wouldn't bother
nobody upstairs.
What goes down on the
street stays on the street.
[clearing throat]
Come on, Frank.
Your old lady's
waiting up for me.
Hell, I know that's a lie.
She don't even wait up for me.
Bye bye, Smitty.
You know, Shifton
is the kind of cop
that give rednecks a bad name.
No, he's got a point though.
Now, when it comes down
to it, it's either us
or them out there.
You cannot be buying
into that garbage, Farrell.
No, I just had a bad day.
DISPATCH (ON RADIO): At
5th and Grand, a 4 59.
Please respond.
2 6, I've got it.
[siren blaring]
Must have fallen asleep
watching television.
I-- I guess I didn't
lock the door.
What did he take?
I don't know.
Nothing.
Did you hear him and wake up?
[sighing]
Did you get a look at him?
Lucinda, I can't help you
unless you answer my questions.
[crying]
He raped me.
I'm sorry, Lucinda.
I'm really sorry.
Can you identify him?
I know him from work.
What's his name?
Where's he live?
Please don't tell my father!
Don't tell my father!
[crying]
[banging]
I'm looking for
Edward Burkett.
Is he home?
No, is there some kind
of trouble, Officer?
Do you know where he's at?
He's not home.
Mind if I have a look around?
Are you Burkett?
You can't barge in here, man.
You're under arrest
for sexual assault.
You have the right
to remain silent.
If you choose to
give up that right--
You crazy, man.
You messed up good.
You're a big man, Eddie.
You're a real big man.
It takes a big man
to do what you did.
I didn't do nothing.
She begged me to do it.
I was doing her a favor.
You messed up good, man.
I ain't even gonna need
a lawyer on this one.
Well, I got me a witness.
Ain't that right, Ma?
Let's go.
You break into his
home without a warrant,
then you conduct an
illegal interrogation,
and then you strike
a handcuffed suspect
while his mother looks on.
My god, Smith.
Do you have a screw loose?
He baited me, sir.
That's because he knows
the law better than you do.
Will he walk, sir?
Will he walk.
Are you kidding?
He's already back
out on the street!
I'm very sorry, sir.
Well-- well, I can
sincerely believe that.
Thank you, sir.
But, Smith, I want you to know
that I've got enough cowboys
out on the street as it is.
I don't need another one.
Yes, sir.
What did he say?
I'm on probation.
So you're still on patrol.
It could have been worse.
I'm on probation, and Eddie
Burkett, who is guilty as sin,
is a free man!
Well.
Maybe in God's eyes he's guilty.
But a man ain't guilty
till a jury says he is.
3-2, crowded plate.
Go ahead, whiff it
on by her-- oh, god!
Strike three.
She is out, gone, goodbye.
So, Stephen,
when are you going
to find yourself
some nice gal and get
married and have some
kids of your own?
Oh, I'll know
her when I see her.
Every day, every other street
corner I say to myself,
today I'm going to arrest her
and I'm going to know she's
the one.
Don't you talk that way.
There's one fact that still
eludes you about women, honcho.
STEPHEN: I'm sure you're
gonna enlighten me, partner.
Most of 'em like furniture.
Oh, Stephen.
Do you still only have
a-- a bed and a table?
Own not, want not.
You're on a long and
lonely road, buddy.
You better buy some lamps
before it's too late.
Take this home with you
and call it a starter set.
FARRELL: No, no, no, no,
not my favorite chair.
Look at him.
You call it.
Draw.
[gunshots]
Damn, don't you ever get rusty?
Wearing a badge is the
best job in the world,
but it don't mean
diddly if you're dead.
Which reminds me, partner.
I've seen you come off your
shift without your vest on.
I sweat like a
pig in that thing.
All right.
This time you're gonna
do it with your ticket
book in your hand.
[chuckling] No,
go ahead, hot shot.
I'll time you.
On the gun.
[gunshots]
1.9 seconds.
Pretty damn good
shooting, buddy.
[glass shattering]
Hurry up!
What's going on?
They're killing each other!
You gotta stop 'em, please!
Hurry!
Ma'am, I want you
to calm yourself down.
I'll take care of the problem.
[shouting]
WOMAN: Stop it!
All right, break it up.
[shouting]
Break it up, I said.
[grunting]
Gentlemen, break it up.
We're gonna settle this
in a civilized fashion.
[shouting]
I said break it up!
[glass shattering]
WOMAN: Stop it!
Stop it!
Horton, give me
that right now!
Give me that!
Stop it!
Stop it, no!
You're killing him!
You wanna kill a cop?
Get away!
Come on, get off.
[doorbell ringing]
BETH: Farrell,
will you get that?
Yeah.
Hey-- what the hell
happened to you, man?
Were you in a wreck?
Domestic dispute.
Come in.
Do you want a
drink or something?
No, I'm full of painkiller.
I had to come here.
I wanted you to
hear this from me.
Domestic dispute.
What are you talking about?
They were animals.
They didn't give a
damn that I was a cop.
Farrell.
The got my gun.
They took your weapon?
A domestic dispute?
What the hell did
we become cops for?
You take an oath, you put your
life on the line for what?
Marriage counseling!
Hey, hey.
Look at this!
STEPHEN: Take it easy, partner.
No, the hell I will.
Am I wrong, or shouldn't you
be a little PO about this?
You're not wrong.
[game beeping]
- Good shot.
Good shot.
Oh.
[laughing]
You missed.
I think he's just Superman!
LEA: Food's ready.
Good shot.
[laughing]
STEPHEN: All right, all right.
OK.
Why do you all
come in here at 8:00?
You never been in here before.
Oh, you know, we
usually eat doughnuts.
But, uh, my partner here, he
saw you through the window.
Once he got a look at you,
well, I couldn't keep him away.
Well, if he come
in here to see me,
he ain't made much point of it.
Well, you see, he's very shy.
And he was sort of hoping that
you would, um, break the ice.
LEA: Oh, yeah?
Oh, yeah.
Ka-boom!
Hmm.
No better kick in
the butt than watching
those little cowboys fall.
Oh, damn.
[laughing] Let's see, uh,
could you get me some napkins?
I think she's got
some napkins up there.
You know, if you'd slow down,
that wouldn't happen, Farrell.
Can I get some napkins, please?
You bet.
Here you go.
I hope these will be enough.
For Sloppy Joe over
there, I don't know.
Is there something
else, Officer?
Excuse me, I don't
mean to be rude.
Uh, if I'm on the wrong track,
you just set me straight.
But do I remind you of somebody?
No.
Are you somebody?
Stephen.
Hey, would you bring me some
napkins over here, please?
Oh, you're a Stephen.
Uh-huh.
[laughing]
MAN: A large soda and an
extra mashed potatoes.
OK, sir.
That's a two-piece
chicken dinner,
side of slaw, extra
mashed potatoes,
large Coke, and a fried--
[gun cocking]
Up!
[woman screaming]
Shut up!
- Hey, man.
Take it easy, all right.
You can have whatever
cash we have, OK?
Just take it easy.
In here, now.
Now!
You too.
OK.
[woman crying]
OK, OK.
Don't push.
Take it easy.
I think he--
I think he went around back.
Smitty, perp's
coming out the back.
Down!
You in the coat, stop!
Police officer.
Stop!
It's not me, man.
Drop what you're holding.
Clasp your hands
behind your head.
behind your head!
[gunshots]
Right back here.
[police radio chatter]
Close up.
[siren blaring]
Patrolman Smith.
I'm Detective Sergeant
Nicholas, Homicide.
Yes, sir.
How are you doing?
I'm doing all right, sir.
Patrolman Castro tells me
that you fired all six shots.
That's right, sir.
Well, you hit him with five.
That's pretty good shooting.
He didn't seem to
want to go down, sir.
Now, why don't you go on home?
You can finish your
report in the morning.
I'm gonna need your gun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, sir.
I talked to the
manager and it definitely
sounds like a right to shoot.
That's good.
How's Smith?
Hanging pretty tough for a
guy who just lost his cherry.
Patrol, this is 10 Henry 4.
Hey, a blanket out of the car.
Stephen, you all right?
Yeah, I think so.
I think.
I mean, Farrell, I
can't even remember
too much of what happened.
Castro and a civilian
witness are saying that it
was a justifiable shooting.
Damn right.
Empty your gun.
Now, you did what you
had to do, Stephen.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah, I did.
In the, uh, past
year, there were
190 murders in San Antonio.
That's an increase of more
than 25% over last year.
We keep our own
statistics, Ms. Burroughs.
Well, in that
same period, there
were at least 40 formal
complaints of police brutality
and 12 confirmed
shootings of civilians
by San Antonio police officers.
I told your editor that I
would answer some questions.
Do you have any
questions, ma'am?
Well, I--
I have to question whether
the police force is
making things better or worse.
Uh, Ms. Burroughs.
Where are you from?
New York City.
Does it matter?
Well, New York
is a vertical city.
San Antonio is a
horizontal city.
And it's a huge area
for a relatively
small police force to patrol.
Well, it's very simple.
If the taxpayers are willing to
give us enough money to blanket
the street with patrolmen,
we'll cut down on the violence
substantially.
But I don't think
that's going to happen.
So we do the best
dang job we can
do with the resources we have.
Well, what about
the police shootings?
Our sources tell us that
patrolmen are carrying caches
of their own weapons around.
If a police officer is caught
with unauthorized weapons
in a department vehicle,
the first time he--
he or she will be reprimanded.
The next time, he or
she will be suspended.
That is department policy.
I am not going to let San
Antonio become Dodge City.
Well, there's nothing
like a good love story.
That's right, a
man and his gun.
Is that really what
it's like to be a cop?
Oh, no way.
Mostly we find lost kids and
we feed them ice cream cones.
Officer, I think these
people were jaywalking.
Freeze!
Get in the car.
See, when you're
old married folks,
you gotta open your own doors.
What do you mean married?
Oh, you.
Take it easy back there.
I'm watching you.
I want to see two pairs
of hands at all times.
Ooh.
Well, Officer, is that a gun,
or you just enjoy my company?
[laughing]
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey.
You keep your eyes on
the road there, partner.
I can't drive with you
all over him like that.
[grunting]
[sirens approaching]
Keep your mouth shut, old man.
Thanks for the loan.
All right, everything's
going to be all right.
You're going to be all right.
I want you to just
think now, OK?
And I want you to try to
tell me what he looks like.
2 6.
2 4, go to channel eight.
STEPHEN (ON RADIO):
Nothing here.
Why don't you do-si-do
up my way, kemosabe?
STEPHEN (ON RADIO): And
where might that be?
I'm in South Military.
Looks like we got
ourselves a winner, buddy.
Just hold on a second.
I want to talk to you.
You, uh, got a
warrant or something?
How about you got
an ID or something?
Listen, man.
You can't just stop the
citizen in the street.
That's a nice brown jacket.
Expensive.
Turquoise earring,
very hard to forget.
Now, let's see the ID right now.
Take it out.
[laughing]
Spread 'em!
Put your hands behind your back!
I said put them behind
your back, right now!
Come on, boy, now!
PERP: Show me how tough you are.
I ain't fooling with you!
Put 'em back!
You showed that old man how
tough you are, didn't you?
Didn't you!
What do I know about old men?
[laughing]
Farrell.
Let's go.
Don't stink up the upholstery.
They aren't guilty till a
jury says they are, partner.
[murmuring]
Hello, Officer Smith.
I'm Janet Burroughs from
"The San Antonio Star."
Pleased to meet
you, Ms. Burroughs.
Oh, my.
Will Ms. ever catch on in Texas?
I surely hope not, ma'am.
What's up?
That officer up
there is my partner.
He nailed that gentleman sitting
over there with his lawyer
after he beat an old man
half to death for 6 bucks.
And?
Well, we're all hoping
there's justice in this world.
Aren't we, Ms. Burroughs?
Your Honor, the
People respectfully
request a 30-day continuance.
Objection, Your Honor.
We're ready to proceed.
What is the People's problem?
You've had two
continuances already.
Well, Judge, our
victim is a 74-year-old
man who's afraid of reprisals.
Now, we haven't been able
to find him and think
he may have fled the state.
Well, can you
proceed without him?
No, we need his testimony.
I think the old guy's just
running scared, Your Honor.
Well, I'm sorry, but if
you can't find your witness
I have no choice.
Case dismissed.
[murmuring]
You are free.
You're brilliant, man.
You're brilliant.
Don't threaten me, pig.
I got witnesses.
Well, go on, while
my lawyer's here.
Go ahead and say something.
We'll be seeing you
again real soon, sonny.
BAILIFF: Next case.
Docket number 4859,
T. R. Brunell.
Draw.
[gunshots]
You're getting
better, Farrell.
Well, beating you is
what keeps me going.
That's a cute puppy.
Stephen told us
you loved animals.
Yeah, you bet.
Ever heard of a man
giving his fiancee a puppy
for an engagement present?
Isn't that the cutest
thing you've ever heard of?
My, you have brought out a
whole new side of that man.
Yeah.
Beth?
- Mm-hm?
Honey, can I be
perfectly honest with you?
Oh, you don't ask me that.
Well, gotta confess as the
wedding gets a little closer.
I'm a little nervous.
I mean, you know,
I ain't marrying
a schoolteacher or nothing.
That's for damn sure.
Yeah.
So?
I mean, what's it like?
Oh, well.
Uh-- it's not the same
as it was for my mama.
Ferrell has to deal with
a whole different world
that my daddy did.
The violence has gotten worse.
And it used to be a
cop was respected.
Now he's killed.
It's harder.
Now it takes its toll.
Sometimes Stephen will
come home with that,
but I know you can handle it.
I hope so.
You fell in love with a man
who wants to make a difference.
And there'll be
times when you'll
be lying in bed wondering what
he's doing, thinking the worst.
But you just gotta replace those
thoughts with pleasanter ones.
Know what my mama told me?
To try to think of movies
with happy endings.
[suspenseful music]
[gunshots]
Oh, god!
Please, please don't kill me!
Please, please, don't kill me!
Please don't kill me!
I'm gonna die!
Another one of our, uh,
upstanding citizens, a B
and E repeater by the name
of, uh, Bobby Lee Duke
got his house shot
up last night.
I understand Bobby Lee
suffered some property damage.
He buy the ranch?
Nope, but he sure was in
need of some clean underwear.
[laughter]
That's a third vigilante style
shooting this last month.
It doesn't make
us look too good.
Well, you're right.
Whoever it was should've
wasted the little weasel.
One last thing, compadres.
Chief's on the warpath
about unauthorized weapons.
You get caught holding,
you're off the street,
you're behind a desk.
Is that clear?
Sergeant Guerrero,
do you mean to tell
us that officers of the
law are in possession
of illegal weapons?
[laughter]
That'll be all.
Watch your butts out there.
Do they make that
wig for men, Guerrero?
[laughter]
Man, this town's
getting crazier.
Old Bobby Lee's house got
hit with automatic weapon fire.
You mean even the geeks
got primo weapons?
Them Dowads always
going to be knocking
each other off out there.
What do I care what
kind of guns they use?
Well, I care what kind
of guns they use, Farrell.
There's a war
going on out there.
I want to know how
they're packing.
Man, if they want to
take each other out,
why should we lose
sleep over it?
Works for me.
- Works for me.
[upbeat music and chatter]
Oh, honey.
When you get your vacation,
we can take our honeymoon!
Can we go to New Orleans?
OK.
Oh, baby, yeah!
I've never been there before.
- My god, Farrell.
You'd think at least
his folks would
come to their son's wedding.
Oh, well, he doesn't
talk about it that much.
I mean, you know, it's bad
enough he became a cop.
Worse that he works
on the South Side.
And now he's gone
and married into it.
Oh, baby, it's
gonna be so great.
Shoot, I never been
out of Marin County!
[laughing]
OK, Maggie.
Come on, now.
How many daughters you
got getting married today?
I think you owe us one.
We near a speech.
Come on.
- Oh, no, shoot.
- Come on, Maggie,
Come on, Mama.
Don't be shy.
[laughter]
I don't have any words.
Well, that's a first, Mama.
All right, hush your mouth.
[laughter]
Well, I'm sure I just
feel like every momma does
at a time like this, you know.
I'm just happy and I'm sand.
I'm sad because my
baby's going away.
Oh, god.
Mama, don't make a scene.
Well, I'm happy too.
Because she's gone
and found herself
someone who's responsible and
strong and with great buns.
[laughter]
Shoot.
I'll drink to that.
Oh, no you wont.
[chatter]
Mama, wake up.
Aw, honey.
My wife works at City
Hall and the word is that
the chief is
starting to take heat
over all them shoot 'em ups.
You gotta admit,
it's pretty wild.
One sleazebag called in
to report a car bomb.
Of course he forgot
he stole the car.
[laughter]
Got his self arrested.
Bad guys blast each other
away, the courts get clearer,
the taxpayers save a buck.
Self-containment.
I say let's have more of it.
Some people just abdicate
their right to suck air.
[laughter]
There you go.
Welcome to the cop club, boys.
And congratulations.
FARRELL: For what?
Well it only took
you three years
to get the right attitude.
[laughter]
Well, hey, we've all been
through a lot of changes
since we first
put on this badge.
And guess what?
There's gonna be a lot
more before we retire.
Um.
Here's to my partner and
to the brother I never had.
I want you to have a long
life and a happy marriage.
There you go.
There you go, Smitty.
Yeah.
[laughter]
Ooh!
Honest to goodness,
you don't realize
how much junk you've got until
you've gotta move it all.
Ain't that the truth?
That's never been
one of my problems.
Well, I'm gonna give half this
stuff away, no doubt about it.
Maybe keep some of
it in Mama's garage.
Except for that green vase.
There's no argument here.
[gunshots]
Just a little after 2100 hours.
We were packing things
in my wife's apartment
when I heard the
volley of shots.
I came down here to investigate,
and I found the victim already
laying dead in the parking lot.
Thanks, Stephen.
Officer Smith.
Ray Nicholas.
I remember.
You were the first
one on the scene?
That's right.
Did you see anything?
Just the alleged
victim already dead.
Alleged victim?
I can't get real
worked up over a dead car
thief, Sergeant.
Look at that shot group.
We found shell casings from
a .45 up on the bridge there.
That's 60 yards away
through a chain link fence.
You could fit both
those shots in a 10 ring.
[siren blaring]
Hmm.
Not much to go on.
That's some shooting.
Officer Tucker?
Yeah.
I'm Detective
Sergeant Nicholas.
This is Detective
Sergeant Arquette.
How you doing?
What's this all about?
You want to come inside?
No, thanks.
Do you know anything about
the shooting tonight?
- Which one?
- Two-bit burglar.
Some kid stealing a car stereo.
Your partner Smith
was right there.
Oh, where was it at?
19th and San Geronimo.
Oh, that's his wife's place.
You know, he just got married.
What's the point?
You and Smith do a
lot of target practice,
don't you, Tucker?
Yeah.
Yeah, we shoot a little.
What about it?
NICHOLAS; How good
a shot is Smith?
He's good.
So am I.
Well, are you good enough
to crank off three rounds
from a distance of
60 yards at night
and hit a man three times
through a chain link fence?
Yeah, sure, if you give
me a rifle and a scope.
How about a pistol?
This is ridiculous.
Stephen's off-duty when
a shooting goes down.
He calls it in,
stays on the scene.
He does what he's supposed
to do, am I right?
You want to know anything
else, you ask him yourself.
Now may I go in to
my family, Sergeants?
NICHOLAS: Yeah, Tucker.
Yeah, thanks.
I sure rather would be
playing more than just a hunch.
[sighs] Yeah, but
the question is, do you
want your hunch to be right?
[clearing throat]
Farrell, what
are you doing here?
Come over here, check this out.
I need to talk to you.
OK.
Thank you.
Is there a problem?
You're a suspect in the
Terry Folsom shooting.
Oh, come on.
That's crazy.
Whoever's saying that, I
can't believe that, Farrell.
I think they're fishing.
I mean, if they had anything,
you know, they'd charge you.
Stephen, did you say anything
that might have set him off?
Anything--
No.
No way.
No, I gave them the facts,
same as if it was my report.
This is just crazy, Farrell.
I know.
It's all these shootings.
It's just got everybody going.
It's getting everybody.
You know, I didn't
have to become a cop.
I chose this job.
My father wanted me to stay in
college and become a lawyer,
but I did not need some
half-baked legal system
to tell me what's
right and what's wrong.
They're messing with
the wrong guy, Farrell.
Oh.
Come in, Tucker.
Have a seat.
Chief, I want to
thank you for seeing me.
Well, what's on your mind?
Well, I'm sure I'm not telling
you anything that you don't
already know, but Stephen Smith
is a suspect in the shooting
of a burglary the other night.
And you disagree.
Yes, Chief, I surely do.
Now, anyone who
knows Stephen knows
that what these detectives
are suggesting is impossible.
HOGAN: Now look--
No, sir.
Now, if what they told
me is all they've got,
then they are risking
a man's career
because they're under some
kind of political pressure.
Officer, I hope
you're not suggesting
that this department is looking
for some sort of a scapegoat.
Sir, all I am asking for
here is a little fairness.
Now, all they've got out
there right now are stories.
And there are stories
about every patrolman
in this department.
There are stories
about me, and I'm
sure there were
stories about you
when you were in uniform too.
Now, you hold it right there.
That's enough.
I'll be the judge of whether
or not an investigation
is being conducted properly.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
Then you're dismissed, Tucker.
Hey, loose lips.
You talking to me, Frank?
Word is you went to the
chief for your buddy buddy.
Is that true?
That's true enough, not that
it's any of your business.
Nice move, Tucker.
Guess what list you
just went the top of?
Listen, Frank, why don't
you get to the point, huh?
Chances are Internal
Affairs will stay out
of this unless someone like you
is in there stirring things up.
Then we run the
risk of a rogue cop
being put on public display.
A rogue cop?
How can you complain
about a rogue cop
in this department shift?
And when was the last time you
played by departmental rules,
huh?
You still got that little
tape recorder with you, huh?
Come on, Farrell.
Nobody thinks Smith
is guilty, OK?
It's a bum rap.
Well, is that
right or isn't it?
Just say it.
All right then.
You keep your mouth shut
or I'll shut it for you.
Any heat your sweetheart
takes better not
burn anybody else, bubba.
[glass shattering]
[grunting]
Come on, guys, break up!
Grab him!
Come on!
Why are these guys so jumpy?
Tucker broke the code
when he came to you.
Hmm.
What do we got here?
A trigger-happy cop.
Maybe two.
[shouting]
Aw, check it out.
Be cool.
Must be lunchtime, otherwise
you'd all be hard at work.
Oh, but you are
working, aren't you?
All right, everybody,
let's come up with some ID.
Oh man.
Man, we're just kicking back.
We ain't doing
nothing wrong at all.
These ladies are
so attractive, I'm
gonna give them a screen test.
Hey, man, what's
this all about?
Damn, man.
Are you crazy?
Say cheese.
OK, you've got yourself three.
That's it for you, man.
This is no time to be shy.
Wait, no!
Look, just no picture.
It ain't right.
Since when does a punk
like you decide what's right?
Clinton Corey.
Look, man, if I
ain't under arrest,
you can't take my picture.
No!
Maybe you got more to hide
than just your face, Clinton.
Look, man, you got family?
You got kids?
You take my picture, and
maybe someday you won't.
You just threatened an
officer of the law, Clinton.
No, man, I didn't
say anything at all.
Did y'all hear me say anything?
WOMEN: Mm-mm.
I didn't.
OK, no screen test for you.
But you're never going
to get to be a star
with that attitude, Clinton.
Easy, partner.
It's just me, class of '79.
Hey.
What are you doing
sneaking around here?
I want to talk to you.
All right.
I know what you've been doing.
Going to the chief.
Laying into Frank Shifton.
But your my best
buddy, and I don't
want you getting fired over me.
- Come on, Stephen.
This is a bunch of bull.
I can't just stand aside.
No, that's what
I want you to do.
That's exactly what
you have to do.
I'm innocent.
You're standing
by the right guy.
But let me ride it out, OK?
I can handle it.
It's my beef.
And I can take care of myself.
All right?
Farrell, don't make it
harder on me, all right?
All right.
Come on, I'll buy
you a cup of coffee.
[suspenseful music]
[explosions]
[dogs barking]
Oh!
You go over to the
Johnsons and call 911.
Hurry, 911!
Hurry, hurry!
How you feel this
morning, honey?
Couldn't sleep again last night?
Hi, sweetie.
Hey.
Hey, Marjorie, come on, honey.
[doorbell ringing]
Come on, Marjorie.
Jimmy.
Hey, Lea.
Everything OK?
What's the matter?
Can I come in and talk
to you for a minute?
Well, sure, you bet.
Come on in.
BETH: Come on, kids.
CHILDREN: Hi, Mrs. Smith.
- Say bye, Mrs. Smith.
- Bye!
Bye, Ms. Smith.
- Jimmy Dean.
I love you.
OK.
Hurry up.
You button up your jacket there.
Hey, you want some coffee?
No, thank you, Beth.
FARRELL: Well,
what's the matter?
It's Stephen.
He don't sleep much, Farrell.
And sometimes a whole day goes
by and he don't eat nothing.
Well, he's under
a lot of stress,
and that can kill the appetite.
It's-- it's like a whole
wall goes up around him.
He don't even know
that I'm there.
This investigation
will be over soon.
OK?
He'll be cleared
of all suspicion,
and it'll just go away.
What investigation?
What are you talking
about, Farrell?
Well, he didn't tell you?
The shooting in back
of your apartment.
You don't know
anything about this?
You're starting to
scare me, Farrell.
What are you talking about?
Oh, sweetie.
Sweetie.
FARRELL: There is
nothing to it, OK?
Stephen is a suspect
in a shooting.
It's all political, Lea.
- What?
FARRELL: He didn't do a thing.
He is innocent.
Chief, can I get
some quotes from you
on the bombing of your house?
Number on, no, you may not.
Number two, how'd
you get in here?
I charmed my way
past the duty officer.
Now, why would anybody want
to firebomb your house, sir?
A police chief
has natural enemies.
Yes, but this
crosses the line.
Can you see how this
looks to John Q. Texan?
No, little lady,
how did it look?
Like the bad guys are winning.
Gentlemen, we have
ourselves an image problem.
But it's one there's not
going to be with us very long.
This, uh, lady
reporter says that she
has taking the pulse
of our community
and that there is
a growing tendency
to view this department
as a bunch of pistoleros.
She further notes that
the Chamber of Commerce
wishes to stress
that San Antonio
is America's
fastest growing city
and not part of the Wild West.
Now, gentlemen, we
are going to pay
heed to what's being said here.
From now on, we play it
strictly by the book.
Then our problem is
going to go away.
I do hope that's clear.
One more thing.
As everybody here is aware,
my home recently suffered
an attack by persons unknown.
I want you to know
that my wife is fine.
She's mad as hell,
but she's fine.
I'm here to ask each one of you
to work extra hard and find out
who did this to me.
Thank you.
All right.
Any questions?
Hey, Sarge.
What's a pistolero?
[laughter]
GUERRERO: Let's hit the streets.
DISPATCH (ON RADIO): We have
a domestic complaint at 1 2
1 4 9 Grant, 2 6.
Sounds like some guy's
wailing on his old lady.
2 6, 10-4.
Might need backup.
What's the problem?
I want that good for
nothing out of the house!
You get him out!
All right, ma'am,
just calm down.
You tell us your name.
Lucy Gorgon.
And that-- that animal in
there is Harold Sanders.
I'll tell you what he did.
He rammed his car into mine.
He beat me up, he threw me
out, and he locked the door!
Hell, I pay half the rent here.
Willing to press
charges, Lucy?
I ain't willing
to press nothing.
You just get him
out of the house!
All right, wait here.
Listen, let's just talk to him.
I don't think you should rip
your new uniform if she ain't
gonna follow through in court.
[banging]
You in there, Mr. Sanders?
MR. SANDERS: You
cops get out of here.
This ain't none
of your business!
Yeah, just open up, sir.
All we want to do is talk.
MR. SANDERS: You want to side
with that ho, you go ahead.
She found out what a
man can do, and so will
anyone else who tries to get
in, and that means you too!
Stephen.
Look, he hit a car and took off.
That's just hit and run.
We call a tow truck,
we'll impound his car.
It'd cool his heels for a while.
All right.
Can you hear me?
I can hear you.
Big man when you got
another guy backing you up.
You get the hell off my
property before I come
out there and make you leave!
Why don't you come out
here, you gutless slug?
What you say to me?
You can't say that to me!
Go on!
You just keep walking out!
And you, you get your
ass down the road now!
Go on!
Move on!
Go on, keep walking now!
I'm tired of looking at you!
I need help.
My car's getting ripped up.
No, don't send a cop!
It's a cop that's doing it!
Stephen.
Hey, man.
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
I can't believe you!
I can't believe you did this!
Why not, Farrell?
You heard him.
Mr. Sanderson there
is a man among men.
A man of his caliber
is going to have
this all fixed up in no time.
You should back off.
I can handle it, all right?
Look, is this
how you handle it?
Don't get bent, man.
I thought you had more to you.
Shut up, Farrell.
Oh, you're just going to let
him beat you down, aren't you?
Until you're as bad as they are.
This is your car, all right?
You go ahead and take it.
It's all yours.
[tense music]
[alarm clock buzzing]
Farrell?
Yeah?
Can you listen to this?
What?
Listen to this.
"San Antonio police officer
was suspended yesterday
after vandalizing the
automobile of a suspect
in a routine domestic dispute.
Police Chief Hogan claiming
that the officer, Stephen Smith,
lost his cool."
It says he took strong
action as quote,
"a demonstration of my intent
as chief of this department
to see to it that each and
every officer of my force
performs his duties strictly
according to the book."
End quote.
Did you know about this?
Yeah.
Yeah, he blew it.
I was there.
I'd better go find him now.
[chatter]
Have you seen Stephen around?
I don't know where
he is, Farrell.
I don't know what he
does with his time.
He's lost without his badge.
[suspenseful music]
[chatter]
Who is it?
What you want?
Oh.
Got your camera, cracker?
Not quite.
Not this time.
[gunshot]
Clinton Corey was a pimp who
dabbled in running numbers.
He could've had a
million enemies.
Is there a possible connection
between the Corey shooting and
any other vigilante shootings?
That'd be a good story, but
no hard evidence to support it.
Clinton Corey was shot
point blank by someone
he probably did business with.
Sergeant, can I talk to you?
Janet, will you
excuse us for a minute?
Sure.
I believe Smith's suspension
is connected to that shooting
outside his wife's apartment.
And you guys are still after
him on that, aren't you?
You offering evidence, Tucker?
That was a long time ago.
If you guys had anything,
you'd have charged him by now.
It's tearing him to
pieces, Sergeant.
I'm doing my job, Tucker.
If it'll make you
feel any better,
you're no longer a suspect.
You guys are
unbelievable, you know that?
Let me tell you something.
If you push Stephen
Smith over the edge
and come to find out
that you're wrong,
well then you're gonna
have to come deal with me.
All right, Nicholas?
[country music]
9-inch barrel.
Of course it's gonna be more
accurate than a smaller barrel.
The thing is, you got this
here, and pointing it down--
Oh, right.
Give me a double
bourbon, Hank.
Oh, Farrell!
It's not even happy hour yet.
Has anybody seen
Stephen around?
Uh, he wouldn't come in here.
He's not exactly this
month's cop centerfold.
Hey!
Now, Stephen is twice the
cop any of us will ever be,
and you know it.
Maybe he is, OK.
But if you care about
your future on this force,
you might just want to
keep your nose out of it.
Is that what you
think too, Castro?
Kevin's got a point, Farrell.
You know, I got a
pension to think about.
It's so dangerous
now, they've got
the attendant in this
bulletproof glass booth
with no door.
You've seen these in the
self-service station,
haven't you?
Yeah?
There's just a little hole
to stick the money through.
How does this guy
get into this booth?
[laughter]
Daddy?
Wanna have a fast wheels race?
Uh-- uh, no, not
tonight, pal, all right?
When?
Well, how about
tomorrow night, OK?
We'll play with
it tomorrow night.
- OK.
Well, I'll just go set up
the track anyway, in case
you change your mind.
All right, you go
ahead and do that then.
Plus, you might
change your mind.
Yeah, I-- I might.
[phone ringing]
Hello.
Yeah.
Hi, Lea.
Yeah, wh-- OK, good.
That's good.
All right, let me--
let me talk to him, OK?
Oh.
Uh-- yeah, well, um--
well, at least he's home.
OK.
I'll see you later, then.
Bye.
Stephen got home.
Oh.
It's about time.
And went straight
to bed, Lea said.
Well, maybe you
should too, honey.
You haven't been
sleeping too well lately.
You know, they're gonna
hang Stephen out to dry.
Just to show how hard
they've been working
to keep this town straight.
He was in the wrong
place at the wrong time,
and now he's gotta
take the heat.
Politics isn't who gets elected.
Politics also says
who gets eliminated.
Politics are also
temporary, Farrell.
Nobody is on the top or
on the bottom forever.
Not if you're a cop
that's going to jail.
They want him for murder.
And Stephen said he would
rather die than go to jail.
Officer Smith, you have been
suspended not for defending
yourself in any improper way
but because you willfully
destroyed private property.
I'm fully aware that, sir.
What I hope to do is look
hard at the word willfully.
The reason that I'm
appealing the suspension
is because I feel like I wasn't
reacting to the situation that
was occurring, but
rather to the one
that had happened before, the
one that I was almost killed.
I got it reversed, Farrell.
All right.
OK.
And aren't you
ashamed of yourself?
Look, I didn't mean to--
Punching out your best buddy.
All right, I shouldn't have.
I shouldn't have.
You see?
You lost faith in me.
I told you I'd handle it.
I got half a chance when
I'm not dealing with all
that political garbage.
Here's to the Civil
Service Commission, who knows
a great cop when they see one.
Cheers.
I second that.
When y'all going
back to work, Stephen?
Tomorrow.
And we are gonna
stomp somebody, partner.
The criminal elements
in San Antonio
will not sleep well tonight.
Bet you're gonna be happy
when he gets out of the house.
Whatever makes you say that?
You don't have
to worry about Lea.
She's a good old girl.
She can take care of herself.
Well, here's to
getting back to normal.
Hey, hey.
[chatter]
Michael Sturtevant.
We meet again.
They cut me loose, man.
What do you want?
Nothing.
Just memories.
Well, I don't even
know who you are.
Michael Sturtevant.
Your specialty: assault
on defenseless old men.
MO: nighttime on foot.
Home address: 13--
13 something Vista Place.
That is a soaring
intellect you got.
I'm a poet now.
Did you know that?
When life has been
lived too long
and the sun is
low on the sky, we
must take our
place in the ground
and cover the grave
with flowers of evil.
What you think?
Got a shot at the Pulitzer?
[suspenseful music]
Michael Sturtevant.
Professional punk
and two-time loser.
Third time's a charm.
Judging from the trajectory, I'd
say he was shot from the roof
of that building over there.
Whoever it is, he
likes a challenge.
- Farrell.
- What?
Going shooting out
at the Grove tomorrow.
You want to come along?
Well, I've got a choice.
I can keep buying ammunition,
or I can make my house payments.
Got a quarter?
No.
Did you hear another one
went down last night?
No, what?
Remember that punk
that wore the earring
and liked to beat up on old men?
Someone rid society of
Michael Sturtevant last night.
Hi, Janet.
Thanks for coming.
Hi.
My curiosity is overwhelmed.
Janet, what if I were to
tell you that I think there's
a connection between the
sniper shootings of Terry
Folsom and Michael Sturtevant
and the point blank shooting
of Clinton Corey?
This is on the record?
No.
I believe strongly that
the person who's committing
these murders is carefully
selecting his victims
based on their criminal record.
Now, if you're writing
an article about this,
I would also mention what
a good shot this person is.
How he can spray a house
with automatic weapon fire
and not hurt anybody.
But when he wants
to put someone down,
he can do it from 60
yards with a pistol.
Raymond.
We're talking about someone who
has access to criminal records
and is a sharpshooter.
Ray, are you telling me
this person is a cop?
I wouldn't tell you to
walk away from that theory.
Forgive my cynicism, but
am I being set up here?
Janet, Chief
Hogan has asked me
to use every means to
apprehend this shooter,
who is also most
likely the man who
firebombed the chief's house.
And I am using every means,
and you are one of them.
[suspenseful music]
[dog whimpering]
Go on, get.
Get!
[dog barking]
What did you do
to her, you bastard?
STEPHEN: I didn't do anything.
Would you listen to her!
The stupid dog was
sniffing around my guns.
I didn't want it to get hurt.
You are such a liar!
Don't you call me a liar!
Oh, you're not a liar?
Did you ever tell me
about all the trouble
you were in about what
was happening to you?
No.
Farrell had to tell me.
For one thing, it's none
of your damn business.
And for another thing, Farrell
should keep his big mouth shut!
Would you just listen
to yourself, Stephen?
Farrell is the only
real friend you've got.
I don't even know you anymore.
I can't live like this.
I cannot live like this!
I can't take this
anymore, Stephen!
I'm leaving!
No.
No, you're not.
You are not leaving me, Lea!
I am not going to be
attacked by everyone!
You are staying right here!
You listen up, girl.
You listen up, girl!
I am not gonna have
you joining forces
with everyone against me!
What are you talking about?
I don't know and I don't care!
You're crazy, Stephen!
Do you wanna know
what I'm talking about?
You wanna know what
I'm talking about?
I'll tell you what
I'm talking about.
I'm gonna tell you a
secret now, baby, that's
gonna join us at the hip.
Ah!
What?
Stephen, stop it!
Stop!
No!
Stephen!
[crying]
I swear I was
gonna pay for it!
They didn't give me a chance.
Next time you'll
be more careful.
[glass shattering]
Dammit!
Stop!
Hey, man!
Hey!
Watch it!
Oh!
Put your hands
behind your back!
Ah!
Ah, it's hurting, man!
You all right?
PERP: You're hurting me!
Get up!
I was about to pay, I swear!
Oh, what, you're
gonna cry for me?
You're gonna cry for
me, a big man like you?
Break my heart,
you gutless punk.
I didn't do anything, I swear!
- Shut up!
- I didn't do anything!
- I didn't!
Ah!
You want something
to cry about?
- I didn't do nothing!
- Shut up!
Take that!
Take that, take that!
Here!
Take that!
Take it like a man, huh!
What's the matter, Officer?
Have you forgotten
how to take orders?
The gun too.
Sergeant, see to it
that Officer Smith is
booked on assault and battery.
Man, I've never seen
anything like this.
Little old lady's
complaint was you
slapped around some
shoplifter, and you get this?
It's like the chief's
gonna come down
on you with both boots, man.
Hey, Sarge.
Chief tells me you're
sending me a bad guy.
Famous too.
A real legend.
Just book him, Frank.
Paperwork will be sent down.
Brutalizing the
citizenry, huh.
My, my.
I thought you'd learn more
than that at the academy.
Indefinite suspension
same as being fired.
You're out of here.
Drop dead, Shifton.
What goes down on the
street stays on the street.
You forgot that rule.
It's the only one you
should never forget.
Your buddy never should've
gone to the chief.
When you made Hogan
eat his suspension,
he just figured he'd
wait for you to screw up.
How didn't have to
wait too long, did he?
Take this guy against the wall.
You know the routine.
Side.
[door buzzing]
Farrell.
Thank god.
I knew I could count on you.
Not you too.
I don't know.
I thought I was sure,
but I don't know anymore.
You're too out of control.
No.
That's where you're wrong.
You gotta listen to me.
They are doing everything
they can to break me because I
am too much in control.
It's all political.
They need somebody
to take the fall.
You want me to
believe in you, then
you answer me this question.
You ask me anything.
I'm your friend.
I won't lie to you.
Why didn't Lea leave you and
why won't she talk about it?
Or is that political too?
No, of course it's not.
She's a victim, just like I am.
And the main reason I gotta get
out of here is to talk to her.
Stop dodging the question.
Why'd she leave you?
You want to know
why she left me?
- Yeah.
- I'll tell you why she left me.
Because she's weak.
She's a frail, gentle woman.
That's why I didn't
tell her my troubles.
Look what happened.
As soon as I told her,
she panicked, she ran.
The strong have to
protect the weak, Farrell.
That's the truth.
That's why I became a cop.
All my life, everything I
worked for, it's all gone.
She's all I got left.
I gotta get out of here
so that I can talk to her.
I spoke to the prosecutor.
He's going to recommend
that you be released
on your own recognizance.
[suspenseful music]
[knocking]
Open the door, Maggie.
Stephen, don't you
make me call the cops.
I love her, Maggie.
I'm not gonna hurt or.
Now open the door.
Come on.
I won't say long.
You're not gonna hit me again?
No, I'm not gonna hit you.
Lea.
We're partners.
And from now on, I'm gonna
let you in on everything I do.
You already told me too much.
If Stephen takes advantage of
his suspension to get therapy,
well that's gotta
work in his favor.
Stephen would never
go to a therapist.
He's already whistled
through several
psychological evaluations.
Honey, you should have
seen the way he looked
at me when he was in jail.
I don't know.
You know, it made me wonder.
I didn't know him anymore.
[car approaching]
Tell me what happened.
It don't matter what
he might do to me.
I gotta make myself
right with God.
Tell me.
He did it.
He's guilty.
He killed them all.
How do you know?
Where's the proof?
He hunts people like animals.
He told me it's him who kills
what's wrong with the world.
It's him, Farrell.
The killer cop.
Where is he?
Where is he right now?
I don't know.
But you better find him.
He's not through,
he's gonna kill again.
Hogan's next.
He firebombed his house.
Now he's gonna kill
the chief of police.
Do we have any grounds
at all to doubt her?
Why would she lie, sir?
There's no way to know
what Stephen might do
if he found out she came to me.
Right.
She doesn't have much of
a motive with any of this,
does she?
Can we pull him in now?
On what, a
four-year-old shooting?
Oh.
A renegade cop.
The media will lap this up.
Every one of these shootings
has been premeditated.
If Smith has announced
his plans to gun you down,
then we have to think
he's going to try.
Yeah.
But can we subpoena his
wife before a grand jury
and get her to tell her
story again to them?
Takes time to
convene a grand jury,
and we don't know a heck of a
lot about Smith's timetable.
Well, look, he's
obviously nuts.
Why can't we go to county mental
health, get him committed,
and hold him there until you
can make your case against him?
Because Stephen would make
idiots out of those people.
You remember the Civil
Service Commission?
He conned me, my wife, his wife.
Stephen could lie his
way straight out of hell.
Tucker, are you
willing to help us?
What do you mean, wear a wire?
It might work.
No, sir.
I can't do that.
I could put my
fist into his face.
I could put him into a hospital.
But I can't sneak
around on him like that.
Well, your friend didn't mind
doing that to you, now did he?
If you don't do it,
Tucker, the alternative
could be pretty ugly.
And what is the
alternative, sir?
Put a team on him.
Follow him, wait for
him to make his move.
We have a sharpshooter.
So if I don't help
you bring him in then
I help you execute him?
Is that it?
Now listen to me, son.
Son.
Listen to me.
Stephen Smith has put
himself beyond the pale.
You didn't put him there.
No one else did.
And a moment ago, you
were pretty angry.
Yeah, I'm angry, but
not just with Stephen.
You know, in the academy, you
told us what made us special
was our humanity.
And from day one, our humanity
has been stripped away.
I'll do it-- but not to
finish him off, to save him.
[phone ringing]
Hello.
Hey, cowboy.
What's on that tiny
little mind of yours?
She did?
What'd she have to talk about?
Yeah.
Sure I would.
I'd like to hear all about it.
OK.
Uh, 7 o'clock.
You pick me up.
[suspenseful music]
Honey.
Might have to eat
a little later.
What is it?
Is someone wrong?
No, something
just come up and I'm
going to have to deal with it.
You promised you'd
help me with history.
I'll be back before bedtime.
Hey.
Aren't you staying for dinner?
Nope.
But you go ahead, all right?
OK.
You mind yourself
while I'm gone.
OK?
- OK.
OK.
[suspenseful music]
You know, I was thinking that
Jimmy Dean's got a birthday
coming up, doesn't he?
How old's that boy gonna be?
10?
FARRELL: That's right.
You want to drive?
No, I drove over here.
You can go ahead and drive.
Well, I got them
working on the carburetor,
so we'll see how
bad I screwed it up.
I'm glad you came by.
I wasn't sure where things
stood with us anymore.
What's that supposed to mean?
The things you
said to me in jail.
Made me feel like you didn't
believe in me anymore.
Should I believe
in you, Stephen?
Yeah, you should.
Otherwise, what's the point?
So what did old Lea have to say?
[laughing] Can't live with
'em, can't live without 'em.
Farrell.
You're the one who knew
what I wanted to do.
You're the only one who really
knew what I wanted to do.
But it cost me.
What do you mean?
I mean that if you
lost faith in me--
you know, don't you?
Lea.
She told you.
And who have you talked to?
What have you got, a .45?
Give it to me.
Stephen.
Shh, quiet.
Don't talk.
[gun cocking]
[gunshots]
[tires screeching]
Stephen.
[soft music]