[flash bulb crackling]
[flashbulb pops]
[ethereal music]
[upbeat rock music]
[upbeat music]
- [Danny] Now, that
is a classy Irish pub.
Well, the exterior anyway.
My parents Pete and
Mary built this place
when they came across
the pond from Ireland.
My cousin Phil and I,
we used to play here
like it was a jungle gym.
And I actually lost my virginity
in the walk-in freezer,
which I don't recommend.
This used to be a
popular spot too,
but we hit a rough
patch after my mom died.
Dad started drinking a lot,
much more than the
average Irishman.
We lost customers, and things
have never really been the same.
And actually my dad's been
having a lot of problems
recently, which
leads me to wonder,
what the hell is next.
- Fuck them!
- Jesus, Pete, how
can you tend bar
when you're drunker than
all of us put together?
- What's the matter, Pete,
banks after you again?
- What do you know about banks?
- Kiss my ass, you drunken mick.
[men laughing]
- That's it, I warned you.
[metal clanks]
[men laughing]
[men clamoring]
- What the hell are
you laughing at,
you half-wit shit mopper?
- Hey, calm down, Pete,
just take it easy!
- They think they're
gonna take this place?
- Pete!
- Fuck 'em, I'll show them.
- Hey, hey, hey!
[men clamoring]
[dramatic music]
- Hey, where you going, Pete?
[engine revving]
- You gonna take my bar, huh?
- [ATM] Would you like
to make a deposit today?
- Oh, I'll deposit Sally
up your fucking ass!
- [ATM] Would you like
to make a deposit today?
[alarm ringing]
- Who's laughing now,
you computer cocksucker!
[siren wailing]
[upbeat music]
[singing in foreign language]
♪ It's hot we not up on it
- What are you doing?
- What's up, cuz?
Little CB, little
cocktail break.
- Well it's getting
busy back there,
and Vince is asking about you.
Did you get that
pizza to Emory yet?
- No worries, next
on my checklist.
- So you have a list.
- Yeah, it's right, see,
it's CB and then Emory.
- Okay great, well, it's
been like two hours,
so you might wanna step on it.
- Whatever, you
should deliver it.
Okay, you owe me from last week.
- Oh, yeah, oh, oh, right.
Right, you live in my
basement and I owe you.
- Why do you always
have to bring that up?
That has nothing to do with
what we're dealing with.
- What did you pay me
last month in rent?
You gave me a Boyz II
Men greatest hits CD,
you know, which I liked,
but just, please, why don't
you go and deliver those pies
so Vince doesn't go crazy on us.
- Whatever.
[can clatters]
[phone ringing]
- Shit, yeah.
- Hey, Danny, it's
Gabe Greenberg.
I've gotta talk to
you about your father.
He's gotten himself
into a real jam,
and I'm not sure I can get
him out of it this time.
- What did he do?
- Let's see, he
got drunk, shocker.
And then of course he drove,
and he drunkenly
attacked an ATM.
- [groans] Okay,
holy shit, bail?
- No, I think we're
looking at some time.
I mean, he doesn't have
a dime in the bank,
and unless you start delivering
cocaine instead of pizza,
you ain't gonna be
able to help him out.
Although pot and pizza's
a pretty good idea.
He wants to talk to you
so let's meet at
the jail at 2:30,
and we'll figure it
all out then, okay?
- [Danny] Okay,
I'll see you there.
- All right, buddy.
- I ordered that pizza,
like, 2 1/2 hours ago.
- Oh, yeah, sorry
about that, man.
I had to take this massive shit,
and I couldn't find a restroom,
so I was like driving
around, it was crazy.
[dramatic music]
- There's a fuckin'
piece missing.
- I don't make 'em,
I just deliver 'em.
Sometimes they organize
it differently.
- You ate my pizza.
- Okay, hold on, 11.50.
- No, I ain't paying shit.
- Oh, you're paying for it.
[shouting]
- Shit.
- Motherfucker!
- You're gonna pay, man.
You're gonna pay, man.
- Hey, what the hell's going on?
- This deadbeat
motherfucker won't pay.
- He ate my pizza.
- We'll get you a
new pizza, all right?
- Yeah, we'll see about that.
- We'll see right now.
- Yeah.
[Phil yells]
- You fired.
- What?
No, no, Vince, hold on.
Let's just back up a second.
We can talk about this.
We've been here before man.
- You drunk dummy, no more
drink beer, no more eat pizza.
Bullshit.
Get out.
- I'm bullshit?
You're bullshit, motherfucker.
You're Chinese and
you're tossing pizzas.
Why don't you get
behind a little stir-fry
and cook me up a
little Kung Pao Phooey.
All right?
You fuckin' wannabe Guido-ass.
- You fired!
You both fired.
- Whoa.
- Get out of my store!
[swears in foreign language]
You ain't seen nothing.
Get out of my store!
Hey!
[shouting]
- Hey, Pete.
- Uncle Pete.
- Dad.
- What's the damage, Rabbi?
- The best the D.A. will
offer us is 60 days in here
or 31 days in a state-sponsored
rehabilitation clinic.
- What?
I thought you Jews were
supposed to be smart.
- Well, we did split the atom
and perfect the Ponzi scheme,
but the Asians have co-opted
the smart stereotype.
And the small-penis
one, thank God.
- I hear rehab is a breeze.
- I heard it's
actually kind of fun.
Big rubber balls and
cookies and punch.
- Shut up, you two.
I didn't bring you
here for moral support.
You two will have to run
the bar while I'm in.
- Wait, what are
you talking about?
- I've got the house
down as collateral,
and if I don't make a
$10,000 payment on the 1st,
they're taking the bar,
they're taking the house,
and you two will be out on
your asses where you belong.
- Don't give me shit.
It's not my fault that you ran
everyone out of your own bar.
- Who do you think
you're talking to?
- Okay, time to go.
- Don't you lose that bar!
Do not lose that fuckin' bar!
- Can they really
take everything?
- Yeah.
The old man took a second
mortgage on the house,
which I had appraised
at five times its value,
thank you very much.
- All right, well,
tell me this, Gabe.
How much does the bar make?
- I think the better
question would be,
how much does the bar lose?
Danny, you need to go down there
and help out your old
man for a little while,
but you boys also need to
find another place to live.
I'll help you out any way I can.
Just give me the word.
- I can't pay rent.
- Except for money.
You know the thing
about Jews being cheap.
Sorry.
- Yeah.
- You got shit all
over your shirt.
- I'll wash it up,
I'll wash it up.
So what is up with
the wig on that guy?
- I don't,
I feel like I was just punched
in the fucking stomach.
- Okay, so what do we do now?
- Hey, come on.
Stop wasting it, will you?
- It's so good.
What do you got?
- Shanahan's Whiskey
is having a contest.
You write an essay, and you
can win a bar in Ireland.
- Hey, you took a semester
of comp at Nassau Community.
Why don't you give it a
shot, do a little essay?
- Your sarcasm right now?
Not really feeling it.
So you're cut off.
- I was kind of serious.
I think you'd be good at it.
Okay, I'm kidding.
I'm sorry.
Give it back.
Okay, thank you.
- Hey, sweetie.
- Oh, I thought I felt
my balls being tied off.
- I got my mom the
greatest birthday gift.
- What did you get?
- A new daughter?
- Shut up, Phil.
Why don't you go in the
back and play with yourself?
- No, he won't let me--
- That's a no-go around here.
When we were 12, Phil got
caught in the bathroom.
- I don't do that anymore.
- So what did you get?
- A pair of gold chopsticks.
- No!
This is great.
- You know, she's getting
into sushi and yoga and stuff.
- Sushi and yoga is
so hot right now.
This is perfect.
She's gonna love this.
- So don't forget, dinner
at seven on Thursday.
- Oh, well, honey, I can't.
I have to run the bar.
- Danny, I told you
about this two weeks ago.
- I know, but you got
my message, right?
- I've been buttering up my
dad about giving you this job,
and I was counting
on my mom's birthday
to put him over the edge.
- Really?
- What job were you
buttering him up for?
- It's nothing.
Just, you know--
- Working for my father's
insurance company.
- Insurance?
Danny, dream come true.
- Fuck you, Phil.
Everybody needs insurance.
- Everybody also needs
their prostate checked,
but I don't see Danny
lining up for that job.
- Hey, listen, you
know that I want to.
I would love to be
there, but I can't.
I have to fuckin'
take care of the bar.
- Whatever, Danny.
- No, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Listen, so business has been
really bad down here recently
and you are just
cute as a button,
and I was wondering if you
wanted to cocktail or bartend.
Some female energy might
completely arouse some business.
It'd be good for the place.
- So you want me to come down
here and wear a short dress
and maybe even show a
little bit of cleavage.
- Yeah, I think that
would be perfect.
- What do you think I am?
If you want a tap-dancing whore,
get Phil's girlfriend to do it.
- There's no tap dancing
in the donkey show.
- You are such an asshole.
- First, I was kidding.
- Lindz, we should try it
first before we get all mad.
- Fuck this place, man.
This place has been
nothing but trouble
my whole fucking life.
- Yeah.
Oh, man, this place sucks.
I wish I was in the glamorous
insurance industry right now.
- Phil, you know that is
my only ticket out of here.
I have nothing.
I have no degree,
and I have no skills.
- Lindz, with a fuckin' z.
She has a z in her name.
What, she starting junior high?
- She's looking out
for me, all right?
And she's my girlfriend,
and she loves me.
So I'd appreciate
if you'd stop being
such an asshole to her.
Can you do that?
- If that's what you want.
- It's what I want.
- Okay.
- Oh, God, that feels so good.
[moaning]
[laughing]
- Do you like that?
- Yes, I do.
I like it very much.
Go back.
Okay, go back.
Yeah.
[moaning]
- Where are the diamonds?
- God!
You asshole!
- You--
- Shit.
I too can play rough
at this, Miss Sinclair.
- Yeah.
Well, you can play
rough by yourself.
Fuck you, I'm not
kidding about this.
- I thought it would be fun
with the whippy and, babe.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, baby.
I'm so sorry.
That was not fun and I
thought it was gonna be fun.
That was weird.
- It's just my act at work.
It is not what I'm into.
- Okay, so Janine is
not Princess Natasha.
- Get down.
Yeah, like that, bitch?
Not unless you have 30 bucks.
- I do not have $30.
- Well, I guess you're
just stuck with Janine.
- Which is actually great for
me, because Princess Natasha
actually scares
the shit out of me.
Just a little bit.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I was trying to get used to it.
I'm sorry.
- You know?
- What?
- If we moved in together,
we could do this
every single night.
- Okay, we're gonna talk,
we're gonna do that now?
We're gonna talk.
'Cause I thought we'd
maybe wait, you know--
- I think it's a great idea.
- Yeah.
- Why do we need to wait?
- That is a fun, fun idea.
It's just that I was
under the impression
we were gonna take it slow,
'cause it's a big step.
- It's been two years.
You're 28.
Don't you think that
maybe it's time for you
to move out of the basement?
- I enjoy my
lifestyle, pardon me.
Okay, I think it looks
very rustic and urban.
Why do we have to talk
about this right now?
- Because I am starting to worry
that maybe I'm just
wasting my time.
God, you act like such
a child sometimes.
- I'm sorry maybe this
child needs to be spanked.
Just on the bun cheeks.
Spank it.
Just a little slap.
Ooh, waah.
No?
- Do you even love me?
[toilet flushing]
It's not--
[knocking]
- What the hell is that?
Damn it, Phil, you forgot
to flush the toilet again.
[gun firing]
- What's up?
What's up, son?
- So,
did you tell Janine to
bring some strippers
from the club tonight?
- I did and it's just
that Janine's friends
don't love dudes around them
unless they're shoving twenties
in their undergarments.
You know what?
It's gonna be fine.
- Okay.
All right.
It has to be fine.
We've got to do this.
- We're doing it.
- And tonight we're
working and not drinking.
- I got that down.
I got that on my
checklist, work.
- Okay.
All right, I'll see you at work.
- Okay, see you then.
Okay.
Fuck.
All right.
[grunting]
[moaning]
[phone ringing]
- Hello.
Shit!
[woman screaming]
Oh, God!
Oh, yeah!
- Hello.
- Hey, man.
Was that your mom?
No, it was the news, man.
- Oh, the news, cool, man.
What are the hot topics today?
- I don't know, war and shit.
What's up?
- Listen, Danny's pop's having
a little financial trouble.
We could really use some
business at O.D.'s tonight.
If you guys can make it,
that'd be fuckin' awesome.
- I think we're supposed
to go down to The Stone
or something but, yeah, we
can try to make it down there.
- Fuck The Stone, okay?
Come to O.D.'s.
Do us a favor.
- Yeah, Phil, all right.
It's cool.
- And, lay off that
shit, all right?
It'll make you go blind.
- It was the news, man.
- [snorts] Stupid.
- Hey, man, can I get a smoke?
Oops!
- It looks like you jokers
aren't very popular.
- Where is everybody?
I thought you called people.
- I did call people.
I called everyone.
- Oh, this place is hopping.
I don't know if I can
make it to the bar.
Next time I'm gonna call
and make a reservation.
[laughing]
Where are the bartenders?
I can't find them anywhere.
It's so crowded.
They're really busy.
- Hello, welcome.
Where the fuck is everybody?
- I don't know.
[laughing] At a good bar?
I came straight over
from the precinct.
- Here you go, buddy boy, 12.50.
- Oh, how do you
know what I want?
- Since when are you so picky?
- Since I stopped
banging your mom.
- Oh, really?
'Cause she's super
into fisting dudes now.
How's that going?
- Okay.
Shut the fuck up, will you?
Don't you guys see we
have a problem here?
There's nobody in
this fuckin' bar.
They're probably all
down at The Stone.
Deadline Friday's playing, and
the Jaaäger girls are there.
- Real Jaaäger girls?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Hey, hey, we're working here.
- Yeah, workin'.
Hey, okay, you know what?
Why don't me and Mike, why
don't we go down to The Stone,
grab those dipshits and
bring them back here?
- Yeah, yeah, that's great.
Go there, grab them,
bring them right back.
- Yes.
- Quickly.
- Like bunny rabbits.
- What, like a what?
[laughing]
- Oh, my God.
Okay, yeah, yeah, so I'm
on top of her, right?
The midget's still
on my fuckin' back,
and I got this bat and
I'm trying to hit it off.
And her mom walks in--
- What the fuck is this?
- I told you guys
we should leave.
- Hey, Danny, we were just
on our way over there.
- Here are your beers, guys.
- Right after these beers.
- You guys can't do
me this one favor?
One time I ask for a favor.
- Danny, relax.
We're having a good time
with present company.
We'll try and make it
down a little later.
- This is fuckin' bullshit.
- You know what?
I just got an idea.
How about we go down to
O.D.'s tomorrow night,
and we'll commandeer the
place like it was old times.
- You guys promise
that you are gonna come
to the bar tomorrow night?
- Yeah.
Just get ready.
Could get ugly.
- The uglier the better.
Okay.
Good.
All right, Phil,
you're coming with me.
Phil.
- Motherfucker!
- How did the customer hunt go?
- We're gonna have a busy
night tomorrow night.
Thanks for watching the place.
- All right, you got it.
- I'm pretty sure that
chick got me in the eye
with her acrylic.
- Hey, is it red?
- Red?
What the hell happened to you?
- Phil only told the Jaaäger
girl that he had a 12 inch cock,
so she slapped him.
- Do you?
- Well, it's not 12.
- Oh, come on.
You have a fuckin'
dick of a hamster.
- It's a little bigger
than that, thank you.
- Why'd you say it?
- For the 5%, man.
- What 5%?
- You don't know about the 5%?
Okay, here we go.
Step one, by approaching
a nice young lady
and announcing
your 12 inch cock,
you can immediately
categorize these women.
95% of them will be angry,
disgusted, even violent.
Once the weeding out is done,
you've got the crucial 5%.
Now, once you've lured
them in with the bait,
you're on your way home.
You're probably getting laid.
Now I found that only
one in 15 of the 5%
will walk out once
they see you've lied.
The other 14 realize I'm young,
I'm healthy, decent-size
wiener, naked, naked.
Let nature take its course.
It's awesome.
- That is brilliant.
- As the great Robert
Browning once said,
take away random pussy
and our earth is a tomb.
- Did he really say that?
- Well, I think he actually
said, take away love.
- What do you think
of that, Harold?
- I think it's a great idea.
- We've got to start
doing this now.
- Yeah.
I mean, with the
women 40 and 50,
we tell them we've
got a 12 inch schlong.
They haven't been
laid in years anyway.
They're gonna go crazy with it.
And the old gals,
they are just damn grateful
to get anything they can.
- All right, hey there Plato,
why don't you take
your jumbo cock
and go move some
boxes in the back.
- Aye, aye, Captain.
[phone ringing]
- Hello.
- Danny boy, how are you?
- I'm good.
I'm good, I'm good, Pop.
How's rehab?
- Not too bad, not too bad.
How's the bar doing?
- Mr. O'Donnell,
remember the rules.
No discussing
alcohol on the phone.
- I mean, I gave you
that new car to drive.
How's traffic?
- Is everything okay?
Are you on medication right now?
Because you're not making sense.
- No, how's traffic?
Is it busy or empty?
- Okay, I got you.
Okay.
It's been about the same, dad.
- Well, maybe you should
work a little harder
and getting your
friends on the road.
- Okay, well, I'm trying as
hard as I possibly can, dad so--
- You've got to keep
those roads full
if we want to keep the car.
- Well, you're the one that
ran everyone off the road
a long time ago.
- Listen, wise-ass!
If I get out of this dump
and I don't have a
place to hang my hat,
there's only gonna be
one person to blame,
you and that shit-heel
cousin of yours!
- Well, that's two people.
- That bar's all I got
left in this world,
and you better
not lose it on me!
And tell the shit heel
not to drink any more
of my goddamn beer!
Son of a bitch!
Fuck!
- Okay.
[doorbell rings]
- Hello, and a very
good day to you.
I'm looking for Mr. O'Donnell.
- Can I ask who wants to know?
Because you guys look weird.
- Oh, I'm Monroe Nunley.
I'm here representing the
Whitestone Federal Bank,
and we want to talk
to Mr. O'Donnell
about delinquency
on his mortgages.
- Oh, that sounds really fun.
He'll be back next month.
- Well, I need to speak
to him immediately.
- Well, if immediately
means next month, then.
Okay?
Yeah.
- Who was at the door?
- I don't know.
Some douche bag from the bank.
- Bank?
Shit.
Hi, can I help you?
Yeah, we've got--
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, okay, okay.
All right, what
are you guys doing?
You can't come in
my house like this.
- We're here to liquidate
$3,000 of your assets
to cover back taxes on
Mr. O'Donnell's account.
It's all explained in here.
We'll try to make this as
pleasant as possible for you.
- Whoa, whoa, horseshit!
Put this down!
Get out.
You want me to fuckin'
cut your nuts off?
What's up?
You want this up your ass?
Fucking kabob your
dicks on this thing.
Not the Xbox!
Shit, no!
- Calm down.
- Give them something
else, not the Xbox.
Give them the
silverware or something.
- Grow up.
It's just an Xbox.
We use that twice a year,
like Christmas and Easter.
We use this every day.
I'm not giving them
Grandma's silverware.
- Dude, she didn't
like you anyway.
Who cares?
- Silverware?
- Absolutely.
- Some little son of a bitch
keeps putting cellophane
over the toilets at school.
I spend all day long
mopping up piss and shit.
When I catch who's
ever doing it,
there's gonna be hell to pay.
And they're always
wising off to me.
Lenny, you missed a spot.
Lenny, shine my shoes.
- Why do they call you Lenny?
- I don't know.
Some stupid book they're
reading at school.
- Could it be "Of Mice and Men"?
- Yeah, that's it.
You heard of it?
- No, I have never
heard of that book.
- Hey, Harold, what are
you doing over there?
- Oh, nothing.
Just writing something.
- Who wants to fuck?
- What's up, Joe?
- Guilty.
- What do you want to drink?
- Give me a shot of whiskey.
- Yeah!
- Hey, hey, yo.
- What's up?
- Motherfucker, what's up?
- Three, four, five.
- Thought it was just three.
- No, we're doing five now.
- All right.
- Can I get one of those?
- Namath was prettier, but
Tittle could throw the ball.
It landed where he threw it.
- I can't believe you
dropped that fuckin' ball.
- Will you shut up already?
It was like nine years ago.
- The pain may go away,
but glory lasts forever.
- It was too high, man.
- Too high my ass.
You don't know how
to run a route.
- I don't know how
to run a route,
you don't know how to
throw a fuckin' ball.
- We'll settle this once
and for all, all right?
All right?
I want you to go out
on a Z-3 slant on one.
- Are you serious?
- Am I standing?
Do I look serious?
- He's very serious.
- Blue 42!
Blue 42!
Hut!
- Oh!
- Come on!
What the fuck kind
of pass was that?
- A perfect one.
- It was three
feet over my head.
- Try wiping the jizz
off your hands, princess!
- I'll clean it up.
- Yeah, Danny will clean it up.
It's on me.
Thanks for breaking that.
- What you reading
there, Einstein?
- About the Shanahan's contest.
- Yeah, maybe you
better get your G.E.D.
before you start writing
any essays, buddy.
- Screw you, Andrew.
- Let's be gentle.
If you have nothing nice to say,
then don't say it, you dick.
- He's pretty special, okay?
- What's up?
How you doing?
How was work?
- The usual, whatever.
- So the girls are probably
parking or something?
- No.
No, they stayed in the city.
- No vag?
- For obvious reasons.
Hello, Joe.
Charming as ever.
- No girls are coming?
- You guys aren't
fuckin' leaving.
You promised me you
would stay all night.
- Fine.
Fine, we'll stay all night.
- Yo, yo, guys, guys,
guys, Monica's at Bogart's
with four new friends from
beautician school or some shit.
They want us there ASAP.
Let's go.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Don't you fuckin' think--
- You guys sit!
- You guys said you
would stay here.
You can't bail on me.
Assholes.
- I'm glad to see you have
such loyal friends, Danny.
- If we can't get our
friends in this fuckin' bar,
who the fuck are
we gonna get here?
- Danny, it's fine.
We can worry about
that tomorrow, okay?
Do you mind if Janine and I
since no one's really here,
if we kind of--
- You guys are basically
having sex anyways right now.
So why don't you just go?
It's fine.
- Oh, I'm sorry, Danny.
I'll try to bring my
friends next weekend.
It's kind of hard getting
them out of Manhattan.
- I understand.
That's cool.
- It's really hard.
- Hey, don't worry
about it, kid.
We're still sticking with you.
- There you go.
- We're here for you, kiddo.
Right, George?
- You should get
a corndog machine.
- What's up, Phil?
Really?
Right now you're gonna
be like, what's up, man?
- Sorry.
We didn't know what to
do with your brother.
He did like, ten shots, and
he's been puking ever since.
- What a dipshit.
What time is it?
- Three.
We didn't wanna take him home.
- Smart move.
I like that.
- Hey, silly.
- Whoa, hey, look who's up.
- Well, hello, Princess Natasha.
- Fucking queer boss.
Will you take him in the tub,
please, and wash him off?
Jeez.
Gross.
Dumbasses.
- It's too bad that your brother
and his friends aren't 21.
You guys would make a
lot of money off of them.
- No fuckin' way.
- Danny, if history
has taught us anything,
it's that success comes
from being resourceful.
You got to make your own luck.
No one's gonna do it for you.
- I'm not having some
high school speakeasy
and getting locked up.
- Okay, first of all, we're
not gonna get locked up, so--
Right, honey?
You're in law school.
We're not gonna get
locked up for that, right?
- You're gonna get locked up.
- Boom.
- I thought this relationship
was about support.
What?
- You're an idiot.
- What do lawyers know anyway?
Come on, man we gotta do this.
- God.
- Case in point.
Bro-ski, how many shots
you have last night?
- 10.
That's 45 bucks.
Times that by 100
horny-ass teenagers.
- No.
- Come on.
Danny, it's one night.
What could go wrong?
- First of all, I wanna say,
welcome Mineola Broncos!
[cheering]
All right, we have some rules
at this fine establishment.
- Rule number one.
- One.
- Is that there is
a three-shot limit.
For every shot you get, you'll
get a stamp on your hand.
After that, you're cut off.
However, there is
no limit on beer.
Rule number one is in place
so that rule number two
does not get broken.
And that is there is
no puking in this bar.
Rule number three is
that if you drove here,
you're not drinking.
Drinking and driving is
exclusively an adult pastime.
You guys aren't
ready for that yet.
Rule number four.
You do not tell anyone
about this place
that's over the age of 21.
Not your siblings,
not your counselors,
not your parents, nobody.
Or I will find you
and I will kill you.
Does everyone understand?
- [All] Yes!
- All right.
Go, Broncos!
Bar's open.
[cheering]
Yes!
[shouting]
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
- Take your shots.
- Receive.
Drink, drink, drink, drink!
- Drink, drink!
- Whoo!
[upbeat rock]
♪ We don't like you
♪ We only want your money
♪ We don't hate you
♪ Take it all in stride
no need to worry ♪
- You have a stamp?
Do you have your stamp?
Drink up!
- [Crowd] Chug,
chug, chug, chug!
[cheering]
- Just have a second here
so I can take a drink?
Ah.
Thank you.
- Stamp me, motherfucker!
- Yes, yes!
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, take
it outside, retard.
[chattering]
- Gross.
- Whoo!
- Go, Broncos!
- Lindsay, maybe we can
do this another time.
- Hey, baby.
I know you.
- Okay, you take--
- Hi.
My parents wanna sign me
up for the daycare program.
- Lindsay!
- You ruined my
mother's birthday.
- I know I'm sorry.
You didn't tell me you
were bringing your parents
down after dinner.
I had no idea.
- I was trying to
do you a favor.
I can't believe you'd
do something so stupid.
- Come on, have
some sympathy here.
We're in a bad situation.
- Fine.
But you better not do it again.
- Believe me, we're done.
We're never doing it again.
- Yeah, right.
You know how much money
we made tonight, bro?
Whoa!
- Phil, do you know how
much trouble we can get in
if we get caught doing this?
- Do you know what Saturday is?
Homecoming.
- I don't get, really?
- Yeah-uh.
- Why do you listen
to this asshole?
- Not all of us can live
on daddy's credit cards.
Some of us have to
work for a living.
- You call serving
beer to kids working?
- Yeah, I do what I have to do.
- So do I.
- No, please, don't leave us!
- Go fuck yourself!
- No!
- You're not helping.
- What?
That was funny.
- Lindsay, would you
just give me a second?
Wait.
- You know I've been talking
you up to my father for weeks.
Then I finally bring him down
here and what are you doing?
You're serving drinks to
the JV cheerleading squad?
- So stupid.
I'm sorry.
- Danny, this is serious.
If you get this job,
you're finally gonna
be on the right track.
Then we can start
thinking about our future.
- You're right.
I'm doing this to
save my dad's ass.
You know that, right?
- I know what
you're trying to do.
But serving drinks to
kids is ridiculous.
Promise me you
won't do it again.
- I promise you, I
- All right.
I have to go home now.
Do a little bit
of damage control.
- You go do that.
Okay?
I love you.
- I love you too.
- Hey.
What'd she say?
- Well, I told her we
weren't gonna do it anymore.
- Really?
Well, that's interesting.
- Yup.
So how much did we make?
- Oh, you know, just,
$2,856 and zero cents.
- Ooh!
- Yeah.
- That just sounds good!
- Shit.
Shit.
[chattering]
- So, hot shot, you didn't
try the 5% on that girl
you're dating?
- No, man.
She's way more upscale
than that, you know?
Met her at school.
- This girl's smart, huh?
- Really smart.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She dances to pay
for law school.
- Oh, a lawyer.
You gonna be a lawyer?
- No, no, no, I'm
gonna be a philosopher.
- What's philosophers do?
- Teach other people
to be philosophers.
- To do what?
- Nothing, hang out.
- I should have gone
to college, Harold.
- Yeah, but Fabio's
thong just got,
because Janine wants
him to move in with her.
- Oh!
[laughs] That's the first step.
Next thing you know, you'll
be buying her tampons.
- I don't wanna hear that word.
- You know what?
Forget about it.
You're all done.
- To the end of an era.
- No.
- Yeah, it's not--
It's not even official, so
why are we cheers-ing to that?
- Oh, come on.
- In the end, they're
gonna get their way.
I gotta go to the can.
- Hey, this is a good
thing you're doing
for your dad here, Danny.
- Breaking the law?
- Putting your ass on the
line to fix this mess.
- Yeah.
What are unwanted sons
for anyways, right?
- You're not unwanted, kid.
The old man loves you.
- He's just playing hard to get?
- Between the banks and the
booze, what do you expect?
He could have used
some help a while ago,
but he's just too damn
stubborn to ask for it.
- Yeah, I don't know
what he's gonna do
if we lose this place.
He's invested his
whole life into it.
- Well, looks like you're
on the right track.
- You know, I don't think
I'm coming back here.
I'm tired of seeing the
kids all day at school.
I don't wanna see 'em here.
- Yeah?
Where are you gonna go?
- I got places to go.
- Where?
- Son of a bitch!
- What?
What's the matter?
- It's the cellophane prick!
[breathing heavily]
- Oh, man, what a day.
- What's up, Mike?
- Hey.
- Let me get a beer and a shot.
- Sure.
- See you, Danny.
- Take care.
- Is that the starting
halfback for the Broncos?
- No.
- Hey, good luck in
the game on Saturday.
- Thanks.
- Right on, man!
Knock 'em dead!
Broncos!
What's he doing in here?
- A lot has happened in
the last couple days.
- Oh, shit.
What is it?
- It's from the
liquor distributor.
Dad owes them 5,000
in back payments.
It says they're gonna
stop delivery tomorrow
if we don't make
a payment in full.
- Whoa, tomorrow?
We got homecoming this weekend.
We're gotta kill it.
- Does it just continually
rain shit on my life?
- All right, well, how much
did we make this weekend?
- Almost four.
- Good, four grand.
Okay, so we just need a $1,000.
Where are we gonna get a $1,000?
What?
What are we gonna do?
- I don't think
you're gonna like it.
- No fuckin' way!
- You're not selling it.
You're pawning it, and
we can buy the car back
within 30 days for
the same price.
- I am not putting Bertha
through that, okay?
We've had a lot of
memories together.
And I got my first hand
job in the back seat.
- I was there.
I was driving.
- I know.
You looked back a few
times, I saw that.
- I did not look back.
- You did look.
- Let's think about
the bigger picture.
- It's your bar anyway.
Why do I have to get
dragged into this stuff?
- You used to live
in my basement
and you have for three years.
- Why do you have to
always bring that up?
That has nothing
to do with cars!
- Okay, homecoming.
After homecoming,
we'll take the cash,
we'll come back, buy our cars.
- It's so risky.
- It's--
All right.
Let's just do it.
Give me the title.
- Okay, this spunky
young man has our cars.
How do we get around now?
I got you.
- Oh!
- Yeah, baby!
- Dude, check this out.
- Whoo!
[whooping]
Give me some of those dice.
- Hell no.
They're my dice.
- You have so many of them.
- If I give you some dice,
you've got to give me your horn.
- Not equal value.
Chicks love the horn, right?
How do you like the horn?
What does it make you feel like?
Horny, horny.
Horny, horny, horny.
That usually is gold.
- I bet they just love the horn.
I'm keeping the dice.
- That used to kill.
What's up, baby?
Who's the baddest motherfucker
riding the mean
streets of Mineola?
Ow!
- Are you okay?
- Yep.
What's up, baby?
- What's up, girl?
- Hi, I have a question.
Remember me?
I'm your girlfriend.
Why haven't you
called me back today?
A little car trouble,
you wanna hop on?
- But remember we were
supposed to go to lunch?
We had a date.
- Sorry, babe.
I was probably going to get
sponsored with this thing,
doing new tricks.
[horn tooting]
- Okay, stop.
Stop.
Danny, what happened
to your cars?
- What is a car really?
I mean, it's just a--
- Are you guys gonna give
me a straight answer,
or am I gonna have to
fuck you with a pineapple?
What is going on?
- Damn!
I'll tell you straight up, girl.
I will tell you straight up.
- Okay.
- We pawned that shit to
pay the beer distributor.
- Okay, wait, wait.
What?
- You heard me.
- Okay, stop that!
- All right.
- You pawned your car?
- Yeah.
- Phil!
- What?
- I can't keep driving
out here every single day.
Wednesday is my only free day.
How is this gonna work?
How are we ever
gonna see each other?
- You guys could
move in together.
- Dude, stop!
- Really?
It's that bad.
- Or we could iChat.
- IChat?
- Very accessible nowadays.
- We can have sex on iChat.
- Yeah.
- Are those my glasses?
- Yes.
Listen, Danny said
it would be cool.
We could get our
cars back on Monday.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I have great news.
- What, tell me.
- My father got an
appointment next week for you
with the human
resource department.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- How did you pull that off?
- I told him everything.
I told him your mom is gone,
your dad's an alcoholic,
and that you're really
being loyal to the bar,
and that you have no real
role models in your life,
and he went for it.
- Great.
- Danny, if you
start a heroin habit,
you can make VP in no time.
Ain't that right, girl?
- So what do you
think of my outfit?
- I don't think you've ever
looked sexier in your life.
- Well I took you
up on your offer,
and I'm gonna come
here and help you.
- I don't think it's gonna
be that busy tonight.
You know, it's a slow night.
- You should probably
just tell her the truth.
- Just tell her.
- I was gonna--
How did--
- Tell me what?
- Say it, don't spray it.
- Look, we're still
doing the underage thing.
- But you promised me.
- I know.
There's nothing else
that we could do.
I had to pawn my car to
keep the liquor flowing,
and it's just until Saturday.
- Why do I even try with you?
- Lindsay!
Lindsay, I'm sorry I have
no other choice right now.
- You okay?
Cheer up, this'll
help you cheer up.
- Okay, stop.
All right, that's good.
Stop.
- Hey, buddy, we've
talked about this before,
and you said to never bring
it up again, but I'm going to.
What the hell are you
doing with that chick?
- Not in the mood, Phil.
- No, seriously, I
want an explanation.
She some kind of trophy
to you or something?
- You know what?
She is the only normal thing
that I have in my life.
- Normal?
You think she's normal?
Because she eats a hot dog
with a knife and a fork.
You know, that's not normal.
You have two hands.
You pick up the hot dog,
and you eat it like,
Janine has a friend that
can eat it in one bite.
She, and it just disappears,
right down the hatch.
- Phil.
- It's awesome.
- I grew up doing my
homework on that barstool.
That one right there.
Do you call that normal?
- I call it real.
That's reality, man.
- That's not the reality
that I want anymore.
- Yeah, she's beautiful
and she has a trust fund,
but that doesn't mean she
can walk all over you, okay?
- What do you know?
- I know she makes
you miserable.
- I'm a big boy.
I think I can take
care of myself.
- Okay.
- Hello.
- Broncos win, bitch.
Oh, you should've seen it.
I rushed the field,
and I knocked out
their fuckin' mascot.
And then he came to, and then
I kicked him in the balls!
- Mike, the fact that you
carry a gun is very disturbing.
- Oh, tough loss, guys.
You suck!
Oh, grow up.
- Were you abused as a child?
Are you trying to
prove something?
- Line them up, because a
hell of a party is on the way!
- Okay.
Can't wait, Mike.
- Broncos!
Get some!
[upbeat rock music]
- Guys, all right, I'll
take these for you.
I'll take these for you.
Hey, buddy.
- Oh, hey.
- Okay, all right.
Hi.
Hey, shithead, let me give you--
You love it.
- Looks like you boys
might just make it.
- Yeah.
- Cheers.
[whistles]
- Who wants to fuck?
- [All] Yeah!
- Yeah!
[shouts]
- Whoo!
Oh!
This place is a zoo.
Give me a shot
and three rubbers.
- I got the rubbers.
- Got the shot.
- Dude, where was this place
when we were in high school?
- Ain't no time to talk, fellas.
- You got some ID?
It's just too bad, isn't it?
Get out of here.
- You son of a bitch.
I thought this place was a
little too risqué for you.
- Oh, I'm not here to socialize.
Just came to
congratulate the team.
They had an awesome game.
- Mike, please, just complete
the circle of weirdness,
will you and become
a P.E. coach.
You can look at these
little boys all day long.
- Hey, pain is passing,
glory is forever.
- That's right.
Broncos!
- Go, Broncos!
Hey, Roach!
Oh, my God, you had an amazing
run in the third quarter.
I was watching you
the whole way, man.
You wanna sit down
and have a beer?
- Dork.
- Yeah, oh, yeah.
- You.
- Hey, Lenny's beating up Tom!
- Take it outside.
- [Crowd] Fight,
fight, fight, fight!
Fight, fight, fight, fight!
- There's not
gonna be any fight.
I'm taking you to the
principal's office.
- Office is closed, bitch!
[shrieks]
- Fight, fight!
- No, no, no, no!
Hey, what are you?
Get out of my way.
- [Mike] Hey, who just hit me?
[siren wailing]
- [Danny] Get back!
Get back!
- [Cop] Break it up.
Let's go, up against
the wall, everybody!
Who's in charge here?
- Thanks a lot, asshole.
That would be me, Officer.
- All right, look.
I gotta do something, all right?
I got called here.
You know that.
- No, of course,
you've got to report.
Listen, he's my brother-in-law.
I'm just asking if you
could just bend a little.
- So what's the skinny?
- Let me say you two are
the luckiest sons of bitches
on the planet right now.
Since everybody was outside
and because I'm such a nice guy
and you're my brother-in-law,
they're only gonna charge you
with five counts of
underage drinking.
Instead of the hundred,
which you probably deserve.
- Shit, well, how much are they?
- 1,000.
- Oh.
- Not bad.
- That's not too bad.
- Each.
- 1,000 each?
- You guys should be
in jail right now.
- You know what?
No, no.
I'm not sure if I'm
comfortable living in a country
where an 18-year-old
can't have a beer.
Yet he can go to war and
carry a gun and kill people.
It's unjust.
It's un-American.
- Shut up.
- All right, move to
fuckin' France then.
- Wha--
- You can drink when you're six.
Thank you very much.
We owe you big time.
- Yes, you do.
And if I may say, it's my
love for Bronco football
that saved your asses.
- Broncos.
- Go, Broncos.
- Go, Broncos!
Fucking idiot.
[phone ringing]
- Hello.
- Danny boy, how are you?
- I'm good.
I'm good, Pop.
How are you?
How's rehab?
- Oh, great.
I'm doing the 12-step shuffle
over here and loving it.
- Oh, that's good.
It's good to hear, Pop.
- So how's traffic over there?
- Well, we had rush hour
there for a little bit.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, till we got pulled over.
Well, that figures.
Listen.
That's probably because
of that fire I read about
over at 2612 Second Street.
- 2612 Second Street?
Dad, that's the bar.
- I know it is.
Ain't that a damn shame?
- Dad, what are
you talking about?
- It was a real shame.
It had to happen, I guess.
Burn it.
- Dad, I'm not
gonna burn the bar.
- Oh, yes, all
those poor people.
I'm sure the insurance
will cover it.
Burn it.
- That's enough, Mr. O'Donnell.
That is it.
- I've just been
told I have to go,
but I want you to burn that
fucking bar to the ground!
- Let's go!
- You old sons of bitches.
Cocksuckers.
Fuck!
- It's a great
entry-level job, Danny.
You'll learn the business
from the trenches,
which will prepare you
to move up later on.
- Great, that sounds perfect.
So I'm gonna be out of
the office a lot, right?
- No, no, no, no.
The first few years,
you'll be at your desk.
We have field agents who
do the actual inspections,
but after two or three years,
there's a good chance
you'll get out there.
- Two or three years?
Great.
Paying my dues, right?
- I think you're going
to like it around here.
The insurance business has
been good to me and my family.
- Is this your son?
- Him?
No.
That's me when I
was about your age.
Handsome devil, huh?
Come on.
Let me show you
around the office.
Fridays around here are
always Aloha Fridays.
It helps lighten the mood a bit.
- Aloha, Herb.
- Aloha, Stu. [chuckles]
Who says insurance can't be fun?
Come on, let me show
you to your desk.
- Whoa.
Hey, cuz.
You look fuckin' good, man.
Watch out, I'm gonna
fuck you. [laughs]
- I don't know if
I'm up for that.
- So, how'd it go?
Did you get the job?
Right?
- I don't think
I'm gonna take it.
- I don't know if that's
the best idea for right now.
- Fuck you, what are
you talking about?
I thought you'd be proud of me.
- Two days ago, you
know, of course,
I would have told you to tell
them to fuckin' fuck off.
You know?
But with these jailbait tickets,
they're gonna kill us
man and we're broke.
And the bar and the house
are as good as gone.
It's not really a great
time to be passing up jobs
no matter how shitty they are.
- I guess you're right
and it sucks too,
because I feel like I
wanted this job so bad.
Now I realize that
I don't want it,
and now I have to
fuckin' take it.
It's like if you broke up
with Janine for some reason,
then realized you're an idiot
and you're in love with her,
and got back together only
to find out she had a penis.
It's like it's
that bad, you know?
- That'd be fuckin' rough,
'cause then it's like,
then you're like, well
whose turn is it to fuck?
Or like, do I do you
and then who does who?
- You would still be with her?
- What?
Oh, no.
It's just like whoever we'd
probably figure that out later,
or like, she would
tuck it or something.
We'd work that out.
- So you're gonna
open the bar tonight?
- I don't really
see any reason to.
I mean if we turn on the lights,
we're pissing away money.
- Do you want to get drunk
and look at some titties?
- Sure.
- Me too.
[energetic rap music]
[patrons shouting]
- Yeah.
- Yeah, baby.
Hi-oh!
- Whoo!
- Shots!
- Yeah!
- [Man] Oh, yes!
- I'm a bad boy.
- Yeah, girl.
Go ahead, baby, go ahead.
- So, Phil tells me
you're a bounty hunter.
- I'm not a bounty hunter.
[laughs]
I actually own a bar.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
I guess I should
say I owned a bar.
- Oh.
- All right, Stace, cough it up.
- Jeez, Tony, give me a minute.
- I don't have a
minute, sweetie.
Come on.
- You want a minute?
I got a stopwatch, hold it.
Ah, go.
- Thanks, sweet cakes.
You've got to be kidding me.
- Two.
Ah, good time.
- Such a slob.
- What was that about?
- We have to give him 200
bucks just to get on the stage.
- That's ridiculous.
- It's so ridiculous.
I know.
If you know of anything
better, you know where I am.
[giggles] I'm right here.
[upbeat rock]
[patrons shouting]
- Hey, hey!
- Danny, how we doing?
- We are killing it.
- Yes!
So what do you think
about the new remodeling?
Not bad, huh?
Titties, never hurt anybody.
- It suits me.
Business is good.
- Yeah, I think
Pete would be proud.
- Fuck!
- Harold, what the fuck
you writing in there?
- My retirement plan.
- Your retirement plan?
What, are you gonna
switch from disability
to social security,
you lazy bastard?
Let me see.
- No.
- Come on, Harold let me see it.
Thank you.
- What's he got?
- Oh.
Take away whiskey, and
our earth is a tomb.
- Oh, Harold, that's my line.
- Harold, you trying to win
that Shanahan's contest?
- Yeah, I sent in a few.
What of it?
Give that back.
- Good for you, hope you win.
- Good luck on that, man.
Good luck.
- We are cleaning up.
You know what?
To making your own luck.
I love it.
- Hey, Danny,
I just want to say thank you
so much for all this tonight.
You have no idea how much
better than Lucky's this was.
- So thank you!
- Anytime.
You guys can come
make money anytime.
- Dude, Danny.
Just a friend.
- What, are you a pimp now?
- No, I'm not, can I explain?
- Hey, Danny, I think we
need to get the donkey ready
for Stacey's show.
- That's good.
We should talk outside.
- I love donkeys.
- Lindsay, she was
just thanking me.
All right, we helped them out.
They made some money.
- That's the lamest
thing I've ever heard.
- How is that lame?
It's gonna save the bar.
- Who cares?
You have a job now.
- About that.
I don't think I'm
gonna take the job.
- What, are you kidding me?
- I'm not kidding you.
I can't work in a cubicle.
I gave it a shot, I went there,
but I can't see myself
being in cubicle 4B.
I won't be Danny anymore.
- That's what adults do.
Maybe it's time for you to
stop being Danny the child
and start being Danny the adult.
- Where does it say
that being an adult
means you have to work in
a cubicle 50 hours a week
doing fifth-grade math?
Where does it say that?
- So you'd rather just serve
beer to degenerates and morons
your whole life?
- I don't know, maybe.
- Danny, I'm trying to
get you out of this place.
- And into what?
A job that I'm gonna hate
for the rest of my life?
- If you don't leave
here, you're gonna
end up in the gutter
with your loser cousin
and your drunk father.
- Wow!
You have done nothing but
make me feel like shit
since we've been together.
Guess what?
[chuckles] I'm tired
of feeling like shit.
Yeah.
- Where you going?
- I think I'm gonna go inside.
I'm gonna hang out
with my loser cousin,
his whore girlfriend
and the bar degenerates.
Is that okay with you?
Have yourself a good life.
- Hey.
How'd it go out there?
- I walked away.
It's done.
- You all right?
- Yeah, yeah, let's
talk about it.
I feel fine.
I feel good.
- Good.
- Yeah.
I mean, we're making money.
- Yes, we are.
- And,
I think we're gonna
save this place.
- Great attitude, I love that.
- And I'm a free man now.
- You're definitely free.
- I think everything's
gonna be all right.
It's gonna be all right.
[upbeat music]
- This is awesome.
Gonna get up here
and dance myself.
What's up, guys.
What's up?
Oh, excuse me, little lamp.
[hums]
- Oh, don't encourage him.
- Sure, right in here, come on.
I'll take it.
Yeah, get your fingers in there.
Sure.
- Get down!
- See who comes out with
more money tonight, baby.
- [Janine] Yeah.
- [Phil] How about some of this?
Some of this.
Oh yeah.
- No.
- Whoa, dollar bills, yo.
- Hey, Mr. O'Donnell.
You okay?
- Oh, over here?
Sure.
Yeah, put that in there.
Hey, guys, yeah!
Spank it!
Come on, Harold
give me a spanking.
I'll dip my balls in it.
Five bucks, and I'll dip
my balls in your beer.
Five bucks!
- [Janine] What is
that old guy doing?
Is that gasoline?
- [Woman] Hey, look!
- Holy shit.
[screaming]
Dude.
- Burn in hell,
you fucking dump.
- Oh, God, oh, God.
Dad, wait!
Jesus Christ, Dad.
What are you doing?
Son of a bitch.
Will someone take him
to the back, please?
- Man, you went down
like a little bitch.
- What are you talking about?
You went down too.
- I teetered first.
You went straight down.
- What the hell
is wrong with you?
- Nothing.
Tie this guy's mouth.
Come on.
[soft blues music]
- What exactly goes on
behind those curtains?
- Those?
Those are lap-dance booths.
Yeah, it's like pleasureville
for the lower half of your body.
Give a girl 20 bucks, she'll
dance around your body,
you know, all that good stuff
for, like, a whole song.
It's pretty awesome.
- It's really good?
- Yeah.
It's amazing what
they can do to you.
What, you want one?
- No, no, I don't
have the money.
- Oh, come on.
Who are you talking to?
Harold, it's on the house.
- [laughs] I'm not interested.
- Janine, Stacey, ladies.
Help my friend
Harold out here, huh?
- I'm too old.
- You're gonna love it.
- I can't, I can't.
- Girls, put your,
do that one thing
when you put your boobs
on each side of his head
and just like shake.
It's awesome.
- Hi!
Boy, oh, golly!
Oh, my God!
- Oh.
- Oh, what are you doing?
What are you doing here?
- Oh, please be kind.
- Have fun, Harold.
Hey, you all right?
- I don't know.
I don't know what to think
about my dad right now.
- Wanna talk about it?
Come on, man cheer up.
Let's do some
shots or something.
Let's get crazy.
[Harold shouts]
[screaming]
[siren wailing]
- All right, so both you
ladies were on his lap?
- We were giving him a dance,
and he started to
breathe really hard,
and he grabbed his chest,
and he just fell over.
- [sobs] He said to
do the boob thing.
- That's all right, sweetheart.
He had a bad ticker.
Listen, it's not your fault.
I couldn't think of
a better way to go.
- Yeah?
- Yes, yes.
- You running the show again?
- We both are.
- Okay.
You have a permit
for the strippers?
- A what?
- Do you have a permit for
the strippers, yes or no?
- Yes, yes.
- Yeah, of course.
- Not this.
No, that's a
Michael's gift card.
Why do I have a
Michael's gift card?
- Arts and crafts sometimes.
- You know what?
It's been a busy couple of
weeks for you guys, all right?
What the hell is
next around here?
[Pete shouting]
- Let go of me, you lousy
pig-faced cocksucker!
There they are!
They fuckin' kidnapped me!
Tied me up and left me to die.
[Pete crying]
Fucking unbelievable!
Their own flesh and blood.
Oh!
Oh, shit!
Oh, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus!
- Who was that?
- Got some good news.
I spoke to the D.A. and I
told him about your father
and the whole situation,
and he's agreed to drop
all kidnapping charges.
- That's good.
- But he's not budging
on anything else,
and he's fining
you guys $10,000.
And you've got to
serve 120 days inside.
- Four months?
- You're kidding, right?
You're joking around with,
you're playing with us?
- It's not a joke.
It's in the papers.
More importantly,
it's on the internet.
Running a den of iniquity,
harboring a fugitive.
Oh, the dead dude.
Yeah, he wants to make an
example out of you boys.
And not that this matters,
but the bank will wait to
foreclose until you're out.
Then you'll have 24 hours to
vacate the bar and the house.
- Honey, I need you
to get clippers.
I'm shaving my head.
I'm gonna do it.
- Phil, relax.
It's county, not Attica.
- Relax?
Really?
Gabe, easy for your
to say on the outside,
with your fuckin' three-foot
bong and your drum circle.
Everything's cool man, right?
I'm in jail, I'm in jail.
You wanna switch places?
Is that allowed?
Ah!
[grunting]
I'm gonna need
fake tattoos, okay?
You got that?
Fake tattoos.
- Why?
- How many is that?
Are you counting?
- Honey.
- How many am I doing?
- Need a place to stay?
[breathing heavily]
- Can't believe we
lost the bar, Phil.
- Dude, forget about that.
We gotta watch
our backs in here.
Damn it!
I need tattoos.
You know what Ed Gangemella
told me when he was in here?
He said you've got to assert
yourself early, get respect.
The first thing you gotta do
is get in a fuckin' fight.
Doesn't matter if you lose.
Doesn't matter if you get
the shit beat out of you.
I guess people know not to
fuck with you if you do that.
- Hey, Ed Gangemella
is a fuckin' moron.
What the fuck?
Why do you think he
ended up in jail?
- We're in jail.
I just like, I really, really,
I don't wanna get butt-fucked.
I just don't wanna
get butt-fucked.
- Then stop saying butt-fucked.
- I have a tiny
anus, you know that.
- Look, just don't talk.
- Yo man, I need
that bottom bunk.
I can't get up there.
- No man, it's mine.
Beat it.
- What?
I don't think I'm
hearing you right.
- You heard me just
fine, get lost.
- You know what?
I have warmed up
this blanket for you.
I'll make your bed.
You wanna lay down here?
- No, no, no, no, no.
Now I want this one.
- Do you know who
I am, motherfucker?
- Yeah.
You the motherfucker
that's gonna be sleeping
on the top bunk.
- [Pete] Is there a fuckin'
problem here, Andre?
- Yeah, I asked this
asshole nicely if--
- Danny.
- Dad?
What are you doing here?
- They kicked me out of rehab.
What the hell are
you doing here?
- Oh, well, wait a sec.
You know this guy?
- You Pete's kid?
- Yeah.
- What's up?
Yeah.
- Man, you--
- Who the fuck is this?
- Whoo.
- I don't know him.
- Hey Dad, so, like do you,
do you, like what's up?
Do you,
have you ever been
like do you butt fuck?
How does that--
Oh, God.
So basically, Foucault says
that anyone who wouldn't submit,
who wouldn't be a cog in the
machine, would end up here,
in jail, until they've learned
how to sublimate themselves
to the will of the
capitalist machine.
It's all economic.
- Now, that is some heavy shit.
- You know where
I can get a shank?
- I can't believe he's dead.
The poor bastard.
- The weird thing
is Gabe got a call
saying that Harold left
you his entire estate.
- Yeah.
- It was only $220 and an
Elvis vinyl collection,
but I never knew you
guys were that close.
- He was trying to
square up his tab.
When he went on the disability,
he didn't have two nickels
to scratch together,
so I let him drink for free.
- You did that?
- He's been coming to
the bar for 20 years.
I'm gonna put him
out on the street?
- But that was really
nice of you, Dad.
- Occasionally I have
moments of weakness.
And I want you to know,
I know you did your best to
save the bar and the house.
And I appreciate it.
- You do?
- And I'm pretty much
sorry for everything.
You wouldn't be here if it
weren't for the mess I made.
- Pretty much sorry?
- I'm sorry.
Thanks.
You gave it a shot.
And I'm proud of you.
- Thanks, Dad.
I love you, Dad.
- All right, all right.
Don't touch me
like that in here.
Jesus.
- Live free or
die, motherfuckers!
- Ow!
- Oh, hey.
- I'm still an ass virgin!
- Yay!
- Yeah, hey.
All right, all right, all right.
[cheering]
- Glad to see you guys are here.
- Glad you guys survived.
- So, what, this is
the last day then?
- Oh, shit.
We gotta be out of
here by tomorrow?
I forgot.
What are we gonna do?
- I know what we're gonna do.
Why don't we polish
off these fuckin' kegs,
drink as much liquor as we can,
get fuckin' wild
for Pete's sake,
before these barbarians
take over the bar?
- Fuck those heathen bastards.
- Yeah.
- Fucking scumbags.
- All right, guys,
let's do this.
This is it.
Yeah!
- This is it.
- To Pete.
- To Pete, yeah.
- Pete.
Come on.
- Mazel tov.
[laughing]
- You know, and I've been
thinking a little bit.
- Oh.
- And I think, if you
think that we're ready,
that we should move in together.
- Yeah, about that,
I changed my mind.
- Really?
- Um, no.
Are you kidding me?
- What?
- Of course we're ready.
- What the fuck?
Okay, gee.
- It was my idea.
- Yeah, I know.
- You're so cute.
- I just [sighs]
I just don't wanna
screw things up.
You know, I'm really
happy with you, with us.
I just never learned how
to do this the right way.
- Hey, we're gonna be fine.
- I love you.
- That's good,
'cause I love you,
a lot.
- A lot?
- A lot.
- Oh, crap.
[groans]
- Ah.
- Oh.
- Gentlemen, we are here
to foreclose on the bar
and on the residence and to
seize any sellable assets.
It's all here in the
paperwork, Mr. O'Donnell.
You can peruse that
at your leisure.
- What are you doing
out of your coffin?
Don't you guys turn to
dust, like in the light?
- [chuckles] Yes, yes.
Yes, Mr. O'Donnell,
that's very funny.
I'm gonna have to
ask you to leave now.
- That's fine.
We'll go.
But we're gonna
get a beer first.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Oh, well.
You gentlemen are aware that
the beer now belongs to us?
- Put it on our tab, shithead.
- Oh.
- Ah.
Oh, my God.
Whoa.
- Oh, my God.
- Ah.
Does that look straight?
- You don't.
- Well, good day
to you, gentlemen.
- What a dick.
I don't feel good.
- I don't feel good either.
- I need to sit down.
- Me too.
Hey.
- What?
- Cousins for life.
- Life.
I need to lay down.
- Might as well get used to it.
- Oh, boy.
- Why?
- Sorry to wake you.
Would either one of you know
where I can find Harold Kahill?
Does he owe you money?
- Quite the opposite.
My name is J.R. Mulvahill.
I'm with Shanahan
Whiskey Incorporated.
He won our essay contest.
I'm here to tell him
that he has a pub
waiting for him in
Dublin, Ireland.
- What?
- No fuckin' way.
- I'm serious.
We called, but the
phone was disconnected.
Then I went by his house
and there was no answer.
He put this place down
here as his work address.
- He won.
- Absolutely.
Our head reader called,
take away whiskey, and
our earth is a tomb
a humorous metaphysical romp,
amply worthy of the
Shanahan essay contest.
- That's my fuckin' line.
He stole my line.
- I'm sorry to
inform you of this,
but Harold died
of a heart attack.
- Oh well, that's a
terrible thing to hear.
- It was all very sudden.
- Do you happen to know
who's handling his estate?
- As a matter of fact, I do.
[upbeat music]
[chattering]
- Hey, Pop.
You want another
sparkling water?
- That would be great.
- You got it.
Come on.
- Thanks, Danny boy.
- Hey, how about I throw a
shot of Jameson in there,
you old sot?
- How'd you like me
to come over there
and kick your fuckin' teeth in?
- Holy shit.
- He's not lying.
- I know.
- So what time do
you guys get off?
We know of a party later.
- Ladies, I'm gonna
have to say I'm sorry.
And as you say in your
language, I'm off the market.
- Oh.
- Sorry about that.
- So sad.
- Oh, it's okay, honey.
We're not missing much.
- Oh!
- Oh.
Maybe missing a
little bit of this.
I'm gonna show 'em.
Little bit of this.
What's up?
Gonna miss that.
[giggling]
What's up, ladies?
- See, this is what
I'm talking about.
- Yeah.
Well, I usually
get off around 12.
- Oh.
- Damn, you're pretty.
I'm liking this town.
Another beer?
- Oh-ho-ho!
- Look at this.
Give me some.
- Not bad.
- Hey, look who's here!
Nice one.
- Hey, guys.
- How are you?
- Finally made it.
- Yeah! [grunts]
- All right!
- [Danny] Oh, boy.
- Who wants to shag?
[cheering]
- [Crowd] Yeah!
- Yes!
[cheering]
♪ I'll wait for you
till I turn blue ♪
♪ There's nothin'
more a man can do ♪
♪ Don't get your
bollocks in a twist ♪
♪ Settle down and
don't take a fit ♪
♪ You drank with demons
straight from Hell ♪
♪ They almost
nearly won as well ♪
♪ You wiped the
floor with victory ♪
♪ Then puked until
you fell asleep ♪
♪ Blackened was the
banshee's wail ♪
♪ These boots will
never fill her jail ♪
♪ So you crawled
into an empty boat ♪
♪ For the Gulf of Mexico
♪ Till Cortez came
and when so did you ♪
♪ From the ashes
charred and blue ♪
♪ Smellin' like a salty dog
♪ Back from hell
where you belong ♪
- Whoo!
[laughing]
- Yeah!
Get some shots!
- Yeah.
- Ah!
- Welcome to Ireland.
- I love Ireland.
[laughing]
- You're taking him home.
- Oh no, all right.
[laughing]
- Thank you, Jesus.
Where's my fuckin' shirt?
[laughing]
♪ Drink, drink, drink
♪ To your heart's content
♪ Lift that glass in the air
♪ Drink, drink, drink
♪ Only fools lament
♪ Over troubles they share
♪ Drink, drink,
drink to oblivion ♪
♪ For it's now plain to see
♪ That this glass
I am holding here ♪
♪ Is alone my destiny
♪ I don't give a bloody damn
♪ What the people think I am
♪ Let them know that
this man will be free ♪
♪ Tilt that glass
and slurp that foam ♪
♪ What's the sense
of going home ♪
♪ For the consequence will be
♪ Drink, drink, drink
♪ Never fear the life
♪ That is calling to you
♪ Drink, drink, drink
♪ Let it share the strife
♪ That's what drinking can do
♪ I don't give a bloody damn
♪ What the people think I am
♪ Let them know that
this man will be free ♪
♪ Tilt that glass
and slurp that foam ♪
♪ What's the sense
of going home ♪
♪ For the consequence will be
♪ Oh, drink, drink, drink
♪ To your heart's content
♪ Lift that glass in the air
♪ Drink, drink, drink
♪ Only fools lament
♪ Over troubles they share
♪ Drink, drink,
drink to oblivion ♪
♪ For it's now plain to see
♪ That this glass
I am holding here ♪
♪ Is alone my destiny
♪ Last call for alcohol
♪ Shake it off
don't lose control ♪
♪ Leave now or don't at all
♪ 'Cause we don't want
your money no more ♪
♪ Last chance order up a shot
♪ Slim pickins all around
give it what you got ♪
♪ Hurry up drink
a pint or more ♪
♪ The party's heading
out of the door ♪
♪ We don't like you
♪ We only want your money
♪ We don't hate you
♪ Take it all in stride
no need to worry ♪
♪ Our only interest is
the tip that you gave ♪
♪ So finish up, pay your tab
and be on your fuckin' way ♪
♪ Yeah