(ambient music)
(atmosphere rumbling)
(paper rustling)
(paper airplane whooshing)
(wind howling)
(gentle piano music)
(heartbeat pumping)
(woman sighing)
- [Woman] How're you doing, baby?
- Mmm.
(woman gasping)
- Holy crap, you look hot.
- Yeah?
Too hot?
- No, like classy hot.
I'm just so used to seeing you
dolling up the other girls,
I never see you all dolled up yourself.
Oh, you look perfect, baby.
- Thanks, Mom.
(eerie music)
Mom?
Mom!
(ominous music)
No, no, no, no!
Mom!
Mom?
No, no, no, no, no, Mom.
Help!
Please, help us!
I don't know what happened,
she just collapsed.
- Mom?
- Someone call 911!
- Jesus.
- Mom?
Mommy?
- Rachel.
- Mom?
- Daddy.
(ominous music)
- No!
No!
- Do something!
(Rachel gasping)
(eerie music)
(cricket chirping)
- Oh, shit.
(birds chirping)
(distant dog barking)
- [TV Host] Which have
been also dusted in flower
but not just to absorb
any excess moisture.
- Uh oh.
"Great British Bake Off."
What's up?
- Nothing.
- Come on, babe, you
know you can talk to me.
- It's just, it's like...
It's a lot of pressure on me, you know?
- I know.
But we're in it together no
matter what happens, right?
Okay, I gotta go get ready.
I have that shoot with that
new bag company this morning.
Are you gonna try and work today?
Okay then, I will see you later.
- It came.
- What?
- I went to the bathroom
this morning and it came.
My period, my uterus just
wasted another 30-fucking-grand.
- Are your sure?
- Amber.
- Okay.
Was it like...
Was it a full period or was it,
I don't know, like spotting?
- I mean, it was...
I guess like spotting but
I still, I have cramps,
and then my back hurts and then...
- Okay, do you remember
what Dr. Fern said to us
when we did our first cycle?
- I know he said a lot before
we gave him all our money.
- I know but he said to us
that spotting and cramping
could be a sign of
successful implantation.
- You sure?
- I am sure that that is what he said.
So I am not trying to get our hopes up
but there's no reason
to get down yet, so...
Come on.
- What?
- Come on, you're gonna go pee on a stick.
- [Rachel] I love peeing on sticks.
- [Amber] Yes, we love them, all of them.
- [Rachel] There's a variety
of ways to pee on a stick.
(Amber laughing)
- Okay.
(gentle music)
40 more seconds.
- Okay, please, please
don't get too excited.
- Oh, I'm not.
I'm not.
- You are!
You're getting all smiley and stuff.
- I'm so sorry.
(Amber laughing)
- No.
- I'm sorry.
- You're gonna get my hopes up.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry, okay.
Look, look, mmm.
No smiles and no hope.
- Seriously.
Dr. Fern said we shouldn't even bother
with home pregnancy tests.
- No, that is not what he said, babe.
What he said was he didn't
want us obsessing over it.
You know, like taking a test every day.
It's okay for us to take one.
- Well it's easy for you to say.
It's not your fault when it
turns out to be negative.
- Babe.
No, no, no, no.
It won't be anybody's
fault, no matter what.
And I'm here for you, okay?
So I will calm down and chill out.
- I'm sorry, I just, you
know, you get anxious
and then you start feeling this thing.
(phone dinging)
(pleasant music)
- Okay.
That's time.
Here we go.
- Oh God, please.
- [Amber] Oh my God.
- It's two lines!
It's positive!
- It's positive?
- It's positive!
- It's positive, oh my god!
Oh my god, oh my god!
Oh my god, Amber!
(pleasant music)
God, we're gonna be parents.
- Yeah.
Holy...
Baby!
(Rachel and Amber laughing)
- Oh my god!
- Congratulations, you're pregnant.
(Rachel laughing)
(doorbell ringing)
- Hey, big sis.
- Oh, no thank you, no, not for me.
- What, you pregnant?
- Gary!
Shut up.
- Oh my god!
Are you guys seriously pregnant right now?
(Rachel chuckling)
- Yeah.
(Amber laughing)
- [Gary] To us!
(glasses clinking)
(doorbell ringing)
(couple laughing)
- Okay, Mom and Dad, this
one is from the two of us,
for you guys.
- Oh.
- Happy anniversary.
- Oh, thank you, that's so sweet.
What is it, what is it?
(Rachel chuckling)
(pleasant violin music)
(mom gasping)
(Amber giggling)
A baby!
(Rachel vomiting)
(pleasant violin music)
(doorbell ringing)
- Hey!
Does it not totally suck
not being able to drink?
Because I feel like it would totally suck
if I couldn't drink.
- Congrats!
You're so brave.
I would never be able to
bring a child into this world,
what, with everything that's going on.
(Rachel gagging)
- So, did you guys do the whole IVF thing
or did you find some dude to
do it the old fashion way?
(Rachel vomiting)
(toilet flushing)
(pleasant violin music)
(bird squawking)
- Okay, the gel's gonna
be a little cold at first.
- Oh.
(doctor laughing)
There we are.
(computer humming)
You ready?
Here we go.
Okay, so...
This is baby's brain.
- Oh, wow.
(doctor chuckling)
That's incredible.
- Just gonna grab a few
images while we're here
so we can measure everything.
And here is baby's heartbeat.
(heartbeat thumping)
It sounds great.
Now for the big spoiler alert.
Do you wanna know the sex?
- Yes.
It's a girl.
- Oh.
(Amber laughing)
- A girl?
- Yeah.
- [Mom] That's wonderful.
- [Amber] Wait till you see her.
- Oh, I wanna see her.
- It's...
- Show us.
- Look at that.
Look at that.
- Oh, would you look at her.
(father chuckling)
Isn't she previous?
- [Amber] Oh wow.
- Can you believe?
(ominous music)
What is that?
- What?
- Is that a face?
- Oh wow.
- There, in the corner.
Doesn't that look like your mother, Rach?
Or am I crazy?
(eerie music)
- No, it looks just like her.
- [Dad] Spooky.
- Daddy!
- But...
How is...
- Rach, it's probably just a coincidence.
You know, the shadows and the
lights and the ultrasound.
- You wanna know what I think?
I think it's a blessing.
(gentle piano music)
I think it's a sign from
God that she's still here.
- [Amber] I love that, Mom.
- Thank you.
(ominous music)
- Oh.
Rach...
- What?
- Your nose.
- Oh.
- It's bleeding.
- Honey, can I help you?
- I'm sorry, I...
Just excuse me.
Sorry.
- Rach.
- Oh, I got it, I got it.
It's fine, I got it.
(ominous music)
- [Amber] I love you guys.
- We love you too.
- [Mom] Bye-bye.
- [Amber] Drive safe.
- We will.
(Amber yawning)
- [Amber] Well, that got a little weird.
- I just saw my dead mom's
face in our sonogram.
Sorry, I don't really know
how to feel about that.
- Rachel, I told you it was just--
- I know, it's shapes and shadows.
Look, I know, I know, I know
that's what it is but...
I mean, it looks exactly like her.
That can't be a coincidence.
I mean, it can't.
- Okay, so what if it is?
Come on, your mom was like
the nicest person I know
and that includes you.
Look, I'm just gonna go ahead and say that
if your mom's face is popping
up in our daughter's sonogram,
well, I'm gonna take that as a good thing.
Like maybe my mom was right
and maybe this is a kind of blessing.
A sign that your mom is watching
over our little daughter.
- You know you're the best, right?
- I try.
(Rachel chuckling)
- Maybe it's a sign that we
should name her after her.
Little Sarah?
(pleasant music)
- I really love that.
- Really?
- Yeah, of course.
(Rachel laughing)
I love Sarah.
(pleasant music)
- Excuse me.
(ominous music)
Hi.
Can I please get a decaf Americano?
- [Barista] What size can I get you?
- [Rachel] Medium.
Thanks.
- Bet I can guess.
- Sorry?
- Bet I can guess the sex.
(heartbeat thumping)
Girl.
- Wrong.
Thanks for playing though.
- [Barista] Medium caramel macchiato.
(unsettling music)
Hello?
Caramel macchiato.
- I think that's for you.
- You know,
you shouldn't be carrying all those bags.
- I appreciate your concern
but I'm fine, thanks.
- Put on a jacket at least, it's chilly.
- I'm perfectly comfortable,
yeah, but thanks.
- Put on a goddamn jacket!
(sinister music)
Uh...
Oh.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Ma'am, you...
You have a...
(eerie music)
- It's really good, we're doing great.
(door creaking)
Can you believe you're gonna be an uncle?
(Amber laughing)
No we're not.
Um...
Hey, can I call you back later?
Yeah, Rach just got home.
Okay, love you.
(dramatic music)
Are you, oh my god.
What happened?
- I don't know.
There was a guy at the
coffee shop and he just--
- [Amber] Jeez.
- My nose started bleeding
and, I don't know,
I just freaked out.
- Okay, okay, okay.
You're home, you're home, you're safe.
But, first of all, what guy?
Wow.
What a fucking asshole.
It's not even like it's that cold outside.
I'm sorry, babe, I know
that's not the point.
- It's not just him though, you know.
Everybody's been treating me weird.
It's like I'm not...
I'm not a person.
I'm just this incubator.
- Hey.
Of course you're a person.
You are the best kind of person.
As a matter of fact,
you are my favorite kind of person.
- I don't mean you, I mean everybody else.
I mean, our friends and your family
and random strangers.
It's just...
Everybody keeps treating
me like I don't know
how to take care of myself.
- Babe, that is just the way
the world treats pregnant ladies.
But look, I've said it before
and I will say it again.
If it's not you and
it's not me, screw them.
We don't need help.
Right?
- Yeah.
- Look, I don't want you
to take this the wrong way
but do you think that
maybe there's a chance
that our friends and my parents,
they just wanna support you
but it's a little hard for
you to accept that support
because you didn't grow
up with a big family?
- What does that have to do with anything?
- No, I just mean,
for a really long time it
was just you and your mom
and now she's gone.
But my parents and our
friends, we're your family too.
And, although we may not
always say the right thing,
we mean well.
- Really?
Okay, so it's my fault.
- Oh wow.
Rachel, that is not what I said at all.
- Okay.
Just
listen.
I am the one who has to go through this
and it is hard.
So I would appreciate it if
I felt like you had my back.
- I do have your back.
I always have your back.
I am just worried...
(dramatic music)
I am just worried that you're
gonna push everyone away
like you did when your mom died.
- And there it is.
- Rachel.
Rach, wait, oh...
I'm sorry.
This is all coming out wrong.
Okay, listen, what I should've said,
what I should've said was,
the hell with that guy.
The hell with anyone
that looks at you funny.
It doesn't matter, they don't matter,
because the only thing that matters
is you, me and this baby.
Our baby.
The three of us.
Okay, that is it.
I'm sorry.
(unsettling music)
(gentle piano music)
(sinister music)
- [Female Host] And it's still breathing.
Look at that fresh, fresh cherry.
- [Male Host] Nice to see both sides.
- She's going to take it.
(Rachel gasping)
- Mom?
- She's going to take the baby.
- What're you--
- You have to stop her.
- Who?
(Rachel groaning)
(ominous music)
- She knows I'm here.
She won't let me talk to you.
You can't let her take the baby.
Don't let her control you!
- Mom.
Mom.
- Rachel.
Rachel.
- [Amber] Rachel?
- Mom!
(sinister music)
What happened?
- No, everything's fine, you're fine.
- No, my mom was just--
- No.
- She was right here.
- No, honey.
No, you were just having a nightmare.
Come here.
It's just a bad dream.
- She was here.
- No, you're fine.
Everything's fine, okay?
(dramatic string music)
- [Woman] Rachel?
- She's here.
Babe, you're up.
(phone chiming)
(ominous music)
- If you have to take it, just...
- It's just the agency.
- It's fine.
- I'll be right there, I promise.
- Okay.
- [Amber] Hey you guys, hold on.
Let me step out, I'm
in the doctor's office.
- Yeah.
Looks good.
Any headaches?
- Huh?
No.
- Also good.
Yeah, I don't think there's anything
to worry too much about.
- Dr. Fern, I don't see how you think
it's nothing to worry about.
- Look, I didn't say it's
nothing to worry about,
I said it's nothing to
worry too much about.
Nose bleeds are a common
symptom of pregnancy.
- Dr. Fern, if you'd
seen it, you'd know that
there was nothing common about it.
- I know it must've been very scary.
A nose can bleed a lot but
I assure you it's fine.
Just hormones and stress.
- Hormones and stress.
- That's right.
- What if it's not just
hormones and stress?
What if it's like a brain tumor
or something like an aneurism?
- The billing department would love for me
to order a bunch of tests to rule out
that very unlikely possibility
but I'm telling you
it's just not necessary.
At least, not yet.
It's my opinion as your doctor
that the best course of action is for us
to just keep an eye on things
and try to avoid all stressors.
Okay, all right, if it'll
make you feel better,
I can order up some blood work
but I really don't think you need it.
You're taking your pre-natals, right?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Let's give her a listen, shall we?
Okay.
(heartbeat thumping)
(gentle piano music)
(eerie music)
- Um...
Dr. Fern?
Dr. Fern, is there something wrong
with the baby's heartbeat?
(eerie music)
What're you?
(pen scratching)
Doctor?
Dr. Fern, are you all right?
(pen scratching)
What're you...
Dr. Fern?
- All hail the Lilith.
(sinister music)
Long live
the first mother.
(intense music)
(Rachel screaming)
(Rachel gasping)
(blood squelching)
(Rachel screaming)
- [Nurse] Oh my God!
Dr. Fern!
Ah!
(ominous music)
- "Hail Lilith.
"Long live the first mother."
What does that mean?
- How should I know?
- You feeling okay, Ms. Robins?
- I just wanna go home.
- Listen,
we wanna get you out of
here as soon as we can.
We need to make sure
we don't miss anything.
So let's just go over
it one last time, okay?
- Come on, again?
I've already told you everything 10 times.
- We just need to make sure
that we don't miss
anything for the record.
- Well I told you everything.
(ominous music)
- You said Dr. Fern was
fine during the appointment
until the very end.
Then he started acting weird.
- Weird how?
(eerie music)
- Just like I told you, he got all quiet
and he...
He wouldn't look at me.
And then he started like scribbling
really hard in his notebook.
He was acting like a robot.
- Like a robot?
- I don't think he was a robot, okay,
I think he was acting like a robot.
He was stiff, I don't
know how else to say it.
He was acting odd,
creepy.
- [Peters] Weird?
- Was it out of the blue or was there,
was there a trigger?
What set him off?
- I don't know, I don't
know what set him off.
(eerie music)
- Kinda looks like you just
thought of something there.
- No, I don't know, I don't
know what set him off.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- All right.
So what then?
Then he just stabbed himself.
- Four times in the neck.
- I don't know how many times
he stabbed himself, okay?
- But he did all the stabbing.
- Yes!
He did this to himself.
- And that blood is?
- This?
It's from a nose bleed.
Look, I swear I never touched him.
- So why did he do that?
- God.
- We talked to his
coworkers, his girlfriend,
none of them believe it was suicide.
Apparently, he was a happy guy.
Why off himself?
- How should I know?
I don't know!
He just...
(gentle piano music)
- Who kills themself with
a pen to the jugular?
Who does that?
- [Peters] Well, Dr. Noah Fern for one.
(ominous music)
- So you're buying it?
- Kwan,
you made detective two years ago.
I'm going on 20 years.
I guarantee you'll see plenty of suicides
weirder than this one.
- Everyone said he was a happy guy.
- Everyone always says he was a happy guy.
Nobody wants to admit they
missed the warning signs.
And the scene backs her up.
There's no way she stabbed him,
put the pen in his hand without
getting any blood on her
and fingerprints all
over him, there's no way.
- But there is blood on her.
You really believe that's a nose bleed?
- That's what it looks like to me.
- Let's just wait for forensics
to tell us what they find out.
- We can't hold her that long.
She's pregnant, for Christ's sake.
Be lucky if she doesn't sue as is.
Nah.
The call on the field is good, suicide.
Let's go get a beer.
- They can't just do this, you know.
They can't just arrest you
without letting you call somebody!
- Look, I wasn't arrested, okay?
They just held me for questioning.
- Well they shouldn't be
able to do that either.
No, they shouldn't be
able to just hold anybody,
much less, a traumatized pregnant lady!
- I'm okay.
I'll be okay.
Look, I'm just really tired
and I kinda just wanna go home.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I should've been there.
I should've been there with you.
Never let you go in there alone.
None of this would've happened.
- [Rachel] It's okay.
Hey.
We're okay.
(crickets chirping)
- Hey, you want some more noodles?
Okay.
Come on, Rach, you gotta eat something.
Especially because you are
not just eating for you now.
You are eating for two.
- Of course.
I almost forgot.
(fork clanking)
Mmmm.
Mmmm, this is so good.
- Hey.
I'm not trying to fight with you.
You know, I just need you
to take care of yourself.
Not to mention, the baby--
- The baby, I know.
Yeah, I know.
You gotta take care of the baby.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
I'll eat, okay?
See, see?
I'm eating.
(phone chiming)
- Thank you.
Oh, don't forget,
we have that new O.B. tomorrow.
We should probably leave around 10.
(gentle string music)
Oh, hey.
I know that it's probably weird,
especially so soon after what happened.
- Why do you think he did it?
- [Amber] What do you mean?
- I mean, Dr. Fern.
Like, why do you think that
he did that in front of me?
You know, like--
- Rach.
I really hate to see you
tormenting yourself like this.
- So what, I'm just
supposed to like forget it?
I'm sorry, I can't, I
can't stop seeing it.
You know?
- I know.
I know.
And, look, I can't even begin
to imagine how horrible it was for you.
But I just don't think it's a great idea,
or healthy for that matter,
to keep dwelling on it like this.
- Oh, that's what it is, right?
I'm boring you.
Okay.
- Come on, that's not what I said.
- No but it is what you meant, right?
See, you just want me to
shut up and stop complaining.
Well guess what,
I get to complain all I
want to, you know why?
Because I am going through
hell to give you this baby.
So you, you don't have to do shit.
You don't have
to sacrifice shit!
- Wow, you know what?
I'm not doing this with you.
Not tonight, Rach.
- Really?
You're just gonna get up and walk away?
(dramatic music)
No, you know what, you don't!
Don't walk away from me like that!
- "Give me this baby."
- Yeah.
- "Give me this baby?"
Correct me if I'm wrong
but I thought you were doing this for us.
Rach, do you have any idea
how jealous I am of you?
- Ugh.
- Do you have any idea how
much I wish that I'm the one
that could be doing this.
- Spoken with the ease of
someone who isn't pregnant!
- That's not fair.
My career is our primary
source of income--
- Which you keep reminding me
all the time!
- And we talked about this!
- I know.
I know, I know, I know.
You're right, you're right.
I am, I'm doing this for...
For us, you know, I...
I'm glad we're doing it, I am.
It just, before I knew how
hard it was really gonna be--
- Which is why I've been
trying to be there for you!
And this entire time, what
do you think I'm doing?
I just want us to be happy.
(Rachel gasping)
- Wait.
- Rachel, what was that?
Did she just kick?
(Amber chuckling)
(ominous music)
Can I feel?
Oh my god.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Why, what's?
- I just--
- What's wrong?
Are you okay?
- Maybe not right now.
- But can I just?
Let me--
- Don't!
(sinister music)
I'm sorry, I didn't...
- Wow.
What is going on with you?
- I know you're gonna think I'm crazy,
and maybe I am.
I can't stop feeling
like something is wrong
with this pregnancy.
- What do you mean, Rachel?
- I don't know.
It's just...
wrong.
I feel like I'm cursed, you know?
- You're not cursed, Rachel.
- Listen, listen,
Dr. Fern only started acting weird
after he heard the heartbeat of the baby.
Okay, it was the same thing at the guy,
with the guy at the coffee shop, you know?
Just listen to me!
What if, what if, what if...
What if it's not my mom?
- Wait, whoa!
(ominous music)
Let me stop you right there.
Are you actually trying
to tell me that you won't
let me feel our daughter
kick for the first time
because you think that
your uterus is haunted?
- So you do think I'm crazy.
- No, Rachel, let's
clear this up right now.
Because if it is,
let me be clear in what I am saying to you
because mine is actually
coming from love and concern.
You need to get your shit together.
- Excuse me?
- Yes, Rachel,
I said that.
Look, I am not gonna pretend
that I know everything
you're going through
but you need to stop acting like
I have not been here with
you this entire time.
Which is why I have to be honest with you
and tell you that this,
all of it, is delusional.
There's nothing wrong with our baby.
- Don't gaslight me, I
know what's happening!
- I'm not gaslighting you.
I am just trying to keep
you here in reality.
- The sonogram had a face!
- It was an optical
illusion and a coincidence
just like I have said every time!
Jesus, Rachel,
I just, I need you here on earth with me.
Both of us do.
- I'm sorry.
It's me, it's me.
It's me, I'm sorry.
(eerie music)
I just...
I...
I don't know what's happening to me.
- And that's when Amber suggested
you try seeing a therapist?
- Yeah.
And she was right, I was just,
I just drag my heels about it, you know?
- It's not easy to ask for help.
I think you're doing a great job
coming here on a regular basis.
So now that time has passed,
what are your thoughts about all this?
- I just freaked out.
You know, I got in my head and...
Look, I know nothing
is wrong with the baby.
- You mentioned early on that
you saw your mother's face
in the ultrasound photo.
What was your mother like?
- My mom was the best.
We were real close.
She was my best friend.
We did everything together,
and now she's just...
Gone.
- It sounds like she was
a positive force for you.
- Yeah.
Huge.
- Was she ever a negative force?
- No, no, she was great.
- Never?
- Honestly, she was a great mom.
- [Therapist] Did she
get along with Amber?
- Oh, sure.
You know, they weren't
super tight or anything
but, yeah, they got along,
there's no problems.
- [Therapist] How about
the rest of your family?
- There is no rest of the family.
My mom's family was abusive to her,
so she ran away and she
never saw them again
and I never knew my dad.
So there was no dad side of the family.
(ominous music)
- Oh.
That must've been difficult.
Obviously, we need to talk
about all of this a lot more
before I'd feel confident
saying anything concrete,
but it seems like you are...
(unsettling music)
(pen scratching)
All hail the Lilith.
Long live the first mother.
- What did you say?
- I was just saying we're
out of time for today.
But I think it's really positive for you
to keep talking about all this.
I feel like you should come back next week
for another session.
Is that okay?
(dramatic piano music)
(ominous music)
(thunder rumbling)
(dramatic program music)
- [TV Host] For thousands of years,
people have told stories about Lilith.
She appears in the mythology
of almost every ancient culture.
Some say she is the first vampire.
Some say she is a succubus.
Some say she was the
first woman, before Eve,
cast out of Eden after
refusing to submit to Adam.
Others, like members of the
Children of Lilith death cult
believe she is the wife of Satan.
- I believed it.
We all believed it.
Hell, I think even Mother
Lilith, whoever she really was,
I think she actually believed it herself.
She convinced us she was
thousands of years old.
That she was reborn into a new body
every 66 years and six months.
She told us if we devoted
ourselves to her and her husband,
the Dark Lord would adopt us
and give us places of
honor in the underworld.
She told us we would be
princes and princesses of hell.
People ask me, how can
you believe that stuff?
How dumb can you be?
I guess the answer is really fucking dumb.
Because I swallowed it,
hook, line and sinker.
I was just a kid when I met Mother Lilith.
Lost, looking for somebody to help me
make sense of all of the fucked up shit
that happened to me when I was a kid.
She was really persuasive.
She had this way of just
getting into your head,
making you think a certain
way, do a certain thing.
Sometimes she didn't even need to say it.
She could just stare into your eyes
and put an idea into your head.
- [TV Host] Was she
hypnotizing her followers?
Brainwashing them?
Seducing them?
It depends who tells the story.
But every version ends the same,
with Mother Lilith leading
her so-called children
in ritual suicide.
On June 21, 1988,
at the Nevada Ranch that
the locals refer to,
in hushed tones, as the commune,
Mother Lilith lead her 46 followers
where they simultaneously
cut their own throats.
All but one perished.
- I remember waking up in an ambulance
thinking I was dead,
being transported to
the morgue or something.
And when I figured out I
was actually still alive,
I was heartbroken.
- [TV Host] It was a long road to recovery
for John Fletcher Jr,
physically and psychologically,
but after 30 years he
finally considers himself
to be a happy, healthy person.
Still, it seems he hasn't been
able to completely move on.
- When the FBI was done with the place,
they put it up for auction.
I had just signed this big
book deal, so I bought it.
At first, it was just a place to live.
I felt weird sleeping anywhere else.
It wasn't around, till around 2003 or so,
that I opened the museum,
started doing the ghost tours.
This is my museum area.
Oh, this?
This was taken six
weeks before the ritual.
That's me standing right
next to Mother Lilith.
Ah, it was an amazing
day, I remember this day.
We had no idea what was coming.
- Wait.
(ominous music)
Mom?
- [John] Standing right
next to Mother Lilith.
(door creaking)
Ah, it was...
- [Amber] Home!
- [John] An amazing--
- Hi.
- Oh.
How are my girls?
- Oh, you know, we're
okay, how was your shoot?
- Well, they dressed me
like a hipster psychic,
so there's that.
(Rachel chuckling)
But everyone on set says hi.
They really miss you.
- Aw, that's sweet.
- How was therapy?
- Yeah, it was good, I think it helped.
- [Amber] Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well I wanna hear all about it.
I mean, obviously, if
you wanna talk about it.
- Sure.
- Okay,
I will go get showered
and then you and I can order some sushi.
I am, oh, I'm sorry.
(Amber laughing)
No sushi for you.
How about we have some Thai?
Think about it.
(ominous music)
(entry bells ringing)
- Hi.
- Yes, come in.
- I'm Rachel.
- Sit.
You want to know about baby?
- Yes.
- You must pay first.
Sometimes people don't pay.
Now you must pay first.
- How much is it?
- 100 dollar, cash only.
I will only say once,
I am, how you say, the real deal.
Sometimes people don't pay
because they don't believe what they hear.
Sometimes they don't pay because
they do no want to believe.
Think hard before I take your money
and maybe you will not like what I say.
(eerie music)
- Okay.
Okay, okay.
I understand.
- Good, then we begin.
Hands.
- [Rachel] Sorry?
- Give me hands.
- [Rachel] Oh.
(eerie music)
- Close eyes.
Your baby is girl, yes?
- Yes.
- And you want to know
if baby is good girl
or not-so-good girl.
- I guess so, I just feel
like there's something that--
(psychic shushing)
Let me listen.
(eerie music)
You already choose name, I hear a name.
Sarah.
Is this for baby?
- Yes, how do you know that?
- This was your mother's name
and now you have chosen it for baby?
- How do you know that?
- You came because I know these things.
Just like I know that Sarah is good girl,
good, healthy girl.
But this other one,
not so good.
- Excuse me?
Other one?
There's not twins, it's just the one.
I've had two doctors
confirm that it's not--
- Not another baby, another
spirit inside there with her.
Babcia.
- Babcia?
- Grandmother.
You feel her, I know.
Don't be scared.
I told you, I'm real
deal, I know these things.
(Rachel sighing)
- Yes.
Yes, I feel her.
- Sometimes when a mother
dies with no grandchildren,
her dusza, her soul, won't leave.
Her spirit stays with us
until her son or daughter has a baby.
Only then will she move on.
- Can you speak to her?
- I can speak, I cannot
make her speak back.
You have message?
- Yes.
Please tell her that I love her so much
and I miss her and I wish that
she was here when the baby--
- She already knows these
things, what is message?
- Tell her to stop.
(eerie music)
Whatever she's doing, whatever this is,
people are getting hurt and I'm scared.
- Babcia.
(psychic speaking foreign language)
(unsettling music)
She says she is not protecting your baby,
she says she is protecting
her new skóra, her new skin.
- What's that, what the
hell does that mean?
- It means she is no babcia after all.
She is demon, an evil spirit with no body.
She waits to be reborn
inside your baby's skin.
- No, no, it can't be a demon, it can't--
- Don't worry, I will evict her.
I am as I say, real deal.
I will help.
- Please.
(ominous music)
(psychic yelling foreign language)
Are you okay?
- She won't let go!
(psychic huffing)
(hand cracking)
(intense music)
(bones crunching)
(psychic screaming)
(Rachel yelling)
(psychic screaming foreign language)
(Rachel gasping)
She's too strong!
(bones crunching)
You must cut her out!
You must get rid of her
before she is reborn
or she will...
(psychic gagging)
(intense music)
(Rachel whimpering)
(sinister music)
(Rachel groaning)
(suspenseful tempo music)
- No.
(Rachel crying)
(ominous music)
No.
I can't.
(Rachel sobbing)
Why are you doing this to me?
- Rach?
Rach!
Oh my god.
Rach, what happened?
- Don't.
- Rach!
Hey.
Rachel, please, whatever it is,
just, we can figure it out together.
Please talk to me.
- I can't.
- Rachel.
- You don't believe me.
- I will believe you.
Look, I don't care if you tell me
you were abducted by aliens, okay?
Please, just talk to me.
(ominous music)
- I don't know what happened.
I ran, I don't even remember driving home.
- Look, it's...
I'm just glad that you're okay.
- God, I didn't even try to help her.
- Hey.
That is completely understandable.
Look, you were in shock.
But I do think that we
need to call the cops now.
We'll tell them that she had a seizure
or a heart attack or something
and that you panicked, so you ran.
- No, Amber,
we can't call the police.
- We have to call the police, Rachel.
- No, even if they don't arrest me,
they're gonna keep me there
forever for questioning,
you know that.
Look, Madame Rose said the
only way to stop the demon
was to get rid of it
before the baby's born.
- Right.
The demon.
- I know you think I'm crazy.
But you don't have to make fun of me.
- I am not making fun of you.
I am trying to wrap my head
around this whole thing.
Come on, you have to
admit that this is a lot.
Okay,
fine.
How did she say that we
get rid of the demon?
- She said we gotta cut it out.
- Well that is just not happening, Rachel.
- Do you think that I want that?
I mean, after everything
that I've been through.
That is why we can't waste
time going to the cops.
All right, we gotta
figure out some other way
to get rid of this thing
and keep it from taking over our baby.
- Okay.
How do we get started?
Do we seen an exorcist or something?
- My mom escaped a satanic suicide cult,
not the Catholic Church.
I don't think and exorcist
is gonna be any help.
Do you remember that
documentary I told you about?
There was that guy, he survived.
- Yeah.
- He survived it.
He's still there.
If anybody knows how to
stop this from happening,
it's gonna be him.
(dramatic string music)
- Okay.
Okay, so we'll give him a call.
- No, look, I did that, I tried that.
As soon as I learned about
him, I left him a message.
I sent him an email, he
didn't return anything.
- Well then we will go see him.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Look, Rach, if this is what
you need to do to fix this,
then that is what we're gonna do.
Okay, I'm in.
(gentle music)
I'm in.
I love you.
- I love you so much.
- Hey, look,
why don't you finish up in here
and I will pack us a bag.
- Okay.
- And we'll take off
as soon as you're done.
All right.
- Thank you.
It's gonna be okay.
(gentle string music)
(phone buttons clicking)
It's gonna be okay.
(heartbeat thumping)
(foreboding music)
Okay, so we're gonna get
on the Five heading north.
- [Amber] North, got it.
- Hey.
Thank you for doing this.
Even if you are just humoring me.
- Rach, I love you, and so
whatever you need, okay?
But there is something that
I wanna show you first.
- What?
Like a surprise or...
- Yeah, like a surprise.
(car whooshing)
- This is...
(tires screeching)
in a parking garage?
- No.
No.
Come on.
- It's really cool of
you to make a plan for us
to like reconnect.
I'm kinda hoping it's the churro spot
you were telling me about.
(Amber chuckling)
Or ice cream, I love ice cream.
Hot chocolate, French vanilla ice cream.
- Anything you want.
- Yeah.
(ominous music)
- Wait.
What is this?
- Rachel, hello.
I'm Dr. Simmons.
I'm a mental health professional here
at the Haven Wellness Center.
We're a private mental health clinic.
- Are you having me committed?
- Rach.
- What?
- You didn't give me a choice.
- [Simmons] Gentlemen.
Escort her inside.
- What're you doing?
No, no, no, no, no!
No!
Did your family put you up to this?
Let me, stop it!
Is this your brother?
Amber!
Don't do this!
- Don't worry.
- Amber!
- She'll be fine.
I know how difficult this must be on you.
But just know, you're
doing the right thing.
- Doesn't feel like the right thing.
(sinister music)
- Fellas.
Fellas, fellas.
- Get off me!
- Fellas, it's fine,
it's fine, we're talking.
- What is this?
Get--
- We're talking.
Hey.
- Treating my like an animal!
- Hi, Rachel, Rachel.
Rachel.
I'm Dr. Simmons.
I want you to know these men--
- Get off!
- These men are
not gonna hurt you.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm your doctor, do you understand?
I'm on your side.
- You think I'm nuts.
- No, no, I don't.
I don't think you're nuts,
I don't think anyone's nuts.
That's why I got into
mental health to begin with.
Thanks, guys.
Please.
Have a seat.
- I don't need a doctor.
- Oh.
What do you need?
You don't wanna talk?
All right.
I'll tell you what I need.
I need to give you a physical
and I need to check the
baby's vitals real quick
and then we can get you
settled in your room
and you can decompress a little.
Okay?
- No.
The last doctor who did that, he--
- No, no.
Amber told us all about Dr. Fern
and I understand your concern.
But I'm willing to risk it.
Like I said,
I'm your doctor and I'm going
to do whatever I need to do
to make sure you're healthy, right?
- Look, if you listen
to the baby's heartbeat,
something terrible is going to happen.
I don't know,
you just trust me, you can't.
- Oh but I can.
You're here in what's
called an involuntary hold.
You gave your wife
medical power of attorney
and she's concerned about your
mental state, and frankly,
darling, so am I.
So, will you let me do what I need to do
or are we going to make this into a thing?
- Go fuck yourself.
- Oh no.
That kind of language
isn't going to help us.
(heartbeat thumping)
(eerie music)
This will only take a second.
(unsettling music)
(heartbeat thumping)
Almost done now.
Deep breath in.
Exhale.
And I'm not
feeling any urges to
kill myself.
Very good.
Now, was that so bad?
- Think I got something.
This old lady, Rose Kocinski,
the psychic at that shopping
center with the good burritos.
Someone found her dead.
Looks like she died of an aneurysm,
but M.E. says somebody crushed every bone
in this poor woman's hands.
- And you thought I'd be
interested in this, why?
- Because guess who's on the
shopping plaza's security tape
leaving her place less than an hour
before her body was found?
(ominous tempo music)
- I'm sorry.
I'm just so sorry.
This whole thing is my fault.
I can't believe I got so fucking crazy.
- You're not crazy, Rach.
- Amber, look at what I made you do to me.
- Okay, but look, it's not...
You're not crazy, you're
just, I don't know,
just going through something.
- Yeah but that's no excuse.
You know, look at the
position I put us in.
- Hey, look, the main thing
is, you're getting help
and I think that that's really brave.
- Don't, don't, don't do
that, don't patronize me.
I made such a scene in
front of that doctor
that I might never get out of here.
You know, and what happens--
- Hey.
- If I go into labor here?
- No.
No.
- Are they gonna
take the baby?
- No.
No, no, no, come here.
I am not going to let
any of that happen, Rach.
I'll be right here with you.
- Dr. Simmons, there
are two detectives here
who would like to speak to Rachel Robins.
- Excuse me!
I don't think so!
You two don't get to talk to her.
No way.
- What?
Who are you?
- I think she's the wife.
- Yes, I'm her wife.
- Nice, good to meet you.
- Oh, save it.
Look, she's been through enough
and she answered all your questions.
So now just let her rest.
- Oh, you're talking about the doctor guy?
Stabbed himself in the neck?
- You're right.
She's answered all our
questions about that.
But now we have questions
about the dead psychic.
- I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
- You don't know about that, do you?
- No.
But what I do now is that you
need to get a warrant to talk to her.
- We actually don't.
Not to talk to her.
If the doctor says she
can talk, she can talk.
- Gentlemen.
Hello.
Dr. Roy Simmons.
You're here for Rachel Robins.
- That's right.
- That's fine.
- Wait, what?
No!
Fine.
But I'm calling our lawyer
and the two of you aren't
gonna say a word to her
till he gets here.
- I'm sorry, guys, I've
gotta get back to work.
You'll have someone page me
when you've sorted all of this out.
(ominous music)
(heartbeat pumping)
- [Woman] And then
we're going to take
five more deep breaths.
(dramatic piano music)
In and out.
One more.
And breath out.
(heartbeat thumping)
- Come with me.
- Is everything okay?
- Everything's fine.
(eerie music)
- I don't...
Mom, Mom, I don't know.
Yeah, Gary's on his way right now.
- Amber!
Amber!
- [Amber] Mom?
Mom, I gotta call you back!
Rachel!
- Amber!
- Rachel!
(Amber gasping)
- Shit!
- Wait, where are you taking me?
Why are we outside?
Slow down, I can't go that fast.
(car beeping)
(suspenseful music)
- Rachel!
- Get in.
- Please don't do this.
- Quiet.
Run, and your wife dies.
(tires screeching)
(intense music)
(car thudding)
(Rachel gasping)
(tires screeching)
(horn honking)
- [Amber] Rachel!
Rachel!
(car honking)
- You hear that?
- Parking garage.
- Let's go!
(car honking)
- [Amber] Rachel!
(suspenseful music)
- Rachel, stop!
- Go, go, go, go, go!
- [Kwan] Call it in!
- [Amber] Are you okay?
- Definitely not okay!
(tires screeching)
You believe me now?
(Simmons groaning)
(suspenseful music)
(heartbeat thumping)
- What happened?
(Simmons gagging)
(ominous music)
- Are you gonna call it in?
What the hell are you doing?
- [Peters] He's dead.
- So what?
You gotta call it in
if we wanna catch them.
Whatever.
I got the plates, I'll do it.
- Hang up the phone.
- What?
- Hang up the phone now!
- Peters, what the fuck?
- Now!
You can't stop her.
(sinister music)
No one can.
- Peters?
I don't know what's going on
here but we can talk about it.
- All hail the Lilith.
- Peters,
what're you doing, man?
- Long live the first mother.
- What're you doing?
(woman screaming)
Don't do it!
Don't!
(gunshots booming)
Peters!
What're you doing?
Talk to me, partner, talk to me!
(gunshots booming)
(ominous music)
Oh, fuck!
(blood trickling)
Peters!
What the fuck, man?
Hey!
You fucking idiot, what're you doing?
Hey, stay with me.
Stay with me, Peters!
Peters, you're all right.
Hey, can someone fucking get me some help?
(gentle music)
(car whooshing)
(foreboding music)
(birds chirping)
(eerie music)
(Amber knocking)
- We close at 6:30.
You have to come back tomorrow.
- We're not here for the tour.
- Please,
we need your help.
(John sighing)
So I thought if anyone knew
how to stop this thing,
it would be you.
I know, I know it sounds insane.
But please,
we're running out of time.
- I'm gonna stop you
right there, young lady.
I don't know what kind
of idiot you think I am
but you picked the wrong
guy for your prank.
Now get out of here, both of
you, before I call the cops.
- No, no, my mom's name was Sarah, okay?
She ran away in 1988.
- I don't know any Sarah!
- Okay, well then who's
that in the photo with you?
- That's Lilian.
- Look.
- [John] Lilian.
- [Rachel] Her name's Sarah.
- Rach, maybe... I don't know,
maybe she changed her name
after she escaped from the cult.
- That's your mother?
And you think she's coming back
to life in your unborn baby?
- Yep.
That about sums it up.
(John sighing)
- I need a drink.
Either of you need a drink?
- Yes, please.
- When I got back, Peters
told me the doctor was dead.
He hadn't called it in so,
I took out my cellphone to do it.
(dramatic piano music)
That's when he drew his side
arm and told me to hang up.
- What'd you do?
- I hung up.
- [Man] And then?
- Then I tried talking to him.
Tried figuring out what the
hell was going on but...
(ominous music)
He just ignored me.
- Did he say anything else?
- Told me I couldn't stop her.
- Interesting.
Who's her?
- I don't know.
- Was that all?
- No.
He said,
"All hail Lilith.
"Long live the first mother."
- What the hell does that mean?
- How the fuck should I know?
(coyotes barking)
(crickets chirping)
- There's something
you need to understand.
That's not your mother in there.
That's your grandmother.
It's Mother Lilith.
- Excuse me?
(eerie music)
- You mean the cult lady.
- Oh, you didn't know?
We all called ourselves her children
but Lilian was her actual daughter.
- The psychic kept saying "grandmother."
I thought she was talking about my mother,
the baby's grandma, I know she was...
She was talking about my grandmother.
- She was the one that
was meant to be reborn.
Not your mother.
We were all meant to kill ourselves
to earn a place in hell as royalty.
Son and daughters of Satan.
But mother Lilith was meant to be reborn
so she could continue adopting
generations of children
for the Dark Lord.
But just before the ritual,
your mother ran away.
Mother Lilith was furious.
She still had to kill herself
to escort us to our new father.
But...
Without your mother
there, there was no baby.
So she just had to wait
for her granddaughter
to have a daughter.
- You're telling me I'm giving
birth to the devil's wife
and that my mom is just--
- Dead.
- Okay, okay.
So, even if our baby is
possessed by this Lilith
instead of your mom,
that doesn't tell us what
we came here to find out.
Which is how do we get rid of her?
- You can't.
(ominous music)
Nothing will stop her.
And even if there was something,
I wouldn't tell you.
What kind of a son would
I be if I did that?
- What?
- You enjoying that drink?
(Amber gasping)
(eerie music)
- Amber?
Amber!
Amber, Amber!
Oh god, Amber!
What the hell did you put in that?
- Don't worry, there's nothing in yours.
She'll be fine.
(eerie music)
As long as you follow
instructions, that is.
But if you don't follow instructions,
she's going to get hurt.
Got it?
(sinister music)
(dramatic choir music)
(wind howling)
- Amber?
Amber?
- You know, I've waited
a very long time for you.
There were some years, I admit,
that I had my doubts.
But Mother Lilith always
said you would come.
And here you are now.
It's an honor to meet you, really.
- If you've been waiting or me,
then you never tried to kill yourself.
- Of course not.
(heart monitor beeping)
I was the only one Mother Lilith
could trust to stay behind.
Keep the homestead going.
(gentle music)
(Rachel gasping)
You know that doctor
who tried to abduct you?
She was gonna have him bring you here.
And then you two escaped
and you came here all on your own.
All the way up here for help.
- Please, you don't have to do this.
You really don't have to do this.
Hey, don't you touch her!
(Amber grunting)
Oh honey, I'm so sorry!
Please don't touch me, please.
- Rach?
- Amber.
Don't touch me, no!
- Get away from her!
(Rachel crying)
Get away from her!
Don't touch her!
(Rachel crying)
- You don't have to do this!
Please, stop.
Please.
- Rachel.
- Please, you don't
have to do this, please.
Please.
(Amber crying)
- Don't touch her!
Get away from her!
- Oh!
(heartbeat thumping)
Oh, oh!
(John laughing)
There she is.
There she is!
(heartbeat thumping)
All hail the Lilith.
Oh!
Long live the first mother.
(Rachel gasping)
- No!
No!
- No.
No word yet.
There will be a ruling anytime soon.
Doesn't look good.
I.A. are fuckers.
(foreboding music)
You know what, I gotta go.
I'll keep you posted.
Yeah.
(suspenseful tempo music)
(horse neighing)
(engine rumbling)
(ominous music)
(liquid sloshing)
(ominous tempo music)
- Knock, knock!
Are we decent?
How're we feeling?
I said, how are we feeling?
About the same, huh?
What do you want for lunch?
Rachel, look at me!
(eerie music)
You know, there are some sharp
tools in the barn out there.
Maybe you should start
following instructions
before Mother Lilith makes your wife
put out one of those pretty little eyes!
I'm sick of this attitude.
I know you don't wanna be here.
But this is where you are.
So you really should make the most of it.
- Make the most of it.
- Look,
Lilith is coming
whether you want her to or not
and you will be her mother.
Whether you want to be or not.
And that position comes
with some impressive perks.
You know, you could have
a really sweet life here
if you just gave up the "fuck yous."
Now what do you want for lunch?
(unsettling music)
- You know...
I think I'll...
(Rachel groaning)
Oh!
- Rachel?
Rachel?
- Oh, it's happening!
- Okay, it's okay.
(Rachel groaning)
(ominous music)
It's okay.
(punch thudding)
(Rachel whimpering)
- [Kwan] Hey!
- Oh, you!
- [John] Don't you open that door!
- No one move!
Let me see your hands!
Up!
- Is there anyone else in here?
- My wife is in the barn.
- Good
because I have plenty of
questions for the both of you.
I said hands!
Keep them up!
- I will tell you everything
but first you've gotta get me
out of here and away from him.
He's been holding me captive
this entire time.
- What, she's crazy!
Her and her crazy wife kidnapped me,
drugged me, dragged me out--
- Hey, shut up, both of you!
- Her and her crazy wife!
- I said, shut up!
Here's what's gonna happen.
Both of you are gonna come
outside with me nice and slow.
We're gonna go find your wife
and then I'm gonna take
all three of you in
and you all can tell me what's going on.
Let's go!
Door!
- I can explain if you
just let me explain.
- One hand!
- Let me talk to you without him.
- I said move!
Slowly.
Don't get too close.
- Please.
- [Kwan] Don't get too close!
- I didn't do anything to your partner.
- Hands up!
(eerie music)
- Watch out!
(hammer thudding)
No.
(eerie music)
(Kwan groaning)
(ominous music)
- I told you her wife was crazy.
(gunshot booming)
(Rachel screaming)
Oh come on, you think I'm
gonna fall for that again?
(Rachel yelling)
(dramatic choir music)
- Shoot him!
Amber, shoot the fucker!
- Amber.
- [Rachel] Shoot him, Amber!
Shoot the fucker!
- It's okay, Amber.
It's okay, Amber, calm down.
Calm down, you're gonna be okay.
You don't wanna shot me.
You don't wanna shoot me, Amber.
Don't, look at me, look at me, Amber.
(Rachel groaning)
Look at me.
You don't wanna shoot me.
(Rachel screaming)
Okay?
(Rachel moaning)
(ominous music)
- It's time.
Get rid of him.
I'll take her to the barn to get ready.
(crickets chirping)
(Rachel huffing)
- Amber.
Amber.
Please.
(heart monitor beeping)
You don't have to do this.
Please, please, I know that
you're in there somewhere.
Please.
Amber.
(Rachel groaning)
Amber, please.
I can't do this alone.
Please, please, I need you, I need you.
I can't do this on my own.
(Rachel crying)
- Rachel?
Rachel?
(chains rattling)
(Rachel crying)
Rachel, Rachel, Rachel.
Okay, okay, okay, I'm here.
I am here with you.
Hey, hey, look at me, look at me.
Look at me, I'm here, I'm here.
(Rachel gasping)
I am right here.
- Oh, I burn so much!
- I know, I know.
- I don't know what to do!
- Breathe, breathe.
Baby, breathe.
(Rachel screaming in distance)
(shovel clanking)
(Rachel crying in distance)
- Welcome home, Mother.
(seatbelt alarm beeping)
(engine rumbling)
(gentle music)
- Just breathe, baby.
I am right here with you,
I'm not going anywhere.
(Rachel crying)
(heart monitor beeping)
I'm sorry, just breathe.
I'm here--
- We're getting closer.
(Rachel moaning)
(eerie music)
(chains rattling)
- Amber.
(Rachel moaning)
Mom.
- It's okay, baby.
Don't worry, I'm here.
- Why didn't you ever tell me?
(heart monitor beeping)
- I'm sorry.
I thought I'd saved you.
I thought you were safe.
- That was you?
It was really you in my dream,
you were trying to warn me.
- Your grandmother,
she didn't want me communicating with you
and she's stronger than I am.
But she's distracted now, so I'm here.
- But you're head.
(gentle music)
- Sweetie.
Doesn't matter if I'm dead,
I'll always be with you.
- I don't know what to do, Momma.
- What do you mean?
- I don't think I could stop her.
- Well, maybe not,
but you don't have to do it on her terms.
You're her mother.
You make the rules.
- They said if I did
anything, he'd hurt Amber.
- They're gonna hurt her anyway.
How do you think this ritual ends?
Your grandmother cut her throat
when she left this world.
Someone has to do the
same to bring her back.
- Cut her throat?
(Rachel moaning)
- I love you, baby.
- [Rachel] Momma, don't go!
(Rachel groaning)
- Rachel, Rachel.
Rachel, look.
- Listen.
Oh, listen to me.
They're gonna kill you.
(Rachel groaning)
You've got to get out of here.
- I can't, I can't, Rachel, I can't!
And even if I could, I'm not leaving you!
- Listen to me.
I have a plan.
(heartbeat thumping)
(heart monitor beeping)
(Rachel gasping)
(intense music)
- Get off her!
It's okay.
You're okay.
- Don't touch me, get off me!
(John shushing)
- It's okay.
(Rachel crying)
It's okay!
- Get off me!
- It's okay, it's okay!
- Get off me, get off me!
- It's okay!
(Amber screaming)
(hammer crunching)
(John screaming)
(John yelping)
(Rachel moaning)
- Rachel, listen to me,
you have to take this.
When your next contraction comes,
she won't make me give it back!
You have to take it!
You!
Where is the key?
(John crying)
Where?
- Amber!
(Rachel crying)
(John crying)
(suspenseful music)
- You piece of shit!
- No!
- Rachel,
I will be back, I promise!
I love you!
- I love you.
(intense music)
(foreboding music)
(John whimpering)
Don't.
Don't you fucking touch me!
(eerie music)
Back off!
- You broke my leg!
- Shut up!
(John whimpering)
(dramatic violin music)
The next contraction I have,
my finger is gonna squeeze
this trigger whether I want it to or not,
unless we can make a deal.
- Deal?
There's no deal.
- Shut up!
I wasn't talking to you.
I was talking to her.
- Well she's not gonna listen to you!
- I said
be quiet,
JoNoah!
(dramatic music)
I'm listening.
- Let Amber go.
Let her go.
I will cooperate.
I will take care of you.
I will be your mom.
The best mom that you
could ever have hoped for.
Just please let her go.
Please.
- I'm afraid that's not possible.
In order for me to come
back, another must--
- Has to take your place, I know.
Doesn't have to be her.
Doesn't have to be.
Let it be him.
- Me?
That's ridiculous.
Mother Lilith needs--
- I told you to be quiet, JoNoah!
(heart monitor beeping)
I accept.
- Wha...
- [Lilith] Now drop the gun.
- You think I trust you?
(ominous music)
- Mother,
no.
(eerie music)
You can't make me take your place.
You won't be able to
escort me to my new father.
(Lilith shushing)
He won't know who I am!
- Yes he will.
(John whimpering)
He will know how loyal you served me.
And you,
you will join your
brothers and your sisters
at the Dark Lord's side.
- Yes, Mother.
(eerie chiming music)
- When your next contraction hits,
tell her to run.
But if I let her go and she comes back,
she's mine.
(ominous music)
(Rachel groaning)
- Rachel.
- Amber!
- Rachel!
- You have to go!
- Rachel.
- Go, go, go!
You have to go!
You can't be here, you need to go!
Go!
(gentle piano music)
(engine rumbling)
(Rachel screaming)
(gentle piano music)
(John huffing)
- All hail
the Lilith!
(Rachel moaning)
Long live
the first mother.
(Rachel moaning)
I love you, Mother.
(blood squelching)
(Rachel moaning)
(body thudding)
(Rachel screaming)
(heartbeat thumping)
(Amber crying)
(Amber screaming)
(Rachel moaning)
(dramatic piano music)
(baby crying)
(engine rumbling)
(birds chirping)
(distant dog barking)
- This is it.
- [Man] Wow.
This place is beautiful.
- [Amber] Rachel?
- I'm out here.
(baby cooing)
It's okay.
Go to sleep, baby.
(baby cooing)
- I brought someone to
say hi to baby Lilith.
If it's okay with you,
he's gonna have dinner with
us and spend the night.
He said that he has lots of friends
that will be coming this way soon.
- Well they, of course, are all welcome.
- Wow, thank you.
Seriously.
That's very generous.
- Don't thank me.
Thank Lilith.
- Uh...
Sure.
Thanks, Lilith.
- [Amber] Hi, angel.
Yeah.
Hi, angel.
- She's got it.
- [Amber] Do you wanna hold her?
- Uh...
I'm not...
- [Amber] Keep looking in her eyes.
Hold her tight, hold her
tight and keep bouncing.
(wind chimes clinking)
(heartbeat thumping)
(eerie music)
(demonic whispering)
(sinister music)
(suspenseful instrumental music)
(dramatic piano music)
(ambient music)