Let's walk through that
night again, shall we?
You said the two of
you were fighting.
It's not what I said.
I said we were having an argument.
How many times do I have
to tell you people this?
As many times as it takes
to work through it, Matthew.
You know that.
As many times as it takes to
find the truth about that night.
You don't want to hear the truth.
You want to hear what you
want to hear.
And what do I want to hear?
That I had something to do
with her disappearance.
Did you?
Sure, I did.
I picked a spot.
I drove us out there.
But I did not take her.
So, who did?
Matthew!
Rachel!
You know, Doc.
I think the question you should
be asking isn't who took her.
But what do they want with her?
And with the rest of us?
Now after Rachel disappeared,
you moved.
Yeah.
And why is that?
'Cause I needed to be near her.
To where she was taken.
But if she vanished as you said,
what were you looking for, exactly?
Anything.
Any sign of her or the ship.
Look, I knew she wasn't dead.
Don't ask me why.
But I knew.
Unfortunately, I seem
to be the only one.
Yeah, let's talk about
Sheriff Espinosa.
From the reports I read, he seemed
particularly interested in your case.
Do you know why that is?
Besides the fact he was a
major prick?
I just know he was always there.
Everywhere I went,
everywhere I looked.
He was there.
Find anything today?
Yeah.
What's it been now?
Almost a year.
You ready?
Sure you don't have to go
to the bathroom or anything?
Last stop before we enter the wild.
I'm good.
Thanks for asking.
Okay.
You know, Matthew.
I don't know if this is some
kind of
sick game you're playing.
Or if it's some kind
of elaborate cover up.
And, frankly,
I don't give a shit either way.
Now I've heard your story, what,
must be a hundred times now.
And I have to say, you are
one believable motherfucker.
Except I'm not buying it.
Not one minute of it.
People don't just vanish
into thin air ever.
There is always a nasty
little reason for it.
And you?
I'm betting you got
the ugliest, dirtiest,
nastiest little reason
I've ever seen.
But don't you worry.
One of these days sooner or later,
you're gonna slip.
And when you do,
I'm gonna be right there.
I'll be right back.
He was even there,
that night with Alicia.
And what night was that?
Matthew, you can do this.
Matthew.
I don't wanna do this.
I don't wanna talk about this anymore.
I wanna go to my room!
Right now!
Okay. We can end the session here.
We'll come back around to it later.
It's open.
♪ I'm alone
What's wrong?
It's so peaceful out here.
Really, what is it?
Don't say nothing.
'Cause nothing's really something.
It's been, what, five,
almost six years.
And I was just thinking when
we're gonna take the next step.
Do you want to have a family
with me?
Little ones running around?
Look, I love you.
I always will and nothing
will ever change that,
But you've got to figure out
what you want.
Because I can only wait for
so long.
I'll be right back.
I gotta go pee.
Rachel?
Yeah?
I have some three ply in
the truck if you need it.
Of course, you do.
I'll be right back.
(Mutters)
Matthew?
Matthew? Is that you?
Matthew!
Honey, you okay?
Rachel?
You're all sweaty.
Having a nightmare again?
I... I...
Come on back to bed.
It's cold without you.
This isn't real.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Honey, you okay?
Just relax.
What are you doing?
What are you doing to me?
I'm not doing anything.
Just calm down.
It's okay, it's okay.
Just relax.
What are you doing? Get the
fuck off me! What are you doing?
You had a night terror.
Your doctor's on his way down.
Just relax. Just relax!
Get off me!
Relax!
Matthew.
Matthew, it's Dr. Vans.
Just relax.
Everything's gonna be fine.
We're gonna fix you up
just like last time.
Last time?
What are you talking about?
Get that thing away from me!
Hold him down!
Look, I cleared my schedule
out next weekend.
Let's go camping.
Get out of L.A.
Away from everything.
Just you, me
and desert sky.
What do you say?
Come here.
Take that as a yes?
Matthew.
Rachel!
We don't have much time.
Listen to me.
Remember this place.
They're bringing me back.
What? Who's bringing you back?
Shh!
Rachel, talk to me!
Who's bringing you back?
Good morning.
I hear last night got a little interesting.
You wanna tell me about it?
No.
You gotta talk to somebody, Matthew.
That's how this works.
You talk, I listen.
We find answers.
And maybe stop having these episodes.
Episodes?
What, is this 1927?
You wanna get out of here?
I don't feel like being cooped
up in this office all day.
Oh, I got him.
I'm gonna tell you what
I tell all my patients.
Being up here is a privilege.
Now you can try to escape if
you want,
but the jump will kill you
and the ladder's too slow.
They'll be waiting
for you at the bottom.
Either way, you lose your privileges.
Watch your step.
Come on out.
Here we are.
Ah.
We got air in the lungs.
What do you say we...
Try to break through
the static a little bit.
Shall we?
Have you always had trouble
sleeping, Matthew?
No.
When did it start?
I guess when she started to
visit me.
What do you mean, visit you?
Where are you going so early?
Gonna go check out this area
in the desert.
It's been getting a lot
of activity lately.
Where is it?
Near...
Near the place...
I last saw you.
Tell me.
Never.
That's how I knew she was
still out there.
I'd spend days searching for her...
I'll be right back.
Only to come home and find
her there.
Just in time.
Dinner's ready.
Mmm, I made your favorite: Enchiladas.
Mm, smells delicious.
But not as delicious as you.
Mmm, careful there.
We might just be skipping dinner
and going straight to dessert.
I'll bring the whipped cream.
Dirty boy.
Go wash up.
I'll set the table.
You'll never guess
what I found today.
There's this mountain lion
ripped to shreds.
Almost unrecognizable.
It got me wondering what
kind of animal out here
could do something like that.
Do you know?
Rachel?
Rachel, did you hear me?
Ever wake up from a dream, Doc?
A dream so good, you're mad
at yourself for waking up?
So you roll over
and try like hell to fall
back asleep
to find your way back there?
Yes.
That's all I did.
Fight to get back there.
Till it got to the point where I couldn't
fall asleep in the first place.
Then they sent me to a shrink.
It's worse than you.
Are you scared of these nightmares?
They're just dreams.
Is that how you explain it?
What?
With Rachel?
Are you trying to get
a confession out of me?
No, I'm not here for that.
This is why I don't talk
to people like you.
You want to twist everything
I say to fit your story.
So why don't you tell me what happened?
I told you what happened.
Why don't you tell me again?
Why?
You think my story's gonna change?
I realize this is a
difficult situation for you
so I'm gonna skip the bullshit
and cut to the chase.
In four weeks, you'll appear
in front of a judge
who will determine your fate.
Based partially on my
psychoanalysis of you.
I did not kill Rachel.
Then she disappeared?
Yes.
Then tell me about that night.
Read the report.
I've read the reports.
I want you to tell me.
Or do you just want to sit
in this room alone?
I'd rather be alone.
It's the only thing that's real.
Looks like somebody's got
your feathers all ruffled up.
What do you want?
I got a question for you.
I woke up this morning.
Checked my calendar.
It's just something I do.
I noticed the day is October 12.
Planning on heading back out
to the scene of the crime?
The only crime is you
calling off the search
and coming after me.
Well, now that sounds
like hard feelings.
Here I thought you were
all over our little run in.
You mean, arresting me for murder?
Well, now see, the way I saw it,
everything kept pointing to
one person:
You.
I'm sure you can understand
my point of view.
No.
People do crazy things sometimes.
Yeah. Sure do, don't we?
And right before I actually
thought I was going crazy,
I met Alicia.
Didn't expect to see you
in here tonight.
Yeah.
The usual.
Any progress?
Keep it open, will you?
You got it.
Thank you.
Mind if I sit here?
Be my guest.
Thanks.
I'm Alicia.
Matthew.
I know.
Don't worry.
I'm not with any government
or law enforcement agency.
Just making conversation.
Besides, you kind of look
like you could use a friend.
You're not from around here,
are you?
Boston.
So what are you doing out here?
I was transferred here nine
months ago.
I'm a Communication Analyst
for a private contractor
called Gemini.
Deep Space, Area 246.
Black Base near Death Valley?
Yeah. How'd you know that?
The desert hides many
secrets in plain sight.
You just gotta know
what you're looking at.
Well, I heard you sold everything,
moved out here,
and spend your days driving
across the desert
searching for your dead girlfriend.
She's not dead.
She's alive?
So what exactly do you analyze?
Listen.
You've heard that noise before,
haven't you?
What do you know about it?
It's an E.T. Communication Signal.
These files go back for years,
but I was only hired to
analyze the most recent one.
From October 12 of last..
That's the same day that Rachel..
Yes, it is.
I don't know any specifics.
What I do know is
you guys weren't alone that night.
So I have to confess something.
Curiosity isn't the only thing
that made me want to find you.
You know, the same thing
happened to my sister?
What happened to your sister?
She disappeared.
Right around the same area
as Rachel.
It's Rachel, right?
By Rainbow Basin?
Seems like a lot of weird stuff
has been happening up there lately.
So what do you want from me?
I want your help.
Look, I'm not trying
to put this on you.
But I have driven back
and forth from L.A.
for as long as I can remember
and I can't find anything.
And you're the only person who was
with someone when they disappeared.
So I was hoping that you had,
I don't know,
seen something or heard something.
I'm sorry, but I can't help you.
Okay.
Well, look, here's my card.
If you think of anything,
just give me a call.
Guess I'll leave you alone now.
Nice to meet you.
93 East.
(Mutters)
1193.
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten.
Ten miles?
You're out there somewhere.
I just, uh,
wanted to apologize for last night.
It's just you're the first
person I've talked to
in a year that hasn't treated
me like a lunatic or a murderer.
So...
I guess I'm out of practice.
Sorry about the mess.
I'm going through a bit of a
nomadic phase in my life right now.
I know the feeling.
So what can you tell me about 246?
What makes it special?
Well, that's kind of the thing.
It's not really.
I mean, it is a hot spot for
these E.T. Com Signals.
But there are hundreds
of them all over the world
all spread out in seemingly
random locations.
That's why the government
hired Gemini
to start tracking them in the
late 70s.
And what have you found?
Not much.
The frequency of the signals
changes in strength,
but I can tell you, the last two
years has been particularly strong.
Have other people disappeared?
Oh, absolutely.
And all the stories you read about
lights in the sky,
Missing Time Phenomena.
People like my sister
and Rachel just vanishing.
Why doesn't the government
or Gemini step in
and do something about it?
Truth?
I don't think they want
to do anything about it.
Right now, it's all about research.
Observe and report.
They don't want people freaking
out about extraterrestrial life
when we can't even keep our
shit together on our own planet.
In the meantime,
a bunch of campers go missing
or people claim they saw
mysterious lights
outside their bedroom window.
They can just write
those people off as lunatics.
Or murderers.
I was just trying to get us out
of the city for a couple of days.
If I could go back,
I would take her anywhere else.
Anywhere else.
Look, I know we just met
and you don't know me from Eve,
but I really think I can help
you, Matthew.
And maybe we won't find the answers,
but I don't know.
Maybe we can start
asking the right questions.
As it turns out,
we didn't have to look that hard.
'Cause she came back to me.
When she got back from the hospital,
could you sleep then?
Hospital?
What are you talking about, hospital?
You mean the one 50 miles
from nowhere in the desert?
But when she came back,
did she change?
Was she different?
When she got back?
Remember this place.
They're bringing me back.
Rachel.
Matthew.
Is it really..
Yes, you're home.
Am I really home?
Yes, you are.
I'm home?
Yes, you're home.
Rachel!
Rachel! Rach..
You waited for me.
I wasn't gonna stop till
I found you.
Here.
You wore it?
How did you know where
to find her out there?
She told me.
She told you.
And how did she do that?
Did she call you to tell you
where she was? Don't do that.
Do what?
Make fun of me.
I'm not making fun of you.
Look, I'm not crazy, okay?
Nobody said you are.
You are! You're painting me
to be a crazy person.
And I'm not, okay?
I know what I saw out there!
I saw what I saw!
Matthew, I know you believe that.
I know you do.
No, no, no!
You said hospital!
What are you talking about?
What hospital?
Matthew! The hospital's not important.
I want you to forget
about the hospital.
Now just take a breath.
Let's focus on Rachel.
Now you're out there.
You find her.
You bring her back.
What happened next?
Matthew.
What are you doing here?
How do you know where I live?
I just want to see how you're doing.
I'm fine.
'Cause you look a little jumpy.
I appreciate you stopping by,
but I think... All right, fine.
So you remember that Communication
Signal I told you about?
Yeah, what about it?
Well, I heard it again.
You heard it, didn't you?
No. I didn't hear anything.
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
What are you hiding?
Nothing.
Matthew.
You should go now.
Okay.
Call me if you wanna talk.
Why is it so dark in here?
The light hurts my eyes.
They're pretty.
You're so beautiful.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing's wrong.
Right now in this moment,
everything's right.
It couldn't be more right.
Do you remember?
Some things.
Mostly it's like seeing
for the first time.
We look...
Happy?
Things were good, I think.
Things were good.
Good.
Everything was good.
All right, that's good.
That's good, Matthew.
Why don't we stop there for today?
I think that's a good place.
Come on. Come on.
We'll get something to eat.
Are you all right?
Something's happening to me.
What do you mean?
Rachel?
Please don't hate me.
No.
I love you.
I'll take care of you.
Hey! Let me outta here!
I gotta get outta here!
Matthew, calm down!
Now what's going on in there?
Carl! Carl, you gotta
let me outta here.
Something's wrong!
I gotta see Stewart!
Dr. Stewart is in group.
You know that.
Now just calm down!
What the hell's going on in there?
Matthew?
(Muttering)
Arianna, can you..
What the hell did you do to
me, Stewart?
Matthew, what are you
doing out of your room?
What did you plant in my head?
Why are you taking her from me?
I want you to calm down right now
or I'll have you restrained.
Do you understand me?
Matthew, do you understand me?
Why am I seeing these things?
She was sick.
She was sick,
but she didn't have Cancer.
They took her.
Carl, Doctor Mai.
I need the room.
Thank you.
Matthew, you can stay.
Okay, come clear the room, please?
Now earlier today,
you told me when Rachel
came back everything was good.
So when did that change?
It's when they started
calling her.
Babe?
Rachel!
What's wrong?
Unfortunately, those are
all common side effects..
She didn't have Cancer! What about
this you're not understanding?
She never had Cancer.
She went missing for months.
I went out every goddamned
day searching for her.
I had Espinosa up my ass.
There was this mountain
lion ripped to shreds.
Almost unrecognizable.
It's got me wondering
what kind of animal out here
could do something like that.
Anybody home?
Sheriff?
Well, Matthew.
What are you doing here?
Following up on several calls
we apparently had last night
about some kind of disturbance.
Terrible noises like dogs
or coyotes getting tortured.
Tortured coyotes?
You know anything about that?
No. Why would I?
Did you hear anything last night?
Not a thing.
I was asleep.
Well, that's strange.
'Cause all those reports,
every single one of them,
said it came from your property.
I don't know what to tell you, Sheriff.
You know, something
smells like shit back there.
Well, that's exactly it.
Come again?
Manure.
I'm gonna plant some grass in
front there.
Really? You mind if I take a look?
I do mind.
It's none of your business.
I'd appreciate if you
just leave me alone.
I'm just a normal guy trying
to get back on my feet.
Fuck you.
You did not leave that
cozy little Los Angeles home
to come out here to get back
on your feet.
You're lying,
and you're hiding something.
I can taste it.
Anytime you wanna come back
with a search warrant,
you're more than welcome.
As far as I'm concerned,
this is my property.
And you're trespassing.
Well, you got fight.
I'll give you that.
Ask him. Ask Espinosa!
Okay.
Ask Alicia. She knows.
Hey.
So?
I mean, I'm assuming you
didn't just call me here
for a beer and chitchat about life.
I needed to talk to someone.
And...
You have no one else, I know.
What's going on?
I found Rachel.
Alicia and Espinosa are not important.
I want you to just to focus here.
I want you to focus only on Rachel.
Now when she started to change,
why didn't you bring her
into the hospital?
No, no.
She wouldn't..
She wouldn't let me.
I..
What is this?
Where did these bruises come from?
Could you please leave?
Something's happening to you.
Nothing is happening.
Could you just leave?
What are you doing?
Taking you to the hospital.
No!
You need to.
Matthew, listen to me.
I said I'm not going.
Matthew.
No hospitals, no doctors.
But you need to go.
Matthew, promise me.
Say it.
I promise.
No hospital.
Matthew, have you ever heard
of Repressive Memory Syndrome?
I'll take your silence as yes.
So you've been told your
relationships are created
around a memory of a
traumatic experience
which is objectively false,
but in which you believe to
be true.
That's why you're here, Matthew.
Rachel did get sick.
She wasn't abducted.
There was no aliens.
You're lying.
I wouldn't lie to you, Matthew.
No, you're lying to me!
You're bullshitting my head.
You're testing me.
They changed her.
They did this to her.
There is no they.
There's only it.
And it's invisible.
And it's insidious.
And it made you feel powerless.
No!
Rachel, talk to me.
What's going on?
No, no, no.
It can't be both.
I'm changing.
Everything is gonna be okay.
Can't be both ways.
I know I said I'd love you forever.
You have to kill me.
What?
It's the only way.
I need to go now.
No.
Do you love me?
Of course, I love you.
Then kill me.
No!
I need to go now.
Nothing's gonna happen to you,
me or anyone, okay?
It already has.
She dies in that bed.
Rachel, come back to me.
Rachel.
Rachel, look at me!
I should have told you
every day how I felt.
that night in the desert.
Rachel.
She dies in that bed.
I never lose her in the desert.
I never would have said those
things to her.
They're coming.
Everyone I know,
everyone you know will all die.
I remember you.
Rachel?
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Hey.
This doesn't exist.
Tonight?
Shit.
Directions are in your email.
Fear does not become you.
You're strong.
You've accepted your becoming.
I've accepted nothing.
Matthew!
I'm on it.
You've changed. You have.
You're strong.
Matthew, they're getting
in my mind. My..
My thoughts aren't mine anymore.
They're all gonna die in the end.
Why are you doing this?
Evolution.
So what's your plan?
Kill us all?
You son of a bitch.
I told you it was only
gonna be a matter of time.
What the fuck?
Come on!
Matthew! Get up!
I can't go any farther.
Get up.
Okay, wait here.
Get in.
Matthew?
Matthew, can you hear me?
Come on, stay with me.
Where am I?
You're safe.
What's going on?
Just rest.
Save your strength.
You been playing me this
whole time.
You're one of them!
Where is she?
Charlie! Take me to Rachel!
I want to see Rachel!
Oh, Jesus!
In the end,
the plan just wouldn't hold.
The Submersive Memory
continues to break
at the point of your death.
I'm afraid he's not
a candidate for reintroduction.
I understand.
What happens to him next?
We have protocols for this type of thing.
He'll be dealt with.
Probably sent to the mines.
But it's important for you to understand.
When it's time for us to descend,
it will be people like you that
will help us to our victory.
Of course.
Remember me, Matthew.
Don't leave me.
I will always be with you.
No!
You can't leave me again!
I don't know if I can do it
this time!
Yes, you can.
You're strong.
No, not without you.
You must.
Destiny is within you now.
You must survive.
No! No!
I love you.
I'm sorry about Matthew.
I know.
I don't know anything!
Please let me go!
Please, where are you taking me?
Matthew! Matthew, wake up!
Matthew, wake up, please!
Don't let them take me, please!
Matthew!