♪♪
(baby cooing)
Thanks, T-Bone.
Yeah, see you
tomorrow, yes?
Same place, time same.
Same, same.
Always same.
See you.
Bye.
♪♪
(woman)
Hi, Amy.
(Amy) Hey, Suzie.
(woman)
We barely know each other.
Where you going?
(man)
Going back to Northridge.
Oh, come on,
just a little bit...
Hi, Amy.
(Amy)
Hi.
Hey, Bear.
Hi, Amy.
You seen Johnny?
Not since breakfast.
Supposed to
meet him here.
Well, he's a man
of his word.
Yeah, right.
(man)
Okay, three guesses,
first two don't count.
I know who it is.
No, you don't,
but I'll give you a tip.
Never bet on
the horses.
They'll outrun
you every time.
That's your tip.
You are so funny.
Hey, Monica.
How you doin', Amy?
School go okay?
Yeah, you know.
You makin' friends?
Yeah, of course
I'm making friends.
What, do you think
I'm a moron?
Did I say that?
Did I use
the word "moron"?
I don't think so.
Did you
hear me say that?
I do not believe that
I called you a moron,
and this is what I mean
about us not communicating.
Hey, Bear, listen,
do me a favor,
will ya?
I want you to pick up
six more cases of
bourbon, all right?
Uh, Brennan's
got a deal.
We can unload
that imported stuff
out the back door, okay?
Sure.
Oh, hey,
listen, listen.
Uh-huh.
How-- how's
Little Bear doin'?
Hates being
stuck in bed all day.
Temperature's still up
over 100.
Yeah, well, listen,
get him a...
get him a fire truck
or something, you know?
Lots of bells and whistles,
all right?
Thanks, Johnny.
Forget about it.
(man)
Hey, Johnny!
♪♪
(Johnny)
Come on, come on.
No.
Come on!
Dad...
Dad, I don't
want to dance.
Come on, it's good
for you, kiddo.
Makes your heart sing.
Dad, I'm not into--
Come on, you're gonna
love it.
You'll love it,
come on!
Dad...
... I'm not into this.
Remember this move, huh?
I'm-- Dad,
I'm serious.
Dad, I'm not into it.
Stop, I'm out...
(sighing)
So, what's this,
you got a thing for Monica?
What are you talking
about, Angie?
You walked in with her.
Angie, what are you
talking about?
She's my star attraction.
I'm just
taking care of business.
I got my pride, you know.
Listen, you got
more than that, baby.
You got character.
Yeah, you're
just saying that.
I'll call you later.
Come on.
Come on,
I'll give you a ride.
Why did you make me
come here instead of home?
Because, I got
something to show you.
Yeah, right.
Look, you ever seen
900 million bucks written out?
That's 900
and zero, zero, zero--
back to work, Myra--
zero, zero, zero.
If this isn't
the biggest score
you ever heard of
in your life,
then I don't
know what is.
(women laughing)
(sighing)
(Johnny)
♪ I was standin'
on the corner ♪  ♪ I was standin'
♪ Of Radford and Canal ♪
♪ I was watchin',
watchin' ♪
♪ I was watchin',  watchin' ♪
♪ Watchin' all the people
gather 'round ♪
♪ Watchin' all the people  gather 'round ♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah ♪
♪ Wah-wah ♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah... ♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah,
wah-wah-wah ♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah, wah-wah-wah ♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah-wah ♪♪
(protesters shouting)
(protesters)
Go away, go away!
(man)
You're stealing our land!
(woman)
Emotions are
running high tonight
as excavationists
and Alaska native people
demonstrate against
what they believe...
Okay?
Hey, Gavin.
Hey, Johnny,
great, great.
Can't swing it, Johnny,
the place is packed.
Money guys come
all the way from New York,
oil guys up from Texas,
and, uh, the TV networks,
radio from Outside--
I never seen
so many big shots.
Okay, that's good,
thank you.
Okay, right.
See you later, okay?
Okay, all right.
Right on, okay.
Come on, come on,
I got an idea.
Yeah?
Saw you before, right?
(protestors)
Go away, go away!
(man)
They're stealing
our land!
Go away!
(Johnny)
Up you go, go on.
(Amy)
Yikes.
You gotta see this
before it goes
in your history books.
Excuse me.
Hey, Freddy,
I knew you'd be here.
Hey, Johnny.
This is gonna be the biggest
land grab in history.
... six bids received.
The apparent high bidder
is Petramco at 22 million.
(crowd groaning)
(man)
Stop stealing our land!
We won't see
a nickel of that.
(Johnny)
Pipeline across
the whole state of Alaska.
People are gonna get
so rich up here,
all those
fitters and welders.
You know how much those
turkeys get paid?
Forget about it.
Where they gonna
spend it, on what?
What, am I a schnook,
I can't figure that out?
Hey, Johnny!
(car horn honking)
Hey, Cozart.
It's kinda cold
for September, huh?
Yeah, well, it's winter,
it's night, it's Alaska.
What did you expect?
See the action
inside, man?
No, we've been marching
with the natives.
Pipeline's gonna be a knife
slash through the Mona Lisa.
Yeah, always with the jokes,
huh, Johnny?
Yeah, well, only
with deadbeats like you
who don't come through
with the dough
they've been
holding, Cozart.
(Cozart)
You'll get your money.
Yeah?
Maybe we can
do some business.
We'll just see, huh?
What do you think?
What do I think?
I think you should give
me back my money.
Then we can
talk business.
Come on.
(man)
Hey, this must be
your not-so-little girl,
huh, Johnny?
Came all the way up
from Los Angeles, I heard.
Hi, Jimmy--
Watch it, Jimmy.
Watch it.
Something could
happen to you.
Oh, yeah?
I'm shaking, Johnny,
look at that, man.
(Johnny)
Come on, put your feet in.
(Jimmy) See that?
Whoa...
Look at that, man.
(grunting)
Okay.
(static blaring)
(incoherent radio chatter)
What's the matter now?
You're just
such a big shot.
The way you treat people,
it's so dumb.
Hey, Cozart's
done hard time, okay?
He owes me money.
And that kid idiot is
just bad business anyway.
You should stay away
from him, all right?
(sighing)
Well, you must be the world's
authority on being good.
I mean, you're just
so squeaky clean.
Wanna drive?
You serious?
Absolutely.
You don't ace your permit,
you're no kid of mine.
Okay.
All right, come on.
Now?
Yeah, now, come on.
Oh...
Careful.
All right.
Don't push me
on the brakes.
I got it.
Oh...
I'm steering,
just get your legs down.
Oh, don't-- don't--
don't take your
feet off the gas.
(horn honking)
I'm on the wheel
and on the gas.
All right, all right.
Wait, wait, don't--
don't let go.
You got the wheel?
No, I don't.
Just one sec.
All right?
Okay.
Okay, my foot's
off the gas.
It's all yours,
it's all yours.
I'm driving.
You're driving.
(sighing)
You wanna
know something?
What?
You got
a beautiful smile.
You should
use it more often.
(bell dinging)
(train whistle blowing)
(Amy)
So, what about
an allowance?
(Johnny chuckling)
(Johnny)
Allowance?
Yeah, allowance.
Hey, look at this.
Look at these
cufflinks.
Where do you
think I got these,
at the county fair?
Like in one of those
little plastic bubbles
you pick up with
the claw thing?
Is that what you think,
like it grows on trees?
(sighing)
Just forget it, Dad.
(train whistle blowing
in the distance)
(chuckling)
Okay, all right,
hey, hey, you want money?
Yeah.
You want money?
All right, two bucks an
hour down at the club.
I don't even pay
Floyd two bucks,
not that he's worth it.
(knocking)
Hey, guys.
Drinks in
the back, okay?
(woman)
Sorry, Johnny.
Floyd, come on,
open up, will ya?
We're turning into a couple
of Eskimos out here.
(man)
Seven, the winner's seven.
(woman)
Hey, Amy, look,
I was saving it for you.
(man)
Hey, Johnny!
Hey!
(woman)
From New York.
(Amy) Yeah.
You can have it.
Hey, Tooty, how are ya?
How you doing?
You feeling
lucky tonight?
(man)
Jackpot!
What's going on?
(man)
When did you get this dealer?
Hey, how are you?
Good to see you again.
Who's the lucky one
tonight?
All right!
(Floyd)
Dog Bite's on a runner.
He can't hardly talk.
He's already
down a grand.
Listen, I told you,
I don't want any
crossroaders
coming in here
unless I get
a piece of it.
Now, am I getting
a percentage?
Am I getting
a piece, huh?
Amy, your supper's
in the oven.
And, uh,
George needs to see you.
He's got something
for you.
Okay.
(man)
I'll be over
sometime this afternoon
and we'll take care of it.
Hey, George.
You like that?
You know what,
I have to call you back.
Okay, yes... right.
Okay.
What do you mean
she just left it to me?
You mean not my dad?
(George)
A court lawyer in
Los Angeles sent it to me
and I have to hand it
over in person,
and then
I am out of here.
Hanging out in a joint
like this eight weeks
after I pass my bar exam...
Your dad's not my only
client anymore, you know?
I-- I got a career
to think about.
Where-- where is it?
There's an express train
about to leave
called
"the state of Alaska"
and-- and your dad's standing
on the wrong platform.
Okay, autograph there,
next to
the red dot.
In receipt of mother's
as per her wishes.
Mm-hmm.
Et cetera, et cetera.
You all right
otherwise?
Yeah.
Yeah, why?
Nothing, just you've
been up here a short while
and Alaska's kind of
extreme.
I'm okay.
I'm sorry about
your mom.
I mean, I--
I never knew her but...
(sighing)
I'm okay.
(man)
Miss?
Just go on, you don't...
want to get busted
in a joint like this.
Right.
(Floyd)
You know the house
can't get beat, Johnny.
That's because he hasn't
switched the dice yet.
Look, do me a favor,
will ya, huh?
Will you
stay off the dope?
You're starting to get
an echo in the attic.
Now go on, take this
and get out of here.
All right, huh?
(woman on record)
Well, here goes.
(sighing)
Feels strange talking.
I just hope this
thing works.
Amy...
I want you to know that just
because I never got to be
a movie star like I planned,
or-- or anything famous
or anything that great,
it doesn't mean that you can't
be anything you want, honey.
It's good to dream big and...
don't you ever let anybody
tell you different than that.
You know, the night
you were baptized,
your godmother dreamed about
the Madonna carved in stone.
That's when I knew
you were gonna be blessed.
(sighing)
Amy, I wish I could have been
a better mom for you, I-- I...
... I do, sweetie.
I wish, I wish,
I wish, I wish, I wish,
I wish...
(record crackling)
(sobbing)
(sniffling)
(car horn honking)
(dog barking in the distance)
(girl)
Hey, Sammy!
(girl) Wait up!
(girl)
Sammy's got a crush!
He is, he is!
Amy.
Hmm?
In my country,
when winter come,
bear, he look for cave.
He choose most
dark cave,
for also most warm.
Meaning what?
Most light
not always best cave.
Da?
Da.
(school bell ringing)
Books away.
"To believe what is true for
you in your private heart
is true for all men."
Emerson.
Good.
"I only regret that
I have but one life--"
Nathan Hale.
Thank you, Miss Tesky.
Is that correct,
Miss Ross?
Miss Ross, it appears, is
an aspiring Georgia O'Keeffe.
Quite original too.
However, not as original
as her assignment.
A work of
scintillating fiction,
most notably in the area
of dates and facts.
(students laughing)
Frances, please deposit
this magnumus opus
in the "circularus filus."
(students laughing)
All right, scholars,
no knowledge, no college.
And how about you, you great
flatulent hippopotamus?
(students laughing)
I think you better go in for
cross-country this year.
I'll give you $25
if you make the team.
(students clamoring)
So what are you
gonna get him?
Don't turn 40
every day of the week.
(Amy)
I don't know.
How about an
adding machine
for the times he don't
count so good?
Three-pound
pinkie ring.
Big, hot diamond.
(woman)
Uh-uh, he's saving
that for me.
Right, Angie?
(Angie)
Yeah, you wait.
You're the one
that's gonna wait, honey.
(woman)
That's right.
... gonna be a really
long time, Angie.
Everybody's
just fooling.
We all love him,
you know that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know,
it's just show business.
Little Miss Stuck-Up.
(door closing)
(factory whistle blowing)
(hammering in the distance)
(drill whirring)
Tell you what, tonight,
as soon as I get off.
(bird squawking)
(tires screeching)
Piece of candy?
Ride in
a fast car?
(chuckling)
Come on,
I was just kidding.
Warm as toast in here.
Why don't you
hop in?
I'm a pussycat,
you can ask anybody.
Come on, we'll go for a walk
on a glacier or something.
Huh, you ever done that?
(girl)
Hey, let's pick her up!
(boy)
Go ahead and call.
(girl)
Careful.
I've never seen her...
We've been looking
everywhere for you.
Crazy cheechako.
We even called
the state troopers.
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
(girl)
Who's that?
I'm Francis Cook.
Cook like in James,
the captain.
Amy.
I know.
Ross, right?
Mm-hmm.
Did you come
from Outside?
Los Angeles.
When?
July.
(car horn honking)
Why?
My mother was stuck
in a psycho ward
for a long time,
then she got sick.
My grandmother was too
old to look after me,
so my dad brought me
up here for a while.
But then my mother
went and died,
so I guess
I'm here forever.
I'm sorry.
About your mother.
I never really
knew her.
You know that boy
you were talking to
killed a girl who lived
out near the airport.
He got off because of
some technical problem.
Thank you
for stopping.
(truck horn honking)
All-American city.
Air crossroads
of the world.
That's what
they call it here.
The place where all your
dreams come true.
(laughing)
Where do you live?
You can drop me
anywhere.
Tell me where
you live.
Are we gonna be friends
or is this just a ride?
(car horn honking)
See where all those
cars are parked?
People really
live there?
Home sweet home.
Do you mind?
It's supposed to be
off-limits.
(man)
Jeez, all right,
all right.
(man on TV)
The whole world
is looking at Alaska.
(Johnny)
Hey, you hear that?
Talking about a dome,
moving sidewalks.
(groaning)
We're sitting on
the Houston of Alaska.
(man on TV)
... and when it starts to get
modern and futuristic...
(Amy)
That's great, Dad.
What's your problem?
Oh, I've got
no problem.
It's you
with the problem.
Oh, yeah,
what's that?
Well, you've got this big
future thing happening,
and all you can
do is what you do.
It's just-- it's so low.
I always thought
you were smarter.
(man on TV)
... tell us about the weather--
the way nature planned it.
And Martin has an update on
all the sports on the Outside.
(door closing)
♪♪
(knocking)
(Johnny)
It's me, the dummy.
Can I come in?
(Amy)
Sure, come in.
(door creaking)
Hi.
Listen, Amy...
... I just--
I just want things to go
good between us,
you know?
I know.
You know,
as a matter of fact,
I've even been thinking
about going legit.
For real?
Yeah.
You know, some kind of
real estate, uh...
(train whistle blowing
in the distance)
Where'd you get these?
Uh, your lawyer
brought it.
This is what
she left you?
Yeah.
Yeah, other stuff too,
you know, pictures
and personal stuff.
Audrey Hepburn.
You know, she had
this whole routine,
the pearls and...
the whole thing.
Listen, Amy...
even though
your mother was sick--
You mean crazy.
She understood things.
We even
talked about it.
She wanted you to come
here and live with me,
have a home.
(scoffing)
You call this a home?
I'm working
on it, okay?
It's an adjustment.
An adjustment?
No, no, no, sweetheart,
I-- I-- I didn't
mean it like that.
Listen... listen.
You wanna bet on
a sure thing, huh?
You and me,
we're gonna get
our own place, okay?
A yard, you know,
pets, birdfeeder,
blender, TV tables,
the whole
ball of wax, okay?
You think you could
handle that, huh?
Hey, hey.
You know I love you,
don't you, kiddo?
Come here.
I love you.
Hey, hey...
you still
my girl, huh?
Yeah.
♪♪
(crowd cheering)
Happy Birthday!
Oh, thank you.
Hey, what did I do
to deserve
such affection, huh?
I mean,
how did I get so lucky?
A kid like this?
I mean,
look at this kid.
Is this a 16-year-old
Miss Universe or what?
Okay, okay.
Look at this
beautiful kid.
Just open it,
just open it.
All right, okay,
all right.
(George)
Cake.
Pass the cake,
pass the cake, everybody.
Oh, sweetheart,
this is beautiful!
Thank you.
Hey, look at this,
a pen and pencil set?
Oh, is that beautiful?
Oh, let me get--
hand me a piece of paper,
something to write on.
Floyd, Floyd?
Floyd, hello, Floyd.
Yeah?
Would you come
to the party for me?
Paper, paper.
Get a piece
of paper.
(woman)
How's that?
Yeah.
Here you go.
All right, here we go.
Is that
legitimate or what?
Is that stylish,
is that classy?
What do you think?
Bank manager?
Stockbroker,
real-estate tycoon?
Real estate, now there's
a con that's legit.
You know, one birthday,
she gave me
this little, uh,
this little gold,
uh, trophy,
she bought it
with her own money.
"World's Best Dad."
That's what it said.
(women)
Aw...
Well, let me tell you
something, kiddo.
You are the best
daughter in the world.
In my book,
you're number one.
I love you, baby.
(all applauding)
(woman)
Hit the jukebox.
♪♪
Hey, come on.
What?
Come dance with Dad,
come on.
No.
Come on.
(all cheering)
Come on, come on.
You remember
this song?
♪ The jive was jumping
jive and jamming cool ♪
♪ Certified and
goofing on a C-note ♪
♪ They was flipping ♪
♪ They was flopping ♪
(woman)
You sure you're
not too old? Yeah!
♪ Flipping and a-flopping
like a catfish rodeo ♪
(man)
Oh, yeah.
♪ They was flipping ♪
♪ They was flopping ♪
♪ They was flipping
and a-flopping ♪
♪ Like a catfish rodeo ♪
♪ Strutting on all fours
going down for the count ♪
♪ Rockin' the boat 'til
everybody fell out ♪
♪ They was flipping ♪
♪ They was flopping ♪
Yeah, oh yeah!
♪ Flipping and a-flopping
like catfish rodeo ♪
♪ They was flipping ♪
♪ They was flopping ♪
♪ Flipping and a-flopping
like a catfish rodeo ♪♪
Ahh...
Don't worry,
kiddo, I got you.
I always got you.
(partygoers applauding)
I am too old
for this!
More champagne!
(Johnny)
I'm dying here!
How did I get so old?
I feel like
I just went 15 rounds!
Somebody get me
a drink here!
Oh, that is so
far out.
Anyway, Tim gives me
the ball and...
We're going over
to the center.
Do you want to go?
There's music,
it should be fun.
No, no, no, no.
I-- I can't,
I've got some homework.
That's all right.
I'll-- I'll see
you later.
Okay, bye.
(girl)
Hey, my parents are
gonna be out of town.
They're going to
the Fairbanks.
Bye.
See ya.
What do think
about it, huh?
Francis.
I'm just not into cheerful
and perfect guys.
Your taxi is here.
(boy)
Yeah, let's do it, man.
(girl)
Bye...
Bye, Barry.
(girl)
Hey, see you later.
Are you going to practice?
(girl)
Will you call me tonight?
(boy)
Bye, Holly,
I'll see you later.
(students yelling)
What was she sick from?
Schizophrenia,
plus liver cancer.
That's a lot.
When did it happen?
August.
I mean, it wasn't like
a surprise or anything.
It's just that, uh...
I never got to see her
before she died.
That's too bad.
Mmm.
Have you, uh,
always lived here?
Like, have you been here
all your life?
I was sent to live
with my uncle and auntie
when I was little.
He works for
the government
and she's an
agricultural librarian.
Did you know we grew
America's biggest
cabbage last year?
73 pounds,
right here in Anchorage.
(chuckling)
No, I did not
know that.
No knowledge,
no college.
(laughing)
Ahh...
I already got into
a college,
a good one,
in New York City.
Have you ever
been there?
Uh-uh.
Macy's and Broadway,
the Rockettes!
♪ In this dirty old part
of the city ♪
♪ Where the sun
refuse to shine ♪
♪ People tell me there ain't
no use in tryin' ♪
Would you say
that my life is blessed?
Come on, let's dance!
♪ Watch his hair there
turnin' gray ♪
♪ He's been workin'
and slavin' his life away ♪
♪ This I know ♪
♪ He's been workin' ♪
♪ I've been
workin' too ♪
♪ Every night and day... ♪
Where'd you learn that?
My dad.
Dancing's the only thing
he likes better
than Fats Domino.
Hey, did you know
this is our school anthem?
What?
♪ We gotta
get out of this place ♪
♪ If it's the last thing
we ever do ♪
♪ We gotta
get out of this place ♪
♪ Girl there's a better life
for me and you ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪♪
Oh wow,
are you ever gonna get it.
Floyd,
don't tell my dad.
Hey, I wanna
talk to you.
Where the hell
you been, huh?
What, do you think
I'm some schnook
runs a hotel you can
come in anytime you want?
Who the hell do you
think you are?
I don't know.
Oh, you don't know?
Who were you with?
Friends.
Friends, huh?
Yeah.
I catch you hanging out
with hippies or taking drugs,
you're not gonna be
able to sit down
for a month,
all right?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, hey,
you watch your mouth.
Oh!
Leave me alone,
you moron!
Okay, that's it!
You're grounded!
Oh, grounded
in a whorehouse!
Now, that's original!
What are you
talking about?!
This is a private club!
Members only!
Whatever you say, Dad!
(door slamming)
Well, what's the matter?
You come here to
play poker?!
Play poker!
Poker, everybody,
come on now, poker!
Poker for everybody!
(train whistle blowing)
(bell clanking)
(train rumbling)
(banging on door)
Can't you read?!
It says,
"Private."
Don't move, angel!
You're under arrest!
(man)
Sorry, Johnny,
gotta cuff you.
(woman)
Oh, yeah, right.
Oh, come on now.
Since when are
ashtrays illegal?
Bunch of turkeys.
This is really starting to
aggravate me, you know that?
Yeah, yeah.
Where's my kid?
What have you guys
done with my kid?
(clattering)
Hey, hey, hey, watch it
with that thing, will ya?
That cost me a mint!
(engine revving)
(man)
Procedure, keep moving.
(woman)
This is the most
ridiculous thing.
I mean, you guys know us.
(woman)
For crying out loud.
You okay?
Look, all I gotta do is make
one phone call to George.
The number-one rule:
Get the property back,
and that includes me.
Okay, let's go.
Hey, hey, hey, I'm talking
to my kid here, all right?
We got a social worker
coming to stay--
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
what social worker?
What are you talking about?
I'll be back before she gets
out of school tomorrow, okay?
You resisting,
Mr. Ross?
Okay, okay, all right.
I'll see you
after school.
What's with you,
you new or something?
Yeah, they brought me up
all the way from Seattle
to help get you people
off the streets.
What, "you people"?
Hey, cheechako,
what do you know about
anything up here, huh?
This is Alaska.
These are
the wide-open spaces.
Yeah, not anymore.
(man)
Come on.
Hey, hey, don't push.
Could be you wanna get
your priorities
straight, Mr. Ross.
You got a nice
girl there.
I got one about
the same age myself.
And a couple times a year
I take her out fishing.
You know, spend
a little time with her,
you know, just
the two of us?
Fishing?
Yeah, fishing.
(man)
Last one.
That's it.
Pack it up.
(pot clinking)
Education seems
to stupefy you
with fatigue, Miss Ross.
Is that because
you are proficient
or because you are a lazy,
self-pitying teenager
who believes the world
owes her a better life?
Uh, I-- I didn't get
much sleep last night.
We had some people over.
I suspect you
are intelligent,
and so I am going to
tell you a secret.
Wake up.
Be conscious.
And if you listen
hard,
you might even
find your voice.
Rewrite this,
in your own words.
♪♪
The Declaration
of Independence?
Guess who?
I don't want to.
Listen, am I a man
of my word
or am I a man of my word?
Come on.
Come on, I wanna
show you something
that will knock
your socks off.
Come on.
♪♪
(car horn honking)
Hi, Johnny.
(drill whirring)
Well, here it is.
Our own place.
Just like
I said, see?
Look, right across
from the club.
(drill whirring)
Beautiful, isn't it?
So, what do you think?
I don't know, Dad.
Oh, oh, and that's your
room right up there.
I got plans
for us, kiddo.
You wait and see.
Ahh...
I really mean it,
sweetheart.
(seagull squawking)
(Johnny chuckling)
All right, now we're
coming up--
Okay-- no, my God.
I feel like I'm gonna
go into something.
No, come on.
Coming up on
a step down.
Ready?
And step down.
Okay.
Oh God.
All right, you ready?
Yeah.
You sure?
Yes.
Ta-da!
Wow!
Don't even need a permit.
♪♪
Turn-- very good.
All right, ready?
(Johnny)
Arms up, arms up!
(yelling)
That's too fast,
that's too fast!
Pull it back, pull it back,
pull it back!
(Johnny)
Arms up!
(both shouting)
Don't-- don't,
let go...
All right, I'll take it.
(Johnny and Amy singing)
♪ Wah-wah-wah ♪
♪ Wah-wah ♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah ♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah-wah ♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah ♪
Hey, hey, hey,
right there.
See that?
Joe Gimble.
Remember that number,
will you?
♪♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah ♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah,
wah-wah-wah ♪
♪ Wah-wah-wah-wah ♪♪
(Johnny)
Look, Mr. Gimble,
I happen to know
a few things
about the law, okay?
What does that mean?
What that means is that
if you haven't
closed the deal yet,
you and I could still talk.
Yeah.
Look, look, look,
all I'm trying to--
Johnny.
Could you hang on
a second, please?
Hey.
Thanks, Jimmy.
Look, look, what I'm
trying to tell you is,
that there's a couple
of things
about this guy Cozart
that you should know
before you close
the deal with him.
Think it would be a good
idea if you...
Yes?
Yeah, yeah, I will.
All right, tonight.
Good, good,
thank you.
Right.
(sighing)
Hey, Johnny.
What do you
think of this one?
Ah, that's beautiful,
beautiful.
Great.
Very nice.
Thanks.
Hey, Monica, listen,
do me a favor, will ya?
Could you-- would you
talk to her?
Would you
do that for me?
About what?
(sighing)
(whispering)
I mean, she never
wears anything.
She doesn't wear lipstick,
she doesn't wear...
I mean, look at those
terrible clothes she wears.
What do you call those
things, pants?
They're cute.
Cute?
Yeah.
Her hair's
like a rat's nest.
Forgot about her hair.
Just talk to her about
the other stuff, will you?
Yeah, yeah.
All right, thanks.
Hey, what time
is the game on?
Uh, 2:30.
Yeah?
(laughing)
Hey, baby.
"Hey, baby" yourself.
You wanna come see
my new outfit?
What is it today?
Everybody's
got a look.
♪♪
(Johnny)
Hey, Mr. Gimble,
thanks for coming.
(door closing)
Come on in, come on in.
(dog barking in the distance)
Look, these are
two very bad guys
we're talking
about here, okay?
Cozart is a felon,
the kid had that
bad business with
the girl at the airport,
all right?
What are
you gonna do?
You gonna sell out to
a couple of
schmucks like that?
(man)
Well, I-- I gave
them my word.
You don't cross
guys like that.
You think I want my
throat slit, or worse?
With all due respect,
Mr. Gimble,
getting into business with
those guys in the first place
is what's gonna get
you killed, okay?
Don't say that.
You're giving me
the screaming ab-dabs.
Look...
... maybe I could
help you out.
These guys owe me money.
I can cut a deal,
ease them out.
You could do that?
Hey, I'm a businessman.
But you're gonna have to
give me a discount.
Sure, you got a discount.
Just get 'em
off my back.
I must've been nuts.
Much better.
Harder, scholar.
Well done, Becky.
You can do better,
Miss Tesky.
Excellent, Miss Ross.
A journey of a thousand miles
begins with the first step.
Improving, John.
Keep trying.
She was a movie star?
I mean, what shows?
Maybe I saw her
and I didn't even know it.
Oh, I don't know
what you saw.
You hear this?
Her mother
was movie star.
Oh, really?
No, she wasn't, like, a star.
You know, she wasn't
big or anything.
What's she been in?
Different stuff.
Like what?
(car horn honking)
Oh, I have to go.
Oh, I wish I had
my own limo.
You are making
friends, yes?
Oh, yeah,
I'm Miss Popularity.
(bell ringing)
That's good, Amy.
♪♪
(men whooping)
(man)
Yeah, take it off!
(men whistling)
(man)
Ooh, baby, baby, take it off!
We want topless!
(man)
Come on!
You hear them
out there?
They want me
to... topless!
I'm an entertainer!
(man)
Hey, go back to Detroit!
Hell yeah!
At least
I used to be.
(man)
Yeah, baby,
that's more like it!
♪♪
(both chuckling)
When are you gonna put some
color on those lips, huh?
Nothing heavy,
maybe Morning Frost
or Banana Go-go.
You should
do something here.
Show off those beautiful
features you've got.
I don't have
beautiful features.
Yeah, you do.
(woman)
Just forget it!
(Monica)
I'm tellin' you,
wait until you see this.
You will love
this color, Amy.
It's so...
(woman)
Just calm down.
(Monica) What's this?
They just kept hittin'
him and hittin' him.
Whoa, back up,
back up, what?
Johnny got beat up.
Is he okay?
(Angie)
I don't know,
they kicked me out.
Who's "they"?
Tony Cozart comes in
with that creepy kid.
(woman)
Oh, no, not him.
Johnny says they owed
him a bunch of money
and he was
gonna call it even
if he could buy them out
of that massage joint
up on the highway.
If he messes
with those guys...
It's all right.
♪♪
(sparks crackling)
Dad?!
Dad?
Oh, man...
I don't believe this.
(factory whistle blowing)
(man)
Hey, Jimmy.
Oh boy.
(whistle tooting)
Where is she?
I honk, she come.
She no going
school today.
What's all this?
She say she no like.
What's going on?
Why'd you do it?
I felt like it.
You felt like what?
None of your business.
None of my business?
You just
destroyed my house!
So?
So, you are
gonna get up,
and then you are gonna
go to school,
and you're gonna come
back here and clean it up,
and then you're gonna
pay for it!
You don't own me!
I'm your father!
You wish!
What's that
supposed to mean?
All you do
is you make rules
and you crack dumb jokes
and then you make promises
you're never gonna keep.
Hey, I got you
this house, didn't I?
I quit the gambling
business!
What do you
want from me?!
It didn't change you!
You're still the same!
You're just one big
phony big shot!
Ahh!
Ow!
♪♪
Get up.
Come on, get up
and go to school.
Amy, did you hear me?
You don't own me.
I have rights!
That's what
the social worker told me.
And you know what else
she told me?
She told me I don't have to
live here if I don't want to.
And I don't want to
live here.
(sobbing)
(sighing)
Look, I admit
I'm no Eisenstein
in the homework department,
all right?
But-- but every night
we eat ice cream together,
like a tradition.
I take her out in my boat,
I let her drive my car.
Ask her where she
learned to sing Fats Domino.
Go ahead, ask her.
(man)
And what about school?
There's nothing more
important than an education.
I sincerely believe that.
Exactly how do you support
her education, Mr. Ross?
I get her there,
rain or shine.
(woman)
That's it?
Well, what do I know
about those other things,
like history and so forth?
What do I know
about that?
Mr. Ross, you dropped out
of school when you were 15.
First criminal charge,
assault with
a deadly weapon--
(Johnny)
Hey, I was a kid,
I was drunk, I was waving
a broken beer bottle around.
What is that?
I object to this line
of questioning.
You ran numbers
in the garment district.
Did your father teach you
how to do that, Mr. Ross?
I don't
speak to my father.
I understand he was close
with Meyer Lansky in Miami.
(George)
That's enough.
You're badgering my cl--
Look, Meyer Lansky
would say hello to my father
when he was walking his dog
on Collins Avenue.
"Good morning, Mr. Lansky."
"Good morning,
Mr. Ross."
Now, is that a crime?
Does that make me
a lousy father?
Then you would like
to see your daughter
stay in school?
Well, of course I'd like to
see her continue in school.
Not only that, but after
she finishes high school,
I'm gonna foot the bill
so that she can go on to
blackjack dealer's school
in Vegas... if that's
what she wants.
I do not believe this.
So, they've
got plenty of room
and their daughter's
about your age.
So we thought the two
of you might hit it off.
Jim?
Whoa...
Hello, Amy.
What is this, you want me
to live with a cop?
Forget it.
Amy...
(man)
I said take your
hands off of me!
(men shouting)
I am on your
side, honey.
I like your father.
He's got
a good heart.
I know that.
Trouble is, he thinks
the shortest distance
between two points
is an angle.
I mean, he works
harder to steal a nickel
than it takes to
earn a dime.
Why are some
people like that?
Will they change?
I don't know.
I do know that
he loves you, though.
(sighing)
And I'll do
everything I can
to make sure that the two
of you get back together
in a better situation.
Sound fair?
(sighing)
(Jim)
Dear Father in heaven,
we thank you for this day.
God bless this wonderful
meal to our use...
and us to thy service.
And all God's
people said...
(all)
Amen.
All right, let's eat.
(knife whirring)
Movie star, huh?
♪♪
If I ever catch you with
any of my personal stuff,
you'll be out of here
so fast.
(Jim)
Bedtime, girls.
Knock off the chatter.
Good night, Dad.
Good night.
He thinks doing this
is some kind of huge
favor for mankind.
But your type
all end up the same.
Born a loser,
die a loser.
Trust me.
Beautiful color, scarlet,
don't you think?
Yeah.
Useful word, too.
"Scarlet Letter,"
"Scarlet Pimpernel,"
scarlet fever...
scarlet woman.
Hmm?
You wanted to see me.
Words are important,
Miss Ross.
They define
what you will be become.
You do want to become
something, don't you?
Yeah.
I don't know.
"Every atom belonging
to me as good...
belongs to you."
(laughing)
(girl)
Far out.
I'd sort of like
a dad like that.
(girl)
I don't know.
Look at the way he's dressed.
He's hilarious,
isn't he?
(girl)
Wow...
Get in.
Please,
get in the car.
(students laughing)
Go, go!
What's the problem
with you?
Just drive!
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
I got permission,
if you want.
For what?
To be together,
just for the weekend.
You can help me
fix up my place.
What place?
I got a new business.
(scoffing)
Yeah, right.
It's legitimate.
Mm-hmm.
Tell me another one.
Hey...
I'm a man of my word.
Yeah.
♪♪
There it is.
What do you think?
Your dad made me
vice president.
That's great.
(bell dinging)
Hello.
Hi.
I'm here for the, uh,
demonstration.
(Johnny)
Now, ladies, this is one
of my favorite stitches.
You insert the cam here,
bring your material in
under the needle,
roll the needle
down in, drop the lock,
and we begin to sew.
It's as
simple as that.
And what we have is...
a beautiful stitch.
Oh, my...
Nice straight line.
Isn't that amazing?
(woman)
Oh, I can't believe it.
One of our
more perfect stitches.
It's a miracle.
Yes, it is.
Now, when you finish,
you bring the needle up,
drop the lock off here,
pull the material out,
take a snip,
and you have an
extraordinary stitch.
Now, this deluxe model
comes with
50 different cams
to vary the stitch
50 different times.
Any questions?
Yes, indeed.
Oh, I must have one--
Just for
the weekend.
(Johnny)
So, you got any homework?
It's Friday.
Well, you got tests,
stuff to write?
Dad, it's the weekend.
Hey, school comes first.
Oh, since when?
I'll help you.
(chuckling)
You don't know
anything about--
Don't know what?
Hey, go ahead,
ask me something.
And not just
two plus two, okay?
Ask me the hard stuff.
Hey, look,
check this out.
Three-way bulb.
Better for the eyes.
Dad.
Come on, you're old enough,
you're smart.
We should be talking
about important things,
like world events.
Come on,
ask me anything.
Geography, history,
science, go ahead.
Um, um...
Okay, okay, um...
How big...
is the moon?
The moon, huh?
(sighing)
That's a tough one.
The moon...
It's pretty big,
I know that.
I know, I know,
let's look it up.
Encyclopedia Britannica.
(laughing)
I read
the whole thing.
Very good books.
(blues playing)
You wanna
know how it works?
Yeah.
Okay.
The flywheel
turns the crankshaft.
Now, that makes
the pistons
go up and down
in the cylinders.
Then the timing chain
turns the camshaft
so that when it rotates,
the cams operate the valves.
Basic rock-'n'-roll.
(laughing)
Oh... Dad.
Is that beautiful
or is that beautiful?
That's beautiful.
(laughing)
(Amy)
"Long enough have you dreamed
contemptible dreams.
"Now I wash the gum
from your eyes.
"You must habit yourself
to the dazzle of the light
"and of every moment
of your life.
"Long have you timidly waded,
holding a plank by the shore.
"Now I will you
to be a bold swimmer,
"to jump off in the midst
of the sea,
"rise again,
nod to me, shout,
and laughingly dash
with your hair."
God, I don't
believe it.
Look what
he gave me.
Is that cool?
Great!
Where are you going?
Swimming.
(car horns honking)
(woman)
Yeah, well, I'll be back
in five minutes.
(car horns honking)
(siren blaring
in the distance)
(man)
What does
this thing do here?
(woman)
Yeah, it goes right
under the furniture,
like he showed us.
So you won't
have to...
Where's my Dad?
In the back.
Wait, Amy, Amy,
he's got a meeting.
Just, it's serious.
Don't.
(Johnny)
What kind of a sucker
do you think I am?
And you're buying this place
with money you already owe me
and now you want more?
I'm only taking a grand
to pay off Gimble.
You get in
on Cindy's with me,
50/50 partners.
I'm telling ya,
the massage business
is gonna make
a killing up here.
That kid idiot of yours
cuts my face, cracks my rib,
and now you wanna
kiss and make up
like nothing
ever happened?
Could be worse.
You threatening me?
You're the wise guy,
Johnny.
You tell me.
Joe Gimble wants to
sell Cindy's to me.
I'm gonna buy it.
We'll see about that.
(sighing)
(clattering)
You quitting?
What are you
doing here?
I saw the signs,
I saw the stuff
in the windows--
Hey, hey, hey.
That was just a gimmick
to bring in customers.
Are you in trouble?
(chuckling)
Hey, what's this,
what's this?
Nothing, I'm asking
you a question.
Are you in trouble?
No, I was just-- I'm--
I was doing business.
I'm gonna pick up
a little real estate.
Mm-hmm.
I'm not in trouble,
come on, come here.
Come on, come here.
Come here,
you still my girl?
Come on now,
hey, huh?
Come on,
it's gonna be okay.
Come on, you'll see.
Everything's
gonna be okay.
♪♪
(window creaking)
(bird squawking)
It's so weird.
What?
I never really noticed
the mountains before.
(bird squawking)
Never really
looked at them.
(bird squawking)
White people are
so sentimental.
Yeah, right,
as if you're not.
A rock is a rock
and the sea is the sea.
(laughing)
You're so full of it!
(boy)
Guys, come on!
They found a body
in the river.
(boy)
Is that it?
(girl) What?
♪♪
(all shouting)
(man)
All right, let's get this
film back to the lab.
(man)
Let's see it.
Joseph Gimble.
Owned Cindy's,
that, uh, massage place
up on the Glen there.
(Jim)
Can you get these
kids out of here?
(girl)
I'll come with you.
Cozart is such a creep,
I hope they fry him.
They want my dad
to testify against him.
Not a good idea.
No.
Look, uh, Amy, Amy,
c-c-could you get that?
Thanks.
Mm-hmm.
Could you get
the door?
(laughing)
(Johnny)
I love you, baby.
(bell dinging)
(door closing)
Morning, ma'am.
Morning, Amy.
What?
Is your dad around?
Nope.
He's busy.
Well, I'm sorry, Amy,
but I got a warrant here.
Gotta talk to him.
So what, so you-- you
think this stuff is hot?
Is that it?
I mean, I get into
a legitimate business
and all you turkeys want
to do is hassle me.
Hey, why don't you go on over
to the Electric Queen dealer?
He's the one that's
ripping everybody off.
Listen, why don't you
just show us
your paperwork,
Mr. Ross?
We'll be out of your hair.
Hey, you're the cop,
you got the warrant.
Taxpayers think
you're such a big hero.
How about you find it?
Schmuck!
It was a mistake--
You liar!
(Johnny)
Amy, Amy, just--
No, you leave me alone!
Just listen to me for
a second, will ya listen?!
I got that stuff at a...
You're a liar!
... cut-rate price
but they're straight goods.
I swear to God!
No!
You're a liar
and a cheater!
All you ever do is you
con people,
then rip 'em off.
Once a loser,
always a loser!
Have you ever heard
that expression?
Well, that's what you are
and you're never
gonna change!
Amy!
(car horn honking)
(Angie)
Get out of here!
(Johnny)
Why don't you go
play someplace else?
(Jimmy)
Now listen to me, Johnny.
We had a deal with
Joe Gimble.
(Angie)
You liar!
He was gonna sell Cindy's to us!
Cindy's is all
bought and paid for.
There's not much you can
do about it,
except maybe cry.
I can make you go away
is what I can do, Johnny.
I'll get somebody
up here, man,
they'll
take care of it.
500 bucks!
That's all
it costs, man.
Take it off!
Take it all off!
Hurt me!
♪♪
(Johnny)
Go on, get out of here!
Get out, you...
(engine revving)
Lay off, you creeps!
Kid idiot's too stupid
to do business.
Be lucky
if he sees 25.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You okay?
You all right?
All right, okay,
all right.
Why don't you tell 'em?
What?
You know.
"Man of your word,"
that's what you said.
What, now?
Yeah, now.
Well...
me and Angie,
we, uh...
... we're gonna
get married.
Hope that's okay.
Sure.
Why not?
It's Alaska.
(Bear)
Congratulations.
(car horn honking)
Cozart's
gonna get off.
How do you know?
Because my dad
testified.
Nobody believed him.
You know, I mean,
he's so...
you know, acting
like he's so cool.
I mean, he's so dumb.
The way he goes around,
acting like he's so hot.
You can't change anything
from what it is.
He's on his own journey,
and you must go on yours.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
(sighing)
I just gotta go
do my own thing.
(man)
Headbands, necklaces?
You know, it's just
like I wish, I wish...
Bells, all kinds--
how about Tibetan?
Listen to this.
I'm beginning to sound
like my mother.
(bell dinging)
Three bucks,
or best offer.
Isn't that
what they say?
We all turn into
our mothers?
Only got two.
It's yours.
That's great.
Looney Tunes,
here I come.
Peace.
Yeah, right, ditto.
(bottle cork popping)
(Johnny)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, listen, listen,
you want some of this?
It's fantastic.
(T-Bone)
Give me shoe,
give me shoe.
Pleasing to be quiet!
Please.
It's time for toast.
(all cheering)
(speaking Russian)
To the newlyweds!
(all cheering)
(man)
Newlyweds!
(T-Bone)
More champagne!
Everybody drink, drink!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
(Monica)
Your garter, your garter,
your garter!
Time to
throw the garter!
Whoo!
(all whooping and cheering)
(all cheering)
Is for woman!
(all laughing)
Uh... Johnny asked me to say
a few good
words on his behalf.
As far as I know, uh,
there only are a few good words
on that subject.
Very good, very funny.
No, seriously, what can I say
about, uh, Johnny?
Um...
Every day the guy's got
a shine on his shoes.
Dust, rain,
muck, slush...
here in Alaska, how does
anybody do that?
Uh...
Johnny, Angie!
(all cheering)
(Johnny)
Hey, somebody, hit the music!
♪♪
♪ I wanna dance
with you baby ♪
♪ Daddy swing ya
all night long ♪♪
Congratulations.
How's it going?
Okay, if you're into teenage
go-go girls for stepmoms.
So what are you here on,
business?
What?
I said, "Are you here
on business?"
The jury came back
this morning.
And?
He's innocent.
Why am I not surprised?
They figured
something bigger
had to be behind
the whole thing.
Mob, hit man.
Somebody from outside.
Yeah, but you know
Cozart did it.
Yes, I do.
And now what?
Well, your father
better watch himself.
Some people didn't like
his testimony.
Listen, if you
have any problems,
I want you to call me.
There's
two numbers here.
You keep it with you.
I know this hasn't
been easy for you.
I don't need a lot
of favors, thank you.
♪♪
(man on TV)
Oil company estimates
the pipeline
will be 800 miles long,
climb two mountain ranges and
cross 350 rivers and streams.
The revenue will generate
thousands of dollars
in royalties
for every resident of Alaska.
However, native land claims are
currently delaying the project.
Without a settlement,
this project...
That's right, that's great,
blow your futures.
Get a beautiful setup,
and then blow the whole deal.
Where do you think
you're going?
Out.
Not tonight.
It's a goodbye party
for Francis.
She's leaving
for college.
No, no,
it's not safe.
I'm going out.
Look, Amy, he might
use you to hurt me.
I can take care
of myself.
Not tonight.
Don't!
Come on.
No.
She's my best friend!
You are staying home
tonight.
Ow!
Let me go!
No, no!
Read a book!
(panting)
(sniffling)
Ahh!
(bell clanking)
(blues music playing)
(Johnny sighing)
(music stopping)
(sighing)
(bell clanking)
(car horn honking)
(Johnny)
Amy?
Amy.
Amy!
Come on, let's go,
step on it!
He's your father.
Go!
It's not good to
run away.
You must
face your problems.
(sighing)
♪♪
(panting)
Amy?
Amy!
No...
Come here,
come here...
(Amy)
No!
Come here.
You wanted to hit me?
Hit me!
Amy, Amy, Amy.
I'm never gonna
hit you again.
I'm sorry, I promise.
(sobbing)
Amy, I'm--
I'm sorry.
Go away.
Don't touch them.
Amy, listen, I...
Look, I know you're doing
great in school,
so I know you're
smart enough to talk.
How do you know that?
Know what?
About school.
I know what I know.
You don't
know anything.
Try me.
Try me, please.
You said
you'd get me there.
Get you where,
sweetheart?
When she was sick
and she
wanted to see me.
You said you'd get me
back to Los Angeles
before she died.
It all happened
so fast.
We didn't even
go to the funeral.
I had business,
I-- I was--
I never
said goodbye.
She never saw me.
You don't
care about her
or me or anybody
but yourself.
That's not true.
I loved your mother,
I love you.
I never said goodbye!
If you love somebody,
you go and say goodbye.
You don't leave them alone
to die like garbage!
Yeah.
No.
Forget it.
It doesn't matter now.
What doesn't
matter now, huh?
I'm gonna go back.
Go back where?
New York.
(sniffling)
Los Angeles,
I don't know.
How you gonna do that?
Gonna save up.
What about school?
It's no big deal.
Look, it is
a big deal,
and I think that
you should stick it out.
It's my life.
Well, what do you wanna do,
you wanna blow it like I did?
You wanna waste
your whole life
and end up
with nothing?
You think I don't
know who I am?
How far I got?
I know.
I know, but you're
different, Amy.
You're...
you're really smart.
You could do something
with that.
I was never legit,
right from day one.
But I-- I've been around
and I know some things.
And I'm telling ya,
knowing stuff like...
like, how big the moon is,
that's your ticket
out of all of this crap.
I love you, Amy.
I know you
got it in you to...
to be whatever
you want.
(sighing)
Get rid of that
massage place.
(sighing)
Look, all I got
to do is just--
No, please.
Just get rid of
the massage place.
Please.
(sighing)
Okay.
(chuckling)
Okay, you got it.
Right.
♪♪
I love you, kiddo.
I love you
with all my heart.
I love you too.
♪♪
(Amy)
My hair was so curly.
Remember that bike?
Oh, God, that bike.
And why did you buy me
such a big bike?
I had a deal.
I got it at
an auction.
It was about six sizes
too big for you.
Look at that.
God, I fell off
so much.
Oh, look at this,
look at this.
The Lucky Horse Bar,
1962.
You remember that?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, look at that.
Vegas.
$1 million
in actual cash.
(chuckling)
(Angie)
Hey, Johnny, what channel
is the fight on?
Leave it where it is!
What was she like
before I was born?
You know,
before she got... crazy.
She sure had
the figure.
Great sense of humor.
(chuckling)
She could make
anybody laugh.
Best B-girl
in the business.
(Angie)
Is there any
Neapolitan left, Johnny?
I'll be right there!
Ah...
First house.
Monterey Park.
Man, she was so proud
of that place.
The big dream,
you know?
She had it right in
the palm of her hand.
She wasn't so crazy.
Not then anyway.
She just thought
that the whole ball of wax
was gonna melt.
That's what did it.
Everything just...
... went dark.
(sighing)
I miss her.
The way she was.
Dad...
Hmm?
(sighing)
Am I like her?
I...
... I mean...
You know.
Only the best parts.
That spark she had.
Whoo...
You sure got that.
But the rest?
That's all you.
Just you.
Let me tell you something.
She would have been
very proud
of the way
you turned out.
Proud as me.
Good night, kiddo.
Good night, Daddy.
(door closing)
(man)
Are you punctual?
Yes, sir.
Ever been
in any trouble?
No, sir.
You like automobiles?
Yes, sir.
Know anything about them?
Uh, my dad
drives a '67 DeVille,
V-8, 429-cubic-inch,
340 horses,
4.13-inch bore,
four-inch stroke,
dual carbs,
dual mufflers...
(car horn honking)
(bell dinging)
(drill whirring)
Put a tiger in your tank
for you, sir?
Yeah, give me
five bucks' worth,
and, uh, make it
snappy, lady.
I'm in a big rush.
Okay.
Hey, wanna come up
to the lake?
Can't you see
I'm busy?
I got a job now.
Now...
I am responsible.
(chuckling)
Hey... look what I got.
Since when
do you fish, huh?
Are you kidding?
You know how big
salmon run up here?
Would you believe
100 pounds?
You know what that
crap sells for in town?
And I'm talking
per ounce.
What, am I a schnook,
I can't figure that out?
Sometimes I'm so smart,
I can't stand myself.
Five bucks.
No tip?
Yeah, get a new wardrobe,
that's your tip.
(chuckling)
So, you coming up?
I can't,
not today.
You still my girl?
Absolutely.
(chuckling)
I'll be home
before dark.
See you for dinner.
(woman on TV)
... residents of
Cook Inlet Basin
can expect a slow rise
in precipitation
than expected
on the coast this weekend.
Highs should reach the low...
expected to dip below freezing
in the Anchorage Bowl.
The area in the north
can expect
some flurries on Saturday.
(foil crackling)
And now Tom Tell
will bring us...
(car horn honking)
(engine idling)
Hi.
So this is it, huh?
My plane
leaves in an hour.
I brought you
some catalogs.
They all have
scholarships.
What, are you dreaming?
Will you write to me?
Yeah, sure.
You too.
Take care of yourself.
(sniffling)
I'm gonna be okay.
I know that.
(engine revving)
(car horn honking)
(sniffling)
♪♪
(door creaking)
I can't wait here.
I know exactly
where he puts the boat.
I can help you,
just let me
come with you, please.
It's against
regulations, Amy.
(sighing)
This is Alaska.
Please.
(engine revving)
(Jim)
There's something I should
have told you before now.
You know the sewing machines
of your dad's?
He got them
on the gray market.
Meaning what?
They weren't hot.
He was legit.
Huh.
Man...
(chuckling)
(handle jiggling)
(grunting)
(sighing)
(Jim)
Hey, give me some backup
over at Eagle River.
I want a search warrant
for Cozart.
C-O-Z-A-R-T.
(man)
Bring him down to the car.
We got him.
Boo!
(man)
Get away from there!
Just need a couple more
minutes with these guys.
They resisted, so we have
to take 'em downtown.
(man)
You better come, sir.
We found him.
Amy!
No.
♪♪
(man)
Watch your step.
Uh, sir?
Come on,
it's all right.
Let's leave her
alone with him.
Oh...
(sobbing)
They told me about
the sewing machines.
I... didn't
believe you.
And I'm sorry.
(sobbing)
I don't even know
where you learned
to sew stitches like that.
(sobbing)
I'm still your girl.
(factory whistle blowing)
(drill whirring)
I'm not going today.
Is most sad day
in my life.
Thanks, T-Bone.
(door closing)
(woman)
You poor thing.
Honey, you'll be okay.
(Angie sobbing)
(woman)
Here you go.
This is so terrible.
Here, honey.
Go ahead.
Oh, God...
(car horn honking)
(tires screeching)
(woman)
I know it's awful.
(drill whirring)
Johnny's first rule.
Get the property back.
Thanks.
Uh, it'll take another
week for the boat.
Police found a letter
that they must have
tried to make him sign
to hand over Cindy's.
He must have
told them--
They were schmucks.
(chuckling)
♪♪
(sniffling)
(woman)
"Dear Mr. Ross.
"In response to your letter,
"I am delighted to inform you
that your daughter is achieving
"well above average grades
in all her subjects.
"I believe she has
an extremely bright future.
If you have any further
questions, please call me."
(car horn honking
in the distance)
(Angie)
Yeah, well, I'm his wife.
And I got rights.
That little kiddo
just better get used to it.
(engine revving)
Amy, Amy, wait, wait.
Open up.
I'm sorry,
I'm really sorry.
I gotta go.
Your daddy loved you, Amy.
He thought about
you all the time.
I mean all the time,
and you know that.
(sniffling)
I'll see ya.
Hey!
Where do you think
you're going?
That is my Cadillac!
I own that now!
Come back here,
you little moron!
♪♪
(sobbing quietly)
(tires screeching)
(sobbing)
(bird squawking)
♪♪
(thundering)
(bird squawking)
(crying)
(sighing)
(bird squawking)
♪♪
(tires screeching)
Get out of here.
(door closing)
What did you
think of his poems?
They don't rhyme.
(school bell ringing)
(students chattering)
♪♪