-  No, no!
- Oh, my god. Little girl?
Little girl, are you okay?
Are you okay?
No. No!
No!
No! No!
-  All right, we
made the left at the fork,
so Lily Road should be
coming up any second.
- I can't find it.
- It's because it's not
gonna be on that phone.
You gotta look up.
Gotta eyeball it.
-  How'd I
agree to this again?
- 'Cause the Young
Writers Club needed you.
Seriously, if you hadn't
signed up for this field trip,
we wouldn't be here.
Thank you.
- Well, my soul
would've preferred
a trip to Steinbeck's home.
- Uh-huh. Too far.
You look like a superhero
with those glasses on.
Like a female Clark Kent.
- Wow, thanks.
- I meant that as a compliment.
- It didn't sound that way.
- Okay, how about this?
You look smart and
drop dead gorgeous.
How's that?
- That's inappropriate.
- Wow. Can't win
with you, can I?
- We work together.
As in, I have to
see you every day
in the teacher's lounge
until I get my tenure.
-  I know. I heard.
- Ooh! Lily Road.
- How we doing back there, guys?
- Nauseous.
-  Okay. Try
looking out the window.
Watch the road.
- Are
you gonna blow chunks?
Hey, yo, yo, yo,
Teach. Stop the van.
We got a spewer in the backseat.
Oh!
Oh.
Thar she blows.
- Go outside and see
if she painted the van.
- I will, I will.
Side of the boat is all clean,
Captain. Nice aim, Teala.
-  Sorry.
- You okay, Teala?
-  Yeah,
just need a minute.
- Okay.
- Best book ever.
You have such a way with words.
It's like I'm inside them,
feeling every pain, every joy.
- You liked it.
- Mm-hm. I loved it.
I can't wait to read the others.
- Well, it's my only one, so...
I appreciate it,
Josie. Thank you.
- Well, you really are an
incredible writer, Chris.
- Mr. Cotton.
- They can call me Chris.
Mr. C. How about Mr. C?
- Eh.
- All right, I'm good. - Yes?
- All right.
- All right, let's do it.
Okay.
- Yup! - All right.
- Give me that. - What's that?
-  Don't touch it.
-  Okay.
-  Yeah, yeah, like,
we don't need to see it again...
- So this is Teardrop. Wow.
- Oh, it was booming
back in its day.
Teardrop was a gold rush town.
Think the mines
are supposed to be
in those hills right there.
But when there's
something of great value,
trouble always follows.
So the miners would chain dogs
up to the mouth of the mine
to keep the thieves out.
But when the gold was
gone, the miners were gone.
Those sick bastards would
leave the dogs tied up to die.
Hell dogs are supposed
to haunt this town now.
They said, at night, you can
hear them howling in pain.
No one's actually ever
seen them, though.
And that is the story
of the great Teardrop.
Come on.
Come on. We're
checking in right here.
Afternoon. We are
looking to check in.
Do you have any rooms available?
- We might.
- I would've called in advance,
but I couldn't find
your number anywhere.
- We like to operate
by word of mouth.
Keeps his place from
becoming a tourist trap.
Pardon my stare. I could've
sworn you've checked in before.
- No. No.
No. Never.
- Must be deja vu, then.
- Denver, is it?
- Like the capital of Colorado.
- Are you the
owner of the hotel?
- I wear all the
hats so to speak.
That your family?
- No. My students.
They're on their senior field
trip. Young Authors Club.
-  Hm.
- It's their last year,
so I wanted to take them
somewhere unforgettable.
- Our town's so forgettable,
most don't know we exist.
- That's exactly why we're here.
So I'll need five
rooms, if that's okay.
- One is what I've got.
- Are you kidding?
- Well, we are almost
at full capacity.
That an issue?
- It just seems quiet.
- Well, we have some old timers
who like to tuck in early.
I don't keep tabs on my
guests, but I do keep a tab.
Care for a drink?
- No.
-  You sure?
- Yes. It's early.
Thank you. I'm sure.
- I do have the old
judge's cabin available.
Gonna cost you extra, though.
- Judge?
- Called him the Hanging Judge.
- The Hanging Judge?
- That's right.
- They have one room
and a cabin available.
- Oh, well, that's perfect.
- What?
- So it'll be the three
of us in the cabin.
And then you guys
can take the room.
- Yeah, that's a great
idea. Let's do that.
- No. The obvious choice is
me and Chris in the hotel.
- Chris and I.
AP English exam next week. And
I thought we agreed on Mr. C?
- Um, I didn't agree
to anything, Ms. H.
- A cabin and a room is fine.
I'll take the girls.
You take Ross.
Nice to meet you. I'm Rebecca.
- I've been cleaning up
things in the back, ma'am.
Don't wanna make your
hands all filthy now.
Room 2 in the hotel,
end of the road.
Cabin about 50 yards from there,
past the church.
- Thank you, Denver.
- You are the very welcome.
Excuse me, mister.
- Sorry. The bill.
So I'm assuming that this
is a cash-only kinda place.
- Teardrop's really
more of a pit stop.
Come through, take a
glance out the window,
and keep on moving.
I recommend you do the same.
- It's not my first rodeo.
- You sure we
haven't met before?
- Oh, I'm sure.
-  Hm?
- I'd remember someone like you.
How much?
- How much do you got?
- Right.
You can just say when.
- That'll do.
- Okay.
-  Enjoy your stay now.
-  All right.
All right, all right.
The cabin and the hotel
are down this way.
So let's go grab our bags.
-  No way.
-  This is me and Ross.
- Oh, this is us?
Oh, swim move.
Ooh. Hey, I got dips on
this bad boy right here.
- Chris, come get in my selfie.
-  We
don't allow photos.
- Sorry. Kids and
their smartphones.
You know how they are.
- Don't do it again.
-  We won't. Sorry.
- Is he serious?
- Real nice guy.
-  Mm-hm.
-  Let's go.
- No. I'm good here.
Unless Josie wants to...
- Okay. - No, I'm good.
Wouldn't want you touching
my luggage anyways.
- Made a friend, huh? - Mm-hm.
♪ My name is Ross
♪ I am the boss
♪ Just took a loss
♪ Still got the sauce
- Woo. Yo, I gotta
write that down.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- What?
-  Any luck?
-  No Teardrop 5G.
- A nice break from
technology never hurt anyone.
- Not when you're waiting
for college acceptances.
- You've already gotten
into, like, a dozen schools.
- Not my first choice.
- Be grateful you got in.
- Yeah.
- I wonder if they
have hot water here.
- Ahem! - Oh.
- What? Never seen a
pair of double Ds before?
- Behind the curtain, please.
- Boob job at 17,
you believe that?
Actually, I kinda do.
- You guys talking about me?
- Oh, no, no, no. - No.
- Nothing.
Yeah.
- This place is wild, isn't it?
Bet this hotel hasn't changed
in over a hundred years.
Wonder what brought
the town down.
Bet it was smallpox.
Smallpox, you know...
You're an entitled little
prick, you know that?
-  Were you talking to me?
- Yeah, I was. - Huh.
- I said this town,
it's crazy, isn't it?
It's like a portal back in time.
- That's crazy.
You know, no offense, Mr. C...
Hey, check this out.
♪ The Old West is a snoozefest
♪ I just wanna get some rest
♪ No more pests
I...
Oh, sweet Jesus.
Did you see that maid?
Mr. C, come on now,
be my wing man.
- No. - Okay?
I love her, I think.
Just be my wing man. - No.
No, no, no, no. - No, yes, yes.
Yeah, come on, come
on. Yo, excuse me.
- Didn't mean to bother you.
- Oh, no, no, no. You didn't.
I just, or, well,
my teacher and I,
we're writing a
book about the town.
We just wanna ask
you a few questions.
We're interested, you know?
- I'd love to hear about the
town of Teardrop from a local.
- I'm not supposed
to talk to customers.
- Okay. Well, what are
you supposed to do, then?
- Clean, quiet as a mouse.
- Well, yeah. She's
a maid, Mr. C.
That's what she...
She cleans, you know.
I'm Ross the Boss.
Or, well, you can
just call me Ross.
I mean, Ross the Boss
is like my nickname,
my alias, you know, my rap name.
It's nice to meet you.
- I'm sorry. I'm not allowed.
- You're not allowed to shake...
Damn.
What did I do wrong
there?
Don't laugh, Mr. C.
Don't act like you have...
- Yes, yes!
- That sounded like hurt.
- No, no, no. That doesn't hurt.
That's great positioning.
That's what that is. - Ew.
- This is pretty ridiculous.
- You know what position
that is, Josie? - Ew, shut up.
- That's cowgirl.
- That's inappropriate.
- That's just the place
we're in right now.
-  Shh.
-  Well, there
are definitely guests here.
- I haven't seen anyone.
- I can hear them,
like, you know.
- No...
I don't know what that is.
- From your room.
The kids are having a
listening party at the moment.
-  You heard them?
- Yeah.
- Something to drink, ma'am?
- No thank you.
-  Hm.
- Like you should be. Us
being the adults and all.
- I had a little
bit of a headache.
I just think one will
help take the edge off.
- A headache, huh?
- Yeah. Headache.
Denver here was about to tell us
about why the town
was named Teardrop.
- You ask a lot of questions.
- It's 'cause he's a novelist.
- Is he now? - Mm-hm.
Published bestseller. And he
still graces us as a teacher.
-  Hm.
- What can I say?
I love to teach.
- What are your books about?
- American frontier ghost towns.
And it's "book," singular.
- He's being modest. He's
writing a new one right now.
- Well...
To answer your question,
the town was named
after a little girl.
A quiet child who loved
her dolls made of straw.
Lorelei.
Lorelei was a strange one,
kept to herself and her toys,
but she became a
pariah around town.
Kids pinched her,
called her a freak,
anything to get a
rise out of her.
But little Lorelei
wouldn't react.
Kids being kids,
they took it too far.
They started pelting
her with stones
until she was
bruised and bloodied.
And still, the
girl would not cry.
Legend has it, Lorelei
never shed a single tear
no matter what anyone did.
Nowadays, we'd know
she had a disorder,
a genetic inability to cry.
- Well, that's some
way to name a town.
- You asked.
- You know, I think
I will have a drink.
-  Yes, ma'am.
- What? We're allowed
to have some fun, right?
-  Look what I brought.
- Are those brownies?
- Mm-hm, edibles. - Nice.
- Who's down to get baked?
Josie? You're down.
Teala? Down to get baked?
- Oh, sorry. Can't.
Studying.
- Teala, have you ever
even gotten stoned?
- Um, no.
- No?
Oh, we are so popping
your weed cherry tonight.
- No. No one is
popping my weed cherry.
Or any cherry for that matter.
- Oh, come on. We'll
guide you through it.
We'll be like your
green Sherpas.
- Yeah, and these are edibles,
so they don't hurt your lungs.
I mean, it's weed.
So you'll lose a couple
of brain cells, big deal.
You have enough for all
three of us combined.
- True.
- Ah, I don't know about that.
-  All right, here. Teala.
Ooh! - Oh.
- You caught it.
Josie. Ooh.
That's the best one.
-  Mm.
- Am I gonna freak
out over this?
- No, you'll get high.
- Am I gonna hallucinate
and shit? - Come on.
It'll be fun. I promise.
- Is that Nutella?
- Yeah, and cannabutter.
Whole jar of it right here.
All right, ready?
Let's all take it.
Three, two-
- One bite, okay?
One bite, that's it.
- Okay, and then
after that first bite,
you'll eat the whole
thing so you can get high.
One.
-  Okay.
-  Mm.
- Mm. - Nice job.
These are amazing. - Mm-hm.
Thank you. That's not the
only thing I do well, Josie.
- That portrait in the hotel
entrance, that's her, right?
Lorelei?
-  Mm-hm.
- What's her mother's name?
- Alice.
- I think we've had enough
story time for one night.
- Maybe I'm a little tipsy,
but I think he's
kinda growing on me.
What?
-  You're a little tipsy.
Don't you like him?
I like him.
-  Josie,
what are you doing?
-  Taking a selfie, duh.
- Yeah, she's taking
a selfie, duh.
Let me get in there.
- Guys, we're not supposed
to take pictures.
- Teala, get in here.
- Gonna get in trouble.
- Come on.
Oh, what the hell?
- What?
-  How do
we look like that?
- Either your phone is messed up
or these edibles are
kicking in quick.
- What's going on?
- Some drama, that's
what's going on.
Here. Be quiet.
Let's keep exploring.
-  Uh, I don't
know about that.
- Oh, god! - Oh!
-  Wait, wait.
Josie, give me your phone.
- Um.
- Just give me
your phone. Josie.
Whoa, jeez! - Oh!
- What the F?! - God.
They're scarecrows.
- What?
-  Just alone, in the bed.
Who does that?
-  It's freezing in here.
- Yeah.
And this vase must've blown
off the dresser from the wind.
- Yeah, those
windows aren't open.
Anyways, it still doesn't
explain the voices.
Guys, can we get
the hell outta here?
- Yeah, I don't like this.
- Yeah, I mean...
- Let's go, Ross.
- There's no more to see.
- I just can't get
enough of this place.
I can't. I wanna
just drink it all in.
Since we've been here,
I feel like I tapped
into a creative
reservoir inside of me.
- What about your new book?
Hello?
- It was rejected.
- What do you mean?
- My publisher hated it.
Hated it.
She said it was uninspired.
Actually, what she said
was that I phoned it in.
So, yeah, I'm starting over.
- When did this happen?
- Earlier this year.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Because it's humiliating.
It's deflating.
I've still been trying to
process it for myself, I think.
But since we've been here,
for the first time
in a long, long time,
I feel like I have pages in me.
Great pages.
I wanna take a totally
different direction.
I don't wanna write
any more bland,
dry stories about
Western ghost towns.
I wanna make it personal.
- I'm sorry they didn't like it.
Fuck them.
- Yeah.
Yeah. Fuck them.
Yes!
- Yeah. - Fuck them.
- Fuck them. - Fuck 'em.
Fuck them.
- Oh. You're drunk.
- Not really.
- Look, if this is gonna happen,
I just wanna take
it really slow.
Okay?
- We should go
check on the kids.
-  Do you
guys think it's true-
- What? - About Chris
and Marie Pannenbaker?
- No. - No, that's not true.
-  I wish it were true.
Means I might
actually have a shot.
- Well, why don't you just
date to guy your own age?
It might actually
work out for once.
- Guys in high school
aren't mature enough for me.
-  Really, no
one in high school's
mature enough for you?
-  Maybe at Hamilton.
-  I knew I
should've gone to Hamilton.
You know what?
I'm high as shit.
We are in the middle of
nowhere. Let's just go back.
-  What? Dude,
don't be a buzzkill.
-  Who are you right now?
- I don't know, but I'm
feeling kinda groovy.
- Yeah, girl.
-  What, you say "groovy"?
- Yeah. - Teala, no, no, no, no.
Okay, now I'm sticking around.
We don't say "groovy" anymore.
-  Well,
we're saying it now.
-  Let me teach
you what we do say, okay?
- What? - We say "lit."
-  Oh.
- All right? - Lit.
Lit, there we go.
-  Lit.
-  Hey,
guys, look at this.
-  Is that singing?
- Sounds like it.
- What did you put
in these edibles?
-  Couple of grams of
indica. And some THC powder.
I mean, they're
strong, but that's it.
- Guys, I'm either
tripping really hard,
or that sound is coming
from inside that barn.
- Oh, hell to the no.
- Oh, hell to the yes.
I'm going in. Who's with me?
-  Me.
- What?
Guys.
-  Singing stopped.
- Yeah, no shit, Sherlock.
- What's that? - What the F?!
- Shh, shh, shh.
- Holy shit!
Run, run!
-  Hey, hey, hey, whoa,
whoa, whoa! What's going on?!
- Mr. C... Okay.
-  I'm just
so glad you're here.
I was so freaked out.
- Okay, that's, all
right... There's something
fucked up in there, man.
- Like what?
- Fucked up!
Mr. C, the eyes...
- Mr. C, swear to God,
there's something in there.
-  Oh, shit.
- Chris?!
- They got him. I say we go.
- Chris!
- There's nothing.
Bunch of barn mice.
-  What?
- Yeah, some barn
mice from hell.
- No way.
- Have you been drinking?
- No. - No, no, no.
- Mm-hm. Breath check.
Ross.
- No, no, no, no, listen,
Ms. Harris, I haven't brushed
my teeth since we got here,
so for your own safety,
keep your distance.
You guys heard the
singing, right?
- Singing?
Why are your eyes red?
- I was in there and I had a
near death experience, Mr. C.
- We're high as shit!
- Fuck! - Mm-hm.
-  They peer
pressured me to doing it.
- Wow, some team player you are.
- I worked way too hard to throw
everything away, all right?
I'm literally going to be
disowned by my parents.
Please. This can't
go on my record.
I have to get into Penn.
- 'Cause she wouldn't
have taken an edible
if I didn't force her.
Punish me.
I'm not going to college
anyways, so nothing to lose.
- What? No, no, no.
Look, it was my weed. That
shit was way too dank.
It's on me, okay?
Josie, I got this.
- Okay, okay. You guys, I
don't care whose idea it was.
It's not okay.
What should we do?
- Give a warning.
- A warning?
- What do you want do?
Yes, a warning. Yes, a big
fucking warning for each of you.
Let's go!
- Thank you so much. - Let's go!
- Ms...
-  No. Turn and walk.
I don't even wanna hear it.
Chris, you're running a jungle.
Walk. Please.
- There's... Please!
- We survived the night.
Generally, a good sign when
you're staying in a ghost town.
The kids reported a
couple of anomalies,
but I'm not sold on it.
When haven't you
been to a ghost town
that didn't try to
pull a fast one?
I know there's more
to you, Teardrop.
I just don't know where to look.
-  Wow. What time is it?
-  Good morning, pumpkin.
- What's up, Mr. C?
-  You ready?
-  Ready for what?
- We're touring the town.
We're waiting on you. Let's go.
- Wait.
Mr. C, someone took my pains.
I need-
- There's the general store,
courthouse, livery stable.
Got the old mine shaft
about a quarter mile off.
All inoperable.
- What's still open?
- The saloon, the hotel.
That's what everyone wants.
A drink and a warm bed.
- What about the cabin that
the girls are staying in?
What's up with that?
- That belonged to the old judge
of teardrop. Judge Wincott.
Or the Hanging Judge, as
they liked to call him.
See the guy gallows over there?
That's where one of the
most horrific hangings
took place long ago.
She was his wife.
She told him he would pay for
what he did, they all would.
And "no one would ever
leave this place."
- That's it?! You're gonna
leave us on a cliffhanger?
- Your stay's not over yet.
- Why'd he hang her, Denver?
- Hey, Mr. C, that
guy's a weirdo.
- Be respectful.
- I agree, he's so weird.
- That guy is such a weirdo.
- I don't...
- Mm.
Chris?
I hear you.
Don't say a word.
This is what you wanted
all along, right?
Well, that's all you get
for now, you dirty perv.
Chris?
- Yo, you need help?
-  No.
- Okay.
- Sorry. I forget who I'm
supposed to be sometimes.
- Ah, anxiety.
Yeah, I suffer from it too.
I even wrote something about it.
♪ Yo, check it
♪ I suffer from anxiety
♪ Bottled up inside of me
♪ Like a knife in
the side of me ♪
♪ Writing rhymes in my diary
♪ Just for the notoriety
♪ Yeah
- You're very funny.
- Thank you.
I try.
I try really hard, actually.
- Hey, I get it. People
often think I'm two-faced.
- I don't think
you're two-faced.
I mean, I act like
a douchebag because,
I don't know, I think
it makes me look cool.
- What's a douchebag.
- Oh, no shot. You don't
know what a douchebag is?
What...
No way.
Whoa.
Where are you from?
-  I never left here.
- You have never left here?
- Can't. Not allowed.
-  Get inside!
- Coming!
- Whoa. Hey, he should not
be talking to you like that.
- He thinks he's my
dad or something.
- Hey. Denver, that's
what a douchebag is.
-  Now!
- Come to the cemetery tonight.
- The cemetery? Tonight?
You're totally a weirdo.
Okay.
♪ Got a date at the cemetery
♪ Hope it won't be scary
- I heard dogs.
- Probably some
wild dogs somewhere.
Preserve the devil.
- The hell hounds
you told us about?
- I don't know.
- Okay, Chris, let's call it.
Let's get the hell outta Dodge.
- Not going anywhere.
- I don't like it
here. I wanna go home.
You can come back on your
own and write your book.
Without us.
- It's not just about my book.
- What are you talking about?
- Found this in my
grandfather's basement.
That letter was
written in this hotel.
More than a century ago.
- I don't understand.
- Becca, I've been looking for
this place for years. Years.
It's not online anywhere.
It's not in maps.
It's not in books.
Okay? Nowhere.
- You're not making any sense.
- Read the letter.
Read the letter.
- Jeez Louise. Okay.
"My dearest son, I
am sending you away
from this wicked place.
Promise me you will
never come back here.
Your loving mother, Alice."
- Alice.
Alice.
Rebecca, I think that Alice
is my great-grandmother.
Alice that's on the
portrait in the hallway.
Alice that was... Who
was hung to death.
- Yes. Yes.
She gave up her son to get
him away from this place.
That baby was my grandfather.
She wrote this letter to give
him when he was old enough.
I think that Alice got my
grandfather out of here
before she cursed this town.
- My god, you don't
really believe in curses?
- I'll tell you what I do know,
is that the town of Teardrop
began to wither away
pretty quickly after that,
along with its history
and everyone in it.
- You shouldn't have
brought the students here.
- I know that.
- Do you understand
how this looks?
- Yes. Abso-fucking-lutely
insane.
- Why are you putting
me in this position?
- Because this is
my family, Rebecca.
This is my past.
This is my history.
Rebecca, I can't leave here yet.
Please. Please, you
have to understand.
I can't go. Not yet.
- I wish you would've told me.
- I should have... Stop.
Enough.
- Rebecca, please.
- Okay. We stay,
but it's for you.
- Thank you.
- Where's Teala?
- I don't know. She
wanted to study outside.
- I told you not to
split up.
Have you seen Teala?
- No.
I'll go look for her.
- What?
- Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, are you all right?
What happened?
- I don't know, I just...
- Okay, okay. Listen.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Hey.
You're okay. You're okay.
Listen to me. We're going back.
We're gonna stay in groups
of at least two from now on.
Okay? Let's go back.
You're okay. You're okay.
It's just a rough
idea right now, okay?
I'm probably gonna rewrite this
a dozen times, but it would-
- It's fantastic.
- Is it?
- It is.
- God. Thank you
for reading that.
- Thanks for letting me.
- Your usual?
- It's 3:45 p.m.
- Yeah, Denver. Gonna
hold off for a while.
- Whatever you say.
-  But while
you're here...
-  Mm-hm?
- Why don't you tell
us why you hung her?
- You have a fetish for this
ghost story stuff, don't you?
- You gonna make me ask again?
- Don't get angry on me.
- I'm not.
- The last thing I ever
want to do is get you upset.
- I'm not angry.
- All right. I'll tell you.
Just don't quote me in
your book or anything.
I prefer to be left anonymous.
The Hanging Judge didn't
have a trace of empathy.
Merciless.
But it wasn't just the
sinners who feared his wrath.
It was his own
flesh and blood too.
By the time Lorelei was eight,
he had grown to hate her.
Plagued him like a disease.
So disgusted by what he created,
he could only do the
one thing he knew how.
Screamed, "Cry!
Why won't you cry?!"
No matter how hard
he ever beat her,
she wouldn't do it,
or couldn't do it.
He murdered his
daughter that night.
They say the judge had no
sorrow, not even a single tear.
Of course, no one dared question
the word of the Hanging Judge.
Poor Alice took the blame.
Her cries could be
heard across Teardrop.
No worse sound than a
mother losing her child.
- What about the baby?
-  "What
about the baby?"
- The baby, did he
make it out alive?
- You're living
proof, my friend.
- What do you mean?
- I knew the moment you
stepped foot in my bar.
You look just like him.
It's remarkable.
- How do you know what the
Hanging Judge looks like?
- Photos were left behind.
I reckon Chris
could show you some
of the old newspapers
he's been finding.
- Ugh, what a trip this
has turned out to be.
I'm gonna be so heated
if next year's class gets
to go to, like,
Hawaii or something.
-  You're just mad
Mr. C won't get with you.
- Hey, I may have lost the
battle, but not the war.
- Okay. You're kinda like
the female General Custard.
- Who's that?
- Do you, like, not pay any
attention in class at all?
- Hey, school isn't as important
as real life experience.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
- Oh. It's fine.
Happened a long time ago.
- I've been told I'm a great
listener. Amongst other things.
- I've been having some weird
thoughts since we got here.
- Like suicidal thoughts?
- Sorta.
I know them really
well, so it's scary.
- Well, you know what I think?
I think you put too much
pressure on yourself.
I mean, you're never
gonna look back
and care about your GPA.
3.8, 3.9, what's the difference?
- Weighted 4.0.
- Okay. Well, live a little.
I mean, be dumb and
stupid for a change.
All those bad thoughts
will go away. Promise.
- Look what I found. Who's
down to get old school drunk?
- Never have I ever
dated a college boy.
- College boys, no. But
college girls, several.
- Several. - Several.
-  Drink up, then.
- All right.
- Okay, my turn. Never have
I ever tried to kill myself.
- The hell? Josie.
- What? It's true.
I haven't.
- No, that's not cool.
I don't care.
- I'm not ashamed of it.
- Yeah. See, Ross,
she doesn't care.
- Okay. Then I got one.
Never have I ever been a ho.
Drink up, skank.
- Fuck you, asshole!
- Fuck you.
You're a DNA dumpster, and
that's all you're good for.
- What, because
I won't blow you?
- No...
All right, screw you.
And you know what?
Screw you too.
I stood up for you.
Get outta my way.
- No. - All right, you bitch.
I got a date with the
maid, so I'll see ya.
- What a dick.
God.
- Well, was fun while it lasted.
- Oh, shut up.
-  Winifred Carmine. 1802.
Would've never predicted
this, would you, Winifred?
- Careful where you step.
Gone doesn't mean
they're gone away.
- I'm sorry. I shouldn't
have done that.
-  Don't apologize to me.
- Winifred, I apologize.
Do you want, are you
old enough to drink?
- On some days.
- Okay. Well, how
about this one?
- Nope.
- Yeah, that's probably
a pretty good idea.
I really shouldn't be
drinking this either.
I mean, this was
my dad's poison.
He's a dry fucking
drunk now, so...
It's just so exhausting
being young, you know?
Like, sometimes, I wish I could
just push a button and bang.
I'm married and have a kid
and I just have
my shit together.
- Being old isn't all that
it's cracked up to be.
Your body starts to rot,
desiccate, and smell funny.
- Oh, gosh. You are unlike
anyone I have ever met before.
- I can be someone
else if you'd like.
- No. No, no, no.
Just be yourself.
That's what I'm into.
- How do I do that?
- Now, that is a
damn good question.
I don't even know sometimes.
I mean...
You know, you were right.
This is peaceful.
- Wait until the sun sets.
- Mm.
I'll be waiting on bated breath.
- A fading sun is the one
pure thing in this world.
It's the last thing you
see on the hanging tree.
- On the hanging, what?
- I'm not good at this.
- No, it's all right.
I'm not good at a lot of...
Hey, where are you going?
-  Catch me!
- Catch you? Okay.
I'm really fast, actually.
Where'd you go?!
Hey.
Excuse me? Have you seen a maid?
Holy shit!
Oh, fuck.
Where's the maid?
- Is that Ross?
Oh, my god.
-  Hey,
hey! You all right?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Okay.
- Not that great, all right.
Whoa, whoa, watch your chain.
- Take it slow.
- Watch your chain.
- Wait, my chain.
Can you get my chain?
- No, I'm not gonna
touch that. Get up.
Get up. You good?
- Yeah.
- What have you been doing?
-  I'm good.
Just too much sauce
for Ross the Boss.
- Too much sauce?
- Yeah, I don't think
any of that is funny, Ross.
-  Where
have you two been?
- Stop it.
- Making sure your friend
doesn't have alcohol poisoning.
- Yeah, I'm sorry, Josie.
I didn't mean what
I said earlier.
- You smell like a frat party.
- Guys, what in the
hell is going on here?
I was 18 once. I
get it, all right?
But with the drinking,
with the weed?
What do I need to do here? Huh?
Do I need to be the bad teacher?
Calls you guys in?
Gets you suspended?
-  It's just some-
- I don't wanna
hear it right now.
Do you have anything
to add, Ms. Harris?
- We leave bright
and early tomorrow.
Set your alarms for 6:00 a.m.
- Wait. I thought we were
in leaving Sunday morning?
- Executive decision.
- Been having these migraines
since I've been here.
In Teardrop.
I feel this rage.
It's coming over me, thinking
about our time together.
It's almost over.
I can't leave yet.
I feel like if I do, I'm
not gonna get to come back.
And I still have
so many questions.
- Um, okay, how about
C?
- There is a C.
Hey, I told you there's a C.
- There's a C? - Yeah.
-  Okay.
-  Chris?
- No. - Mr. C.
-  Chris!
- No. Wait!
Rebecca!
Rebecca.
Rebecca... Get off of me!
- I didn't do anything. I
didn't touch her, I swear.
- I don't believe you, Chris!
I don't believe a single
word out of your mouth!
- I saw her. I saw Lorelei.
- You are fucking unbelievable!
And it's a shame too
because I was just
starting to like you.
- I saw her! I fucking saw
her in the bathtub inside!
- I knew what you were, I
should've trusted my gut.
I'm such a sucker.
- You knew what I was?
I wouldn't make this up.
- You're a writer, it's
what you fucking do!
It's over.
- Where are you going?!
- Far away from you!
-  Ms. Harris.
What's going on?
- Ask Chris.
Is there any way you could
drive me to the nearest town?
- As far as I can take you.
- Thank you.
Beautiful car.
-  A nice old
gentleman left it years back.
Still hasn't returned for it.
I figure he'll thank me for
keeping the engine warm.
-  What is it?
- Can't go any
further than this.
- Oh. I'll pay you.
- Not about money.
- What is it about, then?
- I feel uncomfortable
leaving the hotel.
I'm sure you can relate.
- I can't.
- This is the best
I can do for you.
- Seriously? I could've
walked this far.
- Truly and deeply sorry.
-  Thanks.
-  Nothing even
happened between us.
You caught a look, big deal.
-  So, Mr. C
accidentally walks in on you,
so has the entire
graduating class.
- Watch it.
It's not funny.
-  It's just a brush.
- Mr. C.
- Chris.
You can call me Chris.
- Are you seeing things too?
- No.
I think we all need
to get some shuteye.
Moving back to my room. You
guys stay outta trouble.
- Hey, Mr. C, I was thinking
that I would just stay
here with the girls
so you can be alone.
- Sure.
Why the hell not?
-  Okay.
- Ross! Teala's gone!
- Oh, shit.
Hey! Teala!
- Pack your shit.
We're getting outta here.
Now. Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
-  Ross.
- Hey. We're getting
the fuck outta here.
You should come.
-  Follow me.
- Hey! What are you doing?!
Wait!
- Does this phone work?
Hello?
Hello?!
Fuck!
- Who are you trying to call?
-  The police.
- Now, why would you do that?
- 'Cause there's a
fucking dead girl outside.
- This is Denver speaking.
Mm-hm.
Mm, he's right here.
Yes, it is crazy how
much like him he looks.
All right.
She wants to talk to you.
- Who is that?
Hello?
-  It was nice
to see your face.
You have turned
into a handsome man.
Just like your grandfather.
- Who is this?
-  You know who
this is, my darling.
- What the fuck's
happening here?
- Same thing that
happens every time.
The faces are new, but
it always ends the same.
- Josie?
Josie, we've gotta go.
Listen, I know you
feel guilty, all right?
But...
- Wait! Come with us!
Hey! Wait!
Hey, just hold on.
Hold on. Hey.
Just, please, just listen to me.
-  Lower your lantern.
- What...
No, I'm not gonna
lower the lantern.
-  Pretty please?
You'll go wild for
this. Everyone does.
No cheating.
- What's that voice?
- Lift your lantern.
I can be someone else
instead. Whoever you want.
All of us were hung at the
neck, it's the worst way to go.
With everyone watching,
with everyone laughing
as you squirm.
They're all me. And I'm them.
- Stop, you fucking freak!
- I was a freak.
You're gonna wish
you got the rope.
-  No, no! Oh, god, no!
- You're dead.
You've been dead
for a hundred years.
-  Ross?!
Ross!
Rebecca?!
- I will not be the scapegoat
for what you've done.
- What I have done?
- You have killed, Judge.
- What did you do to me?!
- I myself have
not done a thing.
I told you to leave
while you still could.
Your usual, sir?
- No. No!
- Chris!
What time is it?
-  You! You did it to us!
- I need to know
the time, Chris,
'cause I don't make
it a hair pass 10.
- Hey!
♪ I went out one morning
for to take a little walk ♪
♪ Came upon that
Wild Bill Jones ♪
♪ He was walking and a-talking
by my little girl's side ♪
♪ I bid him for to
leave her alone ♪
♪ He said, young
man, I'ma past 21 ♪
♪ Too old to seek control
♪ Well, he whipped out his
blade, so then I drew my gun ♪
♪ Destroyed that
poor boy's soul ♪
♪ He jerked and he scrambled
and fell down on the ground ♪
♪ And gave one dying moan
♪ I threw my arms around
my little girl's neck ♪
♪ I said, honey, now
you're all alone ♪
♪ Now, let's pass around
them long-necked bottles ♪
♪ Let's all go out on a spree
♪ Today was last of
the Wild Bill Jones ♪
♪ Will tomorrow be
the last of me ♪
♪ Fill your glasses
up to the brim ♪
♪ And let the drink flow free
♪ Today was the last of
the Wild Bill Jones ♪
♪ Will tomorrow be
the last of me ♪
♪ I got out out of
jail without any bail ♪
♪ But the judge said
I was a free man ♪
♪ I looked all around till
my little girl I found ♪
♪ Said I couldn't
see her again ♪
♪ Yes, I took a life of
that Wild Bill Jones ♪
♪ But it still took
my true love from me ♪
♪ I've been overtaken
by a worried mind ♪
♪ Will this trouble
never set me free ♪