(arrows whooshing)
(waves crashing)
(thudding)
(man laughing)
(ominous music)
(soft music)
(birds chirping)
Hi.
Hey.
It's colder than you'd think.
Yeah?
Yeah. I believe so.
So you can read my mind then?
It's colder than it
looks I should say.
Right. Yeah, I know.
I was kidding.
Mm. My tongue is sometimes
faster than my mind, so.
Yeah.
There's probably a joke in
there somewhere, but not me.
Well, I speak a few
languages, so sometimes...
Yeah. You know, it's funny.
I thought I could detect a
little, little accent in there.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What is it?
French, Italian, little German.
That would've been
my guess, a mix.
Then you should've taken it.
Fortune favors the bold.
Right.
Yeah.
That's... It's Latin, isn't it.
Very good. Good for you.
I am a librarian, so...
That's gotta be good
for something, right.
Really?
You don't look like a librarian.
I'll take that as a
compliment, even if it wasn't.
You should.
I will.
So you come around
here often, or?
Really?
I know that sounds super
corny, but you know, I,
I really don't mean
anything by it.
Well, actually I do.
This is kind of my secret spot.
Well, not exactly.
I know about it.
I mean, from my
husband, my family.
I come out here to read, relax.
Like that makes sense.
Sure. No, no, I get it.
Well I'm, I'm finished.
I'm gonna go.
Enjoy.
That's...
You don't have to, you know,
if you're not in a
hurry or anything.
Thank you.
But, I gotta go.
It's a lovely beach.
Enjoy your day.
I'm Marilyn, by the way.
Connor.
Good name.
Thanks.
You too.
(unsettling music)
Can you help me?
Sure.
What can I do?
You again.
Yes, it's me.
You gotta stop following me.
(both chuckling)
I'm kidding.
How are you?
Going all right I suppose.
Now that I'm not so
sure I can believe.
(scoffs) You're very perceptive.
It's kind of obvious,
the way that you said that.
Plus with those on.
Oh.
If you're gonna say
you ran into a door
frame, please don't.
I won't believe you.
I was gonna say cabinet,
but I guess you're right.
I'm not so okay.
I'm really sorry.
No, it's not your fault.
Well, that's good.
Maybe I can be the solution.
Maybe.
Anyway, I suppose
in a way it was you.
Um?
At the beach.
I just took too much
time talking to you
and I was late
getting home, so...
Oh my god. I'm so...
What?
- Connor?
When you're done in there,
could you come here, please?
Take over at the desk?
Absolutely.
Just a minute, I'm
helping somebody here.
She's your boss?
No, just some old lady.
I've been fucking.
(both laughing)
Exactly what I
was imagining, yes.
Yeah.
- I'm really glad
that that's what
went into your mind.
That's good.
Yeah, she's one of several.
That you're fucking?
No. Bosses.
Oh, right.
Well, she sure sounds like it.
That she does.
Anyways, you're
here, where I work.
How can I help you?
You looking for
anything particular?
Something about murder.
Are you serious?
To read. I mean, a
story about murder.
Right? Yeah.
Yeah.
- Not the act.
Not the actual.
- No.
That's yeah.
Yeah. That one.
[Boss] Connor?
I'm getting the... Cat
call from my fuck buddy.
So-
- No, I know.
I'm so sorry. That's my fault.
No, please. Don't
worry about it.
I'd sit here all day and
talk to you if I could.
- I understand.
- Yeah.
Anyways, I'll go
ahead and take you
to the crime section
and you can go ahead
and take it from there.
- Thank you.
- Cool.
I'm sure you'll find what
you're looking for up here.
Mysteries, thrillers,
that kinda thing.
It's kind of our
bread and butter.
What with the name of
our town and everything.
[Marilyn] What's that?
[Connor] Twin Oaks.
It's the name of the cafe
in The Postman
Always Rings Twice.
[Marilyn] Oh.
[Connor] Trust
me. It's a good one.
Here we are.
Alright. Thank you.
No problem.
You looking for
anything in particular?
Not really, something
for the beach.
The beach.
Preferably one where
the husband dies.
Ah, yeah.
One of those, of course.
Yeah, don't wanna ruin
your reading experience,
but just about every other
one ends that way, so...
- Good.
- Yeah.
I'll have my pick then.
Yes, you will.
Um, I should really
get back down.
Oh, yes.
Thank you again.
No problem.
Take care.
It's good to see you again.
You too.
I feel the same.
What's that?
I'd like to talk to you
too all day if I could.
(gentle music)
Okay.
- Hey.
Two by Kane.
Good choice.
- Yes.
Hmm. I got a tip from a friend.
They seem to have good
taste, this friend of yours.
I'd trust him from
now on if I were you.
Hmm.
That one looks pretty good too.
Yeah. You know, not too bad.
Thanks. But we're really not
supposed to take any tips.
Go ahead. Take it.
You sure?
I mean, I don't wanna
take your last dollar.
I insist.
Use it.
Don't spend it.
You understand?
(thoughtful music)
(door chimes clattering)
Oh hey man.
Thank you for coming.
Really.
I'm really sorry.
Oh no, please.
You cool. You good?
Yeah. It's just, you know...
(phone vibrates)
Shit. I'm sorry.
I just had to stay a little
later than I thought.
No, please.
I mean, my time is
your time, right?
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm just saying, you know,
we had a little extra work
Well, I, I kind
of think you are.
I mean you waltz in here
anytime you feel
like it all casual.
I mean kind of makes a
pretty big statement.
Sorry.
What I meant to say is honestly,
I'm late because of my job,
which I'm supposed
to have, so...
(laughs) Um, are you trying
to piss me off right now?
- No.
- I mean is that
what you're doing?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah. Stop.
Ow!
- Kinda seems like you are.
No, no, 'cause if you
want me to sit here all day
with my dick down your throat,
I can definitely do that.
- No, that-
- No, all you gotta do
is say, so.
That is not necessary, sir.
Oh, I, I like that.
The sir thing you just did
there, that's not even required,
but that shows respect.
That's real good.
- Thanks.
- Well, you're very welcome.
But seriously, just let me know
if you need me to come
out here more often,
so you can suck on my cock
to help you recall the
reason that we need
to keep having these
little meet ups.
What do you think?
A fucking asshole.
- Yep.
- Jesus.
Talking like that
in a family place.
Yep. I know.
Hey boys. Hey.
Yeah, you were great in
Deliverance, by the way.
What the fuck's that mean?
- Um, it means show me.
- What?
Show me one family in
here, I'll walk over,
I'll apologize to 'em.
I'll say I am very sorry
for using such bad words.
Come on, show me.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
So why don't you go back to
eating your $3 breakfast.
Stay outta my god
damn business. Okay?
Yeah. Maybe we don't
feel like it, bitch.
Oh, is that right?
Oh boy.
That's really
interesting. Okay.
See if you can guess
what this means.
Whoops.
You know what that means,
what I just did there?
That means I'm a state
appointed law officer.
And I don't like the
way you're looking at me
or listening in on my
conversation over there.
Conversation that I'm
having with a known felon.
Sorry. That's my bad.
So take down my badge number.
You can write up a complaint,
send it off to Providence
if you want to.
But while I'm here in your...
god this is a shitty little
candy corn eating town,
you'll shut the fuck up
and you'll mind your
own god damn business.
Is that clear enough
for you, blubber boy?
Yeah.
Yeah. I get it.
That's great.
How are you there, Dumb Shit?
[Man In Cap]
Yeah. I, I hear ya.
That's great. You guys both
get gold stars for the day.
Pay the bill, meet me outside.
(plate clatters)
Gee, I hope I wasn't too rude
to your cousins in there.
No, that was totally fine.
You have a real natural
charm about yourself.
I think you really
got through to 'em.
Yeah, I felt like we had
a real connection
going at the end there.
Anyway. You okay?
You need anything? You
got any questions for me?
No.
Are you sure?
You're not fucking up are you?
Doing anything stupid, 'cause
you know I'll find out.
I'm sure.
It's the hardest time, first
six months of being free.
But we got your good job, right?
I mean you're not
digging ditches.
Yeah.
I like you Bates. I really do.
But don't you ever
force my hand.
'Cause I will come down on you
like the fucking staff of
Moses right across your skull.
I swear to god I will.
Just so you know.
I understand, Sir.
See, I really,
I really do like that.
Keep that up. We're gonna
do just fine, you and me.
Thank you.
See you next week, yeah?
- Yeah.
I really don't give
a shit about excuses.
So you be on time.
Or you'll be driving
out to see me instead.
And I don't believe
there's anybody
in that whole god damn county
who's very eager to see
your stupid ass face again.
You hear, you hear me?
- I do.
No, no.
Don't touch the car.
- Sorry.
- Later.
Later Jock. Thank you.
(engine cranks)
(phone rings)
Hello?
Hello.
Hey, it's me, Connor.
I did what you asked.
I didn't ask you.
I told you.
Good point.
So yeah.
Hello.
[Connor] Hi there.
Where are you right
now, at work or at home?
Not at work but
not at home either.
Hm don't tell me you're
with her right now.
Your boss.
Oh yeah. Right.
No, I just left her
place a while ago.
She's exhausting.
I can only imagine.
God please don't.
Now what?
I'd like to see you...
again.
Yes, I figured that much.
Yeah. Right.
Okay. (laughs)
Yeah, so that, yeah.
Well I can't right now.
I'm with my daughter.
Oh.
That's, I didn't know
you had a daughter.
[Marilyn] I don't.
[Connor] Okay.
Now I'm confused.
She's my stepdaughter,
but she's here with me.
Got it. Okay.
And so there's no way you can...
None.
We're waiting for
her father to arrive
and I need to be here.
And this is the
guy, who's been...
The bruise.
I can't discuss it right now.
Understood.
Alright.
I would like to
see you again though,
even though I shouldn't.
That would be great.
Really, really great.
Okay, well thank you for
calling and I'll let you know.
Alright. Yeah.
Let me know if you want to
set up a time or whatever.
(phone clicks)
(siren wails)
What are you doing here?
Sitting.
No loitering in the premises.
I'm not.
Sitting is loitering, son.
I was just on a
phone call. That's all.
Then I'm going for a jog.
Is that right?
- Yeah.
- Park closes at 6:00.
I'll be long gone by then.
Says you and I don't
give a shit what you say.
Okay.
Shit.
I know who you are by the way.
Yeah?
You hear what I said?
Yeah.
Don't get smart with me.
I'm not. I said, yeah.
All right then.
And you know who my
fucking nephew is, right?
Yes I do.
So you're a tough guy, huh?
No.
Yeah. You sure you
wanna feel tough?
Why don't you try
getting tough with me?
See what happens.
I'm not a tough guy, sir.
They got you good, didn't they?
Oh yes they did.
Yes. They did.
Six o'clock be gone.
I'll be swinging
back by here soon.
They lock the gates out front.
I know they do.
Yeah, you think you know a lot,
but you don't know
shit, asshole.
(sad music)
(Connor groans)
- Hey Kim.
- Yep.
I can finish up up here
if you want to go do
the poetry section.
Are you sure?
Yeah. It's the other one
they want redone today, so...
Okay.
But that's a lot
smaller than up here.
That doesn't seem fair.
Hey, I'm not always
so magnanimous.
So grab it while you can.
Fine.
I'm just gonna go put these.
Hey, what are you
doing after work?
Um...
Let me guess, going for a run.
Probably.
Yep.
Geez.
You really love it. Don't you?
I guess so.
It's kind of a
habit at this point.
You sure you're not out there
training for the next Olympics?
Yeah.
I gave up on that idea in
about the eighth grade.
I just do it for fun now.
I run too.
- Do you?
- Yeah.
Well I, I jog anyway.
Oh, that's um, cool.
Yeah.
We should go together sometime.
Yeah. That'd be,
um, it'd be cool.
Yeah. Only if you want to.
I know it's nice to
run alone sometimes,
but I would be up for it.
Yeah, no, no, no, no.
Yeah. Let's.
Cool.
(romantic music)
Oh, that's uh, what's her name?
[Connor] Who?
Astrid, I think or
something like that.
She's in the Pilates class I
take and she's kind of a bitch.
She's pretty and all that,
but she's not very nice.
Not to me anyway.
That's 'cause you're pretty.
Thanks.
Yeah, you know, I mean
that's like what happens
when two pretty girls meet.
You know, it's like two
tigers in the wild there.
Like animals chasing after.
Not that I think you're a...
An animal.
I'm done.
You go ahead and
take care of poetry
and I'll take care
of those ladies.
That sounds good.
And thank you for
the compliment.
I think.
Yeah.
Hi.
[Connor] Hi.
I'm looking for a
book about Chanel.
Do you have anything
like that here?
Do you mean the company
or the woman herself?
Um...
Maybe a little bit of
both, like a biography?
Yeah.
I'm doing a paper on
her. It's for school.
Yeah.
We should have something for you
in the fashion
section downstairs.
Would you like me to show you?
Great.
Um, could you actually
go for me please?
I just wanna send some emails.
[Marilyn] Shouldn't
you be doing the work
since it's for your class?
Please?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Hey, we need to hurry.
Alright?
We're meeting your father in
an hour at the club for dinner.
Gross.
I thought you
liked eating there.
Yeah, I wasn't
talking about the club.
Hello again.
Hi there.
I sure am glad we're the
only library in town.
(laughs) Me too.
Your eye looks much better.
[Marilyn] You wanna show me
where I could find the book?
Happy to.
Come on down.
Hey Kim, I'm gonna show
this lady the downstairs.
Would you keep an eye
on the front for me?
Sure. No problem.
Great.
So this is the lower level.
Got our plays, entertainment
stuff, all that crap.
There's some good
stuff too though.
Rare books are over there.
Mm.
I love the smell of old books.
Ah, so do I.
Believe it or not a
million years ago
I was an English
major, but yeah.
Anyways, I'm gonna go
take a look for your book.
(romantic music)
Here you go.
Thank you.
No problem.
It's my job.
I didn't mean for the book.
(music intensifies)
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
(Connor sighs)
(table squeaks)
I hope to see you again.
Oh my god, me too.
[Woman] Marilyn.
I'm coming.
[Kim] So how was your day off?
- Yeah, pretty good.
- Hmm.
[Connor] You know,
caught up on some laundry,
read some Vonnegut
ran, you know.
[Kim] Wait, you ran?
Shocking.
- Yeah, stop.
[Kim] Oh hey, guess who
I saw yesterday after work?
- Who?
- Jared Clifton.
[Connor] Really?
Yeah. I haven't heard that
name in a long, long time.
Oh I know.
And you will never believe
who he's going out with.
Who?
Girl from my
Pilates class, Astrid.
You know the one you
helped her and her mom
find the book, they're together.
Jared and Astrid.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- I know.
That's what I've been hearing.
And people have seen them
around together for a while.
And then I saw him pick her
up yesterday after class
in a really nice car.
Wasn't his, I'm sure of it.
She's been living
here for a while.
Apparently her
dad is really rich
and he had a bunch
of houses everywhere.
La-di-da, but yeah.
That's who she's
dating: Jared Clifton.
(scoffs) Can you even imagine?
I mean he's older than us.
Shit.
Yep.
That's...
- What?
- Nothing.
I mean, who am I
to judge? Right?
Oh please.
Seriously.
You're nothing like him.
Connor.
Okay. You did something and
you got punished for it.
You're not a complete low life,
piece of shit,
dick face like him.
I mean it, there's a difference.
Well, I'm glad you
don't have an opinion
about the subject.
But he is though.
And you know that.
Do I? Mm hmm.
Connor?
(suspenseful music)
[Marilyn] I was wondering
if you'd come or not.
Are you joking?
You called. So I came.
You do like older
women, don't you?
I can't think about another
person since I met you.
Yeah?
Not even the pretty
girl you work with?
Kim?
That's... No way.
You sure?
She sure looked
interested in you.
I'm sure.
Not about her liking me.
I mean about me liking you.
Good.
I was jealous.
Seriously? That's insane.
It's nothing of the kind.
Trust me.
If you only knew my thoughts.
I want you to
whisper them to me.
(romantic music)
(both moaning)
(Connor moans)
I never want this to end.
Me neither.
Too bad it's impossible.
Is it?
Hmm. You know that.
You know that.
No, I don't.
I don't know anything about you.
So how could I
possibly know that?
I'm the same with you.
But I love the way you
look, the way you are.
Thanks.
That's...
What?
Just...
Words I haven't heard
in a long, long time.
Well, I would tell
them to you every day,
if you were mine.
Well I like the sound of that.
Of what?
Being yours.
If only.
Because of your husband?
Is that really it?
'Cause of that and so much more.
It's not just about me.
Astrid.
I'd be afraid for her.
I don't understand.
The times that he's hit me,
the bruises you've seen,
most of them I got
trying to protect her.
(ominous tones)
Oh my god.
Fuck that.
Turn him in.
I mean do it today. I'm serious.
It's not that simple.
Yes it is.
It is that simple.
Call the police when
you've done something wrong
and trust me, things
happen really fast.
I would know.
What do you mean you would know?
This isn't about
me right now, so.
I don't care.
You say something
like this, tell me.
I don't want to let us go.
Oh, you won't.
Just tell me the truth.
Couple years ago,
almost four now,
I was going to college upstate
and I got invited to
this family gathering,
4th of July celebration.
Yeah, so this is my great
uncle who invited me, you know,
he lived up by where
I went to school.
Even though I don't really
know these relatives,
I figure worst case
I get some free food,
some booze, you know,
fireworks, all that.
So. Yeah.
I'm up for it. I go.
And then, this one guy shows up.
Friend of a friend.
Kevin Edmunds.
Kevin starts picking
on this girl.
Friend of one of the kids there.
And went up to him
and I said, "Stop it."
You know, stop.
And he laughed and
he said, "Make me."
Just like that.
And that was it.
I just...
I pushed him.
Kevin fell back and hit
his head on the corner
of a concrete drinking
fountain on the golf course.
He never got up.
He didn't die or anything
like that, you know.
He's had very serious
mental, physical.
They threw me in
jail for three years,
three years for
pushing somebody.
And, you know, obviously
by then I had
dropped outta school.
So I moved back in with my mom,
started living in her basement.
I got a job at the library
because that's just about
the only place
that would hire me.
Yeah. (laughs)
Cue the fucking violins.
No.
(romantic music)
Well, you failed.
How's that?
You failed to scare me away.
So when can I see you again?
Can I see you again?
I hope so.
I don't take anything
for granted anymore.
So, I hope so too.
I understand.
So?
I'll call you, soon, I promise.
That's all I can say right now.
Well, I guess that's something.
Oh shit.
You all right?
Yeah. No.
It's just, my keys.
My dad gave me this
little key chain
when I graduated high school.
It's an Indian head nickel.
Anyways, the tip
of it is broken.
So the keys always slip off.
And I think they
did when we were...
I'm sorry.
Yeah, it's okay.
I mean, I, I would try
and help you find it.
I just gotta.
- Yeah no.
Don't worry about, I got it.
[Woman On TV] Don't be absurd.
Billy's not a criminal.
He's the best friend
we have on this boat.
[Man] We're not in
need of such friends.
You need any
friends you can get.
The only thing
standing between you
and a watery grave is your wits.
That's not my idea of
adequate protection.
Purser, how much longer
before this ship reaches port?
[Man] If we ever do get to port
it should be within
14 or 15 hours.
[Man] That's a long time.
Sit down, make
yourself comfortable.
Have a drink.
Enjoy the Major's piano recital.
Come on, Peterson.
Buy us a drink.
[Peterson] I'm afraid I
can't accept hospitality
from persons who I intend
in a few hours' time,
to denounce.
(pensive music)
(phone vibrates)
Hello?
Hi.
How are you?
(rain pattering)
- Hi.
Hi.
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Of course it's something.
You're upset.
Oh no, it's nothing.
My husband called me
on the way over here,
caught me off guard and
started yelling at me.
And we started to arguing about
nothing like we always do.
I fucking hate this guy.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I'm so happy you're here.
Me too.
(romantic music)
We should go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
(Marilyn moaning)
(both moaning)
Hmm.
At least this can be ours.
Yeah. How's that?
My husband rarely
comes here these days.
Once he owns something,
cars, women, houses,
he tends to lose interest.
He leaves this to me
as my little getaway.
You don't like it?
I don't like this.
I think about us, you,
your body, inside of me
every second of the day.
And I think how's
this even possible.
How can I want him so much?
I feel the same.
And yet...
Exactly.
Maybe he'll leave me.
And until then, he'll
just keep hitting people,
abusing them?
Maybe he'll die.
Doubt it.
Everyone in that man's
family lives past 90.
Trust me, I checked.
People die all the time.
That's true.
Car accidents,
falling down the stairs.
All kinds of shit.
I'm just saying it happens.
Do you think it's fate
that we met, you and I?
I do.
I really do think so.
I do too.
I've been waiting for
this my whole life.
My god, you have
such a beautiful face.
I'm glad you like it.
(gentle music)
I don't mean to rush you.
Yeah, I get it.
- We got everything?
- Yeah.
I really gotta get
that thing fixed.
You sure you had
it when we got here?
I think so, but then again,
I did take off all my clothes
and go in the shower with you.
So, I don't really know.
It's probably at my house,
I think so.
And if it's here,
you'll just let me know.
Okay. Thank you for
your understanding.
Didn't say I understood.
See you soon?
Maybe.
Why does that
sound like goodbye?
What?
Tell me.
Because it could be, Connor.
Are you joking?
Marilyn?
That's crazy. I mean,
after what we just did,
that's not normal.
- But that's just it.
It was incredible
and you're incredible.
But people don't
just die or go away.
So I can't promise.
Marilyn. No!
No, that just, it like,
it can't, I don't,
I don't understand,
like please, Marilyn.
Fuck! No.
- I hope
this is not the end for us.
I really do.
But it could be.
(ship's horn blasts)
You should go.
While you were
inside getting lunch,
my buddy, Walt, he's the best
guy, he sent me this meme.
Look at it. It's hilarious.
Yeah. It's pretty funny.
Hi there.
[Connor] Hello again.
Hi.
So how did your paper go?
Oh, it was fine.
I gotta B+.
So that was pretty okay.
Good.
Well, glad we had
something useful for you.
Hey, Kim.
Hi.
Connor, I think we
should probably go.
Yeah. Probably.
Actually, I'm sorry,
I did have a question
for you, book question.
Okay.
I mean I can go and...
No, no, that's totally fine.
It's totally fine.
- Oh.
Um yeah.
You know, why don't
you cover for me now
and I'll take the
second shift and yeah,
I'll figure it out
the rest of my break.
So would that be okay?
- Oh.
Sure.
- Great.
- Sounds good.
Have a nice day.
- You too.
- Bye Kim.
[Connor] Thanks Kim.
- What's up man?
- Nothing.
What's up with you?
Doing pretty good.
Don't you think?
Hanging out with these
beautiful ladies.
So life doesn't completely suck.
Wait, do you guys
know each other?
Oh yeah.
Everybody from Twin Oaks
knows Connor. (laughs)
Well, you're pretty famous
around here yourself, Jared.
Ah, not like you.
This guy made a real
name for himself.
Huh? Interesting.
Not really.
Anyways, you had a
question about a book.
That's the guy I told you about.
Yes, the one that
you recommended,
about the two lovers.
Both of the books
that you borrowed
have two lovers in them.
Yeah, well the one that
you said was so good,
The Postman Always Rings Twice.
Okay.
I haven't had a
chance to read it.
I was just wondering,
do they get away with it?
Do you mean at the
end or the crime itself?
The crime.
Yeah they do.
Oh.
So it's a happy ending then?
Not necessarily.
But the husband, he...
Yeah, he dies.
(phone vibrates)
Hello?
That was torture today.
Yeah. I agree.
Did you ever find your keys?
No, it's not my keys.
It's the little part that
connects to the end, but no,
it'll turn up, it always does.
Mm. I hope so.
You said it was a keepsake.
(ship's horn blasts)
Are you, are you okay?
Has something else happened?
That means yes.
Fucking piece of shit.
It could have been
a happy ending.
I'm sorry. You mean us?
What you asked me
about today in the book?
Would a turned out just fine
if they stuck together,
but they didn't.
They turned on each other
and fucked everything up.
Everything would've been fine
if they just saw it through.
What are you saying to me?
You know what I'm saying to you.
Tell me, say it.
That...
if we do this,
then it's forever.
And I mean for all times,
does that make sense?
Yes.
And?
I agree.
It's forever.
Okay.
Alright, good.
I'd do anything to be with you.
So will I.
I'll be at the cottage tomorrow.
(phone clicks)
I'm taking Astrid to Boston
next week for two days,
shopping trip he
promised us months ago.
[Connor] Interesting.
Well, if he keeps his word,
which is not always
his strong suit.
That happens often?
More often than I'd like.
Which means a lot.
If this does happen,
where will he be?
At the house.
Which one?
(scoffs) True.
Out on the point.
Any alarms?
Nuh uh, no alarms.
He doesn't believe in them.
He sleeps with a gun under
his pillow, wherever he goes.
Makes him feel like a big man.
Got it.
Is this really happening?
Unless you told me to stop
it this instant, then yes,
it's going to happen.
Tell me it isn't for the money.
His money.
If it is, even partially for it,
lie to me and tell me it isn't.
Of course it isn't.
You don't even have
to think about it?
- No!
- Not even for a second?
It seems like he's
got a lot of it.
He does millions and
millions, but not for me.
I, I don't understand.
Well, I mean, some
of it will come to me
as a monthly stipend,
but you know,
the bulk of his
estate goes to Astrid.
I'm just the executor
until she turns 25 and,
then it's all hers.
Did I say something wrong?
Are you having second thoughts?
About you? Never.
I'm doing this for us
and I'm not gonna
think twice about it.
(ominous tones)
I don't want to know
anymore about him ever.
Never again.
What I know is the way
he treats you and her.
And that's enough for me.
Yes. It's gonna happen
while you're in Boston.
And when it does, we'll be free.
(romantic music)
(rain pattering)
I should go.
I don't want you to.
Soon I won't have to.
We shouldn't talk for a while.
I don't know for how long, but
until we both know it's safe.
I understand.
If anybody ever asks you,
any phone call we ever
had is about work.
I gave you my numbers so that
you could ask me about authors
or I could provide
you with information.
Yes, I'll do that.
Good.
There's a sun room of
the side of the house,
the door doesn't lock.
We're supposed to
leave on Tuesday.
Then have a nice trip.
There's one more thing
I need you to do.
I need you to go
to a drug store.
And I need you to buy one
of those burner phones.
If anything happens while
I'm gone, you can text me.
That way I'll know
you're in trouble
or you need something.
When you use it,
text me one word,
text me the word
books and I'll know.
And I'll get to you
somehow, I promise you.
But do not call me, text me.
And I will meet you
at the parking lot
of the woods where we met, okay?
[Marilyn] Okay.
You do that and I promise you,
I will get to you no
matter what it takes, okay?
At least we'll be together.
Do you understand?
Nothing's gonna happen, alright?
Don't say it.
You'll jinx it.
Will you promise
we'll be together?
I promise.
(unsettling music)
Hello there.
What's up?
That'd be my next question.
Isn't that weird.
Where you been all day?
Good to see you too, Deputy.
You don't wanna
get smart right now.
Smart asses get
read their rights
while I hold their
stupid fucking faces down
against the hood of my car.
Do you see the way
this guy talks to me?
Just answer the question.
I was out. It's my day off.
Out? Where?
Running.
Running? All day long?
Yeah. And whatever.
What is this?
Eh, maybe something,
maybe nothing.
We've had a series of
break-ins the last few weeks.
Last night we had three.
And you're asking me because?
Because you're a
convict and you live here.
We're talking to anybody
with a record, so...
I see.
[Deputy] I bet you do.
Take it easy, please.
He's got no priors when
it comes to stealing
or breaking and entering.
He's been to prison.
Yeah. So has Martha Stewart.
You check on her
whereabouts yet?
You piece of shit!
Come on. Relax.
Okay. You got nothing, right?
Because you have an
alibi for last night.
Don't you?
Yeah.
What is it?
Dinner, with my mom,
until late.
What is going on?
How late?
One or two.
We watched some movie on TCM.
The Lady From Shanghai.
Where is she?
In Shanghai I presume.
Fuck you. Your mom.
Oh, my mother.
At work, at the hospital.
Call her.
Why didn't you
answer my calls today?
When?
Oh, check your phone.
Check your phone.
Six.
It's off.
Oh, keep that
shit on from now on.
Do you hear me?
I don't like driving here
anymore than I have to.
Whether it's bullshit or not.
God, I keep giving you chances.
You keep dicking 'em up.
I'm sorry.
Okay. We should go.
Can we go?
I'll see you soon for
breakfast. Don't be late.
(engine cranks)
Anyway, blah, blah, blah.
Enough about me.
No, I'm interested.
(laughs) No, you're not.
I wish you were, but you're not.
You keep looking around,
checking your phone.
It's like your
mind's not even here.
That's not true.
Isn't it though?
I mean, yeah.
I'm a little distracted,
but I'm interested.
But not actually like I am.
What do you mean, Kim?
Like I am in you.
Oh.
Right. Oh.
Anyway. Change of subject.
Why tonight?
I've asked you out
a couple of times,
well, not out out,
but for a run.
Whatever.
Why now?
Why dinner?
No reason.
Just, and we don't have
to do that, by the way.
You know, change the subject.
I just, I didn't know that
you felt that way about me.
You know, I thought we were
just friends or something.
We are, but Connor, come on.
You know what I'm talking
about, I know you do.
Kim.
Look, I love being
friends with you.
I need friends.
Seriously.
I think you're amazing, but-
- No.
- I just.
I get it.
Yeah.
Would you excuse
me for one minute?
(suspenseful music)
(floor creaks)
(stair creaks)
[Intruder] Whoa.
Oh my god.
Dammit.
(door closes)
(laughs) You look
such a little...
No, I couldn't sleep.
So I walked down to the marina.
(sighs) Okay, yes.
The bar down by the marina.
What?
No, I keep ours on the Cape.
Come on. You know that.
No, I just...
Yes. A couple of drinks.
And now I'm back.
So tell Daddy goodnight
and go to sleep.
Yes.
I said yes.
It's true.
I'll see you soon.
Yes. (laughs)
Good night.
(floor creaks)
(tense music)
(men grunting)
(gun clicks)
(Connor grunts)
You are dead, mother fucker.
(gun clicks)
So I hope to God
that it was worth it.
(thudding)
(husband grunts)
(suspenseful music)
[Connor] Sit the fuck down.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Sit the fuck down.
Wait, wait, dude, it's me.
It's me, it's me, it's Jared.
Jared!
What the fuck are
you doing here?
Same thing as you, man.
What do you think?
Tell me.
Dude, I'm fucking breaking
in and stealing shit.
Bro, don't point
that thing at me.
Who told you to do that?
Your little fucking girlfriend?
No, no dude.
I mean, she hates her old man
and she showed me all
the shit that he owns.
But dude, I've been doing this
all over the fucking town.
I can't help it. It's what I do.
That's not what I
fucking asked you.
That is not what I asked you.
Okay, I was, I
was, I was up here
and I heard someone come
in, so I fucking hid.
And then I heard
you two fighting.
So I came in here and he was...
Bro, he was about to
shoot, I saved you.
Can you not point that
thing at me please?
(gunfire pops)
(Connor pants)
Fuck.
Oh fuck.
Okay, okay.
Take this shit.
Where the fuck is my mask?
I'm okay.
Okay.
Oh fuck.
Where's my fucking mask.
Shit.
Where the fuck?
Oh fuck.
Shit.
(glass shatters)
Fuck!
(door slams)
(unsettling music)
Yes, the roadblocks are up.
We're watching
the railroad station
and he isn't hiding
in the woods.
(phone vibrates)
[Marilyn] Hello?
Connor?
Connor. You there?
(ominous tones)
What did I say about calling me?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to
apologize, but what did I say?
Not to.
That's right.
And now you did.
I'm on the phone
that you made me get.
It's not what I said.
I said, don't call me
on this phone period.
And now you did.
You know why I said that.
Because it's dangerous.
More than that because
it's the type of thing
that you can get you caught.
Well, you've done it now anyway.
So go ahead.
He's dead by the way, if
that's what you're wondering.
Is it?
- No.
- Really?
I, I just wanted to,
I needed to know
that you're okay,
that you're alive.
Okay.
Well, why wouldn't I be?
I don't know.
I just, you're just really
horrible to me right now.
Maybe that's because
I just killed somebody
four hours ago.
Maybe that's why, I don't know.
He'll be found soon if
he hasn't been already.
Nobody's contacted you yet?
No.
All right.
Then there's still time.
Before what?
Before the world comes
busting down on our heads
at 10,000 miles
per hour, Marilyn.
Why was he there?
Because I told you
that he'd be there.
It's his house.
Not talking about your husband.
I'm sorry. I, I don't
follow what you're saying.
I was there and he wasn't.
Then he saw me.
We ran upstairs, we
struggled for the gun.
He won it.
He was gonna shoot me dead.
But he didn't.
Do you know why, Marilyn?
No.
Because someone else was there.
Jared Clifton, your
stepdaughter's boyfriend.
Are you joking?
Why would I joke about
something like that?
Well, I don't know.
He said he was just breaking
in and stealing some shit,
that it was all
just a coincidence,
But that's a pretty huge
fucking coincidence,
don't you think?
So tell me it was just that.
Coincidence. Nothing more.
It was, Connor.
Are you actually saying
that I could possibly...
I don't know,
but her boyfriend
and your boyfriend
both broke into the same
house on the same night
and one of us
killed your husband,
which is awfully
fucking convenient.
I really don't like
what you're saying.
Well all I know is that
Jared Clifton was there
and he saved my life.
And then I shot him.
What?
Yeah. Why not?
It's the perfect alibi.
I mean, your husband's gone.
The answer to our problems
was just sitting
there on his knees.
So I did it and I made it look
like they killed each other.
That was my night.
How was yours?
Shopping was good?
I don't know what to
say to you right now.
Tell me that you need me.
Tell me that it was worth it.
It was.
Okay. Fine.
Then go back to bed and
do not call me again.
Text me if you really
need something,
be ready to lie your ass
off for the next two months.
I love you.
You promise?
I promise.
(somber music)
(door opens)
Ah, see now this is more
like it, you waiting for me.
Yes, Sir.
Boy. Yes, Sir on top of it.
This is my fucking lucky day.
Yours too from the sound of it.
How's that?
Oh, come on.
You must a heard.
Heard?
The little fuck who murdered
the rich guy over on,
out on the water
there, Jared Clifton,
whatever his name is.
Whole firestorm was bad.
Went down out there last
night, shooting and stabbing,
all kinds of shit.
Guy took a fire poker
to the back of the head
and still managed
to kill the perp.
How the hell does
that work? Huh?
Anyway, solves the break-ins
they've been having around here,
which is why I said it was,
well that's pretty good for you.
Yeah, I see.
Yeah, yeah, no.
I heard something
about it at work.
Terrible.
Crime doesn't pay. Right?
That's what they say.
They're right too.
You already know that
though, don't you Bates?
- Sure do.
- Yeah.
What's with your neck?
What'd you do, cut
yourself shaving?
- Oh this?
- Yeah.
Yeah, no, I, you know.
What's that?
You know? I was,
I was, you know, tree.
Oh, you're still running.
- Yeah.
- Right.
You still getting
to work on time?
Still driving that
piece of shit car?
Yep.
Doing it all. Living the life.
Mm hmm.
Hey, is there anything
you wanna tell me?
- No.
- Hey, are you sure?
'Cause I'm here, I'm listening.
Listen, I'm, I'm
really pulling for you.
No, I'm, I'm good.
Really.
- You're you're good?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Let's eat. Huh?
Guess who's buying?
You.
Miss.
(suspenseful music)
(Connor shudders)
(romantic music)
(siren wails)
[Man on TV] No one
could possibly
getaway with an act like that.
They'd be wise to
me in a minute.
Don't be yellow.
You look enough like him,
the same coloring
and the same build.
See how his clothes fit you.
No kidding. You almost
had me fooled for a while.
[Man On TV] Oh, grow up girl.
Don't you think a
father knows his own son
and there must be
other relatives.
[Woman On TV] The father
won't have to know you.
We'll wait 'til he
gives up the ghost.
He's an old geezer and
he won't pull through.
(tense music)
(music overpowers voices)
Whoa, where you going, son.
For a run.
This early, with a bag?
Yeah. I got work after.
What's, um?
Look, I'm not supposed
to be here. Okay?
They agreed to let me talk
to you for a minute or two.
So please just don't
do anything stupid.
Okay?
- Okay.
Okay. Hey please.
I'm asking you nicely now.
Yeah, no I'm, I'm listening.
I'm listening to you.
Alright, they got
you solid on this.
Okay, there's no reason
to make it any worse
than already is.
They know, eh don't,
they know somebody
else was there.
They got blood
under a fingernail.
Not from one of the victims
it's blood that matches yours.
Okay? A lot of
valuables missing.
Stuff not on the body
of the dead perp.
So hey, they know that you
two were working together.
Okay?
Whoa.
I have no idea what
you're talking about, man.
That's crazy.
- Bates, please.
Okay.
Look, I don't know what
you're talking about,
but yeah, I'll come with-
(bag thuds)
(tense music)
God dammit.
Bates!
(siren wails)
(no dialogue)
(tires squealing)
(sirens wail)
(Connor winces)
(Connor sobs)
Bates, these
people will kill you.
They are itching to do it.
I am begging you now.
- Oh no.
Get down on the ground
and stop this shit.
Now god dammit, do it son.
Just listen to me. Alright?
Just listen.
What have you done?
Well I don't. I don't.
What do you mean?
How did you know that
I was gonna come here?
If you didn't...
How could you possibly know?
How?
- We got a tip, okay?
Anonymous caller.
Some lady.
Don't lie to me.
I don't understand
what you're saying.
She told us right
where you'd be.
I, I don't believe you.
Get down on the
fucking ground now.
Gimme a second.
Please. One second.
Very fidgety. Okay?
Just do what they say, please.
Nothing you're gonna regret.
I can't.
Alright, listen to me.
They have your
key ring. Alright?
Or a piece of it.
The little Indian coin.
They have it.
My, my key chain?
Must have dropped
it at the scene
or it broke or something.
I don't know.
They have it.
They found it in the house.
Oh no, no, no, no.
- Bates.
- That's not,
that's, that's,
that's not possible.
No. I'm telling
you that they do.
That's...
They have it.
Let's not make this
any worse than it is.
Hey, just get down.
Get down.
Okay.
Bates.
Get down.
(phone vibrates)
(tense music)
No, just get down.
Don't answer that.
[Connor] I have to.
Hey!
Bates, no!
(gunfire pops)
No! Bates!
Bates, don't!
(gunfire pops)
Bates!
Put your gun down.
(birds squawking)
Bates? Bates?
(police radio garbling)
He's gone.
(water crashing)
Hello.
Hi.
How was the water?
It's colder than you think.
Did you steal this?
I didn't return it.
It's different.
Ah, what happens at the end?
I don't know.
I didn't finish it.
(romantic music)
That's what I've
always wanted for us.
The minute we met.
You and me together.
Me too.
It's like a dream.
Now it's real.
No one will ever come
between us ever again.
I love you.
I love you too.
You promise?
I promise.
(dramatic music)