♪ [Multicom Entertainment
Group jingle] ♪
♪ [music]
Igor...
property is theft.
[pleading in Russian
to spare his life]
[In Russian] Do it.
[In Russian]
- But he's dead.
- Do it!!
♪ [choral music]
[shouting in Russian]
[gunfire and screaming]
Dad?
What?
You awake?
I've been awake since 1974.
Where's the bug spray?
I think the bugs
finished it last night.
Maybe we should try
and start a fire.
Ow.
"We" meaning me, I guess.
You're the camping expert, dad.
Nobody likes a wise guy John.
[Jack] Don't look at me like
that. We're here for the
weekend, if it kills us both.
[cell phone ringing]
Good morning.
Where?
I'm on a camping trip
with my kid, alright?
Dad, if it's important, we
can go camping anytime...
like in my next life
I heard that.
No, not you.
All right...
I said, all right.
I'll be there when I
get there, okay?
[hangs up, clears throat]
A multiple homicide.
I gotta cover it.
Gee, that's too bad.
I'll start packing.
You could at least pretend
to be disappointed, John.
Can we stop at McDonald's
on the way back?
Get out of here...
[Charles]
Well, well, well, if it ain't
Davy Crockett himself.
You don't look so good, Jack.
You guys can't clear up
one little triple homicide
without calling me, huh?
[Charles]
Oh, come on Reed,
we saved your life.
You know what I mean?
One more night out there
you'd be dead of exposure.
All right, what have we got?
[Eddie]
Labor violence I guess.
Gravediggers on strike.
Shooting starts right in
the middle of a funeral.
Well, good, that means we've
got plenty of witnesses.
Nope. Nobody knows nothing.
Well, they're all recent
immigrants, Russian mostly.
They're afraid of us,
or the shooters, maybe.
Or both.
[cell phone rings while
woman cries in background]
Yeah.
[Charles]
Who?
Oh my God, when?
All right, I'll be there
in 15 minutes. No...
keep him in my office.
Gotta get back.
What's up?
Nothing good. Call me later.
All right, so the
scabs dig a hole...
and they get shot for
it. Is that the deal?
[Eddie]
Mmm, no.
The graves were dug yesterday.
No scabs around today.
Well who got shot?
[Eddie]
Bechenko, the Manager.
Now, all that bloods
from the first wound.
The other wounds are
post-mortem. No blood
pressure at all.
[Jack]
What about the other bodies?
[Eddie]
Same deal. Three shots each.
First was the kill
shot, both times.
Seems pretty deliberate for a
picket-line brawl, doesn't it?
I'll tell you what.
Why don't you go...
talk to that priest over there
see what he's got to say, huh?
[dramatic music plays]
[mumbling in Russian]
Shut up, fool.
What are you praying
to, the engine?
I'm sorry, Igor. It looks like
their funeral has interrupted
your funeral.
It'll have to be the river.
Like to take a swim, Igor?
It's a nice swim.
It'll do you good.
[Sheehan]
One of those days, Lieutenant.
What did he do?
Ran a light. Hit a Mexican
family on their way to church.
Mom was in the passenger
seat; she's dead.
The others are banged
up, but they're okay.
Junior, here, didn't
get a scratch
but he totaled daddy's Beemer.
What did he test?
Off the charts.
.22.
It's all in there. [sighs]
I better call his father.
I talked to him.
He's on his way.
I almost felt sorry for
the son-of-a-bitch.
- Oh, c'mon, Billy. C'mon--
- Don't mind me, Lieutenant.
I hate all politicians,
regardless of color.
Which reminds me
Peter Myers called.
He's on his way too.
What about the TV people?
Not yet. But they'll get
wind of it pretty quick.
He get his rights?
He signed the card.
[Gordon Jr.]
Hi, Mr. Silvera. Did
you talk to my dad?
It's Lieutenant Silvera
around here.
Go get a cup of coffee.
You really did it
this time, Gordon.
It was an accident, Mr.--
er, Lieutenant. I swear to God.
I mean, I was just coming
home from a party.
At 8 o'clock in the morning?
Yeah. I mean, yes sir. And I
was trying to make this light--
Your father know
you have the car?
Oh, yes, sir. Absolutely.
I mean, I don't do that anymore,
Lieutenant, I swear--
How much--how much did
you drink last night?
- A couple beers.
- Oh, don't give me that crap.
Your sobriety test
is through the roof.
Actually, it's this cough
medicine I've been taking,
Lieutenant., because I--
- Where is it?
- What?
Where's the cough medicine?
I don't know. I guess
I left in the car.
Well should still be there.
They're searching the car now.
I--I might have finished it.
Save it for your lawyer, Gordon.
- [father] You all right, son?
- [son] I'm okay, Dad.
I'm really sorry about this.
Charles, do you
know Sandy Miller?
Are these handcuffs necessary?
Well, routine for anyone being
held pending felony charges.
Felony? It was an
accident, wasn't it?
[Charles]
A fatal accident. He was
driving while impaired.
He tested at twice
the legal limit.
Those tests are
notoriously unreliable.
They're administered by idiots.
Well, save it for the Judge,
Miller. It's hard evidence
and you know it.
Do we bother with the
trial, Lieutenant
or do you just throw him
into prison right now?
Counselor
if you or anyone else, thinks he
can walk in here and start
pushing me around--!
[Gordon Sr.]
Gentlemen.
Let's calm down.
[Gordon Sr.]
"Anyone else." I
assume that means me.
Sit down.
Charles, we go way back.
I know we don't agree on very
much these days but I have
helped you over the years.
Gordon, don't you come
in my office with that.
I'm not asking for favors.
I'm worried about my son.
Now surely you realize that
there are people out there
who are going to try to
use this against me.
Out there?
Gordon, I came as
soon as I heard.
Thank you.
Are you all right, son?
What is this? Is this necessary?
[Gordon Sr.]
Apparently it is.
Well, not for long. I
have a mittimus here.
Detective Hobart of Central
Division is taking over this
investigation.
Gordon is in our custody
as of right now.
If we leave right away,
we can beat the TV crews.
He's not going anywhere.
He's gonna be book and printed.
He'll be sent over for
arraignment this afternoon
and he'll probably get bail.
Now you can try this mittimus
crap with the Judge, Pete.
And maybe Bozo here
will get the case.
Until that happens
Gordon will be treated just like
every other accused felon
whether his father is
running for mayor or not.
You understand what
I'm saying, Gordon?
He's right. We have to play
this by the numbers, for now.
Whatever we do, we've
got to get out of here.
The press'll be here any minute.
Take care of him, Charles.
Yeah, he'll be fine.
Dad, you mean I gotta stay here?
I'm sorry, son. We'll get
you out as soon as we can.
[Gordon Sr.]
I'll talk to you later, okay?
I don't understand this
attitude, Charles.
Her name was Isabella Rodriguez.
She was 38 years old. She was a
mother of two little kids.
Junior, here, is criminally
responsible for her death.
What don't you
understand about that?
You scared?
Good.
You should be.
[Thunder erupts]
Come on.
It' time for Igor's bath.
Hey.
This is a nice neighborhood.
Yeah. It's a Russian priest from
the cemetery...it's his church.
All hells breaking loose inside.
Why? What's going on?
I don't know. I'm getting maybe
one word out of twelve.
But it's got nothing to
do with labor trouble.
Let's take a look.
[tense dialog in Russian]
I am brother Yurii.
May I help you?
Yeah, my name's Jack Reed. I'm
with the Sheriff's department.
Dirksen, Chicago P. D.
What's going on?
Her name is Irina Lebed.
Her husband was one of
the men killed at the
cemetery this morning.
She says...
People are murdered
in broad daylight.
The police laugh and
shake their heads.
Nothing is done.
Is this what America is about?
Professor Suvorov, a great man.
[Brother Yurii]
His son is gone.
Vanished.
The police do not care.
They smile only; that's it.
And people are robbed.
They... they are beaten.
They... they disappear.
And no one cares.
[Brother Yurii]
And this morning, three are dead
shot to pieces by the
madman, the Butcher.
This is worse than
Russia. This is...
[speaks in Russian]
What?
Little Wolves
What are you doing here?
This is a Holy place.
Do you think you
can frighten me?
can frighten God?!
No! No.
Get out.
Go! Get out!
[Eddie]
Hey!
[Irina]
Policemen, now you come.
For what? A piece of plaster?!
What about us?! What
about the living?!
Who's the Mad Man?
[Jack]
My name is Jack Reed, ma'am.
I'm a policeman too.
Uh, you said that, uh, people
were killed by the Mad Man
by the Butcher. Who
are you talking about?
Who... who are the
Little Wolves?
Come on, lady, talk to me.
I'll try to help you.
No. No.
I don't believe you.
Wait. Hey, wait a minute, lady.
Hey.
What's going on, Jack?
Ahhh, no. No!
Not my new Crown Vic'!
[Eddie]
Let's roust 'em, Jack.
[Jack]
You think they'll
confess, Eddie?
'Cause there sure as hell ain't
gonna be any witnesses.
[Eddie]
I mean, what the hell's going on
here? Where are the cops?
Are we in America or what?
[TV Reporter]
Mr. Thomas, Junior
was charged with
vehicular homicide and
driving while impaired.
Sanford Miller, advisor
to mayoral candidate
Gordon Thomas Senior
suggests there might be a
political motive behind the
arraignment.
[Shouting Reporters]
Mr. Thomas?
Mr. Thomas, any comment?
Any comment at all, sir?
We demand...
this investigation of
this tragic accident
be taken from the
Sheriff's Department
and conducted by the office
of the District Attorney.
That is my statement.
Sandy Miller was always
a cop-hating creep.
What have we got?
Open and shut.
Rodriguez family pulls
up to the stop light.
The light changes, they move
into the intersection, slowly;
it's an old rust-bucket. Bam.
Thomas never touched his brakes.
He's doing 70 or 80
in a 35 mile zone.
He's speeding, he runs a red
light, and he's impaired.
There it is.
What about the cough medicine?
I didn't find any bottle.
And his blood doesn't
indicate any medication.
Like you said, open and shut.
Well, so what. It is a
no-win deal, Lieutenant.
Let Central have it.
Hey, wait a minute, man--
Now c'mon, man, the kid's
gonna walk one way or the other.
And Thomas is gonna be
around for years, whether
he's Mayor or not.
You wanna lay down in
front of that train?
I don't.
All right, finish your reports.
File 'em the same as you
always do. I'll cover for you.
Who's gonna cover
you, Lieutenant?
[District Commander]
If you checked in at the
precinct before you started
nosing around we may have
been able to help you.
We could've watched
your cars anyway.
[District Commander]
And there's no crime wave in
this precinct, Sergeant.
No kidnappings. No murder.
This is an immigrant
neighborhood.
Most of the, uh, so-called
"families" hustle the
immigration people...
[Hanlan]
Yeah, then "Daddy", or
"Little Brother" disappear.
Sure.
They're driving a cab
in San Francisco.
What about extortion? What
about these teenage gangs?
[Hanlan]
Yeah, penny ante crap.
They all dress up like the KGB.
The strong hustle the weak
and nobody talks to the cops.
Hey, they're Hunkies.
I don't like the word, Sergeant.
Look, we do our job here, Reed.
And we are not the U.N.
We're not social workers.
But we can't solve all their
problems, especially if they
won't speak to us.
Excuse me just for
a second, please.
Miss?
Yeah, hi. I wonder
if I could, uh
have a few words with you.
Ma'am? Please, just...
[District Commander]
See what I mean? It's hopeless.
Uh, excuse me a minute, fellas.
Hanlan, why don't you, uh
drop off Sgt. Reed at
his office? We, uh...
can't have him taking
the bus, can we?
I appreciate that, Commander.
What's it say?
Gulov. 135 Kenyon.
[Jack]
Alright, 135. That should be up
here on the right someplace.
Hey wait, wait... whoa whoa...
hold it, hold it. Back it up.
Nah, we can be that
lucky, can we?
[praying in Russian]
He is coming for you, Vassily.
Who is coming?
Satan.
He's coming to punish you
for all your praying.
You are lying, Sergei.
It's true. I swear
it. Satan, himself.
He's in disguise, though.
He looks like two fat man
with bad feet.
Come here, little brother.
[Sergei]
Look at this. I love America.
Come on.
When Satan...
comes to the door...
you must shoot him.
Hmm?
Old Latvian proverb.
[Vassily]
Sergei, who is coming?
Is it police?
Don't worry, Vassily. I will
return. I will save you.
Remember, kill Satan.
I'll be back.
[Jack]
Guess it must be the top floor.
[Eddie]
Why are they always
on the top floor?
[Jack]
Ah, stop complaining. It's
good for your girlish figure.
But it's terrible for my knee.
Maybe we should get
some back-up...
[Jack]
C'mon.
We'll just see if
anybody's home.
Officers under fire at
135 Kenyon Street.
It's that pain the
ass, Reed, again.
I think somebody's home.
Maybe we should have
called for back-up.
[In Russian]
Come in, see what happens!
What'd he say?
I don't know, but he's cranky.
Stay back, pal. He's got a gun!
It's okay. He's my
crazy brother, huh.
Hey--hey, don't go
in there. Hey!
Vassily! It's me!
[in Russian]
It's me!
Remember, be brave.
They cannot hurt you.
You are juvenile.
I will protect you.
I will save you.
Fool! Do you think you
can kill everyone?!
Huh?! It's all right.
I... I have gun.
All right, get down
here. Get down.
You got the right
to remain silent.
[Eddie]
You got the right
to legal counsel.
You got the right to
unlimited phone calls.
You got the right to cable TV.
You got the right to pizza three
times a week with toppings of
your choice.
All right, come on.
Let's go. Get up here.
Hey, Jack.
Hey.
That the cemetery shooter?
That's him. He just took a
couple shots at us too.
- Yeah, I heard. Good work.
- Thanks.
I'll go and talk to
you for a minute.
I don't wanna bust
your hump, Lieutenant
but you gotta deal with
some of these calls.
You got a congressman here,
two state senators, and a
couple of aldermen.
Old friends, so they say.
Yeah. Yeah, we'll see.
C'mon in, Jack. Close the door.
Okay.
[Charles]
Have you heard about
Gordon Thomas's kid?
Yeah. Vehicular homicide, huh?
He's in the big leagues now.
Pete Myers been
on the phone yet?
They were here, the whole
crew, including Hobart.
[Charles]
They want a mittimus, of course.
Of course. They move the
investigation downtown.
Hobart kicks it around
accidentally on purpose
and the judge throws it out.
[Jack]
Let it go, Charles.
You gotta pick your fights.
You can't win this one.
Do they really believe that
I'd try to screw the kid to
hurt his old man?
I mean, we were friends once.
[Jack]
It's got nothing to
do with the kid.
This is big-time
politics. Thomas is
gonna be the next mayor.
Maybe the vice president
in a few years.
[Jack]
You're up against money,
power, and People magazine.
Who cares if he got
a screwed-up kid?
Isabella Rodriguez's family.
[Jack]
Oh, they'll get to them too.
Sandy Miller'll pay 'em a visit.
It'll turn out that their family
junker had bad breaks.
[Jack]
It rolled right in front of
Thomas's car or something.
I-I-I don't like this job today.
Why do you think you're here?
All these politicians trying
to get you on the phone
they helped get you this job.
You think they were just doing
a favor for a brother?
It's payback time, pal.
You hold on a minute, Jack. That
has nothing to do with this--
Hey, hey. Come on, now, don't
get sensitive on me.
[Jack]
It ain't just you. If you are
Irish and Thomas was
some Mick alderman from the west
side trying to get Uncle Seamus
out of a jam
you'd roll over in a minute.
Charles, Affirmative Action is
hardly a new concept in Chicago.
It's just new for black folks.
But there is a price.
There's always a price.
Kick it to the D. A.'s office.
[Jack]
Look, don't beat yourself
up up about this, Charles.
It's your turn in the barrel.
It's Chicago.
He's a juvenile, Jack.
He's what?
He's 17 years old.
His, uh, step-brother here,
Mr. Gulov, brought his papers.
He looks 10 years
older than that.
[Sergei]
Poor boy. Hard life.
You work at the cemetery too,
don't you, Mr. Gulov?
Yes, half-time. No,
not, uh, half-time.
Part-time?
Yes, part-time.
Mind if I ask, uh, what you
are doing this morning when
the shooting started?
Yes, I was in the north section,
uh, passing stone.
What?
A headstone, big one.
I was passing it.
[Jack]
You were moving it?
[Sergei]
Ah, yes, uh, moving
it. I'm stupid.
I can take Vassily
home now, yes?
[Eddie]
You can take Vassily home, no.
But, uh, he is, how
you say, juvenile, no?
[Jack]
A juvenile. Yeah... [laughing]
If you remember, Mr. Gulov, he
tried to kill us this morning.
And, uh, he's gonna be charged
with murder times three, for
the cemetery killings.
We got the shotgun.
We got the shells.
We got his fingerprints. We got
the residue all over him.
No, he's, uh... he's not
going anywhere for a while.
If you wanna help him, I suggest
you give him a good lawyer.
But, uh, thanks for coming in.
Ah, what about car?
What?
My car. I--I need for work.
[Jack]
Impounded, Mr. Gulov,
for evidence.
But that car belongs to the
cemetery, doesn't it?
Yes, of course.
I must call them.
But they let you drive
it, huh? A half-timer?
Nyet. No, no, not me.
Vassily.
Because they are afraid of him.
[Jack]
Oh.
Apparently with reason.
We'll, uh... we'll be in touch.
Well, I guess I better try
to have a conversation
with Junior here.
Hey, how are ya? Okay?
Boy, you like them
cigarettes, don't ya?
- Yes.
- You got key for this?
Why did you try
to kill me today?
I thought you were Satan.
Uh, I'm sorry. Say that again.
But I'm stupid.
A man cannot kill Satan.
What about the shootings
at the cemetery?
[Jack]
Those guys are dead, Vassily.
Why'd you kill them? Did you
think they were Satan too?
I did not kill them.
More smoke, please?
Sure, have some smokes.
I can't give you the lighter,
that's against regulations.
So, Vassily, can you
say "hot seat"?
"Electric chair"? Hmm?
Three murders, Vassily.
Special circumstances.
Death penalty.
Shish kabob.
Not juvenile.
In Russia, maybe.
Here, never.
Juvenile, huh?
[Jack]
We've got three bodies.
We've got all kinds of evidence.
And we've got you.
I mean, even if you plead guilty
you're gonna get hammered.
I don't understand.
You'll do 20 to 25
years minimum.
M.. maybe I'm wrong.
[Jack]
Uh... maybe it was an accident.
The... the gun went off.
Uh, you sneezed or something.
Are we talking manslaughter
here, Vassily?
How much time for accident?
What you say, uh, man-slow...?
Manslaughter.
[Vassily]
Maybe five years.
Okay, it was accident.
But not five years.
Six months, maybe.
Hey, you'll talk to the judge.
Maybe he'll see it your way.
Okay, so the...
the first shooting
was an accident.
What... what about the
other two killings?
Were they accidents too?
Yes. Yes, accident.
You a little grumpy in
the morning, Vassily?
Coffee nerves? What
was Sergei doing?
He do nothing.
He do nothing. He seen nothing.
Okay. Okay.
Why?
What?
These accidents.
You're standing there. You're
holding a shotgun on these guys.
Why? What was going on?
Accident. Juvenile.
[noises outside]
[doorknob turning]
[In Russian]
Help! Help! Fire! Fire!
Help!
[In Russian]
Oh, my God! Fire!
How could they do this?!
How could they do this?
It's okay. It's okay.
Thank you.
[baby crying]
Sasha! Sasha!
Mama! Mommy!
[wolf howl]
[In Russian]
Irina! Hold your
baby close, Irina.
We will come for you. Soon!
[wolf howling]
Go to sleep now, son.
[video game noises]
[Charles]
He's getting real good
with that computer.
[Mary Alice]
Yeah, well, I wish he
do something with it
besides play those stupid games.
[Charles]
Oh, you know, at least
he's learning to use it.
He's way ahead of me.
You pick up my tux?
[Sighs]
I'll do it tomorrow.
[Charles]
Well, now, don't forget.
You know, we want to leave
here around 6:30 or so.
Maybe we should just forget
about the banquet.
I could use a quiet
night at home.
What are you talking about?
You been looking forward
to this for months.
What about the new
dress you got?
I know but I've been
tired this week and...
What happened? Who called you?
Nerissa... and Roxanne.
Maybe I'll just call 'em back...
No, Charles, don't. They don't
understand the situation.
I think they understand it very
well if they're trying to get to
me through my wife.
That's not fair. These
people have been friends
of ours for years...
They're friends of Gordon
Thomas's too, which is why
they called...
[Mary Alice]
He was your friend too. You
named your son after him...
And I'm supposed to let his
son get away with murder!
Is that how it works?!
How can you say that to me?!
[Mary Alice]
These people are our oldest
and our closest friends
and they cannot understand
why you're so determined
to personally ruin
Gordon and his son!
If they, or anyone, thinks that
that's what's going here
then they don't
know me very well
and they're no
longer my friends.
Does that include me to?
I don't know. Does it?
[Charles]
Maybe you're right
about tomorrow.
We'll spend a quiet
evening at home.
[dramatic music]
[Horn honking]
[officer]
Put it back by the fence.
[driver]
All right.
[music gets more intense]
[car alarm blares]
What do ya think?
You're beautiful, baby.
[Charles]
Mmmm...
Oh, you smell good too.
Hey, look, I'm sorry
about last night...
No, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have doubted you.
[Mary Alice]
Forgive me?
I don't know. Better
do that again.
[Charles]
Does, um...
does this mean, uh...
we're gonna go to
the dance tonight?
Yes, we're gonna go. We're
gonna drink champagne.
We're gonna dance
our booties off.
We'll be the happiest
people there.
Can I ask you something, baby?
What?
Do we gotta dance?
[phone rings]
Ah, damn.
What?
[Fireman]
We have a pick-up here.
[Charles]
The fire started in
the middle of the lot?
Yeah, they used
Molotov cocktails.
The... the guard said he saw the
last one coming over the fence.
Why torch it now? I mean,
it's already been searched.
Maybe they didn't know that.
[officer]
Sergeant Reed...
[Jack]
Bicycles.
[Charles]
Yeah. Look at those
footprints. They're small.
[Eddie]
A woman, maybe?
[Charles]
Making that throw?
[Eddie]
Why not? She was wearing
combat boots, wasn't she?
[Jack]
Maybe it was a kid.
[Eddie]
Wait a minute, Jack.
Those kids...
[Jack]
Yeah. The Bonewagon...
[Charles]
The Bonewagon?
What's the Bonewagon?
Hey, come back here
with that umbrella.
Yeah...
that's what they were
after, not Thomas's car.
Whose is it?
I think it's time we had another
talk with big brother, Sergei.
[Charles]
Big brother? What the hell's
going on around here?
[sound of kicking at door]
Told ya.
Waste of time.
[Hanlan]
He's laughing at you, Reed.
He's in, uh, y'know, Brighton
Beach, driving a limo
and he's laughing his ass off.
[phone ringing]
[game show announcer]
Get a good spin, Doug.
Eggplant! Beautiful!
[phone continues]
The phone, idiot!
[in Russian]
Turn it down.
[phone continues]
Hello?
[Vassily]
Sergei. Thank God.
I am waiting long time.
[Sergei on phone]
Vassily, poor boy,
are you all right?
Sergei, you must come.
[prisoners shouting to
get off the phone]
You must help me, I'm afraid.
They put me here
in terrible place.
You must tell them you
are juvenile, Vassily.
All will be better.
I tell them but
they don't listen.
[prisoners continue yelling]
They put me here with
terrible people.
- [Sergei] I cannot help you,
Vassily.
You have sinned, and only
God can help you now. You
must pray, little brother.
- [prisoners keep yelling]
- [Sergei] Pray hard.
[prisoner]
Tell her you love
her and let's go!
- Sergei!
- [prisoner] Move it! Hey!
- C'mon, get off!
Sergei!
[Sergei]
Ah, payday. Who's first?
Mikhail's Bakery,
two hundred dollars.
A generous man, Mikhail.
Georgi's restaurant, $250.
Should be 300 but
I'll talk to him.
What about Brodsky, the jeweler?
Um, Brodsky... he says,
sir, his wife is sick.
How much?
Nothing. It's true. She is sick.
His wife has been sick since the
storming of the Winter Palace.
Now come on, we are wolves, not
sheep! You two, come here!
Go to Brodsky's. Break
the big window.
He'll run out with the money.
Tell him there's a
late charge, mmm, 500.
If he squeals, go inside,
get his wife's wheelchair,
bring it here.
What if she's in it?
I don't want her,
just the chair. Go.
He'll pay. Go.
You three..
go and see the little bitch
with a big mouth, hmm?
I want her terrified.
Do you understand?
I want her wetting
her pants! Go.
Ahhh...
[in Russian]
Watching that junk. Fool...
[wolves howling]
Irina, open the door!
We have come to babysit! Irina!
Bitch! Hey, bitch, open the
door! I'll kill you Bitch!
Open the door!
Don't hurt me.
Please...don't hurt me.
[Jack]
I hate floaters.
[Eddie]
Yeah, so do I. But
that's a fresh one.
[Jack]
Well I guess it wasn't
a swimming accident.
[Eddie]
Not with his head
caved in like that.
Technician said there's a
shotgun wound to the back.
[Jack]
This is the stuff from
his pockets, huh?
Gimme a... lemme borrow a pen
or a pencil or something.
[Jack]
Well, that's really interesting.
What?
He's Russian.
Look, I gotta find out
what we're dealing with
here in this precinct.
How many people are missing?
How many investigations,
if any, were carried out?
Well, you're gonna need the
Precinct Incident Report File
the Investigation File,
and the Complaint File.
Forget about it.
Maybe I can shake
things up a little bit.
Meantime, why don't you see if
you can find me Irina Lebed.
Who?
That little firecracker
who gave us Gulov. I wanna
talk to her.
Now, what do you mean
by "shake things up?"
You really wanna know, Eddie?
Nah, I don't think so.
[Charles]
Good mornin', Pete.
[Myers]
No calls, Sergeant. No one
opens this door, understood?
Gentlemen...
what a nice surprise.
You want some coffee?
Cut the crap. Let's
get down to business.
I'd like some tea, Lieutenant.
Billy, a cup of tea for Mr.
Miller here. Thank you.
Why haven't you
returned my calls?
Pete.
[Miller]
Lieutenant Silvera
we're anxious to resolve
this unfortunate situation
and we'd like to count
on your cooperation.
Well I haven't read the
papers today, Mr. Miller.
You win an election in
the last 24 hours or so?
[Charles]
Am I working for you now?
Listen... the games are over.
You understand?
Well last time I looked,
you weren't Civil Service
either, Pete.
[knocking on door]
[Charles]
You don't need my permission to
take over this investigation.
Sober up the D.A. long
enough to get his signature,
it's a done deal.
We're not going to move the
investigation to the D.A.'s
office, Lieutenant.
It's too late for that.
Too late?
The kid won't go to trial
for another six months...
In six months the
campaign bleeds to death.
We need this over
and done with, now.
In two day's time,
you will announce
that all charges against Gordon
Thomas, Jr. are being dropped.
What's going on, Miller?
I gotta make some calls.
The two investigating officers,
Carini and Cartwright
deliberately manipulated
the circumstances of this
tragic accident
to cause charges to be brought
against Gordon Thomas, Jr.
They lied.
They suborned
witnesses to perjury.
They fabricated evidence.
Have you gone completely
crazy, Miller?
We have affidavits from
a score of witnesses
including one of the
patrolmen on the scene.
[Miller]
We have a detailed statement
from one Rafael Rodriquez
the victim's husband.
It must've been expensive.
What make you think I'm
gonna go along with this?
You'll go along, Lieutenant
or you'll go down with them.
[Miller]
We have witnesses and affidavits
implicating you too.
And make no mistake, Lieutenant
we won't hesitate to use them.
You have 48 hours
to think about it.
Gordon know about this?
Gordon's a politician.
He knows what he wants to know.
You surprise me, Sandy.
Pete Myers... hell, Pete's got
the conscience of a lizard.
But Sandy Miller...
I've watched you all my life.
Birmingham, Selma, Little Rock
all those righteous years...
Forty years, Lieutenant.
[Miller]
It was a lot simpler then.
It was terrifying and majestic,
but pure and simple.
Now it's no longer simple
and it certainly isn't pure.
And we're running out of time.
Gordon Thomas may be the last
chance we have to put this
nightmare of race behind us.
And it's unfair, yes.
And you are the victims
you and your two
detective friends.
And I'm sorry about that.
But there have been many
victims over the years,
millions of them.
And if I'm right about Gordon
maybe you and your
friends will be the last.
[in Russian]
This is your father, angel.
Remember your sweet
father... always.
[knocking on door]
[Eddie]
Police...
I'm, uh, Sergeant Dirksen.
Remember me from the church?
Yeah. Yeah...
Always interesting knocking
on doors around here.
I'm sorry. Come in.
Yeah, come...
[Irina]
We knew it would be hard
but, at least here
there could be hope.
And for her...
and for her there would be more.
My husband, he was, uh...
intelligent, um...a professor.
And he was digging graves.
He hated the cemetery,
of course.
This is no job for him.
And now he's dead.
And now even hope is gone and...
I don't live for myself.
I care nothing for myself.
Only for her.
Tell us about Sergei.
He is a jackal.
When we come here
each of us
we have something.
[Irina]
Some money or some...
gold, diamonds.
Antiques. You understand?
Because you cannot start
over with nothing. You
need something.
And Sergei, he
finds the new ones.
And he watches them.
And he talks to them.
And one day, they are no more.
They are gone.
And we go to the police
and the police laugh.
They say... they say, uh
your son is in Miami, your
brother is in San Diego.
[dramatic music]
[Irina] They... they
are not dead.
They have taken the money and
run away. But this is not true.
But they will not listen.
- No one will listen, until you.
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait wait wait--why would
there be flies in an
empty grave, Eddie?
- What?
- Because the grave isn't empty.
The flies, the Bonewagon
the 'half-time' job at the
cemetery, the flies...
What are you talking
about, Jack?
Of course they're not in San
Diego or Miami, they're here.
They're here in Pleasant
Creek Cemetery.
He buried them in a cemetery
probably underneath the
legitimate graves.
That's why he shotgunned
the cemetery workers,
because he got caught.
[Jack]
That's why your husband
is dead, Mrs. Lebed.
Because that's where
the bodies are.
[singing in Russian]
He needs a doctor, Sergei.
Doctors ask questions.
He can see, can't he?
[Sergei]
Baba Yelena, she got
magic in her hands.
He'll be as good as
new in a few days.
[phone ringing]
It's Vassily.
- Hang up.
- But, Sergei--
I said hang up!
There is no Vassily!
Vassily is finished!
You understand?
You go back. Watch the
building. When she returns,
I will finish her myself.
And you, my frightened
little duck
you can take care of the baby.
[radio announcer #1]
They're just pounding the
boards today here in Tampa.
Parker gets maximum height
on the jump shot.
He's listed at 6'10"
and he's got--
[announcer #2]
Yeah, but he's about 6'8",
Dom. We know that.
[announcer #1]
Maybe 6'9". He's been all
over the defense today
both on offense and defense.
He's on the verge of another
double-double.
[Jack]
So this cop goes to a
doctor and he says, uh
"Doctor, every time I talk to a
newspaper reporter, I get a
headache. Why is that?"
[Russell]
And the Doctor says, 'It's
probably the hangovers.'
You heard it, huh?
How you doin', Jack?
[Jack]
How you doin', Russell?
Good to see you.
Thanks for coming.
[Russell]
So tell me, you ever
make Lieutenant?
Hell, they're still trying
to make am a civilian.
Hey, I've been reading that
stuff that you've been doing
on the Garbage Wars.
That's really great work.
Y'know, I always knew that
alderman was bent.
The dope put the bribe
money in a mutual fund.
I'll tell ya, Jack
if the politicians in this
town ever get smart we're
gonna be in some real trouble.
Russell, that's probably
one thing we don't have
to worry about.
I got a great story for you.
It's got everything in it:
struggling immigrants
teenage gangs, vicious murders
and a local police unit that
just ignores the whole mess.
I need it right away.
Declaring war on the
brass again, Jack?
Nah... more like a sneak attack.
Well, you've never
let me down yet.
So tell me, Jack, what
do you get out of this?
Not a promotion,
that's for sure.
[Nerissa]
I'm really glad you both came.
I think you're so brave.
[Mary Alice]
While I'm glad you're
glad, Nerissa.
But why wouldn't we come?
I mean, with Gordon speaking
tonight. You know...
We've known going for years,
haven't we, Charles?
Oh, sure. You know, in the
old days, we served
together, Nerissa.
I was his tail gunner.
I didn't know Gordon
was in the Air Force.
He wasn't.
If you'll excuse us, I'm
gonna dance with my wife.
[Miller]
Lieutenant, if I may presume
I like to dance with the
most beautiful woman in
the room tonight.
Mary Alice, Sandy Miller.
Mr. Miller, my wife Mary Alice.
Pleasure to meet you.
If you will do me
the honor, my dear.
Lieutenant Silvera.
My father was wondering if
you have a few minutes.
Excuse me, Nerissa, folks.
[Roxanne]
Close your mouth, Nerissa,
before something jumps in there.
So, how you doing, Gordon?
I am all right, Lieutenant.
I'm not scared anymore, either.
Will that's too bad
'cause Isabella Rodriguez
is still dead.
Did you know they work
together on a garbage truck?
You're kidding.
No, it's true.
Gordon drove and Charles
handled the trash.
He was Gordon's tail
gunner, he said.
So this is something I have
to show up for, yes?
No... Friday night?
The Palm. 8 o'clock.
See you then.
Charles, I was afraid that
you wouldn't show up.
Why wouldn't I show up, Gordon?
Junior, could you give us
a few minutes, please?
Oh, let him stay. I mean, this
is all about him, isn't it?
I don't want him to stay.
Junior, could you please give
me some club soda? Charles?
Champagne. Better make a bottle.
Sit down.
Thank you.
[Miller]
Whatever happened between them?
Willy Bradford, a poor,
black boy, stole a car
and the cops shot
him and killed him.
It was a bad shooting,
Charles said.
The cop was in a lot of trouble.
But it was an election year,
and Gordon made some speeches
that were...
...Inflammatory.
Charles thought they were.
A week or so later the cop who
shot the boy killed himself.
Charles and Gordon were
never the same after that.
This is a bunch of
lies and you know it!
You don't think it's possible
that the police could do
what they did to my son,
and me?! What country have
you been living in?!
Oh, cut the crap, Gordon!
Randy Cartwright is a decent,
hard-working black man come
from nothing!
Just like you! And me! He made
detective in eight years.
Goes to law school nights!
He's got two kids!
You think he's going to throw it
all away because he don't want
you to be Mayor?!
Well, we have the affidavits
and the witnesses.
The media, and most of the
people, are gonna be on my side!
Well, I won't! I'm gonna
fight you on this, Gordon--
Yeah, well we're gonna roll
all over you, Charles!
Then you roll on! I'm gonna
go dance with my wife.
Is this what it was
all about, Gordon?
Is this where we wanted to get,
so we could be just like them?
Getting and having?
Taking care of number one?
Screwing or being screwed?!
What ever made you think that
we were better than them?
Dad, you're drinking.
Yeah, I'm drinking. I've got
a bad taste in my mouth.
You wipe that smile
off your face.
You think this is funny?!
That man is the best
friend I ever had
the most honest man I know.
And I have to destroy him
to save your sorry ass!
'Course it has absolutely
nothing to do with saving
your sorry ass, right, Dad?
Don't you ever talk to
me like that again.
Don't you understand?
This is the American dream, Dad.
You.. you work hard.
You make sacrifices.
You save money, so your kids can
go crazy and destroy themselves!
Well, congratulations,
Dad, you've made it!
[fast paced music]
[Miller]
10 years.
10 years...
working full-time days
and going to college and
law school at night.
I learned just this evening
that one of Gordon's day jobs
was driving a garbage truck.
After years of
struggle, graduation
admission to the bar, then what?
A fat job with a
fat paycheck? No.
Because by then there had
been Selma, and Little Rock
four little girls
murdered in Alabama
the Rev. King dead in Memphis.
There was destiny then
and duty
for Gordon Thomas.
You're sure she's alone?
I saw them go.
Except for him.
Okay.
You remember what
I told you, huh?
Lots of noise. Go.
Give it to me.
No I want her looking
at me when I do it.
Right into my eyes.
[glass breaks
car alarm blares]
Let's go.
[Gordon Sr.]
We have come a long way.
Just take a look around
you tonight to see
how far we've come.
Some of us.
Because too many,
black and white
have been left behind.
That is a problem that
America faces now.
Not who will sit in
the front of the bus
and who will sit in
the back of the bus
but how many will be able
to ride in the bus at all.
How many, black and white,
will be defeated by poverty
ignorance, and yes, racism
and the greatest, most
dangerous enemy of them all...
Hopelessness.
[horns honking]
[in Russian]
Stand back.
Find her.
Hi, Sergei.
[Jack]
Put the gun down.
You fooled me.
You fooled Sergei.
Eddie!
He's on the third floor
and he's got a hostage.
[woman screams]
[gun clicks but it is
out of ammunition]
He's on the roof.
[Sergei]
Shhhh...
[man speaks in Russian]
For you, eh. A gift.
Now, tell me.
When you sleep
do you wear pajamas?
Yeah, he's on the roof.
No, were trying to get
everybody out now.
C'mon...
[Jack]
It's pitch black up there.
I can't see a thing.
[Eddie]
Well, he can't go any
place, unless he can fly.
Well, then let's SWAT
team take care of it.
I'm not going to do
anything about it--
Right this way, ladies.
- C'mon, right this way.
- Keep moving. Come on.
- How are you doing?
- It's OK.
I can't even feel it.
Did you get him?
[Jack]
No, we didn't get
him, but we will.
It's all right, don't worry
about it. You take it easy. Just
take the rest of the night off.
You did a hell of
a job, all right?
[Gordon Sr.]
So what it comes down to...
what it always comes down to
is good and evil.
Now I know it's not
politically correct to talk
in terms of good and evil.
To denounce the slippery
slope of moral relativism
we find ourselves so
perilously clinging to.
But I do denounce it.
There is a difference
between good and evil
and we must begin to
choose good again.
[crowd murmurs]
Good...
And evil.
I am reminded of an old
union slogan from the 30s
"Which side are you on?"
Which side are you on?
- [Arlene] Jack?
- [Jack] Yeah, um, Arlene
I--I'm sorry, uh,
we didn't call.
This is, uh--this
is Irina Lebed.
This is Sasha. She's got a
bit of a problem tonight...
Oh, you poor things.
Eddie, take them upstairs
to the guest room.
There are clean towels up in the
closet. Go ahead. Go with Eddie.
Y' know, I'll be up in
a second with some tea.
You can take a nice warm bath,
and I'll watch the baby.
I'm sorry, Jack.
What were you saying?
[Arlene]
Is she smiling at you?
- [baby laughing]
- [John Jr.] Look at you.
-[Arlene] Don't give her that...
- [John Jr.] Cute baby...
- [Arlene] She can't eat that.
- [Eddie] Why not?
- Good morning.
Well, well, well, Eddie.
You been here all night?
[Eddie]
No, I've been home.
I, uh, came back to talk
to you about Sergei.
Oh, yeah. What about Sergei?
He got away.
- [John Jr. talking to baby]
- [Jack] Yeah.
[Jack]
You could've told me that on
the phone. What's going on?
- Jack?
- Huh? What?
- Come here.
- What?
What, what, what?
Eddie is here because he's
concerned about Irina and
the baby, alright?
[Jack]
Concerned? What--?
Sympathetic, okay?
Okay. Okay...
Diapers are in the garbage and
the garbage has been put out.
[John Jr.]
Speaking of diapers. Mom...
Honey, let me walk
you through that.
- Eccch..
- I, uh, just remembered
there is something I want
to talk to you about, Jack.
- What?
- [Eddie] Exhumation.
You came over here at seven
o'clock in the morning
wearing a shirt and tie
and wearing cologne,
if I'm not mistaken
because you wanted to talk about
exhuming bodies, right, Eddie?
Yeah, that was one
of the reasons.
It's hard enough to get an
exhumation order under
normal circumstances.
"Your Honor, we really don't
want to look at the body.
we wanna see if there's anything
buried underneath it."
Eh, forget about it.
No, I think I'm gonna
go pay a visit to
little brother Vassily.
He's been sitting down
there in maximum security
in the county jail
for a couple of days.
his back pressed firmly
against the wall.
Maybe he's looking at things
a little differently.
Coffee?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Yeah, please.
[Jack]
Thank you, my dear.
[Eddie]
They're, uh, holding
the, uh, kids....
the "Wolves"...
at the, uh, detention center.
I suppose I should go down
there and talk to 'em.
Let 'em go.
What, are you crazy?
I wanna try something.
Get their names and addresses,
and their fingerprints
and let 'em go.
We got a wounded cop, Jack.
It might not be that easy.
Nah, you can do it, Eddie.
Just wear that cologne.
[Jack]
So how do you like maximum
security, Vassily?
Terrible.
Terrible people, even guards.
Ah, the guards have gotta be
tough to work in this place.
Hmmm?
[Jack]
What kind of a deal are
they talking about?
Seventy-five years.
Hmmm. Well, you'll do thirty.
That's not generous,
but it's not terrible.
Y'know, you... you plead
guilty to three murders.
I murdered no one.
Sergei tell me to plea.
He tell me to say I am
juvenile so I get out soon.
What's he say now?
He not come.
He not come once.
He don't even talk
to me on the phone.
I'm shocked by that.
I'm truly shocked.
Sergei lied to you. He's not
gonna help you but I will.
First, you gotta help me.
C'mon now, Vassily,
you gotta get smart.
I am not smart.
I am stupid.
In old country...
they put me in place
for stupid people...
crazy people.
Terrible place.
Worse that this one.
But Sergei, he come
and take me out.
He bring me here, to America.
He take care of me.
He protect me.
What... what are you saying,
that Sergei is a good man?
No.
He cheat.
He steal.
He kill people...
not just for money
but because he
likes to kill them.
Then he makes me shoot them
or hit them, after
they are dead.
Misha Sorenski.
Yuri Brodski.
Nikita Bulgov.
I see them always.
Yeah, I let Sergei fool me too.
But I'll help you, Vassily.
I swear to you, I'll help you.
No...
no one can help Vassily now.
Maybe cigarettes.
You get me good cigarettes?
Unfiltered, yes?
Yeah, I'll get you
cigarettes. You gotta
smoke these first, right?
Alright...
tell me where the bodies are.
[dogs barking]
[dramatic music]
Baba!
[dogs barking]
Old woman!
Baba!
My guns! Where are my guns?!?
So you have returned, finally.
Where have you been?
The Old Ones have gone.
They have take the guns.
We must find them. Go.
It wasn't me. It was the police.
It was you, Sergei.
His leg is shattered.
He's crippled.
I had to get away.
I had to shoot.
[Sergei]
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Come back, I have no money.
I... I have no guns.
I have no shoes!
Come back!
Yuri Brodsky.
Misha Sorenski.
-Is that it?
- I don't know.
Some we do it at night.
Some we do in the morning.
It... when it's dark.
One or two, maybe.
Jack!
[Eddie]
Yeah, okay.
Alright. Thanks.
They got Sergei holed
up, you were right.
The Little Wolves turned him in.
[dramatic music]
Hi, Sergei.
[Jack]
What, you wanna
make a run for it?
Hmm?
Go ahead. Please...
I want you to.
Cuff him.
Can we get started, please?
I don't want to miss my ten
o'clock baloney sandwich.
How about a drink?
Yes. Vodka. A double.
A root beer.
[Jack]
I saw your brother yesterday.
Half-brother.
You could get him off the hook.
As you Americans say,
what's in it for me?
My sentence reduced from, uh
three hundred to
two hundred years?
He's your brother.
[Sergei]
Half-brother.
Half-wit.
I saved him once and
brought him here.
It was a moment of
weakness for me
and a total disaster
for both of us.
No, Vassily needs a
structured environment.
Besides...
I like the idea of you
feeling guilty about him
for the next twenty
or thirty years.
What happened to your accent?
I still have an accent.
It's not the same.
Oh, what a detective.
[Sergei]
I speak better English
than you do, Sergeant.
Which is not saying much, I know
because I probably studied
it longer that you did,
when I was in the Army.
When there was an Army.
That's right, nearly Cold
War was lost, you know.
Everyone was so desperate
to study English.
Oh, the Great Detective
is perplexed, hmm?
Who is this person?
Obviously he's intelligent
and well-educated.
Why would he commit such
loathsome crimes?
Okay. Why?
Why not?
[Sergei]
Oh... the good policeman frowns
at the evil outlaw, huh?
What do you want me
to do, beg for mercy?
Tremble beneath the
- [men walk in talking]
- [Sergei] majesty of your law.
- Shut the door. And be quiet.
- [Sergei] What hypocrisy.
An American lives
in a huge house.
Thirty people could like in this
house comfortably, yet...
he's alone.
He has, uh, three cars...
four bedrooms, six televisions.
They sit and gather dust.
Another American, a
block from here...
lives in a cardboard box.
Flea-bitten, and
starving, he breaks in...
to the huge house and steals one
of the unused televisions.
He is arrested and punished
by you, Detective.
So, who is criminal?
The rich man, the poor thief...
or you?
This is your society, your law.
Congratulations.
[Jack]
What a bunch of crap.
You... you preyed on
these people yourself.
Poor immigrants, women,
children, defenseless people--
Of course, because
they are defenseless.
Because you do not defend them.
I'm not a Marxist, Sergeant.
I'm a Darwinist.
A predator.
A wolf, if you will.
I do not accept your
society or its rules.
So I am outlaw.
And I choose to be outlaw.
Ahhh. A Darwinist.
[Jack]
A wolf.
Hmmm. Tell me something, Sergei.
Does a wolf take
pleasure in killing?
What?
Vassily said that you kill
because you like to kill.
Does... does a
wolf like to kill?
Oh... not just wolves.
Shall I tell you, what
joy really is, Sergeant?
[Sergei]
It's looking into their eyes,
right before the end.
They've given up all their
pathetic little treasures.
And they have only one thing
left, and they want to keep
it so badly.
And they beg you
"Please... please..."
And then you take it,
that last thing.
Joy.
Exhalation.
Life.
Oh, I've upset you, Sergeant.
Forgive me.
Finished so soon? I
am disappointed...
What are you doing?
A new game, Sergeant?
This is childish.
Hello? Are you watching?
Stop this, now.
[Jack]
They can't see you.
Besides, they're cops, Sergei.
They don't care about you.
Nobody moves unless I tell 'em.
[Sergei]
No...
No, I don't, uh...
I don't like this. Hello!
- [Jack] Louder, Sergei.
- [Sergei] Hello!
- [Jack] Louder!
- [Jack] Can't hear you, Sergei!
- [Sergei] You don't understand.
I...
You must not...
[Jack]
What? I must not what?
[Sergei]
You can't do this.
You can't do this!
[Jack]
Why? Why can't I?
[Sergei]
I... I don't like the dark.
- [Jack] What did you say?
- I'm afraid of the dark!
[Jack]
They're out there,
aren't they, Sergei?
In the dark...
- they're waiting for you.
- [Sergei] No...
- NOOO!!!
- [Jack] Say it!
- [Sergei] No!
- [Jack] Say it, Sergei!
[Sergei]
HELP ME, SOMEBODY!!!
I'm looking' in
your eyes, Sergei.
I don't feel any joy.
No, all I feel is disgust.
Outlaw, huh?
Shall I tell you what
society is, outlaw?
See, all it is is
a bunch of people
trying to live together, trying
to -- trying to raise their kids
trying to live decent lives
and trying to protect
themselves from scum like you.
Y'see, I get to
choose too, Sergei.
I choose to protect that society
and to kick your arrogant,
bloodthirsty ass.
I got a big present for
you Sergei. Oh, you're
gonna love it too.
You know what?
You're gonna get to spend
the rest of your life
in the most Darwinist Society
on the face of the Earth
a maximum security prison
in the state of Illinois.
Let's see how long you survive.
[noise and commotion in station]
Jack, can I talk to you?
Yeah. What's...
what's going on here?
Press conference in a few
minutes. Gordon Thomas
and entourage.
Why are they having a
press conference here?
Well that's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
Let's find a quiet place.
Where's Gordon?
He said he'd meet us here.
Do we have enough copies
of the affidavits? Of the
Rodriguez statement?
I don't want him saying
anything we didn't tell him.
And no questions.
Sandy, stop worrying.
Ah, we'll start on time.
I'll say a few words and...
Here's Gordon now.
[Gordon Sr.]
Ladies and gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen
my son and I
are announcing that he will
plead guilty to the charges
made against him.
[gasps from crowd]
And that we will cooperate fully
with the District
Attorney's office with
regard to sentencing.
Gordon will plead guilty
because he is guilty.
And because he's prepared
to accept responsibility
for his actions.
I will continue my campaign
for the office of Mayor.
And I will, of course
continue in the support
and love of my son.
I've had a wonderful
successful life.
But I have not been
a good father.
I feel I share in
my son's guilt.
So, Gordon, whatever happens,
we'll face it together.
[reporters talk in crowd]
Now, on to a different matter...
I'm sadly announcing the
resignation from my campaign...
effective immediately,
of Sandy Miller.
At the request of his
doctor, Sandy is leaving
public life for good.
One of my oldest
and dearest friends
a veteran of civil rights
campaigns over the last 35 years
Sandy begins a
well-deserved retirement.
Sandy?
Thanks Gordon.
When is the last time any
of us heard a politician...
a man, speak like this.
Honest. Straightforward.
Genuine.
A revelation...
even to me...
if one was needed.
Ladies and gentlemen, this
is the kind of man-- well...
let me amend that...
this is the man we need
in the Mayor's office
and perhaps someday...
the White House.
[reporters shouting]
- Well, that was a surprise.
- Especially to Sandy Miller.
How about you, Charles?
[Charles]
Jack, I was surprised as hell.
Ah, smart politics.
Get it out, get it over with.
Besides, a lot of voters
have screwed-up kids.
[Charles]
Man, I feel like I
can breathe easy.
Someday I'll tell you why.
- We know why.
- No, you don't.
Sure we do.
[tape recording of
Miller's voice]
"You'll go along, Lieutenant...
or you'll go down with them.
We have witnesses and and
affidavits implicating you too."
- [Charles] You recorded it?
- [tape keeps playing]
The whole thing.
A little trick I learned from
one of your predecessors.
He was a wee bit paranoid
but he had a good reason to be.
Billy, Billy, Billy.
What would we do
with ya, Billy?
[Charles]
Yeah, Billy.
Here's to you.
Ahhh. Is this place wired?
How 'bout some coffee,
Lieutenant?
What?
Oh, man... the intercom?!
[Sheehan]
Sure. Picks up the whole room.
And I recorded it off
the phone on my desk.
And you got a copy
to Gordon Thomas.
And that's why Sandy Miller
got his little surprise.
No.
- [Charles] No?
- No?
[Sheehan]
Up until ten minutes ago
I was the only person who
know anything about this.
Huh, how about that?
Why didn't you tell
me about this before?
Tell him.
[Sheehan sighs]
I didn't know who was
going down, Lieutenant...
You, Carini and Cartwright, or
just Carini and Cartwright.
You didn't trust me, huh?
I was hoping you'd
do the right thing.
And you did.
He folded.
Not really. I guess he just
remembered who he used to be.
[Sergei]
Hello, Little Brother.
Because of your singing, we
are both in here now, huh?
But I will silence you, Little
Canary. I promise you that.
Your singing days
will soon be over.
Get out of the way, man.
I'm walking' here.
I was talking to my brother.
I don't give a damn who
he is or who you are.
When I'm walking,
get out of my way.
Of course, my friend.
Whatever you say.
Who're you calling
'friend,' Hunky?
Vassily...
Help me!
Help me! Guard!!!
- Hey, Jack...
- [Jack] Hold on a sec', Matt.
I got the Sheriff on the phone.
You been sending that Russian
kid cigarettes?
Ah, c'mon, what is it with
this kid and cigarettes?
I... I gave him two cartons of
cigarettes a week ago when he
was here for the interrogation.
I sent him four
cartons yesterday.
He can't possibly need
any more cigarettes.
He don't need nothin'
anymore, Jack.
♪ [choral music]
They happened within fifteen
minutes of each other.
Vassily was stabbed
20 or 30 times.
In the shower, like the movies.
What about Sergei?
You'll appreciate this.
He drowned.
- What?
- In a toilet bowl.
Somebody held him down
and flushed him away.
That's appropriate.
Any line on the killers?
Nah. Vassily was a cash deal...
paid for by his brother,
I guess.
They don't know who
did Sergei either
but he's a heavy smoker.
Why?
Well the word is, the
price for Sergei...
four cartons of
cigarettes, unfiltered.
♪ [music]
♪ [Multicom Entertainment
Group jingle] ♪