[music playing]
[Broughten] So, as of this
minute, a gentleman,
Army Ranger Assault Team
Baker One
no longer exists.
The presence of American Army
ground troops in this sector
is a direct violation of the
United Nations peace agreement.
So you all know what that means.
That's right.
That means
that your government's ass
has got to be protected
in case of capture or death.
You don't have to worry
about that,
Captain Broughten, sir,
I've been farting like
a motherfucker,
so they'll probably send my ass
back to you.
Thanks for your help, Alex.
You all know Captain Shannon.
CIA covert operations.
We are about to mount
an extraction
in a very volatile sector
of this world,
and Shannon's going to fill us
in on the details. Vincent.
Hassim al Haddad.
You've seen his face
all over the news.
Responsible for at least
eight embassy bombings
and the deaths of hundreds
of innocent civilians.
And many of your
fellow soldiers.
So listen up.
Here's the mission specs.
We're all going in
under the cover of darkness,
and we will be disguised
as Syrian soldiers.
Our mission is to extract Haddad
at any cost.
You know what?
I'm not mistaken.
This looks like one of
my grandmother's old vibrators.
You ready to save the world
again, buddy?
Is your insurance paid up?
Vince, what's the matter
with you?
I've known you since basic, man.
Never seen you
like this before a mission.
This mission is dirty, Scott.
What do you mean
this mission's dirty?
Last week, I intercepted
a series of transmissions
from our CIA station
in Cyprus to Haddad's people.
-What was the content?
-I didn't have time to decode.
But they were increasing
in frequency the closer
we got the mission time.
And why would they do that
if they weren't
trying to warn Haddad?
Why in God's name would the CIA
call and warn Haddad
we were coming?
That's the question.
That's what I'm trying
to figure out.
Somebody's dealing
a hell of a hand of poker
and Haddad's
the million dollar chip.
You, me and the rest
of these dummies
we're betting against the house
to see who gets it.
The percentage is always
with the house.
Scotty, don't be surprised
if they're waiting for us.
-[buzzer]
-We're at insertion, saddle up!
[buzzer]
Let's go! Let's go!
[music playing]
[hydraulics hissing]
Thirty years and the Black man
still got to sit
in the back of the fucking boat.
Yes. Yes, I understand.
Sir, the American incursion
is underway.
Good.
Amir, the Americans
are close at hand.
Do not worry, my brother.
The men are all in place.
The dogs will not get through.
[chuckles]
Good.
[music playing]
You boys ready?
Halloween time
till we get inside.
Let's go.
The lookouts have
lost them, sir.
Should I call Amir?
My brother is very competent.
Do not worry. They won't
be hidden much longer.
All right, let's move out.
Rogoff, take point.
Alright.
[tank engine rumbling]
-[rockets roaring]
-[man] Incoming!
[gunfire]
[explosions]
-Alex.
-Sir?
Give me thermal
on that building.
Right.
What do you got?
[beeping]
[Alex] We've got a house party
on the second floor.
Roses, midgets, butt-nekkid
bitches, the whole nine.
All right, good.
Vince, you take Rogoff,
you plant that C4, alright?
Jim, Jo-Jo, Fenton,
you stick with me.
Once we exit with that package
you blow that school
and you run
like a son of a bitch
back to the LZ.
You got it?
You will wait for us.
I always do, my friend.
Alex, stay point. Let's move.
[high-pitched whine]
-Clear.
-All right. Move out.
I look forward to seeing
the surprise on their faces.
All right, boys.
Halloween's over.
This mission is
going easier than that that
20-dollar ho I had in Vegas.
Maybe a little too easy.
-Jo-Jo, you ready?
-Yeah.
Vince, we are ready to go.
-Go ahead.
-Light that candle.
One birthday cake coming up.
[indistinct shouts]
-Clear!
Oh, my God.
Give me this shit!
Take this shit out your ear!
Try to order a pizza or reach
out and touch somebody,
I'll pump one in yo ass!
Shannon was right.
[wincing]
Jo-Jo, are you all right?
I'm hit. It's bad.
-Talk to me. Can you move?
-Yeah. Yeah.
All right, let's move out.
Alex, you got him?
Let's go.
They're within the perimeter.
Move the troops now!
Go!
Vince, we got him
but we're blown.
Get out.
Get out!
[screaming]
[indistinct shouting]
The school roof!
They're on the school roof.
Okay. That's it.
It's the last one.
Hold it right there, Shannon.
You've been looking
through the wrong mail,
asking too many questions.
We all thought it would be best
if you stayed behind.
So you're all leaving me here
to die.
You're already dead.
[indistinct shouting]
[beeps, high-pitched whine]
[screams]
-Where's Shannon?
-He ordered me out
and then the building blew.
[helicopter blades whirring]
Go, go, go!
Alright, there she is.
Let's move. Let's go. Go.
Go, go.
Move! Move! Move!
Let's go.
Move!
Damn you, Vince.
[groans]
-Shit!
-Jo-Jo!
Alex, see what you can do
for him.
I'm on it, Captain.
Come on, Jo-Jo.
Come on, man.
Still alive,
you sons of bitches!
Vince! Vince!
Where are you?!
He's with me.
Well, American...
It seems you've
missed your connecting flight.
Alex.
How is he?
He had to do it, Captain.
It was for the mission.
Guess what?
Fuck the mission, Rogoff.
And fuck you!
There was an explosion,
and then he disappeared, sir.
You should have put a bullet
in his head
while you had the chance,
Goddamn it.
And Langley wants to know
just what the hell they're
supposed to do with Haddad.
The mission
was supposed to fail, Rogoff.
Haddad was supposed
to stay in country.
-We planned for that.
-Well, I guess you didn't plan
-on Broughten.
-Oh, Christ.
Don't punk me
around, Lieutenant.
You help Broughten
and his men get out.
-Even blew up a fucking school.
-By that point,
the enemies thought
that they'd been betrayed.
So they would have
killed all of us.
Even me, sir.
Pity they didn't.
Hello, Captain Broughten
for General Smith, please.
He's in a meeting but I'll let
him know you're here.
-Thank you.
-[beep]
-Yeah.
-Captain Broughten
is here, sir,
to see you.
-Send him in.
-You can walk right in.
Thank you.
They want to debrief you
at Langley, Rogoff.
After that, get off base
for a few days, disappear.
General Smith.
At ease, captain.
You know, Carter Dell,
Frank Jay, CIA liaisons.
We've met.
Begging your pardon, sir, but...
I was surprised to see
Lieutenant Rogoff in here.
Lieutenant Rogoff was giving us
some deep background
on your mission and your team.
-What background?
-That's classified, captain.
Classified?!
I got a man killed over there,
Dell, and I left
another one behind.
I think that gives me clearance,
don't you?
Stand down, Captain.
Rogoff was giving us additional
intel on Shannon's capture.
Shannon's capture
was my fault, sir.
I made an error in judgment
and I left him behind.
I'd like permission to go back
and bring them in.
I'm sorry, Scott, but...
To be honest with you,
we're glad you left him behind.
-Sir?
-Shannon went bad,
sold intel to the Syrians.
We lost two agents.
Mossad lost seven.
I don't believe you.
We've been watching him
for weeks.
-This mission confirms it.
-Haddad was the bait.
Shannon was going to deliver you
and your men to the terrorists.
They got verifiable evidence
of an illegal U.S.
military incursion
into the Mideast.
The peace talks blew up
in our face.
How else do you think
they knew you were coming?
Vince Shannon told me
that this mission
was going to be compromised.
Now, if he was going
to sell us out,
why would he do that?
Oh, you were friends once.
Old loyalties die hard.
Scott...
I gave your team
four weeks' leave.
Forget about all this, huh?
Get off base. Get drunk.
Celebrate with that
pretty wife for yours.
I'm putting you up for Major.
With all due respect, sir,
I prefer to remain a captain.
I have in no way
earned a promotion.
Sir.
He didn't buy it.
Neither would I.
That's a bullshit story.
We have to come up
with something better than that
if we want to cover this up.
Don't worry about it.
We've already started
the intel leaks.
Those terrorists will kill
Shannon by the end of the week,
if the Israelis
don't beat them to it.
Thirsty, American?!
Well, then, eat the bucket.
Sakar! No.
Unchain him.
I want to talk to this man.
Please.
Have some brandy.
My religion forbids me,
but I can enjoy
watching you indulge.
I know you didn't bring me up
here to give me a drink.
What are you offering me?
I'm offering you your life.
You can't give me my life back.
God and country...
This I can understand.
Our intelligence services
intercepted this transmission
to the Mossad.
It appears you've been branded
a traitor
by your own CIA.
You'll note the encryption code
matches this week's ciphers.
It is an authentic document.
Sold out by your CIA.
Left for dead by your comrades.
You have only your god left.
Or your god.
Not with that whiskey in you.
Listen, I know you didn't
bring me up here
to give me a sermon.
What do you want?
-We want Haddad back.
-Well, go get him!
We want you to help us get him.
I'm a dead man as soon as my
feet hit American soil.
We'll get you in.
America has always opened
its arms to our tired,
huddled masses.
And what? What, come back here
and wait for the Israelis
to hit me?
-Man, no, thanks.
-We don't want you here.
But with five million tax-free
American dollars
in a Cayman Island account,
you can retire
wherever you want.
A persuasive offer,
don't you think?
Even for a man
without a country.
Do I have to learn the Koran?
Got you some water.
Just put it down.
This thing
is completely stripped.
You should have called
a plumber.
Kel, I know what I'm doing,
will you just hand me
the screwdriver, please.
You want it?
Come get it, soldier boy?
Come on, Kel.
I don't have time for this.
Don't have time, huh?
You got plenty of time.
You've been spending
the last two weeks
making all
these home improvements.
We don't even need them.
What is it you're
really trying to fix?
I don't know what I'm trying
to fix, Kel.
Me, the Army, Shannon.
I mean, somebody sells out
my mission
and I get
my best friend captured.
CIA tells me
that he's a traitor,
which there is no way
that I'm going to believe.
And then Smith gives me a
promotion that I don't deserve.
You think they're lying?
Yeah, I know they're lying.
I know they're lying.
Just don't know
which lies to believe anymore.
Why don't you just quit?
You know,
take an early retirement.
I know, I know, I know, the army
is your life and all that.
No, you're wrong.
It's not.
And anymore.
Kel, I want to get away
from all this, okay?
I want to see the world
instead of shoot at it.
I want to lie
on the beach with you.
What's so funny?
The beach.
This beach.
Right here.
Senator Branford, I really,
really appreciate you coming
on such short notice.
Aw, hell, Scott,
it's good to see you.
Sorry about the office.
Got a hell of a view though.
How's that wife of yours?
Any children yet?
Well, my wife's fine, sir.
Thank you.
And no, no children.
Not yet.
That's good, because
you stepped yourself
into a big ol' pile
of horseshit on this one.
I hate to see you leave any
little ones behind.
-Sir, is it really that bad?
-I've been keeping an eye
on your Ranger unit
for a couple of months now.
All your little incursions
into foreign territory.
What do you call it?
Hunting trips.
Sir, it's my job.
Black Ops. It's what we do.
According to the amended
Constitution of
the United States,
your job is illegal as hell.
Your daddy, my esteemed mentor
in the halls of Congress,
is probably turning over in his
expensive mausoleum right now.
I would say you're probably
right about that, sir.
Now, Scott, we've been turning
our heads, looking the other way
in the interest
of national security.
But this time your brass
gone too far.
They brokered a deal
between the CIA
and a known terrorist leader
named Haddad.
Is any of this ringing a bell?
Yes, sir, Shannon, uh --
Shannon said something about it.
-Shannon -- he was...
He was on assignment
working for the CIA.
Isn't that right?
He intercepted
some transmission, sir,
but he didn't
give me any details.
And you boys left him to die
when you sprung Haddad,
who wasn't supposed to get
sprung -- is that correct?
I have no comment on that, sir.
You know, they're saying
that Shannon went bad.
Yeah, I know
what they're saying, sir.
And begging your pardon,
it's all CIA bullshit.
-They're hiding something.
-Of course they are.
It's a hell of lot easier to
prove if you come on in
and talk to us,
just you and me.
I'll take your deposition
in private.
No one else has to know.
-It's a little risky, sir.
-You know, Scott,
the best piece
of political advice
I ever got was from your dad,
and he got it
from Lyndon Johnson.
It goes like this:
Your ass is up against the wall,
you call the other guy
a horse diddler.
Maybe he ain't, but he's going
to be real busy denying it.
You testify
against those CIA boys,
they're going to be too busy
denying high crimes
and misdemeanors to bother you.
Sir, with all due respect,
I think I
could do more on the inside.
I appreciate you coming.
Watch your ass, Scott.
These spy boys, they...
They play dirty.
And they start to figure out
that you're not believing
their lies,
they're going to take you out.
And that pretty
little wife of yours,
she becomes a widow.
I'll keep you posted, sir.
If you live that long.
[telephone ringing]
-Smith.
-We've got a problem.
-What?
-Shannon's still alive.
Hasn't Mossad tried to
hit him yet?
That's the problem.
They can't find him.
He went to ground 48 hours ago.
I don't care how you do it,
but I want him dead before
he turns up on the evening news.
Or before we do.
You got it?
I've got it.
-I'm ready.
-So am I.
[door opens, closes]
[glass breaks]
[music playing]
Hey, Dell!
Shannon.
Where have you been?
We've been looking for you.
You know, that's funny,
'cause I've been looking for
you, too.
[music playing]
[beeping]
[man] He's dead, sir.
He was literally blown away.
Just --
Just give me the facts.
My full report will be ready
within the hour, sir.
I'll be back on base by morning.
Broughten, thank God.
This is Jim Kenner,
Carter Dell's control at CIA.
Nice to meet you.
What have you got?
We have reason to believe
that our Mideastern friends
have stepped up terrorist
activities in this country
as reprisals for your mission.
If Shannon was working
with them,
he'd naturally go
after high profile
targets in
the intelligence community.
When he was assigned to CIA,
Dell was his control.
-What's his motive?
-Didn't you brief him, Smith?
Shannon's been working
for them all along.
-He's part of their team.
-Could be revenge.
Revenge?
Why didn't he come after me?
He may.
Look, if Vince Shannon is really
working for the terrorists,
I think they're looking
for Haddad.
That's impossible.
He's buried deep.
Did it ever occur to you,
Agent Kenner,
that maybe these killings
are just a decoy to keep us busy
while they spring Haddad?
You could be right,
but it won't happen.
Haddad's been put in the loop,
and they'll never find him.
-Yeah, well, don't bet on it.
-[telephone rings]
Excuse me.
Sorry about your vacation,
but I'm going to need you back
on base by tomorrow night.
Look, if...
If Shannon did grease Dell
to decoy us,
then he'll do it again.
Sir, I'll be back
on base tomorrow night.
But there is no way
that he's turned.
Need I remind you that our
mission is to free Haddad,
not get even
with your former comrades.
Yeah, well, I'm in this
for the money.
We also have an agenda, Captain.
Okay, here's how it works.
By now, Haddad's in the loop.
I have access
to his transport file.
I need to know
where to make the landing.
Eventually,
they'll drop him somewhere
you can find him --
you and your boys
can go in there,
drag his ass out of Dodge
and be back to Mecca
in time for tea.
So why endanger our mission with
your own private war of revenge?
You gave me the background
on these motherfuckers.
What'd you think I'd do?
I made an error in judgment.
Maybe.
You got anybody around here
that can shoot this?
Kamal.
If you compromise this mission,
I'll kill you.
If I compromise this mission,
we're all dead.
We'll see.
Here's what I need you to do,
man.
I don't trust this man.
He's the devil himself
inside him.
He's nothing
more than a tour guide.
When we have Haddad,
the American dies.
Come on, throw it high!
-You're get the hang of this.
-Told ya I just needed practice.
Whoops!
Spoke too soon.
Come on, Mr. Ranger.
Okay. Okay. All right.
Give it to me.
-Ready?
-Yeah.
Oh.
Gotcha!
Nice to see somebody's
having a good time.
How are you doing, Pete?
What's going on?
Just get out of here.
Look, just go, please.
Get out of here!
I'm not going to shoot her,
Pete.
Look, I was under orders.
General Smith gave us
strict instructions
to make sure that you were dead.
Yeah, I know.
They briefed me at Langley.
Smith told me about the mix up.
But we've got more
important things to worry about.
-How'd you get out?
-Forget about that.
Look, Haddad's men have put
a hit squad out after us,
and I have to warn Broughten.
You got a cell phone?
What's the, uh, lock code?
-R-A-N-G-E-R.
-"Ranger?"
That's cute.
[chuckles]
It's good to see you, man.
[dialing]
She seems like a nice girl.
She is. We're getting married.
-I don't think so.
-Oh, Vince --
Pete!
[sobbing]
God, I told you,
it's just routine.
Yeah, well, what am I supposed
to think, Scott, huh?
Kelly, I'm going back
to the base
and I will
call you in a couple of days.
-Can I visit?
-No, you cannot visit.
Stop worrying, all right?
It's just a, um...
It's a paper shuffle.
You got quiet, Scott.
Whenever you're quiet
you have a mission --
and this time you're worse.
Think I'm lying to you?
I don't know what to believe
anymore, Scott.
I guess I'm not sure which lies
to believe, same as you.
[ringing]
-Broughten.
-Scott. How you doing?
Hey, listen. I just popped
a cap in Rogoff's ass.
You're next.
Right after
I go see Alex Fenton.
He still lives
in Hillcrest Heights, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Bye!
-[beeps]
Kelly, I want you
to go upstairs.
And I want you to pack a bag.
And I want you
to go to your mother's.
-Which lies, Scott?
-Just do as I say, please?!
[music playing]
[beeping, ringing]
[woman] David, get that for me,
I'm cooking.
Yeah, yeah, alright, alright,
I hear you.
I didn't marry you for your
cooking, anyway.
[ringing]
Boo, you know where I put
the cellphone?
[woman] I dunno!
Found it for myself.
Yeah, who this?
Fenton! Shannon's alive.
-What?
-He killed Rogoff,
and now he's coming for us.
Get your wife, get out of
that house right now.
Oh, shit!
Boo! Out the back door now!
[screaming, sobbing]
[explosions]
[Mrs. Fenton wailing]
You guys alright?
Yeah, we okay, man.
Who in the hell
just blew up my house?
Wait right here, honey.
Now, last I checked, Shannon
was a dark skinned brother.
That ain't Shannon.
[cellphone ringing]
That is.
Shannon.
Hey, Scott.
How was my guy's aim?
Vince. You know,
when I find you...
You're a dead man.
You know what?
I've got Kelly.
And I'm keeping her
until I figure out where
and when to take you
out of the game.
All right?
See you.
Shannon.
Shannon!
Oh, my God.
Captain?
Alex, I need your help.
Your wife going to be okay?
Yeah, she's a'ight, she's
staying with my grandma.
Here he comes.
Who the hell
is this guy, anyway?
It's a family friend.
Scott.
I wasn't expecting company.
Sergeant Alex Fenton.
He's on my team.
I don't suppose you'd like to
testify before
the Senate subcommittee,
would you, Sergeant?
A guy like me would probably
just freeze up
in front of a crowd.
-Shannon took my wife.
-He also killed the CIA liaison,
-Dell.
-And one of our men,
Pete Rogoff, I might add.
Maybe the CIA didn't set him up.
Maybe he just went bad.
Yeah, well, maybe he's what
they're trying to cover up.
All right,
so what are your plans?
My plan is to find my wife,
get some fucking answers.
Well, CIA finds him first, they
gon' make him disappear.
If you want to get some answers
you better find him
before they do.
If I do that, sitting around
waiting for those answers.
Look, Scott,
if he took your wife,
he wants something from you.
You find out what that is,
you may just survive this game.
You call his hand.
Just make sure
you don't let the CIA sit in.
Captain, we better go.
He'll probably try
to call the base.
You find him, you find Shannon,
you find out what he knows.
You get the information
back to me,
I'll bring you in from the cold.
Both of you.
Come on.
We'll have four choppers later
this afternoon.
You want some coffee, Captain?
[ringing]
[beeps]
General Smith.
General, is Broughten with you?
Let me speak to my wife.
Sure thing, old buddy.
-Scott!
-Kelly?!
That's our show
for today, folks.
Vince, what do you want?
A game.
And this time I'm the house.
Meet me at yours.
What's he mean by
"now I'm the house"?
Poker.
Percentage is always
with the house.
House rules, his rules.
So now what do we do?
We give him a game.
You just wait for him to show up
and put a bullet in your head?
No, sir.
I think he'll do something
with a little more flair.
We'll send along some watchers.
Blocked.
I didn't get it.
Eh, look at this.
Somebody left it
outside the front door.
I tripped over it.
You have kids?
-You don't have kids.
-Give it to me.
[both] Smith!
[music playing]
[indistinct voices,
woman giggling]
[woman] Bye-bye, General.
General Smith,
how you doing?
Shannon.
-We can deal.
-Sure we can. You talk.
I'll hang on your every word.
So why didn't you guys
want Haddad?
The man's a butcher.
Tensions are rising
in the Middle East.
His continued presence
and strength
is a stabilizing influence.
Oh, so, he's a butcher,
but he's our butcher?
So why did you guys send in
Rangers if you didn't want him?
-If he defeated --
-Murdered.
Murdered...
American soldiers...
He'd increase his power base
in the region
thereby fitting in with
our foreign policy objectives.
How do you sleep at night?
There's more to this
than you know.
Others involved.
Issues of national security.
What others?
The Rangers?
All of them?
Rogoff was CIA, not the others.
He was supposed to take you
out personally.
Not Broughten?
Not Alex Fenton?
No.
How are you going to keep
Broughten from asking questions?
We couldn't...
so he was supposed to die.
-Heroically.
-When?
As soon as he found you.
Or as soon as you killed him.
So I've been a patsy
in all this.
We were improvising.
You were very helpful.
That's beautiful.
Very clean.
And you still get a dead hero.
That always helps when you need
additional funding
from Congress, doesn't it?
Another dead Ranger
giving his all for his country.
Rangers are paid to die.
I got a whole new set
of problems to deal with.
Starting with you.
There's a bomb upstairs.
Should be about
two minutes left.
Shannon!
[timer beeping]
[screams]
There he is!
Do me a favor, take out that
car, go for his tires.
Fuck his tires,
I'm goin' for his ass!
You missed every tire
on the car.
-Son of a bitch!
-I'm out!
-Take the wheel!
-Got it!
-You ready?
-All day long.
Move.
Vince!
You want to play?!
Come on!
-Coffee's hot.
-I don't want it.
I brought you two hash browns.
I always like two,
it starches up your day.
Why are you doing this?
Juice?
Why are you doing this,
Goddamn it?!
I thought we were friends.
I thought you and Scott
were friends.
I'm not going to hurt you,
Kelly.
And I'm not going
to let anyone hurt you.
But I need time.
And as long as I have you
I control your husband.
Don't count on it.
[music playing]
-Go.
-Yes, Colonel.
I have lost three good men
to your foolishness.
And to now this little woman.
Psychological warfare,
keeping yo' ass safe,
sound and hidden.
So get off mine.
I have troops waiting off
your Eastern seaboard.
I must have
landing coordinates now.
Right now Haddad is in transit.
What are they taking him?
Within a few hours, we will know
his exact destination.
You'll have
your landing coordinates.
Right now, I'm trying to secure
these trucks you requested.
It takes time.
-Get up!
-[screaming]
Give us Haddad now,
or I shoot this woman!
Hammad, no!
You need me.
To get at Haddad.
I need you
to get out
of this country alive.
Let's build on that
for a better future.
Enough.
Lower your weapons.
Lower them.
He is insane.
His madness is all we have.
Oh! Oh, my God!
Sorry, man, I never -- I never
meant for that to happen.
I never meant for you
to be part of that.
Then, please, just take me back
to him, take me back to him!
I will, I will. I promise.
Just not yet.
When?
If I pull this off,
you and Scott are going to be on
a beach somewhere
making babies
and all of these bastards
will be dead.
You can't keep fucking
with our lives like that.
I don't --
I don't have any choice.
As long as I control the play,
you and Scott stay alive.
You understand what I'm saying?
You threatened him.
You wanted him dead.
I was wrong.
But now his own people
are going to kill him
unless I can warn him.
And to do that,
I need you, Kelly.
It's the only way he's going to
come talk to me without a gun.
His own people?
This is America.
Yeah, America, America,
the beautiful,
salute, the fucking flag.
Except when there's money
and power involved.
What about you? What about
all the people that you killed?
Only the ones that went bad.
We've been set up for months.
It was a rogue CIA scheme
to keep
some Middle Eastern
dictator in power.
They were going to let him
kill a Ranger team
on a failed kidnapping.
And I thought Scott
was involved.
Scott would never have anything
to do with that.
You should know that.
Has he said anything that you.
Mm.
He said, uh...
He said he didn't know
which lies to believe any more.
Believe mine.
And Scott's going to get out of
this bloodbath alive.
I have, uh...
Really fucked this up.
And I gotta...
try and stop what I started.
You just got to trust me.
You never knew when to give up.
[chuckles]
I gave up on you.
Thanks for making me
not have to choose.
You never were good at
making decisions anyway, right?
Go to hell.
I'm there already.
Why would Shannon kill
General Smith?
Revenge, maybe.
I mean, Smith is the guy
that sends us in on the mission.
-I think Smith knew something.
-I think you're right.
I think Shannon killed him
for some answers.
The question is, did he get
the answers he wanted?
That means we've got
to find him.
-We will.
-Don't count on it.
With Smith dead and Shannon
full of secrets,
they're going to
want you involved.
They don't want you
to beat them to him.
Why do you keep saying they?
I mean, who are they?
The agency?
It's a big question,
isn't it, Alex?
I think it's a rogue operation.
Too many outsiders
for an agency deal.
They like to keep things
in the family.
We're seeing Kenner later on,
how do you want to play that?
Play it straight.
Frightened.
Very frightened
for your wife -- and angry.
That's not going to be
too difficult.
Play a patriotic,
undying loyalty
to your commanding officer.
You know, General Smith
was your C.O. all that,
they'll take you off the case
for your own good.
You argue with them, then get
the hell out of the office.
-And then what?
-Use yourselves as bait.
He's got watchers out there.
He'll know that
you're off the case.
He'll find you.
Just make sure he does.
-Where are we?
-The truck. Relax.
[man]
Welcome to Atlanta, gentlemen,
you can go right through
holding cells downstairs.
Thanks.
Gentlemen, I'm afraid we're
gonna have to pull you
in out of the cold on this.
It's too dangerous.
We've lost too many good men.
Wait a minute.
What about my wife?
It's not too dangerous for her.
Truly sorry about that.
We're doing everything
we possibly can.
Yeah, I'll bet. Listen,
Kenner, we're the only ones
who have
a chance of getting Shannon.
-'Less you don't want him found.
-I want you both to return
to standard duties
until further notice.
Hey.
You're not my C.O.
That was Smith.
And you bastards got him killed.
So I am through taking orders
from CIA. You got that?
-And what about you?
-What do you mean,
what about me?
Listen, Agent Kenner,
officially we're still on leave,
okay, so dig this.
All right, here's a 20.
Take this.
Take you and Phil Drummond from
"Different Strokes" here,
and you guys going to have
a lap dance on me?
Okay? Hey, could somebody order
these two some Viagra?
Cute.
Still planning
to use them as bait?
-[cellphone rings]
-Get a surveillance van ready.
Kenner.
-So what's next?
-What's next for who?
-You're going home?
-I don't have a home anymore,
in case you forgot,
there's nothing left there
but a parking lot
full of dirty drawers
and burnt up girlie magazines
I've been hiding from my wife.
[cellphone rings]
-Broughten.
-It's Shannon.
The Sake House.
You know where it is?
Yeah. 13th and Hudson.
Meet me there in 20 minutes.
Unarmed.
He's coming.
Shannon.
Yeah.
So I guess this means
I'm still in.
Well, I guess this means
you don't blame me
when you take a bullet.
Sound like my mother
at the family reunion.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
-Alex, take Kelly outside.
-Come on.
No, no, no. I want you to listen
to what Vince has to say.
-Alex, take her outside, please.
-What's the matter, Scott?
You can't sit down
and have a drink with a friend.
All my friends are dead, Vince.
They weren't your friend.
Those people sent us over there
to die for a greater glory
of a new world order.
All the proof is on this disk.
Scott, please, just listen
to what he has to say.
Okay? Come on. Sit down.
Come on.
I thought you two
were in on it,
but the late general
set me straight.
Set you straight? Negro,
you blew up my fucking house!
[punch lands]
I made a mistake.
It happens when you have to sort
through the kind of lies
that can kill people.
Now I have
to pick up the pieces.
Vince, what are you talking
about?
I'm talking about
saving your life.
These people want you dead too.
You guys need to disappear,
and there's a million tax-free
dollars in it for you
if you do it now.
And just stay out of my way
until this is over.
I can't do it.
I'm still a ranger.
And you always will be, Scotty.
Alex?
I mean, $1,000,000 could help me
get my house back, but...
I'm with him.
Shit.
Okay, let's go outside.
I could at least tell you
what I know up till now.
There's five players in
this game:
Dell, Smith, Haddad,
Rogoff, and one more.
Sure he's in there?
He's in there.
That's him.
Let's take him.
[gunshots]
-You okay?
-Yeah.
What the hell didn't
you shoot him?
Because he told us to come
unarmed, asshole.
-Weren't you listening?
-Report, Lieutenant!
Man, you ain't talking to me.
I'm still on leave.
Dude.
Fuck.
Kenner, he called you asshole.
[music playing]
Got it.
-You know where Haddad is held?
-The money first.
Transferred once my troops
are onshore
and after you tell me
where Haddad is held.
Okay.
You land your troops right here
just above Daytona.
Quiet beach, rarely used.
I have the trucks waiting.
This is good news.
Very good news.
I wish you were an idealist.
Listen...
We played each other real well,
so let's just leave it at that.
Besides, I'm a madman.
You said so yourself.
Yes, I did.
So what the hell did
Shannon tell you?
Look, he tried to buy us off,
okay?
But I don't
accept personal checks.
-Nothing else?
-No, nothing else. Why?
Because I got an email
from Shannon tonight,
and he knows we've sent Haddad
down to Atlanta.
And Atlanta is an unsecured stop
on the loop.
No, not Shannon. I know him.
He's trying to warn us.
Jakar, the landing is
tomorrow night.
Copy that. We're 12 hours
from the U.S. coast.
Stand by for coordinates.
Grid 405.
Section G-six.
Come on. It's time to go.
I'm afraid.
Well, if Shannon's right,
they're not going to try
anything until after this
is over, so...
You'll be safe at your mom's.
Hey...
Forgot to show you this.
A resignation letter.
I hope you find the time to send
it some day.
I already did.
It's effective
two weeks from today.
Oh!
Any regrets?
Yeah -- that I waited so long
to send it.
[man] Your attention, please.
We need all streets cleared
between Peachtree and Broadway.
All streets cleared between
Peachtree and Broadway.
Well, drop more leaflets
if you have to,
I want a four block radius
cleared by sunset,
clear the killing field.
-Where's Haddad?
-He's in a holding cell
-downstairs under heavy guard.
-Whaddya mean, downstairs?
Kenner, the guy doesn't need to
be here.
They just need
to think he's here.
Shannon is still into
our mainframe.
If we pull him out now,
they'll know about it
and they won't come.
What're we telling the networks?
We're playing this
as a bomb scare.
Oh, nice and neat, huh?
Always tell the truth.
It's the best kind of lie.
You see them?
They're coming.
[fires flare]
-You feel the excitement?
-Yeah.
[indistinct shouting]
You too, can learn
how to drive the big rigs.
Damn!
Looks like we got ourselves
a monster truck
rally going out there.
What's the status?
Sat recon just confirmed
that a large truck convoy
just passed
the Jonesborough interchange?
Look, while we just sent
an airstrike,
torch 'em on the ground and have
barbecued terrorists
for dinner tonight?
Yeah, that's a nice thought,
Alex.
I tell you what, why don't we go
with trying to trap them
in a confined space,
though, huh?
That might be a little safer
for everybody, don't you think?
Man, if you say so.
I want to burn people.
Man, these guys are hauling
and heading right for us.
I'll check in.
Give me Central Command.
Let's go!
Get the trucks! Hurry!
Hurry, move quickly.
Very efficient work.
-Yeah, $5 million worth.
-Let's go.
Yeah. Right.
Just a few blocks now.
Alright, Alex, you tell 'em one
more time,
token resistance only,
they fire a few warning shots,
-they get the hell out of there.
-You got it, Captain.
Steady.
Now!
Commence fire!
Commence fire now!
It seems they were
expecting us.
They probably picked us up
on satellite. Don't worry.
They haven't had enough time
to mount any kind of defense.
For your sake I hope so.
[indistinct shouting]
Now go! In the building!
Go!
Just outside.
Get ground team out of there.
Pull out. Pull out now.
They're coming up here,
it's time to split.
We're picking up a chopper.
All right, that's enough.
Kenner, you call in
that main strike force.
-Let's go.
-Sounds like a plan to me.
Take us down for final approach.
[gunfire]
Move in main force.
It's a trap!
Get out! Get out!
Put down your weapons
immediately
or we will be forced to
open fire.
You have 10 seconds to put
down your weapons.
Five seconds, four,
three, two, one.
[gunfire]
-Sounds like a war outside.
-It's the last remnants
of a National Guard force.
They haven't got a chance.
Where are all the agents?
The guards?
Now, just what the hell does
a general evacuation
mean to you, Colonel?
-They had a little warning.
-They will have taken Haddad.
Maybe.
Those are your friends
outside, right?
The only thing I have to tell
you is I have nothing to say.
Alright.
Yo, my man. Do me a favor.
Tell Elvis I said hey.
Whoo!
[humming]
-Thank you very much!
-What is that?
I don't know.
But I got money to spend,
so don't hold me up --
Haddad's just up ahead.
-If you betray me...
-Take a pill.
Short man, Mr. Spock, follow me.
-Finish your work upstairs?
-All me, baby.
-They're not going anywhere.
-I got 'em.
-They're near the holding cells.
-You sure?
-Uh-huh.
-All right, let's move.
Please allow me to express
my apologies
for any inconveniences
you may have suffered, sir.
No inconvenience.
My men will kill you.
Indeed we will.
Hang on, Colonel. How do you
expect to get out of here alive?
You're losing the war outside.
I suspected as much.
-Continue.
-I want you to take Haddad
out safely --
we don't want him here.
Shannon's Rangers were supposed
to die in your backyard,
-Haddad, remember?
-That was our arrangement
until you betrayed us.
I just killed two of my men
for you.
Now, we all want you in power.
Haddad, it was a mistake.
I've heard what I came for.
You getting any of this, Scott?
I got it all, Vince.
There's our fifth player.
-That's right.
-All right, so let him go,
buddy, we got enough
to put him away for life.
It's not just me.
It's Bradford.
Senator Bradford?!
You know what he's talking
about?
Kenner, that's bullshit!
He's investigating you!
Investigation -- Christ,
Bradford's running
the entire operation.
He has oil interests
in Haddad's country.
He wants Haddad back there
as bad as we do.
They played us like cards,
Scott.
Nothing matters to them as long
as they keep the game going.
Yeah, 'cause the game is
all that matters.
You finish up here,
I'm going after Shannon.
All right, Goddamn it.
Let's get this shit over with.
Woo! 4.5 seconds.
A new ghetto record.
Now let me see your fucking
hands, bee-otch!
All right, Vince!
That's enough! Drop the gun!
It's too late for that.
I've done too much.
Somebody is going to have
to take the fall for this.
-We got Kenner!
-That's bullshit!
You know
it won't happen like that.
I'm getting
the hell out of here.
I can't let you do that.
I guess you can't.
Hey, man, you can't take
that bus!
Out! Move!
Don't do this, Scott.
Get outta the way!
Alright, Vince. I call.
Come on, Scott!
Fold your hand!
Don't make me kill you!
I'm out!
[tires squealing]
[train horn blaring]
[groaning]
I hate to leave loaded guns
lying around.
You didn't have to take it
this far, Vince.
I'm okay.
Was a big game.
I had to stay in it.
I wanted the bad guys,
the girl and the money.
You got the bad guys.
You got the girl.
Bank card.
[music playing]
[wheezing]
Hello, Senator.
Hi, Scott.
How's your wife?
My wife is fine.
Thank you, sir.
Good.
Hell of a set to down there in
Atlanta, huh?
It's a pity we lost Shannon.
I guess it had to be.
That's too bad.
Evidence died with him.
Could have had those bastards.
I don't suppose you'd change
your mind
about coming in to testify?
Well, as a matter of fact,
I already have, sir.
Tell me I'm not dreaming,
Scott, are we really here?
This beautiful beach resort away
from everything.
Just you and I.
Kel, I think we made it.
What cost,
though, I'm still not sure.
Oh, here.
Thank you very much.
Now, hold on.
Thank you.
To Vince.
I agree.
[music playing]