[ Horse Whinnies ]
[ Cows Lowing ]
[ Man ]
Uhh. Iowa gangster blood thugs.
Ghetto-rollin'.
Comin' for that ass
in the 2G.
What?
This ain't no "G."
This ain't no "G", nigga.
Tryin' to be sick with me, man?
I'm-a blast you.
I'm-a blast you!
[ Imitating Gunfire ]
Yeah. Now you know
not to fuck with
Flip Dogg anymore.
[ Man Laughing ]
Uh-uh. Don't do that.
No, no, no, don't do that, man.
No, no, don't touch
the dial, man.
Hey, check it out, man.
* You know
the West Coast Riders
get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside *
* You know them Down South
Posses get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside *
* You know them East Coast
Ballers get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside *
* You know them Midwest Robbers
get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside *
* It's jam-packed
and you know
gettin' rowdy outside *
* You got niggas in time
for a long-ass time *
* Makin' everybody
hella mad *
* So people started bouncin'
and smashin' the gat *
* Actin' bad, breakin' glass
in their path *
* The monkey's ass
swingin' doughnuts
in front of the club *
* Lookin' for love
Blowin' up a dub *
* And a powdered voice
snortin' the crank *
* Pretty women at the bar
havin' drinks, people dancin'
till they fight the song *
* Give a dog a bone
boogie in the zone *
* Touchdown, we clown
We can paint the whole town *
* Running your mouth
will get you knocked out
Ballin' during a drought *
* And we'll kill or steal
on any account *
* Blastin' out the parking lot
we spark the chops *
* Burnin' rubber
up and down the block *
* With my tires screechin'
Ain't nobody trippin'
on the policemen *
* But I could see
some more creepin'
Clubbin' on the weekend *
* I'm never surprised to see
the people that was chillin' *
** [ Continues, Indistinct ]
* They bought the hoorah
they gettin' rowdy outside *
* You know them West Coast
Riders get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside *
* You know them Down South
Posses get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside *
* You know them East Coast
Ballers get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside *
* You know them Midwest Robbers
get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside *
* B-I-E-I-itch *
* I will never switch *
* You heard me *
* I'm gonna stay rowdy
I'm about to bounty for
those that like the dough *
* And like to smoke
I'm gonna let you know *
* If you got weed
let's blow the house down *
* Blow the house down
blow the house down *
* Now if you got mail
let's buy the whole town *
* And I'll pass it
to your phonies *
* You heard me *
* I'm gonna let you know *
* Taint her, invade her
niggas can't fade her *
* Quick to smoke a quarter pound
in the town *
* Look you in the eye
reply, I ain't high *
* But help me focus
through the hocus-pocus *
* You know them West Coast
Riders get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside *
* You know them Down South
Posses get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside *
* You know them East Coast
Ballers get rowdy outside *
* Rowdy outside
rowdy outside **
- * Check it, check it-- uhh *
- ** [ Mouth Percussion ]
* One, two, and I
drop lyrics like this *
* I be the "F" to the "L"
to the "I" to the "P" *
* Destroyin' motherfuckers
yeah, that's my hobby *
* Any sucker emcee
wanna come test me *
* I'll put a bullet in your ass
with my fuckin' Uzi *
* Niggas get killed
tryin' to bite my steam *
* My main nigga Trev
yo, pass the 40 *
What?
* So I can loose and bust
niggas out the frame *
* Don't even try to trip
because Flip be my name *
* Yo, my name is Funky Trevor
Don't fuck with me, never *
* You step in my way, and, boy
your head'll get severed *
Yeah!
* I keep my TEC-9 on my waist
'cause I'm a gangster *
* If you try to pop shit
I'll fuckin' gank ya *
* Nickel-plates 38s and 22s *
* Measure your shit next to me
son, you'll fuckin' lose *
* Got my Philly blunts
plus my 40-ounce brews *
What?
* Hop in the Dually, word up
and then I cruise *
* I say, unemployment checks
could suck my fuckin' dick *
[ Both ] What?
* That nigga Bryant Gumbel
makes me fuckin' sick *
* Sittin' at his desk, he
talkin' mad fuckin' shit *
* Like la-la-la-la-lot of shit
It's fuckin' bullshit *
* Yeah, my I.G.B.T. kids
always make the stack *
* I got the remedy for them
fiends that smoke crack *
* Fuck bein' white
Word up, son, I'm black *
* My niggas is in the front
while you be in the back **
Motherfucker.
Yo, deal, dog.
That shit was fuckin' all that.
Represent every day
up in this mugli.
That shit
was fuckin' real.
I fuckin' messed it--
You ripped it, man.
I messed fuckin'
my rhymes right now.
That shit was real, man.
I feel--
I feel energized.
Word up, man. Like fuckin'
electrical-type shit.
Hell, yeah, dog!
You know what I'm sayin'?
That shit is just comin' out
like little particles
coming out of your lungs.
Yo, mugli.
You know what though?
Splat!
Let me just say
one thing, man.
What's up, dog?
Like, don't take this
as a dis, right?
No, word.
I'm sayin', like, all of us,
but mostly like you, man,
and you,
you need to, like,
work on, like, the way
you spit lyrics, man,
like, more articulate,
'cause it sounds
kind of, like, mushed up.
Man, that shit is, like,
flowin' out of my fuckin' heart
when I'm doin' that, dog.
I know, but you
sound like Wayne Newton
up in that motherfucker.
Oh, shit, dog.
I don't mean
to dis, man.
Hello. Uh, this is Sara Miller
calling on behalf of Offline
long-distance company.
The purpose of my call is
to let you know that Offline
does have some new discounts...
available on
long-distance rates.
I'm gonna go blast
some fools, dog.
All right, man, hold up.
All right, dude.
I'm seein' them.
When would be a good time
to call, sir?
Yo, I'm gettin'
the white Pumas.
That shit's tight.
Yeah, they just came out.
Hello.
Check her out.
Half an hour.
Right here.
[ Girl Laughing ]
Yo, dog,
your mom's so stupid,
it took her, like, an hour
to make minute rice.
Man, that shit's corny, man.
That's old.
I'm-a tell you, your mom's
got no legs and still tryin'
to kick it to me.
[ Trevor ]
That's stupid.
That is stupid.
Y'all fools got to come to
Chicago with me. Word up.
You really going to Chicago?
Hell, yeah,
I'm gonna be there, man.
You know I'm gonna be up there.
I'm gonna get paid,
cool out with my shorty.
Whoa, man.
Damn, baby.
Yo, let's get this shit,
go to the club, dog.
Man, save me one.
Pay the bill.
I wrote you
a little somethin'.
Word. What?
You know. A little rhyme
or whatever.
* Commercial rap niggas
get they dope stacked out *
* We're tired of
these earthlings
actin' like they're cowards *
* When you fuck up
we gettin' down for hours *
* Cold, sly, million niggas
skyin' like twin towers **
Yo, I'm ready for this shit,
dude. Fuck this, man.
Hell, yeah, dog. What's that
fuckin' sign say, dog?
Where?
Hold on.
What's up, girl?
All right.
She fuckin'
waved to me, dog.
Man, she ain't
wavin' at you, man.
What the fuck, man?
She was wavin', like,
"Get the fuck out of here."
Nah, man. She fuckin'
was smilin', man. She was
fuckin' wavin' at me.
All right, whatever.
Check, check, check.
One, two, and you don't.
Look at this motherfucker.
This is it right here.
J., man, park.
Yeah, this is the fuckin' deal
right here. I'm gonna get my
motherfuckin' swerve on. Word.
Yeah,
straight up, dog.
Mmm-mmm.
I smell cash blew up
in this motherfucker.
Hell, yeah.
You smell cash?
Yeah, boy.
You wanna get some?
Straight up, dog.
You ready to get some?
I'm ready
to get it, dog.
[ Bottle Shatters ]
Obey your thirst, nigga.
[ People Chattering ]
** [ Rap Playing, Muted ]
** [ Rap, Indistinct ]
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
Yo, man.
What's up?
How much we got, dog?
Only around 200. About.
I think Trev's about
to bring two more.
I got this fine-ass bitch
outside, gave me
a hundred-dollar bill and shit.
Why the fuck didn't you
bring her in, dog?
It's the men's room, fool.
So what?
Yo, how many she need?
Five, man.
Five?
Shit, man, here.
Come on, hurry up.
All right, don't bring
no more people, all right?
We're almost out of here.
All right, dude.
Let me count that shit, dog.
Chill. What,
you don't believe me?
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, motherfucker!
I don't know what you sold me,
but this shit ain't blow, man.
Nah, man, I swear this shit
is real, man. I swear, yo.
Bullshit, man.
I've had cocaine before.
I know the difference.
I'm not some stupid little
dumb-ass, motherfucker.
This is not coke.
This is fuckin' flour.
- You sold me fuckin'
baking flour!
- No, no, no, man.
I want my money!
Aaah! Fuck, man!
Give me my money now,
or I'll kick the shit out of
you, you little cocksucker.
Yo, man, I'm sorry.
All sales is final.
Gimme my money!
[ Grunts ]
Aw, fuck!
Yo, motherfucker!
What the fuck is up, dog?
Why don't you just back
the fuck up right now, dog?
I will fuckin' blast you, dog!
I will fuckin'-- You fuckin'
candy-coated ass bitch.
[ Man ]
What you gonna
do with that, huh?
** [ Hip-Hop ]
** [ Rapping, Indistinct ]
Please, Don Flip.
It's-- It's all there.
[ Man ]
What do you take us for,
a bunch of idiots?
- Don Flip, what are we
gonna do with this guy, huh?
- You disrespect the Don.
No!
Kiss my shoe.
- It's delicious.
- [ Laughing ]
Uhh!
Yeah, motherfucker.
What?
Yo, motherfucker,
what the fuck is up, dog?
Why don't you just back
the fuck up right now, dog?
I will fucking blast you, you
fucking candy-coated ass bitch.
- What you gonna do
with that, huh?
- [ Screams ]
[ Screams ]
[ Shouting, Indistinct ]
What's your
fucking problem?
- Let's get the fuck out!
- [ Whimpering ]
[ Chattering ]
* Yeah, I be
the illest motherfucker
that you ever seen around *
* I get down, I drop suckers
to the ground *
* Yeah, I got juice *
* I got so much juice
I'm gettin' loose *
* You could call me Bruce *
* Willis **
Thank you.
Thank you, all my fans.
All my millions of fans.
It's Flip Dogg
on the M-I-C.
What you thought
it was, fool?
Yeah. "Beeyatch."
Uhh!
Thank you, Jay.
Thanks a lot, Jay.
You little fucker.
[ Imitates Gunfire ]
Yeah. It's all good.
I know what you're
thinking, Jay.
You're thinking, how is it
this white dude could be
such a dope rapper, right?
Well, truth of
the matter is, Jay,
I ain't white, man.
I'm black. See, I went to
the doctor, Jay. This is
between you and me, man.
And he told me I got this,
like-- like, this rare
skin disorder.
It's called, like,
eosinophilic ionic
dermatitis, right?
And it's, like,
where you look white, okay?
But inside, dude--
Like, all right,
check this out, Jay.
Like, you think that's
a birthmark, right?
Truth of the matter is,
like, that's the real color
of my skin, and the rest of me
is a birthmark.
This shit is mad rare, Jay.
It's mad rare.
I mean, even though
I live in Iowa, I still got
the ghetto in my heart, Jay.
I mean, this is just
temporary, you know?
I'm-a move, man.
You know, I don't belong
here, you know? As soon as
I, like, get some money,
I'm just gonna, like,
move to some straight-up,
like, ghetto, gangster, thug,
projects-type shit, you know?
Like in Chicago, like, you know,
like, the people just kick it.
And just, like, chill
in their BMWs every day.
And, like, you know,
drive around and just party.
Like, all the girls got
bikinis on. Everybody just,
you know, raps.
You know what I'm sayin', Jay?
Where, like, the niggers
just kick it, Jay.
Don't get me wrong, Jay.
When I say "nigger," I don't
mean it in the ill way,
you know, like,
"Oh, you fuckin' nigger,"
or some shit like that.
You know, you just chillin'.
You just kickin' it with
your homeys or whatever.
You just be, like,
"What's going on,
you bitch-ass nigga?"
You know, it's all good, Jay.
It's all love, man,
strictly love.
[ Woman ]
Flip!
What?
The money's not
on the fridge.
Not the fridge!
The microwave!
Oh, don't forget to pick
your dad up from work.
Damn!
Leave me the fuck alone.
I hate this place, Jay.
Bunch of tractor-drivin'
motherfuckers.
Damn biscuit-head bitches.
Man, you got to see
these people, man.
All they do is hang out
at the mall every day...
and walk back and forth
from Footlocker to Chi-Chi's,
Chi-Chi's to Footlocker.
Then they go home
and watch damn... Friends.
Those are whack
fucking activities, Jay.
Are you with me, man?
I mean, I don't aspire
to that in my life, dude.
I want fucking--
I want--
I mean, what the hell
I wanna be white for, man?
That shit is stupid.
[ Machinery Whirring, Hissing ]
[ Horn Honks ]
[ Whistle Blows ]
- Hey, there, Flip.
- Whassup?
How's your mom?
She's all right.
You tell your mom
I said hi.
All right.
What'd you say?
My dick.
Hate to do this, Art.
You've been with us
damn near 25 years.
The company's
out of money.
Hey, Dad.
You all right?
No.
J.
Ah, whassup, nigga?
All right?
Whassup?
What you got to eat,
man? I'm starvin'.
** [ Rock ]
Damn, man, tell your moms
to get some Wonder Bread.
At least then you have something
to put the Cheese Whiz on.
Why don't you
shut the fuck up, man?
Last time I was in your fridge,
all I saw was some, like,
baking soda and
the motherfuckin' lightbulb.
Man, shut up. Why don't we
get some munch for real?
Swing us by Hucky's, you know?
- Get that employee discount.
- Fuck Hucky's.
I'm sick of that fuckin' place,
dog. I'm tryin' to make me
some fuckin' loot, baby.
I hear that. I got the plan.
Some Master P. shit, you know?
That's what I'm sayin', man.
See, see, the plans, dog.
That's what I'm thinkin'.
I-I got thoughts, man.
What?
What, you gonna be a rapper?
Nigga can't rap for shit.
Word. You know
you can't rap, J.
Man, fuck you, man.
I can rap.
I'm not talking about
no rapping shit.
Man, I'm telling you, man,
we could be making cake, baby.
With what?
Some crank, dog.
Crank?
Yeah, baby.
You are some
redneck shit, man.
Leave that shit to them
Denny's-eatin' biscuit-heads.
Man, fuck you, man!
Man, fuck you
and your redneck shit.
I ain't no motherfuckin'
redneck, all right, dog?
Oh, no? Then what are you
listening to this shit for?
You better--
Dog, don't fuckin'
push my buttons so hard.
That shit is some pimp shit,
man. You need to be easy
with that shit.
[ Imitating Electric Guitar ]
You know how fucking old
that shit is, dog?
That's some fucking retro shit.
Don't fuck with my shit.
Don't press the buttons
all hard, dog.
Back to the future, baby.
CDs, all right?
You know what, man?
That's what you were fucking
listening to in your mom's
fucking stomach, dog.
Some fuckin' essence.
That's some essence-type shit
right there, baby.
Essence of what?
Essence, man.
That's your roots.
That shit is old. That's
prehistoric, all right?
You might as well
rub some rocks together
and make a fire, okay?
I'm sayin' rap is
gonna change the world.
That's expression, dude.
Where do you think hip-hop
came from, dog?
Oh, my God!
Some rock shit, dog.
All this hard-core,
hip-hop dada,
that's all some fucking--
[ Imitates Electric Guitar ]
It's the same Master P. shit.
Like in your shit--
Like you wanna just fuckin'
break some shit up, dog.
That's expression, dog.
Ex-pres-si-on.
What are you expressing, man?
It's not that straight-up,
hard-core, ghetto shit.
Dog, ghetto shit is-- Yo,
you don't think motherfuckers...
who are in the fucking ghetto
are playing the guitar?
Motherfuckers are in the ghetto
playing the guitar, man.
You been there?
So you don't know.
See, you a redneck.
You thinkin' redneck mentality.
Man, you gotta get out
of that shit, man.
Man--
You gotta get out
of that shit, man.
Fuck you, man.
You my nigga, right?
Yeah, I'm your nigger, dog.
That's what I'm sayin'.
So chill, then.
I'm sayin' you need to respect
my fucking taste, dog.
'Cause I got taste, dog.
All right, man.
I got me
some motherfuckin' taste.
Let's go get something
to eat, man, all right?
All right?
All right, man.
I'm just sayin'.
All right.
Chill, chill.
It's all good.
And don't push my motherfuckin'
buttons so hard.
Yo. All right, man.
Fuckin' old-ass,
eight-track bullshit.
Don't fuck
with my shit, dog.
Let's go.
** [ Rap, Indistinct ]
Hey, Mom,
Flip and James are here.
Hey, Mrs. M.
Mr. M.
What's going on,
Mr. M?
Have you boys
had dinner yet?
Not really.
Well, we've already eaten,
but there's plenty left over,
if you'd like some.
All right.
Man, y'all a bunch of
hungry, beggin' bastards.
Yo, don't curse in front
of your moms, dude.
Help yourselves.
Fix up some plates.
There's, um, mashed potatoes,
chicken, iced tea,
apple juice, sodas.
Yo, man, don't take
everything, dude.
Yo, put them back,
man. Aw, man.
What's up with your moms,
dog? Straight up
and down, man.
I think she-- Yo, she was,
like, giving me
the mashed potatoes, dog,
and I wanted to take
the mayonnaise and, like,
uhh--
spread some shit
up on some sauce-the-pan
type shit, dog.
Why the fuck you always got
to talk about my moms, man?
I'm just sayin',
your mom is straight up.
Your mom is--
She's a "MILF," dog.
She's
a straight-up MILF.
What's a fucking MILF?
A MILF is...
a "mother
I'd like to fuck."
[ Laughs ]
You know what
I'm sayin', dog?
Hell, yeah, dog!
What's up, man?
'Cause I'd be like this--
** [ Rap, Indistinct ]
Uhh!
Yeah, dog.
All right.
[ Woman ]
* That's the way *
* The real hustlers play *
[ Fades ]
* The real hustlers **
[ Man ]
12-gauge. Back in the 97.
All the way to
the 2000G, baby.
Come on.
This little brother, baby.
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
* Pimps in the front
freaks in the back *
* Pushing your Lexus
and Cadillacs *
* So pimp it up, pimp it up
players, pimp it up *
* All the players in the house
pimp it up *
Break it up, yo, kick it.
* I'm pimping my mind
I pimp before my time *
* I write pimp rhymes
and run pimp lines *
** [ Continues, Indistinct ]
* Pimps in the front
freaks in the back *
* Pushing your Lexus
and Cadillacs *
* So pimp it up, pimp it up
players, pimp it up *
* All the players in the house
pimp it up *
* Pimps in the front
freaks in the back *
* Pushing your Lexus
and Cadillacs *
* So pimp it up, pimp it up
players, pimp it up *
* All the players in the house
pimp it up *
- * This is how we roll *
- * This is how we roll, yeah *
** [ Vocalizing ]
[ James ]
What's up, dog?
What's going on?
** [ Rap ]
[ Chattering, Hooting ]
Khalid!
What's going on, player?
What's up, dog?
I see you're
gettin' your drink on, huh?
You know what's up, Trev.
- This is straight,
no chaser, baby.
- Is that a new pair of And 1's?
Hell, yeah, dog.
I got 'em last week.
You like?
Them pups is all good,
you know.
Them pups?
Yeah, you know. Pups.
Yeah, you pups is
all good, Khalid.
[ Barks ]
What?
- [ Barks ]
Man, shut the fuck up!
You motherfuckers sound
like a bunch of damn hicks.
Fuckin' dumb motherfuckin'
hick-ass bastards.
[ Khalid ] Chill, dog.
Whatever, dog.
Damn. At least we
didn't get left back.
[ Khalid ]
Oh, shit.
What?
Yo, yo,
he's only playing, dog.
What the fuck
did you say?
What's up, man?
Come on, Motherfucker.
[ Khalid ]
Yo, yo, Flip Dogg!
[ Shouting, Indistinct ]
Come here.
Come here, man!
Yeah! Yeah! Say that shit,
you gotta back up
them words, bitch.
You wouldn't last a minute
in Compton, fool. Motherfucker!
[ Scoffs ]
Yeah, you know how we do.
What?
Flip.
What y'all lookin' at, huh?
Go back to your little
cow-tippin' stories now.
Flip, you ain't
never been to Cali.
[ Tsks ]
Yeah, but I know
what it's like, all right?
All right. Hey.
Hey, I love that rhyme
you wrote for me.
Do ya?
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
[ Clinton On TV ] I did have a
relationship with Miss Lewinsky
that was not appropriate.
[ Sara ] Stop. Flip.
In fact, it was wrong.
It constituted a critical
lapse in judgment...
and a personal failure
on my part--
Stop.
Flip.
[ TV Continues,
Indistinct ]
Flip.
Look, pull out
and put something on.
Oh, my God.Flip.
Chill.
[ Flip Moaning ]
Flip.
[ Groans ]
I got it.
[ Moaning ]
[ Panting ]
And I intend to reclaim
my family life for my family.
It's nobody's business
but ours.
Even presidents
have private lives.
It's not funny, Flip.
Aw, come on.
M'kay?
Don't.
Sara, come on.
Don't make me.
[ Giggles ]
Don't, don't.
You know I will.
Don't. Come on. Ow!
Quit it. Move over too.
You take up the whole bed.
Oh, what?
I got to move over?
It's my bed.
Yo, you take it all up too.
[ Sighs ]
I'm tired.
I wrote another rhyme
for you.
Let me hear it.
Read it to me.
Nah.
Come on. Read it to me.
I ain't finished
with it yet.
I'm, like, two-thirds
or, like--
I'm, like, five-eighths
done with it.
[ Laughs ]
Well, let me hear
the beginning.
All right.
Okay.
It goes like this.
M'kay?
[ Giggles ]
Come on.
Whassup? I'm sayin'
I'm thugged out. What?
You ain't no fun.
That's the problem.
No, you ain't no fun.
You don't let me read no shit.
You won't let me tickle you.
[ Mocking ]
Mmm-mm-mm.
I've heard it
all before.
You gonna come
visit me in college?
Visit you? Come on, Sara,
I'm gonna live up there.
What?
I'm sayin', ain't nobody
producin' no rap
up in this motherfucker.
You ain't livin' in my dorm room
with my three roommates.
[ Scoffs ]
Come on.
I'll find some shit.
And then once
I get a record deal,
Mm-hmm.
we could get a place
together, all right?
Why don't you get a job?
You could save some money
and then come out.
Sara, do I look like
I belong here?
All right?
What I'm-a do?
Stand and serve burgers
to some fat, fried-lookin'
motherfuckers?
[ Laughing ]
I'm serious.
I'm talkin' about this,
you know?
I mean, I just
want people to--
I wanna make people see
the truth, you know?
It's like shit they don't wanna
see, just like straight-up,
hard-core ghetto shit.
You know,
just like the truth.
People are ignorant here.
People are ignorant
in Chicago too, Flip.
But in Chicago, they're
livin' the real shit,
all right?
Cabrini-Green.
Cabrini what?
It's these projects up there.
Brothers keep it real
up in there.
And you wanna go there?
That's what I am.
I'm about it.
What do you expect me to do?
You act like I'm an idiot.
[ Woman ] I don't think
you're an idiot. I think there
are plenty of jobs out there.
You'll find something.
Bullshit!
What's up, Ma?
You wanna help me out
with this?
Ma, when is supper
gonna be ready?
I got stuff to do.
What the hell's
wrong with you, boy?
I'm having a conversation
with your mother here.
I'm tryin' to support
a goddamn family,
and all you want to do
is play video games.
It's not video games.
I don't care
what the hell it is!
What the hell is this?
What?
Where the hell did you
get this outfit?
I bought it.
With what?
What? Speak up!
I didn't hear you!
- Are you the man
of the house?
- Art, please.
You don't have half
the sense to jerk off, and now
you're the man of the house.
I must really be the fool.
I'm a jackass, aren't I?
- What a jackass!
- [ Glass Shatters ]
** [ Rap, Indistinct ]
* A lot of niggas don't like me
I don't really
give a fuck though *
* 'Cause I'll just
shoot your ass
Keep shootin' ya *
* Yeah, makin' lots of money
lots of cash, lots of hos **
What are you,
a nigger now?
[ Woman ]
Excuse me.
I ordered a chicken combo,
but I asked for ribs
instead of chicken.
I said I wanted ribs.
I didn't want chicken.
Well, uh, why didn't you
just order the rib combo?
I didn't want the rib combo.
I wanted the chicken combo,
but with ribs.
Ribs.
Oh. Well,
you fucked up then.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Man ]
James, what did you
just say to this customer?
Nothin'.
He said I fucked up.
Did you say that, son?
I'm sorry, did you
just call me son?
Yeah.
Well, for cryin'
out loud, Pa.
I didn't know you was
my motherfuckin' dad.
Keep it down, okay?
Let's talk over here.
I gave you
an opportunity.
I gave you an opportunity--
Hold on. Away from
the customers, dog.
I don't wanna involve her.
You know what I'm sayin'?
What's your problem?
'Cause I don't wanna involve
that fuckin' bitch over there!
Shh!
Or you! Why don't you mop up
the motherfuckin' floor?
What's your problem?
Listen, motherfucker,
I'm sick and tired of
your fuckin' bullshit, dog!
Fuck this whole
fuckin' place, man.
Ripping me off like I'm
some little fuckin' punk bitch.
Fuck that! Motherfucker!
I'm in some fuckin' jail
bullshit, motherfucker!
I'm out of this
fuckin' piece of shit.
Don't think I'm not coming
for my motherfuckin' money, dog.
[ Bell Rings ]
Yo, man, what the fuck, dude?
Yo, I was about to drop
that fool, dog.
Man, fuck that job.
Uhh!
Fuck that shit!
Yo, don't even sweat that, man.
We gonna make loot, all right?
** [ Country ]
[ Flip ]
I'm gonna win this talent show
right now, dog.
Take the money,
do some real business.
* I'm cryin' *
* I'm on a two-way street *
* There's a boy *
* He's on my mind *
Go ahead.
Oh, you missed!
You gotta bust 'em!
[ Muttering ]
Hey, what the hell!
You guys can't do that!
Get out of here!
All right. Whassup?
* Mom says he's not country *
** [ Continues ]
What's up, man?
Bring it, dog.
What?
** [ Ends ]
[ Applause ]
I know everybody's been waitin'
a long time for this. I'm gonna
rock that house for y'all.
So here we go.
[ Rapping ]
* Yo, yes, yes, y'all *
* Yes, yes, y'all
to the beat, y'all
Y'all don't stop, what *
* Smile, chi-town Chicago
is where I come from *
** [ Continues ]
It's Khalid.
- * 'Cause I come from the land
of wisdom and knowledge *
- He's kinda phat.
I never heard him
rap before.
Man, shut up, man.
He ain't no African king.
Man, Flip, you gonna
take this shit, dog.
Hell, yeah.
Man, y'all don't know shit.
We all got African kings
in our blood, fool.
Man, you got watermelons
in your blood, dog.
Man, shut up.
What?
I'm gonna win this money.
That's that motherfucker
that was talkin' shit.
What's up, James?
What's up, Mike?
What's up with
your boy here?
Look like a gangbanger
with those fucking pants.
Watch out, man.
He'll get his peoples
come here and gank us.
Oh, your peoples?
What, you supposed to be
vice lord or somethin',
you folks?
Maybe we are.
Maybe you are what?
G.D., vice lord. Whassup?
What the fuck is your crew,
the fuckin' Marshmallow Posse?
Oh, what's yours,
the Drunk Norwegian
Slavemaster Motherfuckers?
You better stop talkin'
shit, Forrest Gump.
You still bangin' your sister?
Fuck that shit!
Get that motherfucker, man!
[ All Yelling ]
* Turn around, look at me
look at me *
* 'Cause these little, stupid
ingrates can't see **
[ Man ]
Break it up!
What? What?
Yeah, bring it.
Break it up!
Come on, man.
What the fuck?
What the hell?
There goes
the prize money, fool.
Shit.
Man, shut the fuck up,
dog. You always talkin'
some bullshit.
Motherfuckers are stupid, man.
Look where we are, motherfucker.
If we was in Chicago, man,
you don't even know the half.
You go there, and you
see the fucking truth.
Word up.
You on some trip.
I'm down with you, dog,
but that's some--
I know, man.
You my nigga.
I know, man. What up, dog?
I'm not sayin'--
I'm not tryin'-- Don't
fuckin' touch my ass, bitch.
[ Blows In Bottle ]
[ Both Laughing ]
You fuckin'
laughin' at him.
Fuckin' dog.
[ Cow Lows ]
[ Laughs ]
That's your mom.
Yeah, baby!
That's Trevor's moms.
She's calling you for dinner.
Yo, they're answering
to my shit, dog.
[ Stereo ]
* Now, if you down with
this shit, say, hell, yeah *
* If you down with
Soopafly say, hell, yeah *
* If you down to make
a Crip, say hell, yeah *
* If you down for smoking
shit, say, hell, yeah *
* If you like to get high
say, hell, yeah *
* If you like to bang boogie
* If you like to get rich
say, hell, yeah *
* If you like to fuck a bitch
say, hell, yeah **
Chill, dog.
Motherfucker, man.
Do it, man.
Here you go.
- Ow! Fuckin' shit, man!
- That shit has got to sting.
Fuckin' hell, yeah!
What are you talkin'
about, man?
Here you go. Here.
Uhh!
That shit is fuckin'
pimp right there.
Oh, my God.
Shit.
Yo, that shit
is nice, man.
Yo, where's
my next joint, dog?
One more, dog. One more.
Fuck, man, hurry up!
Do it, man.
Do it, Flip.
Ready, dog?
[ Grunts ]
[ Yells ]
Fuck.
[ Trevor ] That shit
has got to sting.
Hell, yeah, man.
What the fuck you think?
Fuckin' shit, man.
[ James ] What the fuckin' deal?
That shit is pimp.
What is up?
[ James ]
Yo, wait, hold on though.
Yo, you gotta--
Blowin' on that shit, man.
That shit is real.
[ Laughing ]
Yo, dog, hold on.
That shit is nice.
You got to keep this on
the shit for, like,
a couple of days.
All right, man.
Hold on, man.
Keep it lathered up.
I need another 40
after that shit, man.
Leave that shit alone, dog.
That shit is
fuckin' pimp.
Yeah. What the deal?
Uhh.
Whoa, player.
Whassup, Khalid?
Whassup, dog?
I didn't know
you was rollin' up.
I gotta give you mad props
for that rhyme you
kicked at the fair, man.
That shit
was phat, nigga.
What? You need to watch
your mouth, man.
Oh, chill, man,
I don't mean to disrespect.
You know, it's all good.
We all brothers here,
right?
[ Scoffs ]
Whatever, dog.
Aw, chill, man,
for one second.
Come on.
I want to do a little
business with you for
one second. Come on. Khalid.
Yo, man,
I was thinking, right?
You know, I'm sayin'--
Khalid, man?
What?
Dog, you know
how I roll, right?
Yeah, dog.
I was thinkin', man, you know,
why don't you, you know,
like, hook me up with
your old set or whatever?
My old set? Dog,
what you talkin' about?
I'm sayin', man, like,
you know, I know when
you was growin' up in Chicago,
you used to kick it with
the Disciples, or you were
down with them or some shit.
The Disciples? Uh, nah.
I mean, yeah. I mean,
I knew somebody.
I mean, my cousin knew somebody
who knew some-- I don't know
if that means knowin' somebody.
- I'm saying--
- Baby, I need to talk
to you about something.
Handle yours, dog.
About what?
Excuse me,
it's important.
I just burned
my damn arm for you.
That's not important?
You see I'm having
a conversation right here.
Why you wanna act
like a dumb trick now?
Yo, dog, that was
uncalled for, dog.
Chill, man.
It's all good, all right?
Don't worry about that, man.
Yo, check it, Khalid, man.
I'm sayin', I'm moving
up to Chicago, right?
And I was wondering if
you could just hook me up
with your homeys.
Some of my homeys?
Yeah, you know,
your peoples or whatever.
You know, your boys,
I mean, I figured you could
hook me up with your crew,
and, like, you know, I could
get some material for my rhymes
or whatever, keep it real.
So you just gonna go
up there?
That's what I'm sayin', man.
Hook me up with, like,
a phone number
or some motherfuckin' shit.
[ Scoffs ]
All right.
All right! That's all
I'm sayin'! Khalid!
Uhh!
I.G.B.T.! What?
[ Khalid Laughs ]
He's a crazy
motherfucker, man.
* Rampage up in the house *
I need some aloe vera
up in this motherfucker.
** [ Rap, Indistinct ]
[ Yells, Laughs ]
What's up?
J., did you say J.?
Wha-What's my name?
I'll say J.
What's my name?
Your name is, uh,
whatever, dog.
[ Laughing ]
What the fuck?
You don't even know my name.
I know your fuck-- I
know your fuckin' name.
Yo, your name is
Sheila E. and shit.
No.
I swear to God. Uhh!
** [ Rap, Indistinct ]
** [ Stops ]
Hey, what you doin', dog?
[ Girl ]
What are you doing, Flip?
Put back the tape. Come on.
** [ Slow Tempo ]
Uhh.
What the fuck, man?
Fuck the bullshit.
You know what I'm sayin'?
I'm trying to get down for this.
Check it out, right?
Uhh! Whassup?
* Hey, Flip Dogg on the mic
While keepin' it real *
* Motherfuckers know my deal
So what's the steal *
* In my pocket, on
the microphone, I rock shit *
* Yeah, I'm causin'
mad prostitution *
* We plus a 40
equals my revolution *
* Uhh, motherfucker, yeah
You know how we do *
* What, baby? Yeah **
[ Cheering ]
You know what I'm sayin'?
I.G.B.T., beeyatch!
Uhh! What?
White people.
Oh, shit.
Hi. You live here?
I guess not.
Okay, let's go, everybody.
This party's over.
- Out the front door
there, little lady.
- Move over. Put it out.
Yo, Trevor, let's go!
Get rid of it! Get rid of it!
Get rid of it!
Get rid of it.
Sara, take this.
Flip, I ain't takin' it.
Nah, take it. Sara.
Just take the weed.
Whoa! It smells like
a dope party.
Who owns this house?
Dope on the table
right here.
What'd I do?
Let me go.
Yo, officer, what's
your probable cause?
Shut your mouth, boy.
You can't do this!
What you arresting me for?
Hey, police brutality, yo.
What the deal, man?
Back off. Let him do his job.
There's 150 motherfuckers up
in here. You arrest a black man.
Put your hands up on top
of there.
Hey, nah.
Racist-ass pigs.
I will break your arm.
All right, man.
Don't touch my arm, man.
I got a tattoo. It's sensitive.
Put the other one
behind your back.
What'd I do?
This is bullshit!
What the fuck?
You fuckin' motherfuckers, man.
I didn't do shit!
- What are we gonna do?
- Get back in the house!
- Fuck the motherfuckin' police!
- Shut up!
Get back in the house.
- Yo, Trev,
go call my mom, man!
- Get back in the house.
[ Policeman ]
Everybody back in the house now.
You, in the house.
Watch my arm, bitch.
Shut up
and get in the car.
Watch my fuckin' arm, dick.
Damn!
[ Car Door Slams ]
My moms gonna kick my ass, man.
I can't be in jail, man.
I start classes next week, man.
Fuckin' cops, man!
Fuck it, man.
It's all good.
No, no, this is not all good.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
I'm in this thing with
drunks and rednecks, man.
You understand?
If this gets on my record,
I'm not getting into law school.
You're actin' like it's
your life and shit, man.
This is my life, man.
What you talkin' about?
Chill, man.
I'll say I did
this shit, all right?
What shit?
Whatever, dude.
Whatever they say we did,
I did it, all right?
It's all good.
Oh, really? Really?
You would do that shit?
You know what I'm sayin'?
Brothers got to stick together
and shit, all right?
Yo, man, hold up, man.
Why you act
like you're black?
Act? I don't act like nothin',
man. Don't let my skin
confuse you, all right?
So what you're saying is
you got black in your family?
No, man.
I'm saying
it's on the inside,
though, you know?
[ Scoffs ]
Look, man,
I was wondering, man,
all them years
when we weren't hanging out,
you dressed and acted completely
different than you do now.
Yeah, but those were
my ignorant days, man.
See, to me, black is
the dope shit, you know.
Like, people that's descended
from kings and queens
of Africa...
and victimized by white devils
for over 400 years, man.
Yo, dog, what are you
talkin' about?
What about your girl?
And what about Trevor
and your boy James, man?
They devils, too?
Is that what you sayin'?
Nah,
they cool peoples, man.
They been down with me from
yea high, but James got
some problems still,
but I'm tryin' to help him
see the light, you know?
Oh. Oh, you're gonna help--
Yeah, you're right. You're
gonna help him see the light.
Yo, Khalid, man,
so you gonna hook me up
with some of your peoples
in Chicago, right?
Man, you don't get it, do you?
You don't understand, man.
If you didn't step to them
cops when you did, do you
realize you wouldn't be here?
I'd be the only one here alone?
Nah, but they want me
to act like a good old boy.
I ain't gonna do that shit.
I mean, that's why I'm in here.
Cops wanna harass
a brother and shit.
A brother? Oh, a brother.
I'm a brother, man!
They were harassing me!
Hey, you. Your parents
are here. Let's go.
Come on now. You're wasting
my time. Let's go.
You wanna be here all night?
Yo, man, I'm gonna be
out of here soon, all right?
You keep it real, all right?
I'll talk to you later.
I'm cool, man.
Everything's chill.
What?
[ Scoffs ]
Yeah. I.G.B.T. up in this
motherfucker, you know?
* Yeah, I say *
* Real niggers stay locked down
every day, keepin' it real **
What, motherfucker? Uhh!
[ Scoffs ]
[ Door Clangs ]
Rack 10.
Flip Dogg,
what's up, baby?
Oh, Snoop, man.
[ Guard ] Close again!
Come on in here, baby.
Make yourself at home, my man.
Oh, yeah.
Sit that shit down.
Welcome to the crib.
Yo, it's good
to see you, man.
[ Indistinct ]
What you in here for, Flip Dogg?
You done murdered somebody
or somethin'?
Hell, yeah.
I murdered everybody, man.
* Posted up with Flip Dogg
Tryin' to get us some ends *
* You know it's a true thing
and you know it's a fact *
* Flip Dogg bust your rap
on how they lock up blacks *
* I said America sins
against young citizens *
* De-educate us
and throw us into bins *
* A couple years later
come out committing sins *
* Assaultin' foreigners
businessmens and even kins *
* The mo' money in jails
the mo' money in rap *
* So if your ass is havin' money
and you think you all phat *
* You better get up out of town
'cause you might get jacked *
* And that's real like dat *
* Uhh, uhh *
* Just like dat *
* You might get jacked
with a bid *
* That's longer
than your age *
* And you won't even make it
to the front page *
* I say everybody know
that I'm the dog named Flip *
* And if a buster say shit
then I'm bustin' they lip **
Beeyatch.
Yeah, you know
what I'm saying?
Hell, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I'm ready to bust shit.
[ Inmates Chattering ]
[ Inmates Whistling ]
Take all these motherfuckers,
you know?
Know what I'm saying?
Me and Snoop.
What the fuck?
[ All Chattering ]
Yo, how much money
we got this week?
Much, much.
Have some of
the strawberries.
Oh, thank you, Snoop.
I'm hungry.
Yo, guard, bring them trays
over here, man.
Damn, man. Yo, let's
see those shrimp
right there, man.
Mmm. Those look kinda good.
You down for some shrimp?
Yo, when we gettin'
lobster, man?
Throw us
some of that cheese.
Pull that cheese out, man.
Yeah. Oh, that's that cheese
from France right here.
We gonna get down.
We got expensive cheese.
I'm thirsty, man.
What's up?
What the fuck is that?
What the hell kind
of champagne is this, man?
Old shit, dog.
1968. That was a bad year.
Flip Dogg.
Fuck. What,
are you stupid, man?
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Inmates Cheering ]
[ Woman On P.A. ]
Price check, Aisle 9.
Price check on Aisle 9.
We need a bagger
up at Register 3.
Register 3 needs a bagger.
Why? Flip,
why you wanna do this?
You make me look
like a fool.
Disrespect your father.
Now I gotta fetch you
out of jail.
Them cops
was being racists.
I don't give a damn.
I won't tolerate
your being in jail.
I had to say somethin'
to the cops.
I had to represent.
What the hell
are you representing
fighting with the police? Huh?
Are you paying for that?
It's just gum, man.
It costs money.
Flip, do I look like I--
I'm rich to you,
like I can just pull money
out of the air?
No. I have to pay
with these.
And these don't buy gum,
so put it back
unless you're paying for it.
[ Crying ]
Y'all fuckin' lose
something over here, man?
[ Knocks ]
Sara, your boyfriend
is here!
What happened?
It's cool.
I mean, I'm free.
How's your arm?
It's all right.
I can't believe
you did that.
Come on. You know
I had to represent.
You're my woman.
Sara, honey, you're not
going out tonight.
We're just talking.
Your mother and I
want you to come inside.
Why?
Sara!
What?
[ Screen Door Slams ]
They don't like me, huh?
You don't try so hard.
You know,
I gotta keep it real.
Flip. Honey,
I missed my period.
What?
I mean--
I think that--
[ Screen Door Opens ]
[ Flip Scoffs ]
Sara, honey, come inside.
Call me tomorrow.
Yeah, like this!
Uhh!
Yeah! Yeah!
Put that shit away, dog!
What you worried about, Trev?
Ain't nobody gonna hear us.
We live in fuckin' Iowa.
Yeah, what?
Break yourself, nigga!
You act like a real bitch.
I'll take your shit
right now.
What? Oh, yeah?
Say something.
Say something, fucker.
What?
Hell, yeah!
Yeah.
Shit.
Yo, man, what the fuck is up
with this next joint, dog?
What's up
with this herb, man?
I don't know.
Yo, think about where
we get our indo from,
right?
Our weed, man!
Our fuckin' smoke!
George Tate grows that shit
on his farm.
He's paid
like a motherfucker.
[ Trevor ]
We ain't growin' nothin', man.
Fuck growin' weed, man.
I'm sayin' we gotta get
some other shit.
We don't know nobody
with no other shit, dog.
Yes, we do. We know
somebody in Chicago.
We do?
[ Trigger Clicking ]
Who we know
in Chicago, dog?
Yo, what's up, player?
What's up, dog?
- What's goin' on?
What's up, y'all?
- [ Sara ] What's up?
You didn't tell me you were
bringin' the whole crew.
Aw, you know how I roll.
[ Khalid Sighs ]
Is anyone chewing gum?
- [ Flip ] Nah.
- All right. This is how
it's gonna go down, y'all.
You gotta take off your hats.
You gotta take off your shoes.
'Cause my moms ain't havin'
nobody step on her rug,
all right?
[ Sara ]
Wow.
[ Flip ]
All right.
Check this out.
Damn. Check--
Statues.
Khalid, you livin' large.
Oh, snap.
Yo, what's this, yo?
Your moms. They got
a statue of your mom.
Yo, that's your moms, yo.
[ Khalid Chattering ]
Yo, put on BET.
Rap City is on, man.
I wanna see
that Wu-Tang video. Word.
That ain't the one, man.
That's not for the TV.
Which fuckin' one
is it, dog?
Yo.
What's up?
Wait. You tryin'
to start the stereo?
Get up, fool.
Yo, it's that one, dog.
I'm telling you, I got
this same shit at my house.
Yo, Rap City's on right now.
You got the fuckin' stereo--
No, no. It's the oth--
[ Woman ]
Khalid.
Rap City, dog.
[ TV Playing, Indistinct ]
Yeah?
[ Mother ]
Khalid.
Let me talk to you
for a minute.
[ Chattering ]
[ Flip ]
It's this one right here.
You didn't tell me
you were having company.
Who are these white kids?
They're just some
of my friends, Ma.
Not the friends that got you
in trouble with the police?
[ Flip ] Chill, chill.
Right here.
[ Flip ] Damn.
Hey, y'all,
this is my mom.
Mom, this is Flip, Sara,
James and Trevor.
This is my mom.
How you doing,
Mrs. Robertson?
I'm glad to see you all
have your shoes off.
Oh, yeah, you know,
Khalid told us...
you ain't havin' no shoes
up in your house.
I can respect that.
You know what I'm saying?
Are you Creole, Flip?
Am I what?
Your accent.
It sounds like
you're from Louisiana.
Oh, nah. I'm from here.
That's just straight-up
ghetto slang.
You know what I'm sayin'?
[ Mouthing Words ]
If you all would like
something to eat or drink,
there's chips and pop
in the kitchen.
[ James ]
What was that shit?
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
Yo, Khalid, your mom's
kind of cool, man.
Yeah. Yeah, dude.
Yo, we goin' to Chicago
right now. You down?
Chicago? No, I can't do that.
I got college next week, man.
- I got a lot of stuff
I gotta do.
- That's what I'm saying.
You want to party
before you go.
You leavin'.
Just to hook us up, man.
You promised.
I gotta pick up my computer.
I gotta get stuff done.
My moms and me gotta shop.
Khalid, I don't mean
to bust on you, man,
but some people might say
you a bitch.
What? I ain't no bitch.
Flip, you know that, dog.
I ain't saying you are.
I'm just saying you always
be studyin' and stuff
like that, man.
You never seem to really
get down for yours.
If you wasn't a bitch,
you'd be up there
in a minute.
All them honeys up there?
Honeys.
Man, honeys, yo.
All right.
All right?
That's what I'm saying, man!
Shh! That's my mom
up there, man.
I don't want her to know
what we're doin'.
No doubt, no doubt.
All right. So, look,
I'll go change.
It's all good.
Hang with them. Make sure
they don't tear up my place.
Yo, man, get your feet
off my table, dog!
[ James ] ...in that
fuckin' rap, dude.
Come on, dog!
Yo, and it's
the third one.
Which third one?
What the fuck
is the third one, dog?
Don't curse
in his house, bitch.
All right, dogs,
we out.
Yo, out? Where we goin'?
Uptown, baby.
Chicago.
Yo, Flip.
Can I just talk to you
for a second, like in private?
What's up?
We need to talk.
Kick it.
I'm listening.
What do you want me
to do, Flip?
I'm saying
come with us, yo.
That's not
what I'm talking about.
What then?
What the hell
do you think?
[ Scoffs ]
What are you gonna do
in Chicago?
I'm saying Khalid's
gonna hook us up.
You just don't get it,
do you?
Get what?
This! What I told you about--
what is happening here.
Don't play me like that.
You think I ain't
thinkin' about things?
I figure, you know,
we should get married,
get out of Iowa.
I wanna be
my kid's father.
I'm having an abortion.
[ Laughs ]
What?
You heard me.
What kind of father
you gonna be--
a wannabe drug dealer?
I think you need
to lower your voice
right about now.
I think you need to stop
acting like an asshole.
You and your crew are just
a bunch of white boys runnin'
around pretending you're black.
You don't even know
what black is.
You need to stop
talkin' shit, bitch!
I am black!
Yeah, go ahead, gangsta man.
That's all you got.
What's up, man?
Let's go!
Let's go, y'all!
[ Trevor ] Chill. We're gettin'
in the fuckin' truck.
[ All Chattering ]
[ Engine Starts ]
* Yo, behold a pair
of white horses
on the death wish course *
* Been watching MTV
readin' articles
in The Source *
* Lost on the other side
of the river *
* Where death approaches
the livest nigga *
* I wonder why this wigga
would even come around
my tilt *
* Where grandmothers cry
uncles get high
and cats get pealed **
[ James ]
What the fuck?
Blunt, please.
Yo, this the real shit up here.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Hell, fuckin' yeah, dog.
I say we just get it
and then find a party,
all right?
[ James ] We get that shit,
and we get the fuck
out of Dodge, dog.
G-G-Get what? What the hell
are y'all talking about?
[ Laughter ]
Yo, man, we gonna
get some blow...
and shit like that,
know what I mean?
[ Hooting ]
What?
Y'all came to--
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Y'all came to buy drugs
up in this motherfucker?
[ Laughs ]
No. Fuck that. Yo,
I ain't with that shit.
Fuck it. Yo, open the door,
motherfucker. Let me out.
Yo, Khalid, man, come on.
You don't got to do nothin'
or say nothin'.
Just come with us.
Just be there.
You know what I'm sayin'?
I don't need this shit!
[ James ] You're like
a little fuckin' bitch.
You actin'
like a little bitch.
James, shut the fuck up, man.
Khalid, look, man, we came
all the way up here,
all right?
Come on, man.
All right.
All right, but you make
this shit quick. Damn!
* Don't come my way *
* Hawks feel the day *
* Things don't change *
Oh, shit.
Yo, you see that shit,
man?
[ James ]
I told you, man.
Dickhead, man.
That's Cabrini-Green.
Word up, man.
[ Khalid ] Oh, shit.
* Oh, no *
* Things don't change *
[ Flip ] Yo, Khalid,
this is the spot, right?
* No, no, no, no, no **
[ Sirens In Distance ]
[ Woman ]
Y'all been playin'?
What y'all been doin'?
[ Boy ]
These girls
were chasin' us.
And doing what?
Chasing us.
Y'all been playing ball?
Excuse me.
[ Flip ]
What's going on?
Fuck, dog.
Yo, man. Straight up, man,
anybody comes at us,
I'm gonna fuckin'
blast their ass, dog.
Yo, straight up, man.
That's my word, dog.
Fuck that, man.
I ain't tryin'
to get fucked up, man.
Yeah?
Yo, man, we lookin'
for Darius.
Who the fuck are you?
I'm Flip, and this
is my nigga Khalid
right here--
I mean, hom-- my homey.
Oh, yeah?
Flip.
Khalid.
So? What do you want?
We was wondering if,
you know, like,
you could hook us up
with some coc--
What!
caine?
[ Laughing ]
Yeah. Huh.
Some coc-caine?
No, man. Just chill
for one minute.
This is stupid!
Just chill, all right?
Why don't you just
slap the cuffs on me?
Want to come in
and search my spot, huh?
I already seen my P.O.
this morning,
you understand?
I been goin' straight, man.
We ain't cops, man.
See, check it, right?
We from Holyoke.
Holy Road?
No, man. In Iowa.
I got this whole business--
Keep your voice down,
man.
[ Whispering, Indistinct ]
Yo, just
get in here, man.
Get the fuck in here.
Move slow.
How you doin'?
[ Darius ]
Grandma, we'll just be
a minute right here.
Yo, man,
What?
you from Iowa?
Yeah.
Are you from Iowa?
Yeah. Yeah.
I didn't know
they had brothers in Iowa.
Yeah, man, they got a lot--
Well, not a lot of 'em,
but--
You don't live in
no trailer park, do you?
Oh, hell, no.
'Cause black people
ain't supposed to be
in no goddamn trailer park.
No, man. He got a statue
in his-- in his house.
That's word.
Yo, why you bringing
this white boy here for, man?
I didn't bring--
That shit
is not cool, man.
Yo, I know what you're thinkin',
but I ain't one of them
Vanilla Ice fools.
I know what's the deal.
I know what's up.
[ Clears Throat ]
Just step inside
for a minute.
Just step inside.
Y'all are cops.
[ Khalid ]
What?
You're cops!
Yo, man. We ain't cops, man.
We hate cops, man.
Oh, yeah?
I just came out of jail,
man, a month ago.
You think
I need that again?
Nah, man. We was
locked down too.
Word up.
That shit was phat.
Yo, man. Check this, man.
This is what I'm saying, right?
I got this operation in Iowa.
[ Scoffs ]
I'm just trying to expand--
Not expand, but just
get my hands on some more shit.
Like, some supplies,
and blow up the whole
motherfuckin' shit.
Nigger, you came to my crib.
I got a sick grandmother
in here, man.
No offense, dog.
She looked good.
What do I look like--
Scarface?
No, man. I'm just saying,
like, I'm trying to network.
That's all.
Aw, man, dude.
That's old, man.
No, dog, I'm not that kind
of player no more.
That's cool.
Killin' my people, man.
Black man,
that sound good to you?
No, man.
Shit. If you want me to poison
some people out in Iowa--
some white folks--
Well, fuck it.
Now, listen, I'm not gonna
promise you nothin'.
If we don't see 'em,
you leave.
You understand?
It's all good.
Listen, one more thing, man.
You see this?
This is Chicago.
I know that.
Yo, this ain't Kansas.
I'm not the wizard.
Yo, man.
What do I look like?
You understand?
All right. All right.
We're gonna see
what you made of now.
[ Door Squeaking ]
All right.
You got the cheese?
"Cheese"?
Scratch, motherfucker!
Dinero, money, cash.
You got it?
Yeah, man,
I got money, man.
Gimme $20, man.
We want more than 20.
Give me $20,
motherfucker!
[ Door Opens ]
Now--
Where your friend at?
Right there, man.
Them white kids
in that truck?
[ Flip ] Yeah, man.
Oh, my God, man.
Yeah, dog, I gotta
settle down, kid.
Girls are stealin'
my rings now.
I woke up, man.
I saw seven
instead of eight.
Wait till I catch her.
Just stay back.
You ain't gonna get
into that shit over no ring.
Peace.
What's up, baby?
What's going on, man?
Show some love here, man.
You all right?
Everything's all right.
I need to borrow the phone
for a minute.
Who you calling?
Mace.
Yo, you a stupid
motherfucker, man.
You gonna go
with Mace again?
I'm fuckin' stupid?
You know you ain't got
to go over there.
[ Chattering ]
Yo, why you give him
fuckin' Mace, man?
Let the man make his money.
Remember how fly
he used to be?
- What's up, Officer?
- What's goin' on?
I ain't no cop, man.
A little undercover.
No, man, I'm a straight-up
thug, you know?
Nigger, did I fuckin' stutter?
I said big money, man.
Big money, man.
These niggers is white, cuz.
What up, dog?
Where you from, man?
Yo, I'm from Iowa.
You know, representin'.
Iowa.
I like that big-ass chain
you got on.
Yo, I'm tryin' to
get my stack like that.
Just be there.
You got some stuff there?
Be there, man, please.
I'm in and out.
You know where you at, man?
I know where I'm at.
I'm an entrepreneur.
I need to talk to you.
This shit is out of order.
You speaking like you know
what the fuck is goin' on.
I know what's goin' on.
You know what the fuck
happens around here.
All right, all right.
You know the rules.
Go take care of your business
before you be broke like him.
Yo, yo!
Let's go, man.
Why you losin' it, man?
What do you mean, why
am I losin' it, nigger?
You got clothes on, man.
You got clothes on too.
Man, you got clothes on,
all right?
Thanks, preacher.
Hey, yo, yo, yo.
Y'all fuckin' up.
** [ Radio: Rap ]
Uhh!
Want some
of this, dog?
No.
** [ Radio Continues,
Indistinct ]
You're gonna go down a couple
of blocks and you're gonna
take another left.
Yo, man,
just tell me, like--
What's that over there, man?
That's some, like--
What's that?
Would you stop fuckin'--
Yo, this shit's
kind of bugged out.
Yo, man, what's the matter
with you, man?
What's the matter
You wanna do
shit like that?
Like what?
Keep your hands
in the truck, man.
Don't point at nobody.
All right, dog.
You don't know
who the fuck is down here.
You will get shot
in your face.
Whatever, dude.
* If you sell coke or crack
I relate to that *
* If you do sticks and stacks
I can relate to that *
* I don't give a fuck
if you white or black *
* If you bust your gat
I can relate to that *
* If you sell coke or crack
* When it's your turn
to blow away
and no turning back *
* Seem like another lifetime **
[ Darius ]
What the fuck?
What's goin' down?
Just chillin', man.
All right. We got some
very thirsty customers here.
Whassup, dog?
[ Darius ]
Yo.
Mace is in the back, man.
Little nigger.
Fuck you up, little nigger.
** [ Stereo: Rap, Indistinct ]
Whassup, Mace?
[ Chattering ]
Yo, yo.
What up, baby?
I just want
my finder's fee, man,
then disappear.
What's goin' on?
Yo, D., where you get this
white motherfucker from?
This white trash just
showed up on my doorstep.
What the fuck
was I supposed to do?
I don't feel good
about this, man.
Chill, man.
Hey, black man.
Go outside. Wait for
your friend, all right?
It's all good. All right?
It's all good.
[ Snapping Fingers ]
So what's up, man?
Shit. Fuck, man.
Where's Flip?
He's inside, dog.
So why the fuck are you here?
I don't know, man.
They told me to leave.
We should kill this white
motherfucker right now,
take all his money.
So what's up, yo?
Where the money?
Aw, chill, man,
I'm sayin', you know,
where's the shit?
Show us the green, son.
Why the fuck did they tell
you to fuckin' leave, man?
Why the fuck didn't you stay?
This shit is crazy, man.
We got to get the fuck
out of here.
What are you talking about, man?
That's our fuckin' dog in there.
I'm not talkin' about leavin',
but what are we gonna do
right now?
Uh,
well, I got, like, 160 bucks.
What? What the fuck
did you just say?
This motherfucker said
he got 160 bucks, D.
What the fuck
did you just say?
I already gave you 20.
Oh, man.
Nigger, you brought me
the fuck down here
for $160?
What the fuck are you doin'?
Yo, J., chill, man, don't--
J., J. J., what the fuck
are you doin'?
Chill with that shit.
I'm gonna go get
my motherfuckin' dog
that's in there right now.
Did you think
I'm some sucka?
What you think?
Maybe, like, you could front me
for the nation, right?
Front you?
Like, for the nation
or whatever, man.
'Cause, you know--
[ Laughing ]
I got this whole shit set up
down in Iowa, man.
And I can just come back
in a week and, like,
come back with mad loot.
We can make, like,
just mad loot, you and me.
- You know what I'm sayin'?
- [ Bills Rustling ]
Get the fuck out of here
with that shit.
[ Sighs ]
Dude, he's been up there
for, like, a fuckin'
half hour, man.
Take a look
at that shit.
[ James ]
What the fuck
do you want, dog?
I'm sayin', what the fuck?
I'm not tryin' to--
Man, fuck you, man.
What do you mean, what the fuck?
I'm not tryin' to fuckin'
stand here, man.
What the fuck?
113.
Mark us out on investigation
at Pershing and Cottage Grove.
Let's just kill
this motherfucker
right now like I said, son.
What the fuck
is this shit, man?
Iowa pork-ass, nigger.
Get him out of here.
Get his ass out of here.
Boy, come here.
Motherfucker!
Take that shit
to the nation!
Take some of that shit
back to the nation!
That's enough.
That's enough!
[ Shouting, Indistinct ]
Chill out, man.
Damn, you already fuckin'
robbed him-- took his money
and all that shit.
What the fuck are you
gonna do, kill him?
Am I in?
What the fuck
are you talkin' about?
Yeah. You in deep shit.
Yo, D., what the fuck
you doin', man?
You brought this bullshit
in here! I'm fuckin'
this motherfucker up.
What?
What the fuck
you mean, "What"?
Nigger, you better have some
respect for me, young blood.
Don't do that shit.
I'm tellin' you right now.
Man, have some fuckin'
respect for me!
Nigger, fuck respect!
Oh, word?
Yeah. Fuck.
Come on the fuck out, man.
Get the fuck out of here.
Get the fuck
out of here.
You okay, man?
- [ Shotgun Cocks ]
- Freeze!
[ Shotgun Blast ]
[ Screams ]
[ James ]
Holy shit!
Get in the car!
- Shit.
- [ Trevor ]
Hurry up, man!
I said freeze, motherfucker!
[ James ] Get the fuck
in this car, man!
Get up, Darius.
[ James Shouting,
Indistinct ]
Wait up. Shit!
I'm gonna blast you!
What? What?
[ Khalid ]
Come on!
He's dead!
[ Flip ]
We can't leave him.
Get in the car, man!
Yeah, motherfucker!
Come on!
- [ Sirens Wailing ]
- [ Trevor ] You gotta get
in the truck, man!
[ All Shouting, Indistinct ]
[ Trevor ]
Get out of here, man!
[ Trevor ] Oh, shit!
Motherfucker!
What the fuck, dog?
Oh, shit! That shit was
fuckin' crazy, man!
What the fuck just
fuckin' happened, dog?
What the fuck happened
in there, dog?
Are you fucking stupid,
motherfucker?
Are you fucking stupid, nigger?
You left motherfuckin' Flip
inside alone, dog!
I told you not to call me
a nigger, motherfucker!
- Nigger! Nigger! Nigger!
Nigger!
- Fuck you! Fuck you!
Shut the fuck up!
Get the fuck out
of the car, nigger.
Get that fuckin' gun
out of my face, man.
James, man, chill!
Get the fuck out of the car
right the fuck now, dog.
You set us up, dog.
I set you up? What?
Is that what you fucking
think I did, pussy?
You ain't no different
than the fuckin' Klan
or the fuckin' police!
The only thing is
you motherfuckers
listen to rap!
So pull the fucking
trigger, bitch!
Come on!
Drive, man.
Home! Now!
Why don't you put
that fuckin' gun down, dog?
I ain't fuckin' with you, man.
Drive the fuckin' Dually
now, man!
I can't believe you get up
with these motherfuckin'
niggers, dog.
Don't say that word, James!
I'll fuckin' pull it, man!
I swear to God!
Don't say a word, man.
[ Crying ] We're gonna get
fuckin' locked up, man.
My fucking mom's gonna kill me.
[ Khalid ]
Shut the fuck up, Trevor.
Pull over, man.
Pull over!
Right here.
Let me out.
Open the door.
Let me out, man.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Vehicle Horn Honks ]
[ Truck Horn Honks ]
[ Water Splashes ]
What happened to you?
Nothin'.
Let me see this.
Nothin' happened.
How was Chicago?
Bad.
I just wanna say...
I'm sorry.
So say it.
You know,
I'm sorry, Sara.
I was all stressed out,
you know, and,
on top of that,
you're pregnant.
How's Junior?
Gone.
What?
What was I supposed
to do, Flip?
I don't know.
I mean, you were right.
What kinda father
am I gonna be anyway?
A wannabe
gangsta rapper?
[ Laughs ]
[ Shotgun Blast ]
[ Voices Shouting, Indistinct ]
[ Khalid's Voice ]
I told you
not to call me a nigger!
You ready?
What's happenin', baby?
All right,
I'm bringin' the man in.
Bringin' the man in.
Watch your back, dude.
Yeah, yeah!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I brought him.
He's here.
He is here.
The new shit
named Flip.
- [ Man ] Flip. Flip, come on.
- [ Flip's Mother ] Come on over
and take a picture, dear.
Picture over this way.
Picture.
[ People Chattering ]
Give me some love, man.
[ Shutters Clicking ]
[ All Chattering ]
- [ Flip ] James, man. Trevor.
- [ Man ] Hey, Flip, what's up?
[ Man ]
Flip, join us.
[ Camera Shutters Clicking ]
- [ Man Laughing Loudly ]
- [ Chattering ]
Let's kick something right now.
I'm gonna introduce y'all.
Yeah. Let's go kick somethin'.
Let's go kick somethin'.
[ Chattering ]
[ Khalid ]
We all brothers in here.
I just don't know
about his next record.
Thank you for comin' down.
* Yo, life is like
poisonous snakes *
[ Both ] * Slick and colorful *
* And that's how
most niggers get bit *
* From bein' gullible *
* See, I believe a liar's
a fuckin' coward *
* And by the same batch
of lies you tell *
* You get devoured *
* I love who I am
and that means
everything to me *
* 'Cause my life
ain't worth a damn unless
I'm dealin' with reality *
* When I look myself
in the eyes
it's just me *
* And I ain't gotta tell
nobody no lies
I feel free *
* And I would rather
deal with the truth
than falsehood *
* Than being fake
with my people and claimin' *
* It's all good *
* You can't run away
from yourself
so that's useless *
* If your word is bond
then you don't have
to make excuses *
* You can't flip the script
Know what I'm sayin' *
* Ghetto rollin'
What's goin' on *
* You know what I'm sayin'
Comin' for that ass
in the 2G? *
* Whatever, vanilla thug *
* Sayin' what's up *
[ People Chattering ]
** [ Rapping Continues,
Indistinct ]
[ Man ] Chill.
Shrimp, Flip.
Would you like
some shrimp?
Nah, man!
Shrimp! Shrimp!
Shrimp!
[ Darius ]
Hey, Flip,
come back this way!
Where are you goin'?
Shrimp!
[ Panting ]
You killed me,
white boy!
Aw, man, I'm sorry.
You killed me, man!
I'm sorry, man.
- You killed me,
motherfucker!
- [ Panting ]
[ Mother's Voice ]
Who the hell
were you representing?
Sara, what are you doin'?
What are you doin'?
Yo, what the fuck?
Is this how you
want it, nigger?
[ Trevor Talking,
Indistinct ]
Trey.
What the fuck do you want,
you fuckin' sellout?
James, man.
J. Dogg, what's up?
What the fuck?
Fuck, man!
[ Flip Panting ]
What?
I had this dream
that I was on this planet.
[ All ]
Bye, Sara.
[ Flip Continues ]
But it wasn't another planet.
It was, like, this planet.
And I started cryin'.
[ Thinking ]
I don't know why I was cryin',
but I kept goin'...
and I kept passin'
these people.
And they saw me crying,
and I was embarrassed--
embarrassed
that I didn't know shit,
that I didn't know
where I was goin',
embarrassed at my history.
And I started thinking about
50,000 murders a year...
and two million people
in jail.
And I think about Columbus Day
and Columbus Circle
and Columbus, Ohio.
And I started thinkin'
about tribes, man--
American tribes--
raped, murdered and moved.
And I started thinkin' about
tens of millions of Africans
dyin' in the sea...
and Malcolm X
and Jeep Cherokee...
and Columbus Day
and Columbus, Ohio,
and I felt ashamed, man--
ashamed of what I was
representin'.
* White boy, white boy
turn that shit down *
* You know that America
ain't ready for the sound
from them white boyz *
* They're slittin' your throat
with a dirty fuckin' razor *
* They drown you in malt liquor
choke you with your pager *
* 'Cause they don't really give
one ounce type of fuck *
* Everybody steps in their way
and they moms
is gettin' stuck *
* Yeah, and you don't stop *
* Keep on till
the break of dawn and-- **
* White boy, white boy
turn that shit down *
Thank you.
I gotta practice
that shit.
* White boyz, white boyz *
** [ Rap Burping ]
[ Flip ]
Man, what the fuck
are you representin', man?
Man, I'm sayin'-- I'm doin'
the human burp box.
All right.
Bust your rhyme, man.
* White boyz, white boyz *
* White boyz *
* Bow wow, white boyz *
* Niggers call me a white boy
White boys call me a nigger *
* How the fuck you figure
[ Indistinct ] *
[ Laughter ]
* And, yes, check this, you
I be bigger *
* And, yes, tell me, uhh **
* This is how we doin' it
for the nine-nine *
* White boyz *
* White boyz, white boyz *
* We blowin' indo smoke
behind these bars *
* Livin' like stars
You know who we are *
* Snoop and Flip,
Don't trip, we get grip *
* Motherfuckers can't touch it
'cause they can't fuck
with this *
Yeah, you know
what I'm saying?
Represent.
[ Man ]
Beautiful, beautiful.
* White boy, white boy
turn that shit down *
* You know that America
ain't ready for the sound *
* From them white boyz
white boyz *
* White boyz, white boyz *
* I'm higher than a motherfucker
Perv on the curve *
* Fuckin' with this white boy
slangin' my herb *
* D.P.G.
to the fullest young cuz *
* My homeboy Ricky
said show me some love *
* He got the club
with this fool named T-Bo *
* From The Dirty South
gold's in his mouth *
* My peoples, all of my homeys
from the L.B.C. *
* All my white homeys
who smoke with me *
* Sell me bud
on the weekdays, cuz *
* This shit's for y'all
for me and my dogs *
* If you don't know
you do know T-Bo
my new dog *
* Fuck what you goin' through
We 'bout to fuck it up
y'all *
* White boyz, white boyz
turn that shit down *
* You know that America
ain't ready for the sound *
* Of them white boyz
white boyz *
* White boyz, white boyz *
* White boyz, white boyz **
[ New Song ]
* Everybody wanna be
like a young "G" *
* Gold teeth
drinkin' Hennessy *
* Slang a ounce to a bird
in the street *
* Like the curb
candy paint *
* Twenty chrome
Chiefin' on green herb *
* Wannabe, wannabe
Everybody wanna be
like a young "G" *
* Gold teeth
drinkin' Hennessy *
* Slang a ounce to a bird
in the street *
* Like the curb
candy paint *
* Twenty chrome
Chiefin' on green herb *
* You tryin' to wear my shoes
You tryin' to wear
my clothes *
* You tryin' to be like me
I'm tryin' to be
like you, bro *
* What I'm really tryin' to say
You got to keep it all real *
* You can't be fakin' no deal
You got to get you a meal *
* See, it's hard out here
Peeps'll end your career *
People'll put you
in the real *
* I'm tryin' to kick you a meal
I'm tryin' to keep it
all real *
* See, you be fakin' a deal
So I'm-a let you see
how it feel *
* Wannabe, wannabe
Everybody wanna be
like a young "G" *
* Gold teeth
drinkin' Hennessy *
* Slang a ounce to a bird
in the street *
* Like the curb
candy paint *
* Twenty chrome
Chiefin' on green herb *
* Wannabe, wannabe
Everybody wanna be
like a young "G" *
* Gold teeth
drinkin' Hennessy *
* Slang a ounce to a bird
in the street *
* Like the curb
candy paint *
* Twenty chrome
Chiefin' on green herb *
* Thinkin' you ballin'
This bangin', you cold
you hungry in your sleep *
* You wish that was your life *
So y'all been yappin'
for a chiefy *
* You're greedy and fiendin'
to be a happy sa-super chi *
* But you don't think it because
there's plenty of dues to be
paid up in this industry *
* Wanna come in out of nowhere
be the king of the streets
radio, air *
* And yet you end up
You have somethin' to gain *
* The record label
Your master's stored there *
* I can't play your album mack
Everybody can't be
on the same thing *
* And everybody can't be
a known rapper *
* Say what, say what, say what *
* In the ghetto
we got ghetto stars *
* Ridin' in a steamed-up car
Lex, with them
tinted windows *
* Pushin' down the boulevard *
In the mouth
you see the grill *
* You face a playa
'cause he real *
* Not because he roll and smoke
or cut some deals
for the bills *
* Plus I'm tryin'
to stack some G's *
* Pushin' weight
like quarter keys *
[ Woman ]
* Hey, let me ride
in that Lexus truck *
* Freak, you better
hit your knees *
* Never will I save a broad
Gangsta playas comin' hard *
* Chicken-heads get out my car
I'm leavin' frantic
in the park *
* Wannabe, wannabe
Everybody wanna be
like a young "G" *
* Gold teeth
drinkin' Hennessy *
* Slang a ounce to a bird
in the street *
* Like the curb
candy paint *
* Twenty chrome
Chiefin' on green herb *
* Wannabe, wannabe
Everybody wanna be
like a young "G" *
* Gold teeth
drinkin' Hennessy *
* Slang a ounce to a bird
in the street *
* Like the curb
candy paint *
* Twenty chrome
Chiefin' on green herb **