[somber instrumental music]
- [Woman] We're
actually going to start
abstaining after today
until the wedding.
I'm gonna ask you this one time.
And one time only.
Are you seeing someone else?
- [Man] No, no, no.
- [Woman] Who are
you accountable to?
- [Man] You are the
only woman for me.
I cannot wait to
make you my wife.
["Drugz" by Stress]
♪ Yo, we cruisin' down the lane
♪ We gettin' loose
while we kissin'
♪ Ya'll hear, we'll repeat
♪ Let it loop for a minute
♪ I know it seem
like we speedin'
♪ But we doin' the limit
♪ Mets throw back jersey
shoes just to fit it
♪ That's how it's supposed to be
♪ You close to me
♪ You and me in soft
leather upholstery
♪ Mommy doin' everything
♪ You can merge in my lane
♪ Climb over but watch
the emergency brake
♪ And yo I got you
♪ Money's no object
♪ She don't be in them circles
♪ With them honeys that gossip
♪ You return what
I'm sendin' you
♪ I can die in the bed with you
♪ I can get high
off the scent of you
♪ You body's like drugs to me
♪ Get high on my love
♪ Your body keeps callin' me
♪ Baby, baby
♪ Your body's like drugs to me
♪ I get high on your love
♪ Like a drug that
keeps callin' me
♪ Baby, baby
♪ Here we go, here we go
♪ You know the routine
♪ Left the club
tipsy 'round 2:13
♪ Little hypnotic,
some Louis XIII
♪ Kissin' on my neck
as she loosen her jeans
♪ Got plans for the evenin'
♪ Shall I say plans
for the mornin'
♪ Getting ass while I'm yawnin'
♪ Listen to enhance
my performance
♪ Can't pass up
the sexual advances
♪ And offers, how convenient
♪ Easy access
♪ Put a hole in her best
box spring and mattress
♪ You'll bow down long
time while I sex you
♪ Protect you from the
front door to your bedroom
♪ I confess a sucker
for a pretty face
♪ And I can't care less
♪ Yo I can't say no
but I can't say yes
♪ Drugs
♪ Your body's like drugs to me
♪ Gettin' high off your love
♪ Like a drug that
keeps callin' me
♪ Baby, baby
♪ Your body's like drugs to me
♪ I get high off your love
♪ Like a drug that
keeps callin' me
[somber instrumental music]
♪ Give me a clean
♪ Give me a clean heart
♪ Lord I wanna serve you
♪ It's my heart
♪ So that I
♪ May be used by thee
♪ Lord I'm not
worthy, I'm not worthy
♪ Of all your blessings
♪ Give me a clean heart
- Yes, Lauren Robinson, please.
- I'm sorry, Lauren's
last day was Friday.
Can I connect you with
another publicist?
- Last day?
No, there must be some mistake.
Lauren Robinson.
- No mistake, sir.
We had a going away party
for Miss Robinson on Friday,
but I can connect you
with another publicist.
♪ Give me a clean heart
♪ I wanna praise you Lord
♪ And I will follow thee
♪ Thee
- I'll be on tonight, all right?
Great.
- I'm so sorry, I
didn't see you coming.
What a gentleman.
- My bad.
I was trippin', I was
in an important call.
- Don't worry about it.
You're totally free.
- Whatever, I apologized.
- Whatever?
Whatever, you ran into me.
- No, actually you ran into me.
- I don't have time for this.
I'm already runnin' late.
[midtempo R&B music]
- Surprise.
- Well, well, well, beautiful.
- [giggles] Hi, baby.
- Mm, what you doin' here?
- I missed you.
- Aw.
- I just stopped by
for a quick minute.
- Ah, you're so, so bad.
Mm, you know you got me
in trouble this mornin'.
- I know.
That's what I'm supposed to do.
- You're so good
at it, too. [sighs]
I cannot wait to
make you my wife.
- Baby, you're so sweet.
I can't wait either.
Oh, you know we gotta go
to counseling tomorrow.
- Oh. [groans]
There ain't nothin' wrong
with our relationship.
Why do we have to
go to counseling?
- Baby, the church requires it.
- The church, the church.
- Plus, you never know what
could come out in counseling.
- I still don't see why
we gotta go to counseling.
- Oh, you don't?
Baby, please?
Just a little meeting.
- I don't know about counseling,
I could use a little physical
therapy say around noontime?
- Well, I have a client, but
I think we might be able to
- Mm-Hm.
- Work that out.
[knocking]
- Oh.
- Oh!
- [Turner] Comfy?
- Woo, hi there, Turner.
All right, baby.
Just, see ya'll later.
- Okay.
Mr. Turner, my conference call
should be dialin' at any minute.
- Good.
Bre's gonna sit in on the
conference call with you.
- Bre?
- Bre, I wanna
introduce you to Ansel.
He's the new Director
of Central Affairs.
You two are gonna be
coordinating often on my behalf,
primarily with
the new contracts.
- Okay.
- Ansel, I know your
mother taught you
better manners than that.
- [clears throat] Ansel.
- I know, Turner told me.
Coffee?
- Um, no thank you.
I have some green tea.
It's supposed to
be better for you,
antioxidants, prevents cancer
or something like that.
- I wasn't offering, but
thanks for the health lesson.
I think we've met before.
Remember, you almost
made me spill my coffee.
- Oh, yes.
- I'm out.
- How could I forget?
Sorry about that.
Please, take a seat.
- I've already
taken the liberty.
- So, you work for Mr. Turner.
[midtempo R&B music]
- Hello, welcome.
So glad you could make
it, come on inside.
- Thank you.
Babe, if you don't
come in this church.
- I'm so glad the two
of you could make it.
More young people should
be getting married,
but you know kids these days.
They put the cart
before the horse.
- I know what you mean.
- Kids are just shackin'
up and having babies.
Oh, but you two
aren't, of course.
- Well--
- We recently moved in together.
- Oh.
Well, how's your
mother, sweetie?
- Oh, she's good.
- The pastor will
be with you shortly.
Right this way.
Just in here, have a seat.
- [Lauren] Thanks.
- Sure.
And we'll see you Sunday?
- [Ansel] Doubt it.
- Stop it.
- I knew this was a bad idea.
- This was not a bad idea, okay?
Just quit being so negative.
Please.
- Praise the Lord.
- [Lauren] Hi, Pastor!
- How you doin'?
- [Lauren] I'm
good, how are you?
- I'm doin' wonderful,
good to see you.
- Yes.
- How you do?
- Pastor Smith.
- Good, good to see you as well.
- Mm-hm.
- So, I remember
when you was just a little
somethin' boppin' around.
Look at you now.
You're getting married.
- I know.
- So tell me about your
plans for the future?
- Uh.
That's a little broad.
- What about the children?
- Oh, well we both agreed
that we wanna have kids
in a couple of years.
- Yes, first a little
boy, then a little girl.
- Or a little girl
and a little boy.
- No, honey, remember?
We talked about this.
You said it would be
nice for our daughter
to have an older brother
so he could protect her.
- But an older sister can
protect a little brother
just as well as an older brother
can protect a little sister.
- Well, you two
really understand
that you really have no
absolutely no control
which one really comes first.
Amen?
- Yes.
- [chuckles] Amen.
- So, okay.
We got the money squared
away and the kids.
So tell me, what
about premarital sex?
- Oh, that's great.
Love that.
- You know what, Pastor?
We are going to be
abstaining starting today
until the wedding.
- We are?
- We are.
- What exactly do
you mean about?
- [Lauren] Not here, okay?
- As I was saying,
there are going to always
be trials and tribulations.
But so long as the both
parties and persons
have something to
hold them accountable
for their actions and
the risk of misdeeds
and other infidelities
lessens greatly.
- You know what, Pastor,
I'm really glad that
you brought that up
because I made it very,
very clear to Ansel
that I will not
tolerate cheating.
- Oh, and realize that cheating
is not always a
deal breaker, honey.
- Yes, it is.
It is to me.
I mean, I've been on
the receiving end,
and I just will
not put up with it.
- Baby, I would never
do anything to hurt you.
- Never say never, Ansel.
- I'm saying never.
You know I love you.
- And I love you, too,
but all I'm saying--
- But, where's this but
coming from, all of a sudden?
- But I won't deal
with it again.
- If you both have
respect for one another,
there should be no
reason for either of you
to need to stray.
You should be able to ask
Ansel for whatever he's lacking
and vice-a versa.
- You're right.
- Of course he's right.
He's a man of God.
- Great, now I know Lauren
is here on a weekly basis.
But Ansel, what about you?
- Yes, I know, Pastor.
And believe me,
I will come more,
it's just first I gotta
take care of some things--
- Great, then I'll see the
both of you all Sunday.
Sunday?
- See you Sunday.
- Sunday, great.
- Oh, this is a nice store.
- I know, I'm tryin' to
redo the whole living room,
but I wanna start with the rugs.
But I'm lookin' for something
with some orange in it.
- Well, they have so
much stuff in here.
- I know.
This is cute.
- Girl, no that is not.
That look like wolf hair,
dog hair or something.
- Shut up.
[women giggle]
- Stupid.
Now, this is nice, though.
- Mm, that look more like you.
No offense.
- Uh-huh.
- That's cute, I'm gonna
write that down, Stardust.
Now, what were you
sayin' about Lorenzo?
- Oh, girl, I don't know
I just basically
fail to understand
why I have to be the
one to apologize first.
He's just too sensitive.
I don't understand that.
I mean, is it my fault he can't
take instructive criticism?
[Lauren chuckles]
And he's a man anyway.
Ain't he supposed to be tough?
Whatever.
- Now Misty, you know
you are not known
for your constructive criticism.
- And what is that
supposed to mean?
- I'm just sayin'
that sometimes you lack a
little thing called tact.
- Who?
Me?
Girl.
- Who, yes, you.
- No, I have tact.
I'm sorry, I have tact.
- Tell the truth
and shame the devil.
- [Woman] Okay, okay,
it's such a thing now.
- Nobody asked you anyway.
- Now, you guys.
- Can I get black?
- Can you get black?
No, you--
- Can I get blue?
- Can you?
No, no, no.
- [Child] Can I get pink?
- We're gonna have one
color in the whole house.
We can't have blue
and pink and black.
- Oh, uh-uh.
Girl, did she really
come out the house
with rollers in her head?
- Yes, she did.
- Don't you worry about
what it is I'm doing.
- Who you talkin' to?
[Lauren giggles]
- You are the one came
outside all unprepared.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
- What?
She don't know me.
- Misty, see?
That is exactly what
I'm talkin' about.
- Whatever.
- You need to learn to give
constructive criticism.
- You know she was wrong.
- I mean, even if she was wrong.
And she was wrong for that.
- I know she was.
- But it's not up to
you to tell her, okay?
Just chill out.
- I got you, I got you.
But anyway, what I was
sayin' about Lorenzo,
I just, all I said was,
you just don't wear sandals
with socks in the summer.
No, not unless you
movin' to Miami Beach,
old folks don't want
sand in your toes,
and even still,
you don't do that.
It's not cute.
And he think he's just fly, too.
- Socks and sandals.
- He got the nerve to
get made about it, too.
- I don't want that.
- I like it.
- [Giggles] Socks with sandals.
- He'll have to get over it.
- That's even kind of
cute on the green rug.
[slow instrumental music]
I still like this
one, I like that one.
- Lauren.
[midtempo R&B music]
- [Man] Lauren, Lauren.
- [Lauren] I don't have
anything to say to you, Jeff.
- Lauren, were you just
gonna leave me here?
- Misty.
Look, Lauren, please.
I know you're hurtin'.
- No, she's not hurt.
You're hurt and confused.
You see this rock?
Lauren does not need you.
- Okay, you know what?
Thank you, Misty, all right?
Just please, just
get in the car.
I'll only be a few minutes.
- Waste.
- You have two minutes.
What do you have to say?
- Oh, so you just gonna
get engaged on me, huh?
- Where's the confusion?
30 seconds.
- Don't you think
it's a little soon?
- [scoffs] What?
Are you kidding me with this?
What, am I just supposed to be
in mourning after you left me
for another woman?
Oh, excuse me, your wife.
At least I have
the decency to wait
until after we broke up.
Oh, but we never did
break up, did we?
You just up and left me.
- I know it might
seem like that.
But baby, I just didn't
know how to tell you.
You know I never
meant to hurt you.
- Yes, you did.
Or do you forget telling me
that you never even loved
me in the first place
and that you were just using me?
- I was angry.
Lauren, I loved you.
- Well, that was
three years ago, Jeff,
and I've moved on now.
- I still love you,
and you look great.
- Don't you dare do that.
- I deserve that.
Look, Lauren.
Now, you the best friend
anybody could ask for.
It took me a while
to realize that,
but what I did was unforgivable.
- You leavin' me saved my life.
- Well, I just hope
he makes you happy.
- He does.
He's everything you
weren't and could never be.
- [Wife] Jeff!
- Give me couple
minutes, all right?
I'll be in one second.
- What's her name?
- Look, um.
I just wanted to apologize.
- What's her name, Jeff?
- It's Sonya.
I promise, no matter
how tempting things get,
I'll never cheat on her.
- That's a promise that
you need to make to her.
Not me.
That promise doesn't have
nothin' to do with me.
- So, can I call you some time?
You know, as friends
like we used to be?
- You know, somehow no
doesn't seem like a
sufficient enough response.
Have a nice life, Jeff.
[engine hums]
[midtempo R&B music]
- I understand.
[uptempo hip hop music]
♪ He got my 'rati
♪ Hey then cut him loose
♪ Let the dog off the chain
♪ And I'm about to
put a lock on the game
♪ They call him G Fox
♪ Turn this city to roses
♪ You know the business
♪ And we gonna
make the hell raise
- [Ronnie] [chuckles]
They dig Ronnie.
- [Lauren] Ronnie.
- Yeah, let me hit
you back, okay.
- What is this I hear
about these rumors of you
hangin' out in West Hollywood?
I mean, what you do is
your business, but--
- Uh, that's right.
My business.
- Okay, but how do you expect
me to do damage control
if I don't even know
what's going on?
I mean, that's what
you pay me for.
- Hold on.
Hold on, Lauren.
Do you think I'm gay?
- I'm not sayin' anything, but.
The tabloids are
calling you a flame.
- What?
- And I quote, "Hardcore rapper
by day, homo thug by night."
- Oh no.
See, let me tell
you what happened.
Okay, I ran out of
gas, I get out the car,
and next thing I know,
paparazzi everywhere.
They're takin' pictures,
and I was just waitin'
for one of the homies.
- Okay, whatever.
But they have a
picture in here of you
in a compromising
position with--
- With who?
- A drag queen.
- That's nuts.
- Bre, Bre!
- Hold on.
I tried to catch you
before you left the office.
I know you're headin'
to lunch right now,
but I need to know
you're gonna have those
reports ready for me.
They are gonna go out by 2 p.m.
- [chuckles] You, the
director of whatever,
came all the way down here
to ask me for reports?
- Director of Central
Affairs, and yes, I did.
- You, not your secretary,
needed to come ask
me for reports.
- Are they prepared or not?
- Do you wanna
join me for lunch?
- Uh, I can't right now.
I'm right in the
middle of somethin'.
- Don't worry about it.
I understand.
- Yeah, yeah.
I gotta do somethin'
back in my office.
- Do I make you nervous?
I don't bite unless
you want me to.
[phone rings]
- [sighs] Wait, hold on.
- I can't believe it.
- [Lauren] Hold on.
- Oh my goodness.
- Hold on, I gotta
take this call.
- They know I'm street!
- Hey, what's up Misty?
- I'm out.
If he thinks he can talk to me
like some chick of the street,
he got me mixed up, girl.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Just hold on a second,
just slow down.
Now, just tell me what happened.
- Lorenzo.
- Well, I figured that much.
- You know what, he has
gotten on my last nerve,
for the last time.
I can't do this.
I'm tired.
I'm tired of him!
- Just don't do anything
drastic, just wait.
- No, no, he's out.
He's out, he's gone,
I can't do this.
Nobody.
- [Lorenzo] What do
you think you're doing?
- [Misty] You know what, I
need you out of my house.
I want you out of my house now!
- Your house?
I pay the bills here, not you!
- Lorenzo, I need
out of my house now!
- Misty!
- You get out!
- What are you doin'?
- Misty.
- No, he don't
tell me to get out.
I cook and clean, and
this son of a bitch.
How you gonna tell
me to get out?
- Get out!
- You know what, fine.
You want me out?
I'm gone.
Lauren, come get me girl
before I do somethin' to him.
- I'm with a client right now.
- Just come get me!
- All right, look,
I'm on my way, okay?
♪ Been waiting for
someone like you
♪ I'm waiting oh, I'm waiting
♪ Oh yeah
- It's just lunch.
It's just lunch.
Bre!
Hold on.
I am a little hungry.
- Lauren, where are you going?
- Look, I have to go
take care of something
really important
right now, okay?
- So, tell me a little
about your fiance?
- My best friend.
- I am in the middle
of a crisis right now.
What could be more
important than that?
- Ronnie, you are not in
the middle of a crisis.
- Oh!
- Look, I will make a
couple of phone calls
and everything will be
okay by tomorrow, okay?
- Please, Lauren, don't go.
Lauren!
They think I'm gay.
[slow R&B music]
♪ I'm waiting, oh, I'm waiting
♪ I'm waiting
- Do you still think I'm cute?
- Beautiful.
- I think you're
rather sexy yourself.
- Is that right?
- That's right.
- I'm engaged.
- Lauren, right?
- That's right.
- That's too bad.
- Are you always this forward?
- [laughs] If I see somethin'
I want, I go after it.
Life's too short,
and I like you.
- So where do you
think you're going?
So you're just gonna
stand here by the door?
[Misty sighs]
I know you hear me, Misty.
- Look, you said
what you have to say.
You wanted me out, I'm out.
- Let's talk it over.
- I want a divorce.
- A divorce?
- Thank you for comin', Lauren.
- Oh, no problem.
Hey, Renzo.
Sorry I'm late.
Ronnie started some
mess in West Hollywood
that I had to take care of.
- Oh wait, hold on.
And here are your keys.
- Don't do this.
- Let go of me!
Now, here's your ring.
- Don't be like that,
that was a wedding gift.
Talk to her, Lauren?
- No, there's nothing
to talk about.
You wanted me out, I'm out.
You don't put me
out of my house.
- Just give her some time.
I don't need any time.
- [Lorenzo] But
you can put me out?
- You call me out of my name.
- I was upset.
- Girl, just forget
about it, just let's go.
["I Remember" by Lefty]
♪ I remember I recall
♪ I remember all you said
♪ To all the youngsters
♪ All of the grown folks
♪ This place a trip
♪ Oh yeah, here we go
♪ What
♪ I remember, they thought
I wouldn't amount to nothin'
♪ Since a little scrawny kid
was always into somethin'
♪ No pops, so my
family was the rock
- I called you at lunch.
- I had a business
thing at lunch.
- I thought I saw you
walkin' with Bre today.
- Who's Bre?
- Yeah, who's Bre?
- Man, Bre is fine, brother.
She just started.
And Maxwell over here is head
of the welcoming committee,
ain't that right?
[men chuckle]
- Please, we just had
some business to discuss.
- Oh, so you couldn't
invite your boy?
- It was last minute.
- Sure it was.
- Come on.
I know ya'll don't think I
get down like that on Lauren.
- No, did you hear me say that?
- No, you?
- Hey, I'm in love with Lauren.
[man clears throat]
- You said that already brother.
- Twice.
- And I'll say it again.
I'm in love with Lauren.
And i don't appreciate ya'll
questioning my devotion.
- I mean, she is
fine. [chuckles]
- Hook me up.
- She's not your type.
- How you know my type?
- Brother, she's
everybody's type.
Man, this girl got
platooka and bladooka.
She bad man, she bad.
- Well, hook me up!
- Aren't you married?
- It's common law, my brother.
[men laugh]
- [Friend] Same thing.
- Nah.
- Hey man, I'm out, ya'll.
I got some business
to take care of.
- All right.
- Yo, we're goin'.
Yeah, let's go, my bros.
I'll talk to ya, buddy.
- All right.
- Brother, I told
you, my game is sweet.
- You got about this much game.
- Ah, man please, dude.
You crazy.
So what's goin' on?
- Gotta go see my father.
I ain't been over
there in a while.
- [sighs] That's not
what I'm talkin' about.
- What?
- Bre?
- Oh man, it's nothin'.
I'm tellin' you.
- All right, all
right. [clears throat]
- What am I gonna do?
- About what?
- Bre.
I can't stop thinkin' about her.
- I knew it, I knew it.
- Come on, man.
- Okay, okay.
- She's diggin' me, too.
- Mm-hm, let me see.
I think I got a plan for you.
- What's that?
- Ready?
Stay away from her!
- What kind of advice is that?
I work with her.
- Man, when she comes around,
just tell her you got an
important meetin' or somethin'.
You busy.
- I'm busy?
- Yeah.
- Well, I am the Director
of Central Affairs.
- Yes, you are.
- I do stay busy.
- Very.
- Mm-hm.
- Like that, I like that.
Okay, okay.
- Ansel, don't do it.
- Lauren would kill me.
- No, Lauren will leave you.
- Yeah, you're right.
It's all good.
[midtempo R&B music]
[man coughs and groans]
What's with this mess?
And who the hell are all
those people out there?
- What people?
- Those transients
in the living room.
Now what the hell
are you doing here?
- I fell.
And those transients?
Those are my friends.
- Your friends?
Whatever, man.
Do what you want.
I mean, what are
you doin' all day
that you can't pick up a
bottle or two around here?
You're in the damn bathroom,
why don't you take a shower?
It stinks in here.
- My god.
Don't nag me.
It's as if Myrtle has
come back from the dead,
and my only sanity
comes from knowing
Myrtle is dead and gone.
- Figure it out.
I'm out.
- Wait!
Wait!
I don't know why you are
getting so sensitive.
She was not your mama.
Your mother was a woman,
beautiful, strong and sweet.
Sometimes a man cannot see
the forest for the trees.
[father groans]
Did I ever tell you
about my trip to Africa?
That's a beautiful country.
I had the women there fallin'
all over themselves for me.
And they didn't mind sharing.
If you know what I mean.
- I'm sure it was great.
- The only thing I regret
about my trip to Africa
was the fact
that I missed your junior
high school graduation.
- Junior high, high
school, college.
- I never meant
to disappoint you.
- I don't have time to
listen to this right now.
- Wait!
Wait, god damn it!
I hurt, Ansel.
I hurt hard.
I wish I could have been a
better father to you kids,
but I can't take
it back, I can't!
Do you understand?
Recognize the blessings God
give you in a good woman.
- You don't have to give
me advice on women, Dad.
- I know you think
I'm an old drunk.
You probably think
you better than me.
- Dad.
- You do.
And that's fine,
quiet as it's kept.
You probably are.
- Clean up.
[sirens wail]
- Look, I told you that I
don't wanna talk about it.
That chapter of
my life is closed.
[Lauren giggles]
Oh, oh!
Girl, I'll call you back.
[uptempo hip hop music]
♪ Hey
♪ Ooh
♪ You don't know
♪ Already in love with you
♪ The first time that I saw you
♪ Everything you did
just turned me on
♪ Boy you know you
got it goin' on
♪ Boy I got a crush on you
♪ Can't get you off my mind
♪ Tell me what I gotta do
- [Pastor] I'd like to talk to
the two of you individually,
if you don't mind.
- Uh, doesn't that
defeat the purpose
of couple's counseling?
- [Pastor] I think the
two of you could benefit
from the individual attention.
- You know what, I think
that's a great idea.
Why don't you go first, baby.
- Me?
- Yeah, just get it over with.
I'll be right outside.
- Lauren is like
a daughter to me.
I'm glad she found
a man she can trust
and that can trust her.
You know, the Bible says,
"He who finds a wife,
"he finds a good thing."
- [Ansel] Amen.
- [Pastor] Is
there anything else
you'd like to talk about son?
Is there anything bothering you?
- No.
Not really, like what?
- Something at work?
You seem distracted.
Whatever you say to me will be
kept in complete confidence.
Well?
- [Ansel] Work's a
little stressful.
[phone rings]
- Babe, get the phone.
[Lauren groans]
This better be good.
- Can I crash with
you for a couple days?
- Are you okay?
- No.
- [Lauren] What's goin' on?
- Who is that?
- It's Misty.
- Lauren, he hit me.
- He hit you?
Why don't you just
come over here, honey.
- Are you sure?
Is it okay with Ansel?
- Yes, just come
over here, Misty.
Do you need me to
come pick you up?
- No.
I'll be over there in a few.
- Oh, come in, come in.
Oh my goodness.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine now.
- Oh my god.
Oh my god, what happened?
- Girl, you know the score.
He got mad because I said it
wasn't workin' out anymore.
I'm tellin' you, Lauren.
I'm sick and tired of
this sensitive crap.
Every time I open my
mouth and say somethin',
he gets his feelings hurt.
But I tell you one thing,
that's the last time
he gonna hit me.
- Well, did you talk to
Pastor Smith like I said?
- Lauren, come on.
- I mean, you really
shouldn't have had
to work it out on your own
before talkin' to
somebody about it first.
- Look, I shouldn't have
tried to work it out period.
- Misty, that is your husband.
- I don't care who he is.
He ain't my dog gone daddy!
And I don't give no
man permission to
put his hands on me.
I don't care what I
said, I'm his wife.
- Look, Misty, I'm not tryin'
to make excuses for him, okay?
Lord knows if you
went back to him,
I'd be the first one to
kick your butt myself.
- Girl, you ain't gonna
kick nobody's butt.
[women giggle]
- You right about that.
But seriously, though, I
have to tell you somethin'.
I am a lethal weapon.
[women laugh]
- Get outta here.
- No, no, look.
You can stay as long
as you need to, okay?
Mi casa es su casa.
- Oh, I love you girl.
- I love you too, sweetie.
- And thank you so much.
- No, no problem.
- I'm just like always
thankin' you for something.
- Mm-mm.
- Guardian angel.
- Get you some rest, okay?
And I'll see you in the morning.
Make yourself at home.
- All right.
Good night.
- Good night.
- [groans] Is she okay?
- Yeah, she'll be fine.
I guess there's never any
guarantees when you get married.
They used to be
so happy together.
- Are you having
second thoughts?
- No.
I don't know.
I mean, how well do we
really know each other?
He hit her.
- Baby, I love you.
And I would never put
my hands on a woman.
Especially not one
as sweet as you.
You're beautiful,
loving, kind-hearted,
and you can cook your butt off.
[Lauren giggles]
I would never do
anything to hurt you.
- I love you.
- I love you back.
[Lauren sighs]
Okay, I'll have my
secretary fax those over
first thing in the morning.
Okay.
Bye.
What are you doing?
- I feel like you've
been avoiding me lately.
- I've just been busy.
- What, you don't
like me anymore?
I know I'm not
the only one who--
- Look, what we've been
doing is a mistake.
- There are no mistakes.
Besides, we haven't
done anything yet.
- Look, I admit.
There is some attraction here.
But I'm in love with my fiance.
- You're, you're right.
I was wrong to pursue it.
I'm sorry.
- No, wait.
I was wrong.
- Knock, knock, knock, knock.
Ooh, I'm sorry, did I
interrupt something?
- Spencer, what you
still doin' here?
- I'm gonna talk to you later.
- I was workin' late.
Man, what are you
doin' with that woman?
Look, I told you to stay away.
- I know, she just came in here.
The woman's tryin'
to eat me alive.
Spencer, you gotta help me.
- You need Jesus.
- I go to church.
- But do you listen?
Like when the minister's sayin',
do not commit sins
against the flesh.
I am a man who's about
to marry this woman.
- You ain't helpin' me.
- Today, that we
have to be careful
how we abuse our relationships.
God is saying we
have to be careful
how we take our young
ladies for granted,
we have to be careful
of how we perceive them,
how we deal with them
because God is sayin'
that when you find a wife,
you're not just
findin' somebody.
When you find a wife,
you not just findin'
something off the shelf,
but when you find a
wife, God is sayin'
you have found a good thing.
God is trying to
get us to see, men,
that when we find a
wife, God is saying
he's ready to open up
the windows of heaven
and began to pour
out a blessin'.
And God is sayin' that blessing
comes in many fashions.
He said this blessing
comes as a treasure.
A treasure to you that's
better than diamonds,
a treasure that's greater and
can shine sharper than gold,
a treasure that can be
favorable unto the world
to ever ending.
And so we find that God
is trying to get us to see
that when you find a wife,
you have found something.
When you found a wife
that you have saw
and caught God's attention.
When you find a wife, God
is tryin' to get us to see
that that's all you really need.
God is tryin' to get us to see
that when we find a wife,
he said you not only
found favor with God,
but when you find
favor with God,
God is sayin' I'm going to give
you favor that have riches.
I'm not talkin' about
riches of this world,
but riches that's going to last.
I'm talkin' about favor that
somebody's gonna love you
despite of, favor that God is
going to keep havin' this wife
give you hope, favor that this
wife is going to protect you
when nobody else is
gonna protect you.
Favor that will last when
nothin' else will last.
God is tryin' to get us to see
that there's a great treasure
when you find a wife,
a wife that is beauty,
a wife that is awesome,
a wife that is ever-lasting,
a wife that is going to keep
you and stick by your side
when nobody else will
stick by your side.
I'm talkin' about even when
your friends turn your back,
you got a wife to go to.
Even when folk lie on you,
Even when folks stab
you in the back,
God is sayin' this wife
that I've given you
has many treasures,
a treasure to love
you unconditionally
when you mess up.
God says she still
gonna love you.
Even when you don't do right,
God says she's gonna
stick by your side,
even when you don't act
right, God is sayin'
that wife will
show favor upon you
that's goin' to stick with you,
when nobody else
will stick with you.
The man that finds a wife.
God is sayin' has
found somethin'.
Not just any old
thing, but something.
God is sayin' a good thing.
And we've got to understand
that when God has blessed us
despite of our short comings
despite of all the
things we used to do,
God is sayin' I still
showing favor upon you
by His grace and by his mercy,
and I'm willin' to
give you a good thing.
Now, this good thing is
just not going to open up
in the beginning,
but God is sayin'
you got to love this thing back,
you got to shake this thing up.
You gotta work with it to get it
to what God really
called for it to do.
God is saying, when he bring
man and woman together,
we become one.
That means when I
hurt, she hurts.
When she hurts, I hurt.
And God is sayin' when
we love, and I love,
she's gonna love.
When I began to forgive,
she's going to forgive.
And when I began to
show unconditional love,
she's going to show that back
in return and vice-a versa.
God is saying, this
is the kind of favor
that comes from the
Lord because we know
that God so loved the world,
that he gave His
only begotten son
and God is sayin', we got to
have this same old agape love
for when we find a wife.
So we just don't find a wife,
but God has shown favor to
design and to lead a wife to us.
We may have met her
at a football game,
we may have met her at the club,
we may have met
her on the street,
but God is sayin'
when you find her,
you've found a good thing.
- [Congregation] Amen.
[congregation applauds]
- Thank you.
- [Pastor] God bless you.
- Oh, that was a really
good sermon today, Pastor.
- Thank you so much.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- I'll look for you tomorrow
- Okay.
- [Pastor] God bless.
A pleasure seeing
you, thank you.
[midtempo R&B music]
- Talk.
- [Jeff] I know it was wrong
of me to come here like this.
- Yes, it was.
Hold all my calls, please.
- [Jeff] Sonya and I separated.
- So?
What does that
got to do with me?
- It was over that incident
in the parking lot.
- Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
- Well, it looks like you're
movin' up in the world.
- I can't complain.
- You don't have
to act like that.
All right, I'm here to
tell you that I love you,
and my leaving you was the
biggest mistake I ever made.
- Well, what's done is done.
Let's just leave it at that.
- Just tell me you don't love
me anymore, and I'll leave.
- Look, you're gonna leave
me alone, regardless.
And I do love you.
Unfortunately, I'll
probably always love you,
but I'm not gonna continue
to make a fool of
myself for you, Jeff.
- [Jeff] I want you
back, I need you back.
- No.
- Why not?
- Hello, I'm engaged!
- You didn't say
you were in love.
- Well, that goes
without saying.
Besides, I don't
want you anymore.
- Now, you don't mean that.
- You've hurt me.
I've taken you back
a hundred times,
and a hundred times
you've hurt me.
Why would I do that
to myself again?
- Because you love me, too.
- I can't.
And you need to leave.
- All right, fine.
You have my number.
Call me anytime.
- Don't ever come
back here again, Jeff.
[uptempo R&B music]
- Where's my boy?
Ansel!
His mother named him that.
Who ever heard of a black
man named Ansel anyway?
Ansel!
Need some wine.
- Why are you talkin' so loud?
- I need some money!
- Calm down.
Have a seat.
What's wrong with you?
[midtempo R&B music]
- Pastor, he just,
he just walked right
up into my office
like we were old buddies.
- I just gave you some
money the other day.
- They're talkin' about
foreclosin' on the house.
I don't care, forget it.
Forget it.
- Have you been drinking?
- I'm a grown damn man.
- Then you need to act like one
and show some
respect for yourself.
- I can't deny that I still
have some feelings for him,
but I love Ansel.
I would never do
anything to hurt him.
I just can't believe
Jeff had the nerve
to do somethin' like that.
- Well, did you give
him any reason to think
that he would have
another chance prior?
- No.
I mean, he probably thinks
that I'll take him back
like I've always done.
He'll just give me that
sad little puppy dog look,
and everything will be okay.
- Are you embarrassed
of your old man, Ansel?
Your mother named
you that, by the way.
- Yes, I know.
You seem to feel the
need to remind me of that
every time you get drunk.
- You should have been a junior.
- Oh, god.
What's going on with the house.
I thought the
house was paid for.
- But I am done
with that, Pastor.
I'm a different person now.
- I believe that.
But you know, once you
give yourself spiritually
to someone, you become one.
That person becomes
a part of you.
It's important for
you to understand
that first he must put God first
and then you second.
- I took out a second
mortgage on the house
to pay some people I owed,
and now they talkin'
about takin' my house!
- I'll look into it.
- Are you gonna give
me some money or what?
- And God has an order in order
for a marriage to be happy,
not perfect, but happy.
He still feels connected to you.
And I think the best thing to do
is continue to pray for him.
- Hm.
You know, I never even
looked at it like that.
Thank you, Pastor.
- You're welcome.
[Lauren giggles]
My prayers will be with you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
[Lauren hums]
- Hey baby.
- Wow.
What's the occasion?
- Well, Misty is staying with
her cousin Jamal tonight,
so we're all alone again.
- So, does that mean--
- No, Ansel I told you, not
until after the wedding.
But, I can give you
a nice bubble bath
and I can give you a
nice hot oil massage.
Mm, baby you're so tense.
- Yeah.
My dad came by the office today.
All drunk and talkin' crazy.
- Aw, honey I'm sorry.
- I had to go pay
his second mortgage.
They're about to
foreclose on the house.
- After I give you your massage,
we can cuddle up
and fall asleep.
It'll be nice.
- Great.
Can't wait.
- Oh, don't be like
that, it'll be fun.
Come on.
[midtempo R&B music]
- Man, I can't
take this no more.
I have got to get some.
- So what, you mean you
guys ain't doin' it?
- Nah, man.
Ever since we started this
premarital counseling,
all of a sudden we're abstaining
until after the wedding.
- Abstaining as in all sex?
- All sex.
- Brother, I'm sorry to
hear about that, man.
- Wedding's not for
another two months, man.
I think I'm gonna
die before then.
- I mean you've gone
two months before.
Right?
- Yeah, but I was single then.
Sleeping alone.
I wasn't layin' next
to the temptation.
That's like wavin' a bag
of bones in front of a dog
and tellin' him not to eat it.
- So what, you're callin'
yourself a dog now?
- No, man, what I'm sayin' is
I don't know how much
longer I can take this, man.
Bre is drivin' me crazy.
All my thoughts
are focused on her.
Her lips, her hips.
- Listen, man, the reason
you're all focusin'
and fantasizin' about her is
because she's forbidden fruit.
Look, the minute you bite
into that fruit, man,
you're gonna lose everything.
So stop thinkin' about it.
- What?
- You know what.
It.
- I really like
Turner's idea for us
to relaunch that First
Five LA campaign.
We really need to
relaunch that in West LA,
like immediately.
- I think it'd be good too
at the end of the year.
- Really?
[phone rings]
- This is Ansel.
- Hey baby.
- Hey.
- Yeah, I'm gonna go
out to my mom's house
for a couple of days to pick
up some stuff for the wedding,
so I'll probably be
back in a couple days.
- Uh, okay.
You're gonna be
stayin' at your mom's?
- Yeah.
- Um, all right, well call
me when you get a chance.
- I love you.
- Love you, too.
So, where were we?
- I think you were
about to ask me
over to your place tonight.
- Is that right?
- What's wrong, you
can't keep a secret?
- I can keep a secret.
["Next 2 Me" by Damion]
♪ Next to me
♪ Girl I just want
you next to me
♪ Your body's trapped
and it's callin' me
♪ Well, I'm here to set you free
♪ Next to me
♪ Girl I just want
you next to me
♪ Your body's locked
and I've got the key
♪ There's time to open up for me
♪ Girl I see you walkin' 'round
♪ Can't you see me find me now
♪ Girl I'm concentrating girl
♪ Wonder what's on your mind
♪ So I tap you on your shoulder
♪ As if I already knew you
♪ But to my surprise
the look in your eyes
♪ Prove that my search is over
♪ Next to me
♪ Girl I just want
you next to me
- After I give you a massage,
we can cuddle up
and fall asleep.
- So that's it?
- What do you want?
- What do I want?
Don't get all
self-righteous on me now.
- Wait.
Don't leave me like that.
- You don't regret it, do you?
- Not yet.
Maybe if we do it one more time.
♪ Taste of your lips keeps me
[phone rings]
Hello?
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
- What's going on, I
tried to call you earlier
but you didn't
answer your phone.
- Yeah, I must have missed it.
- Well, what are you doing?
- Nothing, why?
- I'm just asking.
Are you okay, you seem
a little preoccupied.
- No, I'm fine, I'm
just readin' the paper.
- Oh, well, I was just
calling you to tell you
that I made it to
my mom's house okay,
and she says my aunt is sick.
So I'm gonna go have
to visit her tomorrow,
so I probably won't
be back until Sunday.
- Okay, okay.
- Don't forget that
you have that meeting
with the pastor tomorrow.
- I think I'm just
gonna relax tomorrow.
- Ansel, come on.
- Okay, um, yeah, I'll be there.
- All right.
Love you!
- Me too, bye.
[plane roars]
[uptempo R&B music]
[Lauren knocks]
- Hi, babe.
- Hey.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
What you doin' here?
- Well, hello to you too.
- I mean, when'd you get in?
- Just now.
- How was your flight?
- [Lauren] It was fine.
[Ansel clears throat]
- Mom okay?
- She's fine.
- That's good.
- Well, I did come over here
to surprise you for lunch,
but I guess I shouldn't
have bothered.
- Lauren.
Lauren, wait!
[midtempo R&B music]
Lauren.
Lauren, I'm home.
Spencer said hi.
Lauren.
Hey.
You hear me callin' you?
Why'd you run out
my office like that?
- If you were so concerned,
why didn't you come see about me
instead of going out
with your friends?
And why'd you change the sheets?
- Oh, um, I spilled
some ice cream on it.
- Ice cream, huh?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothin'.
- I missed you.
- Yeah, I can tell.
[phone rings]
Well, aren't you
gonna answer it?
- Hello?
Yeah, I had to run
out the office.
I'll be back in tomorrow.
Okay.
- Who was that?
- Oh, Spencer.
- Spencer.
- Baby.
Are you gonna stay
pissed off at me,
you ain't gonna give me a
kiss or a hug or something?
I'm sorry.
You came in, I was just busy.
I was right in the middle of
something really important
and I needed to get it finished.
When you came in, you caught
me by surprise, that's all.
Come on.
- All right, I'm sorry.
Guess I just jump to
conclusions or somethin'.
- Yeah.
- I'm glad you brought
your butt home.
[Lauren chuckles]
- I missed you.
- I missed you, too.
[phone rings]
- Yeah?
[Lauren giggles]
Look, I'm gonna have
to talk to you later.
- [Bre] [sobbing]
You know the second
you don't wanna do
this I can't believe!
- I'm gonna have to
give you a call later.
- [Bre] Please.
- Look, I can't talk right now.
- [Bre] Oh gosh.
[Ansel yells]
[Lauren laughs]
- Ah, you so jumpy.
- It's 'cause you always
sneakin' up on me.
- I wasn't checkin' up on you.
I was cold, so I came
to get a blanket,
thank you very much.
- [Woman On Television] I
never worried about shopping.
As many chances as I gave him,
he'd be broke today.
He gave this bitch eight
months since we broke up.
You need to get
on with your life.
I'm sure as hell back all alone.
- Where you goin'?
- I'll be back.
- [Lauren] Where you goin'?
[somber instrumental music]
[Ansel knocks]
[phone beeps]
Hey Misty, it's Lauren.
I need to talk to
you, so call me back.
[Ansel knocks]
- [Ansel] Spencer!
Spencer!
- No you didn't.
- What am I gonna do?
- Um, hi, Jeff?
I need to talk to you.
- How am I going to tell her?
- You don't tell her.
You end it with Bre, and throw
that old bone in the closet.
I suggest you tell her tonight.
- I can't.
- What you mean, you can't?
- I know we'd just end
up having sex again.
- Brother, are you that weak?
Look, you got a good
woman, a beautiful woman.
Look, why you gonna
throw that all away
over some girl you
hardly even know?
Hold up man, you got me
feelin' like a chick right now.
Don't be no ass.
- You're right, you're right.
- Then call her right now.
- Now?
- Yeah, not now, but right now.
- [Bre] Hi, baby.
Did you change your mind?
- Are you busy?
- [Bre] No.
- Can you meet me?
- [Bre] Sure, sweetie,
but what's up?
- I'll talk to you
when I see you.
[seat creaks]
- This is a bad idea.
- No.
What's going on?
- Me and my fiance,
we got in a fight.
- Over what?
- I don't know.
I think he's seein'
someone else.
- I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
- I understand.
- It's just not right.
I can barely look
her in the eye.
- So, what do we do now?
- I don't know.
- Should we just act like
nothing ever happened?
- Can you do that?
- I don't know.
- I appreciate
you understanding.
- I came in knowing, sweetie.
I just wish it would have
lasted a little while longer.
You're special.
[midtempo R&B music]
I guess I'll see you at work.
- Yeah.
Baby?
- Well, I never thought
I'd be sayin' this,
but you don't know for sure,
you can't go around
jumpin' to conclusions.
- I'm not stupid, Jeff.
- Lauren?
[Ansel sighs]
- Then just ask.
- Just ask?
Yeah, right.
Like he's really gonna
tell me the truth.
- Lauren, just ask him.
Believe me, then you'll
know whether or not
he's tellin' the truth.
Or you can challenge the game.
Go ahead and get married, and
hope he's learned his lesson.
Have a bunch of kids,
get fat. [chuckles]
[Lauren chuckles]
Live happily ever after.
- Yeah, you're right.
Thank you.
- No problem.
I still love you.
- So.
How's your wife?
- We got separated.
I told you that.
- You got any kids
I don't know about?
- None that I know
about. [laughs]
[midtempo R&B music]
- Lauren.
Lauren.
[phone buzzes]
Where have you been all night?
- The same place you've been.
Out.
- So that's how you
talkin' to me now?
- You walked out
on me, remember?
- And I apologized.
- So where'd you go?
- I just needed some air.
- Well, so did I.
- Lauren.
Lauren!
Lauren. [knocks]
Lauren, open this door.
- [Lauren] Sleep on the couch.
- Lauren. [knocks]
[Lauren sighs]
- Good afternoon.
- Hi, Pastor.
- I suspect the both of
you are blessed today.
- Doin' pretty good.
- I missed you
this weekend Ansel.
- Yeah, I apologize.
Something came up this weekend.
- I understand.
Is there something
I should know?
You know, this is this last
session before the wedding.
- Yeah, Ansel.
Is there something
I should know?
- I told you I needed
to rest this weekend.
- And I told you not to
miss the appointment.
Look, if you're not into this,
or if you're having second
thoughts or something,
you should just tell me now
because I don't need a man
who's just going
through the motions
just because that's what it
takes to get what he wants.
- What is that supposed to mean?
What are you talkin' about?
- I'm talkin' about you.
Ever since I came back
from my mom's house
you've been trippin'.
- That's because you're always
accusing me of cheating.
- I'm not accusing
you of anything,
and I never even
mentioned cheating.
So if you're feeling
guilty about something,
then that's your fault.
- I don't feel guilty.
- [scoffs] Then where
were you this weekend?
- I told you, my father
was having some problems.
Do we have to talk
about this here?
- Ansel, we are in counseling.
What better place is
there to talk about it?
- My father has nothing
to do with this.
- Are you kidding me?
Your father has everything
to do with this.
Have you ever even thought
about bringing him to church?
He needs help, Ansel.
What he doesn't need is somebody
who constantly enables him
to keep on doing
the same damn thing!
I'm sorry, Pastor, but--
- So now, all of a sudden,
you're all concerned
with my father.
- Ansel, don't act like
this is the first time
we've talked about this.
- May I interrupt?
- Excuse me, Pastor,
just hold on.
- Who are you accountable to?
- Myself.
- That's all I needed to know.
Excuse me, Pastor, thank you.
- Where you goin'?
Lauren.
Lauren!
Excuse me, Pastor.
♪ Lord give me wisdom
♪ That I might do your will
♪ And Lord give me knowledge
♪ That I might know your word
♪ Teach me to know your will
♪ I will wait
♪ That I might serve you
♪ Each and every day
♪ Lord give me wisdom
♪ So that I might serve you well
♪ Lord give me patience
- I just need to get away.
- Whatever.
- I'm gonna ask you this
one time, and one time only.
Are you seeing someone else?
- No.
Baby, I love you.
It's you I wanna marry.
- And I want someone
who loves God
more than they love me.
More than he loves himself.
♪ So that I might serve you well
- Steve.
- What?
- Steve, you don't remember?
- S-S-Steve?
[Misty laughs]
Stuttering Steve.
- I used to tell him,
just figure it out.
[Lauren laughs]
Oh, I frustrated him, too.
You know, I officially
filed for divorce.
- Really?
- [Misty] Yeah.
- [Lauren] Wow.
- And you know, I've been
thinkin' about what you said.
You know, about talkin'
to Pastor Smith.
- Oh, Misty that is so great.
That's good, that's really good.
He's gonna help you out a lot.
- Yeah, but girl
it's been a journey.
I finally realize that
there's just some things
you can't get through
without God's help.
- Ain't that the truth.
Mm-hm.
- And that's probably
why I had it so rough.
- Yes, indeed.
- You look different.
- Different how?
- I don't know, just different.
It's true what they say.
When you go through
a whole lot of stuff,
it shows all over your face.
- I guess you're right.
- That's all right, you strong.
You my girl. [giggles]
- Learn from the best, huh?
- Yeah.
Do you know what?
I miss you.
I've missed you.
- Well, you here now.
- You mind if I stay and
enjoy the fire with you?
- Of course.
You can stay all
night if you want to.
- Okay, well break
out the champagne.
[women laugh]
[somber instrumental music]
- Dad.
Dad!
Oh my god, Dad!
Dad, Dad, Dad!
No, please God,
please, please, please.
Dad!
Dad, Dad!
- Yes, yes, 911.
My father, I think he
overdosed on pills.
Dad!
Yes, please send somebody quick!
[somber instrumental music]
- [Lauren] Who are
you accountable to?
- [Ansel] Myself.
- [Lauren] I just
need to get away.
- If you are reading this
letter, then I am gone.
I can only hope I'm not
jumping to conclusions,
but I know I'm not trippin',
'cause that's not my earring
I stepped on in my living room.
- [Lauren] I gave you every
chance to admit you're wrong,
but you didn't take it.
I can't say that
I don't love you.
But I can say that I know
who I'm accountable to,
and that is God.
You might want to try and find
out how you can do the same.
- They gonna be lookin'
at my face and my wallet.
- Let me see.
Oh yeah, you're sharp.
Cute as a button,
cute as a button.
- I'm gonna be all right.
[Ansel laughs]
- [Lauren] Believe it or not,
I understand why you
didn't wanna tell me
you've been seeing
another woman.
I guess I made it clear
that I wouldn't accept it.
That still doesn't
give you the right
to pretend it never happened.
I hope you find the real Jesus,
and I hope you found
your real true love.
Lauren.
♪ The blood
♪ That Jesus shed
♪ For me
♪ Way back on Calvary
♪ The blood that
gives me strength
♪ From day to day
♪ It will never
♪ Never never never lose
♪ His power
♪ How can help me signal now
♪ Reach yes
♪ To the highest, to
the highest mountain
♪ High and this is
what you should do
♪ Let me tell you now
♪ It blows, it blows
♪ To the lowest, to
the lowest valley
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ The love that
gives me strength
♪ From day to day
♪ It will never, never, oh
it will never, never lose
♪ I'm gonna leave
you with this ya'll
♪ His power
- All right, last shot.
- I think I met the one, man.
- Man, you always
think you met the one.
- Where'd you meet her at?
- At the club.
- You ain't gonna meet
the one at the club, man.
- There are some good
ones at the club.
[men laugh]
- I go to the club.
- My point exactly.
You're not talkin' about
that weird girl you met
the other night when
we went out, are you?
- She's not weird, she's
a little bit different.
- No, not different, weird.
The girl's weird.
- All right, see if I
tell you anything else.
- Hey Ansel, you talk
to Lauren or what?
- Nah.
- That's messed up, man.
- You was almost married.
- Yeah, it's my fault, though.
I messed up.
- Look, don't worry about it.
She'll come back.
- I don't think so.
- You still talkin' to Bre?
- Nah, way too different.
It just wasn't any more
fun after the hunt.
Twin.
- Yeah?
- You really like this girl?
- Yeah, man.
She's cool.
- You know, the Bible says,
"He who finds a wife
finds a good thing."
You really like this girl,
you should make her your wife.
Damn what everybody else says.
[midtempo R&B music]
[phone rings]
Hello?
Hey.
No.
Yeah.
Okay.
Bye.
[children chatter playfully]
Thank you.
["Lane to Lane" by Slane]
♪ He got my 'rati
♪ Then they cut him loose
♪ Let the dog off the chain
♪ And I'm about to
put a lock on the game
♪ They call him G fox
♪ From the city of roses
♪ We'll make the motel raise
♪ You know the business
♪ And we gonna
make the hell raise
♪ We gonna make the motel raise
♪ Then we gonna blaze
♪ High octane
boostin' lane to lane
♪ And if it ain't full blown
♪ Leave it alone
♪ Park your ride outside
if it ain't all grown
♪ We make the motel raise
♪ Then we gonna blaze
♪ High octaine
boostin' lane to lane
♪ And if it ain't full blown
♪ Leave it at home
♪ Park your ride outside
if it ain't all grown
♪ You got nitro, then
you might go fast
♪ The dog chase
suckers over vapor law
♪ Fade 'em all, 454
and I ain't gonna stall
♪ Like a rock my Chevy's a whole
♪ Pound for pound, false
case buzz in the trunk
♪ Next to the pump with
surround by the sound
♪ Now disturb the
peace like Luda
♪ Praise the Buddha
♪ Flip game like Kamasutra
♪ I'll be there fast parkin' DMV
♪ I rock Zifferelli
is the way I'm seen
♪ They got highway patrol,
interstate troopers
♪ All they see is
white like rotor rooter
♪ Eat sauce from the crime boss
♪ They try to run my place
♪ Mad 'cause I say I
bounce like Norman Bates