(energetic electronic music)
- [Elenora] Tell me, children,
what do you know about the vampires?
(ominous rock music)
♪ That skirt doesn't hide ♪
♪ The truth of your intentions ♪
♪ My face doesn't hide ♪
♪ The death of my passion ♪
♪ And I could walk a mile ♪
♪ Across your wicked smile ♪
♪ Or lay here for a while ♪
♪ And wind up witless tonight ♪
♪ You make me sick ♪
♪ Sick and bored ♪
♪ You make me feel like ♪
♪ Feel like a whore ♪
♪ You make me sick ♪
(screams)
(tense music)
(foreboding piano music)
(rain patters)
(thunder rumbles)
(banging)
(woman roars)
(film reel clicks)
(dramatic music)
(foreboding music)
(horn honks)
(relaxed bass music)
- [Hitchhiker] Live here?
- I'm staying here.
I bid you enter of your own free will.
- Okay.
Really, you live here.
- I told you I was staying here.
- Alone?
- You ask a lot of questions.
- I just wanna know who
all the players are.
- Are we playing?
- You know we are.
- Would you like to clean up?
- Sure.
- What size are you?
- Excuse me?
- Shirt size, pant size?
The owner left some clothes,
and I'm sure he wouldn't
mind if we used them.
- Large shirt, 38 waist.
Just like high school.
- I believe we can accommodate.
(foreboding music)
- Sorry.
Why did you pick me up anyway?
- Seemed like the thing to do.
- When I'm standing there,
I just watch the cars go by.
There's nothing much else
to do but that or think,
and I don't like to think.
Then your car passed by.
A few minutes later you
came back and picked me up.
Why?
- I liked the way you looked.
- So you picked me up to fuck me.
- [Theodora] I picked
you up to bring you here.
Whatever happens after that...
- Doesn't happen a lot, but it happens.
- [Theodora] Does it?
- Some chick drives by, sees the package,
starts to ask herself what it'd be like.
What it'd be like to
pick me up, take me home,
have her way with me.
Oh yeah, it happens.
- Now you're hurting my feelings,
I thought I was going to be your first.
- You're too late to be my first.
I'm not yours either.
- My what, my first hitchhiker?
- Sure, am I?
What are you?
- What am I?
- Nationality, Italian?
What is this stuff?
- It's wine.
- [Hitchhiker] Where's the bedroom?
(unsettling music)
(serene piano music)
(ominous music)
(gun fires)
(woman yelps)
(screeches)
(screams)
(crickets chirp)
(wolf howls)
(gasps)
- Somebody's out there!
- What the fuck?
What?
I don't see anything.
- [Sky] Where are you going?
- [Morrissey] I'm gonna go look about.
- Be careful.
- I'll be all right,
stay here.
(door opens)
There's nothing.
What did you see out there?
- A hand, a bloody hand
hitting the window.
- [Morrissey] There's nothing.
- I definitely saw something.
- [Morrissey] Were you dreaming?
- Don't start.
- I'm not starting, I'm just asking.
So you saw a hand hit the window.
- [Sky] Yes.
- Man's hand, woman's?
- I don't know, what does it matter?
- [Morrissey] You said it was bloody.
- Yes, that I know.
- Well, there's no blood on the window.
There's nothing on the window
except for some bird crap.
Just a big damn bird.
- You think I was dreaming?
- Bird crap.
(Morrissey sighs)
- I dreamed that two
women were making love.
- I could use a dream like that.
Sorry.
- I shot them.
- [Morrissey] Well, it's a good thing
I don't subscribe to Freud.
- Then I woke up, I heard a sound,
I looked out the window,
and a hand hit the glass.
- Is that kinda like the
shit hitting the fan?
- You are so not funny.
- Come on.
Come on, Sky, I'm sorry.
- No.
- I'm sorry.
Baby, I'm sorry.
I was just trying to lighten the mood.
Hm?
You want to...
- You are impossible, no.
Early to bed, early to
get started, remember?
(phone rings)
- Saved by the bell, great.
- [Sky] Hold onto that for me, won't you?
- Oh, well, it's always
there if you need it.
(sighs) So you're just gonna
leave me just like that, huh?
- [Sky] You can always
take things into hand.
- Nice.
Thanks.
So you wanna fuck or what?
Cause I think that's a yes.
Cause I'm feeling yes.
Yeah, no?
Oh.
I see.
(foreboding music)
- It is just memory.
(cries)
It is just time.
Taste the past.
- No.
It was Bulgaria.
How they would burn, kill,
violate women and children.
And nail the prisoners' ears to fences
where they would hang them in the morning.
- Don't do this to yourself.
- I can see the bodies
hanging from the trees.
I can hear the rope scratching the bark.
- They're humans.
They're animals.
- Imagine a baby in the
arms of a trembling mother,
surrounding by men who
have just entered her home.
They're having great fun.
They fondle the baby and
they try to make it laugh,
and they are successful, yet lax.
That moment a man pulls out a pistol,
points it inches from the baby's face.
The baby stretches out its
fingers to touch the pistol,
and it laughs.
And suddenly, the man pulls the trigger,
and blows the baby's brains out!
(gasps)
Artistic, isn't it?
- Time to sleep.
- Just look at this.
Whoa.
There's gotta be 30, 40
years of history here.
It's just the top layer.
- [Morrissey] Will you be
all right here for a while?
- [Sky] Yeah.
- [Morrissey] Sky, come here!
- What is it?
Well that would put an
end to the festivities.
What do you think it means?
- I saw this in Bosnia.
This is what was written on the wall
where I found my grandfather's body.
It's the Jan Kantas, the symbol
for the castrating mother,
the all-consuming female.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
That was a long time ago.
- Hey, sorry.
- What?
- [Sky] What's this?
- This.
- This looks like cuneiform.
It's a little bit different,
what the hell is this doing here?
- [Sky] Shouldn't be here.
Didn't really want too many
to be here, a collector?
- I don't know.
I'll take it to the lab.
- [Sky] There can't be any more.
- This just might be graffiti, but...
(camera shutter clicks)
God damn it!
- [Sky] Are you all right?
- [Morrissey] Not really.
- Let me see.
I said let me see it.
- Ow.
- You may need stitches.
- [Morrissey] Come on.
- Or at least a good cleaning.
What did you do?
- Uh, I cut it.
- No shit, Sherlock.
Let's get you back to camp.
Here, go.
- [Morrissey] It hurts.
- [Sky] Deserve it.
(rumbling)
(tense synth music)
(serene humming)
- This is fantastic.
You live here?
Is there someone else here?
- Only you and I.
Perhaps a ghost or two.
(foreboding music)
Would you like to take a shower, clean up?
(suspenseful music)
♪ Look back in sorrow ♪
♪ See my sins of the past ♪
♪ I fear tomorrow ♪
♪ How long can this last ♪
- You're staring.
- You remind me of someone
I knew a long time ago.
- Wasn't me.
I would've remembered.
- Memory can be a funny thing.
- [Dietrich] How so?
- Well, I forget things
that I should remember,
and sometimes I remember
things that never happened.
- [Dietrich] I think I know what you mean.
(train horn blares)
(rhythmic ethnic music)
- What is this?
- It's Mormon.
(ominous rock music)
♪ I can taste your fear as I ♪
♪ Lick away the teardrop
from your breast ♪
♪ It excites me in a way ♪
♪ That I can't explain ♪
♪ And I'll feel your nails as if they ♪
♪ Are still tearing the
flesh away from my spine ♪
♪ Twisting up my cells,
my head, my future ♪
♪ You're like a drug I can't deny ♪
♪ And even when I sleep,
I dream and I see you ♪
♪ Go running right behind my eyes ♪
♪ And I swear I'll have
to cut my own head off ♪
♪ To cut you out of my mind ♪
♪ Come on, why ♪
♪ Must you hurt me just
to make me feel so good ♪
♪ Come on, you've got me coming ♪
♪ Now I'm coming inside
while you're drawing me ♪
♪ Why don't you just leave ♪
♪ Just before I break ♪
♪ Every time I try to die,
you pick me up again ♪
♪ Feed me poison ♪
♪ Still you keep me alive ♪
♪ Why is it so hard for you ♪
♪ Just let me die ♪
♪ I said why is this so hard for you ♪
♪ I can feel your angel touching me ♪
♪ I can feel my insides tied to you ♪
♪ But why can I feel my heart ♪
♪ Spill onto the floor ♪
♪ Still you keep me, I turn around again ♪
♪ I can feel my wrist ♪
♪ Torn up from my sleeve ♪
♪ Hear you promise me I'm in Heaven ♪
♪ Why don't you just leave ♪
♪ Just before I break ♪
♪ Every time I try to die
you pick me up again ♪
♪ Feed me poison ♪
♪ Still you keep me alive ♪
♪ Why is it so hard for you ♪
♪ Just let me die ♪
- Do you have to leave in the morning?
- No, I don't have to be anywhere at all.
- You say that with such sadness.
- It's sad, isn't it?
Nobody's waiting for me.
No one's expecting me.
And if I died right
now, nobody would know.
Or care.
Christ.
Listen to me.
How melodramatic can you get?
- I would care.
- Why would you care?
- I don't know.
- In the morning, can we explore?
- You can do whatever you
want, I won't stop you.
- Anywhere at all?
- Through any door that isn't locked.
- Locked doors?
- There are always locked doors.
(foreboding music)
- Good morning.
Are you the owner?
- [Dietrich] No, I'm just visiting.
- [Sky] Visiting, does
somebody live there?
(train horn blares)
- You know, I'm not sure.
- Hey, how you doing?
- All right.
I'm Dietrich.
- [Morrissey] Morrissey.
- Nice to meet you.
- Sky.
- Nice to meet you, Sky.
- Don't ask.
- [Dietrich] So this is, so
what are you guys doing here?
This is a strange place to be camping.
- Yeah, well, we're starting
a new fad, you know?
Urban camping, maybe you heard of it.
- Really?
- No, no, not really.
- Ignore him, the thinks he's funny.
We're from the university,
Department of Urban Archeology.
- [Dietrich] What are you
guys doing on the terminal?
- Unfortunately we're not.
We're not allowed in.
- Private owner, refuses all requests,
won't return phone calls.
Just lets it sit there rotting.
We were hoping you were him.
- Sorry.
- Hey, hey,
is there any coffee?
- I was just gonna make some fresh.
Would you like a cup?
- Please, thank you.
So what do urban archeologists do?
- We preserve future history.
- Future history?
- Mm-hm.
It's a term my grandfather used to use.
He'd say that most
people think that history
is something that
happened a long time ago.
But actually, history's
an ongoing process.
Every second history's being formed,
even right now as we speak.
And all this, all these
buildings, they are history.
One day they won't be here, but
the records of them will be.
Or at least we hope they'll be.
- Thank you.
- Just grab that, so yeah...
The warehouse, it predates the terminal
by what, 30 years?
- [Sky] More than that.
Terminal was built in 1930,
warehouse was built around
the turn of the century.
- That's the turn of the 20th century.
- [Sky] Warehouse was built for cattle.
- Cattle?
- Beef cattle.
- Yeah, this whole area used to host
a huge slaughter industry in the 1800s.
It was only second to Chicago.
Tens of thousands of cows
were slaughtered here
and shipped all across the east coast.
- Yeah.
(sighs)
In 1918 it was turned
into a hospital ward.
- [Dietrich] Hospital ward?
- The great influenza pandemic of 1918.
More Americans died during that
than the whole of World War I.
Literally thousands of
patients were isolated here.
- They ended up burying most.
- 90 something plus mortality rate.
- [Dietrich] Man.
- You're sitting in a graveyard.
- [Morrissey] They
moved most of the bodies
to Forest Lawn in 1930.
- [Dietrich] Most of the bodies?
- [Morrissey] Most.
- And in 1930 they built the terminal.
And it ran till what, the early 70s?
- 72, the time in between,
the terminal and the warehouse
used to house psych patients.
- Most violent in the warehouse.
- Whoa, I didn't know that.
- It's another interesting story.
- What?
- Well, supposedly,
when the warehouse was used
to store psych patients,
there was a separate ward
for deformed children.
I'm talking serious deforms, like kids,
by no rules of nature should
have survived childbirth.
For whatever reason they did.
There's no proof of that, though, however.
- Wow, someone just walked over my grave.
- [Morrissey] Yeah, well...
I gotta get back to work.
(sighs)
- I should join you.
- [Morrissey] Mm-hm.
- Um, the private owner.
- What about her?
- [Sky] Are you gonna see her later?
- I think so.
- [Sky] Could you ask if we
can visit, just to look around?
- Assuming I see her again.
- [Sky] Thanks.
- No problem.
- [Morrissey] All right, take
it easy. (serene piano music)
- You monsters, you
bring me back my child!
(chatting)
- Mysterious.
- Yeah, I guess so.
- I'm so glad you're still here.
- You have my backpack
and the door is locked.
- I'm so sorry.
I had to leave early, forgive me.
You were sleeping so soundly.
This is Elenora, my old friend.
And her friend...
- Griffin, how are you?
- Dietrich, hi.
- Charmed.
- The door was locked.
- Well, the door might have swollen.
You know, changes in the
temperature and all that.
It's a natural fucking phenomenon.
Come on.
- This is pure wine.
- Thank you, sweetheart.
- You'll love it.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
So Dietrich, yeah?
- Right.
- So what do you do?
- I'm in-between doing,
I guess you could say.
- (chuckles) I hear you.
Yeah, I've been there.
- What do you do?
- Oh, me?
I'm a writer.
- Really?
What have you written?
- A little bit of everything.
Copy, blogs, screenplays.
You name it, I done it.
- [Dietrich] Anything I might
have seen or read about?
- Oh, you?
You, no.
I doubt that, probably not.
My publisher says my work tends to lean
towards the esoteric.
But, you know, it pays the bills.
(chatting)
- Elenora.
- Yes.
- [Dietrich] How do you know Theodora?
- Where do I begin?
(laughs)
- Elenora and I have known
each other for a long time.
(ominous electro song)
- Oh, I love that song.
(giggles)
- Yes.
Did you find anything?
- Find anything?
- I assume you did some
exploring this morning?
- A bit.
I was tired.
Hey, did I break a glass last night?
- There's tons of broken
glass in this building.
Why do you ask?
- Cause I cut my arm, I think.
- Show me.
- [Dietrich] Well, it was
so much worse this morning.
- Every time you look at
it, you will think of us.
- Imagine so.
(foreboding music)
(chuckling)
- So...
What's all this about then?
- Vanity.
- Sorry, that wine must have
gone straight to my head.
- It will do that.
Come.
(chuckles)
- So is this leading
to where I think it's leading?
- And where do you think
this is leading to?
- Me.
And you.
(laughs)
Naked.
Fucking.
- Well.
Let's find out, shall we?
(somber acoustic music)
♪ If only for a moment ♪
♪ The sun sets in your eyes ♪
♪ I hold your hand, my heart dies ♪
♪ If only for a moment ♪
♪ Obey the light in me ♪
♪ Tell me everything ♪
(gasps)
♪ Say this is your last day ♪
♪ Would you let her smile and run away ♪
♪ Would you give her last kiss ♪
♪ Did you know it would end up like this ♪
♪ And would you live in the fast lane ♪
♪ Just like the day before ♪
♪ You know you'll try to survive ♪
♪ If only for a moment ♪
♪ The sun sets in your eyes ♪
♪ I hold your hand ♪
(fire crackles)
(tense music)
- [Elenora] You have to kill him.
- I will.
- [Elenora] When?
- When I'm done with him.
- [Elenora] You've
played this game before.
- I know.
- And you lost.
- That was a long time ago.
- You lost everything.
- I know.
- [Elenora] If you love me,
you'll kill him.
- I will.
(tense synth music)
(shuffling)
- [Sky] Hello.
I'm with the university.
Do I know you?
- Perhaps we were sisters
in some past life.
- [Sky] What?
- I always knew we'll meet again.
- [Sky] I don't understand.
- I won't hurt you.
Protect you.
- No.
(unsettling music)
- [Dietrich] Finally.
- [Theodora] What happened?
- Come on, get me out of here.
I've been here, I've
been down here all day.
- Oh, poor baby. (giggles)
- Come on, get me out of here.
- [Theodora] Why should I?
- Please.
I feel really weak right now.
Get me out of here.
- You don't deserve it.
- Get me out of here, Theodora.
- Why should I, what
are you gonna do for me?
- [Dietrich] This is not
funny, get me out of here.
I've been down here all day.
(moans)
- [Theodora] Poor baby, suffer for me,
just a little bit more, come on.
(laughs)
- Let me out!
- [Theodora] Did you miss me?
- Just get me out.
Come on, open this door.
Open it.
God, get me out of here.
(foreboding music)
(cup clatters)
(gasps)
- [Theodora] Stop!
You're killing him!
Stop it, Elenora, that's enough!
That's enough!
- What do you want me to do?
Suck the rats in the basement?
(foreboding music)
(garbled voices)
(suspenseful rock music)
- What the fuck is the matter with you?
What are you doing in here?
- There's two women down there sleeping,
well, I think they're sleeping.
But they're in some sort
of placenta membrane sac.
- Did they invite you in?
- What?
- What does that have to do with anything?
They're down there...
- I don't give a shit, Sky!
This is their property, it ain't yours!
- There's something wrong with them.
- I don't give a flying fuck in a tree,
what's wrong with them isn't the issue!
What's wrong with you is.
- How dare you talk to me like that.
- How dare you break in.
- Yeah, and what are you doing here?
- I'm looking for your stupid ass.
I got back early, I went to the warehouse,
I called your cell phone,
I called your name.
I was gonna call the cops!
Jesus Christ, I...
I said to myself, she
wouldn't go in there,
she wouldn't go in there.
But you know what, I knew that you would.
And look, here you are.
- Right, good deal, you found me.
(man whimpers)
- What an amazing place.
- The phone is over here.
- Phone's over there.
Phone's over here, phone's over here.
Rotary, what the frick?
Come on!
What the...
Aw, come on!
There's no dial tone!
- This is an old building,
sometimes the lines can be funny.
- [Moby] (groans) Damn it!
- Would you like a drink?
- You and me, yeah, sure.
Oh, why not?
Oh yeah.
- Take the edge off a little bit.
Perhaps you can try again
later and the lines will work.
- Oh, this is good.
- I'm glad you like it.
- Yes.
Yes, I do.
Tell me.
Do you really live here?
- We're staying here,
just for a little while.
- [Moby] Oh, who's we?
- Myself and my friend.
- Oh really, yes.
- Am I interrupting?
- Not at all, Mr. Moby
here was telling me.
- Oh, please, please!
Mr. Moby, Mr. Moby's like my dad.
- Moby?
- [Theodora] Found him
on the side of the road,
his car broke down.
His cell phone doesn't work,
and apparently our lines are down too.
- That's too bad.
If you call again
after a while...
- Oh, they might be up,
yes, yes, I know.
Damn it!
That is so nice.
- Have some more.
- Where were you going?
- To a party.
- What's the old saying?
The party's where you at.
- Something like that.
- My sentiments exactly.
Oh yeah.
1940.
- Pardon me?
- This vintage.
- Oh.
Much, much older.
- (gasps) What was that?
(suspenseful music)
- What's wrong?
- I had the tablet translated today.
- Really?
Why didn't you tell me?
What did it say?
- It translated to, "With silver"
and "At the eater of flesh".
(pounding)
(gasps)
What the hell?
- Oh my god.
(gasping)
- Jesus.
- Oh my god!
(Dietrich coughs)
He looks like he lost a lot of blood.
- Fuck, there's no signal.
- [Sky] We have to get him to a hospital!
- [Morrissey] Start up the car.
- [Dietrich] Theodora!
- Who?
- [Sky] One of the women.
- [Morrissey] Aw, they're
probably hurt too.
I better go up there and check.
- [Sky] You can't leave me here.
- [Morrissey] They might
have a phone up there,
I have to go check at least.
- Please!
- Fuck.
Christ, Sky, the man's
dying and you wanna argue?
What's the matter with you?
I'll be right back.
(serene piano music)
(tense music)
Hello!
(ominous classical music)
(banging)
(suspenseful rock music)
(screams)
(Morrissey coughs)
(groans)
(Elenora screams)
- Morrissey!
God, please no.
No.
God, no.
(suspenseful rock music)
(whimpers)
Oh god, oh god.
(ominous music)
Oh god!
Stop!
Okay, stop!
Hey!
Stop.
(Elenora wails)
- [Theodora] Wanna see you dead!
Come on, pretty lady, come out here!
- Leave me alone!
(women laugh)
Please!
Leave me alone!
- Oh, Sky!
- Leave me alone!
Stop!
Leave me alone, please.
Please!
- [Elenora] Come on!
(yelps)
- What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
Why are you doing this to me?
How can you be so cruel?
- [Theodora] We're vampires.
- Please, please don't kill me.
You made that sign on my forehead.
You said it would protect me.
- Not against us.
There are options.
Shall I turn you, make you one of us?
A sister in darkness?
A sister of sorrows.
We've long sought a third
to complete our triumvirate.
Or you could come back here in 1,000 years
and discover this place all over again!
Wouldn't you like that, huh?
You would, wouldn't you, you little bitch!
Oh, don't you wanna
know what it feels like
to taste the blood?
To feel the hot flesh melt like butter.
And taste the blood and feel
it rush up into your mouth
and down your throat.
Taste the life within that blood!
Taste the memories, taste the pain.
Taste the love and the lust
and the hate and the fear!
And the regret?
The regret that the pleasure
you feel as we suck you dry
will not last forever!
(giggles)
(suspenseful music)
(Sky wails)
(screeches)
She would have joined us!
- She was soiled with child.
Enough games, end it now.
Kill him!
- Too late.
- Damn you!
(crow caws)
(heart thuds)
(ominous music)
(energetic heavy metal music)
♪ Liar ♪
♪ Thought things would change ♪
♪ But they remain the same ♪
♪ Insane, tolerating your shit ♪
♪ And playing your game ♪
♪ You always wanna pass the blame ♪
♪ All your bitching, but
things remain the same ♪
♪ It's a shame I can't
talk to you like a human ♪
♪ Think you're the victor,
but reality, you're a loser ♪
♪ So listen up, let me tell
you a little something ♪
♪ You got a way of just
pushing my buttons ♪
♪ Every single word you say ♪
- Theodora!
♪ Some time I've lost
as I leave the sling ♪
- Have you come back?
Have you returned for me?
♪ Cause you never fail to fail me ♪
♪ Cause you never fail ♪
- Theodora!
(zombies gasp)
- Return for me.
(zombies groan)
♪ I got a good view of
the world without you ♪
♪ Don't fucking give up, why even bother ♪
♪ You ain't gotta sort
it out, motherfucker ♪
♪ Cause you never fail to fail me ♪
(somber music)
(solemn rock music)
♪ I'm leaving it behind ♪
♪ Smothered in honey ♪
♪ I am poisonous tea ♪
♪ My other part got scared for lying ♪
♪ And ordered me to sing ♪
♪ I dug it deep and sang my song ♪
♪ Here in ecstasy ♪
♪ I need friends, I bring them here ♪
♪ Caught in winter underneath ♪
♪ All of them so deep removed ♪
♪ I must find refrain ♪
♪ My life's energy spent,
and all that's left ♪
♪ An irritation on my skin ♪
♪ My other part got scared for lying ♪
♪ And ordered to sing ♪
♪ I dug it deep and sang my song ♪
♪ Here in ecstasy ♪
♪ Release my poison ♪