(music)
(child squealing with laughter)
(voices, laughter)
Where is he? Where's daddy?
Daddy, daddy. Take my picture.
Oh Thorold, turn that thing off, I look terrible!
No, you look great, honey.
How about a smile? Lemme see.
Maybe after you're finished here,
you and I might jump in that tub.
Thorold!
Come on in.
Yeah, hold on a second, here.
Look who's here, Maggie. Come on up here.
Daddy!
Look into the camera with daddy, yeah...
(music)
Hi, Thorold. Merry christmas.
Say Merry Christmas to Daddy, Maggie. Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, Daddy.
What is it?
Teddy bear!
Show Daddy.
Look, Daddy.
Say Merry Christmas, Daddy.
Merry Christmas, Daddy!
That's great, wow.
(music)
(giggling, laughter)
Why can't we do this together, as a family?
We don't need church to make us a family, all right?
I'm gonna tell you one more time, honey. I'm not goin'
I don't wanna hear anymore of this bible stuff.
You wanna go? Go!?
Why can't you just open your heart a little? Please, Thorold.
We're talking about "eternity, here.
Smile, honey.
Daddy, daddy, come on, push me up to the sky!
Wendy?
(telephone ringing)
The Messiah had this to say.
My children, you are now ready for the day of wonders.
(telephone ringing)
Ready to take a giant leap--
(smacking down remote control)
(telephone ringing)
Stone.
(sirens wailing)
(fire extinguishers hissing)
I didn't do anything.
Hm?
Tell them I didn't do anything.
They know you didn't.
I wanna go home.
You'll go to the hospital first.
No!
Yeah, they're gonna check you out, make sure you're okay.
Where is everybody else?
Fortunately there was enough left in the
mechanism for us to isolate the frequency.
Now, I've put in a request to have it traced--
Agent Stone!
Satellite tracking just located the source of the detonator signal.
It came from an abandoned warehouse across town.
Let's go.
The device that destroyed the bus was detonated from a suspected haters' hideout.
A S.W.A.T. team has been dispatched. The haters are
to be considered armed and extremely dangerous.
I don't get it.
Come on, Thorold.
They've seen the same thing as the rest of us.
Every nuclear weapon on earth gone.
Millions of people vanishing into thin air.
If Macalusso's not God, then who is he?
He's just some con man who saw what was goin' on and took
advantage of it before anyone else came to their senses.
And maybe he's an alien from another planet.
Maybe he is.
You know, ever since we were little kids,
you never believed in anything. At every puppet show,
you're looking for strings. At Christmas,
you're looking for Santa's footprints on the roof. Finally
you got all the proof you need, and it's still not good enough!
Maybe I'm not looking for God.
I'm just looking for my family.
Orders are to terminate. No prisoners, no dialogue.
(device beeping)
What's that?
It's something my buddy Willie Spino gave me to try out.
He does things with computers that would blow your mind.
Claims this thing can read human D.N.A. through solid concrete.
And sure enough, there's a bunch of them down at the far end.
(truck rumbling to a stop)
All right, I know you heard the order to shoot these
people on sight, but listen up. Nobody fires a single shot
unless they get the word from me, you got that?
Yeah, I got it.
Let's go.
♪ I will enter His gaze with thanksgiving in my heart, ♪
♪ I will enter His cause with praise ♪
♪ I will say this is the day that the Lord has made, ♪
♪ I will rejoice for He has made me glad, ♪
♪ He has made me glad, He has made me glad, ♪
(clapping, cheers)
Amen, Amen, Amen Hallelujah.
Why are you glad, friends?
One reason. One reason: the truth.
Yeah, Praise god and then blow up the buses, huh? Nice touch.
Well, it's not the first time something was
blown up in the name of the Almighty.
Satan cannot win!
Hallelujah!
Amen...
And that's why they're trying to exterminate us.
Your job is to keep the faith, and to spread the truth
to whoever will listen. But I warn you, it won't be easy.
No sir, it won't be easy. Because they've all seen
Macalusso's miracles, well, I'm here to tell you today
that in God's world, seeing is not believing. No, sir!
That's satan's way of trickery.
In God's world, you must first believe it before you see it.
All right, here's the deal.
We're gonna load 'em all into the truck
and take 'em down to headquarters for questioning.
Whattya mean, take 'em down for questioning?
Our orders are to shoot--
We're takin' 'em down to headquarters!
Back off.
...that is why the bible says that only, only as a child
will you enter through the gates of heaven.
Hallelujah.
Hallelujah!
Do you know what that means? Do you know what that means?
I'll tell you what it means!
Go!
Get 'em up, now! Get 'em up, now!
You're all under arrest! Get your hands up!
Get up!
Get 'em up!
Get back!
We didn't do anything!
Yeah, back off, lady!
If it wasn't for him, you'd all be dead right now.
'Cause if it was up to me, I'd shoot every one of you.
Nothing. Not even a knife.
What do you expect? We're not criminals!
Not until worshipping the true and living God became a crime, that is.
Well, if the God you're worshipping is so full of hate,
he's got you blowin' up school buses, then maybe
it's time to re-examine your faith, preacher.
Load 'em up.
Time to get off the soapbox. Let's go, go now!
We didn't blow up anything! Can't you see we're bein' set up?
Don't waste your time--
Hold on a second. Set up by who?
Franco Macalusso.
And all his disciples who believe he's God.
And let me guess, you really believe he's the devil, right?
I guess he'd have to have horns and a red pointy tail for you to see it.
The bible makes it perfectly clear!
See Thorold, the same thing your wife was talkin' about.
And you know where that got her?
Gone, just like the rest of them!
It got her to heaven, young man.
I only wish we all could've seen the light before that day.
We are all guilty of believin' the same thing your wife believed.
I've heard enough, man. You deal with this.
Let me ask you somethin'.
Do you think your wife would be killin' children if she
were still here? If you would just open your heart.
Why didn't you let them shoot us?
You don't look dangerous to me.
If we're not dangerous, why do you think they want us dead?
They believe you slaughtered innocent children.
They know that's not true. They sent you here because of this.
I worked for the O.N.E. until a couple days ago.
I suggest you take a look at this.
Do it for your wife.
Let's go.
Move it! Go!
(alarm beeping)
Oh, no. They got the Davis group.
What about the CD?
We'll have to assume they got that too.
Poor Selma Davis. She was supposed to meet me here with it this afternoon.
Oh well, that's just great! Now what?
That CD was our only chance for seeing what the O.N.E.
has planned for the Day of Wonders.
It's okay, Jake. We'll just have to find another way.
It's okay?
We've been in this filthy dump for three months already.
There's not a soul out there that wouldn't
shred us to bits if they had the chance.
I mean, for heaven's sake, the crowds cheered
when they strung your boyfriend up on national television.
I don't think that "okay" actually describes our situation!
We can't blame them, Cindy. They don't know what we know.
They also don't know that Macalusso's having
everyone who disagrees with him killed.
All they see are the miracles.
Any luck, Ronnie?
I'm all set up on the O.N.E. personnel file now. I'll be
able to get in there tonight as a security guard. Without that
disk, though, I don't have a clue what I'm lookin' for.
Anything. Anything that can help us
figure out what these guys have planned for the Day of Wonders.
Because whatever they're planning, it's big.
And it can't be good.
Here, take a look at this. It's from a tape
I found at my grandmother's house.
We are living in the last days, friends.
We know it because of all the prophecies that are being fulfilled.
But it's going to get much worse.
In fact, do you know that there will be a time
when the devil rules over the entire earth?
He will be a super-deceiver.
And he'll try to let the world know that he is the promised
Messiah, the Prince of Peace of Isaiah 9:6.
And he will tell the world "I have come to save you
from destruction", and they'll believe it because he confirms
the peace pact for a period of seven years, in Daniel 9:27.
But he's not the Messiah. He's an impostor.
He is empowered and incarnated by Satan, Revelations 13:3.
And therefore the peace pact fails.
For the bible says "when they say 'peace and safety'
then sudden destruction cometh upon them as a veil upon a
woman with child, and they shall not escape".
These people don't look any more dangerous than my wife and daughter did.
Hey, I checked the satellite readout myself, okay?
The command that detonated that bomb came from this very building.
Well, maybe the detonator was on a timer, not the bomb.
Maybe somebody just placed it here long before these people got here.
No, no, that bomb went off exactly when the last kid got on that bus.
Whoever set it off had their finger on the button.
Wait a second, Niddy. You'd need some pretty sophisticated
equipment to pull that off, and I didn't see anything in there like that.
Okay, that's not our job. The bomb squad guys will find it.
Maybe only one of them did it, and the rest of them are innocent.
Yeah, and maybe the bomb was set off from a spaceship.
Look, don't let what that lady in there said to you play with your mind, okay?
(truck starting)
Just trying to keep an open mind.
Yeah, right. You're makin' a big mistake.
Do you hear something?
I didn't hear anything.
(device beeping)
What do you see?
It's a piece of junk.
(door banging open)
(machine gun fire)
(gunshots)
Hey, stop!
(gunfire)
(machine gun fire)
(gunshots)
Sir, I don't know how they found us,
but we have two O.N.E. agents in pursuit.
Well, take care of it.
Yes, sir. We'll take care of it.
(body slamming on floor)
I took this off the other one.
O.N.E.
A detonator.
Yeah, what's that tell ya?
The haters didn't blow up that bus.
That's right. Gimme your cuffs.
He was talkin' to somebody on that walkie.
Drop your weapon!
Mr. Parker, I'm gonna have to ask you to drop your weapon!
Drop that weapon, now!
You're in way over your heads, my friends.
(gunfire)
Who are you?
What are you?
I am servant of the Messiah. I'm here to help him rid
the world of anyone and everyone who stands in his way.
And now, gentlemen, that includes you!
(gunfire)
(grunting in pain)
Oh...
Aw, man...
Just don't give me a reason to shoot you.
Let's gol get in there! Now, get in there!
(doors slamming)
Please, you don't know what you're doing.
Not another word.
Dad, you're making a mistake!
I've got one more foz you, officers.
Dad, please! Please don't do this!
I have to do this!
Please, you don't understand!
I'm afraid I do understand, son.
And I'm doing this for your own good. These men can help you.
Last night, I found a bible in his room.
And this morning, I found him kneeling by his bed.
Dad, I was praying for you!
You've done the right thing, sir.
I wish it felt a little bit more like the right thing.
You're not the first father to turn in his son.
Probably half the haters in captivity have been
turned in by families, for re-education.
Son, I'm sorry. But you've gotta believe,
I'm only doing this because I love you.
Aw...
What are you lookin' at, kid? School's about to begin.
We'll have more on the hater bombing next hour.
This is WNN.
Well?
Sir, we have a rather large problem.
What large problem is that, Spencer?
The second agent, Thorold Stone.
It would appear, sir, that something went wrong.
Our reports from the scene indicate that- that things-
Spit it out, man!
He's not dead, sir. And he's gone.
Gone?
How can that be? I shot him myself.
I want Stone, and I want him dead.
Issue the order. Shoot on sight.
Yes, sir.
There's more, sir. We didn't find the disk at the haters' hideout.
You listen to me, and you listen very carefully.
The Day of Wonders is less than 72 hours away.
If that CD makes its way into the underground,
and those idiots manage to find out what's on it,
they'll do everything they can to expose the Messiah's plan.
I understand, sir.
No, I don't think you do!
If you did, you wouldn't be standing here snivelling.
You'd be out looking for the disk. And Thorold Stone.
But remember this.
I have come to save you, not just your earthly bodies,
as I did when I removed your terrible weapons of mass
destruction, but your heavenly bodies as well...your souls.
And in order to save your souls, I've had to remove those who
stood in the way. Now is the time for yet another step forward.
A step that will lead you into a world of wonders.
A world unlike anything you have ever imagined. Finally, those
things which, until now, have been hidden will be revealed.
We'll have more about the Messiah's message at the top of the hour.
In other news, O.N.E. officials are combing the city tonight,
looking for one of their own agents. Thorold David Stone
is suspected of several acts of terrorism and the murder of partner David Nidd.
Coming up on the international news, a look at the new Europe.
Not since the days of the holy roman empire...
This is WNN.
Coming up this hour. The incredible transformation of
the Middle East in the wake of the seven-year peace treaty
between Israel and her neighbours.
And construction continues on the Temple of Humanity
in Jerusalem, as One Nation Earth officials struggle to
ensure that the expected crowds can be managed.
But first, another haters strike has rocked the world...
...perfectly clear to anyone who's not too scared to open up a bible.
...see Thorold, the same thing your wife was talkin' about.
And you know where that got her?
Gone, just like the rest of them.
...it got us to" heaven, Thorold...
...the answer is on the disk. It's open to you...
...do it for your wife...
...drop that weapon now!
(gunfire)
(car horn honking)
(door opening)
(sound of gunfire)
Now listen here, pilgrim.
There ain't room in this town for the two of us! Ha!
Whoa!
Who are you?
Thorold Stone. Friend of Nidd's.
A friend of Nidd's. Oh yeah, that's funny. 'Cause I heard you killed him.
I'm sure that's not the only lie you've heard today.
Yeah, and what makes you think I'm gonna believe you?
Because I need your help.
And my gun's real.
It's a good point.
(door clanking open)
Open the door.
You ready to meet your maker?
Let her go!
C'mon!
(gunshot)
No!
Daddy, no!
Good afternoon, Mrs. Davis. We haven't caught you at a bad time, have we?
Take her.
Let's go, let's go! Let's go, I said. Sit down! Shut up!
Shut up!
No!
Daddy!
C'mon kid, let's go! Let's go, shut your mouth!
Let her go, she's just a child!
Oh, not for long.
Susan...no...
Scrambled frequency modulation, double UHL conversion,
this is high-tech. This is very high-tech.
There's no doubt this is clearly an O.N.E job.
So the haters weren't responsible for any of these things.
The school buses, the orphanages, the old age homes.
Nothin'.
Why? One Nation Earth has always been completely
dedicated to peace and unity.
Why now? Why do they go to all this trouble to make us think
the haters did these things?
I don't know.
But if the O.N.E. is lyin' about the haters,
what else are they lyin' about?
Maybe even Macalusso's lyin' to us?
The Messiah?
Maybe you wanna back that truck up right now, okay?
I mean, what makes you think he knew anything about this?
Would you think I was crazy if I said
I thought they were from another planet?
I'd say you're nuts.
Well, I don't know anyone from this planet who's walkin' through walls.
One of the haters gave me this.
She said O.N.E. was trying to kill her over it.
Yeah, it's O.N.E. all right. What's on it?
I was hoping you could tell me.
How do I know I'm gonna regret this?
C'mon, baby. There we go, bing.
(tapping computer keyboard)
Hey, what's goin' on, here?
This is a top secret project I've been workin' on.
The haters had a copy of this?
What is it?
It's what the Day of Wonders is all about.
(tapping computer keyboard)
Aw, c'mon. What's the matter with you? This is my system.
This is my security system, how can I be locked up?
You know what this is?
No, I have no idea.
This is a new program for the Day of Wonders virtual world system.
It's the new program, but without a password,
there's no way I can run it.
Well, why do you need a password? I thought you wrote it.
No, no, not this.
I wrote the virtual reality package that runs this,
but I have no idea what it is.
It's like I built a VCR and this is some kinda top secret videotape.
(tapping computer keys)
What is the Day of Wonders? What does it do?
Nobody knows exactly.
Nobody knows?
No...you remember when I told you it was like a computer game?
I may have understated that just a little bit.
Hold on one second. I'll be right back.
It would seem we've chosen different sides, haven't we?
We are soldiers in a war that only one side can win.
I thought about joining your side once. I came this close.
But do you know what?
When God claimed to be the only God, that was a pack of lies!
We can all achieve godhood. He just doesn't want anyone to know it.
So let's try this one more time.
Did Thorold Stone become a believer?
Or does he still think this is all about technology?
I know you gave Thorold Stone that disk.
Your daughter told us all about it.
What have you done with her?
Oh, don't worry! She's not in any pain. Now.
No!
Now you see why I keep my curtains closed.
I'm tellin' ya, women will kick straight through
windows to be near a body like this.
We got stuff to do. Here, put these on,
and I'll show you what I cannot explain, all right?
You ready for this?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Lotion?
Do I need it?
Not really. I'm just a big fan of ambiance.
Good thing you didnt come on nudist beach day.
How is this possible?
No it's not how It's who
Macalusso?
Amazing huh? This guy is so far beyond us
"it's like we've gone through a time machine
Look at me I've'been around computers'all my life
buv this is beyond even my wildest dreams.
If' had one of these, I'd never leave the house.
yeah if I have one of these I'd never leave my chair
you know the onlt thing I cant have in here is my step sister
and my grandmother
if that were possable I'd live in here.
Lost loved ones?
Yeah.
Were you close with your grandmother?
Aw, no. Not really.
I was closer to my sister my grandmother she was a nut.
That gives both of us good reason to look at this stuff.
What do you mean? I thought you said Macalusso was lying?
Maybe he is.
Ane what if he is? What !about this? All this?
What about our families? What happened to our families?
This is amazing.
Yeah, so much for seeing is believing, huh? I mean,
you can't trust your senses when you're in here, Thorold.
Truly a world without consequences.
Hey, take a look at this.
(groaning)
Ow!
Go on. Take your goggles off.
Hey?
(laughing)
This is incredible.
So whatever's on that disk is something like this?
Could be.
I mean, it could be anything, but from what I've been able
to put together, it's gonna be a whole lot more than what I got here.
(bell ringing)
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa! Whoa, cowboy!
Hold on a second.
There you go. It's just a delivery boy.
(door clanking open)
Hey.
Hello.
William W. Spin-o?
Yeah, close enough. That's me.
Are you still the only occupant of this building?
Yeah, that's right. Just me and my dog.
I need you to sign for your Day of Wonders package.
Can I see your global I.D. please?
Oh yeah, yeah, sorry about that.
There ya go. Hey, you know, it's nice not just to be a
number anymore. Now I'm three numbers, a dash, five numbers,
another dash and seven more numbers.
So I guess this stuff's keepin' you pretty busy, huh?
Oh shucks, yeah. But they've hired a bunch of extra guys.
By this time tomorrow, every man, woman and child on the
planet will have a pair of these glasses.
Can't wait to see what the fuss is all about.
You and me both, pal. You and me both.
Now these are the real deal, Thorold.
When the O.N.E. computer transmits its signal at noon
on the Day of Wonders, these babies come to life.
And what the whole world's gonna be lookin' at is
whatever is on that CD.
Yeah.
And that CD belongs to some very dangerous people.
Now, Macalusso may not know anything about this,
but we know Parker does. And whatever he's got planned
for the world, I can guarantee it's not a walk on the beach.
There's gotta be a way to crack that code.
There is.
What is it, Agent Spencer?
Sir, someone has hacked into the Day of Wonders security system.
Who?
One of our engineers, sir, William Spino. He's on the phone.
What's going on, Spino?
Stone made me hack into the database,
but I gave him the wrong password.
Nice work, Spino.
I also got a tracking chip on him, sir.
Excellent.
Stay right there. We'll send some men down to talk to you.
Well? What are you waiting for?
Follow that signal and kill them.
Them, sir?
You heard me--them! Stone and Spino! No loose ends.
Yes, sir.
Disabling the security system gave me access to the
password files, but it also set off an alarm. Now they not only
know I did it, but where I did it from. So we're just gonna
have to grab whatever we can and get outta here.
We'll have to try and find someplace else to try this disk.
What do you mean, "we"?
Hey Stone, I know Parker, okay?
He doesn't like loose ends, and that's what I've just become.
Like it or not, buddy, you just got yourself a partner.
Actually, two. Come on, Elvis! Come here!
Attaboy!
What are you holding on to?
Don't you see you've lost? You've lost! God's lost!
Once you and every other Christian is dead or converted,
He'll have no reason to return.
He won't have anyone to come back for, and that's what the
Day of Wonders is all about!
You're gonna renounce Christ, or you're going to die!
Prophecy will fail, and we will win.
So save your life now. Renounce Him!
(loud slap)
What's wrong with you?
I can see him.
Shut up.
I can see him!
Silence!
He's standin' at the Father's right hand...
What have we to do with thee, Jesus, the Son of God?
Aren't thou come hither to torment us before the time?
Look, it's not gonna take those meatheads followin' a chip
too long to realize they're barkin' up the wrong tree.
Yeah, how we gonna find out what's on that disk?
I don't think we have much choice.
We're just gonna have to take it to the haters.
The haters?
Yeah, the haters.
Well, first of all, we'd never be able to find 'em.
Even if we did, what makes you think they'd talk to us?
Well, like my friend Quasimodo used to say, I got a hunch.
Hold it.
We got him on the screen.
(device beeping)
We've got him on the monitor, Mr. Parker.
Yes?
Must be trying to set up some kind of
electronic relay via the telephone system.
They keep stopping at every telephone pole.
Well, take care of it.
Yes, sir. Spencer out.
Look, my stepsister's a hater, all right?
I told you I lost her. I never said she vanished.
I mean, why do you think I even listened to you
when you told me the haters were bein' set up?
'Cause you got such a pretty smile?
Hey, there he is!
Let's go, boy!
Attaboy, attaboy. Come here, stay still. Here we go...
Let's get outta here.
Jesus said in John 15:18, if the world hates you,
remember it hated me before it hated you.
If you were of the world, the world would love his own.
But because you're not of the world, but I've chosen you out
of the world, therefore the world will hate you.
Remember the servant is not greater than his Lord.
If they persecuted me, Jesus, they'll also persecute you.
In fact, Jesus said in John 16:2, the time will come
that whosoever kills you will think he's doing God's service.
Hey. Any word from Ronnie?
No, no not yet. How about you? Anything?
The only way we're gonna find any answers is if we can
break into the O.N.E. computer system and find that disk.
And who knows where that could be?
I do!
Jake, no! Stop, it's okay!
(laughter)
Willie!
How ya doin', sis?
Oh...
The news said you were killed by some crazed lunatic.
Helen, come on, you gotta know better than anyone else
not to believe everything you hear on television.
Helen Hannah, the woman who denounced the Messiah on
national television, the world's most wanted fugitive and my
very dear stepsister, meet Thorold Stone,
the crazed lunatic that killed me.
Hi.
Um, we've got some left over salad, if you're hungry.
Salad, you gotta be kiddin' me. Don't you have some steaks
lyin' around here someplace?
Well, I'm vegetarian.
Yeah, well if God didn't want us to eat animals,
he shouldn't made them outta meat.
Oh, I'm not vegetarian 'cause I love animals,
I'm vegetarian 'cause I hate plants.
Yeah, well. I didn't work my way to the top of the food
chain to sit around chewin' on a cucumber.
Well, that explains a lot. Vegetables are brain food.
Ooh.
She's not only gorgeous, but she's rude and sarcastic, too.
And best of all, she can't see my shortcomings.
Tell me something, Cindy.
Where have you been all my life.
Mm. Well...
Aliens? Come on, Thorold?
Take a look around. I mean, it's not people who believe in
flying saucers they're sending to concentration camps.
It's people who believe the bible.
And how is it that your aliens happen to be
fulfilling bible prophecy in exact detail?
Well, maybe they're just doin' it to throw everyone off track.
Whoever it is, they have my wife and daughter.
And whatever it takes, I'm gonna find 'em.
You're gonna have to find God first.
No offence, Helen, but if I didn't buy God from my wife,
I'm sure as heck am not gonna buy it from you.
Why is the answer so difficult for you?
Other than the fact that my family just vanished?
Oh, I don't know.
They found peace, Thorold.
Peace.
Yeah. I hope.
My mother taught me to believe in God.
She did. We used to pray together.
When I was seven years old, I used to kneel next to her
bed and pray with her. We prayed together,
while cancer ate away at her insides. And when the pain was
so much that she, she couldn't pray, well, I prayed for
the both of us. Prayed night and day. Right up until she was
65 pounds and her last breath just slipped out of her body.
I looked in face for peace. You know what I saw?
I saw anguish. I got my answer.
There is no God.
You're wrong.
And you're making a big mistake.
You're both making a big mistake.
Hey sis, if a man speaks in a forest and there's no woman
around to hear him, is he still wrong?
Okay, you guys. Come here. The hardware's all set up.
We are ready to take an early look at the Day of Wonders.
Now, the password I downloaded opened the program,
but there's still one line encrypted. It shouldn't
stop me from runnin' it. I'll keep tryin' to crack that.
Sorry Cindy, but right now,
I wanna take this baby for a test drive.
(computer beeping)
Let's see what all this fuss is about.
Whoa!
Yeah, nice look.
Hello?
Hey, some curtains would be nice!
Wow.
So this is the Day of Wonders. Wonder who's gonna lose his job over this.
Well?
It's nothin'.
What do you mean, "nothing"?
Try and picture the opposite of everything.
There's no trees, there's no beaches, there's no ocean,
there's, there's just nothin'. There's zero! There's zilch!
I'm sorry, there's absolutely nothing to this program at all.
No, there's somethin' to it, all right.
I suggest you get back in there and find out what it is.
What can I do to help, Willie?
You know what, sis? I think maybe you better just leave
this one to the professionals, okay?
Professionals built the Titanic.
Amateurs built the ark.
All right, lemme see if I got this right.
You believe that Macalusso, who the rest of the world
believe to be the Messiah, who has done nothing short of,
uh, supposedly saving the world from utter destruction is Satan?
Satan, okay. And everyone else who believed in God
before the vanishing--
The rapture.
The rapture. And all the others who believed in God before the,
the rapture, have found eternal peace and happiness in heaven.
Right, well, that's all fine and dandy Helen,
but there's just one thing. I don't believe in God.
Well, He's still God, whether you believe in Him or not.
Well, why doesn't He show himself?
He does.
No, I mean really. Really show Himself.
So do I.
Why don't you ask Him to do something, Helen?
To give me some proof.
Like maybe turn the page of this book,
or knock that glass of water over?
Well, if He did that, you wouldn't need
much in the way of faith, would you?
Why is it always about faith?
That's what my wife used to say. Faith, faith, faith.
It's all about faith. What about proof?
It's not all faith, Thorold. Far from it.
I mean, God says all you need is faith the size of a grain
of mustard seed. He'll do the rest.
But I want some proof. Some real proof. That's what I want.
No proof is enough if the heart's not ready.
What's that supposed to mean?
It just means that whatever God may do,
you won't believe it was Him anyway.
You'll always manage to find another explanation.
Another explanation.
Well, I have an explanation.
How's this for an explanation? There is no God.
I wanna see Him. I wanna see it. I wanna see this thing,
this thing you call God. I wanna see some real proof.
Knock over this glass of water, God. Knock over this
little glass of water right now, and I'll be a believer.
Come on!
Come on, God, make a believer outta me!
You couldn't save my mother from cancer when I was a kid,
and you sure as hell couldn't save my family from vanishing,
so why don't you just knock over this little glass
of water, and make a believer outta me!
How 'bout it, God? Make a believer outta me! Huh?
I guess He's not up to the challenge today, Helen.
Looks to me like Macalusso's the only one around here pullin' off miracles.
(bumping table)
(glass rattling on floor)
I'm not looking for God.
I'm just looking for my family.
Wendy...
You know what, Cindy? I wish this were the same old program I already had.
Why?
'Cause then maybe I'd get to take a peek at you in a bikini.
For heaven's sakes!
Talk about your Day of Wonders, huh?
Ruff!
(howling)
You're terrible.
Hey.
Right now, I'd give anything in the world to see
Wendy and my little Maggie. For just a minute.
What would you tell them?
That I love them.
Sounds to me like you've pretty much figured out
what's going on in this world, then.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about God.
Think about it. Just like Maggie is your creation,
we're a part of God's creation.
Helen...
Thorold, think about Macalusso.
I mean, he claims to be our creator.
But at the heart of it, his message isn't about love it all.
It's, it's about power. And selfishness.
It's about having whatever you want,
regardless of the consequences to anyone else.
I mean, can you imagine sitting down and
telling Maggie that in the name of success,
she should kill anyone who stands in the way of her dreams?
Isn't that exactly what Macalusso is telling the world?
I'm telling you, Thorold.
It's the same lie the serpent told Eve in the Garden of Eden.
Come on, Eve. Eat the fruit.
It won't hurt you. Look how good it looks.
You know you want to.
God's just afraid that if you eat it, you'll be just like Him.
And what was your God doing when all this was happening?
Just sitting there powerless?
Oh, no. He wasn't just sitting there. Far from it.
Now it's all in your hands.
God doesn't want to win you with cheap tricks.
He just wants you to reach into your heart and answer
one question: Do you believe in Him?
It's time for you to decide what you believe, Thorold Stone.
(computer beeping)
Hey.
You always carry a big stick.
Only when there are new slobs in the house.
Oh, great. Is this seat saved.
No, but I'm sure you guys are prayin' for it.
Oh...
Hey Cindy, let me ask you something.
Blind people always wear sunglasses, right?
How come deaf people don't wear earmuffs?
Willie, let me ask you something.
Do men in wheelchairs complain when you leave the seat up?
You, uh...you ever take those glasses off?
Ah, only to drive.
I'm trying to be serious, here.
I've never seen you without 'em, that' all.
Neither have I.
Do you mind?
Where are you?
Wow.
Well, I think you should definitely take them off more often.
You're the most beautiful woman I've ever seen.
Thanks...
So, what makes a nice girl like you become a bible-thumper, anyway?
Well, I was really an atheist, but you know,
they didn't have enough holidays.
Now, come on, I'm bein' serious, here.
I mean, look at the way you people live.
Hidin' out in this rathole, livin' every day in fear.
You must really believe this stuff, huh?
I'll tell you the truth, Willie,
I really don't know what I believe.
My parents used to drag me to church every Sunday.
I would pray for eyesight. Mom and dad vanished and Jake
here came to get me, well, what was I gonna do?
I guess you could say I just came along for the ride.
Aw, come on. Along for the ride?
I mean, I watched you last night. I saw you out there
prayin' and singin' with them.
Please!
Going to church makes you about as Christian
as going to a pet store makes you a cat.
You know? What about you, Willie? What's your story?
The truth?
No, lie.
Well, I still believe Franco Mcalusso is who he
says he is, the Messiah. And if I can just get to the
bottom of this whole program mess, I can prove that.
To the whole world.
For the last time, Helen, I don't wanna hear about it!
I've explained it to you so many times--
Thorold!
Oh, it's okay, guys! Wait, it's okay. We're all on the same side.
We're all on the same side.
Ronnie, how did you do?
A lot better than Selma Davis.
What do you mean?
I got this tape out of the security camera.
What are you holding on to?
Don't you see you've lost? You've lost! God's lost!
Once you and every other Christian is dead or converted,
He'll have no reason to return.
He won't have anyone to come back for, and that's what the
Day of Wonders is all about!
You're gonna renounce Christ, or you're going to die!
Prophecy will fail, and we will win.
So save your life now. Renounce Him!
So that's what the Day of Wonders is all about, huh?
Killing people?
How's he gonna do it? With some fancy computer game?
What about all the people he vapourized? He didn't say
anything about that. What's gonna happen to them.
He didn't vapourize anybody, Thorold.
God took them home. Your family's in heaven.
(static)
Special Agent Thorold Stone. I know you're listening.
I just thought you might be interested in some special
guests I have here, visiting me in my office.
It took some doing to get them here, Stone.
I hope you appreciate the effort.
Please don't hurt us anymore!
We don't know anything. I haven't seem him in months.
Mommy, why doesn't daddy come and save us?
I don't know, honey. I don't know.
Shut up, both of you. Unless you want more of the same.
Stone? You have one choice, and one choice only,
so you'd better listen to me very carefully.
I want to see you here, and O.N.E. headquarters
by 2:00 a.m. with the disk. Have you got that?
If you're not here by one second past two,
then they'll be the first ones to discover
what the Day of Wonders is all about.
Please don't hurt my daughter. She hasn't done anything. Please, you--
Thorold? Thorold.
You've got to listen to me, it's a trick.
Parker doesn't have your family. It's a trick.
No, that's my Wendy and my Maggie.
No, listen to me. He's done it before and he's doing it again.
No, it's okay. I'm not gonna take the disk to him.
But tell me, what do I do?
I'll destroy it. I'll destroy the Day of Wonders.
That's what I have to do. Will you help me?
Thorold--
Please, I need your help.
Please, will you help me.
I know how we can stop it, Thorold.
Willie-
Listen, Cindy, I don't know what Macalusso had planned for
the Day of Wonders, but Parker and his gang of dirtbags
obviously have some very different ideas.
Now look, the mainframe computer at the O.N.E. building
is the hub for the entire system, right?
If we could just upload a virus, that could infect every computer on the network.
Meaning?
Meaning that if it works, tomorrow afternoon when
the whole world puts on those goggles,
they won't see any more in there than Cindy sees out here.
And without me, they won't be re-writin' it any time soon.
But what about that line of encryption on the program?
I mean, are you going to destroy the Day of Wonders
before you even see what it is?
No, the computer's still workin' on that,
but I can guarantee you that that is not the answer.
Yeah, well how do you know that?
Thorold, remember that day we went walkin' on the beach?
Yeah.
Yeah, you remember that seashell?
Yeah, well that single seashell was made up of
almost 4,000 lines of code.
We're talkin' about one line, here.
I'm telling you, whatever they have planned for the day of
wonders, it's not on that disk. And at noon tomorrow,
the whole world's gonna put on those glasses,
and find themselves in the middle of who knows what.
Yeah, well we don't have until noon tomorrow. So let's stop
wastin' time talkin' about if, and start talkin' about how.
I got a plan.
Look, the O.N.E. cleaning staff comes in at around 11:30, right?
I can access the security computer and get Thorold in there as a janitor.
Oh yeah, right. Like they won't notice a new face.
No way. That place is huge. About 5,000 people walk by that security desk every day.
Well, let's do it.
Are you going to be able to find the V.R. lab?
Shouldn't be a problem as long as the
files Willie pulled are complete.
Now, the challenge is gonna be the alarms.
This notepad contains all the info you're gonna need to
deactivate the alarm system, but once you're inside
you're gonna have to hurry.
Now, if you come to a fork in the road, Thorold, take it.
Oh Willie, everything's a joke to you.
Thorold?
Godspeed.
I told you, I don't believe in God.
It's okay.
He believes in you.
Man, I just... I don't know what else I can do.
There is just nothin' in there, Cindy.
I guess we'll just have to wait to hear from Thorold.
And this stupid line of code!
I mean, it's only one line. What can it possibly say?
Then why did they go through all this trouble to keep you out?
I guess I better call Thorold before he gets inside.
Thorold?
Yeah, here I am, I'm doin' fine.
I'm about three minutes out. How are you doin'?
Yeah, no problem.
I'm just checkin' to make sure that whoever you are isn't
gonna be on duty tonight. Yeah, okay, your name is
Bill Rowesome. You're workin' the night shift.
Now, you take your radio with you, but whatever you do,
do not transmit once you're inside.
You wait to hear from me. Love you, baby.
(fumbling with goggles)
Here.
Still blind.
How ya doin'.
Go ahead, Mr. Rowesome.
I'm going to be in a critically important meeting,
and I don't want to be disturbed. Is that clear?
(computer beeping)
(electronic theme playing)
Yes, we're in!
What?
That line of code. It's finally cracked.
Now we can see what all this fuss was about.
No, you can see what all the fuss is about.
I can only hear about it.
Hello.
(footsteps)
Ah!
What?
My god.
Oh my God, I can't believe it. This is impossible!
What, Willie? What?
My finger! Look at my finger.
Very funny.
This has nothing to do with technology,
I don't care what's in that line of code.
Helen!
All right, here we go. "Cross white wire with yellow wire"...
There is no yellow wire.xpppx
Ronnie?
Yeah?
Oh Ronnie, thank God you got my message. Listen, Willie's
cracked the code, you better get back here right away.
Do you really need those things?
Hey sis, listen, any wimp can quit smoking, okay?
It takes a real man to deal with lung cancer.
Well, at least wait until I'm out of the room.
Okay, fine.
Listen, Helen, it just doesn't make any sense.
I mean, there's nothing in there but images.
Whatever we're dealing with here, it's not just technology.
There's something else.
Helen, what's wrong?
Images.
That's it, images.
Speak to the world as you spoke to Eve,
let the Day of Wonders begin.
When she plucked the apple from the tree,
Let each man see his heart's desire,
let the Day of Wonders begin.
And believe our path will take him higher,
The real wonders are pride and greed,
let the Day of Wonders begin.
And those shall be our apple tree,
let the Day of Wonders begin!
(alarm beeping)
Welcome to the Day of Wonders.
Willie!
Oh...
(gasping)
Oh!
(crying)
Hello, Cindy. Congratulations. You are the very first
to participate in the Day of Wonders.
My eyes!
I can see you!
That's right, Cindy. You can see.
You can see. Look, all around you.
You can see the blue sky. You can see the beautiful sunsets.
From now on, you'll be able to see everything,
not just in here, but out there.
Your voice. You're the Messiah.
That's right.
There's nothing to be afraid of. Give me your hand.
No...
Give me your hand.
There's absolutely nothing to be frightened of.
Come on.
Look.
Oh...
No, but I wore the goggles before and I couldn't see this.
No, but today is the Day of Wonders.
Everything that you see is real.
(sobbing)
All illusions have been shattered.
This is real.
Yes!
I am real.
All you have to do, Cindy, is trust in me. Believe in me.
And all of it shall be yours.
But I do! I believe in you! I do, I do...
Then renounce him, Cindy. Tell the son of man
that he has no place in your heart,
that he has no place in your life. Tell him
that you have tasted of the fruit of the tree of knowledge.
(gasping)
Tell him, Cindy. And then, pledge your allegiance to me.
Take my mark.
Worship me as the one true god.
I do.
I do! Oh, I do!
(sobbing)
Yes!
This has gotta be what the Day of Wonders is all about.
It's coming, my friends, and coming very soon.
And when it does, you'll know that you're living
in the darkest days of the great tribulation.
The antichrist, the devil incarnate, will deceive
the whole world. He will come as a man in peace,
but he will bathe the world in blood.
The antichrist will have supernatural power,
power to give life to the image of the beast, and the image
of the beast will live and speak. The antichrist will
kill every person on earth who will not worship
the image of the beast. He will cause all the people
of the earth, both small and great, rich and poor,
free and bond-servant, to receive the mark on their
right hand or on their foreheads.
Without that mark, no man will be able to buy or sell.
"And let him that hath understanding count the
number of the beast, for it is the number of a man
and his number shall be six hundred, three score and six."
Oh, 666!
Hey, you know what? I live at 668, maybe I'm the
neighbour of the beast. That would explain that
strange smell comin' from Mr. Apelbi's garbage.
Willie, this is not a joke.
Aw, come on, Helen, get a grip! This is real life,
not a horror movie.
Yeah, well I'm afraid it's about to become one.
You said it yourself, Willie. The Day of Wonders is all about images.
Yeah, whatever. We don't have time for this right now.
This is incredible, Cindy. I don't know how it works,
but unless we can stop it, Parker's plan to kill all of
the haters might actually become a reality.
I need to talk to you.
Okay, can you just hold on a second,
I gotta find out where Thorold is.
It is really important.
Okay, can you just hold on one second, please?
No, it is really important!
All right, what is it?
That is the ugliest shirt.
Yeah, well those...
But...
How?
Willie?
Hey, Elvis, it's okay, look, it's just Willie.
It's just Willie.
You know, sis, I've been thinkin'.
If Thorold doesn't get that virus uploaded,
we might need to warn the others, and right now,
you're the only one who knows where the other hideouts are.
I can't do that, Will.
Helen, a halo only needs to fall a few inches to become a noose.
Well, thanks for the encouragement, Will.
Helen, I'm serious. I really think you
should tell me where the other hideouts are.
I can't do that, Will. You know I can't.
No, you can. And it's okay, Helen. I'm on side now.
I found God.
What? That's wonderful, Willie. When?
I mean, when did this happen?
Just now. I finally saw the truth.
Was it worth it, Willie? Was it worth your soul?
Cindy! What happened?
I saw the light, that's what happened.
I guess now we know what the Day of Wonders is all about.
Oh God, no.
Oh God, yes!
Put it down!
Any time now.
Get over there.
Sorry, sis. He made us an offer we just couldn't refuse.
No.
No, Willie. How could you?
How could you? You, you knew all this!
I mean, how could you know this was gonna happen and fall for it anyway?
"How could you? How could you?"you're so stupid!
Thanks to Thorold and that CD, Cindy and I got a sneak preview
of the Day of Wonders. And I'm tellin' you, sis, it is the
greatest thing that ever happened to me.
Ain't that right, Cindy?
Oh yeah. I've been hanging with you bible-thumpers for
three months now, and I haven't seen one single miracle.
But now I've found the true God. And now I see everything.
But the price. Willie
Save your breath, Helen. It's no use. Their souls are gone.
And once you take the mark, there's no going back.
Oh yeah, that's right, Helen. You know,
you're preaching to the perverted right now.
Listen, once the world checks in to the Day of Wonders,
we're gonna have a whole lotta company.
All right, that's enough talk, now.
Just tell us, where are the hideouts?
I'd rather die.
Well, that can be arranged.
You know something, Helen? I shoulda shot you a long time ago.
Do what you have to, Willie.
(gunshot)
(crashing on floor)
Helen, what's goin' on?
Get back in the car!
(dog barking)
Lie down!
(gunshot)
Good doggie!
Thorold.
I wouldn't be doin' this if it weren't absolutely necessary.
The virus will not work unless the program is running.
I repeat, it will not work unless the program is running.
Now, find the V.R. goggles, put them on,
and spend a couple of minutes in V.R.,
and then you can come out an upload the virus.
Good luck, my friend.
That was perfect.
Wendy. Maggie.
Welcome to the Day of Wonders, Thorold Stone.
I've been waiting for you.
Ron, nige work. Got the big fish, Helen Hannah.
I'm takin' her to Parker myself.
Macalusso.
Where am I?
Well, it's a little bit like heaven.
Only better.
Look who it is, Maggie.
Daddy, daddy, we miss you, daddy. We miss you.
Don't abandon us again, Thorold.
You've got to open your mind this time, and listen to him.
It's the only way.
Take a look at them, Thorold. They're exactly as you
remember them. Do you know why? Because they are inside of you.
Everything there is is inside of you.
That's what I'm here to teach you.
That's what the Day of Wonders is all about.
Now, for you, it's your family.
For others, it's something- something else.
But all of it can be yours.
All you have to do is believe.
Know who I am, and believe.
And you can have everything there is. Everything.
Please, Thorold. You can be with us today.
And what about the rest of eternity?
(chuckling)
Oh, I was wrong about you.
I actually thought you were an alien.
Yes, I know.
But now you believe. Don't you?
Now I believe.
Hold it.
Oh Ronnie, I hope he hasn't put those goggles on yet.
Let's hope he hasn't.
Which way now?
This way.
Now all you have to do is give me your pledge of allegiance,
and everything you've ever dreamed of will be yours.
You're not about love at all, are you?
I would rather believe in a creator who would die for his
creation than have his creation die for him.
My son--
I am not your son, Satan.
And they are not my family.
I know where my family is, where they'll be safe from you for eternity.
So be it.
You've made your choice.
And now you will pay the price.
Not even your God can save you.
He already has.
(maniacal laughter)
(locks snapping shut)
So this is the Day of Wonders?
You make the world worship you or die.
I don't have to make them worship me.
They'll want to worship me.
And do you know why? Do you?
Because I give them everything that they want.
And just like Eve in the Garden of Eden,
they snap it up in a second. And those that don't,
well, they die. So either way, I win.
Pretty soon everything on this whole earth will be mine.
All of it will be mine.
And there's no reason for God to come back, now, is there?
I found out who you really are by saying no.
What about those who said yes? When do they find out?
Tomorrow.
But by then, it's going to be too late.
You see, once they give me the pledge of allegiance,
they will be mine for eternity. And those that aren't are dead.
It's a wonderful day, don't you think?
Lord, I didn't honour you with my life.
By your grace, may I do so in death.
Oh! Very touching.
Goodbye, Thorold Stone.
Thorold, are you okay?
Helen!
Everything really happened in there.
I know, I know. But I heard you make the right decision.
Oh...
Where's Willie?
He met Macalusso in there too.
He made the wrong decision.
He took the mark of the beast.
That's why he wanted me to put the goggles on.
Once you're inside, you either accept the mark or you die.
Yeah, either way you wouldn't be uploading that virus.
Well, they won't be far behind us, guys. Let's move.
All right. All right...
The first thing he's gonna do is check this console.
That's where I was supposed to upload the virus. There's gotta
be another computer that linked to the main network.
How about that one?
We're in.
(computer beeping)
How long is gonna take?
Hopefully no longer than we've got.
We've got no time. They're here.
Thorold!
Okay, okay, all right. Find me another black disk.
What?
Another black disk! Find another black disk!
Thorold, got one.
Spin that console around.
Hold it right there, my friend!
Looks like we got here just in time.
Well, what are you waiting for? Get the disk!
I'll take that.
What's the matter, stupid? Did all the big words confuse you?
Nice to see you.
Open the door.
(computer beeping)
What's the matter with the door?
I don't know why it's so slow.
All the access doors were a little slow on the way down here.
The boys upstairs must be running some big program on
the main computer system.
Three more guests for your little fireside prayer meeting.
The virus!
But before we turn up the heat,
I'm gonna give you all one last chance.
Renounce Him.
Let me tell you something, Mr. Parker.
The God we serve is with us.
And he is fully able to deliver us from this place. But even
if he doesn't, rest assured we will never serve Macalusso.
Nor worship his image or take his mark.
Ever.
Amen.
As you wish.
I'm glad the Lord has opened your eyes, son.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're forgiven. We all are.
And if the end result is your soul,
then what we've been through is a small price to pay.
♪ Amazing grace how sweet the sound ♪
♪ that saved a wretch like me ♪
♪ I once was lost but now I'm found ♪
Let's see if they can sing and scream at the same time.
(roaring flames)
(door crashing open)
Cindy, get off of me! Look for the disk!
♪ was grace that taught my heart to fear ♪
Why are they still singing?
Why aren't they burning?
It's a black O.N.E. Disk!
But Willie, I can't read!
Just pop this! Pop this!
Pop any disk! Pop any disk!
They're not burning.
It's Him! He's protecting them!
Turn it up more! Now!
(flames roaring)
He can't do this. He can't do this!
Where is it?
It's not here!
It's gotta be here! It's gotta be here!
Where else? Where else would it be?
Right there.
(singing growing louder, flames roaring)
These souls are mine! They have to die!
Yes, yes...
Cindy...
What?
Wait a minute...
What, Willie? What?
Turn it up more! Turn it up more!
It's overloading. You'll burn down the whole building.
(gunshot)
No, no!
No! No!
This is impossible! No!
(singing, roaring flames)
This is our day! Our time!
No!
What? What?
(hail of gunfire)
All the way!
No...
What?
What, Willie, what?
Tell me! Tell me!
It's over, Cindy.
What?
It's over.
No-- NO!
I'll finish them myself.
(screaming)
♪ ...from when we first begun... ♪
Former WNN news anchor Helen Hannah has
apparently done it again. Authorities are scrambling
to make sense of what happened last night as
the O.N.E. headquarters burned to the ground.
However, there is no doubt that the much-anticipated
Day of Wonders project has been postponed.
(cheers, applause)
We've also learned that Miss Hannah escaped from the
O.N.E. Rehabilitation facility overnight. The Messiah had
this to say from Jerusalem just a few hours ago.
And yet another act of hatred and of selfishness.
The haters have stolen the Day of Wonders from us.
From the new and united world. But rest assured,
they will not prevail against us. We will double
our efforts of the followers of the deceiver, Jesus.
(music)