[MUSIC - LINDSEY RAY, "PICTURE
PERFECT"]
(SINGING) You played your
piano, wrote silly love songs
and sang me fast asleep.
You drove me to New York,
healed my first heartache.
And I remember how every
night and every day
you're never afraid to
always say that I'm your moon
and stars.
You've got me singing,
la da da da, la da da da,
life is never picture perfect.
La da da da, la da da da, but
we are perfect just the way
we are.
You told me stories,
took me to movies
and held my hand so sweet.
We dressed in our snowsuits,
made pretty angels.
And I remember lying on
our backs, taking a rest,
making a guess, trying our best
to count the moon and stars.
Oh, thank you.
I don't know.
How does my hair look?
Ugh, perfect as always.
Thank you.
OK, ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
Ladies, it's time.
Shall we?
(SINGING) La da da
da, la da da da.
We are perfect just
the way we are.
Being in a sorority
is a privilege.
But being a Delta,
that's an honor.
I don't need to tell you
how deeply the actives rely
on the insider
opinions of us alumni
when judging our
local girls at rush.
Now it's up to us to do our
part to ensure that only
the right girls get in
to protect the legacy
we all built. Lutie.
You can endorse as many
as you like this year.
We all understand the pressure,
so please keep the good
of the house in mind.
Strong crop this year.
Which reminds me--
spoke to my Gwen.
Reminded her that Katie
is prime Delta material.
She'll be in good hands.
LUTIE: I still can't believe
it's her time already.
I still feel like a freshman
pledge myself some days.
Oh, honey, don't we wish?
[LAUGHS] This is
the next best thing--
both our girls following
in our footsteps.
I couldn't ask
for anything more.
(SINGING) Just the way we are.
[MUSIC - DANIELLE MCKEE, "THIS
IS ME"]
(SINGING) This is my life.
I'm on my own.
Don't need anyone to
guide me down the road.
I'm finding out who--
Hi.
(SINGING) Yeah,
who I want to be.
This is me.
This is my life.
I'm in control.
Moving so fast to
where I wanna go.
Name, please, so we
have your information.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Hi.
Hey.
So I guess those
are the preppy girls,
and those are the slacker guys.
God, it's like some
kind of gang war,
only really, really perky.
Oh my goodness,
how are you girls
going to keep them straight?
There's so many.
A house for every girl.
That was our mission
when I started here.
Oh, this is so exciting.
Aw.
Katie Parker!
Look at you, all grown up.
I can't believe you're here.
You two must be proud.
My Gwen tells me your Katie
is quite the hot rush ticket.
Oh.
What?
Every year, there's a
handful of premium girls
that all the good
houses fight over.
Poaching a legacy is
total sport around here.
Be warned.
But we already have dibs on you.
In your pledge, I totally
want to be your big sis, OK?
Pinky swear.
OK.
Gwen's been elected
Delta rush chair.
It's quite an honor.
Mm-hmm.
And if she does a good job,
she's a lock for president
next year, just like her mom.
All right, I'm headed
back to the house
with the other alumni.
See you later?
Yes, definitely.
Come on.
Gwen!
OK, bye.
KATIE: Come on, let's go.
You guys go ahead.
I'll catch up.
Mom?
You OK?
Oh, just being silly.
Reliving some ancient memories.
Some of the best moments of my
life happened on this stage.
This is where Delta won
its first ever Tri Crown.
I was lead vocals.
I bet you rocked
the house, huh?
I held my own.
Ooh, go, mom.
Oh, it's your turn
in the spotlight now.
Three months, I'll be
watching you up here.
Oh, mom.
Chill.
I'm not even in Delta yet.
You will be.
You are beautiful and
talented, all grown up.
Mom, you promised
you wouldn't cry.
I can't help it.
Well, you owe me 5 bucks.
I am so proud of you
and so excited we're going
to have all this to share.
Yeah, me, too.
Hey, I have a crazy thought.
How would you like to visit
Delta and meet all the girls?
Can we?
I don't think I'm supposed to
be fraternizing during rush.
I think I can
pull some strings.
Come on, let's go get Sara.
It'll be fun.
Come on.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Katie!
Hey!
Oh my gosh, do you
believe this place?
What do you think?
I think this is the actual
floor plan of the Barbie dream
house.
Oh, I know.
Can you imagine living here
for the next four years?
That's not all.
Full-time cook, weekly
maid, and sleeps more girls
than any other chapter.
Best house ever.
I'm telling you, if they
have half as much fun as we had
when we were here, this is
going to be quite a year.
Whoa.
What's with the Super Bowl?
Is this what I think it is?
I've only seen it in pictures.
LUTIE: Mm-hmm.
That is the Tri Crown trophy.
Tri Crown is legendary.
It's this amazing competition
between all the sororities
every year.
More like a war.
And not to brag, but
we totally dominate.
And our mother started
the whole thing.
Well, that's a bit of a fib.
It was actually a
fraternity competition
until the school went coed,
and then us ladies just sort of
took it over somehow.
I like Gwen's version better.
I still can't believe you
talked me into all of this.
What, the most fun
you can have at college?
Right, I'm sorry I
twisted your arm.
You should be.
Now I have to face the fact
that I am a secret conformist
at heart.
That vexes me.
Well, if it suits
your anarchist ego,
Greek life isn't just about
keggers and formals, OK?
Are you drinking the Kool-Aid?
Seriously.
It is a proven fact
joining increases
your odds of staying in school
and earning more after you
graduate.
- Wow.
Will it also make my hair
shiny and manageable?
Fine.
We just better get
in the same house.
I'm not doing this without you.
Hey, we're only
here for Delta.
We're only doing full
rush because we have to.
I kind of like
these Kappa girls.
We're about
friendship, not gossip.
Fun, not drama.
That sounds great.
Still not Delta.
I don't know.
Speaking of Delta,
is it me, or was
Gwen totally about to dry hump
you in the quad this morning?
[LAUGHS] I don't know.
What was that about?
She barely even talked
to us in high school.
I guess you weren't such a hot
ticket when you had a retainer.
Or was it headgear?
No, she was just being
nice in front of our moms
because we're BFFs.
Probably ignore us
again the rest of rush.
[MUSIC - GIRLS LOVE SHOES,
"SUPAMEDICINE"]
(SINGING) I'm in a
pickle 'cause I'm fickle.
Don't know what to do.
Every girl has the right
to need a change of view.
I'm so impatient it takes--
[KNOCKING]
(SINGING) --imagination
to get through.
Gwen!
Hi.
So, big news.
There's a party at our
brother fraternity tonight.
Very VIP.
You in?
Absolutely.
Wait, you meant-- you
meant both of us, right?
Of course.
Any friend of Katie's
is a friend of Delta's.
Be ready at 9:00.
OK.
Let's go, girls.
Lucky bitches.
[GIGGLING]
[MUSIC - ST. JOHN, "KEEP IT
COMIN'"]
(SINGING) We like to party like
we party all night long, yeah.
Come on, come on.
Pump, pump it up.
Keep it comin'.
All right.
The other sororities will
try to tempt you this week.
But they can suck it!
You're ours.
Hey, I thought taking
rushes to parties
was against the rules.
Screw rules.
You're worth it.
It's like, we're continuing
our mom's legacies.
You and I, we are totally
going to own this house.
So whose party is this?
The Betas.
Definitely the hottest
guys on the campus.
Come on.
And we're like this with them.
Join Delta, and
you will be, too.
Hi.
Thanks.
Here.
Oh, you like?
Don't be shy.
What a Delta wants,
a Delta gets.
Come here.
Beau Beau.
Gwenny Gwen.
Meet Katie.
She's our top pick.
Definite Delta material.
So you be nice to her and
tell her how we're the hottest
house on the block, OK?
Have fun.
I gotta mingle.
- Bye.
Wow.
Friend of Gwen's, huh?
Mm, bet I can
guess your major.
Go for it.
English.
No, no, no, no, history.
Why would she want to waste
her time majoring, Deac?
I bet Katie's just here
for her MRS, right?
Actually, I'm an econ major.
But apparently, you're
majoring in sexist ass.
[CHOKING]
Well, good luck with that.
Oh, we like her.
Ow.
Ooh.
You should put
some ice on that.
OK, that-- that's
a little funny.
Seriously, though, I'm--
I'm really sorry.
I'm PJ, by the way.
Katie.
Katie, are you rushing, too?
Yeah, that's the plan.
Well, tell you what, uh--
Hey, man.
Thanks, bro.
If we both make it
out of rush alive,
I'll buy you some real
beers to celebrate,
in bottles and everything.
OK, you've got a deal.
OK.
PJers, [INAUDIBLE] now!
OK, I'll, uh--
I'll see you around, OK?
I'm serious about those beers.
Unbelievable!
We're here 10 minutes.
I have a migraine.
You have a date.
Well played.
Here.
Who wants your pity beer?
OK.
I'm kidding!
I totally want your pity beer!
[GIGGLING]
Woo!
I'mma dance!
[CAR REVVING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Welcome to rush, ladies.
Get ready for the five
hardest days of your lives.
Oh, this is amazing.
Let's move it, girls!
Let's go.
Now for those of you who don't
know, here's how rush works.
Each day you'll visit a
different sorority house
and start narrowing them down.
Now every sorority has a chance
to sell themselves to you
through theme days, using pledge
songs, slideshows, and skits.
(SINGING) Gamma
rho your boat ashore.
You're so cool.
Gamma rho we adore.
We're no fools.
Gamma rho your boat ashore.
You're so cool.
Gamma rho we adore.
[SNICKERING]
Not every house will fit you.
But some houses you'll
like right away.
So the brave rush crept slowly
down the old, haunted door
stairway.
And into the
empty, dark foyer,
desperate to know
if Kappa bid her.
She felt her way
to the mailboxes.
Took out her keys,
reached her hand deep inside
for her bid card, and--
[AIR HORN]
[LAUGHTER]
Just a little reminder, ladies.
BOTH: Life would be
scary without Kappa.
[CLAPPING]
Oh my god, they are insane.
I love it.
We like to think rushing
is like falling in love.
Both sides have to feel it.
And you'll know it
when it happens.
Our alumni are the most
dedicated and connected.
It's instant
networking potential.
Research shows that Delta girls
go on to higher paying jobs.
Unofficial research says
we also date cuter guys.
In closing, we also
have the highest ratio
of legacy retention.
We even have a Delta
legacy in our midst.
Stand up, Katie Parker.
[APPLAUSE]
Thank you, ladies, for coming.
Thank you.
Do not forget
this is all a test.
We are so excited.
While you are judging them,
they will be judging you.
No matter how much
they seem to like you--
Hey, you.
SARA: Hey.
Come here.
--don't take
anything for granted.
Every night, each
of you rushees will
choose your favorite houses.
Meanwhile, the sororities
will be cutting you.
Oh.
She's cute.
I like it.
[LAUGHS] No, never
going to make it.
Totally Delta.
We get her or die, ladies.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I got invited.
Awesome!
Oh my god, I knew
Delta liked me!
Holy crap, I actually
made [INAUDIBLE]..
Delta asked me back.
Yeah, why wouldn't they?
Wait, whoa, why do you
have one for Kappa, too?
I thought we were only
rushing Delta all the way.
You know, I just don't
want to look cocky.
Oh.
Well, I wouldn't worry.
You're their dream
girl, remember?
I'm the one who still
has to pray I get in.
I can't believe you're
so stressed about this.
You know whatever happens,
I have your back, OK?
What can I say?
In the gym class of life, I am
the fat kid on the sideline.
But you wouldn't
understand, Miss I
Have Two Pref Parties Tonight.
[MUSIC - BEAUTIFUL SMALL
MACHINES, "SUPER CONDUCTER"]
KAPPA GIRL 1: Woo!
Woo!
Go, Kappa!
KAPPA GIRL 2: Ready?
Kappa rules!
KAPPA GIRL 3: Woo!
(SINGING) Hey!
Hey!
I've got the frequency
to turn you on.
Superconductor, keep it going.
I've got the frequency
to turn you on.
Hey there, tin smiles, I've
been loading down your files,
moving up your dials and I
think I know what's going on.
I am programmed clickety-click
at your command.
Shift for a man with the
heart of an automaton.
Did we scare you away already?
I understand.
[INAUDIBLE] this
can be intimidating.
Sorry, I gotta get going.
I was supposed to be
at Delta a while ago.
Gotcha.
Look, I had a really
great time tonight.
But I don't want to mislead you.
I'm sort of supposed
to go Delta.
Oh, the legacy thing, huh?
Can I ask, why
did you pref me?
Well, I'm not going to lie.
Stealing a Delta
legacy would be a coup.
But mostly, you know your
people when you meet them.
And trust me.
You're Kappa people.
Thanks.
Just one piece of advice.
Whichever house you
pick, make sure you
like what they stand for.
Because you're about
to stand for it, too.
See you.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
Woo!
Get your cute butt
in here, girl!
We missed you!
Let's all make Katie welcome,
you hot Delta bitches!
Katie!
Oh my god, I'm so
glad you're here.
Oh, jello shots!
I was this close to calling
standards on those Kappa skanks
for keeping her too long.
I know.
It's like, hi, have
some tact, people.
Tell me.
[GIGGLING]
(SINGING DRUNKENLY) Beauty in
her heart and soul, my sister
till I'm gray and old.
There's no greater treasure
in all the world than a Delta
Theta Theta girl.
You were right.
The Deltas are the best!
Woo!
What's that all about?
That's Lana.
We were having boat races
before you got here.
And she puked on Gwen's shoes.
And it was awesome!
I am so glad you
talked me into this.
You are the best friend ever.
Mm, creepy.
Oh my god.
[LAUGHTER]
So what did you tell her?
Who, Lana?
I said that we would
forgive and forget.
But we expect you to
show loyalty and only put
Delta's name on her bid.
Wait, we're going to bid her?
Of course not, stupid.
But this way, no
one else can either.
And she'll be left
with no house.
Serves her right.
Hey, what about
that Sara chick
you keep letting hang around?
GWEN: That one's not my fault.
Katie won't cut the cord,
but Sara's a brain.
She can earn her place.
I mean, someone has got to
raise the GPA while we have fun.
But I want to stay.
You're leaving?
Um, yeah, it's kind of late.
Am I crazy here?
Because I'm picking
up some attitude.
I mean, first, I have to
practically drag you away
from those Kappa
bitches with my teeth.
And now you can't wait to leave?
I gotta say, you're not
really feeling the Delta love.
Look, it's nothing personal.
And I'm just tired.
Where are my shoes?
I forgot my shoes.
Don't panic.
I'm all over it.
Are you rejecting me?
What?
No--
Do you know how
bad this will make
me look if we lose a legacy?
How pissed my mom will be?
Your mom?
You humiliate Delta like this,
trust me, you will be sorry.
Look, go take
your Xanax, Gwen.
This isn't a big deal, OK?
No, you're right.
You're right.
Cold feet are no big deal.
And that's all this is.
You and I are
practically sisters.
And sisters support one another.
Do the right thing here, Katie.
Have some principles.
Me?
Wow, you're really one to talk.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, it means you've broken
every rush rule that there is.
I mean private parties, bribing
these girls with drinks.
Oh, and what about promising
that poor Lana girl a bid just
so she'd be cross cut?
What the hell was that?
Boohoo.
So I break a few stupid
rules to get the best girls.
That's what makes me a winner.
And as for the
dirty rushing, I'd
like to see you try to prove it.
So would I. Standards
meeting tomorrow at 10:00.
We'll get to the bottom of this.
Oh my gosh.
Now look what you've done.
Found them!
Hey, what's her problem?
Promising bids?
Cross cutting?
Drinking games?
This makes all of us look bad.
But we still have to prove
it, and Lana won't go on record.
Besides, it's her word
against the Deltas.
She's not the only
chance we've got.
We'd like to hear
from rushee Parker.
Wow, so this is, like,
Sorority Supreme Court, huh?
OK, wrong crowd.
Just to clarify,
you personally
overheard plans to promise
a rush a bid with the intent
of cutting her?
Look, I don't want to
cause any drama, honestly.
Can we just forget all this?
No.
Accusations were made.
Either you were
lying, or you weren't.
I wasn't lying.
Thank you.
Take your seat.
I was starting to get worried.
We really need to talk.
Sara Snow, please stand.
Do you confirm
these accusations?
No.
Are you denying rushee
Parker's version of events?
Do you deny there was alcohol?
I just didn't
share her experience.
I mean, the Deltas have been
proper and conscientious
around me the entire time.
(WHISPERING)
Sara, what the hell?
We've heard enough testimony.
Some conflicting,
but I have to trust
what I witnessed last night.
Deltas, please stand.
You know the rules.
You know the consequence
of breaking them.
Your annual house formal
is hereby canceled.
You can't do that!
What?
Mom?
It's not my fault. Do
not get angry at me.
OK, Gwen, slow down.
What-- what are we
talking about here?
Standards.
Katie said we were dirty
rushing, and they believed her.
They canceled our formal!
What?
Oh.
Oh, hell no.
Hang on.
Hello?
Lutie, what did
your daughter just do?
Snitch.
Come on, guys.
Let's go.
Ugh, hater.
Nice.
Very mature.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
GWEN (ON PHONE): You
just made a big mistake.
This isn't over, bitch.
We're going to make
your life hell.
[KNOCKING]
Mom.
What are you doing here?
Get dressed, dear.
We need to talk.
How is Sara?
KATIE: I don't know.
She's been avoiding
me since yesterday.
I can't believe you came all
the way to campus over this.
I had no choice.
So we're going to have a meeting
with the Dean in an hour.
Are you serious?
This is serious, Katie.
Now I'm not impressed with
how you've handled yourself.
Well, I'm sorry.
God.
Oh, and I'm fine, by the way.
Thanks for asking.
Don't be smart.
Your well-being is what
I'm concerned with.
Darling, you've
tainted yourself.
The right sorority can provide
you social and business
contacts for life.
Being a Delta practically
guarantees you job interviews
when you graduate.
What house is going
to take you now?
It doesn't matter.
I'm not rushing anymore.
I'm dropping out.
What?
Look, I know this isn't
what we had planned.
But it doesn't have
to be a big deal.
Katie.
Mom, I'll be fine, really.
OK, school starts in three
days This will all blow over.
Look, I gotta go.
Well--
GIRL 1: Delta?
GIRL 2: Yes!
Ah!
GIRL 1: Ah, I'm so excited!
GIRL 2: Me, too!
GIRL 1: Woo!
Yes!
Sara.
Not so fast, Judas.
What the hell
happened yesterday?
You're the one who
put me in that position
in the first place.
What was I supposed to do?
Oh, I don't know--
support me, tell the truth?
And get blackballed by the
one sorority I was bidding?
Look, why do you care
about a stupid sorority?
So first, you tell me
Greek life is awesome.
Now sororities are stupid.
Gee, am I allowed to have
thoughts of my own on this?
Yes, of course you are.
Just, I thought
you'd share mine.
It doesn't matter anyway.
We obviously can't
join them now.
Am I stroking out here, or
did you just give me an order?
Oh, don't be so dramatic.
I just--
You told me I couldn't do
something because you weren't
doing it?
Yeah, that's an order.
And it's too late.
Sara.
I can't believe how selfish
you're being about this.
Me?
The whole campus wanted you.
You could have gone anywhere.
Finally, I meet people
who like me for me,
and you're being
such a baby about it.
Let's just cool off.
OK?
And so we'll be in
different sororities.
So what?
It doesn't mean we
can't still be friends.
When you had to stab me
in the back to get there?
I guess that's
exactly what it means.
Fine.
I guess I should pack my
stuff and move into Delta.
Maybe you should.
[MUSIC - SWEETERSONGS, "WHY NOT
NOW"]
(SINGING) La da
da da da da da da.
La da da da da da da.
Give it up, break the hold.
Take the edge of all that noise.
[KNOCKING]
What now?
(SINGING) Turn it down.
Feel the crying.
Oh!
Hi.
I got into Beta.
Whew.
[LAUGHS]
I've been celebrating.
I can see that.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
I guess only one of us made
it through rush alive, huh?
Hey, I still
owe you that beer.
Uh, we're having a keg and
egg party tomorrow night.
It should be insane.
Katie Parker, will
you be my date?
Yeah, I'd love to.
OK, I'll pick you up at 8:00.
Wear your jammies.
(SINGING) Just let go.
There's no way I would drop you.
La da da da da da da da.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Ew.
Hey, econ girl.
Great.
So look, other night, rumor
has it I may have come off
as a bit of a--
- Jerk?
Nope.
A neo misogynist?
Actually, it was--
Troll?
Hun?
Reprobate?
Wow.
And she's as good
with her adjectives
as she is with numbers.
That's awesome.
Thank you.
This was good.
Glad we had this little talk.
I feel better.
Here comes herpes girl.
Excuse me.
No kidding.
Ew, she's coming this way.
Don't get too close.
No kidding.
Do you think it's real?
Ew, I can't believe he's
sitting down next to her.
Let's go.
OK.
Awkward.
I don't know.
Let's try this again.
I'm Beau, and I'm really not
as bad as you think I am.
Considering how
low that bar is,
I'll conceive the possibility.
I just can't stand
Gwen and her girls.
I just made you
guilty by association.
And that was wrong of me.
Thank you.
Especially now, I'm not
associating with anyone.
What does that mean?
Come on.
I mean, after that
stunt you pulled,
you're like Typhoid Mary.
Now there's probably never been
a less popular girl on campus,
thanks to Gwen and
her [INAUDIBLE] mafia.
Is this seat taken?
Hey.
I don't recommend the company.
Wow, I have never seen you
tank with a girl before, Beau.
That was almost art.
I know, right?
I'm off my game with that one.
I guess I should go apologize
for being a jerk again.
No, let me.
I need to talk to her anyway.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
Sorry, I just really
needed some air.
Well, it's no problem.
So how are you doing?
I haven't seen you since the
Great Sorority Inquisition.
I'm OK, I guess.
Liar.
I think I know
what's bothering you.
And I just want you to know
that Kappa has got your back.
It is the least we could do.
Oh.
Oh my god.
I know, it's really crazy.
What the hell are these?
Where did you get them?
They're all over
campus since last night.
So this is why everybody's
been staring and laughing?
Are you kidding?
Oh my god.
Katie.
Look, Gwen's a freak, no doubt.
Knowing her, she won't
stop this anytime soon.
So what do I do?
Talk to Panhellenic.
I've never really heard
of a girl being allowed
to join a house after
quitting rush, but--
Wait, that's your solution?
Joining a different sorority?
Yeah.
They're not all
like Delta, Katie.
Every house is different.
Some are sluts, some are snobs.
Some are the best
girls you'll ever meet.
It doesn't matter.
It was a mistake for me to
rush in the first place.
It's not for me.
Because of Gwen?
No, because I have
an IQ above dryer lint.
And I don't need to buy my
friends with sorority dues.
Wow.
Thanks.
No, I--
No, look, you had one bad
experience with one bad house.
I get it.
But judging every
sorority because of that
makes you as big
a snob as Gwen is.
I guess I had you wrong, Katie.
Maybe you do belong with Delta.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, screw it.
[MUSIC - THE EXPLODERS, "PRETTY
GIRLS"]
(SINGING) Nobody will love you.
Nobody will love you.
Nobody will.
Nobody will, hey!
Hey.
There you are.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Um, you invited me?
Yeah, but I thought when
I didn't come by, you--
you know.
Look, if you
don't want me here,
then have the decency
to say it to my face.
OK, look.
Gwen and her Deltas date a
lot of our senior brothers.
And if you come to our parties,
the Deltas [INAUDIBLE]..
So it's kind of the house rule
that we can't be seen with you.
You're serious?
Look, Katie, I
think you're great.
But I'm just a pledge.
These guys can make
my life a living hell.
And it's not my fight.
It's a lot of other
things to think about it.
It wouldn't happen in real life.
Yeah, I like your PJs.
Well, I like yours, too.
Sara?
They gave me a
little Delta makeover.
Do you like it?
I can't even deal
with this right now.
Oh my god.
What are you doing here?
Trust me--
Snitch.
ALL: Snitch.
[GIGGLING]
Snitch.
You are a piece of work, Gwen.
[LIGHT CRYING]
Mom?
Look, I was wrong.
I need your help.
Can I come home?
Uh, motion to
send an arrangement
to the senior actives
congratulating them
on a job well done.
I mean, we have a really strong
looking rush class this year.
Mm-hmm, seconded.
How are the other houses looking
for this year's competition?
What competition?
Now let's not get glib.
You know the moment
we sit on our laurels,
some sad little house
will come from behind
and steal that Tri-Crown.
Any new business to table, hmm?
Actually, I do
have some business.
Hmm?
I had a chat with
Katie, and it seems--
and believe me, I find this
hard to believe myself.
It seems she's been the
target of some harassment.
It needs to stop.
What?
That's appalling.
You-- you're not saying you
think it was one of our Delta
girls, are you?
Well, who else could it be?
What?
Hello?
Don't you remember
college at all?
Yeah.
Your daughter stepped
on a hornet's nest
when she opened her mouth.
What are you talking about?
Katie not only defamed Delta,
she smeared the whole rush
system.
I'm sure girls from
all over campus
were offended, from
pledges to wannabes.
Yep.
Any one of them could
have taken matters
into their own hands.
I mean, because nobody
likes a tattletale.
It's-- it's really true.
It's sad, and it's wrong.
And really, our
hearts go out to her.
Mm-hmm.
But if fingers are going
to be pointed anywhere,
don't you think they should
be at Katie for starting all
this drama in the first place?
Mm-hmm.
Let's talk
fundraising, shall we?
- Yay.
- Woohoo!
I think that's just
sororities, honey.
There's always some
kind of drama going on.
Dad, that's so sexist.
Well, look at your
mom and her friends.
I don't know any grown
man to give a damn
about fraternity politics
20 years out of school.
No, but you and
your father still
cry over college football.
Yeah, but that's important.
Fine.
Maybe we're each just
stupid in our own ways then.
Agreed.
Hey, honey.
Hey.
I'll just, uh, leave you guys.
So, did you talk to them?
I did.
And they are very
concerned about you.
Concerned?
What does that mean?
They think it's terrible.
And they wish they could
help, but honey, it's
all been anonymous.
Are you sure it's Delta?
You're seriously
asking me that?
Katie--
Don't worry about it.
I thought you could
help me, I was wrong.
It's no big deal.
Honey, it's not that simple.
Things are complicated
at the alumni level.
It is very political.
Mom, it is an alumni
group, not the freaking UN.
It's fine.
I'll handle it myself.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHTER]
[KNOCKING]
KAPPA GIRL: Somebody
get the door!
[KNOCKING]
God, make it stop already!
I want to be a Kappa.
And I want to
be Angelina Jolie.
Brad Pitt years, not Billy Bob.
What's your point?
You said that I could
petition to late rush.
Is that true?
It's a long shot.
Anyway, why should we
give you a second chance?
Because you were right, OK?
I screwed up, and I judged
all sororities based on Delta.
And I was wrong.
Just listen.
We're about
friendship, not gossip.
Fun, not drama.
I mean, that's all I
wanted in the first place.
And if I can still be a
part of a house like that,
I'd really like to try.
Well, we'd have to
vote on it as a house.
I understand.
Hey!
If we can get it by
standards, you're in.
If everyone could
please calm down.
Ladies, take your seats.
Sisters, what say you?
Given the circumstances,
does Katie Parker
have your permission to
join Kappa as a late pledge?
The nays?
And the yeas?
Yeas have it.
So ordered.
[APPLAUSE]
Oh, I'm sorry.
If you're looking for Sara,
she had to hurry back and do
all her homework.
But I don't see why.
Your calendar should be cleared
since you have no formal
at all.
How's that working out for you?
Well, it's good to see
you in a good mood again.
Leave some room.
Your mom made custard.
Oh, no, I can't stay long.
I just came to
grab a few dresses.
I've got somewhere
to be tomorrow night.
Were you even
going to tell me you
joined a different sorority?
Should I have?
Don't be smart, young lady.
Here we go.
You know, I was beginning to
understand why you did what you
did.
I even felt for you.
Maybe I pushed you too hard.
Maybe sororities
weren't right for you.
Mom--
Only then I heard
from everybody but you
that you like
sororities just fine.
You just decided to
humiliate me and mine.
How do you think I look
to the other alumni?
Why are you making
this about you?
Not me.
Us.
We were supposed to
share this moment.
Remember?
Enjoy your initiation.
Meanwhile, I have to help the
Deltas affirm their pledge
class without you.
She can't stay
angry forever, kid.
Yeah, I'll watch her
starting to feel that way.
ALL: See here at
Kappa Theta Psi,
we pledge ourselves to thee.
With our free hearts and minds,
forever sisters we shall be.
And all our Kappa lives,
we will build your legacy.
These pens symbolize
your acceptance among us.
We are all sisters now.
Wear them with pride.
Kappas forever.
And some of you have special
guests waiting to welcome you
here tonight.
Mom!
Honey, you look beautiful.
I'm so proud of you, baby.
[HUMMING]
ALL: (SINGING) Beauty in her
heart and soul, my sister
till I'm gray and old.
There's no greater treasure in
all the world than a Delta Beta
Theta girl.
[HUMMING]
Such a shame.
This could be so special
for you with Katie here.
[MUSIC - SAMANTHA JADE, "GET
AWAY"]
(SINGING) Seize the
moment, attempted fates.
Step up the cold, dark into you.
So many boys who want to holler
at me, better make your move.
Tick tock, tick tock.
(SINGING) You're on the clock.
Say it, 'fess up.
Come on, now what?
What makes you think
that you're so special?
Flaunting like I'm
not on your game.
Don't mean to seem
disrespectful.
Hey, girl.
Hey.
You can really sing.
Thanks.
Bam, what do you think?
I love it.
Order, like, 20 of them.
Put them all over campus.
Shove it down Delta's throat.
You got it.
Hey, that reminds me.
I need your date's name for
the foam formal by Friday.
Just a security formality.
Oh, right.
You do have a date?
Yeah, what, are you kidding?
Tons.
Not really.
None.
You aren't shy, are you?
No.
But apparently, I'm
contagious, remember?
And I kind of
worry about any guy
that's willing to date
herpes poster girl.
Right, I never
thought about that.
I'll tell you what.
Don't give it another thought.
I'll handle it.
Really?
Absolutely.
One Prince Charming coming up.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCKING]
Ugh.
Whoops, I think you
accidentally closed the door
on my face.
Hello, Beau.
Hello, Ms. Parker.
You look lovely this evening.
Yes, well, unfortunately, I
am developing a bit of a cough.
[COUGHS]
Wow, faking sick.
That really gets you, huh?
That's a good sign.
What, your impending homicide?
I was thinking more like
unbearable sexual tension.
I take it Heather didn't fill
you in on this arrangement.
Not so much.
Look, you've got
a party to go to.
And I'm just guessing, but I'm
probably the only guy who's
come to your door tonight.
[SIGHS] Fine.
And thank you.
But I don't have to like this.
You ever been to
a foam party before?
No.
No, what-- what
exactly am I in for?
[MUSIC - HAWK NELSON, "YOU HAVE
WHAT I NEED"]
[CHEERING]
(SINGING) I've tried my
best to hear out the masses.
I've heard it all
from A to Z. I've
read it all, been to
all of the classes.
And still I'm trying, but I
just can't see through the smoke
and I don't want
it, this confusion.
I don't want a false solution.
Give me something to hold onto.
I want what you have 'cause
you have what I need.
You have what I need.
Oh my gosh.
Exactly.
[PHONE VIBRATING]
Come on, let's go.
(SINGING) But all I
got was empty fists.
Can you hear me?
I don't want it, this confusion.
I don't want a false solution.
Give me something to hold onto.
I want what you have 'cause
you have what I need.
[MUSIC - GIRLS LOVE SHOES, "COME
GET YOUR RIDE"]
(SINGING) Come get your ride.
Come get your ride.
Come see how fun it
could be to be alive.
Come inside and
baby, get your ride.
Get it started!
You give it.
The feeling don't start
keep on 'cause you really
got me reeling.
You know, I am starting
to believe my mom.
These might just be the
best years of my life.
Totally.
I gotta say, this kicks
the ass of any formal I've
ever been to.
Well, everyone knows that
Kappa girls are just more damn
fun.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, yeah!
Woo hoo!
Want to go for a swim?
Not exactly what
I had in mind.
Careful.
This goes deep before
you swim in it.
I'll avoid the
deep end, I promise.
You know, you're-- you're
hard to get a read on.
At that first party, you were
an ass, and here, you're--
Charming, roguish, debonair?
You're less ass-y.
I'll take less ass-y.
I just realized something.
We were at a Beta
party when we met.
You're a Beta.
Yep, me Beta, you Kappa.
Your point?
I thought your fraternity made
up some rule that you couldn't
be seen with me.
Or what, the fraternity
police is going to bust me?
Are you serious?
I know Gwen's putting
you through hell,
but I don't need anyone's
permission to like you.
OK?
Yeah, did I overplay that?
No No, it was hot.
Let's go get some air.
[RETCHING]
Ah, that's gotta be a
health code violation.
Ooh.
[GURGLING]
Let's go, come on.
You OK?
Are you OK?
What the hell's going on?
There's gotta be something
wrong with the food.
What did you eat?
What didn't I eat?
Oh my god.
What's up, ladies?
Oh, hey, tonight's your
big formal, isn't it?
How's that working out for you?
Toodles, bitches.
Bye.
Woo!
OK, they want war?
They got it.
Katie, you in?
Yeah, try and stop me.
We've put up with
Delta long enough.
It's time to take Gwen down.
Yeah.
And there's only
one way to do it.
We've got to steal
the Tri-Crown.
Yeah.
Um, isn't that illegal?
She doesn't mean
literally, Seana.
God.
Katie, you know Gwen
better than we do.
What do you think?
I think I love it.
Gwen needs this.
Winning Tri-Crown, it's her
only shot at becoming president.
Hello, random
voice of reason here.
Steal it how?
It's not like we've been
letting them win it on purpose.
No, but we never wanted
it as badly as they did.
We just wanted to have fun.
Right, well, now
it's more than that.
This is more than just
winning the Tri-Crown.
It's about taking it from Delta.
OK, if we're going
to do this, then we've
got to nail them in the
three legs of the crown--
intramural, trivia,
and talent show.
Katie would kill at
the talent portion.
We've all heard her sing.
Definitely.
Um, OK, sure.
And I can cover volleyball.
We could totally do this, girls.
Everybody in favor?
ALL: Yes!
All right.
Come on!
[MUSIC - SAMANTHA JADE, "GET
AWAY"]
[GIGGLING]
ALL: Go, Kappa!
Nice!
Oh!
- I got it, oh!
- Bump it!
Ah!
OK, here!
(SINGING) Seize the
moment, attempted fates.
Step up the cold dark into you.
So many boys who want to holler
at me, better make your move.
(SINGING) Tick
tock, tick, tock.
(SINGING) You're on the clock.
(SINGING) Say it, 'fess up.
Come on, now what?
(SINGING) What makes you
think that you're so special?
(SINGING) Flaunting
like I'm not on your game.
(SINGING) Don't mean
to seem disrespectful.
But--
(SINGING) I don't wait.
Woo!
No.
OK.
All right.
Good.
Right, um, OK, but
maybe all together?
And maybe a little
less jazz handsy.
(SINGING) What makes you
think that you're so special?
Flaunting like I'm
not on your game.
Don't mean to seem
disrespectful,
but I don't wait.
All right, ladies.
That's it.
Looking good.
All right.
Got it!
Set it up!
Yeah, just like
that everytime, OK.
You're on fire.
All right.
OK, now bump it.
Nice!
Delta!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
[SCREAMING]
Woo!
[LAUGHTER]
Woo-woo!
ALL: Go Kappa!
OK, I need some advice.
Hmm.
I'm-- I'm dreading
going home this weekend.
Who dreads Thanksgiving?
Maybe turkeys.
Well, Sara and her
mom join us every year.
And apparently, this
one is no exception.
Even though you
guys are fighting?
Well, her mom is like the
sweetest woman in the world.
Probably thinks all we
need is some pumpkin pie
and stuffing to magically
be friends again.
Have you even talked to
Sara since the foam party?
No.
I'm so angry, I don't
even know what I'd say.
But it's going to be so awkward.
Just eat enough turkey
for a tryptophan coma
and sleep through it.
Look, you're going to have
more fun than me anyways.
I mean, I'm going to be
stuck here on campus.
You're not going home?
No.
I never do.
It's too expensive,
and, you know,
plus, it's just me and my mom.
Well, why don't you
come home with me?
It's perfect.
You can diffuse the tension.
And before you read too much
into this, this is not--
this is not me taking
you home to meet
the parents or anything.
I mean, yeah, they'll be there
and you'll say hi and talk
to them and stuff, but, uh.
I'd really like that.
Beau, I am so glad you
came for Thanksgiving.
Here we are!
Oh, Lutie, you've
outdone yourself.
Thank you.
Who wants a leg?
Well, wait.
We can't forget tradition, Will.
Do you guys beat each
other for Thanksgiving?
It's a prayer stick.
We all pass it around and
say what we're thankful for.
Sara and I made it at camp.
And in light of
recent events, I
think the girls should go first.
Katie.
No, I'm--
I'm not really feeling it.
[SCOFFS]
OK, I changed my mind.
Here's one.
I am thankful that this
food hasn't been messed with
and that I'm not one of
the cowards who sabotaged
our formal.
- Katie.
No, that's not what I meant.
Wow.
OK, my turn.
I'm thankful I've grown
up since high school
and know how to let things go.
BEAU: I'm thankful--
Well, I'm thankful that--
--for this turkey, this
lovely, juicy turkey.
I'm thankful that I can still
look at myself in the mirror.
I'm thankful for
all my new friends.
Yeah, well, you know what?
I'm thankful that I don't
have my head stuck up--
Ooh, ooh, all right.
There's a lot of
thanks in this room.
Thanks.
Yes, well, let's eat.
I like that Beau.
He seemed sweet.
Did you want to talk about Sara?
Not really, but thanks.
How's your
Tri-Crown prep going?
Are you girls ready for
the competition next week?
Mom, are you digging
for inside information?
Maybe a little.
[CHUCKLES]
What are you working on?
We've decided to
put an alumni photo
on the backflap of our
charity cookbook this year.
So I'm just sifting
through some old ones.
You've been really working
your butt off on this.
Yeah.
I just hope the
alumni appreciate it.
Can I see?
Oh, please, yes.
KATIE: You know,
it's really great
that you made so
many true friends.
I can only hope to be as
close to my sorority sisters
in 20 years as you are to yours.
I think I have more
photos in the garage.
I'll be back.
[APPLAUSE]
1, 2, 3.
ALL: Delta!
Ready to be humiliated?
Can you teach me?
I've had a little more practice.
[WHISTLE]
[CHEERING]
It's right, girls!
We should go for
lunch after this.
I feel like I haven't
seen you in ages.
What are you talking about?
We see each other at meetings
practically every week.
Outside of that.
I worry that this
Katie and Gwen issue
is impacting our friendship.
Isn't it?
All right, girls!
Kill those Kappas!
Woo!
[WHISTLE]
Come on, girls!
Gwen!
Come on, Delta, kick it up!
Woo!
[CROWD JEERING]
[WHISTLE]
What?
Wow.
Play a little rougher than in
our years, don't you think?
Well, that's what
makes you winners.
[CHEERING]
All right!
Good one, Katie!
Ref!
Sara, sub in for Cass.
Cassidy, come on.
Go on, get in there.
Uh, come on, that's just low.
KATIE: You've got
to be kidding me.
This is all I need.
Get in the game, Katie!
Woo!
Yeah!
What's the matter?
You can't look me in the eye?
Please, why don't you
just get over yourself?
I tried warning you.
I had nothing to do
with ruining your party.
KATIE: You could
have told me sooner.
SARA: Hey, my
conscience is clear.
I'll bet.
What, you were too busy doing
everyone's homework that night?
Deltas help each others study.
Who cares?
You just can't stand that I
have new friends, can you?
Down, now!
Trust me, those aren't
the kind of friends I want.
Woo!
Woohoo!
Go Delta!
Woo!
Go Delta.
Sara.
Sara, they aren't your friends.
OK, they only picked
you because of me.
You're lying because
you're jealous.
It's pathetic.
No, I heard Gwen say it
that night in the bathroom.
And that's why I quit to protect
you, you ungrateful spaz.
You're right.
You are a great friend, as long
as I stayed in your shadow.
Sara, look, I've known
you since kindergarten.
OK, you-- you're the funniest
person I've ever met.
You're freakishly smart.
You can't dance for crap.
And you quote Monty
Python like it's your job.
You know, do they know this?
Have they even tried to
get to know you at all?
Sara, you are a lot of things,
but you're not a follower.
At least, you never used to be.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(SINGING) You're going
to cry in to the--
BEAU: What is this?
KATIE: These are my mom's
Tri-Crown competition tapes.
You know, when
you called me here
for an evening of stolen goods,
I was expecting something more
exciting.
Sorry to disappoint.
So what exactly
are we looking for?
Inspiration.
We completely blew
the volleyball game,
so now we have to win the other
two events to win Tri-Crown.
Heather's leaving the
musical show up to me,
and I'm totally blocking.
BEAU: And what's
the theme this year?
Looking back moving forward.
Oh, catchy.
I know, right?
[CULTURAL MUSIC]
Look, it's the new
Kappas on the block.
[CHUCKLING]
[BAND MUSIC]
And that's a whole lot of
Lycra all in one place.
Whoa, wait, hang on.
[MUSIC - "AIN'T NO MOUNTAIN HIGH
ENOUGH"]
I know her.
That one on the right,
isn't that your mom?
LUTIE (ON TV): (SINGING)
Ain't no mountain high.
That's my mom.
LUTIE (ON TV): (SINGING)
Ain't no mountain low,
ain't no river--
Oh, she was pretty.
LUTIE (ON TV): (SINGING)
--wide enough, baby.
If you need me, call me
no matter where you are,
no matter how far.
Don't worry, baby.
Just call my name.
Ah!
Match.
So anyway, Sissy's got a
3,000 square foot dance studio
for the girls to practice in.
Mary Ellen's got a line on
a New York choreographer
who's going to help
them with their routine.
We are set!
Yay, wow.
That's wonderful.
Well, we might need the edge.
Looks like Kappa is going to
be a real contender this year,
thanks to Katie's inside
information maybe.
What's that supposed to mean?
Dana has a point.
Maybe President-elect isn't
the right position for you--
right now, until
this all blows over.
Why not?
One could question
where your loyalty lies.
Are you saying--
what are you saying?
Lutie, don't
take it personally.
It's just with all
this distasteful drama
with your daughter, it
just doesn't look right.
Look right to whom?
We're the alumni.
You're the only people
who could possibly
have a problem with it.
Well, all right then.
We have a problem with it.
We had a vote, Lutie.
Dana will be taking
over as President-elect.
Yeah.
We, of course,
still want you to stay
part of our regular membership.
Of course.
For sure.
Lutie.
Lutie Parker, that is
not Delta behavior!
I'm not here to fight.
I just want to give you this.
What is it?
Delta stole the questions
to the quiz challenge.
You deserve a fair
fight against them.
Them?
Not us?
Not anymore.
I quit Delta.
Now you quit?
I only joined them because
you told me I couldn't.
And you said we weren't
friends anymore,
and I had nowhere else to go.
Well, according to what you
said at the game the other day,
being my best friend was
no great thrill anyway.
It was great.
It was just humbling.
Come on, Katie, every party
I got into, every double date
only happened because of you.
You're so much
better with people.
It was easier to
follow your lead.
Even if that is
true, what does that
have to do with Delta?
It was a chance to see
if there's more to me
than your sidekick, to find
out who Sara is without Katie.
And now she's kind of a douche.
Seriously, man!
I mean lame.
Blah blah, Delta.
Blah blah, Gwen's so cool.
Ugh.
I miss the old me.
I miss the old you, too, Sara.
Let's be friends again.
You know I miss you.
But you also really
screwed me over.
Come on.
I've had to live
with Gwen for months.
Isn't that punishment enough?
Close.
OK, just do one
more thing for me.
Give the judges an
anonymous tip and tell them
that the questions
were compromised.
Wow.
That's pretty noble.
Not really.
I just want Gwen to
know that we beat Delta
because we're better,
not just better cheaters.
Done.
Now if you'll excuse me, I
have an ass load more studying
to do.
Sara, you were right.
I did take you for granted.
I was an idiot.
Hey, so Sara and I finally
buried the hatchet.
You know, it's really weird
imagery for forgiveness.
Well, that's good.
I knew you would.
Old friends are
the best friends.
Now, why don't you go
get yourself some snacks?
Preferably healthy.
Oh, yeah, I think that
would have been perfect.
Oh!
Fancy running into you.
We were just picking up some
things for the Delta girls.
Listen, Lutie, I hope there
aren't any hard feelings still.
Barely any feelings at all.
I understand how
you'd be frustrated.
I'd be frustrated, too.
Then, again, some of us know
how to control our daughters.
Or how to raise them
in the first place.
Yes, Summer, I
know your daughter.
How proud you must be.
[THUNDER]
All right, what's wrong now?
I heard Summer's trash talk.
Would it have killed
you to defend us?
Oh, so we're an
us now, are we?
I know you're angry, but I
thought you'd at least defend
me in public.
With what magic wand am I
supposed to protect you, Katie?
Huh?
Tell me.
How am I supposed to
cover for your mistakes?
I'm not even on the
alumni board anymore.
What are you talking about?
Mom.
I've been asked to step
down from President-elect.
Wait, they fired you?
They tried.
I quit before they could.
But that's ridiculous.
But you helped
start that chapter.
Can they even do that?
What do you think I've
been trying to tell you?
You think Gwen and her
friends play mind games?
These women have had
20 years to perfect it.
Well, I mean, obviously,
they're just punishing you
for what I did.
Is there something
that I can do to--
Oh, I think
you've done enough.
Please don't tell your father.
I think I've had enough
humiliation for one day.
[APPLAUSE]
If everyone could settle
down, we could get started.
I hope you were right about
returning those questions.
All right, first question.
Oh, this is from the
psychology department.
Freud qualified the unconscious
into these three parts, the id,
the ego, and--
[BUZZ]
The Parthenon.
[CLAPPING]
[LAUGHTER]
Incorrect.
Uh, Kappa, you buzzed in next.
Your answer?
That would be super ego.
Correct.
Yeah!
[APPLAUSE]
I'm surprised you missed
an ego question, Gwen.
Game on.
[POP ROCK MUSIC]
[BUZZING]
Micro and macro economics.
Indeed.
[APPLAUSE]
[BUZZ]
[CHEERING]
That would be the
French Revolution.
Absolutely right.
[CHEERING]
[BUZZ]
[BUZZING]
BOTH: [INAUDIBLE]
Delta buzzed first,
and they are correct.
Yes!
[APPLAUSE]
Well, we have a tie
so this last question
will be for the win.
Well, this is interesting.
We are going to mix it up
a little with some Tate
University history.
Ladies, which
Greek house started
the Tri-Crown competition?
Delta's first.
That would be Delta.
I'm sorry, but
that is not correct.
Over to Kappa.
According to my mother, it
was started by the school's
first five fraternities.
Correct.
Kappa wins.
[APPLAUSE]
There are no excuses.
Listen to me, Gwen.
That performance
was unacceptable.
Did you prepare for this at all?
Crying is not going to
get it done, young lady.
I'm not crying.
I'm tired.
Well, I am tired
of the excuses.
You need to pick it up a
whole bunch of damn notches,
sweetheart, because when you
look a fool, I look a fool.
OK, fine.
I get it.
Are we winners
or losers, Gwen?
Hmm?
Look at me.
Are we winners or losers?
We're winners.
Good girl.
Now give Mama a hug.
Mm-mm.
Wow.
It's harsh.
Mind your own business.
Look, I'm just saying.
I still can't stand you,
but you didn't deserve that.
Whatever, your
mom is just as bad.
Actually, she's not
anything like your mom.
You're right.
Your mom didn't even
care enough to come.
We used to be able to
talk about everything.
I don't know when that stopped.
Puberty?
[CHUCKLING]
I'm really sorry, mom.
All my drama getting dumped on
you, I didn't mean for that.
Oh, sweetie.
It's me who should
apologize to you.
You were just expecting me and
Summer to behave like adults.
The truth is, seeing you
here, being back on campus,
it reminds me of how I felt back
then, how much potential I had,
and 24 years later, how
little I have to show for it,
except for you and Delta house.
Oh, come on.
You don't really feel
that way, do you?
Oh, honey, I
got married at 23.
I have loved my
life, but there's
something they forget to tell
domestic goddesses like myself.
What?
Well, that when you stay
home, raise your children,
keep your house, your
family will love you.
They will appreciate you.
They just might not respect you.
Is that how you
think I look at you?
I know what people think
of sororities these days.
I suppose I always hoped
that one day, when you came
to Delta, that you at
least would understand,
that you'd be proud of me, too.
I do understand.
Now.
[CHUCKLES]
So what can I do to
make this up to you?
Honestly, grind
Delta into the ground.
Steal the Tri-Crown.
What?
Trust me, the humility
will be good for them.
OK, I'll see what I can do.
And for the record, I have never
been anything but proud of you.
[APPLAUSE]
Thank you, Gammas.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
here with their interpretation
of this year's theme,
Looking Back Moving Forward,
Delta Beta Theta.
[APPLAUSE]
[MUSIC - JESSIE JAMES DECKER,
"BLUE JEANS"]
(SINGING) I step
in my blue jeans,
homewreck in my blue jeans.
I got it from momma
so I'm blessed in my.
I sing in my blue jeans,
bling in my blue jeans.
When I hit the country
club, I get in free with my.
Oh, I'm like whoa.
I got a fresh new pair.
They're so dope.
Oh, I'm like whoa.
I got a fresh new pair.
They're so dope.
I got a brand new
pair of blue jeans.
Me and my posse looking
fresh and so clean.
What are they doing?
That's like little
whores on the prairie.
[LAUGHTER]
(SINGING) Giving my sugar
one sweet performance.
Hey, hey.
Don't matter what
you're wearing.
Hey, hey.
It's about the way you wear it.
Don't what you're wearing.
Hey, hey.
It's about the way you wear it.
Y'all ready for this?
Hey.
When I bend and snap, when I
step and clap, everybody else,
who, who is that?
When I'm out in public,
everybody loves 'em.
I know what they're wondering.
When I bend and snap, when I
step and clap, everybody asks,
who, who is that?
When I'm out in public,
everybody loves 'em.
I know what they're wondering.
[CHEERING]
MC: Let's hear it
for the Deltas.
Follow that.
Bring it, blondie.
Leave it on the stage, ladies.
You're up, Kappa.
[ZIPPING]
[MUSIC - "AIN'T NO MOUNTAIN HIGH
ENOUGH"]
(SINGING) Ain't no mountain
high, ain't no valley low,
ain't no river
wide enough, baby.
If you need me, call me,
no matter where you are,
no matter how far.
Don't worry, baby.
Just call my name.
I'll be there in a hurry.
You don't have to worry.
'Cause, baby, there ain't
no mountain high enough.
Ain't no valley low enough.
Ain't no river wide enough to
keep me from getting to you,
babe.
Remember the day I set you free.
I told you, you could
always count on me.
And from that day
on, I made a vow.
I'll be there when you
want me some way, somehow.
'Cause, baby, there ain't
no mountain high enough,
ain't no valley low enough.
Ain't no river wide enough to
keep me from getting to you,
babe.
(SINGING) Oh, no, darling.
No wind, no rain.
(SINGING) Or winters
cold can stop me, baby.
(SINGING) No, no, baby.
(SINGING) 'Cause
you are my goal.
(SINGING) If you're
ever in trouble,
I'll be there on the double.
Just send for me.
(SINGING) Oh, baby.
My love is alive way down in
my heart, although we are miles
apart.
And if you ever
need a helping hand,
I'll be there on the double,
just as fast as I can.
'Cause, baby, there ain't
no mountain high enough,
ain't no valley low enough,
ain't no river wide enough
to keep me from
getting to you, babe.
Ain't no mountain high enough.
Ain't no valley low enough.
Ain't no river wide enough to
keep me from getting to you,
babe.
To keep me from getting to you!
[CHEERING]
On behalf of the judges,
it is my honor to present
the Tri-Crown trophy
to Kappa Theta Psi.
[APPLAUSE]
Gwendolyn, sweetheart.
Sweetheart, don't you worry.
We can fix this.
They cannot use a
Delta in their song.
I am sure of it.
There's got to be some--
Mom, let it go.
Someone once told me.
Don't get me wrong.
I still can't stand you.
But you deserved what you got.
[MUSIC - MARJORIE MAYE, "THIS IS
MY STORY"]
(SINGING) No time for cynical
when life's so beautiful.
Glass of empty seems so full
when you look at it that way.
The world can try and bring
me down, but I want to fly.
This is my story.
This is my life.
I don't know the ending
but it's mine to write.
This is my story.
This is my chance.
I'm not going to sit it out.
I'm going to dance.
There's my girl.
Hey.
I was just looking for you guys.
You were amazing.
Thank you.
Hey, sir.
Good to see you again.
Did you like it?
Oh, honey.
I loved it.
Aw.
KAPPA GIRL 1: Katie!
KAPPA GIRL 2: There she is!
KAPPA GIRLS: Katie!
Can you believe we
got the Tri-Crown?
Just one second, ladies.
One for the record.
Say "Greek."
Greek!
(SINGING) This is my story.
This is my life.
Don't know the ending,
but it's mine to write.
[MUSIC PLAYING]