[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[thunder booming]
[glass clinking]
- [snoring]
[coughing]
- Oh.
Here, Uncle Randolph. Let me.
- No. Preston, get it for me.
[coughs]
Thank you, Pres.
It's a fine thing to trust your lawyer
more than your own niece and nephew.
- Know any good jokes? We could probably end this right now.
- Behave yourself, brother dear.
- Olivia, Bernie...
- The name is Bernard, Uncle Randolph.
- You want my money, don't you?
[thunder booming]
Get your keisters over here.
- Here we are. - I've got eyes, girl.
You're your father's kid, all right.
Little drama queen he was, and god rest his soul.
You know exactly how much money I've got, right?
- 3.24 billion in cash and liquid assets.
- I expected you'd know it right down to the last penny.
- Is there anything that we might do
to ease your suffering?
- Yes, there is, girl. Come closer, both of you.
I'm not going to leave you one thin dime.
[thunder booming]
Tell 'em, Pres.
- Come with me.
- What's this nonsense about our not
getting any inheritance?
- We're his last living relatives.
Who else could he give it to?
- His only other living relative.
- Who? - Who?
- You both know about Mr. St. John's
only son dying in a car accident 12 years ago.
- Of course we know about that. Cut to the chase.
- Even though he hadn't spoken with his father in over a year,
he still was sole beneficiary to Randolph St. John's estate,
until the accident, of course.
- All right. Forget the chase. Cut to the credits.
- Patience, Bernard. Go on, Mr. Preston.
- Well, it seems the young man left behind a widow
and a young son,
who Mr. St. John had never seen.
Edward, I believe, was the child's name.
- I heard that the baby had died.
- There's no death records for an infant
named Edward St. John. He's out there somewhere,
and I've hired a private investigator to find him.
Let's see. By now, he should be about 12 years old.
- In the meantime, we're supposed
to cool our heels and wait?
- This search of yours could take months, years.
- You'll be pleased to know that Mr. St. John has given me
until his passing away to find little Edward.
Who knows? You may be lucky yet.
However, with the computer-assisted tracking,
we're likely to find the boy by this time next week,
or maybe even sooner,
at which time all of this goes to him.
- You're enjoying this. Aren't you?
- Immensely.
You might think about packing your things now.
Avoid the rush.
[thunder booming]
- I knew this would come back to haunt us one day.
You were supposed to take care of that little brat.
- I cut the brake lines to the car.
- Keep your voice down.
- I arranged the accident. How could I have known his wife
would suspect foul play and go into hiding?
She knew we would come after that baby.
- What's done is done.
We need to do some damage control.
- If that investigator finds that little brat,
we're done for.
- Perhaps not, brother. Accidents happen all the time.
You could say that they run in family.
- Dear sister, I love the way you think.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[thunder booms]
[bell tolling]
[birds chirping]
- New Horizons Orphanage has been around for 65 years.
We have placed over 1,000 children.
Oh, and isn't it a lovely atmosphere?
The children love to come around the fountain.
Of course, they all know how to swim.
Oh, they're just beautiful.
It's so nice you've taking an interest
in one of our older kids.
Normally people only want the babies.
- William and I have discussed this at length,
and we both agree that this is the way
to go, haven't we, William?
- Yes, dear. - None of this 2:00 a.m.
feeding and diaper changing nonsense of us.
Isn't that right, dear?
- Yes, dear.
- Then I have just the young man for you.
He's one of our best and very clever.
His name is Edward.
He's quite advanced for his years.
- He's not what you call a problem child, is he?
- Judge for yourself.
Eddie, it's Ms. Mason.
- Come on in.
- After you.
- Hello, Edward. I'm your mummy.
- Where you are and await arrest.
- Intruder, stay where you are and await arrest.
- Ahh!
Ohh!
- Eddie, you little brat.
Oh, get your hands off me.
- Stay where you are.
- You--you are... I just had my hair done,
you little monster.
Oh, you blew it big-time, buddy.
We were going to adopt you, but not now, mister.
- Oh, gee. What rotten luck. - Is--
is that a smirk, William?
- I wouldn't know what that was, dear.
- I'm terribly sorry about all this, Mrs. Robbins.
Perhaps one of our other children--
- "Other children"? If that little demon spawn
is any indication of the horrors in this place, I--
come along, William.
We're going to adopt a puppy dog.
- Yes. - You are laughing at me.
Aren't you?
- With you, dear, with you. - Oh, shut up.
- Sorry about that.
It's been a pretty rough week. She's been a little on edge.
- And you, I'm sending you my cleaning bill.
Come along.
- [laughs]
- That makes four sets of prospective parents
that you've scared off in the past six months.
- Yep, four for four.
- Why can't you direct your intelligence in other,
more constructive ways?
One would think you don't want to be adopted.
- I don't. I'm waiting for my mom.
She's coming back for me. I know she will.
- Eddie, it's been 12 years
since your mother dropped you off here.
We haven't heard one word from her in all that time.
- I don't care. She's coming back for me.
- Eddie, you can't stay here forever.
Now that you're 12,
there are a new set of state guidelines to follow.
You've had four chances at adoption,
and the government requires
that we place you in foster care.
- Foster care? No way, please.
- And after that, you'll have to go
the youth farm until you're 18.
- But I want to stay here. - My hands are tied.
It's the law.
I wish things could have been better for you.
I really am sorry, Eddie.
- Yeah, me too.
- Hold that, Josh.
Hand me that test tube.
Ah, finally.
- Karl, Josh, dinner.
- After all these weeks, after all this trial and error,
it's ready. You want to try it first?
- Go ahead. You first.
- You sure?
- Guys, second time I've called you for dinner.
- Honey, honey, we have done it.
We've created the ultimate vitamin drink
you only have to take once a month.
It's time-released, you see, guaranteed to give you
a daily kick in the pants. Care for a sip?
- Oh, gee. You know, after what happened the last time
I accidentally drank one of your experiments,
I don't think so.
- Well, they say in school that if something tastes bad,
it has to be good for you.
- This stuff must be a wonder-worker.
- Come on, boys. Dinner is ready.
- In business news, billionaire industrialist
Randolph St. John still clings to life in the desperate hope
of being reunited with the grandson he's never known.
- What?
- Albert Preston, the St. John family attorney,
has been charged with the task of locating the young man,
who would now be 12 years old.
Anyone with any information is asked to contact Mr. Preston.
Further proof will be required
if you want to get rich off this little guy.
In other news, pleas for clemency continue for...
- I never stopped loving you, Eddie.
I just I can get to you before your cousins do.
- I tell you, I can't wait to get that formula
down to the lab on Monday morning.
The directors at Applied Technology
are going to flip their lids
once I get the bugs worked out, naturally.
- Josh, eat your food. Don't play with it.
[telephone rings]
Excuse me.
Hello?
- Mrs. Griffin, this is Deborah Mason
at the New Horizons Orphanage. Have you got a moment?
- Oh, Ms. Mason, hi.
Well, actually, we were just sitting down to dinner,
but sure. I have a couple of seconds.
Is this about another foster child?
- Yes. Your family did such a wonderful job
with the last two young people that I placed in your care
that I was wondering,
would you be so inclined to take on a new foster child?
- Oh, well-- - His name is Eddie Brown,
and this orphanage is the only home he's ever had.
I know that your family could give him the love and attention
he needs to make the proper adjustments.
Would you be interested?
- Well, I'd have to discuss it with my family.
You know, we had such a good time with those other two kids.
I'm so glad they found a good home.
- I know you'll have as good a time with Eddie.
He is 12 years old and very bright.
I think he'd make an excellent little companion for Josh.
- Well, we'll talk about it tonight,
and I'll call you in the morning.
- That will be fine.
Looking forward to hearing from you. Goodbye.
- Bye-bye.
- Was that Ms. Mason from the orphanage?
We haven't heard from her in a while.
- Yeah. She has another foster child for us,
a 12-year-old boy.
- Is he going to stay with us?
- How do you feel about that, Honey?
Honey?
[mystical music]
♪ ♪
Honey? Honey?
- Mom, it's okay, really. - Okay.
Now, now, just breathe deep, Laura.
All right. Come on. Breathe with me. Come on.
Breathe. Yeah, oh, that's better.
- Sit down.
You know, at least it doesn't happen as often as it used to.
- It's been two years. The invisibility formula
should have been out of your system long before now.
None of the test I've run on you can explain it.
- It's okay, honey.
You know, as long as I just don't get too excited
and I do my meditating and my yoga, I'll be fine.
- Maybe we should tell Ms. Mason
to find another foster family for this boy.
- No. I don't want to do that.
I don't want this to get in the way of helping that boy.
- Are you sure, Laura? - Yeah, let's do it.
Josh, what do you think?
- It's cool with me if it's cool we everybody else.
- Good. I'll call her first thing in the morning.
- Okay.
[thunder booming]
- I'm very sorry, but he did go peacefully in his sleep
if that's any consolation.
- Oh, I know you did your best, Doctor.
- Oh, yes.
Thank you for coming out on such a gloomy night.
- I'll send you my bill. - Yes, please do.
[laughs]
- We're rich!
- No more, "Livi, get me my pills."
- No more, "Bernie, prop my pillow."
- Oh, we're rich.
- Drowning in a sea of cash.
- Summers in Madrid...
- Winters in the South of France...
- Thanks to Uncle Randolph. - That crotchety old coot.
- I thought he'd never kick the bucket.
- Yes. - You might want to wait
to dance on his grave until it's actually been dug.
- Who let you in?
- The doctor, as he was leaving.
- What do you want, Preston?
- This.
- Oh, no. - It's not possible.
- Sorry to be a spoilsport, but there he is, Edward Brown,
or should I say Edward St. John,
the sole heir to the family fortune.
His mother must have changed his name in fear
that something bad might happen to him
if his true identity or whereabouts were known.
- Imagine that. - Where is he?
- Not far. He could be here as early as tomorrow.
- But you arrive too late.
Under the conditions of the will,
you were to find him before the old codger--
before Uncle Randolph passed away.
- So you're a day late and a dollar short,
Preston, old buddy.
- Oh, I may have arrived here after the fact,
but the boy was located earlier this evening,
just in time, a matter of fact. Once again, sorry.
The boy will be here tomorrow, and as executor of the estate,
I'll be making sure that his transition here
is a smooth one,
which means having the two of you
packed and out of here by noon tomorrow,
which shouldn't be too difficult
considering all you'll have are the clothes on your back.
Sleep well.
- Oh, Mr. Preston. - Yes?
- Didn't you say that you were going
to look after the boy's care?
- That's right.
- But aren't we his only living relatives?
- And if we petition the court,
wouldn't they grant us sole custody of the child?
- And wouldn't they wonder why you had shut us out,
perhaps to control the family fortune for yourself?
- You are sly devils. I'll give you that.
All right. You've won for now, but I'm not letting this rest.
- Such diligence.
- Ever the consummate professional.
- Now get out, and draw up those adoption papers.
- We must do this quick. We must get rid
of the little brat with one very convenient...
- But very natural-looking... - Accident.
- Don't boys always climb trees and then fall out of them?
- They also stick their fingers into light sockets.
- Or they trip over staircase railings.
- Yes, leaving us as the sole owners of the estate.
[thunder booming]
Welcome to the family, little Edward.
- Hmm. Too bad you're not going to survive the experience.
[thunder booming]
- This is it.
Come on. I'll introduce you to the Griffins.
[doorbell rings]
- Oh, Ms. Mason, hi. - Hi.
It was wonderful getting your call this morning.
This is Eddie Brown. I told him all about you and your family.
- Oh, terrific. Hi, Eddie. Nice to meet you.
- A pleasure to meet you too, Mrs. Griffin.
- Well, a very well-mannered young man.
- Mm-hmm.
- Josh, Karl. - What do you think, Eddie?
- It's a cool house. - Guys, this is Eddie Brown.
- Put her there, pal. I'm Karl Griffin.
- And this is our son, Josh. - Hey, dude.
- Hey.
- Well, it looks like it's time for me
to let you all get acquainted. You okay with everything?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- I'll be checking in every now and again
to see how things are going. Take care.
- Thank you. - Thanks. I appreciate it.
- So, Eddie, you're going to be sharing a room with Josh.
You want to show it to him? - Yeah, sure. Come on.
Hey, you like "Death Race" comics?
- Yeah, cool.
- Cool. I've got every issue. You want to see them?
- Sure.
- Oh, I think this is going to work out just fine.
- [chuckles]
- All right. Now, this up here is my room.
- It's on the second floor? That's awesome.
- Yeah, man. It is the second floor.
So you like horror movies? - Heck yeah.
Have you ever seen, "Lizard Brides From Saturn"?
- Never heard of it.
- It's, like, the coolest of the all-time horror flicks.
They show it sometimes on the weekends.
- Well, maybe I can get my mom to take us
to the Olen Ray Theater this weekend.
- Hey, check this out. - Play Slime.
My mom told me that if she ever caught me
with this stuff again, she'd ground me for a week.
- Well, if parents hate it,
we got to love it. - Yeah.
I can tell you and I are going to get along just fine.
But there is something I ought to tell you.
Weird things happen here sometimes.
- Weird things? Like what?
- Well, like, sometimes when my mom gets a little stressed,
and her blood pressure goes up, she turns invisible.
- Invisible? No way. - Big way.
You see, my dad is a scientist, and it all started
when he invented this invisibility formula.
- Yes.
It looks good. Huh, Cosmo?
[dog whining]
You want to help Daddy with an invention?
- First he tested it on the dog.
- That's right, Cosmo.
[dog barks]
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow. Wow.
- Then I tested it on my friend's iguana,
because I wanted to use the formula
to sneak out of the house when I was grounded.
And then I wanted to use the formula later,
so I hid it in a soda bottle.
Then my mom found the soda bottle,
Well, you can guess what happened next.
- [gasps]
What?
Oh, my gosh.
- But she seems okay now.
- Well, that's because my dad invented an antidote,
and she returned to normal-- well, pretty normal anyway.
- Gross.
- Look at that. Amazing.
- But it doesn't happen as often as it used to.
She just fades in and out every now and then.
- Hey, is there any more of that stuff hanging around?
- Nope. Government came and took it, and that was that.
- We could have had some major fun with that stuff.
- Yeah, right.
[crickets chirping]
- He seems like a nice kid.
- Yeah, he and Josh have sure hit it off.
I think he's going to be a good friend for him.
All those years in the orphanage
must have been so hard on him.
I just--I want to make it up to him, you know?
- Have I told you lately how much I love you?
- Better be careful talking up a woman like that.
It could get you into more trouble than you bargained for.
- Oh, Mrs. Griffin, I thrive on trouble.
- [laughs]
You just remember that until I get back.
I'm going to say good night to the boys.
- Hurry.
- Whew.
- Okay, guys, bedtime.
Cute.
So, Eddie,
I'm never going to take the place of your real mom.
I'm not even going to try. I just want you to know
you have a home here for as long as you want it.
- I like it here, Mrs. Griffin. You guys are so cool.
- Yeah. Well, you're pretty cool yourself, kiddo.
I think we better take this off to go to sleep.
What do you say? Okay, bedtime, both of you.
Just because it's summer vacation,
there's still plenty to do around here. Good night.
- Good night, Mom. - Good night.
[thunder booming]
- Bernard. Bernard.
Oh, there you are. I need you to show me
how to work the sound effects system.
- I can't go through with it, Olivia.
I can't send this poor child to a cold, early grave.
Goodbye, dear sister. Goodbye.
- [gasps]
[shrieks]
- Mu-ha-ha-ha-ha. Boog-a, boog-a, boog-a.
- Ahh! Ahh! Ahh!
- Boo.
- Uhh...
- [laughs]
- You nearly scared me half to death.
- Well, then I only did half a job. Didn't I?
- Save the comedy for later.
[wind whistling]
[thunder booming]
I want you to tell me how to operate this wretched machine.
- Ohh.
[knock at door]
Are we expecting anyone?
- Shut up and answer the door.
- Yah vol, da commandant.
- Oh. I was walking my dog,
Lester, and we heard screams.
Is everything all right?
- Oh, that? We were rehearsing. - Oh, really?
Rehearsing for what?
- A scene...
a scene we're doing for Uncle's funeral tomorrow.
- Yes, he was such a fan of the theater that we thought
we would share a scene
from his favorite play with the attendees.
- And what play would that be?
- What play? Yes, of course.
- George Bernard Shaw's... - Bernard.
- George Bernard Shaw's "Man and Superman."
- I don't remember that play having any screaming in it.
- Well, this is the modern version.
Now, if you will excuse us... - Well...
- We have a lot of work to do. - Oh, I dare say.
Oh, this dog. Take your dog with you, huh?
Good night now.
- Ooh. Well, I don't know about you, Lester,
but I think those people are downright weird.
- "Man and Superman"? Why didn't you say, "Macbeth"?
At least they scream in "Macbeth."
- How would you know? You're illiterate.
- I am not. Mommy and Daddy were married.
- I think they're up to something.
We'd better keep a close eye on them.
- Okay. If you put the soap on now
and let them dry,
they'll wash themselves right after the meal.
- I'm not too sure about this. - Oh, trust me.
All my inventions work. Okay? Now, let's put them back.
- All right.
- [grunting]
[grunts]
Ehh! Ahh!
Ugh!
[grunting]
Ugh! Ahh!
[both grunting]
- You've been out in lab all morning.
Anything come of it?
- I've been going over the blood samples
we've taken from you since you drank the formula.
The potency of the invisibility potion appears to be lessening.
I think one day soon you'll be back to 100% normal.
- [mumbling]
- Mm! Oh!
[coughs]
Honey, what did you put-- what is this meal?
- Josh! Eddie! - Boys!
- Get down here this minute.
Somebody's got some explaining to do.
- Told you you shouldn't have put soap on the dishes.
- How was I supposed to know?
- [coughs] - [spits]
- Oh, no.
If I don't get this stain out Josh is going to kill me.
This will do the job.
It's ripping it.
Oh, great. Oh, no.
Whoa. That's a big hole. Oh, jeez.
This is going to be big.
Well, you can look at it this way.
It will be cooler in the summer.
- Not exactly one of your brightest ideas, Eddie.
- I can't do anything right.
You guys have been so cool to me.
I mean, all I want to do is help out.
Nobody at the orphanage treated me like you guys do.
- Yeah, I can imagine.
I did a day at New Horizons Orphanage myself.
Right after my mom drank the invisibility formula,
the state stuck me in there
until we could work some things out.
- Really? Then you know what it was like.
I mean, sometimes it was okay, but it was really fun
messing with the dweebs that tried to adopt me.
- You don't want to get adopted?
- No. Because my mom is going to pick me up.
I know it.
- What was she like? - I don't really know.
She left me when I was really young, but I do have a picture.
- She's pretty. - Yeah.
- So why did she leave you there?
- Well, Mrs. Mason said it's because she couldn't
take care of me.
Maybe I messed things up even then.
- Hey, man. You're just trying to do the right thing.
That's all that counts.
- Well, I'm sorry about messing up your jacket.
- Oh, don't worry about it. It's cool.
I never really liked it anyway. Want to play some croquet?
- Oh, sure.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- You missed.
- There's no do-over [indistinct]
Says the manual.
- Let me try again.
- Close, but no cigar.
[laughter]
- Hello, Eddie. Josh, are you parents home?
- Yeah. They're inside.
Mom, Dad, it's Mrs. Mason.
- Is anything wrong?
- These people are Olivia and Bernard St. John.
- Bernard. - Bernard.
And they're Eddie's last living relatives.
They've come to take Eddie home.
- I didn't know I had any living relatives.
- We were unaware of your existence
until we saw this newspaper article.
- St. John?
As in St. John Industries? - The very same, sir.
You've heard of us.
- Well, I'm Karl Griffin,
project director for Applied Technology.
One of St. John Industries subsidiaries.
- Oh, so you work for us?
Small world, isn't it?
And you are?
- Laura Griffin.
I'm Karl's wife and Josh's mother.
- Well, would you like to sit down?
Have some coffee and talk?
- Have you any tea?
- I think we could round some up.
- Well, that would be lovely.
- Well, I think that I'd better get back to the office.
Call me if you need me.
- Yeah, we'll be in touch.
- I admire a woman who remains a housewife.
It's so retro.
- Master Edward is the sole heir
to our late uncle's fortune.
We've come forward to shepherd him through the difficult days
that no doubt will lie ahead.
- Sole heir? Does mean I'm rich?
I'm rich! Oh, yeah! - Yeah!
- Edward.
Edward will come and live with us at the manor estate,
and we'll be one big, happy family.
- But I don't want to go.
I want to stay here with the Griffins.
- Well, that's quite impossible.
We're family now, and that's that.
- You know, this has been a pretty big shock
to all of us, especially Eddie.
Maybe if he could just ease into this gradually,
spend a couple of nights a week here.
- That is out of the question.
If we'd known about his existence
sooner he would never have stayed here in the first place.
- Well, I find it pretty interesting
that you just couldn't find him until after he was rich.
Excuse me.
- More sugar?
- The nerve of those people.
Ohh...oh, great.
What a perfect time to turn invisible.
- Pack your things, Edward. It's time to leave.
- But, I like it here. - We're a family.
We belong together.
There's nothing more to discuss.
Eh...ehh...
[gasping]
Ahh! Ahh!
- Olivia.
What the devil has gotten in to you?
- I don't know. I can't control myself.
- It's not a good idea to tick off my mom.
- You know, maybe you should see a doctor
before you think about adopting the boy.
- I am fine. - Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure, you twit.
- Hey, maybe Josh could spend the night with me tonight
at my new place?
- Yeah, that would be cool. - Yeah.
- Actually, we want to spend some time
with our newfound cousin.
We have to get to know him; you understand.
- So what did I miss? - Nothing.
Get your things, Edward. We are leaving.
Anyone who tries to stop us
will be hearing from our attorney.
- I'm sorry, Eddie. There's nothing we can do.
We have no choice.
Josh, would you help him pack?
- Go on. Scat!
- Yeah.
- Do you need something to clean off with?
- Thank you. No.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- We love you, Eddie.
No matter what, we'll always be here for you, okay?
- I know, Mrs. Griffin.
Oh, can you give them the address
so Josh can write to me?
- Thank you for taking such good care
of our dear little cousin.
- And we know you'll do the same.
- But of course, dear lady.
You have no idea how much he means to us.
- Josh, come out and say goodbye.
- We already said our goodbyes, Mr. Griffin. That's okay.
- Come along, Edward.
We're going to have such fun together.
- I suppose this is for the best.
- You don't believe that any more than I do.
♪ ♪
[thunder booming]
- Home sweet home, Edward.
- Stay down until I get inside, okay?
- Okay.
[thunder booming]
- Olivia, it's feeding time.
- Oh, good.
- Here, fishy, fishy, fishy. Time for din-din.
Oh. - Lovely. Aren't they?
- They get so testy when they have to wait.
- This will be one of your chores.
- Cool. - But don't fall in.
[chuckles]
Welcome to your new home, Edward.
- Who built this place? Boris Karloff?
- Our late uncle was a bit eccentric.
- Talk about the slime calling the algae green.
- Excuse me?
- Oh, I was just wondering where my new room was.
- Right this way.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Just think. All of this is yours.
- I am so excited.
- And this will be your room.
- Could I, like, stay with you guys tonight?
- Such a sense of humor you have.
- I think you'll find enough to occupy yourself,
what with the ghosts and all.
- Ghosts?
- Now, don't frighten him, Bernard.
Pay him no mind. This house isn't really haunted.
Or at least we don't think it is.
- Boo! [chuckles]
Sleep tight, Cousin Edward.
See you in the morning.
- Open the door.
- It's for your own protection, Edward.
We wouldn't want you sleepwalking and falling down
and hurting yourself now, would we?
Off to bed now.
- What are you looking at?
- Falling down and hurting yourself.
[laughs]
You slay me.
- Well, not until we're ready
for the nasty little accident at least.
- We have to act quickly.
Is everything prepared on your end?
- Perfectly. Operation Scared To Death can start at any time.
If this works, he'll fall over the railing
and break his little neck on the foyer floor.
- The sooner we dispose of the little nuisance
the sooner we'll have everything we ever wanted.
- I'll lock the main door.
- And I'll go get ready for tonight's festivities.
[thunder booming]
Money, money, money, money, money, money, money.
[laughs]
Ahh!
[car horns honking]
- I'm innocent.
It was Stevens. He framed me.
[Indistinct]
- Nobody's seen any flying saucers tonight.
And give my regards to Elvis, you nutcase.
Jeez, I hate the full moon.
- You're not really going to send a unit out there, are you?
- Nah, I was just saying that.
We do things a little differently out here
than you did down at the Ninth Precinct.
You shine these rich folks on,
and they forget they ever called you.
- Which is exactly what caused me to come down here
to lodge my complaint in person.
- Ma'am, would you like a seat? - No, thank you, officer.
- Shining on the rich folks, huh?
- Ma'am, that's not what I meant.
- What's your complaint?
- There's some very strange behavior going on down
at the St. John estate
in the Diamond Hills development.
- What sort of strange behavior?
- I've heard screams and moans.
- Probably kids just goofing around.
- Oh, no, officer. These are very serious screams.
I tell you, there is something awful going on in that house.
I went to investigate,
and they told me that they were only rehearsing for a play.
- Well, that doesn't sound so nefarious,
unless they were really bad actors.
- Did I happen to mention that my husband and I
donate huge sums of money
to the Policeman's Retirement Fund every year?
- No, ma'am. - Ma'am, we'll send someone
out there to investigate right away.
- I Hope so, because I'm going to be watching.
Good evening, gentlemen.
- Your first day in the precinct,
and you've already schmoozed the richest crackpot in town.
Good going, kid.
- Yeah, but I wasn't schmoozing.
Get your coat. We're going to check it out.
- Karl, have you seen Josh?
- I think he's still sulking about Eddie.
- Ohh, the two of them bonded so quickly.
I feel badly for him. - I'll go talk to Josh.
Maybe I can get him to come down.
Josh?
- Well? - He's gone.
- Gone? Oh, you don't suppose...
- He sneaked off to go with Eddie?
- How could we have missed him? - He's a clever kid.
Must have gotten it from your side of the family.
- Well, we have to go after him.
- Oh, no. I'll do it. I'll do it.
You stay here in case he calls or comes back.
I've got the address they gave us.
It's up in the Diamond Hills development.
I'll be right back.
- Joshua Martin Griffin, when you get back here
you are grounded until you are on Social Security.
[engine turning over]
- No, sir. The young man has been found.
No, he's not an imposter.
We've confirmed his identity.
Sir, may I be blunt?
You sound to be, oh, about 30. Yes?
Well, the real Edward St. John II is 12.
It was in all the reports. Therefore, you can't be him.
Listen closer next time.
Parasites.
- Come in. - Hi, Mr. Preston.
- Do we have an appointment? - Well, no. Not exactly.
But I think you may be looking for me.
- [chuckles]
Ma'am, it has been a most tiring day.
So let's dispense with the pleasantries.
Edward St. John II has been found.
You are the wrong age
and frankly the wrong gender to be him.
But I do admire your hutzpah. Now, if you'll excuse me.
- I'm his mother. - Nice comeback,
but I'm not buying it. Unless you have some proof.
- This isn't proof. This infant could be anybody.
- I knew I should have gone to the orphanage first.
- Orphanage? What orphanage?
- New Horizons, where I left him 12 years ago.
- And you left him under the name of?
- Eddie Brown, Brown being my maiden name.
- Mrs. St. John, I am so sorry to be so rude.
Please sit down.
Sit down. You have to understand a story
like this brings every gold digger in town out.
- You have to be careful, I understand now.
Where's my son?
- Regrettably, I've drawn up adoption papers.
His cousins Bernard and Olivia, they've petitioned for custody.
- No. Those two are the reason I put him in hiding
in the first place. If they get their hands on him,
they'll kill him the way they killed my husband.
- You can prove they murdered your husband?
- I don't have to prove it. I know it.
We have to stop this before they get to him.
- Mrs. St. John, come with me.
- It's just me, dude.
Man, this is some kind of weird place.
- I hate it. It gives me the creeps.
- Easy, buddy. It's just a house.
- No way, man. They said it was haunted.
- No such thing.
- Let's just relax and hang out until morning.
- I don't know, Josh.
- Come on, it will be fine.
Night, Eddie.
- Night, Josh.
[thunder booming]
- I had no idea these things were so uncomfortable.
- Quit griping. It's well worth it.
Remember, it has to look like an accident.
- Does anyone ever told you you have a terrible habit
of repeating yourself?
- Oh, don't be such a smart aleck.
Ohh. Ohh.
And now for my brilliant plan to commence.
- You mean our brilliant plan.
- Now, hurry up.
You have two minutes to get into position.
I'm going to unlock the little troll's door.
[eerie noises]
- Ow.
[thunder booming]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- What? - Look at the painting.
The eyes just moved.
- It's just your imagination, Eddie. Go back to sleep.
- No, I'm serious.
- It's just your mind playing tricks on you.
There's no such things as ghosts.
[woman screaming]
- You were saying.
[eerie noises]
♪ ♪
- Let's get out of here.
- I told you. Didn't I tell you?
- There's got to be a logical explanation for this.
- Yeah. It's haunted.
- Ah-hah!
Booga booga booga!
both: Ahh!
- Get down. Get down. - What for?
- Just get down. Get down.
- [chuckles]
Booga, booga.
- You lead rust bucket.
- Ah-ah! Ahh! - Yeah!
- Ooh! Augh!
Classic.
- Jeez, augh!
- Let's get out of this nuthouse, what do you say?
- Hey, hey, stop. Hey, hey, stop. Come here.
Ohh.
[telephone rings]
- Hello. - Mom, it's Josh.
- Joshua, there you are. Are you all right?
- Yeah. Mom, we're fine.
Look, you've got to come get us; we're in trouble.
You bet you are, mister.
And your father's on his way over there right now.
- No, Mom. Look.
There's ghosts here. Real ghosts.
One of them possessed a suit of armor, and it tried to kill us.
- Cute story, and you're still grounded.
- No, Mom. I'm serious.
- It's no joke, Mrs. Griffin. - Oh, all right.
I'll call the police.
But if you're making this up--
- No, Mom. I'm not. I swear.
- All right. I'll call them now.
- Thanks, Mom. And Mom-- - What?
- I love you. - I love you too, Josh.
Stay there till the police get there.
- Okay. Bye. The calvary is coming.
- Yeah.
Well, I hope they bring a couple of wooden stakes.
- Joshua Griffin. What a lovely surprise.
- How can you live in this place? It's haunted.
- Haunted? Why, whatever do you mean?
- We heard all these noises,
and there's these pictures with eyes that move.
- You have a wonderful imagination.
You'll have quite a career writing horror movies one day,
but in the meanwhile, let's have some refreshments
while I call your mother to come and collect you.
This way. This way.
[line trilling]
- 911. - Operator, I need you
to send a unit over to the Randolph St. John estate.
Two boys are in danger.
- What is the nature of the emergency?
- I just told you.
- Are they in imminent danger? - I don't know.
Something weird's going on over there.
My son just called and said there were ghosts after him.
- Sure, lady. You almost had me there for a moment.
- Blast it.
Oh, great.
Wait a minute.
This might not be such a bad thing after all.
Let's see. Mm-hmm. Here it is.
Well, I didn't think I'd be needing this old thing again.
And to finish the ensemble.
Hold tight, Josh and Eddie. Mom's on her way.
Okay, Laura. Just keep cool till you get there.
Now, where is this place?
Diamond Hills. Diamond Hills, where are you?
Ah, there.
[thunder booming]
- It's quite late. You two must be very tired.
I know, how about if I make you a little toddy for the body.
It's a drink. You do want one, don't you?
- Sure. - Sit down. I'll be right back.
- Ooh.
You know, you're pretty clever sneaking out of the house
without your parents finding out.
I hope you won't get in too much trouble
when they come and get you.
- I'm sure I'll be fine.
But, you know, I really should be going.
- Nonsense.
Here you go.
- What was that? - Oh, just a little nutmeg.
Now, be careful; the cups are hot.
Go on. Drink up. Drink up.
Drink.
[knock at door]
Oh, no. You two stay here.
Mr. Griffith, what a surprise.
- Griffin. - I'm not going to drink it.
- Me neither.
[sizzling]
[plant gagging]
- Holy cow. That was poisoned.
- Yeah, just like in the "Spider-Woman Strikes Back."
But why is she trying to kill us?
- I can think of about a billion reasons.
- My inheritance.
- Exactly. Now let's book.
- I--I'm very sorry to bother you,
but I think my son, Josh, may be here.
- I beg your pardon? - He's missing, you see.
And he was so distraught over Eddie having to come here
that he... - Come inside.
- Well, Griffin. What brings you by?
- He thinks his son might be here.
- Edward's little friend?
Now, how would he have got in here?
- Most likely he stowed away in your car.
- Uh, Bernard, why don't you
show him around and...
maybe the child will turn up.
- Ah, yes. I think I know where they might be.
Come this way.
[thunder booming]
- Children. I hate children.
- Ahh!
- That was my dad's voice.
We've got to get out of here or they're going to waste him too.
- Wait. Hold on. I've got a match somewhere.
- What are you doing with matches?
- Hey, you don't light firecrackers
with your tongue, you know?
Here we go.
both: Ahh!
- We're locked in!
- Come on, this way, this way, come on.
- Do you think he might have got in a car?
Boys will be boys.
- Yes.
- Maybe they're playing hide-and-seek?
- Oh, yeah.
- Let's look down here.
Ah! I'll bet they're in there. After you.
- Dad! - We've got to help him.
- We need a plan.
- Cute place.
- This was Uncle's little play room.
He wasn't quite right, you know?
- Well, the boys don't seem to be down here.
Maybe we should go back upstairs.
Ohh.
- Let's not and say we did.
- Be quiet. Here he comes.
- There he is. Shh!
- Come out, come out, wherever you are.
- Bernard, Bernard! Come here.
- Boy, that was close. Come on.
- What did you do with him? - He's in the dungeon.
We'll dispose of him with the rest.
- No problem.
I just gave the two little brats enough cyanide
to knock out a white buffalo.
- Oh, that will look really accidental.
- Of course it will.
They got into the poison cabinet by mistake.
It happens all the time.
- Hmm. Then we're rich!
- No, we have to dispose of the bodies.
Now, come on, help me.
[gasps] They're gone.
- Hmm.
The best laid plans of mice and men.
- Oh, shut up and help me find them!
- How are we going to get Dad out of that cellar?
- They're going to do away with all of us.
- Not if I can help it.
- Oh, no. Here we go again. Let's get out of here, go!
- Oooh.
Oooooh.
- Uh, uh, uh...
both: Ehhh!
- [cackling]
both: Ahh!
[coughing]
[cackling]
- This way! - No, this way! Come on.
[upbeat piano music]
♪ ♪
- Man, this is nuts! - Ahh!
- Now, that was some serious commotion. You had to hear it.
- We got a little thing called probable cause to consider.
- So when do we take them in, when they come running out
of the house with a bloody butcher knife?
- One false step,
and you'll be writing parking tickets in Pacoima.
- So what do we do now?
- Wake me when it gets interesting.
- I don't know about you, but I'm getting tired of this
running and screaming stuff.
- This ain't like any horror movie I ever saw.
- Well, then you've never seen
"Abbott and Costello Meet Frankenstein."
- You okay? - I'm okay. You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- What's this all about?
- Okay, nobody's here.
Aha! Great. No, oh! It's locked!
Oh, now what do I do?
Let me think; let me think.
Um...
Yes! I got it!
Off everything. Quietly keep your cool.
You can do this, Laura. You can do this!
If somebody comes, you'll be fine.
Huh, think. Off with this.
Yes! Yes!
- Say what? Hey! Ski, Ski!
- I'm up. I'm here!
- You're not going to believe this.
- What? - See that car over there,
somebody just got out of it. I think it was a lady.
She climbed those steps and disappeared.
- Disappeared?
- Hey, I swear; that's what happened.
- Uh-huh. You been putting
in a lot of late hours, haven't you, kid?
Trying to make a good impression.
- Yeah, maybe you're right. - Let's head for the barn, kid.
This is a total bubkis run.
- Man, I'm too young to be seeing things.
- Can't we get any blasted quiet here?
Get out; it's private property!
What the?
Well...
Bernard!
- Blasted suit of armor was nearly the death of me.
- Hurry up and find those little heathens.
We have to get rid of them and arrange their bodies
properly before morning if we want to get away with this!
- Don't speak to me as if I'm an idiot, Olivia.
- Then stop acting like one.
Two little children outwitting a grown man.
- Funny, I don't seem to see them in your clutches either.
- Oh, shut up!
- Wouldn't be a shame
if something happened to you, dear sister?
- Oh, gosh! It's so dark in here.
Oh! Josh, Eddie!
- Mom! You're, you're invisible again!
- Huh? Mrs. Griffin?
- Oh, are you boys all right? - Yeah, we're fine.
- Look, we don't have much time. Where's your father?
- They locked him up down in the basement.
It's down the hallway, down there.
- [gasps] Somebody's coming! Get back in there, hurry up!
You stay here, I'll go rescue your father.
What have you gotten yourself into, Laura?
- [gasps] Hold it! Well, well.
Mrs. Griffin. The gang is all here, eh?
- Please let my family go. - Sorry, no can do.
Bernard? Bernard!
- What is it now? - We have a new arrival.
- Well, aren't we the fashion plate?
- I've taken care of the pleasantries.
Let's lock her up with the other one.
- Where's my husband? - Oh, come with us.
He's dying to see you.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, we should have jumped them.
- Yeah, and then we all would have been caught.
No, we got to do this sneaky-like.
- Yeah. So what's your plan?
- I don't know; I'm just making this up as I go.
- Honey! - Oh, Karl, Karl!
- What is this all about? - I came to save you.
Some rescue, huh?
- How touching. - Come on!
- Ow! - Don't you hurt her!
- Ow! - Oh, sorry, did I hurt you?
- Yes! - Good.
- There now, all better.
- You'll never get away with this, you know.
I called the police. They're going to be here any minute.
- Spare us, the police won't come out
unless a crime has actually been committed,
especially to the St. John Estate
and probably not even then.
- They'd be afraid that we'd sue the pants
off them for harassment.
- But it was a darn nice try. - Nice try.
- I don't supposed you saw where the rooms are?
- I think it's one of these, why?
- Those ghost ain't real, pal. Now, Olivia tried to poison us,
and I'm willing to bet that Cousin Bernie
was the guy in the armor.
- Which means that the moaning
and screams were probably off the record.
- Yeah. If I could only find the record, I've got an idea.
Oh, cool! Good thinking, Josh.
This room? - Yeah.
[thunder booming]
- There's nothing here!
- Get down, Cousin Olivia!
- Come on, get serious!
- Is this serious enough for you?
- All right, cool. Let's find Bernie's room!
- Hey, maybe this is Bernie's room!
- Come on.
- Don't you think it's going to look a little suspicious
when an entire family disappears?
- She's right, even the St. John Family
name won't be able to save you then!
- Oh, no! Oh, gosh, well, I guess
we're just going to have to let you go.
You won't tell anyone, will you?
Educate them, brother dear.
- Well, I was thinking, since your car is already here,
we could just stash your already dead bodies
inside of it and run it off a cliff.
- Ridiculous! Forensics would find you out in a heartbeat!
- Tell that to my dearly departed Cousin Edward.
- Edward I, the brat's father.
- He underestimated me too, paid the ultimate price.
- All so you could be the sole inheritors.
- Can you think of better reason?
- But then another heir showed up, and, well,
naturally, he has to be disposed of well.
Heir today, gone tomorrow!
[laughter]
- Oh! That's funny.
- Jackpot!
- You know, this would all be over with if your brat of yours
had stayed home like you told him.
- Yeah, if he did Eddie'd be dead now.
- True, but no matter.
You'll all be out of the way soon enough.
[eerie noises]
- Let's go.
- They're in your room!
Don't go away; we'll be right back.
- How did you get in here? - Oh, Karl, how do you think?
- Honey, that was dangerous!
- I couldn't worry about that. You guys are my family.
Can't just stand around and do nothing
while you're in trouble.
Oh, terrific.
Oh, this is just great!
- All right. That's it! We've had enough!
[eerie noises]
Where are they?
- They're in your room!
- What the devil?
- We'll see if they can get out of that.
- What's the matter with you? Open it!
- You open it if you're so bloody clever!
- Do something about the blasted racket.
- Ohh, for...
[record needle scratches]
Okay, enough of this foolishness.
We have to finish them.
- Come out, little kiddy winks.
We won't hurt you...much.
- Come on out, children. Where are you?
- Downstairs.
- Let's make it work for us! There's a set of shackle keys
hanging by the skeleton over there, unlock us!
Hurry, Josh! These shackles are killing me. Hurry, hurry!
- Come on, come on, get it open!
- Oh, yes!
- You really are a hopeless fool.
- Shut up! By the way, how is it you had a key to my room?
- Oh, well, I... - Never mind.
We'll discuss that later.
- I don't feel like discussing it.
- Oh, there it goes. Oh.
- Come on, help me, Josh!
- Just pretend like I'm not even here!
- Help him, Josh.
- I'm not worried.
- None of them! None of them work!
- Well, isn't this special?
The whole family here to-- hey, how did she escape?
- You idiot! - What do you mean me?
You're the one that locked her--
no, I'm the one that locked her up.
- Oh! Who hit me?
- Nobody hit you.
- I'm telling you, someone kicked me.
- Oh, get a grip, sis.
The stress getting too much for you?
- Do not patronize me, you fop! - Now, now, play nice kids.
- How about if we start with you, you poor, helpless man?
- You better not!
- Yeah, she's upstairs right now calling the cops.
- Get up there, Bernard; stop her.
Shoot her if you have to.
Oh, shoot her if you don't have to.
- What about you?
- I'm going to make sure the little twerps stay here
and behave themselves.
- When I get back, we'll get down to businesses.
- But he said to wait until he got back.
- Yes. But I don't see why he should have all the fun.
- Ugh!
- Leave them alone, you witch!
You want to torture someone, torture me instead!
- Wait your turn, Griffin.
- [gasping]
No! Olivia! Olivia! Olivia!
- What is it now? - Ah!
- Can't he kill one simple housewife?
- There's nothing simple about this housewife, lady.
- Help! No! Don't shoot, don't shoot.
- Ugh, give me these! - Don't shoot!
- Stay here! - Don't! Olivia! Ah!
- Psst, boys, the keys. Behind me. Hurry, hurry.
- Bernard? Bernard! what is your problem?
- Telephone floating in the-- and then chair!
The gun was pointed-- it's a ghost!
- Get a hold of yourself.
- Come on. Come on.
- Get it up. Get it up.
- There is no such thing as ghosts.
- Then what was it?
- Her.
- Oooh!
- Be careful.
- The housewife. Get a hold of yourself, you big sissy.
- Oh! - Watch this!
- Housewife.
I knew that.
- [whines]
- Help me.
The keys.
- Oh, dear God!
[gasping]
- The keys! Get those keys, or we'll never get out of here!
- What the? Why me? - Because you're the man!
- Shouldn't we go help her?
- Oh, I think she's got the situation under control.
- Ahh-ahh-ahhh.
Why did you kill me, Cousin Bernard?
- Oh, my God!
It's not Uncle Randolph; it's Edward's father!
- This is your fault! You're the one who killed him!
- On your orders!
[laughter]
It wasn't my fault. It was her idea!
- Mine? You traitor!
Look, he's got it all wrong; it was an accident.
We're really very sorry.
- Then repent for all eternity.
- Eternity? I don't think so.
- [screaming]
- We'll be safe in here.
- Oh, you may be safe from the ghost,
but you're not safe from me!
- Stop it. Stop it. All right?
Look, we're in this together, all right?
There must be a way out of here.
[upbeat piano music]
♪ ♪
- [gasping]
- Ah! Bernard! Ah!
- All right, which key? Which key?
- The silver one! The silver one!
- Silver? They're all silver!
I got it. I got it.
- All right, all right, where are you going?
- The police! Oh, thank God; we're saved!
Take us away; arrest us!
- Arrest us! We're murderers.
- Oh, yeah? So who did you kill?
- Our Cousin Edward; I cut the brake lines on his car.
- And I told him to do it!
Take us away, please! We can't stand this!
- I told you rich folks are nuts.
- Yeah, here's your proof. Will you two sign a confession?
- Anything! Anything at all!
- Just get us out of here! - Yeah, of course!
She was the mastermind. I was only the helpless patsy.
- Shut up, Bernie! - Bernard!
- Put them in the car.
I'm going to get a statement from these folks.
- Nice, warm police car.
You got any doughnuts or coffee? I'm hungry.
- Karl! - Honey!
You're-- - Yeah, I'm fine; I'm fine.
Boy are we glad to see you. How did you know where to come?
- Well, I brought them. Good evening.
I'm Albert Preston, their late uncle's attorney.
- It's a real pleasure. - So you must be Eddie.
How nice to finally meet you.
- Likewise, I guess.
- Do you need us to swear out a complaint against those two?
- Not with them singing up a storm.
Why don't you guys go home and get some rest?
- You about done in here? Those two out there
keep going on about how the ghosts are haunting them.
I think they're candidates for the bughouse.
- Yeah, I think we're done.
You said you're the family lawyer.
You probably want to come down to the station.
- Oh, not necessarily.
It couldn't happen to a more deserving pair, if you ask me.
Good night, officers.
- Good night.
- I handled all of your late grandfather's business affairs.
You're quite a rich young man.
You'll need some financial guidance,
and I'd be more than happy to continue on in your employ.
- Yeah, sure, whatever. - What's the matter, Eddie?
This is a great opportunity.
- I guess.
I mean, I have to live in this big house all by myself.
Josh can't live here,
because he's got his own family,
his own home, and his own mom.
- Oh, Eddie.
I will always be here for you.
You guys can get together whenever you want.
- Really? You mean it? Cool. - Hold on now.
Did I say you were going to be living here all by yourself?
Not on your life. You're going to have
an adult here with you night and day seven days a week.
- Oh, terrific.
- Let me introduce you to your new guardian.
- Mom? - Eddie.
You must be the Griffins. Mrs. Mason told me about you.
Thank you for taking such good care of my son.
- He's a good kid.
- You know, I'm a little confused.
It might not be any of my business,
but where have you been all of these years?
- In hiding. You see, after Eddie's father died,
thanks to his cousins, well, I couldn't prove it.
I knew they'd come after us to finish the job
and wipe out any inheritors.
There I was alone and penniless.
I knew I couldn't keep Eddie safe
unless I put him away in hiding.
So I went to the orphanage, and I changed his last name.
And I prayed Bernard and Olivia would never find him.
- And when they made such a big deal out of adopting him
after Randolph St. John passed away,
I knew it was just a matter of time before Eddie
met up with a quote, unquote unfortunate accident.
- When I heard about Randolph passing away,
I knew it was time to surface.
I tracked down Mr. Preston, and here I am.
Eddie, I'm sorry it took so long.
Can you ever forgive me?
- You're my mom.
- Well, I guess that settles it.
We have papers to sign,
but that can wait for a day or so.
I think there's more important things
to take care of right now. Good night all.
- Good night and thank you. - Good night.
- Oh, wow.
What about you, honey?
Are you okay? - Oh, I'm fine.
I think the serum has finally worn off.
- You know, I kind of like this wraparound look. Look at you.
- Stop, not here; let's go home and let them get acquainted.
[upbeat piano music]
♪ ♪
- If we're all here, who's playing the piano?
- Ahh!
[thunder booming]
♪ ♪