[letters clinking]
[gentle music]
[word pings]
[futuristic music]
[gentle music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[Daniel grunts]
[wine sloshing]
Here you go, baby.
Oh, thank you.
- Oh, you're welcome.
- Oh, this looks great.
[Daniel laughs]
Cheers.
Cheers to you.
Mm.
Oh yeah, nice.
Today was such
a beautiful day.
We're so blessed with
our beautiful family.
We are.
Oh, which reminds me, I
have something for you.
- You do?
- Yeah.
- What is it?
- Ah!
Hey!
[both laughing]
What is it?
Something corny.
No, it's a, it's a bunch of our
family photos, my favorites.
I mean, I've made you a
playlist a thousand times.
I just thought I'd do
something different for you.
This is so sweet, I love it.
Aw, you wanna look at it?
- Yes.
- Come on.
- Let's watch it.
- Oh.
- I'll show you.
Better there?
It's so nice.
Start like this.
Oh my God.
[both laughing]
These are so great!
[gentle music]
[Daniel] Look at
this, look at this.
[Abby] Oh.
[Daniel] Look at this one.
Wait, this one's one
of my favorites, right?
[Abby] Oh, wow.
Oh my God.
[Daniel] Look at your hair.
Look at my hair!
Ooh, ooh.
[Daniel laughing]
Awesome!
Oh my God.
- Look at you.
- Oh.
Aw, aw, look at him.
- Oh, babe.
- Wow.
Maybe not my best look.
[Daniel laughing]
Aw.
Look, you're always traveling.
I just wanted you to know
that we're always
with you, alright?
I love it.
Good, I'm glad.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh my gosh.
Look at this.
This is amazing!
Look at the mess here.
[both laughing]
This is so sweet!
[Daniel laughing]
I'm glad you like it.
Mm, smells good.
[Daniel chuckling]
Mm, it does.
Are you doing
this salad tomorrow?
Nope, it's already done.
Oh, wow.
You do know what
time it is, don't you?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
It's time for
the dance! [laughs]
You are so silly.
Stop that.
[Daniel laughing]
Just because you're some
big time music executive,
doesn't mean you
can make me dance.
Oh, but I can.
Oh. [laughs]
I love you Abby Thompson.
And I love you,
Daniel Thompson.
[Daniel chuckles]
- Mm, oh, this is great!
- Nice.
- You guys are gonna love it.
- Ooh.
Oh yeah, look at this.
- [Daniel laughing]
- Thank you.
You're welcome,
you're welcome.
Alright.
- That looks so good.
- That looks great.
Who wants to say grace?
You know, I'd like
to say it tonight.
Alright.
Dear heavenly Father,
we thank you for the
blessings bestowed upon us,
for the food before us,
for the roof above us,
for our family together,
and for all the love
we share between us.
Amen.
[Jay] Amen.
That was beautiful, Mom.
Thank you.
It was a beautiful day.
[Jay] You're beautiful.
Uh, thank you, Jay.
Is there something
you want, Jay?
No, I mean it.
I do not want anything.
Mm hmm.
[Daniel laughing]
Well, unless I
can get something.
We already have
everything we need.
Oh, which reminds me.
[Abby] Mm hmm?
Time you leaving for
your trip tomorrow?
[Abby] Oh, that's right,
I still have to pack.
I'm gonna get on the road
at eight tomorrow morning.
Mm, yikes, you're gonna
hit a lot of city traffic.
[Abby] I know.
[Lindsey] How long are
you gonna be gone this time?
Ah, should just be overnight.
One meeting, a
couple of signatures,
and then I'll be headed home.
Good, I want you to
be here for the dance.
Oh, I wouldn't miss
it for the world.
[Jay] I would, unless I
could be the photographer?
Jay, when you
get to high school,
you can be on the
school paper like me,
and you can be the photographer.
[Jay] Great.
- [Daniel laughing]
- There you go.
[Daniel] That's it.
Eat up, guys.
This looks great.
[Daniel] Mm, glad you like it.
[Jay] Mm, oh, the
macaroni's good.
- It's very good.
- Good, it is.
[somber music]
[machines beeping]
[ventilator whooshing]
[door knocking]
[Officer] Are you
Daniel Thompson?
[Daniel] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What do you need?
[Officer] Sir, there's
been an accident.
Okay.
Your wife.
Whoa, wait, wait,
wait, wait, Abby?
Mom?
Wait, wait, yeah, is
she alright, where is she?
I'm sorry, sir.
She was in an accident,
and she was killed on impact.
What?
[Jay] You're lying!
No!
[Officer] Sir, I'm sorry.
[Daniel] No.
We found all her
belongings in the car.
We're gonna need you to
come down and identify her.
Abby, no, no.
[Lindsey sobbing]
[Lindsey sniffling]
I need you to come down,
and call me on your way,
and I'll meet you there, okay?
Okay.
[Officer] Here's my card.
Alright.
I'm sorry again.
[Lindsey sobbing]
- Abby.
- Mommy.
- No.
Jay, are you okay?
No.
Okay, it's gonna be okay.
You gotta just take
it one day at a time.
[somber music]
Where's my mom?
She was so good.
She loved us.
I don't know, Josh.
I don't think there's a God.
Why would he do this?
I don't think God did this.
Okay, this was a
drunk driver, Josh.
An accident.
But she didn't have to die.
Do you think there's a God?
I don't know what
to think right now.
I just miss Mom.
[air whooshing]
Beautiful.
You think so?
My baby girl's all grown up!
[air whooshing]
I just miss Mom.
[sniffles] I do too.
I know, I know.
Daniel, I'm so sorry
about what happened.
She was a beautiful person.
We all loved her.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, thank you so
much for coming.
Brandon, please say
hi to the family.
Thank you.
The church is there for you,
your family is there for
you, I'm there for you.
I know.
[Jack] Did you know I
brought your kids back
from the church?
Thanks.
Nice to see you, Jack.
Jack?
Hey, hey, Pop?
Oh, pastor, it was
a beautiful service.
Well, thank you.
I'm glad you liked it, Jack.
You guys wanna go with
me and greet the guests?
I do.
We can't, Jay.
Sorry, Grandpa,
our dad needs us.
Okay, but if you
wanna get away,
I have a getaway car outside.
If you kids feel you wanna
get away, let me know, okay?
I'm sure they'll take
you up on the offer.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Pop.
How are you two doing?
- [somber music]
- We're not good.
Lindsey, do you
know Pastor John?
He runs the youth
group at the church.
Yeah, I've met him.
Pastor John runs a grief
support group as well.
Lindsey, please, we
would like you to join
our grief support group
when you're ready.
Jay, you can come too.
Thanks, pastor.
I'm not ready yet.
I know, I know.
When you are, we're
there for you.
Thanks, pastor, really.
And the church is
there for you too,
and we'll always
be there for you.
[Daniel] You've been
a lifelong friend.
We appreciate it, alright?
Thank you, thank you.
Alright.
God bless.
God bless you.
Hey, how're you doing?
- [melancholic music]
- [sighs] Oh, God.
[drawers banging]
Oh, God, I'm gonna be late!
Where is it?
I thought it was...
[Lindsey yelling]
Mom, I can't do
this without you.
God, why would you
take her away from me?
Why?
[Daniel] Hey?
[door knocking]
Is everything alright?
No, nothing is alright!
Why can't you understand that?
I think I might be able to.
No, you can't, because I'm 16.
I should still have my Mom!
Hey, hey!
Have you forgotten that
your mother was my wife?
I lost her too!
I lost her!
I'm sorry.
[Daniel] Oh God.
- I'm sorry, Dad, I didn't...
- No, no, no, no.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
- I'm sorry, Dad.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Look, we're all going
through this, alright?
We all lost her.
Lindsey, look, do you
remember that group
the pastor was talking about?
No, please,
- that's not gonna help.
- No, no, no.
No, it's not gonna help.
It won't bring Mom back.
No, but it can't hurt either.
Look, no, listen,
your heart is so pained,
your mother would never
want you to feel this way.
Please, just go for me.
Just go, please,
just once, just once.
- Please, okay?
- Fine.
But I wanna do this on my own.
Okay.
Let me drive, okay?
- Okay.
- Come on.
[Lindsey sniffles]
[elevator rumbling]
[John] How's your
week been, Ava?
[Ava] Good.
[John] That's good.
We're glad to see
you back again.
Yeah, it's been a, it's
been a wonderful week.
We had a lot going
on with the church.
And, yeah, so we're very excited
to have those special activity
things lined up as well,
so it's always fun with them.
Ricky, how've you
been this week?
For those of you
just joining us,
I'd like to tell you a
bit about what we do here
in the group.
Our grief support group is a
place of healing and of hope.
We like to remember our
loved ones out loud.
We share stories, we share
memories good and bad,
but more importantly,
we support each other
through the sadness of loss,
and we move into the
comfort of knowing
that they remain in our hearts
and our memories forever.
Now, I'd like to
have our new members
go ahead and
introduce themselves,
then we'll share some stories.
Would you like to go first?
Hi, I'm Lindsey.
I lost my mom a few months ago.
Hi, Lindsey.
We're happy to meet you.
Thank you for being here.
And how about you?
Hi, I'm, I'm Andrew.
I lost my brother in a car
accident about a year ago,
and things haven't
really gotten better,
so my mom recommended I
come to a support group.
Well, thank you, Andrew.
At the very least, we hope you
can find some comfort here,
and know you're not alone.
Thank you.
So, would anyone like to
begin by sharing a story?
I'd like to share
my story, John.
[John] Oh, Ava, please.
My husband and I were trying
to have a baby for so long.
We thought after IVF and
for trying for so long
that it would never happen,
but we were happy because
we knew that we had options.
One night we went to a restaurant
with my husband's boss.
It was this restaurant
on the top of a building,
really high up.
Now, I don't do heights,
[gentle music]
so I got really sick.
It was so embarrassing.
The next night I was still sick.
I mean, every smell, just about
anything made me feel sick.
He knew I was pregnant,
but I was like, "No,
I mean, it can't be."
He went out, he
bought me a test,
and it turns out he was
right, I was pregnant.
We were so happy.
I mean, it was probably one
of the second best moments
of our lives.
Our first was when
our baby boy was born.
It was pure joy.
Our family was complete.
A week later, he went
on a business trip,
and the plane crashed,
and he didn't make it.
But he got to meet Ryan Junior.
[John] Ava, thank you so
much for sharing that story.
You're welcome.
It's hard, but I realized
through the process of healing,
there are more good memories
than there could ever be bad.
I just wish that I could
hear him again, or see him.
Thank you.
Would any of our new members
like to share a story?
I'm not ready yet.
That's okay.
When you're ready,
we'll be here.
You know, remembering
our loved ones out loud
is greatly helpful.
[gentle music]
It keeps them in our hearts.
Andrew, would you like to share?
I guess, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'll go.
But it's kind of hard to
remember things right now.
No good memories, no bad
ones, just, it just all sucks.
You know, I was in that car
accident where my brother died.
Why not me?
What makes me so special?
He was my brother.
He was my twin.
He was a part of me.
We were supposed to
travel the world together,
and now it's just me,
and that ain't right.
Andrew, it's,
it's not just you.
You know, he's
still part of you,
and remembering him
is gonna help you.
Thank you for sharing.
[Lindsey] Pastor John?
[John] Yes, Lindsey.
Could I tell a little
about my mom, maybe?
Yes, I think we'd love that.
My last memory of her,
she was helping me
pick out my dress
for my first school dance.
My mom was so sweet,
always loving.
Her dream was to be there
for me at my wedding,
but now she won't be able to.
I'm sorry, I can't
talk about this yet.
And that's okay.
Thank you so much for sharing.
You know, the healing
process takes time.
And Lindsey, when you're
ready, we'll be here to listen.
Well, I think that's a
good place to leave it.
We do have some flyers
over on the table there.
It has some fun activities
to help the healing process.
And before we go,
I'd like you do a
little bit of homework
for this, this next week.
Now, before you look at me
like that, it's nothing hard.
I'd like you to talk to a
relative or a mutual friend,
and have them share a
good memory with you.
I'd like you to write it down,
and if you feel comfortable,
share it when you
come back next week,
and we'll start on
our memory books.
Alright?
Thanks again for
coming everybody.
Remember, there are some
flyers over by the coffee,
that have some
recommended reading.
As always, if you need
to talk to me at all,
feel free to come find me.
Have a wonderful week.
Chocolate chip was
Matthew's favorite cookie.
Hey, I'm sorry
about your brother.
Thanks.
Sorry about your mother too.
Guess we all gotta lose
someone at some point.
Yeah, but it
doesn't feel fair.
I know.
Were you close
to your brother?
Yeah, we were pretty
much like the same person.
We even had our own way
of talking to each other.
Yeah, I've heard that,
that twins can have their
own secret language.
That's actually really cool.
Yeah, yeah, guess so.
Well, I gotta go,
my dad's waiting.
But it was nice to meet you.
[hopeful music]
Hey, I hope you come back.
I think I will.
[Daniel] Ugh, it's
a hot day today, man.
Hey, you alright?
No, seriously, you okay?
I don't know.
What's wrong?
Alright, you
wanna talk about it?
Why?
It won't bring Mom back!
No, but it's nice
to remember her.
Lindsey says Mom is living
in heaven now with God.
I just wish I could
talk to her, Dad.
It would be so nice if
a text or phone call
could reach all the
way up to heaven.
I know.
Look, I knew someone that
wrote a message in a-
- I don't want that, I want Mom!
I want Mom too, okay?
I'm sorry things have changed.
Dad, I don't wanna hike today.
I just wanna go back home.
Right, you don't wanna hike?
You just wanna go home?
Yeah.
Watch a movie with me?
Sure.
It's hot anyway, right?
Come on, come on.
[rain pattering]
[gentle guitar music]
[Daniel sighs]
I'm having a real
hard time here, Abby.
The kids are so sad.
I'm just trying to
make them feel loved.
Just don't laugh at me if
I start to cry. [laughs]
You know, I remember
you saying once
that real men do cry.
Well, this man cries for you.
I love you, Abby.
[gentle guitar music]
Oh, man.
[hopeful music]
Those cookies smell great.
If it's cookies,
you know it's for me.
Every kid loves cookies.
Dad, it's for group.
[Daniel And Josh] Oh.
Can we just have one?
Just one?
Not unless you come
to group with me.
Good luck.
This is a real nice
thing you're doing here.
Thanks, Dad.
How about one for the old man?
Want an apple?
Sure.
[Daniel and Lindsey chuckling]
Andrew, this is my
little brother, Josh.
Josh, meet Andrew.
Hey, Josh.
So, you're the reason
my sister won't let me have
any cookies, aren't you?
Me?
Well, nice to meet
you too, Josh.
I'm gonna go sit down.
You can stop now.
I'm just messing
with you, little man.
Coming to a good spot.
Place helps me out a lot.
[Josh] Sure.
How's your week been?
I've had a good week.
Did you have a good week?
Yeah, it was.
My dad set up to scholarship
in my mom's name,
and we met a few
of the recipients.
Oh, that's cool.
Yeah, it really was.
Hey, you wanna go
get coffee sometime?
Maybe talk about your mother,
or my brother, or the weather?
Yeah, I'd like that.
Maybe you can meet my
best friend, Katie.
Yeah, yeah, that'd be cool.
Okay, let's go.
Yeah.
Alright, everyone.
Well, let's go ahead
and take our seats,
and we can begin.
It's always nice to see
new faces in the group.
And as a little reminder,
I like to say what it
is we do in this group.
Our grief support group is
a place of healing and hope.
[gentle music]
We like to remember our
loved ones out loud.
We share stories, we share
memories, good and bad,
and more importantly, we
like to support each other,
as we move from the
sadness of loss,
to finding the comfort
of knowing that our loved
ones reside in our hearts
and our memories forever.
I'd like the new
faces in the group
to go ahead and
introduce themselves.
And we'll go ahead and
start sharing some stories.
My name's Josh and
my sister made me come.
Well, it's good
to see you, Josh.
Thank you for coming.
Thanks for bringing
him, Lindsey.
And?
Hi, my name is Carrie.
I lost my baby boy.
He had cancer.
Hi, Carrie.
I really hope both of you
can find some comfort
in being here with us.
Carrie, would you like
to share a little more
about your story?
No pressure.
No, I'm not ready.
It's, it's hard to
talk about still.
We're glad you're here.
If you need to talk,
I'm always here.
I lost my mom not too long ago,
and I know it's not the same,
but this group is
really helping me.
Thank you, Lindsey.
Whatever we can do to help,
that's why we're here.
So, everyone, how's
the week been?
It's been better.
My mother and I went
to see my dad's grave.
So, well, she decided
to start a scholarship
in his name, so.
That's wonderful,
and I'm sure he'd be very proud.
Thank you for sharing, Ricky.
How's your week been, Ava?
Oh, mine, mine actually
has been really good.
I've had more good
days than bad,
which I never
thought would happen.
We're actually planning a
trip to see Ryan's parents
this weekend, so.
[John] That sounds
like a wonderful trip.
Yeah, I might be
missing a few meetings.
Oh, well, that's okay.
Certainly a good reason.
Yeah.
[John chuckling]
Andy, how's your
week been, sir?
You know, I'm still
having a hard time.
You know, sometimes I still
feel angry about it all,
him dying and me surviving.
But my mom was actually
going through his stuff,
and she found this dictionary.
It's the dictionary,
we used to use it,
to make our own language.
When I looked at it,
something clicked.
Just realized he
was a part of me.
[John] And how has that
impacted your healing?
Well, I can at
least talk about him.
You know, that's
a big step for me.
That's a great start.
You know, continuing to
remember our loved ones out loud
is always so helpful, you know?
It keeps them right
in our hearts.
Yeah.
It hasn't been easy,
but I've been trying.
Lindsay, how you been?
Honestly, I'm okay.
You know, I know my
mom's always with me,
and my dad and I, we did
some things in her memory.
And I guess I'm just not
as angry as I was before.
That's great to hear.
I'm happy to hear
with your progress.
I'm really proud of all of you.
You know, these, these
reports are great, you know?
I'd actually like to
take a time of prayer.
Bow our heads in prayer.
Heavenly father, we thank you
for this wonderful
night you've given us.
Thank you for reminding us
that your mercies
are new every day.
It says in the book of Matthew,
that blessed are
those who mourn,
for they will be shown mercy.
We pray that your grace
continuously follows us
through our day.
And we pray that
you bless our going
as you blessed our
coming here tonight.
Thank you.
It's in your name we pray.
Amen.
[upbeat guitar music]
Dad, Dad.
[Daniel] Yeah.
Teach me to play guitar.
What now?
Yeah, I wanna write
songs like you do.
Look.
What have you got?
[strings twanging]
[chuckles] This is pretty good.
Yeah, it's for Mom.
You know what,
here, you got it.
Here, give me that guitar.
Take the old man's guitar.
Do you remember that E minor
chord that I showed you
- a while back?
- Yeah.
Yeah?
Let's see what you got.
Here, take the pick.
Try that.
[strings twanging]
Yeah, you're right on the mark.
Let's do another one.
Do you remember D7?
Yeah, one there.
Actually, no, put
this finger up here.
Hit that.
See how that works?
[strings twanging]
Not bad, could be better.
- [Daniel laughs]
- Very good!
[gentle music]
Hey, there you go.
Thank you.
Of course, you're welcome.
So, did you enjoy
group last time?
I dunno, I'm starting
to really like it.
Like, it's helping me.
Me too.
I didn't think I could
stop feeling angry
or guilty about it all,
but little by little, I am.
That's good.
Oh, there's Katie.
Katie's here.
Hi.
Hey, Katie.
Hi, hi.
Katie, this is
Andrew from group.
Andrew, this is Katie,
from like my whole life.
[Andrew] Hi,
hi, how you doing?
[Katie] Hi.
So, you're the one that
eats all the cookies.
Um, how did you know?
[Katie] I heard. [laughs]
[Andrew] Hmm.
Hey, Dad.
Oh hey, pumpkin.
How was your day?
It was great.
Oh, that's right,
it was your third date.
How'd it go?
Dad, it's not a date.
Alright, alright, it
wasn't a date. [laughs]
Look, I got some dinner in
the fridge for you, alright?
Don't be up too late,
school tomorrow.
I won't.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Alright, alright.
Goodnight.
We're gonna be okay, Abby, girl.
[gentle music]
So, I was thinking we
could go to Mayfields.
I heard they have a sale, so.
Katie, Katie, are you okay?
Sorry, what?
Is everything alright?
No, not really.
Okay, I can just pull over.
What's going on?
Everything, Lindsey.
Tell me.
My mom has cancer.
Stage four.
[Lindsey] What?
I'm trying to be
strong. [sniffles]
We just found out.
It's bad, but she said
she's going to fight.
I'm so sorry.
[Katie sobbing]
God, I can't even...
I don't know what to do.
I don't want her
to see me crying.
I'm so scared.
Hey, hey, it's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna be here for
you no matter what, okay?
Thank you.
How about we talk
about some happy stuff?
Okay.
Isn't that, what's his face
who's taking you to prom,
that guy?
Brett.
Brett, the
basketball guy, yeah.
He hasn't asked me yet,
but I was thinking it'd be fun
if just a bunch of
us went together.
Yeah, gonna be fine.
We can get a limo,
ride in style.
Love you, girl.
It's gonna be okay.
[Katie sniffling]
[gentle music]
So, you excited
for prom tonight?
Yeah.
Do you think it's weird,
Lindsey and I decided
not to go with any boys,
and just go with
our girlfriends?
Oh, yeah, it's so weird, Kat,
but better for your dad and I.
Now, we don't have to do
that whole crazy father
parent thing that dads do.
[doorbell ringing]
Here's the lovely
Miss Lindsey.
[Lindsey] Hi!
I'll be right back.
[Lindsey] Hello,
Sara, how are you doing?
I'm fighting hard.
It's good to see you.
[Lindsey] It's
good to see you too.
Why don't we go get ready?
[Lindsey] Okay, bye.
You girls have fun.
[Katie] Thank you, Mom.
[Lindsey] Sorry, I
left my makeup bag.
Actually, I'm
glad you're here.
Can you sit with
me for a minute?
Yeah, of course.
What's wrong?
I need your help, Lindsey.
I don't have long.
I'm struggling with it.
And I know that Katie is not
gonna do well when I'm gone.
I wanna do something for her,
that'll bring her comfort
you know, during important
times in her life.
Will you help me make a
video message for her?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
And don't tell her.
I'll entrust them to you,
and you just make
sure she gets them
when the time's right, okay?
Okay.
You go on, get ready.
I'll contact you to set
up a day and time soon.
I'll see you.
Bye.
- Tom?
- Yes, dear.
Can you bring me
my Bible, please?
Anything for you, my love.
You mind if I read with you?
No.
[melancholic music]
Oh, oh, thank you.
Katie sure did look
beautiful for the prom tonight,
didn't she?
Oh, she did.
There you go.
[Sara groaning]
Thank you, honey.
Huh, for what?
You know.
What, for loving you?
I love you, Tom.
And I know you're going
to do the right thing,
and raise our daughter right.
I'm not giving
up on you, Sara.
I know.
Thank you for this, Lindsey.
You're welcome, Sara.
I know how much this
is gonna mean to Katie.
Right.
It means everything to me too.
I don't have much
I can leave her,
but reminders of how
proud I am of her,
how much I love her,
bring me some peace.
She's gonna be here
in about 30 minutes,
so we should get started.
I'm just gonna put
some lipstick on.
Of course,
How does that look?
You look beautiful.
Okay, I'm ready when you are.
Katie, when you
receive this message,
I'll be with God and our
savior, Jesus Christ,
in heaven and free of pain.
I will always be watching
over you in spirit.
And today is such a special day.
You're graduating from
high school with honors,
and I'm so proud of you.
I want you to enjoy it,
and take tons of pictures with
your friends and your dad.
And enjoy that moment,
when you move your tassel,
and throw your hat in the air.
Going to UF is going
to be amazing for you,
and I hope that you have
a memorable college
experience, honey.
Katie, please try and
go to church regularly.
Read your Bible and pray.
I've left my Bible for you,
and I've had Pastor Mark notate
all my favorite Bible verses
for you to reference,
and give you strength.
I will always be with you.
I love you, Katie.
[Sara sniffling]
Okay, I got it.
Lindsey, I have
one more favor.
Yeah.
Anything.
I got a graduation
card for Katie.
Can you make sure she gets
it when she graduates?
Yeah, of course.
But you'll be able to
give it to her, right?
Appreciate it.
[Lindsey sniffling]
Thank you so much
for sharing, Rick,
and let's put that
in your memory book.
Hello, Lindsey.
- Hi.
- Hey, Lindsey.
I'm sorry I'm late.
[gentle music]
I was helping my friend's
mom with something.
No, that's okay.
Sometimes we have things to do.
Don't worry about it.
Well, it wouldn't be
the same without you.
I'm having a hard
time with this one.
Why?
It's my best friend's
mom, she's dying,
and I'm trying to do
something special for Katie
so she can have something
after she's gone.
Well, that's very
sweet of you to help her.
But are you okay?
I am, but I can't stop
thinking about my mom.
Sometimes, it's just like
I lost her all over again.
Well, I'm sure what
you're doing to help Katie
will bring her great comfort.
Well, I'm helping her mom
make a video message for her,
and I still have to edit it
with some of her mom's
favorite pictures at the end.
But, I don't know.
I like that.
I'd love to see
my brother again.
Or my baby.
Or my husband.
My father.
My mom.
You know, I think
we all have someone
whose voice we'd
love to hear again.
I think it's very sweet of
you to help your friend.
And you know, you could always
invite Katie here, you know?
She doesn't have to wait
until her mother passes
to get support.
I don't know.
She's not ready to deal
with her mom dying yet.
And Sara's still fighting.
Maybe she'll make it.
It's true.
We'll be praying.
Thanks.
Ava would you like
[phone ringing]
to continue with your story?
[Ava] Alright.
[John] Oh, why
don't you go ahead
and check that?
It doesn't happen often,
it might be important.
I'm so sorry.
I have to go.
No worries.
Where are you?
[Daniel sighs]
Dad, what happened?
You're scaring me.
Katie's mom passed away.
Oh, I need to go see her.
No, no, no, no, no,
listen, you can't.
They're at the hospital.
You're not gonna be able
to see them until tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
We finished just in time.
[melancholic music]
What, what did you, what?
What?
Her mom and I, we made
this video for Katie
for her graduation.
It's like, she knew.
That's gonna mean
the world to her.
It's like losing
Mom all over again.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I wanted to-
- Hey, Dad, I really, I
really need to be alone.
No, no, no just wait.
[Daniel sighs]
This is so beautiful, Mom.
I wonder what you
would have said to me.
But I know this will help Katie.
I just know.
I think Mom would
have liked the ceremony.
Yeah, I think so too.
Does the pain ever go away?
Honestly?
It does and it doesn't.
We'll never stop missing them.
I don't know how you did it.
It's so hard.
Time, remember
the good things.
[air whooshing]
Mom, do you think I can do it?
[Abby] You can do it, Lindsey.
I believe in you.
[water splashing]
[air whooshing]
[Lindsey] I guess
that sometimes helps.
We graduate in one month.
She wanted to be
here so bad for that.
Just one more month.
I know this probably
won't mean much right now,
but I truly believe
that she's here with us.
She's with God now.
[gentle music]
It's not the same.
Hey.
Just, I wonder why
she's not here yet.
She's never late.
I don't know.
Maybe call her?
I have a really bad
feeling about this,
like she's not okay.
I'm sure she's alright.
Just call her.
Okay, well.
[phone buzzing]
Oh, I bet that's her now.
Everything okay?
No, it's not.
Katie's not okay.
[Andrew] What happened?
She said she's not coming.
She said she can't stop crying.
It's gonna be alright.
[Lindsey] What should I do?
What can you do?
I mean, I can go give her
the message from her mom.
I know it's supposed to
be for the graduation,
but I think she needs it now.
You sure?
I mean, it is your party.
I don't know.
Why do bad things
happen to good people?
I just don't understand.
Hey, hey, hey, you know what?
You know what, listen,
I'll finish these
decorations up,
and you go see Katie.
Deliver that message to her.
Are you sure?
I'm sure, alright.
Parties come and go,
but best friends are forever.
Thank you.
[Lindsey sniffling]
[hopeful music]
Katie.
Lindsey.
Hey, it's gonna be okay.
I'm not so sure.
I'm not ready to
be without my mom.
I know, I know,
but she's with you.
How would you know?
I have something for you?
I was supposed to give it
to you after graduation,
but I don't think
your mom would mind
if I gave it to you now.
What do you mean, my mom?
It's from your mom.
She made it for you.
What is this about?
What is this?
Just trust me.
Watch it.
Katie, when you
receive this message,
I'll be with God and our
savior, Jesus Christ,
in heaven and free of pain.
I will always be watching
over you in spirit.
Today is such a special day.
You're graduating from
high school with honors,
and I'm so proud of you.
I want you to enjoy it.
I'm sorry, Katie.
I didn't mean to make
you cry like this.
- Take tons of pictures
- No.
[Sara] with your
friends and your dad.
No, it's just so beautiful.
And enjoy that moment.
[hopeful music]
I miss her so much.
[Sara] When you
move your tassel.
Thank you.
- Yeah.
- And throw your hat
in the air.
Kat, you should come to
group with me sometime.
Maybe.
Going to you UF,
- I'll just take it
- is going to be
- one day at a time.
- amazing for you.
Okay.
[Sara] Katie.
Oh, open your card.
[Sara] Please try and
go to church regularly.
Read your Bible.
I, I've left my Bible for you.
Thank you.
[Sara] And I've
had Pastor Mark,
I have to go and show
Dad, but thank you!
- notate all my favorite
- Thank you so much.
- readings,
- I really needed this.
[Sara] for you to reference
and give you strength.
Dad, Dad, look, you
have to come watch!
[Tom] What's happening?
Look, just come watch.
What is it?
Just watch, trust me.
[Sara] And I'm
so proud of you.
I want you to enjoy it.
That's...
Mom.
[Sara] Take tons of pictures.
She left it me
for my graduation.
She remembered me.
[Sara] And enjoy that moment,
when you move your tassel.
She's here with us.
[Sara] And throw
your hat in the air.
And she's with God
watching over us.
[Sara] Going to UF
- is going to be amazing
- She loves us.
[Sara] for you.
Katie.
[door knocking]
Hey, honey.
Hey, Dad.
Okay, I was just thinking,
you know that video that
Sara made for Katie?
Yeah.
I mean, it really helped her.
You know, I thought it was
gonna make her more sad,
but she was excited,
and she ran and told her dad.
Oh, I'm happy to hear that.
You know, I've
been researching,
and I wanna do this for
more people, you know?
Do you think I'm too young
to start a nonprofit?
No, no, I don't think so.
Let's do a little research.
With a little faith,
I'm pretty sure you're
the one that can do that.
Thanks, Dad.
[Daniel] Goodnight, alright?
Night.
[gentle music]
Hey, come sit by me.
Katie, it's good
to see you again.
Thank you.
[John] Katie, you're
Lindsey's friend?
Yeah, since elementary school.
[John] Oh, well it's great
to have you here with us.
Thank you.
I'm not sure I'm ready
to talk about it yet,
but thank you.
That's quite alright.
Thank you for being here.
Alright, everyone,
let's go ahead and get started.
You know, as always,
I like to just put a
little reminder out there,
about what we do
here in this group.
Our grief support group is
a place of healing and hope.
We like to remember our
loved ones out loud.
You know, we share stories,
we share memories good and bad,
and more importantly,
we support each other
and move through
the sadness of loss
to find the comfort
in knowing that our loved
ones remain in our heart,
and in our memories forever.
Now, before we get started,
I'd like to have our
guest introduce herself,
and then we'll go ahead
and share some stories.
Hi, everyone, I'm Katie.
I lost my mom to cancer.
I'm just taking it
one day at a time.
Well, thank you for
being here, Katie.
This is a great
place of healing,
and to know you're not
alone in this process.
Pastor, Katie's the one I
helped make the video for.
Oh, that's great.
We've heard great things.
How did it make you feel, Katie?
Honestly, until Lindsey
showed me that video,
I didn't know I was
going to be okay.
But seeing my mom and
hearing her voice,
I felt so close to
her, close to God.
I was angry until that moment.
I showed my dad right away,
and we laughed and cried
and pulled out the family
videos and photo albums.
And I mean, it helped us realize
that my mom was always
going to be with us.
I just wish Lindsey would've
gotten a video like that
from her mom.
[gentle music]
Me too.
[John] Yeah.
Well, I mean, I bet everyone
would like to hear a message
from their loved ones.
I think that's a
wonderful legacy to leave,
you know, for
anyone's loved one.
Yeah, I think getting a
message from your loved one
can be really comforting.
- The legacy of love.
- Yeah.
Pastor, I've been
thinking about this a lot,
and I think there's a way
that we can channel all of
our pain and our suffering,
into something that
can help others
who are grieving
like us one day.
What do you mean?
Well, I've been researching,
and I think a nonprofit
could be created.
Call it the Living
Legacy of Love.
We can reach out to those who
soon may be transitioning,
and help them leave messages
for their loved ones.
I'd be down.
You could help out
a lot of people.
- Yeah.
- I'd be game.
We should do it.
Wait, what?
Do you really think that
you can help these people?
What if you cause more pain?
Like, are you really
thinking this through?
I hadn't thought about that.
I just know what I
witnessed with Katie.
Yeah, I mean, I get
what you're saying,
but what if it actually
does provide comfort?
What if?
You don't know that.
I understand where
you're coming from,
but I think it could
bring more love,
and a reminder to
a deeper connection
with those who passed on.
Yeah, that's what
I was thinking.
[John] Well, I'd
like to know more.
Yeah.
I'm not saying I
don't approve of this,
but what if you're reminding
them of what they lost?
I can't speak
for other people,
but that message
gave me strength.
It gave me hope.
[Ava] I mean,
it's worth a shot.
Losing someone you love
is just too painful.
How do we start?
Well, we start where
there's the most need.
Hospice, hospitals,
assisted living, you know,
things like that.
Yeah, and we can, we can,
[Andrew And Lindsey]
We could make flyers!
Yeah, and we can let
them know it's free, and-
- That'd be so cool.
And I bet a lot of
people would help out.
[Lindsey] Yeah, totally.
I'm not crazy about the idea,
but I work at an
assisted living facility.
I can ask if you can
speak with the residents.
You can bring your flyers.
That would be so awesome.
I do know that
the community center
rents out camera equipment
from time to time.
I can talk to them.
And, you know, I mean, you know,
I think we should
do this, you know?
But we have to make sure
we do it the right way.
Okay, well, my
dad's already set up.
He's trying to get
the nonprofit rolling.
And it'd be great if
you all wanted to join.
I wanna help.
It's brought me so much comfort.
I want to.
You know, I'll go ahead
and get in contact
with your father.
That way we can kind of have
this thing all taken care of.
And you know, I'd like to
talk about it more in depth
after the, after group, okay?
Thank you.
[gentle music]
Pastor John, I have good news.
Well, you must
have with that smile.
Go ahead and tell me.
My dad says a
Living Legacy of Love
is ready to begin
helping people.
Well, that is good news.
Okay, well, let's
let everybody know
to get ready to
distribute these flyers,
and we can start
spreading the word.
Well here, what do
you think of this?
I love it.
Well, good.
Call Katie and Andy,
let them know the
flyers are ready,
and the shirts will
be done in a few days.
I will.
We need to put these everywhere.
I hope people will respond.
I believe they will.
I do too.
[gentle music]
Hey, Pastor John, I
put flyers everywhere.
Oh, good work, Andy.
Thank you.
Now what?
Do we do more flyers?
Guys, why hasn't
anyone called yet?
Maybe I'm wrong.
No, you're not wrong.
Ladies, have faith, you know?
We're meant to help people.
Just give it some time.
[phone ringing]
Hi, this is the
Living Legacy of Love.
[Woman] Hi, can
I talk to Lindsey?
This is Lindsey.
Well, Lindsey, I
just got your flyer,
and I would like
to record a message
for my daughter.
Yeah, of course.
What time do you
want us to come?
Wednesday at six?
Okay, we'll be there.
Thank you so much.
Guys, we just got
our first client.
- [groups applauding]
- Wow.
- Let's go!
- That's awesome.
Go!
[John] That's very awesome.
[men laughing]
Hey, Brian, nice to meet you.
[Brian] Hey, how
you doing, man?
- Good, good.
- Hey, Brian.
- Pleased to meet you.
- How are you guys?
- Good.
- Oh man, I've been better.
I love what you guys do here.
[John] Well, we're
glad you're here.
Thank you.
We'll give you a hand with-
- Oh, thank you, thank you.
Yeah, I got it, I got it.
Thank you, you're too kind.
[Brian groaning]
How you doing, man?
Oh, I've been a little better.
But, one day at a time.
But hey, I was wondering,
can you visit my
little brother for me?
He's gonna need someone
to teach him how
to ride his board.
- Yeah.
- You know,
it was only the beginning
before this happened.
Yeah, yeah, I got you.
What's his name?
His name is Jake.
Yeah, yeah, I'll
deliver it myself.
Oh, thank you, man, thank you.
Oh, one more thing?
Yeah, what is it?
50, actually.
[Andrew] What do you mean?
It's, it's for my dad.
[gentle music]
Yeah, there's a few notes
and whatnot for my mom,
but his birthday is next month.
[Lindsey] That's so sweet.
Thanks.
Hopefully he can get
some laughs out of it.
You know, we are pretty close,
and he hasn't been
taking this very well.
[Brian coughing]
Well, Brian, we're
actually just about ready.
How you doing?
Oh, I've been better,
but I'm gonna say,
this is, this is great.
I'm just thankful I
could even do this.
Hopefully it brings
me some peace.
Well, before we
all start crying,
Brian, you ready?
[Brian] [sighs]
Just tell me when.
[Ricky] Whenever you're
ready, the camera's rolling.
Alright.
So, Dad, I hear you're
turning 50 next month, man.
[Brian chuckles]
Oh, geez.
Looks like you're heading
over that hill, huh?
Look, I just, I just wanted
to wish you happy birthday.
Mom, give the old man a
hug from me, yeah? [laughs]
[Brian coughing]
Look, Mom, I'm sure when
you had children, you know,
this wasn't exactly what you
had in mind for our future
or anything.
But I just want to
let you know, [coughs]
even though my
time here is short,
I had a wonderful life.
I couldn't have asked
for a better family.
I'm always gonna be
watching over you, kid.
Because God has a plan.
So, remember these two things,
keep your faith,
and I will always love you.
Thank you for giving me
such a wonderful life.
[gentle music]
He was really sweet.
He was.
It must be hard for them,
not having their parents
know who they are.
I mean, at least
they have each other.
Yeah.
Me and Josh really needed
each other when my mom died.
I never realized just how much.
No, it isn't easy
what we're doing.
It, you know, it doesn't make
the pain and loss go away.
But I hope that it makes
them feel less alone.
Yeah, me too.
I can't believe we've
already helped 50 people.
Yeah, I know, it's crazy.
We've helped a
lot of people out.
Like, I was thinking people,
like, wouldn't like my idea,
but it's helped people so
much to see their loved ones,
- you know?
- Yeah, yeah,
I mean, we're impacting
a lot of lives.
A lot of people are gonna be
impacted by what we're doing.
And there's hundreds more.
It can never end.
We could do this forever.
Yeah.
I can't.
[gentle music]
Hey Linds?
[Lindsey] Yeah?
I was thinking maybe, maybe
we can go to dinner sometime?
- Hang out a bit.
- That'd be fun.
We can invite Katie.
Hey.
Hey, Ricky.
- Got my camera.
- What's up?
Yeah, we're good.
Yeah, but I was
thinking more me and you,
more of a me and you thing.
Not really all of us.
Like a date?
Yeah, if you want to.
- No, no, yeah, of course.
- I'm not trying
to pressure you but-
- Yeah, I can call Katie later.
Okay, yeah.
You ready to?
Let's get out of here.
Mikey, Michael, by
the time you see this,
you'll be heading off to
college, or you better be.
But I'll be proud of
you no matter what.
[Ricky] Cut.
One down, two to go.
You're strong, man.
It must be hard doing
this so many times.
Yeah, it is.
But hey, maybe we'll get
lucky and we won't need them.
They say I got some time.
I'm starting chemo.
But I knew that when I saw this,
that it was a great opportunity
to leave something
beautiful for my family,
just in case.
Well, why this park?
I've always been a runner.
It's the only way I can unwind.
I bring the kids with
me on shorter runs,
and we always stop here,
right at this bench.
We just, you know, talk
and laugh and goof off.
That's a great reason
to pick this place.
[Ricky] Ready for another?
Ready.
[Ricky] Camera's rolling.
I just want you to know
that you have always amazed
me with your brilliance,
your ability to solve problems.
You are such a kind soul.
I did a good job with you.
Ah, your mom helped a little.
What I'm saying is I love you.
And as you graduate,
know that I am with you and
watching over you always.
So, say your prayers,
and believe that great
things can happen,
because they can and they do.
And keep me in your life
by remembering me out loud.
Go with your mom to church.
Seek comfort in God,
because God and I, we got you.
I love you, kid.
You did good.
[gentle music]
I can't believe how many
people we've helped so far.
It's a blessing
for us and for them.
I feel like this is
my purpose, you know,
to help these people.
I don't-
[door knocking]
[Rebecca] Excuse me.
[John] Hi, yes,
how many we help you?
My name's Rebecca Alton.
I got a call from someone
that my mother left
something for me here?
Yes, hi, Rebecca.
Yeah, hi, I'm Lindsey.
We do have something from you,
actually from your mother.
My mom passed away a few
weeks ago, so how can you?
Well, Rebecca, we met
your mother two months ago,
and she left you a message.
Would you like to watch it now?
Please, it'll
bring you comfort.
She loves you.
I'm not sure that I
understand that, but okay.
My darling little girl,
when you watch this,
I will have moved on
to be with the Lord,
but I will always be with you
on the journey
through this life.
I want you to know, I love you,
I'm so proud of you,
and you will never be alone.
[Rebecca laughing]
I'm always be with
you in your heart.
I'm watching over you.
I love you, Mom.
I love you, Rebecca.
[car rumbling]
[gentle music]
[Andrew] Excuse me, sir.
What do you want?
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm from a Living
Legacy of Love.
Your son, Brian, sent me.
[Brian's Mom] Robert, Robert?
What's going on here?
This guy, he said
that Brian sent him.
Why?
Brian's dead, leave!
Jake, Jake, please.
Brian sent us for you.
Why?
He said you needed
a big brother figure.
He wanted me to teach you.
I don't need
anything from you.
Jake, please
just listen to me.
I understand what
you're going through.
I lost my brother too.
We just wanna share the message
that Brian left for you.
I can leave this here and go?
Come on, let's go.
Come inside.
Let's talk.
[gentle music]
I don't understand.
What is it that Brian did?
[Andrew] Here,
this is for you all.
What is this?
It's a message
from your son, Brian.
What does it say?
I can't say.
Just, just watch.
Go on.
Son, it's, go
ahead and hit play.
Looks like you're heading
over that hill, huh?
Look, I just, I just wanted
to wish you a happy birthday.
Mom, give the old man
a hug from me, yeah?
Even though my
time here is short,
I had a wonderful
life, and support,
and I want, I want you
to feel the same as well.
I hope this message
brings you comfort.
Even though I'd much rather
be here in my own body,
I'm always gonna be
watching over you, kid,
because God has a plan.
So, remember these two things,
keep your faith and I
will always love you.
Thank you for listening.
Jake, whenever you're ready,
just give me a call,
and I'll teach you
how to use that thing.
[Jake] Okay.
[Brian's Mom] Thank you.
Of course.
[Brian's Mom]
Thank you so much.
This was so beautiful.
You're welcome.
[gentle music]
[water splashing]
Seriously, don't
push me in again.
I'm sorry, I couldn't resist.
You're so bad.
Oh, yeah, how'd it go
with Brian's family?
I wish you were there,
but it went pretty well.
The mom seemed to be really
moved by the message.
You can, you can tell the
family's still hurt by it all.
But I think seeing Brian's
message brought them some hope.
So glad we're
doing this together.
It just feels right.
It does.
Yeah, me too, me too.
Hey, I'll give you
two seconds to swim.
[Andrew laughs]
[Josh] Dad, it's 24!
I knew you'd get it.
Very good.
[phone ringing]
What else do we have here?
Hello, this is Lindsey.
[Man] Hi, Lindsey.
We'd like to send
our news reporter,
to interview you
about a Legacy of Love.
Yes, yes, when?
[Man] How about
Monday at 6 p.m.?
Okay, I'll be
there, Monday at six.
Thank you so much.
Dad, Dad, I need to
tell you something!
[gentle music]
This message
really hit me hard.
So much heart.
Dean really did love his wife.
I know.
I'm glad he called
us to record him.
It doesn't get easier,
doing what we're doing,
making these videos,
but there's a genuine
comfort in knowing
that even a little bit
of their loved ones
are gonna come back to them
through what we're doing.
It's something for them
that will live on
through generations.
A living legacy of love.
[phone ringing]
So, that's where
the name comes from.
It all makes sense now.
Living Legacy of Love.
How can I help you?
Okay, yeah, we can come to you,
or you can come to us.
Okay, perfect.
What's the address?
Okay, Wednesday at six.
We'll be there.
Thank you.
Hey, you know what'd be nice?
If we invited everyone
we gave the videos to,
to come to group.
[Andrew] We could do that.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
We can prepare a
special invitation,
and bring it with the
messages when we deliver them.
I love it.
Here they come, let's go.
Fantastic, okay we'll do that.
Yeah.
[Interviewer] Are you the
Living Legacy of Love group?
Yeah.
Lindsey, the Living Legacy
of Love was your brain child.
Now, that you've helped
over a hundred people,
how do you feel?
Well, I'm at peace with it,
but there are hundreds
more and it will never end.
As long as we can keep bringing
love and peace to people,
then the Living Legacy of
Love will have a place.
It's never ending.
That's beautiful.
Lindsey, how was the name
Living Legacy of Love chosen?
Was there something
that inspired you?
Yeah.
Well, our loved ones are alive
when they record their message.
And their message
is a gift of love,
and it's a legacy
they leave for us.
I mean, it's priceless,
worth more than any material
thing could ever be.
It can be shared with the
loved ones left behind,
and even with future
family members.
It's a living legacy of love,
as it brings them back to us,
even if it's just for a
few moments at a time.
Yeah, the name just felt right.
I can see that.
It's so powerful to know
that when someone's
hurting so much,
that they can be touched
by a loved one's message.
What would you want us to take
away from your experiences
and path of giving that?
When my mom died,
I was so lost.
I didn't think my life
could have a purpose,
or a direction
without her in it.
But slowly I realized that
we all have a purpose,
and we're never alone.
God is with us always.
Our loved ones are
always with us.
And I really want people to know
that even though their
loved one has crossed over,
they're always with you,
and that love never dies.
I think she said
it perfectly, folks.
If you'd like to learn more
about Living Legacy of Love,
go to our website and you
can find their information
and their links.
[gentle music]
Alright, thank you so much.
Dad?
Yeah.
Don't you think
Grandpa's dementia
is getting kind of bad?
I mean...
Yeah, look, you know how
Grandma's in the hospital
for hip surgery,
well when she's not around, his
memory begins to fade and...
Yeah.
I don't know, maybe we
could play a video of her,
see if he remembers?
Yeah, do you have one?
Yeah, I have multiple.
[Daniel laughs]
We could play that one?
That was a good day.
Give it a shot.
Right.
Hey, Grandpa.
Hey, Pop.
Hey, we-
- Pop, Pop.
We have a video of Grandma.
[Josh] Oh, let me see.
You remember Grandma?
Grandma?
[Grandma] Okay, open it.
Where is she?
- Are you ready?
- She's in the hospital.
She's in the hospital
for her hip surgery.
[Grandma speaking faintly]
Hey, look, it's her.
- Really?
- Really.
Really?
[family laughing]
You know I love
wine and chocolate.
She is so beautiful.
I miss her.
She's, look at her.
Oh, well, what a beautiful,
her smile just radiates.
- Aw.
- I love her, oh.
Oh, look at that.
Oh my goodness, that's...
[Daniel] [laughs]
Yeah, that's the best.
You used to give
a fig, Grandpa.
[Jack] Oh my goodness.
I do love it.
We could be twinsies [laughs]
[gentle music]
Cookies, again?
Yeah!
You know I wouldn't
mind being with you.
I gotta go though.
My dad says we have to be home.
Linds, before we go,
could I talk to you
about something?
Yeah, of course,
babe, what's up?
I brought you something.
It's little, but it
means a lot to me.
Linds, you mean the world to me.
Since we met at the church,
you fully restored
faith in my life.
And not only in my life,
but we've helped so many
people restore their hope
and their love.
Most importantly, we
brought love back to them.
[air whooshing]
Mom, how do you know
when it's true love?
Well, you just know,
like your dad and I.
The right person will represent
hope and faith and love.
I wouldn't worry about that.
You look so beautiful.
[air whooshing]
I don't know what to say.
Linds, when you
wear this necklace,
I want you to be
reminded of three things.
The cross represents faith,
the anchor represents hope,
and the heart represents love,
which is everything
you are to me.
It's beautiful, Andrew.
You look great in it.
[Lindsey] Thank
you, I love it.
[Andrew] You're welcome.
[gentle music]
[Lindsey] I
would give anything
to have my mom here with me.
For a long time, I was
angry with my own pain.
Sometimes people grieving, well,
we get caught up
in our own pain,
so much so, we can't see
how serving others
in pain would help,
or why we should even do it.
I was just so angry
with life, with God,
but I grew in my faith.
I realized that helping
people also helped me heal.
For me, being able to help
people heal and have faith
has been the greatest
gift from God.
I know that a Living
Legacy of Love
has brought hope
to so many people,
and it will for years to come.
Never feel alone.
Know that God is
always with you.
[gentle music]
Hey, Mom.
First off, I wanna say thank you
for finally sharing that
secret lasagna recipe with me.
You made Tony and
my boys so happy.
Maybe you could make
it for them too.
I also, I just,
I wanna say that, that
being your daughter,
has been such an honor.
You've always been my hero.
I hope I've made you proud.
I'm gonna miss your hugs.
I'm gonna miss your hugs
and your weird mom jokes.
Please tell them to my boys.
Help them remember who I am.
And remember that
they're your family too.
Don't be sad and don't be alone.
I love you, Mom.
I love you.
Carla, this message means
that I'm watching over you.
Please don't be sad.
We had 20 beautiful years,
and three beautiful children.
I want you to laugh, feel joy,
and tell stories about me,
so that our children
and our grandchildren
would know how much I
love you and our family.
Until we meet again, I
love you, my sweet wife.
Thank you for so
many wonderful years.
Oh, honey, I know
you're hurting without me.
That's why I wanted to
try to do this, a tape,
while I still could.
I can't thank you enough
for being there for
me all these years,
and facing the big C with me.
[gentle music]
I know it wasn't easy.
How could it be?
I wasn't always myself
and I'm sorry for that.
It just wasn't fair.
But I want you to know
that you weren't just
the love of my life,
you were my life,
and you brought so much joy
and laughter into this family.
But now it's time for
you to live, baby,
and share that big, beautiful
light inside of yours,
with the world.
Hey, Megs, I know everyone
says this in the movies,
but if you are watching this,
I have left this world.
I wanted to leave you something
that not only would inspire
you, but comfort you.
And even though I'm not in
this world with you physically,
I will always be with you here.
No tears.
You have to keep
your chin up, okay?
You have to be strong
for Scotty, alright?
Promise me you'll fill
yours and Scotty's life
with as much love as
this world can give you.
In this life, the afterlife,
and in the lives to follow,
together forever.
Until we are together again,
I love you so much.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull