[AMBIENT SOUNDS - INSECTS]
WILL, KEEP THAT SHIRT CLEAN
FOR THE PICNIC, HEAR?
YES, MA'AM.
I WILL.
I MEAN IT!
YEAH, MA,
I PROMISE!
[SIGHS]
[WACK!]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
[AMBIENT SOUNDS]
[WACK!]
WATCH OUT!
WILL! YOU JUST RUINED
MARY'S SHOT!!!
OH, QUIT YOUR
WHININ', ROB.
IF I DIDN'T STOP IT, IT WOULDA
ROLLED DOWN TO THE CREEK.
STILL SHOULDA
LET IT GO.
WELL, IF IT WOULD MAKE
YOU HAPPIER...
EZEKIEL, DEAR, I THINK
EVERYTHING'S READY INSIDE.
EVERYBODY,
LET'S GO ON INSIDE.
IT'S TIME FOR
A LITTLE CULTURE.
WELL, GOTTA GO.
OH NO,
LITTLE BROTHER.
YOU'RE GETTIN'
THE BALL FIRST,
AND IF IT'S IN THE CREEK,
YOU'RE GOIN' IN AFTER IT.
I'M NOT GONNA
GET YOUR BALL.
YOU THREW IT,
YOU FETCH IT...
AND IF NOT,
I'LL TELL PA.
COME ON,
MARY.
[SPLASH!]
HEY, TOWN BOY.
HEY.
WHAT KINDA
BALL'S THET?
CROQUET.
CROW WHAT?
YOU, UH...YOU THROW IT
AT CROWS.
YA LIVE UP THERE?
YEAH.
TODAY'S THE SUNDAY
SCHOOL PICNIC.
WHERE DO YOU LIVE?
OVER ON MILL HILL.
I WAS BORN N' BRED
IN A SHOTGUN HOUSE.
HEY, SPANGLER,
YOU GOT A GAME TO PLAY
WE NEED
THAT BALL!
YOU PLAY BASEBALL?
WE'S PLAYIN' A GAME,
IF YOU'D LIKE TO PLAY.
YOU MEAN I CAN
PLAY WITH Y'ALL?
YOU KIN BE
THE UMPIRE.
I'M JUST KIDDIN'.
'COURSE YA KIN PLAY.
C'MON.
SINCE WE'S A LITTLE
SHORT OF PLAYERS TODAY,
I FOUND US
AN EXTRA.
THIS HERE'S -
WHAT'S YER NAME?
WILL.
WILL WRIGHT.
WELL, I'M CHICK UH,
THAT'S MY BROTHER PIKE.
AND THET'S WILLIS,
YOU'LL LEARN 'EM.
THIS HERE'S
A TOWN BOY.
SO?
HE KIN STILL
PLAY BASEBALL.
HEY, TOWN BOY, RECKON
YA KIN SLIDE INTO BASE
'THOUT TEARIN'
YER KNICKERS?
[CHUCKLES]
DON'T NO MIND PIKE.
HE'S JUST BEIN' ORN'RY.
[SNIFF, SNIFF]
CHICK... I DUNNO
AS I KIN PLAY BALL
WITH SOMEBODY THET
SMELLS LIKE SOAP.
[CHUCKLES]
YEAH,
THET'S MY BOY.
NOW LET'S
PLAY BALL!
TOWN BOY,
TOWN BOY'S GOT A GLOVE.
HAND IT OVER!
WILL, WE DON'T
HAVE MANY GLOVES.
SO WE LET TH' TEAM IN THE
FIELD USE WHAT WE HAVE.
C'MON.
HEY WILL,
YA WANT FIRST UP?
C'MON.
SEE WHAT
YOU KIN DO?
C'MON WILL,
C'MON WILL.
YOU GOT IT...
YOU'LL GET IT.
IT'S OKAY,
YOU'LL GET
THE NEXT ONE,
JUST MAKE HIM THROW
YOU A GOOD ONE.
C'MON WILL.
YOU'LL GET IT.
PIKE, WE'RE NOT GOING
TO HAVE THAT TRASH.
THET WAS JIST
A WASTE PITCH.
ALL PITCHERS
DO THAT.
YAY, WILL!
(CHEERING)
RUN, RUN, RUN, RUN,
RUN, RUN, RUN!
OH, MAN...!!
YAY, WILL!
THET'LL SHOW 'EM!
I RECKON YOU
ARE A BALL PLAYER.
OFF WITH YOUR HAT
AS THE FLAG GOES BY!
AND LET THE HEART
HAVE ITS SAY:
YOU'RE MAN ENOUGH
FOR THE TEAR IN YOUR EYE
THAT YOU WILL NEVER
WIPE AWAY.
OFF WITH YOUR HAT
AS THE FLAG GOES BY!
[WHISPERS]
I DON'T SEE WILL.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE HE IS?
AND UNCOVER
THE YOUNGSTER'S HEAD;
TEACH HIM TO HOLD IT
HOLY AND HIGH
IN THE SAKE OF
ITS SACRED DEAD.
[CLAPPING]
(CHEERING)
YEAH, GO, GO, GO...
THET'S OKAY.
WE STILL GOT THE LEAD.
HEY PIKE,
IT'S YER LAST AT BAT.
I KNOW IT,
CHICKEN HEAD.
JIST SHUT UP
N' PITCH.
PIKE'S UP FIRST THIS
INNING, ISN'T HE?
YEAH.
TRY PITCHIN' THIS TO HIM
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
YOU KNOW, FOR A TOWN BOY YOU
GOT SOME PRETTY GOOD IDEAS.
UGH!
LET ME SEE
THAT BALL!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU DID TOWN BOY,
BUT I'LL GIT YOU
FOR THET.
JIST WAIT AN'
SEE IF I DON'T.
ALRIGHT, TWO OUTS TO GO.
WHO'S UP?
[VIOLIN MUSIC]
I'M CONCERNED
ABOUT WILL.
ROBERT,
DO YOU KNOW
WHERE WILL IS?
LAST TIME I SAW HIM,
HE WAS HEADIN' DOWN
THE HILL TOWARD THE CREEK.
WHEN WAS THAT?
WHEN YOU
CALLED US IN.
YES, WE'S THE
SLUGGERS TODAY!
LET'S GO COOL OFF!
YAY!
[LAUGHTER, SPLASHING, CHEERS]
WILL, C'MON,
TAKE A TURN.
WILLIAM EDWARD WRIGHT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET ON HOME!
THE REST OF YOU BOYS,
GET ON HOME, TOO,
IF YOU HAVE ONE.
WE AIN'T
HURTIN' NOTHIN'.
WILLIAM, I'LL MEET
YOU AT THE SHED.
(MOCKING EZEKIEL)
MEET YOU AT THE SHED.
HA! SERVES YA RIGHT,
TOWN BOY.
YOU AN' YER OL' MAN OUGHT TO
STAY ON YER SIDE O' TH' RIVER.
TOWNIES.
SON...
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN TOLD
ABOUT THE BOYS THAT LIVE
ON THAT SIDE OF TOWN?
EVER SINCE THE TEXTILE MILL
CAME TO NEWTON
THERE'S BEEN AN UNWRITTEN CODE
OF SORTS.
WE DON'T INTERFERE
IN THEIR DOINGS
AND THEY DON'T
INTERFERE IN OURS.
NOW, I'M SURE THERE ARE SOME
FINE FOLKS OVER THERE,
BUT WE DON'T MIX
WITH THEM.
SORRY I SNUCK
OFF, PA.
BUT WHAT'S WRONG-
SORRY YOU DID IT?
OR THAT YOU GOT CAUGHT?
BOTH I GUESS.
BUT WHY CAN'T WE-
NEVER MIND.
YOU DID WRONG,
AND YOU'LL BE PUNISHED.
STAY PUT.
I'M NOT GOING TO SWITCH
YOU OVER THIS.
BUT I DO WANT YOU
TO LEARN A LESSON
ABOUT GOING
YOUR OWN WAY.
THERE'LL BE NO BASEBALL
FOR A WEEK!
NO BALL?
BUT, PA-
NO ARGUMENTS!
THIS IS MY LAST WORD.
IT'S TIME YOU LEARN THAT
YOU CAN'T JUST DO
WHATEVER COMES
TO YOUR MIND.
BUT-
NO MORE!
THERE ARE NO STAINS ON
THE PAGES OF TOMORROW.
AND NO BASEBALL NEITHER.
HEY, TOWN BOY!
WHACHA DOIN'
UP HERE?
I WANNA SEE IF YE KIN
COME PLAY BASEBALL AGIN.
NOT ALLOWED TO -
FOR A WEEK.
CAIN'T YA JIST
LIKE SNEAK OFF?
TELL 'EM YER GOIN' FISHIN'
OR SOMETHIN'?
THET'S WHAT
I DO.
I DON'T WANT TO GET IN
WORSE TROUBLE WITH MY PA.
HOW ABOUT SATURDAY?
CAN YOU
COME SATURDAY?
YEAH, SATURDAY
WILL BE A WEEK.
ALRIGHT, I'LL MEET
YOU AT THE TRESTLE.
(MOM CALLING OUT)
WILL!
RISE AND SHINE!
HONEY,
YOU KNOW IT'S SATURDAY?
DON'T WAIT
DINNER ON ME, MA!
HEY, TOWN BOY.
YOU READY TO PLAY
SOME BASEBALL?
SURE!
CAN I CARRY
YOUR GLOVE?
OKAY.
[WACK!]
DO WE GET TO PLAY
ON THIS FIELD?
SINCE THE MILL WORKERS
WORK UNTIL NOON,
WE CAN PLAY IN
THE MORNING.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO DO
TO GET ON THE MILL TEAM?
FIRST, YOU GOTTA WORK
FOR THE MILL.
THEN, I'VE
GOT TIME.
FER WHAT?
FOR THAT.
THAT'S WHAT.
[WACK!]
C'MON CHICK, YOU'RE HANDIN' IT
TO HIM ON A SILVER PLATTER.
BE QUIET PIKE, I'M GIVIN'
HIM MY GOOD STUFF.
YOU READY, WILL?
[WACK!]
DON'T LET 'IM
FOOL YA, SCOOP.
HE'S BEEN HITTIN' MY
BROTHER'S STUFF FER YEARS.
YOU THINK YOU KIN
DO ANY BETTER?
WATCH ME.
(SCOOP)
OKAY, CHICK.
LET'S SEE WHAT HE CAN DO
WITH SOMEBODY ELSE.
[WACK!]
OKAY,
BRING IT ON IN.
WILL WRIGHT,
HUH.
OKAY, I'LL GIVE
YOU A CHANCE.
BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO PROVE
YOURSELF IN THE REAL GAMES.
FIRST, I NEED YOU TO GO TO THE
MILL AND SIGN UP FOR WORK.
PRACTICE AFTER WORK, GAMES
ARE ON SATURDAY AFTERNOONS.
WHAT DO YA SAY?
DO BASEBALL SCOUTS COME DOWN
TO WATCH MILL GAMES?
YOU'RE ONE OF
THOSE, HUH?
FIGURES.
YEAH, YOU MAKE
ENOUGH NOISE.
SCOUTS'LL COME DOWN FROM
CHARLOTTE LOOKIN' FOR NEW BLOOD.
BUT YER GONNA HAVE TO
PROVE YOURSELF FIRST.
ARE YA IN?
YES, SIR.
I AM.
POLITE, I LIKE THAT.
SHOW UP AT THE MILL
GATE MONDAY MORNIN'.
CHICK'LL SHOW YOU
WHERE TO GO.
NOW WE'RE TALKIN'.
I'LL TAKE CARE
OF HIM.
(PIKE)HEY,
TOWN BOY.
SEE WHO
HITS FARTHEST?
MILL VERSUS
TOWN.
YEAH, OKAY.
(PIKE) HEY GINNIE...
WATCH THIS.
[WACK!]
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT,
LOOKS LIKE MILL BEATS TOWN.
YOU AIN'T NEVER
GONNA MAKE THE CUT.
HEY THERE.
THANKS
SWEETHEART.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
WELL, WHO'S
THE NEW FACE?
NAME'S WILL -
WILL WRIGHT.
I'M DARLENE.
NICE TO
MEET YOU.
YOU WANNA
CELEBRATE?
I'D BETTER NOT.
UH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE WON'T TELL.
I GOTTA
GET HOME.
THEY MIGHT
SMELL IT.
GOTTA LOOSEN THAT
ONE'S STRAPS A MITE.
DON'T YOU WORRY
NONE 'BOUT THET.
(CHICK) LISTEN, Y'AIN'T
NEVER GONNA MAKE IT,
IF'N YA DON'T LEAST TRY
T' FIT IN, TOWN BOY.
(WILL) YOU KNOW
ALCOHOL'S ILLEGAL.
(CHICK) THEY'S TONS
A' FOLK AT THE MILL
JUST AS DRY AN'
AS TEETOTALIN' AS YOU.
BUT BASEBALL AN' BOOZE JIST
SORTA GO TOGETHER -
KINDA LIKE CHEWIN' - BOYS
JIST LIKE T' HAVE A GOOD TIME.
(WILL)
AND THE GIRLS TOO?
(CHICK) NO, NOW, DARLENE'S JIST
FRIENDLY T' BALL PLAYERS.
JIST A BIG FAN.
SHE DON'T MEAN NUTHIN'.
(WILL)
I DON'T KNOW.
MY PA WOULD
KEEL RIGHT OVER
IF HE'S FIGURIN'
I'M BECOMIN' A LINTHEAD.
NO OFFENSE.
ANY TOWN BOY BUT
YOU EVER SAID THET
HE'D BE PICKIN' HIS
TEETH OUT A' TH' DIRT.
LISTEN, WILL, YA ONLY MET
TH' ROWDIEST THEY IS.
IF YA WANT T' MEET
SOME REAL MILL FOLK,
I'LL TAKE YA BY
MY HOUSE SOMETIME
AN' T' INTRODUCE
YA TO MA, OKAY.
ALRIGHT, BUT IF I DON'T MAKE IT,
FIGURE MY PA KILLED ME.
[CHICK LAUGHS]
[HEARS A FOOTSTEP]
WILLIAM?
EVENIN', PA.
SURE IS A BEAUTIFUL
NIGHT OUT TONIGHT.
WHERE'VE
YOU BEEN?
SEEIN' ABOUT
A JOB.
AFTER DARK?
IT WAS OVER
ON MILL HILL.
ONE YEAR.
ONE YEAR DOWN AT WESLEYAN IS ALL
WE'VE ASKED FROM YOU, WILLIAM.
PA! COLLEGE IS
FINE FOR ROB.
HE'S STUDYIN'
FOR THE MINISTRY.
I'M NO PREACHER,
AND I'M NEVER GONNA BE.
SO WHY GO?
VERY WELL...
WHAT IS THIS "JOB?"
BASEBALL -
WITH THE NEWTON MILL TEAM.
YOU WOULD JOIN A MILL
FOR A FOOLISH GAME?
IT'S GOOD,
HONEST WORK.
YOUR FATHER KNOWS A THING OR TWO
ABOUT BASEBALL ON MILL HILL.
I HAPPEN TO KNOW THAT
BOOTLEG WHISKEY
FLOWS LIKE WATER EVERY
SATURDAY NIGHT.
NOW ARE YOU GOING TO DENY THAT
BASEBALL AND BOOZE GO TOGETHER?
NO, SIR, I
CAN'T DENY THAT.
WILLIAM, I-
I ALREADY TURNED IT
DOWN FLAT!!!
WELL, IT'S GOOD
TO HEAR THAT.
PA!
BEING AROUND PLAYERS WHO DRINK
WILL NOT MAKE ME A DRUNK!
I'VE SEEN WHAT SPIRITS
CAN DO TO A MAN
AND I NEVER WANT TO SEE IT
AGAIN - NOT IN MY FAMILY.
WILLIAM, YOU'VE HEARD
US TALK ABOUT UNCLE FRANK?
SURE.
HE DIED IN THE
GREAT WAR, RIGHT?
NO, HE DIDN'T
DIE IN THE WAR.
HE DRANK HIMSELF
TO DEATH.
FINALLY HUNG HIMSELF
UP IN THE ATTIC.
WILLIAM, I HAD TO HELP
CUT HIM DOWN.
PA, I'M SORRY.
I TRULY HOPED I'D NEVER HAVE
TO TELL YOU THE WHOLE STORY.
PA, I'M STRONG
ENOUGH TO SAY NO.
YOU'D BE SURPRISED HOW EASY
IT MIGHT BE AFTER A WHILE,
JUST TO TASTE IT, WHEN EVERYBODY
ELSE AROUND YOU IS DOING IT.
NOT IF YOU
KNOW BETTER.
I DON'T WANT
TO HEAR ANY MORE.
PA, WE'RE NOT
DONE TALKING!
WHAT MORE
IS THERE TO SAY?
YOUR PARENTS ARE OPPOSED TO YOU
PLAYING BASEBALL AT A MILL.
PA, DON'T YOU
SEE?
I WANT THIS MORE THAN
ANYTHING I'VE EVER WANTED.
LIFE IS NOT ABOUT
GETTING WHAT YOU WANT.
IT'S NOT ABOUT
BEING MISERABLE!
I GOTTA DO THIS!
THIS IS MY
FINAL WORD.
FINE...
I'LL PACK TO LEAVE
TONIGHT, THEN!
WILL...YOU CAN'T
GO LIKE THIS.
MOM... IT'S ONLY A COUPLE
OF MILES AWAY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY MONEY?
A LITTLE I'VE SAVED UP.
SON, WILL YOU DO
ONE THING FOR ME?
WHAT IS IT?
YEARS AGO
I MADE A PLEDGE
THAT I'D RAISE MY FAMILY
TO ABSTAIN FROM ALCOHOL.
MA, I'M NOT GONNA START DRINKING
'CAUSE I'M PLAYIN' BALL.
IT'S PROHIBITION,
FOR CRYIN' OUT LOUD!
WILL YOU JUST LOOK ME IN
THE EYE AND PROMISE ME
THAT YOU WILL NOT
TAKE A DRINK?
MA, IF IT'LL MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER, I PROMISE.
BUT STOP WORRYING
ABOUT ME SO MUCH.
I'M GONNA BE FINE.
HERE, TAKE THIS.
I'LL PRAY FOR
YOU EVERY DAY.
THANKS, MA.
I LOVE YOU,
SON.
TOO.
AND I'M GONNA
MAKE YOU PROUD.
YOU'LL SEE.
GOOD MORNIN'!
CHICK?
WELL, IT AIN'T YER
GUARDIAN ANGEL.
HOW'D YA FIND ME?
I WEREN'T PA'TICULAR
LOOKIN' FER YA.
I THOUGHT 'YAZ COMIN'
THIS AFTE'NOON?
KINDA A LONG STORY.
WHAT'RE YOU DOIN'?
C'MON.
WHAT DO
YA THINK?
SURE IS A LONG
WAY DOWN.
YOU KNOW UP THAT WAY
'BOUT SIX HUNDRED MILES
GOT "THE HOUSE
THET RUTH BUILT."
AN' UP OVER THET WAY'S
GOT COMISKEY PARK-
"BASEBALL PALACE
OF TH' WORLD."
I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING-
ONE DAY THIS OLD MILL HAND'S
GONNA BE UP THERE
STRIKIN' OUT THE BIG BOYS.
WHY'S YOUR BROTHER
HATE ME?
WILL, YOU'VE BEEN BORN
WITH EVERYTHIN' HE NEVER HAD.
NOW YER GETTIN' TH' ONE THANG
HE HAD THAT YOU DIDN'T.
PIKE AIN'T GONNA
GO EASY ON YA.
HEY, HOW 'BOUT YA
COME BY OUR HOUSE
THIS AFTERNOON FOR
SUNDAY DINNER?
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE I'D BETTER
EAT AT THE BOARDING HOUSE.
SO WHAT, NOW YOU'RE TOO GOOD
TO EAT WITH PLAIN OLD MILL FOLK?
NO. NO, IT'S JUST -
I'LL FEEL KINDA OUT OF PLACE.
WELL, THEY'S ONLY ONE WAY
FER YOU TO CHANGE THET.
YOU JIST HAVE TO BECOME
ONE OF US.
AND YA KIN
START RIGHT NOW.
"FOR WHAT WE
ARE ABOUT TO RECEIVE
MAY THE LORD MAKE US
TRULY GRATEFUL. AMEN."
"A-MEN AND A-WOMEN"
TOO.
GIMME A BISCUIT.
HEY, MA, LOOK
WHAT I BRUNG!
THIS HERE IS WILL.
[CLANK!]
OH, HEY, PIKE.
DIDN'T KNOW YOU
WAS HERE.
BO, MOVE ON OVER AN' MAKE
A PLACE FOR ONE MORE.
HOPE YOU LIKE
CHICKEN 'N DUMPLIN'S.
WELL, I'VE NEVER HAD 'EM
BEFORE, BUT I'M SURE I WILL.
THANK YOU,
MA'AM.
WELL, I WISH MY BOYS WOULD
LEARN THEIR MANNERS LIKE YOU.
(MA) PAY
ATTENTION, BOYS.
WHAT'S HE
DOIN' HERE?
PIKE, HE'S GONNA BE
PART OF OUR TEAM.
I AIN'T EATIN' IN THE SAME
HOUSE WITH NO TOWNIE.
[CLANK!]
YOU GOT
A LOTTA GALL.
PIKE, YOU SIT DOWN,
AND I MEAN NOW!
I'M BO.
PLEASED TO MEET YOU BO.
I'M WILL.
YOU KIN HAVE MINE.
UH, BO.
THAT'S VERY KIND.
BUT I THINK OUR GUEST WOULD
APPRECIATE A WHOLE BISCUIT.
THANK YOU,
BO.
THE DUMPLINGS
ARE GREAT.
I THINK I FOUND
A NEW FAVORITE.
WELL, I'M GLAD YOU
LIKE 'EM.
(MA) ARE YOU STARTIN' AT
THE MILL IN THE MORNIN'?
I RECKON HE IS.
WELL, MRS. BREWSTER WILL
FEED YOU SOME SUPPER,
BUT SHE EXPECTS A DAYS
NOTICE TO MAKE YA LUNCH.
NOW, I HAVE SOME PRESERVES
FOR YOUR BISCUITS...
AND HOW MANY BISCUITS
WOULD YOU LIKE?
RECKON THAT
WILL DO.
I GUESS I DIDN'T
THINK ABOUT TOMORROW.
THANK YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN VERY KIND.
SOON AS WE'RE
DONE HERE,
I'LL TAKE YOU BY MIZ BREWSTER'S
BOARDING HOUSE.
[CAR ENGINE]
GOOD AFTERNOON,
MIZ BREWSTER.
CHARLES.
THIS HERE
IS MY FRIEND, WILL.
HE'S GONNA BE STARTIN'
AT THE MILL IN THE MORNIN'
AND WE'S WONDERIN' IF YOU
HAD AN EXTRA ROOM AVAILABLE.
I DO INDEED.
A NICE QUIET ROOM.
GLAD TO MEET YOU,
WILL.
NOW, IF YOU'LL
JUST FOLLOW ME.
LIKE I TOLD YA,
IT'S A NICE, QUIET ROOM,
AWAY FROM THAT STREET.
HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT THERE ARE DAYS
WHEN SIX OR EVEN SEVEN
AUTOMOBILES GO BY OUT THERE.
CLEAN TOWELS
ARE RIGHT HERE.
BATHROOMS AT THE END
OF THE HALL.
MAKE SURE YOU JIGGLE
THE TOILET CHAIN
TO MAKE THE TOILET
STOP RUNNIN'.
HERE IT IS.
THINK IT'LL SUIT YA?
YES, MA'AM.
I THINK IT WILL BE FINE.
TWO DOLLARS A WEEK.
GLAD TO HAVE YA.
JUST MAKE YOURSELF
AT HOME.
THANK YOU,
MIZ BREWSTER.
WELL, YOU'RE IN.
I'LL SEE YA FIRST THING TOMORRA
MORNIN' AT TH' MAIN ENTRANCE
AND A BASEBALL PRACTICE
RIGHT AFTER WORK.
THANKS, CHICK.
SEE YA.
[MUSIC]
[TRUCK HORN]
THIS HERE
IS YOUR FLOOR.
HEY, MR. SMITH.
THIS HERE
IS WILL WRIGHT.
PLEASED TO MEET YA.
I'M YER FLOOR BOSS.
BUT I'M GONNA LET CHICK
HERE SHOW YOU AROUND TODAY.
HEAR YOU CAN HIT
A BASEBALL A LONG WAY.
I RECKON.
WELL, WE'RE GLAD
TO HAVE YA.
MAYBE WE CAN BEAT THAT
ANDERSON TEAM THIS YEAR.
CERTAINLY HOPE SO.
[AMBIENT MACHINE SOUNDS]
HERE'S YOUR WRENCH
AND YOUR SCREW DRIVER.
WHAT DO I DO
WITH 'EM?
CRANK BOLTS AND
TURN SCREWS, IDIOT!
IGNORE HIM.
YOU'RE A "O"FFICIAL
MECHANIC NOW.
SO IF SOMEONE HOLLERS
THEIR MACHINE IS STUCK,
YOU JIST GO FIX IT.
BUT I DON'T
KNOW ABOUT-
YOU DON'T NEED
TO KNOW NOTHING.
YOU JIST CHECK ALL THE NUTS
AND BOLTS ON THE STUCK LOOM
AND IF'N THEY'S ALL TIGHT,
THEN YOU GO GIT
A REAL MECHANIC.
SIT DOWN.
I'M GONNA TEACH YA HOW
TA MAKE A LITTLE EXTRA MONEY
WITH A DECK OF CARDS.
YOU SURE THIS IS
AN HONEST DAY'S WORK?
YOU'RE TOO GREEN TO SPIT,
TOWN BOY.
[AMBIENT MACHINE SOUNDS]
OH! I'M SORRY.
I - DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
I SAW YOU - AT THE
TRYOUTS THE OTHER DAY.
OH?
I'M NEW HERE.
I JUST SIGNED ON
TO PLAY BALL.
SO I GATHERED.
DO YOU WORK
AT THE MILL?
IN THE OFFICE.
I'M A SECRETARY.
YOU LIKE MUSIC?
I THINK IT'S ONE OF GOD'S
GREATEST GIFTS TO US.
MY MOM MADE ME TAKE PIANO
WHEN I WAS YOUNGER.
YOU PLAY?
I HAVEN'T KEPT UP
WITH IT.
TOO BAD.
SAY, I HAVEN'T
INTRODUCED MYSELF.
WILL WRIGHT.
GINNIE.
AND ACTUALLY, I WAS JUST
TALKIN' TO MY FRIEND CHICK
THAT WE SHOULD FIND
SOMETHING TO DO AFTER WORK.
AND HERE'S
THIS CONCERT!
SO YOU'LL COME?
COURSE WE'LL BE THERE!
GOOD.
OH, YOU'VE
DONE IT NOW.
PIKE'S SWEET
ON THET GIRL.
YEA, BUT IS SHE
SWEET ON HIM?
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
HI WILL!
HEY, BO.
YOU BEEN PRACTICING
YOUR BASEBALL SKILLS?
YEAH!
YEAH?
ALRIGHT, WHY DON'T
YOU COME WITH US.
[RAGTIME PIANO MUSIC]
[CHEERING]
HEY ROOKIE,
SHOW US WHACHA GOT.
GIVE US ONE OF THEM
LONG BALLS, HUH?
YES SIR.
[CHEERING]
HIT THAT BALL.
YOU CAN DO IT.
C'MON WILL.
HIT IT OUTTA HERE.
(UMPIRE) STRIKE ONE.
(CROWD) THAT'S OKAY.
C'MON, YOU CAN DO IT.
YOU'LL GET THE NEXT ONE.
(SCOOP) LET'S HAVE SOME
PEP OUT THERE.
STRIKE TWO.
(CROWD) C'MON MAKE 'EM
PITCH TO YOU.
STRIKE THREE,
YOU'RE OUT.
(CROWD)
YOU'LL GET THE NEXT ONE.
[CHEERING]
(SCOOP)
LET'S GO BOYS.
COME ON, LET'S SEE
SOME PEP OUT THERE.
YOU'RE LIKE A BUNCH
OF DEAD FISH.
SPANGLER, YOU KNOW
WHAT I TOLD YA.
STRIKE ONE.
[CHEERING]
[WACK!]
UHHH, WHAT ARE YA THINKIN'?
UGH!
YOU KNOW
WHAT I THINK?
I THINK THAT WAS THE WORST
FIRST GAME I EVER SAW!
AIN'T GONNA HAPPEN
NO MORE! YA HEAR?
MAYBE WE GOT A BAD LUCK CHARM
SPLITTIN' TH' TEAM UP, SCOOP.
SPANGLER, YOU WORRY ABOUT
YOUR OWN SORRY GAME
N' KEEP YOUR
TRAP SHUT.
ALL OF YA BAD
LUCK TODAY.
CLEAR ON OUT.
[THUD!]
I RECKON YOU GOIN' TO BE
JOININ' US FER A DRINK?
I DON'T
GUESS I AM.
MAYBE YOU ALL COULD TAKE
A LESSON FROM THE ROOKIE
AND SPEND SOME TIME THINKIN'
'BOUT WHAT JUST HAPPENED.
HE'S GOT A LOT MORE T' THINK
ABOUT THAN THE REST OF US.
[WACK!]
YOU GOT THE MAKIN'S
OF A NATURAL HITTER.
VERY FUNNY.
WHO ARE YOU?
JUST A FAN.
CAN I SHOW
YOU SOMETHIN'?
I'VE WATCHED EVERY BIG STICK
COME THROUGH HERE -
FROM SHOELESS JOE JACKSON
ALL THE WAY DOWN.
AND THEY ALL HAVE
ONE LITTLE SECRET.
I SUPPOSE YOU'RE
GONNA TELL ME.
IT'S ALL ABOUT
A LEVEL SWING.
RIGHT NOW YOU'RE SWINGIN'
UP AT THE BALL.
YOU'VE GOTTA LEVEL OUT SO
WHEN YOU STRIKE THE BALL
IT'S LIKE A HAMMER
HITTIN' A NAIL.
AND THIS IS
THE HAMMER.
MADE IT MYSELF.
IT'S THE BEST BATTING
COACH I'VE SEEN.
C'MON.
TAKES A LITTLE BIT
OF PRACTICE BUT...
[WACK!]
IT'LL FLATTEN OUT
YOUR SWING.
AND THE WEIGHT'LL
INCREASE YOUR BAT SPEED.
I NEED SOMETHIN'.
GIVE
IT A TRY.
[WACK!]
LIKE I SAID, TAKES
A LITTLE BIT A' PRACTICE.
I CAN SEE.
YOU GOT ANY GOOD IDEAS
FOR READING A CURVE BALL?
NEVER SWING AT A PITCH
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN.
WATCH HIS RELEASE UNTIL
YOU KNOW WHAT HE'S THROWIN'
AS HE LETS IT GO.
AND JIST GOTTA HANG BACK AND
WAIT 'TIL IT DROPS INTO ZONE.
EASY TO SAY,
NOT QUITE SO EASY TO DO.
YOU GOT AN ANSWER
FOR EVERYTHING.
BEEN AROUND A WHILE.
KEEP THE HAMMER
AS LONG AS YOU LIKE.
HERE'S YOUR
BUCKET OF NAILS.
[WACK!]
[SIGHS]
[CHURCH BELL RINGING]
I DON'T REALLY HAVE
TO TAKE A BATH, DO I?
YOU SAID
YOU WOULD.
YOU AGREED TO PAY ME
TWO BITS TO COME.
BATH'S EXTRA.
I'LL GIVE YOU FOUR BITS
JUST TO BATHE AND COME ON.
UP FRONT.
ONE OF OUR FAVORITES,
BICYCLE BUILT FOR TWO.
[BAND PLAYS]
(CLAPPING)
JOHN PHILLIP SOUSA'S,
KING COTTON.
[BAND PLAYS]
[PIANO MUSIC]
IT'S THE FIRST GOOD RAIN
WE'VE HAD IN A WHILE.
YEP.
WE CAME TO NEWTON FROM A MILL IN
CHATTANOOGA YEAR BEFORE LAST.
DID YOU
GROW UP HERE?
YEAH, OVER ON
THE TOWN SIDE.
IT'S A PRETTY
LITTLE PLACE.
IT IS.
I WON'T BE HERE FOR LONG
IF I CAN JUST CATCH THE EYE
OF THE CHARLOTTE
SPINNERS SCOUT.
SAY, HOW DO YOU PLAY AND
TALK AT THE SAME TIME?
WELL, YOU GET USED TO IT
AFTER A WHILE.
SOMEONE'S ALWAYS TALKING
IN THIS EAR
WHILE I'M TRYING
TO LISTEN WITH THE OTHER
WHEN I PLAY THE PIANO
FOR THE MILL CHURCH.
HAVE YOU BEEN?
NO, NOT YET.
I'M SURE I WILL.
WHY DON'T YOU PLAY
SOMETHING FOR ME.
NO, NO, LIKE I SAID
IT'S BEEN YEARS.
NOW I CAN TELL YOU
HAVE NICE HANDS -
FOR PLAYIN' THE PIANO
AND FOR PLAYIN' BASEBALL.
NO, IT WOULD NOT
BE A GOOD IDEA.
DO YOU LIKE
BASEBALL?
NOT MUCH.
BUT DADDY WILL
NEVER MISS A GAME.
SO YOU THINK YOU
COULD COME WATCH US
AT THE ANDERSON GAME
THIS WEEK?
I WILL - IF YOU'LL COME
TO VISIT AT OUR CHURCH.
YOU COULD BRING IMOGENE ALONG
TO KEEP CHICK COMPANY.
TIME TO GIT GOIN',
HUH WILL?
YEAH, I
RECKON.
SO, WE'LL SEE
YOU SATURDAY!
OKAY.
(RADIO ANNOUNCER) WELL, LADIES
AND GENTLEMEN,
THIS HAS BEEN A
HARD FOUGHT GAME.
HERE WE ARE IN THE TOP
OF THE NINTH INNING
AND THE SCORE IS STILL TIED
AT ONE RUN APIECE.
SLOAN IS STILL ON THE MOUND
FOR ANDERSON.
HE'S PITCHED
A GREAT GAME TODAY.
AND NOW THE STRONG HORSE
OF THE NEWTON TEAM,
THEIR RETURNING HERO,
APPROACHES THE PLATE.
PIKE SPANGLER IS NEWTON'S
POWER MAN IN THE BATTER'S BOX.
SLOAN IS READY NOW.
THERE'S A WIND UP
AND THE PITCH...
STRIKE.
STRIKE ONE ON SPANGLER.
BALL.
ONE AND ONE
THE COUNT
AS SPANGLER STEPS
BACK UP TO THE PLATE.
HIS KID BROTHER CHICK,
NEWTON'S STARTING PITCHER,
SCORED THE TEAM'S
ONLY RUN.
HERE'S THE NEXT PITCH.
HE SWINGS...
IT'S A HIGH POP UP
GOING FOR A LEFT.
LOOKS LIKE THIS ONE
MAY BE DRIFTING FOUL.
FRAZIER'S TRYING TO CHASE
IT DOWN FOR THE OUT.
AND FRAZIER HAS IT.
TWO OUTS.
NEWTON'S DOWN
TO THEIR LAST OUT.
LOOKS LIKE PIKE SPANGLER IS
A RUN-OF-THE-MILL HITTER TODAY.
NEWTON NOW LOOKS FOR RELIEF
FROM THEIR ROOKIE
RIGHT FIELDER,
WILL WRIGHT.
WILL HAILS FROM THE
UP-TOWN SIDE OF NEWTON,
AND THIS IS HIS FIRST
YEAR OF ORGANIZED BALL.
WRIGHT MAY BE NEWTON'S
LAST CHANCE FOR A WIN.
NOW HE'S AT THE PLATE...
THERE'S THE WINDUP
AND THE PITCH.
STRIKE.
IT'S A STRIKE.
THAT WAS A SWEET ONE BUT
THE NEWCOMER PASSED IT UP.
0 AND 1 THE COUNT.
NEXT PITCH IS A BREAKING BALL:
HIGH AND OUTSIDE.
ONE AND ONE
THE COUNT.
STRIKE.
WRIGHT SCANS
THE STANDS.
MAYBE HE'S LOOKING
FOR INSPIRATION.
ONE AND TWO
THE COUNT.
THERE'S THE PITCH-
[WACK!]
IT'S A LONG LINE DRIVE
WAY OUT TO CENTER FIELD.
THE CENTER FIELDER'S
BACK TO THE TREES.
IT'S GONE!
[CHEERING]
A LONG HOME RUN
FOR WILL WRIGHT.
NEWTON TAKES THE LEAD,
TWO TO ONE,
AND WILL WRIGHT HAS TIPPED
THE SCALES FOR HIS TEAM.
WHAT A GAME FOR
IRON WILL WRIGHT,
THE NEXT BIG STICK
AT NEWTON.
THERE'S THE WINDUP
AND THE PITCH,
AND THAT'S
STRIKE THREE.
THAT'S THE LAST
OUT FOR NEWTON.
WE GO TO THE BOTTOM
OF THE NINTH.
WITH NEWTON AHEAD ON
WRIGHT'S LONG HOME RUN.
NOW IT'S UP TO YOUNG
CHICK SPANGLER
TO SEE IF HE CAN HOLD THE LEAD
FOR THREE MORE OUTS.
[CHEERING]
HE'S OUT!
THAT'S ONE DOWN,
THAT LONG HOME RUN IS LOOKING
BETTER AND BETTER FOR NEWTON.
STRIKE THREE.
AND THAT'S TWO DOWN.
ANDERSON'S DOWN
TO THEIR LAST OUT.
[CHEERING]
BALL.
[WACK!]
IT'S A LONG FLY BALL,
ITS WAY OUT TO CENTER FIELD.
THIS ONE'S DEEP.
WRIGHT'S GOING BACK, BACK, HE'S
AT THE TREES, AND HE'S GOT IT.
NEWTON WINS, NEWTON WINS,
NEWTON WINS!
[TRUCK ENGINE]
C'MON, WILL,
SHE AIN'T HERE.
AN' I FER ONE DON'T WANT TO BE
HERE WHEN TH' SUN GOES DOWN.
HEY.
[SPLAT!]
(COACH) C'MON, LET'S
GET OUT OF HERE.
YEAH, YOU PRETTY BOYS
NEED TO LEAVE.
ALRIGHT, Y'ALL GO AHEAD,
I'M GONNA HITCH A RIDE LATER!
RIGHT, LIKE I'M JUST
GONNA LEAVE YA HERE.
SCOOP! WE'LL
SEE YA LATER!
YA'LL BOYS BETTER
RUN FOR HOME.
THAT'S WHAT YOUR
GOOD AT, AIN'T IT?
RUNNIN' FOR HOME?
WE DON'T RUN FROM
NO GREASED PIGS.
YOU SHOULDN'T 'A' SAID THAT.
NOT HERE.
[WACK!]
YA'LL CLEAR ON
OUT OF HERE.
I MEAN NOW!
DON'T STAND THERE WITH THAT
STRAW IN YER MOUTH. C'MON.
MUCH OBLIGED, MISTER...
BOYS LOOK LIKE
MIGHTY SORE LOSERS.
JOHN DOUGLAS.
CHICK SPANGLER.
WILL WRIGHT.
GLAD TO KNOW
YOU BOTH.
BEEN TO EVERY
GAME.
GINNIE'S HERE
IN THE TRUCK.
OH-YOU'RE
GINNIE'S FATHER?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M GINNIE'S FATHER.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR
SWING'S LEVELING OUT.
YOU'RE SWING
AIN'T BAD EITHER.
WHERE D'YA
GIT THAT?
WELL, I MADE IT.
IT'S A HOBBY OF MINE-
MAKIN' BATS.
GOOD THING
FOR US.
GREAT GAME,
WILL!
WHAT A HIT
THAT WAS!
THANK YOU!
AND YOU PITCHED
REAL WELL, CHARLES.
THANKS.
ALRIGHT, LET'S GET
OUTTA HERE.
YOU BOYS RIDIN'
IN THE BACK.
[MUSIC]
I THINK I'LL HAVE
A DOPE AND A LIME.
LET'S ALL
HAVE ONE.
FINE.
A WHAT?
IT'S NOT AS BAD
AS IT SOUNDS.
JUST COCA-COLA
WITH A SQUIRT OF LIME.
DADDY'S FAVORITE.
SHOELESS JOE SPECIAL!
THAT'S RIGHT.
NOW, THERE'S A MAN WHO COULD
TEAR THE COVER OFF A BALL.
WAIT, YOU SAW
HIM PLAY?
STILL SEE HIM ONCE IN A WHILE
'ROUND THE GREENVILLE AREA.
EVEN AFTER THAT
BLACK SOX TRIAL.
HE'LL ALWAYS BE A HERO
TO THE MILL.
YOU KNOW THAT WHOLE SERIES
HIS BATTING AVERAGE WAS .375.
AND HE SET A WORLD SERIES
RECORD WITH 12 HITS!
AND THEY BANNED HIM
ALONG WITH THE TAKERS!
ONE OF THE GREATEST PLAYERS
THAT EVER STRODE THE DIAMOND.
HE WAS A NATURAL.
SPEAKING OF FAMOUS
BALL PLAYERS,
DID YOU BOYS HEAR
THAT BILLY SUNDAY'S
GONNA BE HOLDING A MEETIN' IN
THE COUNTY SEAT THIS MONTH?
BILLY SUNDAY?
I HEARD ABOUT HIM
MY WHOLE LIFE!
HE USED TO PLAY WITH
THE CHICAGO WHITE STOCKINGS.
I'LL BE GLAD TO TAKE ANYONE
WHO CARES TO GO.
COUNT ME IN.
SURE.
SOUNDS INTERESTING.
HERE WE ARE.
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU,
SIR.
I HOPE YOU
ENJOY THAT.
SAY, DO YOU THINK I COULD
COME BY THE SHOP SOMETIME
AND WATCH YOU
TURN A BAT?
I'VE GOT ONE ON THE
LATHE RIGHT NOW.
YOU WANNA COME
BY TONIGHT?
SURE, OKAY!
HE'S GOTTA GET INITIATED
JUST LIKE ANYBODY ELSE.
WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO HURT HIM, PIKE.
WE NEED HIM.
HE IS BRINGING
US LUCK!
FALLON, DIDN'T YOU GET
DRUGGED ON THE STONE STEPS
ON YOUR BACKSIDE
YER FIRST SEASON?
YEAH, BUT WHAT YOU
WANNA DO IS CRAZY!
HOW 'BOUT YOU,
WILSON?
YOU GET INITIATED?
YEAH, THEY HOG TIED ME TO THE
BACK STOP AND LEFT ME ALL NIGHT.
SEE!?!
EVERYBODY GETS
INITIATED.
HE COULD
GET HURT.
I AIN'T HELPIN'.
ME NEITHER.
AIN'T NOBODY GONNA.
HE'S OUR BEST HITTER.
SUIT YOURSELVES.
YOU JUST MIGHT WISH YOU
HADN'T LEFT IT UP TO ME.
ALRIGHT, WILL,
COME HERE.
GRAB A HOLD OF THAT
AND TELL ME WHATCHA THINK.
MAYBE A BIT THICKER
THAN I'M USED TO.
ALRIGHT...
LET ME SEE.
I THINK I KNOW
WHAT IT NEEDS.
MORE LEMONADE?
YES,
THANK YOU.
IT'S A LOT LIKE
MY MOM'S.
GINNIE, WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR MOM?
WELL, IT'S NOT
A LONG STORY.
SHE DIED
WHEN I WAS BORN.
BEEN DADDY 'N ME
EVER SINCE.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT'S YOUR
MOM LIKE?
SHE'S A HUGGER.
AND A TEETOTALER.
ME TOO!
UM, TEETOTALER,
THAT IS.
YEAH, SHE'S
A TEMPERANCE WOMAN.
WHAT DID SHE THINK ABOUT YOUR
LEAVIN' TO PLAY BASEBALL?
WELL, TO BE HONEST, SHE AND PA
WEREN'T TOO HAPPY ABOUT IT.
THEN WHY'D
YA LEAVE?
IT'S NOT THEIR
LIFE TO LIVE.
DO YOU REALLY
THINK IT'S YOURS?
WHO ELSE'S
WOULD IT BE?
[MUSIC]
ALRIGHT, SON,
YOU'VE GOTTA NEW BAT.
SHE'S A BEAUT.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO STAIN IT
OR DOUSE IT UP
WITH SOME LINSEED OIL
TO SEAL IT.
MUCH OBLIGED.
THINK I'LL STAIN IT
BLACK FOR GOOD LUCK.
HOW MUCH DO
I OWE YA?
IT'S YOURS.
BUT NOT FOR LUCK.
GOD'S GIVEN YOU A GIFT.
USE IT
FOR HIM.
THANK YA.
GOOD TALKIN' TO YA,
GINNIE.
GOOD NIGHT,
YA'LL.
'NIGHT, WILL.
GOOD NIGHT.
[MUSIC]
(PIKE)
HEY TOWN BOY...
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
THIS ON FOR SIZE?
[GRUNTS AND GROANS]
YOU IDIOT!
THAT THING COULDA
KILLED ME!
A SHAME IT DIDN'T.
EVERYTHING JUST GOES
YOUR WAY, DON'T IT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
YOU GIT BIT?
A COPPERHEAD
WON'T KILL YA.
JUST MAKE YA SWELL UP
AND HURT A LITTLE.
I RECKON IT SERVES
YOU RIGHT.
[SHOUTS IN PAIN]
YOU NEED TO GET
THAT LOOKED AT.
I'VE BEEN
SNAKE BIT BEFORE.
IT AIN'T NOTHIN'.
NO, YOU NEED TO GET
TO A DOCTOR!
I DON'T NEED
ANY HELP FROM YOU!
YOU KNOW, PIKE, PROB'BLY WENT
TO GIT HIM A JAR A' SHINE.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU COULD
DO WITH A JOLT YERSELF.
MAYBE IT'S TIME YOU JOINED
THE TEAM FOR REAL.
I THINK MAYBE EVEN
MY MA'D UNDERSTAND
IF I TOOK A SWIG
AFTER WHAT I SEEN TONIGHT.
YA REALLY THINK SO?
NO.
BUT I'LL NEVER KNOW WHAT
THE FUSS IS ALL ABOUT
IF I DON'T AT
LEAST TRY IT.
HERE'S TO
THE TEAM.
WELL?
THAT'S THE WORST STUFF
I'VE EVER TASTED!
NOBODY EVER LIKES
THEIR FIRST SWIG.
BUT IT'LL GROW
ON YA.
YOU'LL SEE.
AND NOW I KIN OFFICIALLY TOAST
YA AS A BONA FIDE MEMBER
OF THE NEWTON SLUGGERS.
WELCOME ABOARD,
TOWN BOY.
[MUSIC]
STRIKE ONE.
[WACK!]
[CHEERING]
[CAR ENGINE]
[WACK!]
[CHEERING]
WAY TO GO
IRON WILL!
[CAR HORN]
CAN WE GIVE YOU
LADIES A LIFT?
NO, THANK YOU.
CAN I PICK YOU UP LATER
AND BRING YOU BACK?
NO, THANK YOU.
HEY, THAT BILLY SUNDAY MEETIN'
IS COMIN' UP ISN'T IT?
THIS FRIDAY NIGHT.
YOU RECKON WE CAN CARRY
YA'LL OVER IN MY AUTOMOBILE?
THAT WON'T BE
NECESSARY.
GINNIE, WHAT'S
WRONG WITH YOU?
WILL, DO YOU
HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW MUCH THE BOYS IN
THE MILL LOOK UP TO YA?
I DO HAVE QUITE
A LITTLE FOLLOWING.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S NOT JUST BASEBALL
THAT THEIR GONNA
FOLLOW YOU INTO.
IMOGENE, WE CAN COME
INTO TOWN ANOTHER DAY.
LET'S GO.
WAIT, GINNIE.
WAIT A MINUTE, GINNIE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
DON'T FOLLOW ME.
LOOK, I KNOW HOW THINGS LOOKED
AT THE GAME THE OTHER DAY.
I THOUGHT YOU
WERE A CHRISTIAN.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY THAT?
WERE YOU DRUNK?
GINNIE, LISTEN.
I PROMISED MA BEFORE I LEFT THAT
I WOULDN'T EVEN TOUCH A DROP.
WHAT YOU SAW AT THE GAME
THE OTHER DAY -
THAT WAS JUST
THE TEAM DRINKING.
WELL, IT LOOKED LIKE YOU
WERE GOING RIGHT ALONG
WITH THE REST OF THEM.
YEAH, I KNOW, THEY DO KINDA
GIVE ME A HARD TIME ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE SURE WE CAN'T
GIVE YOU A RIDE NOW?
THANKS FOR THE OFFER
BUT WE'LL WALK.
LET'S GO.
CHICK, LOOKS LIKE I'M
BACK ON THE WATER WAGON.
WHAT?
WHY?
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
NEVER MIND.
BUT I'M DONE
DRINKIN' FOR GOOD.
I MADE UP MY MIND.
[CAR ENGINE AND MUSIC]
I KNOW OF A WORLD THAT
IS SUNK IN SHAME,
WHERE HEARTS ARE
FAINT AND TIRE,
BUT I KNOW OF A NAME,
A PRECIOUS NAME,
THAT CAN SET
THAT WORLD ON FIRE.
IT'S JESUS CHRIST,
THE SON OF GOD.
THIRTY-TWO YEARS AGO I WALKED
DOWN A STREET IN CHICAGO IN
COMPANY WITH SOME BALL PLAYERS
WHO WERE FAMOUS IN THIS WORLD.
SOME OF THEM
ARE DEAD NOW.
IT WAS SUNDAY AFTERNOON.
AND WE GOT TANKED UP AND WENT
DOWN AND SAT ON A STREET CORNER.
SAY, I NEVER GO BY THAT PLACE,
BUT I THANK GOD FOR SAVING ME.
IT'S VAN BUREN STREET,
CHICAGO.
WELL, AS I SAY, WE SAT DOWN ON
A CORNER AND ACROSS THE STREET,
A COMPANY OF MEN AND WOMEN
WERE PLAYING ON INSTRUMENTS
AND SINGING THE OLD GOSPEL SONGS
I USED TO HEAR MY MOTHER SING
BACK IN THE LOG CABIN
IN AMES, IOWA
AND BACK IN THE CHURCH WHERE
I USED TO GO TO SUNDAY SCHOOL.
AND GOD PAINTED ON THE CANVAS
OF MY MEMORY A VIVID PICTURE
OF THE SCENES OF OTHER
DAYS AND OTHER FACES-
MANY HAVE LONG SINCE
TURNED TO DUST.
AND I SOBBED
AND I SOBBED.
AND A YOUNG MAN STEPPED
OUT AND HE SAID,
"WE'RE GOING DOWN
TO THE RESCUE MISSION.
WON'T YOU COME
DOWN AND JOIN US?"
I SAID,
"WHAT WILL I HEAR THERE?"
HE SAID, "YOU'LL HEAR DRUNKARDS
TELL HOW THEY'VE BEEN SAVED.
"YOU'LL HEAR GIRLS TELL
HOW THEY'VE BEEN SAVED
IN THE RED LIGHT DISTRICT."
WELL, I TURNED AND I SAID
TO THE BOYS, "WE'RE THROUGH.
WE'VE COME TO THE PARTING
OF THE WAYS."
AND I TURNED
MY BACK ON THEM.
ONE OF THEM LAUGHED,
ONE OF THEM MOCKED ME,
OTHERS NEVER
SAID A WORD.
THIRTY-TWO YEARS AGO, I TURNED,
AND WENT DOWN TO THAT MISSION,
FELL ON MY KNEES AND
STAGGERED OUT OF MY SIN
AND INTO THE ARMS
OF THE SAVIOR.
SAY, HAVE YOU EVER BEEN WASHED
IN THE BLOOD OF THE LAMB OF GOD?
HAVE YOU EVER TURNED FROM
YOUR OWN SINFUL WAY OF LIVING
AND ASKED JESUS
TO SAVE YOUR SOUL?
I WONDER IF THERE
IS SOMEONE HERE TODAY
WHO WOULD ASK JESUS
TO SAVE HIM.
HE HAS MADE ALL THE
DIFFERENCE IN MY LIFE.
HE'LL DO
THE SAME FOR YOU.
JESUS SAID, "I AM THE WAY,
THE TRUTH, AND THE LIFE.
NO MAN COMETH UNTO
THE FATHER, BUT BY ME."
GOD HELP YOU
TO DO IT.
RODEY,
LET'S SING A SONG.
I'VE WANDERED FAR
AWAY FROM GOD.
NOW I'M COMIN' HOME.
THE PATHS OF SIN
TOO LONG I'VE TROD
NOW, I'M COMIN' HOME.
COMIN' HOME, COMIN' HOME,
NEVER MORE TO ROAM;
OPEN WIDE,
THINE ARMS OF LOVE
LORD, I'M COMING HOME.
KEEP YOUR EYES ON THE LORD.
W.A. SUNDAY.
THANK YOU,
SIR.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
NICE TO
MEET YOU.
YOU TOO.
GOD BLESS YOU.
MR. SUNDAY,
I WANT TO THANK YA.
YOU'RE WELCOME, SON.
EVERYTHING YA
SAID TONIGHT,
IT WAS LIKE YOU
WAS SPEAKIN' TO ME ALONE.
I GAVE MY HEART
TO CHRIST TONIGHT.
YOU'LL NEVER
BE SORRY, SON.
WHAT'S THE NAME?
CHARLES SPANGLER.
CHARLES.
I GREW UP
IN THE MILL.
MY DADDY
WAS BAD TO DRINK.
SO MY FOLKS NEVER TOLD
ME HOW TO BE SAVED.
GROWING UP IN A CHRISTIAN
HOME WON'T SAVE ANYONE.
MY OWN BOYS,
THEY HAVE THEIR STRUGGLES,
JUST LIKE EVERYONE ELSE.
EVERY SOUL MUST COME
TO CHRIST FOR HIMSELF.
IT'S NOT A
FAMILY DEAL.
HEY, UM, THIS HERE'S
MY FRIEND, WILL WRIGHT.
(MR. SUNDAY)
HELLO, WILL.
WE PLAY BASEBALL
FOR NEWTON MILL.
IS THAT RIGHT?
JOE JACKSON GOT HIS START
DOWN HERE, DIDN'T HE?
THAT'S RIGHT, SIR!
OH, IT'S A GREAT GAME.
I LOVED IT DEARLY.
BUT, AS I
SHARED TONIGHT,
I FOUND A HIGHER CALLING
WHEN I FOUND CHRIST.
THAT'S WHY YOU
LEFT BASEBALL?
WELL, I PLAYED FOR A FEW
YEARS AFTER I GOT SAVED,
BUT I FELT LIKE I WAS-
LIKE I WAS WEARIN'
SOMEONE ELSE'S SHOES.
I STILL LOVE THE GAME...
YOU ROUNDED THE BASES
IN 14 SECONDS.
AND NOW I ROUND THE PLATFORM
IN 2 HOURS.
[CHUCKLES]
YOU RECKON' YOU
COULD SIGN MY BIBLE?
SURE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
THANK YOU, SIR.
CHICK, WE'RE SO GLAD
FOR YOUR DECISION!
THANK YOU
FER INVITIN' ME.
I'VE BEEN
PRAYIN' FOR YOU.
THANKS FOR THET -
IMOGENE.
HAVE YOU TALKED WITH HIM ABOUT
CHRIST BEFORE?
I DON'T RECOLLECT.
MAYBE I HAVE.
WILL - WHEN DID YOU
ASK CHRIST TO SAVE YOU?
WHEN I WAS
REAL LITTLE.
I CAN'T HARDLY
REMEMBER.
BUT YOU DO REMEMBER
IT HAPPENED?
YEAH, MY MA PRAYED
WITH ME.
MAY I SEE WHAT MR. SUNDAY
WROTE IN YOUR BIBLE?
SURE.
"TO WILL, KEEP YOUR EYES ON
THE LORD. W.A. SUNDAY."
SO, UM, EZEKIEL, WHAT DID
YOU THINK OF MR. SUNDAY?
WELL, I'M THANKFUL FOR HIS
STRONG STAND FOR RIGHT.
GRANTED THE WAY HE SLANGS
UP THE GOSPEL
IS A BIT UNDISTINGUISHED
FOR A PREACHER,
BUT HE DOES SEEM TO CONNECT
WITH THE COMMON MAN-
WELL, I DIDN'T EXPECT
TO SEE YOU HERE!
WILL!
OH, MY DEAR BOY.
LIKE I SAID,
SHE'S A HUGGER.
MA, I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET
A FRIEND OF MINE.
YES, DEAR.
OF COURSE.
THIS IS GINNIE DOUGLAS.
SHE'S A SECRETARY
DOWN AT THE MILL.
I'M PLEASED TO MEET YOU, MA'AM.
AND I YOU,
GINNIE.
HOW DO
YOU DO?
I KNOW
THE YOUNG LADY.
HOW ARE YOU,
VIRGINIA?
I'M DOIN' FINE,
MR. HAMPTON.
IS YOUR
FATHER HERE?
YES, HE'S OUTSIDE GATHERING UP
THE BOYS IN THE TRUCK.
UH, VIRGINIA'S
FATHER IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE BOY'S RECREATION
DOWN AT THE MILL.
IN FACT, IF YOU
WOULD EXCUSE ME,
I'D LIKE TO GO THANK HIM FOR
BRINGING A GROUP OUT TONIGHT.
LADIES.
MR. HAMPTON TELLS ME YOU'RE AN
APPRENTICE MACHINIST, WILLIAM.
WELL HE'S JUST
PUTTING IT KINDLY.
I JUST LOOK
AFTER THE LOOMS
AND THEN IF SOMETHING
GOES WRONG THEN,
I GO AND GET
REAL HELP.
WILL'S TOLD ME
ALL ABOUT YA.
GOOD THINGS,
I HOPE?
YES.
I'M SO PLEASED TO HEAR ABOUT THE
PROMISE YOU ASKED HIM TO KEEP.
HE TOLD YOU?
WELL,
I'M GLAD HE DID.
(MA)
WILL?
YES, MA?
I'M THANKFUL THAT YOU HAVEN'T
FORGOTTEN THE PROMISE
THAT YOU MADE TO ME THE NIGHT
YOU LEFT HOME.
CAN YOU LOOK ME IN THE EYE
AND TELL ME YOU'VE KEPT IT?
MA, THIS IS HARDLY
THE TIME OR PLACE
TO BE TALKING ABOUT
PERSONAL MATTERS.
WHAT IS THERE
TO TALK ABOUT?
OKAY,
I TRIED IT.
BUT I HATED IT.
I JUST PROMISED MY PAL
THE OTHER DAY
THAT I WOULD NOT EVEN
TOUCH ANOTHER DROP.
WILL,
I'M DISAPPOINTED.
IT'S OKAY, MA,
I'M DONE FOR GOOD.
WILL, WILL YOU COME
HOME FOR A VISIT?
I CAN'T, MA.
I'M SORRY.
I'M A JUST A BIT TIED UP
TONIGHT.
PA, YOU'LL BE GLAD TO KNOW
I'M HITTING WELL.
I MIGHT MAKE IT
OUT OF THE MILL.
IS THAT RIGHT?
WELL, IF NOT TONIGHT,
MAYBE SOME SUNDAY YOU CAN MAKE
IT HOME AND BRING YOUR FRIENDS.
I'LL SEE IF I CAN MAKE
THAT WORK, MA.
WE'D BETTER GO.
SO ANYWAY, PEP,
THIS MR. SUNDAY
HE DELIVERS HIS SERMONS
LIKE A MAN ON FIRE.
SAYS IT DON'T MATTER
HOW RICH YA ARE-
OR HOW SMART YA ARE-
OR EVEN HOW FAMOUS.
EVEN IF YOU MAKE THE HALL OF
FAME- IT AIN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
YOU GOTTA PUT YER
FAITH IN CHRIST ALONE.
OH, SPANGLER,
ARE YOU PREACHIN' OR PITCHIN'?
I'M PITCHIN'.
THEN SHUT UP
AND PITCH.
'TWEEN YOUR FOOL PREACHIN' AND
YOUR BROTHER'S FOOL SNAKE BITE,
WE'RE THE WORSE OFF
FOR THE BOTH A' YA.
AND AS FOR YOU, WRIGHT, YOU
LOOK LIKE YOU'RE SLEEP WALKIN'.
LET'S SEE SOME
PEP OUT THERE.
[MUSIC]
READY TO GO?
I...I GOTTA GET SOMETHING
TO DRINK.
I THOUGHT YA'S
ON TH' WAGON.
YEAH, I JUST,
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST DON'T
FEEL LIKE MYSELF.
WILL, YOU BETTER
STAY AWAY FROM IT.
LOOK, I'M GLAD YOU'RE A
CHRISTIAN NOW AND EVERYTHING,
BUT JUST CUT IT OUT,
DOGGONE IT!!!
WHEN YA FIRST COME,
YA NEVER TOUCHED IT.
WHEN I FIRST CAME,
YOU WANTED ME TO!
I'M AS SORRY AS
I KIN BE FOR THET.
YOU KNOW THE BIBLE SAYS TAKE
A LITTLE WINE FOR THE STOMACH.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT,
DID YOU?
YOU'RE USIN' THE BIBLE
TO JUSTIFY BOOZE?
HEY, MR. HOLY ROLLER,
JUST QUIT TRYIN' TO SHOVE
RELIGION DOWN EVERYBODY
ELSE'S THROAT!
HEY, JOHN.
HEY, CHICK.
HEY, CAN YOU GIVE ME
A HAND A SECOND?
SURE, WHAT DO
YOU NEED?
TURN THAT THING
ABOUT A QUARTER TURN.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S
GOOD, THAT'S GOOD.
THANK YOU.
CAN I ASK
YA SOMETHIN'?
SURE.
D'YA KNOW CHRISTIANS
THET DRINK?
THAT'S A LONG STORY.
THERE ARE SOME
CHRISTIANS THAT DRINK.
WHOLE DENOMINATIONS
ALLOW "MODERATE DRINK."
I DON'T SEE HOW
THEY CAN JUSTIFY IT,
BUT THEY SAY AS LONG
AS THEY DRINK IN PRIVATE
OR DRINK JUST A LITTLE BIT THEY
WON'T HEAR ANY DIFFERENT-
EVEN THOUGH IT'S AGAINST
THE LAW OF THE LAND.
BUT THERE'S ONE THING
I DON'T HEAR 'EM SAY.
(CHICK)
WHAT?
(JOHN) THEY DON'T SAY
THEY'RE DRINKING
SO THAT GOD WILL BE
GLORIFIED IN THEIR LIVES.
(CHICK)
RECKON NOT.
(JOHN)
BUT THAT IS BIBLE.
"WHETHER THEREFORE,
YE EAT, OR DRINK,
OR WHATSOEVER YOU DO,
DO ALL TO THE GLORY OF GOD."
PEOPLE DON'T OFTEN THINK
ABOUT GOD'S GLORY.
THEY THINK ABOUT THEIR
OWN PLEASURES INSTEAD.
(CHICK) SO YOU THINK
PROHIBITION'S TH' RIGHT THING?
(JOHN) WELL, THIS
MAY SURPRISE YOU,
BUT SOMETIMES I WORRY ABOUT
THE EFFECTS OF PROHIBITION.
I FEEL LIKE
IT'S MADE IT HARDER
TO REACH SOME PEOPLE
WITH THE GOSPEL.
REALLY?
IF CHRISTIANS EVER
COME TO THE PLACE
WHERE WE THINK WE CAN
MAKE PEOPLE ACT LIKE
THEY KNOW THE LORD EVEN WHEN
THEY DON'T, THEY'LL HATE US.
AND MAYBE RIGHTLY SO.
THE CHOICE TO COME TO CHRIST
IS A CHOICE MADE IN THE HEART.
IT CAN'T BE FORCED
ON SOMEONE.
NOW, I KNOW THAT LIQUOR
IS THE BANE OF OUR SOCIETY.
AND I KNOW THAT LIVES ARE BEING
SAVED BY THE 18TH AMENDMENT.
BUT THE ROOT OF THE PROBLEM
IS STILL SIN
AND THE ONLY WAY TO GET TO
THAT ROOT IS FOR JESUS CHRIST
TO CHANGE THE HEART OF A MAN
FROM THE INSIDE OUT.
MY PA WUZ
BAD T' DRINK.
HE LEFT AFTER LITTLE
BO COME 'LONG,
WENT BACK T' TH' MOUNTAINS
T' SELL MOONSHINE.
HE GOT REAL MEAN WHENEVER HE
GOT A SNOOTFUL OF THE STUFF,
SO WE WERE KINDA HAPPY
WHEN HE FINALLY TOOK OFF.
I HATE T' SAY IT.
I'M SORRY TO HEAR
THAT, CHICK.
GIVE ME A HAND.
PICK IT UP JUST A LITTLE.
THERE YOU GO.
ALRIGHT.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M DOIN' WRONG.
I'VE ONLY BEEN A CHRISTIAN
FOR A FEW DAYS.
BUT, IT SEEMS NO ONE ON
THE TEAM KIN STAND ME.
EVEN WILL.
HE SAID I'M ACTIN'
LIKE A HOLY ROLLER.
WILL SAID THAT?
YES, SIR.
BUT THEN, I GIVE HIM
HIS FIRST DRINK.
I KNOW I'LL HAVE
TO ANSWER FOR THAT.
GINNIE TOLD ME HE TOOK
A PLEDGE NOT TO DRINK.
I THINK HE DID,
THEN HE WENT OFF IT.
I'M AFRAID HE GOT
A TASTE FOR IT NOW.
WELL, MAYBE YOU AND I -
OR GINNIE -
ONE OF US CAN
TALK TO HIM.
DO YOU KNOW FOR SURE HE'S
A BORN AGAIN CHRISTIAN?
I RECKON.
HE DON'T TALK MUCH
ABOUT IT, THOUGH.
CHICK, DO YOU THINK YOU
COULD TAKE FRIDAY OFF?
I'M TRYING TO ORGANIZE A DAY
TRIP FOR THE MILL BOYS,
AND I SURE COULD
USE A HAND.
AH, YOU CAN
COUNT ON ME.
DO YOU THINK IT WOULD BE ALRIGHT
IF I BRUNG WILL ALONG, TOO?
HE'D HAVE TO BE
BONE DRY.
DON'T YA WORRY.
I CAN TAKE CARE OF THET.
I'LL BRING LITTLE BO.
HE'S GOT A SOFT SPOT A MILE
WIDE FER THET BOY.
THET'LL DRY HIM RIGHT OUT.
GUARANTEE IT!
WELL GOOD.
[MUSIC]
[TALKING]
OH, LOOK...
[EXCITED SCREAMING]
ALRIGHT, EVERYBODY STAY
TOGETHER AS A GROUP.
AND NOBODY IS TO GO OUT
IN THE WATER
DEEPER THAN WHAT
YOU CAN STAND IN.
RIGHT?
RIGHT.
AND THESE ARE YOUR
TWO LIFEGUARDS.
YOU DO WHATEVER
THEY TELL YOU TO DO.
OR ELSE I'LL PUT YOU IN
THE BACK OF THE TRUCK
WITH ME AND GINNIE,
RIGHT?
RIGHT.
AND EVERYBODY KEEP YOUR
LONG JOHNS ON ALL DAY!
RIGHT?
RIGHT.
SAY RIGHT?
RIGHT!
GO IN!
[EXCITED SCREAMING]
PRISONERS HAVE BEEN
SET FREE!
YEAH.
I SEE YOU LIKE TO
SPLASH, HUH!
CAN I BE NEXT?
YEAH,
YOU CAN BE NEXT.
OKAY,
YOU TOO.
LINE UP
FOR CANNON BALLS!
I HOPE I'M NOT
INTERRUPTIN'.
WELL, YA ARE,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
THAT THE INTERRUPTION
IS UNWELCOME.
WILL, I WANTED TO ASK
YA SOMETHIN' ANYWAY.
ALRIGHT, ASK AWAY.
ALRIGHT...
WELL...
WILL, HAVE YOU KEPT YOUR
PROMISE TO YOUR MAMA?
WELL, I GUESS THERE'S NO
USE TRYIN' TO FOOL YA.
I KEPT IT TIL THE NIGHT PIKE
INITIATED ME TO THE TEAM
WITH A FULL GROWN
COPPERHEAD.
THEN, I STARTED DRINKIN'
WITH THE TEAM.
I WAS TOO ASHAMED TO TELL
YOU ON THE ROAD INTO TOWN
AND SO I TOLD YOU ABOUT
THE PROMISE I MADE
AND I SET OUT
TO KEEP IT.
HAVE YA?
I DID FOR A WHILE.
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETIMES I KINDA
FEEL LOUSY WITHOUT IT.
WILL,
THAT'S DANGEROUS.
I KNOW.
MY PA HAD A BROTHER THAT DRANK
HIMSELF TO DEATH, AS THEY SAY.
THAT'S WHY HE NEVER
WANTED EITHER OF US BOYS
TO EVEN TOUCH IT.
THEN, WHAT POSSESSED
YOU TO DO IT?
UH, I JUST FIGURED I WAS OLD
ENOUGH TO MAKE MY OWN CHOICES
AND NOT DO WHATEVER
MY PARENTS SAID.
SO, YOU DIDN'T TELL
THE TRUTH THAT NIGHT.
NO. I'M SORRY,
GINNIE.
WILL, YOU NEED
TO GET HELP.
NO, I DON'T NEED HELP, I JUST
NEED TO QUIT IT, AND I WILL.
IN YOUR OWN STRENGTH?
WELL, I'M NOT GONNA LET
ANYONE ELSE DO IT FOR ME.
LOOK, GINNIE, I'VE NEVER
KNOWN ANYONE TO CARE ABOUT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO TELL YOU THIS,
BUT I CARE ABOUT YOU
AND WHAT YOU THINK.
THEN STOP PLAYIN'!
WHAT?
BASEBALL?
I MEAN - LIFE!
NO. NO, I CARE ABOUT YOU TOO,
WILL WRIGHT.
TOO MUCH TO IGNORE
YOUR WALK WITH GOD.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU JUST ADMITTED THAT YOU
WANT TO DO IT ALL ON YOUR OWN.
YOU!
IT'S ALL YOU.
YOU'RE TOO PROUD
TO GET HELP.
WILL, ARE YOU
A CHRISTIAN?
WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
I TOLD YOU I'VE BEEN
A CHRISTIAN MY WHOLE LIFE.
I KNOW THAT'S
WHAT YOU SAY.
BUT I DON'T SEE-
WHAT?
WHAT DON'T YOU SEE?
WILL, ARE YOU A CHRISTIAN
IN YOUR HEART?
OR ARE THEY
JUST WORDS YOU SAY?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
GINNIE, I'VE BEEN
WRONG AND I'M SORRY.
WILL YOU FORGIVE ME
AND GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE?
FORGIVE YOU FOR WHAT?
FOR DRINKIN'.
I NEVER SHOULD
HAVE LIED TO YOU.
GINNIE, I KNOW IN
MY HEART I CAN QUIT.
I'LL EVEN GET HELP.
ARE YOU JUST SAYIN'
THAT TO PLEASE ME?
GINNIE, I'LL DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
NO! NO YOU CAN'T
JUST DO WHAT I WANT.
WILL, IN YOUR HEART DO YOU
WANT TO PLEASE JESUS CHRIST
BECAUSE YOU BELONG TO HIM,
BODY AND SOUL?
OR DO YOU JUST
WANT TO PLEASE ME?
CAN'T I DO BOTH?
THIS FRIENDSHIP BETWEEN US -
WHATEVER IT IS - IT HAS TO END.
I'M SORRY, WILL.
BUT I AM NOT
HELPIN' YOU.
GINNIE.
I'M SORRY,
I CAN'T...
[MUSIC]
[CHEERING]
[DISAPPOINTED MOANS]
HEY SLUGGER.
[LAUGHTER]
WILL, WILL, DO YOU HAVE ANY
IDEA HOW MANY PEOPLE
ARE LOOKING FOR YOU?
C'MON, C'MON.
NO, NO, THIS WAY,
REMEMBER?
[CHEERING]
YOU'RE UP.
C'MON, WRIGHT!
WE NEED A RUN!
IT'S THE FINAL PLAYOFFS,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD!
[CHEERING]
(CROWD) LET'S GO,
LET'S GO.
[DISAPPOINTED MOANS]
(CROWD) YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO HIT THE BALL.
C'MON SCOOP,
GET THET TOWN BOY OUTTA HERE.
TAKE HIM OUT.
IT'S OKAY, WILL.
YOU'LL HIT IT NEXT TIME!
THERE AIN'T GONNA BE
NO NEXT TIME, WRIGHT.
YOU'RE OUTTA
THIS GAME!
YOU'RE OUT
OF THE NEXT ONE, TOO.
YOU'RE A DISGRACE
TO NEWTON MILL!
BUT, IF I DON'T PLAY THE FINAL,
THE SCOUT WON'T SEE ME.
YOU DON'T WANT NO SCOUT
TO SEE YA!
OUTTA ALL THESE MUGS,
I EXPECTED MORE OUTTA YOU.
HEY TOWN BOY,
BET YOU NEVER BEEN
CALLED A DISGRACE
TO A MILL BEFORE,
HAVE YA?
SHUT UP, PIKE.
FINALLY GET TO SEE YOU
RIGHT WHERE YOU BELONG.
AT THE BOTTOM A' THE HEAP 'NEATH
A WHOLE TEAM A' LINTHEADS.
I SWEAR,
DON'T PUSH ME.
YEAH?
I SEEN THE GAME, YOU COULDN'T
HIT ME EVEN IF'N YA WAS TO TRY.
THERE HE IS,
CHICK!
PIKE,
LEAVE HIM ALONE!
YA HERE THAT,
IRON WILL?
MY LITTLE BROTHERS,
THEY'RE TRYIN' TO HELP YOU.
THEY WANT ME
TO LEAVE YOU ALONE.
(BO)
WATCH OUT WILL!
BO, GO HOME.
THE BOTH OF YOUS!
THIS HERE IS BETWEEN
ME AND THE TOWN BOY.
I AIN'T FIGHTING
A ONE-ARMED MAN!
DON'T YOU WALK
AWAY FROM ME!
[WACK!]
I SAID-
LEEEEAVE ME ALOOOOONE!!!!
[WACK!]
C'MON BO? BO.
NO. NO!!
WILL, WHAT DID
YOU DO?
YOU KILLED HIM.
YOU KILLED HIM!!!
NO. PLEASE, GOD, NO!
HE AIN'T DEAD!
HE'S STILL
BREATHING!
PIKE, WE GOTTA GET HIM
TO THE INFIRMARY!
RUN AHEAD
AND GET THE DOC.
PIKE!
IT'S A BAD BUMP, BUT HE'S
BREATHING STEADILY NOW.
AND HE'S GOING
TO BE OKAY.
WILL,
BO'S NOT DEAD.
HE'S KNOCKED OUT
BUT HE AIN'T DEAD.
DON'T DO
ANYTHING CRAZY!
JUST LEAVE
ME ALONE.
NO, I'M NOT GOIN'
ANYWHERE.
THEN I'LL GO-
NO, YOU'RE STAYIN'
'TIL WE TALK.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO TALK ABOUT.
ALL I COULD THINK ABOUT WAS HOW
MUCH I HATED YOUR BROTHER.
HOW I WANTED
TO HURT HIM BAD.
BUT IF BO DIES-
BO AIN'T GONNA DIE.
YOU DON'T KNOW THAT!
I KNOW HE'S
IN GOD'S HANDS.
WE KIN PRAY FOR HIM.
DON'T - TALK TO ME -
ABOUT GOD!
YOU WON'T EVEN
PRAY FOR HIM?
GOD WON'T HEAR
MY PRAYER.
SURE HE WILL.
GOD HEARS
ALL PRAYERS.
YOU DON'T KNOW YOUR
BIBLE LIKE I DO.
THE BIBLE SAYS IF THERE'S SIN
IN MY HEART, GOD WON'T HEAR ME.
THEN GET RID
OF THE SIN.
THET'S ALL THE BIBLE
I DO KNOW.
MR. SUNDAY SAID, IF YA TURN FROM
YER SIN, GOD'LL FORGIVE YA.
HE WANTS TO.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS
TO BEIN' A CHRISTIAN
JUST ASKIN' JESUS FORGIVENESS
FOR YER SINS.
IT'S NOT
THAT SIMPLE.
WHY NOT?
MY WHOLE LIFE
IS A LIE.
I'VE ALWAYS SAID WHATEVER
PEOPLE WANTED TO HEAR.
BUT IN MY HEART I NEVER
TURNED FROM MY SIN.
YA KIN CHANGE THET.
I'VE HEARD ABOUT BEING
A CHRISTIAN FOR SO LONG-
IT'S NOTHIN'
BUT WORDS.
DON'T JIST
SAY THE WORDS.
MEAN 'EM.
IT AIN'T THET
HARD TO DO.
I WOULDN'T EVEN
KNOW HOW...
WILL, ARE YA SORRY
FOR YER SINS?
I AM.
DON'T TELL ME.
TELL HIM.
I AM SORRY
FOR MY SIN.
GOD, I'M SORRY FOR GOING AGAINST
YOU AND GOING MY OWN WAY -
FOR SAYIN' THAT
I WAS A CHRISTIAN
AND DOIN' WHATEVER
I WANTED TO DO.
I'M SORRY - FOR EVERYTHING
THAT I'VE DONE AGAINST YOU.
GOD, FORGIVE ME
FOR MY SIN.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
WERE YA JUST PRETENDIN'?
NO.
LET'S PRAY
FOR BO. OKAY?
YEAH.
OKAY.
[KNOCK, KNOCK, KNOCK]
YEAH.
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE?
SURE, COME ON IN.
I HEARD ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED.
BUT, YOU DIDN'T HEAR
ALL OF IT.
I ASKED THE LORD
TO SAVE ME.
IS THAT RIGHT?
I'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE TO LOOK
SOMEONE IN THE EYE BEFORE
AND TELL THEM THAT
I KNOW I'M A CHRISTIAN.
BUT I CAN TODAY.
THAT'S AN ANSWER
TO PRAYER, WILL.
BUT THERE'S STILL SO
MUCH I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN I LEFT HOME -
THAT WAS WRONG.
WHEN I BROKE MY PROMISE
AND STARTED TO DRINK -
THAT WAS WRONG.
LETTING MY TEAM DOWN BECAUSE
OF MY DRINKIN'...IS MORE WRONG.
LYING AND ACTIN' LIKE
I'M SOMETHING I WASN'T.
I'M SO WRONG;
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO GET RIGHT!
I DON'T EVEN KNOW IF I SHOULD
PLAY BASEBALL ANYMORE.
IT'S BEEN MY
WHOLE LIFE -
I - I JUST
DON'T KNOW!
IS BASEBALL
REALLY THE PROBLEM?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, WHAT DID
BILLY SUNDAY SAY?
HE SAID HE DIDN'T HAVE
A PROBLEM WITH THE GAME ITSELF.
HE SAID HE FOUND
A HIGHER CALLING.
YOU'VE GOT A NATURAL
GIFT FOR BASEBALL.
I'VE WATCHED YOU DEVELOP IT
ALL SEASON.
YOU'VE GOT A GIFT FOR
WORKING WITH THE BOYS.
I'VE SEEN THAT
THIS SUMMER, TOO.
MAYBE YOU CAN FIND A WAY TO
TAKE ALL THAT GOD'S GIVEN YOU
AND BRING GLORY TO HIM.
I'M WILLING TO DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
THEN HE'LL MAKE IT
CLEAR TO YOU.
"IN ALL THY WAYS
ACKNOWLEDGE HIM."
HE'LL DIRECT YOU.
FIRST OFF, I HAVE A LOT OF
APOLOGIES I NEED TO MAKE.
SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD START.
CAN I SPEAK TO GINNIE?
WILL! BO'S AWAKE!
HE'S FINE!!
HE JUST WOKE UP.
HE'S GONNA BE ALRIGHT.
CAN I GO SEE HIM?
THET'S WHY I COME
TO GET YA!
CAN I COME
BACK LATER?
SURE, GO ON.
MRS. SPANGLER, I'M SO SORRY
ABOUT WHAT I DID.
HAS BO -
IS HE AWAKE YET?
DOC SAYS IT WILL TAKE A COUPLE
OF DAYS FOR THE GOOSE EGG
TO GO DOWN
BUT HE'LL BE FINE.
HE'S UP.
I'M SO GLAD
TO HEAR THAT.
IS IT OKAY IF
I GO AND SEE HIM?
AS A MATTER OF FACT, HE
ASKED ABOUT YOU FIRST THING.
REALLY?
YES.
HE WANTS TO MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
FEEL BAD ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED!
HE DOES?
THERE IS NOTHIN'
YOU CAN DO
TO DIM THAT BOY'S ADMIRATION
OF YOU, WILL WRIGHT.
HE'S WAITIN' IN
THERE FOR YA.
GO ON IN.
IT'S AMAZING.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE,
I FEEL FREE!
IT DOES KINDA SEEM LIKE YOU'RE
BOUNCING OFF THE CLOUDS.
TO THINK FOR SO LONG I LIVED
TRYIN' TO ACT LIKE I WAS FREE -
I NEVER KNEW
HOW IT FEELS!
AND NOW I BET YOU'RE
JUST ITCHIN' TO GET BACK
INTO THE BATTER'S BOX.
WELL, THAT
I DON'T KNOW.
I APOLOGIZED TO THE TEAM
AT PRACTICE,
BUT SCOOP SAYS
HE STILL WON'T PLAY ME.
I CAN'T BLAME HIM.
THEN THE SCOUT MIGHT
NOT SEE YA PLAY?
HE MIGHT NOT.
BUT WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE SCOOP'LL CHANGE HIS TUNE
IF I SHOW UP AND ACT RIGHT.
I HOPE SO.
IT USED TO MEAN THE WORLD TO ME
IF I CAUGHT THE EYE OF A SCOUT.
I KNOW.
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
IT'S STILL THE CHANCE
OF A LIFETIME.
BUT THERE ARE SO MANY
OTHER THINGS I CARE ABOUT
MORE THAN BASEBALL.
LIKE...
WELL, BO -
HIM BEING OKAY.
I'M GOING TO GO SEE HIM AT THE
HOSPITAL RIGHT BEFORE THE GAME.
THAT'S A
GREAT IDEA.
AND OF COURSE,
I WANT TO BE RIGHT WHERE
GOD WANTS ME TO BE -
THAT MEANS THE
WORLD TO ME.
THAT'S THE BEST THING.
YEAH.
AND, WELL...
WHAT?
FRIENDS - THAT I'VE MADE
WHILE I'VE BEEN HERE.
GINNIE, I KNOW I TOLD YOU
AT THE LAKE THE OTHER DAY,
BUT I GOT
TO SAY IT AGAIN...
YOU'VE BECOME
MY BEST FRIEND.
I FEEL THE
SAME WAY.
[MUSIC]
(VENDOR) PEANUTS!
POPCORN!
PEANUTS!
IRON WILL!
YOU GOTTA GIT GOIN'.
YOUR GONNA MISS
THE FIRST INNIN'.
OKAY,
I'LL GET GOIN'.
BUT YOU KNOW I'D
DO ANYTHING
TO MAKE SURE YOU WERE
THERE, TOO, RIGHT?
IT'S OKAY.
I'M GETTIN' BETTER.
GOOSE EGG
GOIN' DOWN?
SOME.
CAN YOU HIT A HOME RUN
FOR ME TODAY?
I DON'T KNOW IF I'LL EVEN
GET A CHANCE TO BAT, BO.
WHY NOT?
WELL, GOTTA SAY IT.
I WAS LIVING FOR
MYSELF, BO,
AND I MESSED UP PRETTY
BAD FOR THE TEAM.
BUT THEY'LL GIVE
YOU ANOTHER CHANCE.
THEY JUST GOTTA!
WE'LL SEE.
BUT, HEY, I PROMISED TO GIVE YOU
A PLAY-BY-PLAY OF HOW IT WENT
WHEN I GET BACK, OKAY?
OKAY.
THANKS FOR COMIN'
TO SEE ME!
THANKS FOR BEING
MY BIGGEST FAN.
WILL, HIT ONE...
OUT...FOR ME.
[MUSIC]
NO!
NURSE! WE NEED
SOME HELP HERE!!
I'LL GET
THE DOCTOR.
[MUSIC]
ANYBODY SEEN
WRIGHT TODAY?
I SAW HIM
THIS MORNING.
PROBABLY SLEEPIN' OFF HIS
MOST RECENT SPIFFLICATION.
NO! HE AIN'T
BEEN DRINKIN'.
WHAT?
CUZ HE GOT RELIGION?
I SEEN THET KINDA FLASH
IN THE PAN BEFORE.
BUT HE'S DIFFERENT!
I KNOW IT.
THEN WHY AIN'T
HE HERE?
EVEN IF HE DOES SHOW, THERE
AIN'T NO WAY I'LL PUT HIM IN.
HE'D ONLY FOUL
THINGS UP.
NEVER SEEN A FOOL BALL
PLAYER LATE TO THE BIGGEST,
DOGGONE BALL GAME
OF THE YEAR!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WELCOME TO THE
CHAMPIONSHIP GAME,
WHICH BRINGS THE
ANDERSON TEAM TO NEWTON MILL
FOR THE LAST GAME OF THE SEASON.
(UMPIRE)
PLAY BALL!
[CHEERING]
NOW YOUNG MAN, I WANT YOU
TO BE JUST AS STILL AS YOU CAN.
I DON'T WANT
NO MORE NEEDLES!
WE'RE GIVIN' HIM SOMETHING
TO SETTLE HIM DOWN.
HE'LL BE ALRIGHT.
IT'S OKAY, BO.
THE DOCTOR'S JUST DOIN'
WHAT HE'S GOT TO DO
TO MAKE SURE
YOU'RE OKAY.
I'M HERE WITH YOU,
BUDDY.
WILL, YOU GOTTA GET
TO THE GAME!
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THE GAME.
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT
THAT I SEE YOU'RE OKAY.
WILL, PLEASE GO.
IT'S OKAY, BO.
JUST TAKE IT EASY.
IT'S ALL GONNA BE OKAY.
(ANNOUNCER) TWO OUTS IN THE TOP
OF THE SECOND.
SPANGLER'S TRYIN'
TO GET THAT LAST STRIKE.
COME ON, SPANGLER!
STRIKE HIM OUT.
YOU'RE OUT!
[CHEERING]
CHICK, I'M WORRIED
ABOUT WILL.
YEAH, I'M WONDERING
WHERE PIKE IS.
HE'LL SLEEP
A LONG TIME NOW.
YOU CAN GO.
YOU SURE DOC?
THANK YA.
SORRY.
[MUSIC]
UGH, PIKE!
(ANNOUNCER) THAT'S THE LAST OUT
FOR ANDERSON.
WE GO TO THE BOTTOM
OF THE FIFTH.
I DON'T SEE
WILL ANYWHERE.
IT'S NOT LIKE HIM
TO MISS A GAME.
I HOPE THERE'S
NO TROUBLE.
HE'S PROBABLY ON
HIS WAY RIGHT NOW.
(ANNOUNCER) WE'RE HALF WAY
THROUGH THE GAME.
NEWTON HAS A MAN ON SECOND,
BUT THEY NEED TO GET HIM HOME.
COME ON, HUNNICUTT.
GET ON BASE!
[CHEERING]
OUT!
[DISAPPOINTED MOANS]
SAFE.
[CHEERING]
(COACH) ON THE BALL NOW;
KEEP YOUR EYE ON THE BALL.
SAFE!
[CHEERING]
[MUSIC]
'SPECTED YOU
A LONG TIME AGO.
I FIGURED AS MUCH.
GOT SOME UNFINISHED
BUSINESS WITH YOU TOWN BOY.
I GOTTA GIT TO
THE GAME, PIKE.
NO... SEE, THAT'S
THE WHOLE POINT,
YOU AIN'T GOTTA
GO NOWHERE.
CLEAR OUTTA
MY WAY.
I THINK WE'RE
GOOD RIGHT HERE.
I'M COMIN' THROUGH,
PIKE.
YA THINK SO?
GET OUT OF
MY WAY.
HOW DO YOU
THINK IT FELT
WHEN THET BALL YA THREW
HIT BO IN THE HEAD?
I DON'T KNOW.
MUST 'A' HURT
SOMETHIN' AWFUL.
YOU'RE CRAZY!
AND YOU'RE DEAD.
I AIN'T GONNA THANK YA IF
THETS WHAT YER WAITIN' FER.
IF YOU EVER KNEW WHAT IT
FELT LIKE TO BE SET FREE -
I DON'T KNOW, YOU MIGHT BE
A DIFFERENT PERSON.
MAYBE ONE DAY.
[MUSIC]
THERE HE IS,
THERE'S WILL.
[MUSIC]
WHO DO YOU
THINK YOU ARE?
YOU THINK YOU CAN JUST WALTZ
IN HERE ANYTIME YOU WANT?
SIT DOWN AND KEEP
YER TRAP SHUT!
IS THAT SCOUT
FROM CHARLOTTE HERE?
YEAH, HE'S HERE.
HE AIN'T SEEIN'
MUCH FROM US THOUGH.
WILL, YA WANT ME TO TALK
TO SCOOP FER YA?
NO.
I MISSED THE FIRST SEVEN INNINGS
OF THE CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
WHAT ELSE
CAN HE DO?
[CHEERING]
(UMPIRE) SAFE!
(ANNOUNCER)
LOOKS LIKE WILSON'S HURT.
WRIGHT, YOU'RE ALL I GOT,
GO IN AND RUN FOR HIM.
OKAY, COACH.
(ANNOUNCER) HERE COMES
WILL WRIGHT INTO THE GAME
TO RUN FOR WILSON.
[CLAPPING]
AT LEAST HE
WON'T GET TO BAT.
[WACK!]
[CHEERING]
THAT'S THE THIRD OUT.
NEWTON'S STILL BEHIND
BY TWO RUNS
AND WE'RE DOWN
TO THE LAST INNING.
[MUSIC]
(ANNOUNCER)
TWO OUTS FOR ANDERSON.
SPANGLER NEEDS
ONE MORE STRIKE
TO BRING THIS TEAM UP FOR
THEIR LAST CHANCE AT BAT.
[CHEERING]
[WACK!]
SAFE!
WELL, WRIGHT, NO ONE
I'D RATHER HAVE COMIN'
TO THE PLATE RIGHT NOW.
Y'AIN'T BEEN
DRINKIN'?
NO, SIR.
OKAY, THEN,
MAKE US PROUD.
[CHEERING]
(UMPIRE) BALL.
GO WILL!
[WACK!]
[CHEERING]
GO, GO!
NO, NO!
SAFE!
[CHEERING]
OH, YAY, YOU DID IT!
MR. WRIGHT,
MR. WRIGHT.
CAN I SPEAK WITH YOU
FOR A MOMENT?
THANK YOU.
I OWE YOU A DEBT OF GRATITUDE,
MR. DOUGLAS.
THIS IS A CONTRACT FROM
THE CHARLOTTE SPINNERS!
I KNEW IT, I KNEW
YOU COULD DO IT.
IT'S WHAT YOU
ALWAYS DREAMED OF!
YOU DID NEWTON MILL PROUD,
WILL!
WILL, I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT!
I KNEW YA HAD IT
IN YA, TOWN BOY.
COULDNA DONE IT
WITHOUT YOU.
AIN'T GONNA BE TH'
SAME 'ROUND HERE.
YOU CAN'T GET RID
OF ME THAT FAST.
JOHN AND I CAME UP
WITH A PLAN.
IF I DO WELL
IN CHARLOTTE,
I CAN COME BACK IN THE
OFF-SEASON TO THE MILL. RIGHT?
THE OFFER'S
ALWAYS OPEN.
I WANT TO START
HELPIN' JOHN
WITH THE BOYS'
RECREATION LEAGUE.
I KNOW I CAN
USE SOME HELP!
AND, WELL, WHO KNOWS
WHAT THE FUTURE BRINGS!
(MA)
WILL!
MA?
SO PROUD OF YOU,
SON!
HOW IN THE WORLD
DID YOU -?
YOUR FRIEND TOLD US
ABOUT THE CHAMPIONSHIP.
SHE EVEN OFFERED TO COME
AND DRIVE US FROM TOWN.
MA, PA,
I'VE WRONGED YOU BOTH.
I'M SORRY.
WE CAN TALK ABOUT
THAT LATER, WILL.
WE FREELY
FORGIVE YOU.
LIKE I SAID -
SHE'S A HUGGER.
WILL, YOU'VE MADE SUCH WONDERFUL
FRIENDS WHILE YOU'VE BEEN AWAY!
GINNIE, THANK YOU
SO MUCH FOR TODAY!
I KNEW YOU'D
WANT TO BE HERE.
WILLIAM, I HAVE TO SAY I'VE BEEN
A BIT NARROW IN MY PERSPECTIVE
ON WHAT YOU COULD DO
WITH YOUR LIFE.
I'VE BEEN A BIT NARROW
IN MY PERSPECTIVE
ABOUT A GOOD
MANY THINGS.
BUT I AIM
TO DO BETTER.
THERE ARE NO STAINS ON
THE PAGES OF TOMORROW.
THAT'S RIGHT, SON.
THERE AREN'T.
WELL, IN THAT CASE, I HAVE
JUST ONE QUESTION FOR YOU.
WOULD IT BE ALRIGHT IF
I BROUGHT A MILL GIRL
TO MEET THE TOWN FOLK
AT CHURCH TOMORROW?
IF YOU DON'T BRING HER,
SON, I WILL.
SHE'S A KEEPER!
WELL, YOU READY?