( Faint beeping )
( Beeping louder )
( Jet engine roaring )
- ( Man speaking, distorted )
- ( Electronic hum )
( Beeping )
( Heavy breathing )
( Laser firing )
( Screams )
( Pants )
( Crickets chirping )
( Loud bang echoing )
( Jet engine roaring )
Man over radio:
Delta flight, this is
pike control.
You're clear
to 16,000'.
Proceed to coordinates
6-tango-Charlie.
Roger, control.
It's a beautiful day
in the neighborhood.
E.t.a. To entry point,
95 seconds.
Yeah, I'm right
behind you.
Try to keep US
out of trouble,
okay, outlaw?
- I always do.
- Yeah, right.
What about
last Saturday night?
Did you forget about
those two bottles--
kill the chit-chat,
delta flight.
I shouldn't have
to remind you this is
an operational test flight.
Switch v.R. Display
to external channel 3.
- Yes sir.
Delta 1 ready.
- ( Beeps )
Pike control,
this is delta leader.
Start v.R.,
power level 5.
Affirmative, delta flight.
Confirming transmission now.
- ( Beeps )
- ( Whirrs )
( Beeping )
Outlaw:
Delta 1, system activated.
Visual display checks.
Glen:
Delta 2, initiate
hyper-reality.
- ( Beeping )
- Hound dog: Yes sir.
System checks good,
colonel.
Okay, delta flight,
descend to angels-2,
maintain 400 knots,
enter control point Sierra.
Descending to angels-2.
Here we go.
This is gonna be
one hairy ride.
- Ever fly
with your eyes closed?
- All the time.
Outlaw:
Let's bring it down.
Colonel,
this is pike control.
Telemetry is good.
We're ready to record.
Glen:
Let's start the profile,
delta flight.
Increase speed
to 700 knots.
Delta 1 copies.
Increasing speed
to 700 knots.
Hound dog:
2 copies.
( Outlaw breathing deeply )
I'm right behind you.
Holy shit. This is
one hell of a video game.
Outlaw:
Yeah, but it's real.
Come on. Come on.
- ( Alarm buzzing )
- Outlaw: I got it.
I got it.
Whoa.
That was awful close.
( Beeping )
- ( Pants )
- ( Beeping )
( Flatly )
Delta 2 awaiting
instructions.
Glen:
Proceed to Alpha formation.
Outlaw,
this is hound dog.
I'm moving up
on your wing.
Outlaw:
Negative, hound dog.
Maintain tactical spacing.
Don't crowd me.
I'm in position.
Jesus, hound dog,
back off.
- Settle down, gentlemen.
- Colonel, hound dog's
too close.
The system can't handle
this formation.
The system's fine,
captain waters.
Get ready
for the next run.
Yes sir.
Hound dog:
2 copies.
Head for
the control point now.
Outlaw: 40 seconds
to control point Sierra.
Increase your speed
to mach 1.6.
Yes sir.
Mach 1.3,
1.5, 1.6.
( Breathing shakily )
( Humming, beeping )
Hound dog,
what are you doing?
Come in, hound dog.
Hound dog,
acknowledge!
Delta 2 awaiting
further instructions.
Hound dog,
terminate your run.
( Breathes shakily )
Glen:
Terminate your run, captain.
That's an order.
( Beeps )
Colonel,
what's happening?
Glen: Hound dog,
pull out of there!
Colonel, he's gonna hit
the canyon walls.
Outlaw:
Hound dog, hound dog,
do you copy?
- ( Alarm buzzes )
- Tom, I'm losing it!
Pull up, hound dog!
Pull up!
Tom: Listen to
the colonel, hound dog!
Pull up! Pull up!
( Screams )
Damn it!
Son of a bitch,
hound dog.
God, no.
( Beeping )
Glen:
We've done a thorough
review of the accident.
This is a satellite view
of the crash site.
It shows
no unusual conditions
of any kind.
No cloud cover,
no weather fronts,
no heat activity
or wind shear.
There was
no equipment malfunction,
no atmospheric
disturbances.
Bottom line,
extrinsic factors did not
cause the accident.
Hound dog:
Delta 2 ready
for further instructions.
Glen: Hound dog,
terminate your run.
Hound dog:
Colonel, what's happening?
Hound dog,
pull out of there!
Tom:
Hound dog, hound dog,
do you copy?
Tom, I'm losing it!
Pull up, hound dog!
Pull up!
Listen to the colonel,
hound dog.
Pull up! Pull up!
- ( Alarm buzzes )
- ( Hound dog screams )
( Whirring )
For some unknown reason,
captain Matthews deviated
from the flight plan
and panicked
at high speed.
Virtual reality
- worked perfectly.
- Tom: Excuse me, colonel,
we practiced this run
in the simulator rig.
Hound dog knew
what to expect.
He wasn't 100%
in the simulator either.
None of you have been.
Colonel, I know--
I know hound dog
took some chances,
but don't you think
the v.R. System could've
been partially responsible?
No, I don't.
The system
functioned perfectly.
I appreciate your concerns,
captain waters.
I want to assure
every one of you
that I am overseeing
this project
as well
as this investigation.
If I thought
for one moment
that any of your boys
were in real jeopardy,
I'd pull the plug
on this puppy
quicker than you could say
"god bless america."
( Inhales ) Now...
Secretary of defense
Spencer testifies
before the senate budget
committee next week.
You all know that he is
on a one-man crusade
to cut back
on electronics programs,
starting with ours.
If he gets
so much as a hint
that there is a glitch
with virtual reality...
I don't think I need
to fill in the blanks.
Gentlemen,
our work here is vital
to our country's
security.
Let's keep
a tight lid on it,
shall we?
- We can't afford
another mistake, Glen.
- I know.
Mrs. Matthews.
I'm so sorry
about your husband.
General breslaw,
I just don't think
it was his fault.
No one is trying
to lay blame here,
I can assure you
the air force is
going to great pains
to determine
the cause of your
husband's accident.
Fighter pilots perform
extremely difficult jobs.
Unfortunately, danger is
a part of that territory.
Excuse US.
I know, Beth,
some people think
he was a real hotshot.
I just can't believe
the air force ruling on this.
- It's tough.
- Oh.
Tom, something was
disturbing him.
I know
this sounds crazy,
but I think that somebody
did something to him.
What do you mean?
He never had
any trouble sleeping
and then all of a sudden
he started having
this reoccurring nightmare.
He'd wake up in the middle
of the night screaming.
But everybody has
bad dreams.
These were different.
Woman:
Good morning, gentlemen.
We're just about ready.
- ( Switches clicking )
- ( Computer beeping )
- How you feeling,
cowboy?
- Good.
- Sit still.
- ( Exhales slowly )
- ( Helmets whirr )
- We've added a new feature
to your v.R. Displays--
an enlargement mode.
Your prayers have
been answered, cowboy.
He needs it
more than I do, lil.
Aim the enlargement reticle
on the subject you wish
to see in more detail,
then you squeeze
the missile-fire button.
( Beeping )
( Hums )
( Whistles )
( Chuckles )
Captain Riley.
That's enough.
Today's simulation
will continue
where our last
flight test ended.
That's a comforting thought.
Glen:
Outlaw, you're flying red.
Cowboy, you're blue.
( Beeping )
Lily:
Initiating brain stimulation.
No response from outlaw.
Enemy threat activated.
( Laser fires )
Got a bandit
on my tail, outlaw.
Give me a hand.
I can't.
I've got my own.
- ( Dings )
- ( Laser firing )
Cowboy:
I'm getting out of here.
( Dinging )
( Alarm buzzing )
I hate tailgaters.
You're mine now.
- ( Beeping )
- Line it up.
Come on. Come on.
Let's go.
Line it up.
Come on, here we go.
Lock on, lock on!
Good lock!
All right, gotcha now!
Fox-2, fox-2,
missiles away.
Whoa!
I can save it.
Glen:
Congratulations,
captain.
You've just been
shot down by a dead man.
You've sucked in
half his plane.
Increase waters'
dosage to 3.6.
Waters, go back
and start again.
( Breathing hard )
( Beeping )
Aw shit.
Colonel, he doesn't
seem to be responding
to the increased dosage.
He seems to have
an unusually high resistance.
( Traffic sounds )
( Man inhales )
have him take a look
at the patio door, would you?
It's sticking.
That sounds
very nice, dear.
Any color you want's
fine with me.
All right.
I'll see you tonight.
( Sighs )
May's redoing the kitchen.
She's been asking
since 1967.
Finally wore me down.
I have something
I want you to hear.
Glen, listen to this.
"In an enthusiastic
assessment
of his plan to scale down
the armed forces,
defense secretary
Spencer said,
'it will signal
to the rest of the world
that the cold war is over
and it's time to invest
scarce resources
in building a better life
for average citizens.'"
amazing, isn't it?
Do they realize
that defense has driven
this economy since f.D.R.?
Pendulum always
swings back, Glen,
which is why our work is
even more important now.
How's the program going?
Riley and Tate are
responding well.
And waters?
He appears to have
an innate resistance.
Maybe you should drop him.
I'm confident it's just
a matter of finding
the right dosage.
You were also confident
you could control
captain Matthews.
What did they call him?
- Hound dog.
- Hound dog!
That's right.
I still get a kick out
of those names.
It's a terrible tragedy,
though.
He has a lovely wife.
Well, Glen,
it's your program,
so it's your call.
You do what
you want with waters.
Just remember there's
no room for a wild card
in this program.
Don't worry about waters.
I can handle him.
It's breslaw
I'm worried about.
You just handle
the captain.
I'll deal
with the good general.
( Cap rattles )
( Clicks )
- How's it going, cap?
- Hey, Joe. How you doing?
Pretty good.
Uh, I've been thinking, cap.
Do you think
you can get me one
of those flight suits?
It ain't
the flight suit, Joe.
It's the man in it.
- ( Rock music playing )
- I'll see what I can do.
( Bell dings )
- Take a look
at that one, huh?
- ( Music, engine stop )
Not bad.
I got this one.
Check this out.
( Footsteps approach )
Here, I got this.
( Clicks )
Mmm-mmm-mmm.
I like
my steak medium rare,
baked potatoes stuffed--
broccoli and cheese,
that is.
Asparagus is good.
Apple pie...
A la mode.
Could you not lean
on my car?
I just had it waxed.
So I'm supposed
to be impressed
- because you're in the army?
- Air force.
Whatever.
So what do you do
in the air force,
private waters?
I'm a captain.
Tom. I fly jets.
( Chuckles )
I see.
Because you fly jets,
I'm supposed to sink
into a girlish swoon
and ply you
with high-cholesterol
cuisine, right?
Yeah, well, I guess--
I guess it lost a little
in the translation.
I think so.
Why don't you
translate this?
I don't cook.
Well, maybe you'll find
someone who does.
Hey, captain.
I do takeout.
Man.
I've gotta get me
one of them flight suits.
- ( Caitlin giggles )
so why the air force?
- ( Jazz music playing )
Tom:
I don't know. I guess
I didn't have much choice.
My father was
in the air force.
It just seemed like
the only thing to do.
Besides, it's a good way
to meet women.
Does it always work?
( Laughs )
Every time.
So what's it like?
What's what like?
Flying.
Flying jets.
It's great.
Well, your passion is just...
Overwhelming.
( Clears throat )
I guess I had a rough week.
What happened?
I can't tell you.
If I did,
I'd have to kill you.
( Chuckling )
Not really.
What do you do?
I am a financial consultant
and right now I'm on loan
to a software manufacturer.
Mmm.
So what would you do
if you couldn't fly anymore?
I don't know.
Oh, come on,
there's got to be something.
I'd drive cross-country--
no map,
no destination.
Just see where
the road takes me.
That could be
a lonely drive.
Huh.
- ( Both breathing heavily )
- ( Jazz music playing )
Mmm.
I'm sorry.
It's just a little fast.
Ah.
- ( Chuckles )
- Should I go?
No.
I just think you've had
too much to drink, you know?
You shouldn't drive home.
Why don't you stay
on the couch?
I got a better idea.
Why don't I sleep
in your bed...
( Both moan )
...and you sleep
in your bed?
Hm-mmm.
No.
Hey.
Why don't I sleep
on the couch
and you sleep
on the couch?
I like my eggs
over easy!
( Man speaking,
distorted )
( Beeping )
( Panicked breathing )
( Screams )
Are you okay?
I mean,
it's just a bad dream.
- Yeah.
- It's okay.
- Mmm, yeah.
- Hmm?
Want to tell me
about it?
No.
( Sighs )
Mmm.
I don't think
we should.
I think we should.
( People chattering )
( People laughing )
( Locker slams )
- ( Man sighs )
- You look like shit.
Well, I think
I forgot how to sleep.
- Yeah?
- I've been having
these dreams.
( Loud bang echoes )
Riley:
I keep waking up
in the middle of the night.
It's really weird.
Tom:
How long had he been
having these nightmares?
About a month
before the accident.
Did he describe them
to you?
Not really.
I asked, but...
( Chuckles )
He didn't want me to see
that he was worried.
Do you think
maybe I could
take a look
around his office?
If you think
it would help.
You never know, right?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Hound dog's voice:
"Ever since we started
v.R. Testing,
I've been feeling odd.
Can't remember what went on
in the simulator today.
Getting strange dreams.
Can't tell anybody
or I'll be grounded."
Oh god.
Huh.
Do you realize you've been
staring at that same page
for over an hour?
This doesn't sound
like hound dog.
He was not
the paranoid type.
Maybe he was sick.
Then why are we all
having nightmares?
I'm starting to think
Beth was right.
There's something going on
with this v.R. Project.
Tom, would you just
forget about it, okay?
I just can't deal
with this anymore.
( Over radio )
look, I'm sorry.
I've really had a hard day.
Why don't we just
go to sleep?
( Loud bang echoing )
( Door shuts )
( Beeps )
( Beeping )
( Keyboard clacking )
( Buzzes )
Damn!
( Laser humming )
( Beeps, whirrs )
Man:
Lamison, is that you?
- ( Whining stops )
- ( Door opens )
( Tires screeching )
All right, asshole.
You want to play?
( Tires screech )
- ( Beeping )
- ( Tom breathing deeply )
Bandit at 3:00.
I'm on his tail.
This one's mine, outlaw.
I'm going after him.
- Lily: Initiating
brain stimulation.
- ( Beeping )
Lily:
Colonel, captain waters
was almost under.
Cowboy's under.
Cowboy, do you have
a visual on him?
Affirmative.
I have him in sight.
Okay, nail this sucker.
- Come on, cowboy,
fire on him.
- ( Buzzing )
Tom:
What are you waiting for?
( Cowboy breathing shakily )
He's gonna fly
right into him.
Cowboy?
Cowboy!
( Breathing shakily )
I told you.
Let me handle this.
Tom:
Cowboy, I'm moving in.
Cowboy:
He's mine, outlaw.
- Tom: Cowboy,
I'm locking onto him.
- ( Beeping )
If you're not gonna
take him, I am.
Fox-2, fox-2,
missiles away.
Damn it.
That was mine.
When were
you gonna take him out,
next century, cowboy?
Cowboy.
What happened in there?
You tell me.
You're pissed
I took out your target?
What are
you talking about?
Why were you flying
like a kamikaze?
You don't remember,
do you?
Maybe you
shouldn't fly tomorrow.
Maybe you should
take some time off.
Something is happening
with this project.
I found some
of hound dog's notes.
He was having
nightmares too,
trouble remembering
what happened during
the v.R. Sessions.
- He was losing it!
- Oh, so I'm losing it?
Don't put words
in my mouth, cowboy.
It's just that you're
not acting like yourself.
Yeah, well, don't worry
about me. That's my job.
Look, I was just
trying to help.
Yeah, well,
worry about yourself.
Caitlin on tape:
Maybe he was sick.
Tom:
Then why are we all
having nightmares?
I'm starting to think
Beth was right.
There's something going on
with this vr project.
Tom, would you just
forget about it, okay?
I just can't deal
with this anymore.
( Clicks )
It's a top-priority
project, Glen.
We have bugs
on everyone.
Are you still confident
you have
the waters situation
under control?
Don't worry
about it, okay?
I'm not worried.
Mild concern is probably
a more appropriate term.
You don't understand.
I just want you to have
all the information we do.
I know how important
this project is to
your career, Glen.
Hate to see anything
untoward happen.
( Whirring )
- ( Beeping )
- ( Engine starting )
Echo flight,
you have clearance
to launch.
Authentication is
bravo Sierra.
Pike control out.
Tom:
Echo flight copies.
Echo 1,
set course 2-9-7.
Ascend and maintain
4000' agl.
Roger, pike control.
Echo flight,
let's descend to angels-4.
Glen:
Approaching
control point Charlie.
Echo 1,
start your run.
Tom:
Echo 1 copies,
here I go.
- ( Beeps )
- ( Whirrs )
Echo 1
v.R. System activated.
Display checks.
No target in sight.
Missiles armed.
Still no target.
Boost his
v.R. Power level to 8.
- Level 8?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, do it.
- Yes sir.
( Beeping )
Tom:
I see it.
Target acquired.
( Lasers firing )
Tom:
I'm also getting
ground fire.
Starting
evasive maneuvers.
I'll put it through
the front door.
- ( Beeps )
- Missile away.
Bull's-eye!
Perfect visual
substitution.
Cowboy,
you're up next.
Yes sir.
Activate
default program #2.
Default v.R. System
program #2
is activated, sir.
( Beeping )
( Flatly )
Echo 2 waiting
for instructions.
Take up heading 0-5-7,
ascend to angels-1
and start your run.
Roger, control.
I'm starting my run.
Hey, cowboy,
where you going?
The target range is
over here.
Hey, cowboy,
you want to clue me in?
- ( Beeping )
- Tom: Cowboy!
- He's on the new
course, colonel.
Echo 2, echo 2,
radio check. Come in,
- ( pinging )
- Where are you?
Cowboy, this is outlaw.
Come in.
Pike control,
I lost cowboy.
I'm making
a turn to the north.
Echo 1,
maintain current heading.
Tom:
Colonel, there's something
wrong with cowboy.
He's still not responding
to my radio calls.
Glen:
Captain, we're handling
the situation from down here.
Hold your original heading.
That's an order.
Yes sir.
( Flatly )
Echo 2.
Approaching
checkpoint tango.
Call back when you get
a visual on the target.
( Laughs )
Mm-hmm.
- Huh.
- Man over radio: Webster.
This is Taylor.
Come in.
Ah!
Uh-huh. Mmm.
( Clears throat )
Webster here. What's up?
Hey, buddy,
where are you?
Another air force test.
I got route 234 closed
to all traffic.
It's a thrill a minute.
I'm at marker 13,
but I don't see you.
That's 'cause
I'm at mile marker 30.
You're supposed to be
at 13, Einstein.
No, uh...
Oh shit.
Uh, hold on.
( Radar gun beeping )
What the hell?
( Mutters )
( Beeps )
- ( Mutters )
- ( Sonic boom )
Oh!
Oh! Jesus Christ.
I have visual,
pike control.
Target is
an armored vehicle.
Stand by, echo 2.
Sir, the satellite image
is coming in.
- ( Beeps )
- It's hard to make out.
That looks like it.
( Beeping )
Pike control
to echo 2.
Your objective is
to destroy the vehicle.
Oh Jesus.
( Flatly )
Good target acquisition.
Colonel,
this can't be right.
The coordinates are off.
Enhance this
satellite image.
Hurry up.
That's a police cruiser.
( Breathing heavily )
- ( Beeps )
- Missile away.
( Pants )
What's he doing now?
- ( Beeping )
- His v.R. Power level
is too high.
Get it back to normal.
( Breathing heavily )
( Beeping )
That's a person running.
Echo 2 acquiring
secondary target.
Son of a...
Echo 2, you have
the wrong target, damn it!
The wrong target!
( Grunts )
Cowboy:
Target destroyed.
Returning
control point Charlie.
Echo 2 out.
- ( Radio chatter )
- ( Phone ringing )
What the hell happened?
Colonel Anderson,
the target vehicle
was never hit.
It was a mile away
from the vehicle
echo 2 attacked.
( Beeping )
( Breathes heavily )
( Grunting )
What's code 7700?
Where are you, cowboy?
Where are you?
Got him at 3:00.
Cowboy, come in.
Echo 1,
echo 2 is not responding.
Cowboy,
this is outlaw.
I'm coming up
on your right wing.
Cowboy, come on,
respond. Answer me.
( Whirring, beeping )
Tom:
Man, what the hell
are you doing?
Man:
Colonel, that's a gun.
Tom:
Put the gun away, cowboy!
Come on!
Talk to me, cowboy!
Cowboy, listen to me!
- Cowboy!
- ( Gunshot )
Damn it, cowboy,
talk to me!
Come on!
Come on, man!
Stay with it!
Come on,
pull it together!
Get it back!
- He's going down.
- Tom: Bail out!
Bail out, damn it!
Bail out!
I want to remind everybody
that this operation
is black.
Security is
of the highest priority.
All inquiries
will be referred to me.
Is that clear?
Drugs?
Can you think of any other
rational explanation?
I knew cowboy
better than anybody.
He didn't do drugs.
People aren't always
what they seem, Tom.
Perhaps you didn't know
captain Riley as well
as you thought.
He didn't do drugs
and he wasn't suicidal.
He was reckless.
You saw how he flew during
the v.R. Session yesterday.
- Like hound dog.
- Yes.
Cowboy wasn't
like hound dog.
Look, captain,
I know this is hard
for you to accept.
Sure, colonel.
The v.R. Worked great.
The program's going fine.
Just one minor
little problem--
you've lost two pilots.
No need to get excited.
What the hell are you
trying to say, captain?
I think
you know, colonel.
No, I don't.
Why don't you tell me?
Say it!
No need to get
emotional, gentlemen.
We're all
on the same side here.
Colonel,
why don't you
give me a moment
with captain waters?
( Door opens, closes )
What was that about, Tom?
I don't want to lose
any more of my boys.
Do you know something
that I don't?
It's a gut feeling,
but I think
Anderson might be
covering something up.
- Like what?
- I'm not sure.
I trust
your instincts, Tom.
I want you to come
to my office tomorrow.
We will further
this discussion.
But right now, I want
you to go home and have
a couple of drinks.
That's an order.
Yes sir.
( Phone ringing )
- Anderson.
- Glen. Arthur vick.
I'm afraid
I have some bad news.
We're taking you
off the project.
But there was
a police cruiser
at the target site.
There was no way
to anticipate it.
Glen, it's a black project.
No one will ever
know anything about
what happened out there.
I promise you.
You can't do that.
You need me.
I'm sorry, Glen.
There's nothing I can do.
It's out of my hands.
Good night, Glen.
( Crickets chirping )
You know, you never
told me what happened
after they--
are they gonna
do an investigation
or something?
( Softly ) Yeah.
I'm gonna be there
to see Anderson
take the blame.
What? You think--
you think Anderson
killed cowboy?
I know
he killed cowboy,
and breslaw's
gonna know it too.
I'm gonna
see him tomorrow.
You know,
when there's a tragedy,
it's natural to look
for somebody to blame.
But sometimes
there just isn't anybody.
It's not your fault.
Listen to me.
You're gonna
get over this.
( Sniffles )
( Distorted noise )
( Loud bang echoing )
( Touchtones )
( Rings )
Anderson:
Who's there?
( Door closes )
( Dial tone,
touchtones )
( Ringing )
- Anderson.
- ( Loud bang echoing )
Look, who is this?
( Door opens )
You're awake.
I can't.
What is it?
( Pants rustling )
Would you just
talk to me, please?
I'll call you later.
( Sighs )
Give me a break.
( Car honks )
( Car honking )
( Tires screeching )
( Honks )
That does it.
Come and get me.
I hate tailgaters.
( Distant sirens )
Should've used
your seat belt, pal.
- It's the law.
- ( Sirens approaching )
( Tires screech )
Ah.
( Ringing )
Anderson.
Uh, I'll be right there.
( Crickets chirping )
( Cocks, fires )
( Lock rattles,
clicks )
( Beeps )
( Beeping )
( Keyboard clacking )
( Anderson speaking softly )
Final mission.
( Loud banging )
( Beeping )
Bingo.
( Loud banging )
Gotcha now, Anderson.
- ( Cocks )
- That's very good, Tom.
Too bad
you weren't smart enough
to lock the door.
You're a better spy
than I am.
Give me your gun.
What's your story, Caitlin?
Latent James Bond fantasies?
It was my job.
You have
an interesting work ethic.
Anderson had to get
subjects to respond
to certain commands,
things they would
never do normally.
So he had you
screw me over
in as many positions
as possible.
You screwed yourself over,
you and your paranoia.
Why didn't you just
let things be?
( Clicks, whirrs )
- I'm turning you in.
- ( Switch clicks )
- You all right?
- Yes sir.
What is this?
What's going on?
You're under arrest
for suspicion of murder.
- Murder?
- I received a phone call
that colonel Anderson was
murdered at approximately
2300 hours this evening.
- What?
- I've since been made aware
that you
and colonel Anderson
have been conducting
brainwashing
experiments on several
of our fighter pilots.
I just work
for Anderson.
And when he became
an embarrassment,
you killed him.
No, this is a setup.
I left miss Cole's apartment
at 2200 hours.
That's a lie.
I didn't kill him.
That's a lie!
I didn't kill him!
Let go of me.
Tom!
let go of me!
Thanks, general.
Like I said, I always
take care of my boys.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go back to bed.
Breslaw:
It's imperative
that we demonstrate
to secretary Spencer the value
of our v.R. Technology.
We have to show him
how virtual reality picks up
where human biology
leaves off.
It lets US see 100 miles
when we can only see one.
It creates the sensation
of being someplace
that we're not.
It allows US
to react faster,
better
than humanly possible.
This is the sole purpose
of today's mission.
You don't have to worry
about colonel Anderson.
I'll be flying
in his place.
Amber 1 and 2,
this is warlord 1.
- Stand by
for v.R. Transmission.
- ( Beeps )
Amber 1 standing by,
general.
Amber 2 copies.
Pike control,
start v.R. Transmission
at this time.
Transmitting
v.r. Routines now.
General, you have clearance
to enter the range.
Weather conditions
are good.
Roger, control.
Is there any conflicting
traffic in the area?
No factor
at this time, sir.
Secretary Spencer
will be passing by
the southern boundary
in 10 minutes,
call sign "rainmaker."
We'll stay clear.
Amber flight,
engage your vr now.
Amber 1 copies.
2 copies.
Okay, boys,
let's show 'em
what the v.R. Can do.
Roger. Hey, flash,
you ready
to rock and roll?
Hey, man,
what are you, deaf?
Flash, what the hell are
you doing back there?
( Beeping )
Shit, I'm getting
a missile lock from you.
- What are you doing, man?
- ( Alarm beeping )
Come on,
talk to me, damn it!
Initiate
battle code X-ray.
Roger, warlord.
No!
Warlord 1,
this is control.
Uh, general sir,
- it appears that Amber 2
just fired at Amber 1.
- ( Alarm beeps )
Please advise me
of your situation. Over.
Damn it.
See if you can find
battle code X-ray.
Damn it, flash,
break it off!
Break it off,
you son of a bitch!
Amber 2, carry out
your mission.
- ( Breathing heavily )
- ( Beeping )
Damn it, general,
call him off!
That's a negative.
You're in the way, Tom.
All right,
you crazy bastard.
Damn it, flash,
I'm on your 6:00.
- Break it off,
do you hear me?
- ( Beeping )
Come on!
I'll bring you down
if I have to!
I have my orders.
I'm taking you out,
you bastard.
- Now get out
of the damn plane.
- ( Beeping )
Missile away.
Do you hear me?
Get out, flash!
Bail out!
- ( Hisses )
- Tom: Bail out!
( Beeps, buzzing )
God damn it.
- Get rescue on the horn.
Did you find anything?
- ( Alarm beeping )
Just this--
something about
classified codes.
Flight control,
Amber 1 has gone renegade.
He's a threat to all
aircraft in the area.
Damn you, general.
You're the one
who's out of control,
you lying son of a bitch.
- General?
- What's the location
of rainmaker?
He's skirting
the southern boundary, sir.
Control,
this is outlaw.
There's a woman
being held in security.
- Her name is Caitlin Cole.
- Ignore that, control.
- ( Beeps )
- Tom: She was working
for colonel Anderson.
( Beeping )
She can tell you
everything.
Give in, Tom. Relax.
You can do it.
It's your duty.
( Flatly )
Yes sir.
Good, Tom.
You're about
to make history.
What's he saying?
- ( Keyboard clacks )
- Warlord 1, this is control.
Could you repeat? Over.
- ( Beeps )
- I need a target, general.
Breslaw:
Turn to heading 1-5-7.
1-5-7. Roger.
General-- sir,
that's rainmaker's location.
General?
General,
this is pike control.
Come in. Over.
Damn it.
Call security,
find out if they're
holding a Caitlin Cole.
If they are,
get her up here.
Rainmaker,
this is pike control
with a high-priority warning.
Come in.
Rainmaker:
Pike control,
this is rainmaker.
Go ahead.
Approaching renegade f-16
with hostile intent
being pursued
by a mirage fighter.
Take evasive action now.
Against an f-16?
This is a Learjet.
You do understand we have
a high-priority passenger
onboard this aircraft?
Uh, yes sir, I do.
Okay, control.
What's the distance
on that f-16?
25 miles and closing
on full burner.
Control,
he's gaining on US.
Sergeant, here's the woman
you were asking for.
What do
you want, sergeant?
We've got a hell
of a situation here, ma'am.
Captain waters shot down
captain Tate.
He said he was attacked
on orders from the general.
He said you might know
something about it.
Captain waters is
probably right.
Could it have something
to do with these codes?
What codes?
They come up each time
before the attacks.
I can't override them
and I can't break in.
- I can.
- ( Handcuffs clink )
Do it, soldier.
- Are you in contact
with captain waters?
- Sporadic.
- Get him.
- ( Keyboard clacking )
Amber 1, this is
pike control. Over.
Amber 1,
this is pike control.
Please acknowledge.
Rainmaker:
We're not gonna
last much longer.
( Beeping )
It's just like
the simulator, Tom.
- There's no difference.
- I'm-- I'm losing
lock on him.
Tom, the time has come
to send a message
to the secretary.
What's he talking about?
- Who's on that other plane?
- The secretary of defense.
He's trying to kill
the secretary.
Jesus.
( Caitlin, distorted )
Tom, can you hear me?
Tom, answer me.
Tom.
Tom!
Tom, this is Caitlin.
If you can hear me,
please acknowledge.
Carry out
your orders, Tom.
- I just about have it.
- ( Beeps )
( Breathing heavily )
- I'm in.
Oh my god.
Tom, listen to me.
The number's a code--
it's a brainwashing code.
Tom, it doesn't matter.
This is something
we have to do.
Caitlin:
You were right, Tom.
There is something going on.
You're being
programmed by breslaw
and you're on
a collision course with
the secretary of defense.
You've gotta pull up, Tom.
You've gotta pull up.
- Stay on target!
- Tom, please pull up!
- ( Panicked breathing )
- Caitlin: Stop your attack,
Tom. Pull up!
No!
Damn it. I am very
disappointed in you, Tom.
- ( Sighs )
- Rainmaker: Okay, control,
this is rainmaker.
Get US out of here now.
- ( Clicks )
- Rainmaker,
this is pike control.
Proceed
to coordinates 2-9-2.
- Sergeant?
- Sergeant: Stand by, rainmaker.
- What is it?
- I have warlord on tactical
intercept with rainmaker.
Shit! General,
what are you doing?
Keeping america strong, son.
I can't allow any one man
to compromise that.
Oh my god.
You'd better alert
base command.
( Clears throat )
Rainmaker, this is
pike control on guard.
Warning, warning,
approaching mirage fighter
with hostile intent.
- Acknowledge. Over.
- Rainmaker: Now it's a mirage?
What the hell are you idiots
doing down there?
Outlaw, this is
pike control.
General breslaw is on
an intercept course with
the secretary of defense.
Acknowledge. Over.
Acknowledge, outlaw. Over.
Do you read, over?
Tom, this is Caitlin.
If you hear me,
please respond.
Cai-- Caitlin?
Turn off Tom's v.R.
- Sergeant: What?
- Turn it off!
Tom, it's Caitlin,
can you hear me?
- Tom: Yeah.
- Warlord at 20 nautical
miles and closing
Tom, you have to
get to breslaw.
He's trying to kill
secretary Spencer.
Do you remember
what just happened?
Umm...
Flash attacked me.
I shot him down.
That's right.
But you had to do it.
Breslaw programmed him
to kill you.
Those numbers
on your display are
mind-control codes.
10 nautical miles
and closing.
You were right, Tom.
There was something wrong.
I only worked
for Anderson.
I don't think he even knew
what breslaw was doing.
They lied to me.
They were controlling you.
Outlaw, this is
pike control.
Tom:
Is that you, Wyatt?
Yeah, captain, it's me.
What she said is true.
Warlord--
five nautical miles.
Tom:
I'm on my way.
( Beeping )
Control,
my weapons won't arm.
Your weapons won't arm
unless you're in v.R.
- That was my idea.
- Control, turn my v.R. Back on.
No, Tom, you can't.
Breslaw can feed you codes.
You see, Tom,
it's sort of a catch-22.
Turn on your v.R.
And I'll break you.
Leave it off,
you're helpless.
- Power me up, Wyatt.
- No!
Tom:
Just do it!
That's an order!
Rainmaker:
Control, where's our help?
Tom: I've got
warlord in my sights.
I'm moving in.
( Buzzes )
- ( Static hiss )
- He's jamming me.
I can't get a missile lock.
I'm switching to guns.
- That won't be necessary.
- ( Beeps )
( Beeping )
Tom, do you see
that number flashing?
( Confused )
Numbers?
Tom, that's a transition code.
You've been programmed
to follow signals
following this number.
Do you understand that?
Yeah.
You do
what's right, Tom.
That's what you've
been trained for.
I'm doing it.
Damn it!
Damn!
I should've taken you
out of the program
a long time ago.
- I'll do it now.
- ( Beeps )
( Pinging )
Warlord is locking
onto outlaw.
- ( Alarm buzzes )
- Outlaws can't be heroes, Tom.
Missile away.
Get the hell
out of there!
Is this how you take care
of your boys, general?
You're goddamn right!
( Alarm beeping )
Son of a bitch.
( Alarm buzzes )
( Both sigh )
- Tom: No.
- Tom?
Oh god.
That's the same code
cowboy got
- just before he...
- Killed himself.
Turn it off.
Turn off the goddamn v.R.
( Keyboard clacks )
I can't.
The general must've
locked US out.
( Breathing heavily )
Tom, now listen to me.
That's the suicide code.
Don't do this, Tom.
Just put the gun down.
Do you hear me?
Put the gun down!
Tom, answer me.
Tom!
Don't be like cowboy.
Just think for yourself, Tom!
Just think for yourself.
You don't have
to die like that.
What the hell
do you believe in, Tom?
What, fighting?
You want someone
to fight with?
Is that what you need?
Well, god damn it,
listen to me!
I will fight
with you, Tom!
Listen to me!
I will fight with you,
you weak bastard!
Tom:
What did you call me?
( Laughs )
( Engine starts )
( Bell dings )
Hey, captain.
Joe, call me Tom,
would you?
Where you headed, Tom?
I figured we'd check out
the countryside
from a different perspective.
I got something for you.
- Here you go.
- Wow, a flight suit.
Man, that's...
- You sure?
- Tom: Yup.
- I'm sure.
- He's not gonna be needing it
where we're going.
( Clicking )
- ( Clicking stops )
- Caitlin: Tom?
- ( Laughs )
- You bas-- ( Laughs )
( Rock music playing )
( Classical score playing )