How are you?
People, I can't hear you.
That's too loud.
Thanks for coming out tonight.
My name is Tig Notaro, and--
No, no, no, no, no.
Let's-- let's relax.
Um...
Who wants to hear
a story about Kool-Aid?
It's about the Kool-Aid Man.
And, um--
I don't know if the commercials
still are on TV. I have no idea.
Has anyone seen
a Kool-Aid commercial?
- Oh, yeah.
- I am not--oh, yeah.
I just found part of my dinner
in my mouth and chewed it.
Yeah, I don't know if the Kool-Aid Man
is on commercials anymore.
I don't care about
if my material is relevant.
I do "Sanford and Son" jokes.
I do whatever feels right.
Does anyone-- is anyone not
familiar with the Kool-Aid Man?
Everyone.
Tig, are you kidding me?
I bet there is somebody
out there that's like,
"Who's the Kool-Aid Man?"
The Kool-Aid Man is a pitcher.
No real clear indication
that he's a man, but--
has kind of a rounded bottom.
But somehow he's for sure a man.
He, I guess, is aware
when people buy Kool-Aid.
Kicks down walls.
Right now,
the person that didn't know
who the Kool-Aid Man is like...
"What?"
Yeah, be careful.
He is out there.
Just to sidetrack here a little,
it reminds me of--
I had this job.
I worked with children.
And there was this woman
that annoyed me to no end.
And when I was cleaning up,
sweeping, she was talking to me.
And I rarely paid attention
to what she said.
And this was so long ago.
And she was, like, going on and on
about dinosaurs and how they were,
you know, eating people.
And I was like, "Wait, what?
Why are we just
standing here?"
And she's like,
"Yeah, like, scientists,
you know, took an insect
and took the blood, and--"
And I was like, "And they're just
running around eating people?"
And she's like, "Yes, I can't believe
you haven't heard about this."
Had no idea it was
"Jurassic Park."
What does that have to do
with the Kool-Aid Man?
I don't even-- I can't even
follow myself here.
Guys, have you seen
the Kool-Aid Man?
He has a round bottom
and a front bottom--
a round, front bottom.
He knows if you've had Kool-Aid.
Kicks walls down,
busts through walls, fences.
You can't just have Kool-Aid.
Oh, I know where
my train of thought was.
I just saw it right there.
This guy was like, "Ah!"
"Ah! Get on with it!"
No.
The Kool-Aid Man
with his round bottom.
You can't just be hanging out
having Kool-Aid.
This guy is coming at you.
Wh-- is he dangerous?
Is he violent?
What is happening?
It's weird enough
for the person who's having
the Kool-Aid
to have the Kool-Aid Man...
End up in their backyard.
That's a weird,
very uncomfortable day.
That sounded like somebody
trying out a new laugh tonight.
Just like,
"I think I'm gonna do it now."
And their friend is like...
"Well, that's a new laugh."
"What? I thought
I'd try it out tonight.
I thought I'd blend in."
"No, you did not."
"When I did it in the car
"on the way,
it felt more natural."
Feel free to try and wedge it in
any other point.
So that's a-- that's an odd day
to be in your backyard,
Kool-Aid Man showing up
with a little rounded bottom
and front bottom.
But think about,
more importantly,
if he's busting through a fence,
that means he was waiting...
In their neighbor's yard...
For God only knows how long.
And even before that was like,
walking through the neighborhood,
you know, just sensing
that somebody got Kool-Aid,
and then coming in the side gate,
waiting on the other-- he was just--
the whole time, nobody really
considers he was waiting
in the neighbor's yard
all that time.
And...
the neighbor is like,
in their kitchen
having breakfast or lunch
and there's just, like,
a little pitcher with a couple of legs.
And then who yells "Kool-Aid?"
Doesn't somebody yell
"Kool-Aid?"
What?
They go, "Hey, Kool-Aid."
And he goes, "Oh, yeah!"
Do you do voice-over?
Are they saying it like,
"Hey, Kool-Aid!"
Like they're happy
that they're having Kool-Aid?
No, like, "You're gonna pay
for that brick wall."
Like, "Pay me."
No, I think that happens before--
then he's like, "Oh, yeah,"
and then he busts down the wall.
Do you under-- do you understand?
We found the person not
familiar with the Kool-Aid Man.
Ah, we caught ya!
I dated somebody years ago,
and I realized
that I was more into them
than they were into me.
And the way I knew this was--
I had to get
all four of my wisdom teeth
surgically removed.
And when you have it done,
they need you to have somebody
drive you there,
sign you in, and sign you out,
agreeing to drive you.
And I asked her
if she could drive me...
to the hospital.
She said that she could not.
The crazy part also being
that, um, she was self-employed.
And I was like, "Really?
"You-- you can't ask
the boss man for this one--
this one favor?"
And then I said,
"Oh, here's an idea.
How about you follow me
to the hospital,
and I'll park my car.
You sign me in,
and then you can just leave.
I'll get the procedure done,
and then I'll just drive myself home."
And she said, "I can do that."
In that moment, I was like, oh,
I like her more than she likes me.
It's confirmed.
So she signed me in
and went off to work.
I love you.
More than I love myself, apparently.
So I get my wisdom teeth
surgically removed.
And when they're moving me
to just kind of recuperate
in this room, I kind of
woke up and realized,
"Oh, yeah.
There's nobody here
to drive me home."
And as soon as the nurses
left the room,
I jumped up
and just started hauling ass
down the hall of the hospital,
all crooked, slamming into walls.
And, uh, I got out to my car,
started it up...
Drove off,
and I was awoken,
when I rear-ended
a car in front of me.
It wasn't really bad.
It was just-- I think I just
fell asleep at a light,
and my foot slid off the brake,
and I just rolled
into the car in front of me.
And the guy jumped out
of his car and was beating
on my window, like,
"What is your problem?"
And I was like, "I'm sorry.
Sorry about that."
There was no damage.
Everything was fine.
And so I continued on.
And when I finally got home,
I was in so much pain that I needed
to get back to the hospital.
I hadn't stopped at the pharmacy
to get pain medication,
so I just had four
gaping holes in my mouth,
and I realized there was no way
that I was gonna be able
to get back to the hospital.
So I went over to my neighbor
and friend Leslie's apartment,
and I knocked on her door.
"Leslie!
Leslie!"
No response.
And in my crazy, drugged-up head,
I had made up the story
that Leslie was in there
and she knew I was in pain
and she was just refusing
to help me.
So I got down.
"Leslie!
Leslie."
I didn't see her.
So I got up, and then I went around
to the front of the apartment.
And one of the other tenants
was in a bikini, sun tanning.
And I come around the corner,
and she's like,
"Oh, my God!"
And I said, " Hi.
"Have you...
seen... Leslie?"
"No."
"Okay.
"Well, if you
"do see Leslie,
"can you tell her that
Tig needs to go
to the hospital?"
"Yes."
"Thank you so much.
"Leslie!
Leslie!"
Just stood next to this woman
in a bikini
throwing pebbles to Leslie's
second floor window.
No response.
So I was like, "You know what?
I'm gonna go ahead
and go back around,
try the door again."
So I went back over up the stairs.
However, this time,
there was a trail of fresh blood
leading to Leslie's door,
with a little pool at her door.
And I was like, "Oh, no!
Leslie! Leslie!"
This time, she opened the door.
And I was like,
"Are you okay?"
That was my blood.
My face was so numb
that I did not realize
that...
I had blood
pouring out of my mouth,
down my shirt.
So if we can for a moment
go back to the woman sunbathing.
How did she not have
a single question for me?
'Cause, I mean,
I am essentially just
pouring blood out of my mouth like,
"Hey, if you see Leslie,
can you tell her that I need
to go to the hospital?"
And she's just like,
"Yeah, absolutely.
I'll let her know."
Not one question.
Like, how about,
"Oh, my God, what happened?"
Or, "Can I take you
to the hospital?"
What is her problem?
I mean, you know, to be fair,
maybe she also was self-employed
and, you know,
was unable to help me out.
My friend that I grew up with--
her mother gave her a car.
And she had to drive it
to Los Angeles
and asked if I would go with her.
And so we hit the road
and filled up on Funyuns
and what have you.
And then she said,
"I feel like I have an aunt
in West Texas somewhere,
and we'll go crash
at her place."
And I was like,
"Sure."
So we pull up to this woman.
I don't remember her name.
Great-Great Aunt Myrtle.
She's like the a-- Yoda--
grew up with Yoda.
I don't think anybody
has ever visited this person.
This elderly woman was just
pacing back and forth
waiting for us once--
Oh, my God.
What do you mean, "Oh, my God"?
There was an old woman
pacing at a window.
So excited somebody
was coming to her house.
My apologies.
We park.
We go in.
We are so tired.
We want to go to bed.
Mm-mm.
Guess who has cooked the equivalent
to a Thanksgiving feast.
Great-Great Aunt Myrtle.
And we're like,
"Oh, my gosh, thank you,"
and sat down
and had to eat apple pie
and mashed potatoes
and just so-- creamed corn.
And, you know,
you're probably not gonna like
what I'm about to say.
She was boring.
All of her stories.
Everybody was dead
that she was talking about.
Our eyes were cr-- we were
so, like, "Oh, my gosh,""
having to eat this food,
tortured by her stories.
"Oh, and you think that's bad?
"Well, you know,
and then she'd come down...
"Do go on.
Do go on."
Oh, my God, I'm so tired.
We get up,
we help her do the dishes,
and then she explains
where our rooms are.
"Thank you so much for dinner,
for letting us stay."
We go to the room, and then we hear,
"Ah, ahh!"
"Ahh!"
This old bat had fallen.
We now have to take her
to the emergency room.
We are up all night
at the hospital with this woman.
She was fine.
She just needed a little
tender love and care.
We bring her back home,
drop her off.
It is now tomorrow.
And we need to just
get back on the road.
We're saying our goodbyes.
She did-- they had gotten her
a walker to help her,
you know, with her hip.
And she was like, "Oh, no,
"you're not getting on the road,
not till
I make you breakfast."
We had to sit down
while she pushed
a walker around
and made us a feast of a breakfast.
Never got sleep, got on the road,
saved 40 bucks on a motel room.
We won.
Thank you.
Um...
You guys--I mean, fir--like,
"Oh, not our Aunt Myrtle!"
And then you're like, "
Yeah, pocket that 40 bucks."
There's no way
she's still alive, by the way.
And probably nobody has found her.
"Oh!
Not our Aunt Myrtle!"
Um... I was in--
before Stephanie and I
got married,
before we were even engaged--
"Aww."
Mm-hmm.
It's a very sweet story
that I'm about to tell you.
I was in Philadelphia,
and I had collapsed
after a show from internal bleeding.
And, um...
- Whoo!
- Thank you.
So, um, I-- luckily,
Stephanie was with me.
And we go-- we go to the hospital.
And when you're bleeding internally,
it is so painful.
It's-- your blood is supposed
to be inside of your veins.
And when it's just
going everywhere, it burns.
And so it was the most pain
I've ever felt in my life.
And I've felt some pain.
And so I was like--
it was this kind of thing.
Very attractive.
And we're not engaged yet.
And I'm--I'm just like--
And I'm-- I'm in the hospital,
and the nurses are lifting me up
to put me on a bedpan.
And, um, I said,
"Is it okay
if I just go everywhere?"
And the nurses were like, "Um...
"Please, no.
"No. We have a bedpan.
That's what--"
But in my drugged mind,
I was just like,
"There's no way you can contain
what I'm about to do."
So I was just like--
"Can I just go on everybody,
just everywhere?"
They were just like, "No."
And so Stephanie was next
to me, and she was just like,
"I love you, I love you,"
as they're putting me on the bedpan.
And I was like--
And then I just thought...
It crossed my mind to be like,
"Will you marry me?"
Even though I was in so much pain
and on so many drugs,
I just thought,
"This would be unbelievable,
"to give her this moment
and to give the nurses
this moment."
I just seemed like the
grossest person in the world.
"Can I use everyone as a toilet?
"And will you...
spend the rest
of your life with me?"
I knew in my drugged-up mind
that it would be so amazing
if people were like,
"Oh, my God, you're engaged.
How did it happen?"
"Well...
"very typical love story.
"Tig was in a diaper.
They took it off."
That weekend together--
we had so many times
where I was like,
"This is the person,"
but that particular time,
I was like,
"We are good, we're all set,"
because I did have
to wear a diaper after that
and I had to have stomach surgery.
And so I was walking about
this fast in a diaper,
just, crinkle, crinkle.
And I couldn't leave Philadelphia.
I had to get a hotel in
Philadelphia to recover there.
So-- but I'm in my little diaper,
crinkle, crinkle,
as I'm moving, and this is
how I knew Stephanie--
I was like,
"Oh, she's the one."
She was laughing so hard
and, like, taking pictures
and videos of right here.
And I was like,
"Okay, fine, fine."
And so I have an entire iPhone
full of just close-ups
of my diapers.
And I just like, "I'm in pain,
but this is funny."
"I'll laugh another time."
Um...
I think I've been hospitalized
six or seven times
in the past six years, and--
- Wow.
- It's a lot.
Like, my-- my stomach is scarred,
and just tonight I was saying
to Stephanie-- I was like,
"This is hilarious.
You have one here,
one here, one here."
You know, the tits got
yanked off a few years ago,
tossed in a dumpster somewhere,
an alley in Hollywood.
I like to picture
just rodents fighting over...
When people ask, "Where--
where did your boobs go?"
I truly assume
they're just in an alley,
just getting run over.
A doctor cut 'em off,
tossed 'em and out the window.
What else?
Um...
Uh, do you guys know
the comedian Jenny Slate?
I was just curious.
I've known Jenny for years.
She's not, like, my best friend.
But we had each other's numbers,
and she texted me and said,
"Hey, I'm moving to L.A.
Do you want to have tea?"
And I said,
"I'm not feeling very well.
"I've been in bed.
"I should probably be better
in a couple of days.
Let's get in touch then."
Jenny said, "Feel better."
She texted me in a couple of days.
"How you feeling, Tig?
Wanna have tea?"
"Jenny, turns out
I have pneumonia now.
"I can't have tea, but, uh,
when I'm feeling better,
absolutely, we'll grab tea."
Jenny texts me,
"How you feeling?"
"Oh, my gosh, Jenny.
I'm in the hospital.
"Uh, I have developed a disease.
"It's eating my digestive tract.
I can't have tea."
And she was like,
"Oh, my God."
And she said, "I'm going to Boston
"to get married this weekend.
I will check back in with you
when I'm back."
And I'm like,
"Okay, well, congrats."
I mean, I wasn't even invited
to her wedding, you know?
But, like, she's moving to L.A.
She wants to grab coffee. Sure.
She gets back to town,
and she's like, "Hey,
just seeing how you're doing."
"Jenny, I am now
out of the hospital,
"but my mother has had
a terrible accident,
and I have to go take her off
life support."
She's like, "Oh, my God."
"Yeah, I am so sorr--
I ju-- I'm sorry. Um...
Sorry for the inconvenience."
But, like, poor Jenny Slate.
I mean, okay,
I'm sure there were, like,
20 people that she was like,
"Hey, I'm moving to town.
Let's get tea."
She got caught up
in my swirling hell,
and had to keep checking in with me.
And now every ti-- I'm like,
"Oh, my God,
what am I gonna tell Jenny?"
"Jenny, I'm feeling a lot better.
"You know,
I'm gonna come through this.
"We will have our tea,
but I just gotta
to pull myself together a bit."
She checks in again.
And I was like, "Oh...
"my God.
"Jenny,
I have cancer."
And she was just like,
"What is going on?"
Like, every time
she contacted me, I was like--
it got worse and worse
and worse and worse.
Okay, I come through all of this,
and I was on my couch,
in recovery,
emotionally, physically.
Somebody had sent me
a huge bouquet of balloons.
You know, those just, like,
20 balloons kind of bouquet,
and it's like--you know?
Have you seen those?
They're gigantic.
And there was--
somebody had sent that.
It was taking up half of my loft.
It was like "Get well,"
"Feel better," "Hang in there,"
"Oh, my God,"
"Yikes,"
"Hoo, boy."
So Jenny comes over to my loft
to have tea, finally.
And we're sitting there on my couch.
And, um-- and I was just barely
able to move at this point.
And I told Jenny, I said, "You know,
I've been sitting here
looking at these balloons."
I was like, "I want to release
"these balloons out into the world
"with a note that says,
'Hello, my name is Tig Notaro.
'I-- I have cancer,
but I'm--
I'm gonna beat this.'"
And, uh, Jenny's like,
"That is such a great idea.
Let's shove these
out of the window."
And so we open the window.
I'm like--
Pushing, you know.
All these huge balloons.
We're, like,
getting it across the room.
And-- and we push all these balloons
with all these little messages
out of my window.
And it has this little note
attached to it.
And out they went,
and it was this really
kind of freeing moment
that the balloons went out.
And then they immediately
got stuck on the fire escape
of the apartment right above me.
So now the man that lives above me
has just gotten this
outrageous message
from this cancer-riddled person,
just like, "Hey, I have--
"This is what's been
going on down here,
"but I'm doing a lot better.
I'm coming through it."
That's essentially
what he had to deal with
and pull off of his fire escape
and drag into his window,
thinking I was sending him
that message.
And then the awkwardness...
In the lobby and elevator
after that,
just like, "How you doing?
"I'm still doing well.
Thank you.
How are your balloons?"
This is a very stupid thought
that I had,
and I just have
to share it with you.
Why are they called "pigs"?
Why weren't they just called "bigs"?
Guys, I'm sorry.
They're big.
That's dumb, I know,
but it still crossed my mind.
Oh, my gosh, there's a spider.
So you guys were watching the--
It's coming down.
"It's coming down."
I love that this spider
lives up there
and is just like,
"Who is...
"Who is performing tonight?
Not a fan."
This spider is like, "Oh, I thought that
was Demetri Martin, but--"
I mean, he's hauling ass right now.
So you guys were watching
a spider come down,
and you didn't tell me.
- We didn't wanna interrupt.
- Didn't want to interrupt?
There was a spider
coming down.
Let me put it this way.
If there's ever a spider
coming down on top of me
during my show
when I'm talking about all
the deadly diseases I had...
Interrupt my show.
I don't want
to be bitten by a spider
'cause God knows Jenny Slate
is gonna wanna have tea.
I was so into Van Halen as a kid.
And, um, like,
I loved Eddie Van Halen.
I just--to this day,
I still just really enjoy him.
Any time he played guitar,
I was just like,
"Oh, my gosh."
And I played soccer.
And I would be outside
just juggling the soccer ball
for hours, just going at it.
And there was-- there
was woods right by my house.
I would make up that Eddie Van Halen
heard I was out
juggling the soccer ball
and, uh,
would just appear out of the woods,
not to where
I could totally see him,
but he'd lean against a tree.
And just in my head, he was like,
"You're doing
a great job, kid."
So that means that Van Halen
was on their tour bus...
Driving along,
and Eddie was just like,
"Guys, there's this little girl
"in Spring, Texas,
"juggling a soccer ball
"for hours on end.
"We need to pull off the route here
and swing by, and I just need
to check how she's doing."
And there he was, every time
I juggled a soccer ball.
I never looked 'cause I didn't
wanna scare him away.
I was just like, "I know
you're back there, Eddie.
I know you think I'm great."
All right, that's not worth sharing.
You don't have
to share everything, Tig.
I was thinking about my life
and how I identify with being cool.
I am a cool person.
That is what gets me through,
is being cool.
I smoked from the time
I was, like, four
until I was 25.
So, you know, that's kinda tough.
And I kind of had this total
Fonzarelli vibe about me.
But as a kid,
in many times in my life,
I have blown my cool,
where I'm just, like, out there
trying to be
an interesting little person,
and then, boom, blow my cool.
My friend lived on a farm,
and she asked me
if I wanted to come over
and ride motorcycles
out in the pasture with her.
"Uh, yeah.
"If I'm not doing it at your place,
I'm doing it at mine."
I have seen people ride motorcycles.
It's not that hard.
Yeah, I'll be over
to ride motorcycles
through your pasture.
I got over to her house,
and they were just, like,
little tiny motorcycles.
And in my head,
before I got over there,
it was like,
"Yeah, I know how to ride
a motorcycle."
And then as I was getting
closer to it, I was thinking,
"Oh, my God, I don't know
how to ride a motorcycle."
And it was just a minibike,
which wasn't as complicated,
I guess,
but I put it in gear
and gunned it.
And you know that reckless,
horrible feeling
where you're going over
a bump and into a hole
and over a bump and
there is no control over it?
And then I slammed into the fence.
And I was in so much pain.
But I was so cool
that I couldn't even reveal
that I wanted my mommy.
Fonzarelli wanted her mommy.
I was just like, "Ohh."
And I was still
regularly wetting my pants
at that point in my life.
Blowing my cool constantly.
Just a horseshoe of urine
all the time.
"I don't have time
to use a toilet."
I am riding motorcycles
through pastures--
horseshoe of urine.
Do you know what I would do
to cover that up?
I'd go sit in a puddle.
Really, I-- the world was my toilet.
Anything was fine.
A bed?
Sure.
A friend spent the night.
I woke up.
They were covered in my urine,
sleeping like a baby.
I woke up my friend.
I was like, "I am so sorry.
"My cat...
"She always does this.
This is gross.
This is gross."
There was another time
I blew my cool.
I play guitar.
And I was kinda known in my school
for being pretty amazing
even though nobody had seen me play.
And there was a talent show,
and this girl asked me if
I would play a song with her.
And, uh, I was like,
"Yeah.
You came to the right one."
So we rehearsed, I guess,
one time at her house,
and I can't really remember
what that was like.
I don't imagine it went that well
because show day,
we were introduced,
we come out onstage,
she's playing piano,
and she's singing,
and I'm up there,
you know, in my head.
I was just Eddie Van Halen.
About three strums in,
I forgot all of the chords.
There was even a guitar solo
I was supposed to go into,
and none of that happened.
So at the talent show,
it was just the girl playing piano
and me standing there
with my guitar on...
For four minutes.
It went absolutely nowhere,
and I remember her
looking back at me like,
"You know,
you can pick up anywhere."
"Mm-mm.
"No, I cannot.
I'll just stand here while
you finish out the song."
Just a guitar
right there around my neck.
I mean, I'm sure
it went around my back,
not, like, around my neck
like a complete nerd.
The worst day of my life.
Let's end with a fun story,
shall we?
No way.
I went-- I went on the road,
on tour, a few years ago
with some friends of mine.
And we brought--
you know, it was--
it was a few years ago.
We brought our favorite CDs, and--
does that ever happen anymore?
Well, I brought
Dolly Parton's "Greatest Hits."
Yeah. That's right.
She is beyond a national treasure.
She's an international treasure.
She's just a precious person.
And, I mean, who-- it's like,
who doesn't like Dolly Parton?
Every now and then-- okay.
Who doesn't like Dolly Parton?
Clap if you don't like Dolly Parton.
Okay, psychopath right there.
That's the only answer.
To not like Dolly Parton,
it's just like there's
a psychopath in the room.
So we're listening
to Dolly Parton's "Greatest Hits."
Then this song--
one of her songs is called,
"Three Doors Down."
It's so good.
It is so Dolly, okay?
It is the Dolly
we know and love, okay?
- Did I say "Three Doors Down"?
- Yeah.
That's not a Dolly Parton song.
I think that's a band.
"Two Doors Down." Dolly Parton's song
is "Two Doors Down."
I promise I'm a fan of hers.
It's really, really a great song.
And I asked my friends,
I said, "Hey, do you mind if we listen
to that song again?"
And they're like, "Okay."
They play it.
And then I was like,
"You know what?"
And they kind of
came around to it, like,
"Yeah, this is a really good song.
It's so fun."
And so I just said, "Why don't
we just put it on repeat?"
So we did, and we must've listened
to it, like, 30 times.
All right, let me tell this
story from the beginning.
I'm flying down the road with
my friends Martha and Steve.
We're listening to the song
over and over.
We were smiling.
We were glad.
We were having a blast.
You haven't seen a happier group.
And then...
There's this part of the song
where the-- the song slows down a bit
and hits a minor key.
And I started to imagine a reality
where things maybe
weren't so fun anymore.
I started to imagine we were
losing control of the car,
just sliding off the road.
The car starts
flipping sideways, longways.
The car's upside down.
Then, in this alternative reality,
we come to a crashing halt,
all three of us
gurgling on our own blood,
watching each other die
slow, painful, imaginary deaths.
But if you remember, it's on repeat.
Thank you.
Good night.