[ominous music]
♪♪
[Man] They told me but
I had no idea.
[woman panting]
[country rock on radio]
[woman moaning]
[trucker moaning]
[diesel engine rumbling]
[lighter flicking]
["Pets" by Porno for Pyros]
[horn honks]
♪ Children are innocent ♪
♪ And teenagers fucked
up in the head ♪
♪ Adults are even
more fucked up ♪
♪ And elderlies
are like children ♪
♪ Will there be another race ♪
♪ To come along and
take over for us ♪
[radio chattering]
[Trucker On CB] Breaker
1-9, this is R-Danger-7,
crossing into the Sooner State,
heading for Candy Land.
Any angels on the airwaves
listening out there?
Danger, Danger. How
you doin', baby?
You recognize this voice?
How could I forget?
Merry Christmas,
kitten. How you doin'?
[urine splashing]
[man moaning with pleasure]
[toilet flushes]
♪ My friend says we're
like the dinosaurs ♪
♪ Only we are doing
ourselves in ♪
♪ Much faster then they ♪
[Woman] Any plans
for the holidays?
♪ We'll make great pets ♪
The kingdom awaits you.
Follow God in the
great cleansing.
The kingdom starts
with your family.
God wants you to repent
so you can join us in
the kingdom of Heaven.
♪ We'll make great pets ♪
- ♪ We'll make great pets ♪
- [man chattering indistinctly]
You know, the ones
and the twos, okay?
Oh, and there she
is. The lady herself.
Oh, oh.
[woman laughs]
You got the steps.
Y'all are so stupid.
[Levi] Oh, you just don't know
how to have a good time.
- [Levi] Oh, Sadie-bug.
- [laughing] No!
Give me a bite of that Sno Ball.
I'm fucking starving. No.
Come on, girly girl, just...
Get out of here, Levi.
Thank you.
You're a bum!
♪ We'll make great pets ♪
Levi.
I'll be there with you
by the white truck.
Uh, Sadie, just so you know,
when I'm done with this,
I'm gonna go buy every
Sno Ball that Max has,
and if you want another one,
you're gonna have to come
and beg me for it, all right?
So fuck you.
[women laughing]
[Riley wincing in pain]
Ooh.
You okay?
Yeah, fucking cramps.
Aw, man. You want
me to get something?
No, it's okay.
I already took something
earlier. Thank you.
Ugh, I might actually have to
cum for one of these Johns.
- [Liv laughs]
- It hurts, it hurts!
You can get me off
if you want [laughs].
Ugh, I thought they left.
[horn blaring in distance]
Oh, God.
Have you all repented?
No, no. Thank you.
Pass.
I know what it is you do.
I can see right
through you, your sins,
and so can Heavenly Father.
Repent, or you will be left
for the final cleansing.
Ooh, the final cleansing.
[Liv laughs]
What's your name?
Theo.
You gonna teach
me how to repent?
Oh, yes. Yes.
We will show you the way
to the kingdom of Heaven.
There is still time for you.
You gonna show me your cock
- before God's Kingdom, Theo?
- [Sadie laughs]
[women laughing]
God help you, child.
He hasn't helped
me yet, I'm sorry.
[women laughing]
Oh my God.
What are you doing?
[Sadie] What's happening?
- [van engine starts]
- [Riley chuckling]
[van doors shutting]
That's probably the first
eagle he's ever seen.
[women chuckle]
[Woman] Hey, Sadie-bug.
Hey, Nora.
Are you tired?
You know you have someone
coming at 8:00, right?
Yeah, I'm just gonna shower.
Okay.
[gentle music]
[ominous music]
[knocking on door]
Fuck.
Ho, ho, ho.
What's up, Rex?
[Rex] Levi, why
don't you hop in?
I'm all right, Rex.
Come on, Levi.
Nah, I didn't walk straight
for a week last time.
And I'm hungry, so...
How about I get you a burger?
No. I'm alright, Rex.
But thank you all the same.
Get in the fucking truck, Levi.
[Sadie slurps drink]
[Levi] What the fuck am I
supposed to do with this?
Why don't you use that big
old noodle of yours, Levi?
Surprise me.
Rex, there's a hair on this.
It's not even fucking clean.
You got a mouth.
Clean it.
[Levi hocks spit]
This better be some
fucking burger, Rex.
Best damn burger you ever had.
♪ When we finally
kiss good night ♪
♪ How I'll hate going
out in this storm ♪
♪ But if you really
hold me tight ♪
♪ All the way home,
I'll be warm ♪
♪ And the fire is slowly dying ♪
♪ And my dear, we're
still goodbye-ing ♪
- ♪ But as long as... ♪
- Hey.
What are you doing back here?
Are you okay?
She said I needed
to cleanse them.
"She"?
Um, where did "she" go?
She left.
Hey, you were in
the car yesterday
with those people, right?
What's your name?
[ominous music]
Remy.
- [Riley humming]
- [urine splashing]
Thank you, truck stop gods.
[ominous music]
[Riley humming]
What the fuck?
[ominous music]
You okay in there?
I just got my period
too [chuckles].
Oh, please be a joke.
Oh, my God!
Sadie!
- Sadie!
- What?
Um, there's, like, a
dead guy in the bathroom.
What?
[ominous music]
Son of a bitch.
Well...
You kinky freak.
[stall door squeaks]
What...
did you leave me?
Hm.
Show me, show me, show me.
[ominous music]
Hm.
[Rex sniffs]
So Maxine, you didn't
see nothing weird,
nothing suspicious, huh?
No, just a normal Tuesday, Rex.
I already told you.
[Rex] All right.
[ominous music]
[truck horn blares]
- [crushes can]
- [Rex] One more time.
What the fuck is
wrong with you, Rex?
Don't you fuck with me, Riley.
Nora, what the fuck
is wrong with him?
I was peeing.
I got my period.
I bought a tampon, and he was
just fucking dead like that
when I found him.
You don't say.
Can you just leave, please?
She didn't do it.
What, did you have
a fucking hunch?
There's my hunch.
Oh.
Look, I'd love for
it to be that cunt
more than anybody else,
and you know that.
But she ain't good for nothing
but giving mango cakes.
She ain't no killer.
[Nora] What do we do now?
Nothing.
They took the body,
bring it to the morgue,
bury it in a few days.
Life goes on, Nora.
Who was he?
Who fucking cares?
[ominous music on TV]
[indistinct chatter from TV]
[Sadie] How's Riley?
She's fine.
I think she just needs
to be left alone.
Who's this?
She's from that weirdo cult,
the 13 somethings.
[Liv] My cousin went to
a few of their meetings.
They think they're
gonna leave for Heaven
before the rest of us.
[indistinct chatter from TV]
[Nora] So what are
you doing here?
They made her leave, I think.
I don't know.
I just didn't think it was safe
to let her stay
at the stop alone,
especially after what happened.
Hm.
Okay, who's got
something for me?
On the TV.
Yeah, mine's there too.
[Nora] Okay.
Night.
[door squeaks]
[Liv coughs]
[ladies moan]
Hey.
Hey, pumpkin.
You snored.
Yeah, you too.
[kissing]
[knocking on door]
Levi.
Hey. Let's go eat.
All right, give me a second.
Yo, Riley!
Let's go eat.
[Riley] Go away.
[Liv laughs]
Mm-mm.
["Run Rudolph Run"
by Chuck Berry]
All right, so we got
root beer for Sadie,
- Sprite for Livy.
- Thank you, baby.
And Coke for Remy.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
You're gonna let me
order for you, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, good.
You ever had a Coney?
No. What is it?
- She's never had a coney!
- [Liv laughs]
It's like, uh, it's like
a hot dog, pretty much.
Okay.
You've had a hot dog, yeah?
- No fucking way!
- [Liv laughs]
Okay, uh, it's like a sausage.
You're gonna like 'em.
But my grandfather
once, in under an hour,
ate 21 of them bad boys.
- Oh, here we go.
- No, no, no. He did, he did.
Yeah, he did, and they put his
plaque on the wall over there
- Oh, really?
- Yes! He did. For years.
[Liv] Oh, yeah?
[Levi] Mm-hm.
What happened to him?
I mean, he died, like everybody.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
So how long have
you worn this getup?
Since I was a girl.
How long have you worked
at the truck stop?
For a little while.
[music continues]
What?
Nothing.
Come on, say it. What is it?
Just, how can you...
how could you do that?
- [Liv sighs]
- [Levi chuckles]
I hate that question.
I'm sorry, I don't...
No, it's okay.
I don't think too much about it.
It's just a way to make
some money for now.
You?
I mean, you don't
think I've worked a job
for six bucks an hour?
I've done that.
Turn one trick, make a
whole day's pay, you know?
It's kind of hard to
go back after that.
I just like to party.
[Liv laughs]
- Slut.
- You know,
you make a little dough.
It's not a bad gig.
But you're gay.
No.
You know, I can blow the horn,
but, well, I like ladies too.
We're together.
But it's, you know,
it's whatever.
What about you, Remy?
What do you wanna do?
I don't know.
Are you gonna go home?
I can't go home.
Why not?
I just can't.
Okay? I can't go back.
So I got someone coming over.
You're gonna have to
wait outside the room
for a little bit, okay?
Okay.
You know, I can talk to Nora
and probably get her to let
you stay another couple days
while you figure out
what you wanna do.
Thank you.
All right.
I'll make it quick.
[engine rumbling]
[truck door squeaks]
[truck door slams]
[footsteps approach]
- [door squeaks]
- Hey.
[Client] Hey, baby.
[couple chatters inside room]
[door squeaks]
[lighter flicks]
Still here, huh?
Why don't you come wait inside.
It's okay. I like it out here.
Thank you, though.
Oh, come on.
They don't like you hanging
out out here anyway.
Come on. I'll make some tea.
[client in room moans]
You're so pretty.
People must say that
to you all the time.
They don't?
Well, then you are hanging
out with the wrong people.
Sadie's a nice girl, huh?
Yeah. She's really nice.
They're all really good kids.
And they take care of
each other, you know?
'Cause it's rough out there.
And it's nice to have
someone who has your back.
But we have a rule.
You stay, you work.
But if you work, we
take care of you.
Hey, don't be so nervous.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
So what do you think?
You think you wanna stay
with us for a while?
Good.
Stand up for me.
[ominous music]
Look at you.
Where do they even
get these dresses?
Where is that store?
I mean, is it like
a pioneer thing?
It's so pervy.
[ominous music]
Don't be ashamed.
You really are an angel.
I have to ask, have you ever
even kissed someone before?
No.
Not so bad, huh?
[ominous music]
[Sadie] So, this whole
lot is exit 17.
There's three stops
like ours on route 66,
but if you're heading west,
this is the last stop
for any quality action.
If you wanna unbuckle
the bible belt,
this is the place to do it.
Good, clean, old-fashioned,
drug-free pussy.
And dick.
We have a bit of
a reputation here,
and we're so proud of it.
Hey, you know, Riley's mom,
she worked exit 17.
Gave it the nickname,
too. Candy Land.
So there's four parts.
The pit. Think of it
as a neighborhood.
Yeah, you'd never just
walk up to any old house
and knock on the door
at 3:00 AM and be like,
"Hey, how's it going? You
want your cock sucked?"
There's rules.
If someone wants company,
they'll let you know.
[Sadie] The first is simple,
back-in parking.
Next is more of the same,
if they flash their lights.
Remember, they're
watching for you too.
Next is the bathroom
cruisers. Levi?
So your bathrooms are for
your thrill seekers, you know,
not just about getting off,
but about not getting caught.
Stalls around here
are most active
in the afternoon
and the evening.
I usually post up in the stall
at the end, against the wall.
When someone comes in,
[door squeaks open]
you can tell a lot by
their body language.
Do they go straight
to take a piss?
[urine splashing]
Do they bust through the
door and take a shit?
[man farts]
Or do they come in casually?
And if they do, I
start to tap my foot.
[boot tapping]
If they tap back,
then it's game on.
You know, and a lot of
these cats are not truckers.
They're married men,
and proud of it too.
They're just looking
for a little excitement.
Who's that?
That's Rex. Don't
worry about him.
Not unless you're Levi.
[Levi] Mm-hm.
[Liv] Babe, the radio.
Right. Go.
So we use these.
[static crackles]
[Liv] We're listening
for our code words,
[CB radio chatter]
commercial company,
angels on the
airwaves, lot lizards,
or anyone who says they're
headed for Candy Land.
[Trucker On CB] I-9,
this is Hot-Karl
heading for Candy Land.
Any lizards running today?
33.
So once they put out the signal,
we have 'em flip over
to a private channel,
and there, we make plans.
Hot-Karl, what did
you have in mind?
[Sadie] And no matter what,
you always use one of these.
They'll beg you not to, but
don't be stupid like Levi.
Or for an extra 40
bucks, you can always
- ride bare back.
- Stop.
- Do not listen to him.
- It's...
So what do you think? You ready?
Wait, now?
[chuckles] No, I'm kidding.
Relax, we're not
gonna start you here.
So, this is your room.
Liv was nice enough
to move in with Sadie
so that you could
have it for yourself.
Do whatever you want with
it. Make it your own.
And I got you something.
Why don't you try it on.
We'll let you get settled.
[ominous music]
- [engine rumbling]
- [ominous music]
[gravel crackling]
[ominous music]
[knocking on door]
Wow. You look like a real woman.
How do you feel?
[Remy] I feel okay.
[Nora] Great. I'm so
glad to hear it.
We have a guy coming to see you.
He's a really nice man.
He's super gentle.
We don't let guys
in here who aren't,
you know, people we trust.
It is okay to be a
little nervous and shy.
That's fine. It's normal.
But I know that
deep down inside,
there's a woman who
is dying to come out.
So don't be afraid
to enjoy yourself.
You're gonna be great.
And you know I'll
be right next door,
so just knock if you need me.
[Remy] Okay.
[Levi sighs]
You a Goodbuddy?
[Client] Sure am.
I'm looking for a little... fun.
All right. Well,
what you looking for?
[Client] What's on the menu?
Well, we've got 40,
60,
and 80.
[Client] Fine as you are,
I'd hate myself not saying 80.
[Levi chuckles]
Well, you wanna slide in the
back and let me join you?
[Client] It's a little,
uh, tight in here.
Why don't we, uh,
go back over there,
someplace quiet.
[ominous music]
[Levi] All right, here work?
[Client] Yeah.
Then what are you waiting for?
You gonna whip that thing out?
[Client] Why don't you
come help me with it.
Okay.
[pants unzipping]
- [fist thuds]
- [Levi grunts]
[blow thuds]
- [Levi screams]
- [blow thuds]
[man grunting]
[Levi whimpers]
[assailant] You fucking
make a sound,
I'm gonna slit your
fucking throat.
- Do you understand me?
- [Levi sobbing]
[Levi] Yes.
[assailant] You understand me?
[Levi] Yes, yes, yes!
- [assailant grunting]
- [Levi whimpers]
[Levi coughing]
[assailant moans]
[Levi whimpers]
- [Levi screams]
- [metal clangs]
- [Levi crying]
- [metal clanging]
[Levi cries]
[knocking on door]
[man] Hi, there.
May I come in?
My name's Father Phillip.
What's your name?
Remy.
Remy?
I hear you're a Christian.
How cool is that? So am I.
Do you say your prayers
every night, Remy?
Yes.
That's good.
You can never get too
old to say your prayers.
May I take a seat next to you?
My gosh.
You are so beautiful.
[Priest inhales sharply]
They told me, but I had no idea.
I rushed over here to meet you.
Oh, you don't have to be scared.
I couldn't hurt a fly.
Is there something
I can do for you?
Oh, you're so sweet.
What if I did something for you?
How would you like that?
[Remy breathes heavily]
Okay.
Great.
Well, why don't you lay back.
There you go.
[ominous music]
[Priest inhales sharply]
[Remy breathes heavily]
[ominous music]
[Remy moans]
[Father Phillip] Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
[ominous music]
[Remy] Oh, Lord.
[Father Phillip] Yeah.
I ask for your forgiveness.
[Father Phillip screams]
Cleanse me.
I receive your grace.
[Father Phillip screams]
I accept your forgiveness
and your sacrifice
[Father Phillip screaming]
to pay my debt.
[Father Phillip screams]
Cleanse me.
- [neck snapping]
- [body thudding]
[Remy exhales deeply]
Amen.
[Remy breaths heavily]
[ominous music]
[knife scrapes cheek]
[knocking on door]
Hold on.
You okay?
Yeah.
Come here.
It's all right.
It's over, okay?
♪ Happy V-Day to you ♪
♪ Happy V-Day, dear Remy ♪
[Remy] What is this?
It's a cherry cupcake,
for the girl who
just lost her cherry.
[Liv] Oh, yeah. Blow it out.
[ladies laugh]
[Remy] This looks really good.
Levi?
Levi, what happened to you?
Baby, what happened?
[Levi sobbed]
Barely nicked you.
You got lucky, kiddo.
You'll be all right.
Give him a little Bactroban.
I'm just glad you're okay.
So what do you think?
You think it was the same
guy from the bathroom?
Stands to reason.
He did say he'd
carve my throat up.
Seemed like his thing too.
Hey.
How's your back end?
Why, just swell, Rex.
Thanks.
So what now? Are you
gonna call it in?
You sure he's cooked?
You don't wanna call
this kind of thing in,
it just creates more problems,
more eyes on the lot.
You got the same son of a bitch
that carved up
our bathroom John,
and I'll bet dollars
to donuts it is,
then you did a
great thing, Levi.
You did a real great thing.
Now we just gotta clean it up.
Fuck.
[truck engine rumbling]
Face looks like scrambled eggs.
You weren't fucking around.
Yeah, what was I supposed to do?
Well, what could you do?
You got nothing to
worry about, Levi.
No one's gonna come
looking for this psycho.
Why don't you grab his feet.
[Rex breathing heavily]
I'm glad you're okay, Levi.
I'm glad you're not hurt.
Thanks, Rex.
I care about you, Levi.
I've got feelings for you.
Okay.
Claudia's a good woman.
Cooks, cleans, knows when to
keep her fucking mouth shut.
But she just doesn't
have that wow factor.
You wow me every time, son.
Every time.
What the fuck are you doing?!
[Rex] Kiss me.
Rex, stop! No, not tonight!
Not tonight, no!
I just thought...
What do you mean
what am I doing?
- What are...
- What...
[Levi] Can we, can
we please just...
Fuck you!
[Levi] Please, can
we please just go
move the body, please?
- Please?
- Fuck you.
All right, just, just, let's go.
Can we go?
You've got some fucking nerve.
♪ So tender and mild ♪
♪ Sleep in heavenly peace ♪
[knocking on door]
[farts]
Go away.
[knocking on door]
What the fuck?
- [girls laugh]
- God damn it.
Sadie!
Hi.
Turn around, Jonah.
I remember you.
Did you come to
show me that cock?
Take me to God's kingdom?
We're here to see Remy.
[Sadie] You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
It's okay, I'll
meet you over there.
[truck horn blares]
[Theo] Would you like
to put on some clothes?
[women laughing]
Psst.
Hey, cutie.
[women laughing]
What are you doing here, Theo?
I could ask you the
same thing, but I won't.
I didn't ask to withdraw.
I want you to try
and hear me, okay?
-Your mind has been poisoned,
-[disjointed music]
and I know it is not your fault.
I recognize that, I do.
Your mother and her beliefs,
they were not that of the
apostles, but of her own.
She instilled them into you,
and I need you to see that.
That is why you were
asked to withdraw.
Theo, my mother
taught you how to see,
and you turned on her.
I did not turn on her, Remy.
- Yes, you did.
- I did not.
She became ill, Remy.
Ill.
And when that happened, she
changed. Her mind changed.
She became barbaric,
with no mercy for
the dissenters.
Now I've made peace with
her since she left us,
and I am grateful for the
life that she showed me,
and that is why I feel I
owe the same debt to you.
We are not here to cleanse
the dissenters of the world.
We are here to cleanse
ourselves of this world,
and when we are cleansed,
then we will leave it.
Theo.
Your mind has
always been so small.
Ye shall tear down
their altars, Theo,
rip down their sacred
constructs, and burn them,
cut down the images
of their gods,
and erase their
memories of this place.
You know this.
You are so lost.
We must be the ones
to drive the stakes
into their hands and their feet,
for they cannot
do it themselves.
We must cleanse the world
before we can cleanse
- ourselves of it.
- Stop it.
Stop it, please.
I just came here to tell
you that we are leaving.
The other elders and myself,
we have decided that it is time.
When?
Tomorrow morning.
And I know that we asked
for your withdrawal,
and I know that our
beliefs are not the same,
but deep inside you, Remy,
there is a light so bright.
And I know that. And
so does the Lord.
And we just thought
that we owed you
the opportunity to come with us.
You know where to find us.
Say goodbye to your sister.
Hey.
How are you?
Good.
Theo says we're leaving soon.
Are you coming with us?
I'll think about it.
Come, Jonah. It's time.
It's time. Let's go.
[ominous music]
Father.
Father... I am ready for you.
[Remy] Use me.
[ominous music continues]
Guide my hands to
do your bidding.
I am ready.
How come... your legs are...
I shaved today.
Alright, well, yeah, but
like when it's, like, cold,
like, my hair just grows
back so fucking fast.
Like, yours are all smooth.
Look at mine.
These are nice.
No, I have strawberry legs.
What?! What's a strawberry leg?
I have, like,
black dots on my legs,
so when I shave, and it,
it's just, like, it
always looks hairy.
It's really unbecoming.
It's really...
[Remy] Hey.
[Sadie] Only you
would notice that.
Hey.
Is everything okay?
Everything's okay.
You want a smoke?
No, I'm okay. Thank you.
Okay.
We'll break you down
though, soon enough.
[Levi] Oh, Sadie-bug, let me
get your cigarette.
Hey, you feel okay?
Yeah, I'm okay. Thanks.
[truck horn blares]
Heads up.
Oh, man. I just sat down.
I'm gonna go get
something to eat.
No, no.
I need to eat.
I need...
Don't do that!
And my fucking feet, too.
Well, who's gonna go?
I'm not going.
Hey, why don't you go down?
Riley, fuck me.
Come on, she's not ready
for the pit, okay?
- Sadie.
- I'll go.
Stop.
Hold on.
Yeah, I can do it.
[Riley] Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
Mm-hm.
What'd I tell you?
- You got a rubber?
- Mm-hm.
Yeah.
You've got this, girl.
Go.
You've got it.
There she goes.
[truck engine rumbling]
[pants unzip]
All right, let's
do half and half.
Money's in the cup holder.
You ain't touching
it 'til you're done.
What, you just gonna sit there?
Come on. Mash your motor, honey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
- I was...
- No, no, no, no.
I'm not wearing no raincoat.
There's an extra 40 in there.
All right?
So quit your fucking
lolly-gagging
and give me that
bean cap, right now.
Woo, woo!
Hey! Get over here,
you little whore.
[trucker screams]
[ominous music]
[Remy screams]
[Remy breathes heavily]
[ominous music]
[toilet flushes]
Oh. Hey, babe.
So how did, uh, how'd it go?
Good. It went good.
[Liv laughs]
What is that?
Remy, what is that?
[ominous music]
Shh...
[Remy] Just witness.
[Liv groans]
[Woman] I'll meet you outside.
Meet me at the car.
[ominous music]
[water running]
[Liv gasping]
Hello?
[Liv gurgling]
Are you okay?
- [woman screams]
- [blade slashing]
- [woman crying]
Hey, catch.
Thank you.
No problem.
How are you?
I'm good.
I heard that some guy
came by the motel for you.
Yeah.
Is that, like, your dad, or
your brother, or something?
You got, like, a
boyfriend or something?
- No.
- No?
That's cool.
He likes to think
that he's, like,
my dad, or my older
brother, but he's not.
Yeah, I was just asking.
[engine rumbling]
Looks like you're up.
Hold that.
You can have it.
I'll save it for you.
Okay.
Uh, hi.
Hi.
Uh, to tell you the truth,
I haven't done this before,
and I really don't
know what to say.
Why are you here?
Uh, well, let's see.
Well, I suppose I'm lonely,
just looking to feel
the touch of a woman.
But now you must be cleansed.
Um, is that part of the game?
Salvation is not a game, silly.
Clothe yourself in him.
Make no provisions of the
flesh to fulfill its desires.
[man exhales deeply]
Um, you know, I think
maybe this was a mistake.
I think I'm gonna
be leaving now.
I'm so sorry, sweetie.
No, no.
Let me do this for you.
[ominous music]
[indistinct EMS radio chatter]
[inaudible dialogue]
Why don't you get
some rest, honey?
I'm right down the hall. Okay?
I'm so sorry, Sadie.
Come here, Rem.
Come here.
Nobody goes out tonight, okay?
Just stay in.
[ominous music]
[door squeaks]
["Joy to the World"]
♪ It's the time of
the year again ♪
♪ For you to share ♪
♪ All the love that you
have with everyone ♪
[man] Yeah, let it snow.
Gonna get this shit today.
- [knocking on door]
- ♪ Christmas day is here ♪
Have you been naughty or nice?
Oh my god, Bruce. Not today.
What?
You ain't got a
fucking sense of humor?
Dead in a truck stop bathroom?
Yeah.
I wouldn't have
come if I'd known.
I've been at the mall all day
getting coughed on,
beard getting pulled,
shitty diapers.
Just another Christmas.
But hey, I'm still here,
so what the fuck, you know?
Yeah.
I'll get outta your hair though.
Just let me finish
this drink first.
You know, I'm gonna see
if another one of the
girls is available.
Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Seriously?
[Nora] Yeah.
Oh shit, yeah.
She could tell a fella, baby.
[truck horn blaring]
[Bruce sighs]
Why don't you stop
what you're doing,
come in here, and
sit on Santa's lap.
[Riley chuckles]
Oh, yeah. There you go.
There it is.
Take a load off, baby girl.
Relax.
You had a hard day, girl.
Mm-hm.
I'm here for you.
Thank you, Santa.
Mm.
Why don't you tell Santa
what you want for Christmas.
[gentle music on radio]
[knocking on door]
Come in.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it's okay. It's your room.
Should I?
Yeah, please.
No, just makes
yourself comfortable.
I'm okay.
[gentle music on radio]
How do you feel?
Just so crazy.
You know, you can be there
one minute and then just gone,
like a light.
That's what I can't get over.
You know, you hear about it
on the news all the time.
It's like, whatever.
But then when it's
somebody you know,
you just can't stop thinking
if there was something
you could have done,
or, like, the last
thing you said to them.
Shoot.
What?
That was the last
thing I said to Liv.
Rock, paper, scissor, shoot.
So stupid.
What usually cheers you up?
Music.
Okay.
But that's not working tonight.
Okay, well what's
your favorite music?
Here.
Get up.
["I'm on Fire by
Dwight Twilley Band]
[music volume increasing]
Stuff like this, you just
gotta let it get in your bones.
♪ Got your name on the cover ♪
[Remy laughs]
[both laughing]
Come on.
♪ Honey you ain't got no lover ♪
♪ 'Cause you ain't, you ain't ♪
This is so silly.
♪ You ain't got no lover ♪
♪ You ain't, you ain't,
you ain't got no lover ♪
♪ I remember the feeling
that I could be free ♪
♪ Now I know it could
never, ever be me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm on fire ♪
♪ Mama, I'm on fire ♪
♪ Got your joker on the table ♪
♪ You've been told
from time to time ♪
You've got a great smile.
[both laugh]
♪ I'll be willing,
I'll be able ♪
♪ You could read
between the lines ♪
♪ 'Cause you ain't, you ain't ♪
♪ You ain't got no lover ♪
[Remy moans]
♪ You ain't, you ain't,
you ain't got no lover ♪
[both moaning]
♪ I remember the feeling
that I could be free ♪
[Remy moaning]
[both breathing heavily]
♪ 'Cause I'm on fire ♪
- [flesh squelching]
- [Levi grunts]
- [Remy moaning]
- [Levi gurgling]
[Levi gurgling]
[Remy moaning in pleasure]
[Remy breathes deeply]
I'm glad you came by, Brucy.
The pleasure's all mine.
Merry Christmas, baby.
[Bruce chuckles]
Money's on the table.
[truck horn blares]
[ominous music]
[door squeaks]
[knocking on door]
Remy?
- [Remy grunting]
- [blade slashing]
[ominous music]
[Remy grunting]
[knocking on door]
[Sadie sighs]
Hey.
How's it going?
Where are you going?
I can't do it anymore.
I'm done.
Why don't you just stay tonight,
and then we can talk about
everything in the morning,
and if you still wanna go,
then I'll help you pack
your things, and...
Okay.
Where are you gonna go?
Um, I've got some
family in Fort Smith.
I don't know.
It's okay, Sadie-bug.
It's okay.
I got you.
I just feel like I just
can't do it anymore.
I'm really sorry.
I know.
Are you gonna be
okay without me?
[Riley laughs]
Yeah, I'll be alright.
I've got Levi.
[both laugh]
Yeah.
I'm really gonna miss you.
And I'm gonna miss you too.
Thank you for everything.
[ominous music]
[Riley sniffling]
[knocking on door]
Nora?
Shit, Nora, open
the door, please.
Sadie's packing up
her shit, and...
Can you just come down and help?
[ominous music]
[knocking on door]
Remy, come out here.
Oh my god! What the fuck?!
[ominous music]
[knocking on door]
Levi, God fucking damn
it, open the door, please!
[banging on door]
What the fuck?
Levi, what the fuck?
[ominous music]
Remy, what the fuck happened?
[blade slashing]
- Shhhh.
- [Riley wheezing]
Witness.
[crunching]
[ominous music]
My God, I have now
cleansed them for you.
Please accept them into
your kingdom of Heaven.
Guide my hands and
ignite my spirit
as I carry out your will.
Amen.
[ominous music]
[water splashing]
Riley said you're leaving.
Oh my god, Remy.
God, you scared me.
I'm sorry,
I'm just still a little
jumpy from everything.
It's okay.
Yeah, I uh, I just can't
be here anymore.
[Sadie] I need a change.
I've felt it for a
while, now I know.
Where will you go?
I don't know, and
I don't even care.
Anywhere else, you know?
Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry if it feels
like I'm abandoning you.
It doesn't.
I'm leaving too.
Oh.
Where are you going?
Home.
I, um, I found
this in my dresser.
I saw the photo of you
and, is that your mother?
Yeah.
What happened to her?
She got sick and left us.
She gave you that?
Yeah, this was hers.
Wanna see it?
[ominous music]
Why don't you come with me?
I think I need to
do this on my own.
Thank you, though.
Give me a hug.
I'm really glad
I met you, and...
Me too.
Please come.
I can't.
This isn't goodbye, okay?
Riley and Levi are coming too.
[ominous music]
They're coming where?
They've already left.
What? What do you mean?
They witnessed, and now
they're waiting for us.
Liv too.
Remy, what are you saying?
I'm saying it's okay.
Sadie.
[ominous music]
- [knocking on door]
- [Sadie] Riley?
- Riley?
Nora?
[knocking on door]
Nora, come out here.
Everything's gonna
be okay, Sadie.
[ominous music]
Levi, come out here!
Levi.
[ominous music]
[Sadie sobs]
Oh my God!
[Remy] Don't be scared, Sadie.
They're waiting for us.
They've been cleansed.
It's okay.
Don't come any closer.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
What do you want?
What the fuck do you want?
I want you to come with me.
Riley and Levi, they
are waiting for you.
Listen to me!
I am not going
anywhere with you!
[Sadie spits]
Just leave me alone!
[ominous music]
Fucking leave!
Leave!
I'm sorry you
won't come with us.
- [blade slashing]
- [Sadie screaming]
- [flesh squelching]
- [tense music]
[Remy breaths heavily]
[ominous music]
[Sadie chokes and coughs]
[truck engine rumbling]
[knocking on door]
- [keys jingling]
- Nora!
[pounding on door]
[keys jingling]
Motherfucker.
Sadie?
Riley?
Levi!
[Rex] You motherfucker.
[Remy sobs]
[ominous music]
Oh my god.
[Rex sobs]
Levi, look at you.
Not you.
God, not him, please, not him.
[Rex sobs]
Where am I taking you?
[solemn music]
Just take me home, please.
[solemn music continues]
[switches engine off]
Could you maybe
come inside with me?
Come. Please?
[ominous music]
[Riley] No! No!
No, no, no, no!
No, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No!
No, you were supposed
to wait for me!
You told me to come back!
[Remy sobs]
[ominous music]
Oh, Jonah!
[Remy sobs]
[gentle music]
[Remy sniffles]
[ominous music]
[Remy cries softly]
They left me.
They all left me!
Why'd you do it, Remy?
It's what God wanted.
I did what God wanted,
and they all left me behind!
They all left me!
They went without me!
Drop the fucking blade.
I have to go.
I'll fucking shoot
you right here!
Don't make me do it!
I'm sorry you
can't come with us.
- No!
- [flesh squelching]
[ominous music]
["Don't Dream It's Over"
by Crowded House]
[Remy gurgling]
♪ There is freedom within ♪
♪ There is freedom without ♪
♪ Try to catch the
deluge in a paper cup ♪
♪ There's a battle ahead ♪
♪ Many battles are lost ♪
♪ But you'll never see
the end of the road ♪
♪ While you're
traveling with me ♪
♪ Hey now, Hey now ♪
♪ Don't dream it's over ♪
♪ When the world comes in ♪
♪ They come, they come ♪
♪ To build a wall between us ♪
♪ We know that they won't win ♪
♪ Now I'm towing my car ♪
♪ There's a hole in the roof ♪
♪ My possessions are
causing me suspicion ♪
♪ But there's no proof ♪
♪ In the paper today ♪
♪ Tales of war and of waste ♪
♪ But you turn right
over to the TV page ♪
♪ Hey now, Hey now ♪
♪ Don't dream it's over ♪
♪ When the world comes in ♪
♪ They come, they come ♪
♪ To build a wall between us ♪
♪ We know that they won't win ♪
♪♪