Oh yeah I forgot
you were here.
Gettin' it, huh?
I can't believe I just did that.
We have a mayday, mayday.
No, no, no.
I need to take a dump.
I need to take a piss.
All right.
Come on, Lane,
Laine started this,
she wants us to do
this, take the camera.
Javi, I don't care
what Laine started,
all right, man?
I don't want it, I
don't want the camera.
Hey Christy?
Don't go out there too
far, all right now?
Oh you worried about me?
Yeah, baby I
am, you know that.
I always am.
Michael grab
this camera please.
Javi, hey,
no comprende my friend,
don't know what
you're sayin', I'm not
taking the camera...
What's your wife up to?
Christy.
Hey.
Christy...
What is it Michael?
Christy.
Dude, she's gone.
How can she be
gone, what do you mean?
I mean she's gone, man.
We were just like, we were there
and then she just disappeared.
Something got her.
Okay.
Maybe there's
something on the tape.
We gotta find her.
Maybe something
on the tape that we missed.
What?
On the tape...
Yeah check the
tape out, dude.
Hey.
What are you doin' up?
How you feelin'?
What happened?
How's your head?
Uh, stopped the
bleedin' earlier.
It's not that bad.
Not like South
Africa bad, huh?
Not even close.
How long was I out?
I don't know, 'bout
five, six hours.
Where is everybody?
They went looking for help.
And the pilot?
He was the first one to leave.
He took off by himself
and he didn't look well.
Was he sick?
Hey look, I have
some aspirin in my camera bag.
Let me get you a couple.
No,
it's
okay.
Did the pilot radio for help?
He tried but
he didn't get a response.
Did he say
anything about this island?
I'll be back, Greg.
Where you goin'?
All right, but you be careful.
Those rocks look nasty.
Nastier than Peru?
No.
Are you sure?
Identical, Greg.
We're just gonna get a head
start right now, that's all.
Hey, are you all right?
Look, Laine,
why don't we just wait for the
rest of the crew to get back?
We could
but I just wanna
take a little peek.
Get a little head
start, come on.
I got a bad
feeling about this.
You trust me, right?
Yeah.
All right, so uh,
you just wanna get some cut
away and B roll stuff, right?
Oh, I hate that thing.
Put it in your bag.
Come on, safety first.
Hey, take it
easy on that water.
You think the two cases
we have is gonna be enough?
We don't have a
choice right now.
Food's gonna be a bitch.
What is it?
See something?
It's nothing.
You just did all that
staring for nothing?
You know what I really
dislike about our job?
Is that no matter
how much we research
and no matter how much
knowledge we have,
we always find out how
little we researched
and how much knowledge
we don't have.
That's the fun part.
Oh yeah.
Do you see that?
You know these
cats aren't rare,
but the fact that they're
on this island is.
We just need to take the
precautionary measures
that we would normally take.
Mm.
Like the one in Guadalajara?
That wasn't my fault.
What?
You're crazy.
I couldn't feel my left arm for
two days.
You should've seen Michael
when we got back home.
That was funny.
Man, I'm hungry.
I can't wait to get
back to the plane
and get in my beef
jerky that's in there.
There's food on the plane?
Well, just some snacks.
Not much.
That's all?
Didn't plan on crashin'.
How good is the
mic on the camera?
This is the moment.
A moment of discovery.
A moment of wonder.
This is the moment that
will now be revealed
but remember,
if you want the moment to last,
it's still a perception.
Discovery,
wonder,
maybe nothing.
Let's find out.
Laine.
Did you see it?
See what?
This is not a good way to
start a project, Laine.
I mean, the plane crashin'.
It's only an ankle sprain.
Where's your camera?
What?
Come on, you know the rules.
Rules haven't changed.
Seven years, seven.
It's that feeling I get.
It's that same old feeling.
Now you know I trust you,
it's not that
but every time I feel like this,
somethin' happens.
Did the crew ever
mention what time they
were coming back?
So how many days do we
have left with food?
Not many.
The pilot has a crate of beans
in the back of his plane.
I got my snacks, but
that's not a lot.
It's what, beef
jerky, some chips,
crackers.
The others take some food?
Very little.
All right.
I'm gonna go plan
my shot list for our
next round in the
jungle tomorrow.
Cool.
I'm gonna hit the
hay right now but um,
first I'm gonna
review the tapes,
make sure they're not damaged.
I'm working.
Okay, okay, okay.
My name
is Javier Nunez
and I
am the key grip,
gaffer and sometimes
I do Craft services
for the team.
Okay, how's that?
Am I done now?
We're good?
This is my truck.
I'm not an actor.
Hm, vulnerabilities.
Here's my vulnerability.
How's that, Greg, you like that?
And my strength,
yeah.
And when it does,
I'm gonna buy that
wife of mine that house
she's always wanted.
I love you, baby.
Black jaguars,
here we come.
You scared?
You know, you shouldn't be.
Jaguars don't like fire.
Nah, it's not that.
It's just, I've been freezing
my ass off every night
and I can't sleep.
Take a drink.
It'll warm you up
and put you to sleep.
That stuff actually
helped my headache.
Ah.
You don't sleep
in the nude, do you?
Not unless you want me to.
Goodnight, Greg.
Goodnight.
Yo, Laine.
Hm?
I'm sorry about today.
I mean with the
camera and all that.
It won't happen again.
Thank you.
And thanks for
saving our lives.
Ah.
Mayday, mayday, this is 201,
can you read me?
Over.
This is 201, can
you read me now?
Over.
This is,
Nancy 201, Jackson Mary,
I repeat this is Nancy
201, Jackson Mary.
We have an S.O.S., mayday,
our plane has gone
down, do you copy that?
Yes, very, coordinates...
I don't have our
exact coordinates.
We're somewhere off
of Gabriola Island.
I repeat we are somewhere
off of Gabriola Island,
do you copy that?
Yeah, Mary,
and we should be there shortly.
Over.
Do you copy?
Copy that.
What are you doin'?
No,
you did not just talk
to someone on the radio.
They'll be here shortly.
Nice, nice.
At least you learned
something from Jeff.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Let's get to working.
We don't have a lot of time.
Extinction comes to all.
You still have
that feeling today?
I'll be all right.
You know, I think we
have something here, Greg.
Something special.
I trust you.
Okay let's go.
Oh,
hold on.
What are you doing?
Bum knee.
Old high school football injury.
You never played football.
'93 marching band.
I accidentally got tackled.
You know, Laine,
what if our producers
got it wrong?
I mean,
what if what's out here
isn't really a jaguar?
I mean,
you yourself said,
"How would they get here?"
Then what is it?
I don't know.
Maybe some like new
breed or something.
Could be.
I mean living in this
ecosystem can change an animal.
Especially if it's not the
normal habitat they're used to.
How much more
footage of these trees
you want me to get?
You know, I
saw something earlier.
Eyes.
Saw a pair of eyes.
Eyes?
Yeah, but there was
something different about them.
Something intelligent.
Something,
I don't know.
We just need to be careful.
No, no, no, wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
You can't freak me out
with a story like that
and end it with, "We
need to be careful."
We are always careful, Laine,
but for you to say it,
okay, now I'm worried.
Why?
Instincts,
instincts.
Follow it, follow it.
Wait, wait,
wait.
Laine,
Laine, wait a minute.
You can't just take
off and run like that,
you oh,
god.
What could've done this?
This isn't a jaguar, Greg.
Then what is it?
This is a family of jaguars.
Um,
let's head back, all right?
The rest of the crew's
probably waiting for us.
Come on, Laine.
Laine.
I'm just worried, that's all.
Maybe they're already saved.
I mean,
them getting saved
and finding us
can be the difference
of a day or two.
They're coming for us.
Soon.
Look,
I don't wanna sound
like a pussy or anything
because we've been
in worse situations
and in nastier places than this
but I feel naked out here.
Sounds funny, but
I don't feel equipped.
It's just because we didn't
prepare for this, Greg.
We're good, though.
Believe it or not,
we're not that bad off.
Can I tell you
something about Jeff?
Will it make you feel better?
He said no one
could make Laine happy.
What does that have to
do with our situation?
Nothing, it just
stuck in my head, that's all.
So,
what do you think about
those guts on that rock?
You know, I'm not
afraid to talk about him
if that's what you
wanted to know.
Do you wanna talk
about the divorce?
Let's just talk
about the jaguar.
Do you think they
led us to that rock?
I mean, I don't know
if they're capable
of doin' something like that but
somethin' tells me they
wanted us to see that.
Those cats are cunning.
Smart.
Maybe.
Let's go back
tomorrow and find out.
Then it's a date.
I'm gonna go get
something to show you.
I'll be right back.
What the hell is your problem?
Did you see the others?
Maybe, maybe not.
I don't see anything.
Is this the right spot?
What happened?
I don't know.
I want a shot of those trees
and then I want you to come down
and follow it to where
the blood trails were at
and stop at the rock.
I'm gonna squat down in frame,
say my little thing and
then exit into the jungle.
Hey,
let's not stop until
we get something
to take back home with us.
Something good.
Yesterday it looked
like a bloody massacre.
Today just an eerie aftermath.
A sequel that leaves even
more unanswered questions.
Somewhere out there
lies the truth.
Explanations to
questions that maybe,
just maybe, should
be left unanswered.
Let's stop asking questions.
All right that was
good, I think we got it.
Let's get back.
Anything else?
It was probably just the wind.
I'll, I'll get some rope,
I'll tie it down,
don't worry, I'll
take care of it.
I need this, Greg.
We need this.
It was just the battery.
I can't afford another loss.
You're Laine Wells.
With your name and reputation,
backing's not a problem,
distribution's not an issue.
Look, listen to me,
once we're rescued,
we'll regroup with the others,
we'll fly back here and
get all the pick
ups that you need.
You know our producers will
give us the budget
and the extension.
But we lost money
on the last two films.
This...
Don't even think about those.
I need you to focus on this one.
Laine, you've never let me down.
How many batteries
do we have left?
Um, I just have
a couple, like,
can always charge them
in the plane, but,
but I'll have to use
the plane juices.
The small generator, the gear,
I sent it with the plane that's
probably already at Gabriola.
Where's the pilot?
He's not there?
John Andrew?
Hey, John Andrew.
He's probably out drinking.
Yeah, probably.
I mean where'd
you find that guy?
He couldn't be our only choice.
He was our only choice?
Yes.
Because of um,
time or budget?
Both.
Forget about it.
I trust you.
Gettin' that, huh?
Oh,
you mean like this?
Oh god.
I can't believe I just did that.
What you doin'?
I just showed my boobs.
Let me see.
Oh yeah, I forgot
you were here.
So what's goin' on?
What are we doin'?
Greg, I'm not really a very good
on the spot talker,
you know that.
I'm a sound guy.
I am uh,
one of the fantastic five
on team Cinema Verde
original uh,
members assembled uh,
back at Cal State
University North Ridge.
Whoa, sea sign.
Whoo hoo, sea sign, yeah.
Um,
I don't,
I don't know what to say.
Come on, tell 'em, why
don't you just tell 'em?
Okay.
That's not all I do.
I'm also production manager
and accountant
and
I
Have a big pimple on my face
and I would really appreciate it
if you got that
camera out of there.
That's all I have to say.
So,
honey.
Why don't you get us
when we're drunk or like,
when we're movin' around.
Uh,
it'll be a lot...
Honey, I'm just warning
you, Greg's out here.
Huh?
He's out here again.
Let's just give
him what he wants.
Okay, well I'm not addicted
to the pain killers anymore
and in two months I'm gonna
give one of my kidneys
to my sister
and I love my wife very deeply.
Ooh.
And I love my husband
and I love
my new boobs.
Whoo.
Oh, why do I always do that?
She bought those
a long time ago.
Greg.
Greg is that you?
Can I help you?
Were you just
throwing rocks at me?
Why, should I?
Why didn't you tell
me you were sick?
I knew.
You could've killed us.
Are you hearing me?
I'm grounded, I was suspended.
You knew that when
you came to me.
Remember saying, "Hey John",
don't tell 'em I could."
Remember that?
Yeah well, I didn't know
that you were drunk that day.
Drunk.
You thought I had
speech problems?
Hey, hey, what's
going on guys?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
Hey John,
do you know anything
about Gabriola?
Yellow.
Carbs and high in fiber.
No, Gabriola the island,
I'm trying to figure
out where we're at.
Oh, I don't even remember...
When I talked to the
rescuers on the radio earlier,
they said they'd
be here shortly.
Why does it seem like they're
having trouble finding us?
Yeah, John, I mean,
why don't you call 'em,
tell 'em where we're at,
it's not like they can't
see the plane from the sky.
I think there's a
reason why I can't answer
your questions, right?
Why?
Ask your boss.
What's that supposed to mean?
What the hell is your problem?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
John, John, please, please.
Hey, Laine, please.
Come on, come on.
What's that all about, huh?
Dang, girl, you
been working out,
you're a beast, look at that.
Girl, you got muscles.
Help!
Hey.
Hey...
Help!
Hey!
Rescue team should've
been here by now, huh?
I'm going to take your advice.
We can wait on the footage.
I think we should
look for the others.
I mean we should at least
check the southwest parts.
Can I ask you something?
How come you never talk
about your divorce?
'Cause I don't really
think I ever had a marriage.
I liked Jeff, you know?
I mean,
before.
He was like,
one of those
perfect good looking guys
you just wanted to hate
but you couldn't.
I could.
I don't blame him
for cheating on me.
No, no, no, no.
Nobody deserves that.
Yeah well some people do.
Did you ever wonder,
you know um,
we should maybe get some rest.
You ever think we'd
make a good couple?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
Goodnight, Laine.
Goodnight.
Michael!
Christy!
Javi!
Michael!
Christy!
Jav!
Michael!
Christy!
Laine!
Laine, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, Laine,
Laine, it's okay,
it's okay, you're safe now.
You're safe, I'm here.
It's okay.
What happened?
They were chasing me.
What?
Are you okay?
I need a drink.
Let's uh,
let's get back to camp.
Whoa.
What's wrong?
Greg?
It's okay.
They would've killed me.
Did you see what
they looked like?
No, but I could
hear them breathing.
I nearly saw it.
The growling.
They were that close?
I could smell them.
Greg,
they're toying with us.
Yeah, let's um,
let's get back to camp.
Okay?
I couldn't find him anywhere.
Who cares?
He's a big boy, he can
take care of himself.
Here.
Take one for the team.
Come on.
Nice.
Ugh.
Okay, this one.
Here's to
not being rescued.
Do we have any more food?
'Cause I'm kinda hungry.
Not for tonight.
We only have enough
for two more meals, so,
I'll give you something
in the morning.
You think the others are okay?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
No, yeah, they're
fine, they're fine.
I mean,
come on,
big Javier, who's
gonna mess with him?
And you know Michael.
Oh yeah, Michael.
He's a wilderness
guy, all right.
You're crazy.
Hey look.
I found it in the airplane
when you were looking for John.
Hm.
Batteries are old, but
it might last us
through the night.
Later on we could turn it up.
You know those
kitties hate noise.
Oh hey, about that, you know,
I'm really sorry I
didn't get to you fast...
Are you still in love with Jeff?
I divorced him.
Are you still
in love with him?
Did you know I took belly
dancing classes for him?
Yeah.
How?
Did he tell you?
No, actually, I told him.
Remember that job
we did in Hawaii?
Afterwards, you guys
had a few drinks and
you started to dance for him.
He passed out.
I saw you from my bungalow.
So I suggested it to
him in the morning.
Well then it's
only fitting that I
give you the first one.
You never danced for him?
No.
That ugly pilot
isn't around is he?
No.
Oh my god, I can't believe
I'm gonna do this.
Okay.
All right.
I hope we get off
this island soon.
Get a search party and
come back for our friends.
I'm gonna get back
on the radio later.
Maybe they're close
to finding us.
You know you
hurt me last night.
What?
Yeah.
When you laid me on my back
and you got on top
of me and rode me,
got a rock in my butt.
See that's what
I'm talking about.
Laughter.
We have to keep
each other smiling.
What's the difference
between a white owl
and a black owl?
A white owl goes,
hoo, hoo.
A black owl goes,
who dat, who dat?
It's not good.
All right,
my turn.
Oh, I gotta hear this.
Um, okay.
How does a blonde part her hair?
You're crazy.
You are crazy.
See,
I can be loose.
Yeah,
yeah, I know,
I know.
It's nice to see you
smiling like that.
I haven't seen that
in a long time.
Yeah.
You know I meant
what I said last night.
Which part, the uh,
or the um,
"Goodnight Laine."
No.
Yes.
When I said that
I can make you...
I,
I know you can.
Gunshot?
John Andrew has a gun.
John is that you?
Greg come here.
Holy shit.
John Andrew what are you doin'?
What's wrong?
Hey what's wrong?
Did you see something?
I saw a body.
A girl's body.
Where?
About 20 yards
down that way.
We have to go check it out.
I shot one,
it was by the body.
Will you help
me take Christy's
body back to camp?
Have you seen my
wife's purple shoes?
Okay, well that's easy because
there's nothing bad
to say about Laine.
Oh get out...
Come on.
Baby, we're all gonna say it.
You're not
gettin' off that easy.
Come on.
Okay, okay, fine.
If there's
one thing that's
bad to say about
Laine is that,
sometimes
she's too ambitious.
I think everybody thinks that.
She's a little over
the top ambitious-wise
but that can be a good thing,
but it's just, you know,
I personally, I'm
not that way and
I don't know, anyway um,
so, Javier,
I think it's your turn next.
Well, I'm gonna keep
it short and sweet.
I love Laine.
The greatest thing
about her is that
I met my wife through her.
Aw.
I love you baby.
Um, she has very
strong convictions.
Like if she sets
ff to do something,
it's gonna get done.
Um, with our help of course.
She's very uh,
trustworthy
and truthful, well trustworthy.
I'll go with trustworthy, yes.
Those are good things, right?
Yup.
Those are good.
What am I
going to tell her family?
I mean, what about
the rest of them?
Where's the rescue team at?
Where's the help?
I don't know.
Bad news.
Help ain't coming.
What do you mean
help ain't coming?
They having
difficulty find us.
What do you mean
difficulty finding us?
We're near Gabriola Island.
I'm not sure we're
around Gabriola Islands.
I think we might be uncharted.
Uncharted?
Doesn't mean
they can't spot us.
They can
rescue us in few
hours or a few days.
Days?
Days.
On the tape...
Yeah check the
tape out dude.
Wait,
did you hear that?
What?
Michael did you hear that?
Come on Michael, this is it.
Javier, wait
a minute, wait a minute.
Let's move.
Dude, hang on.
Javier!
Man.
Michael!
Javier!
Oh my god.
They're coming for me.
They got Christy, oh my
god, it's right behind me.
Somebody help me.
No!
No god no!
Laine!
No!
They took her.
Son of a bitch.
I'll be back.
I'm going with you.
Me too.
No,
okay what if help comes?
Stay in the plane
and lock the door.
Let's go.
This is it.
It's as far as we can go.
What?
Well maybe a mile
or a mile and a half.
That's it...
Come on, John.
I need to find my friend's body.
I don't know what's
beyond this point, Greg.
I need to find Christy.
You may not like
what you find.
Think my other
friends are still alive?
Let's hope.
Not the answer
I was lookin' for.
So how'd you get a
name like John Andrew?
Born Andres Gregorio.
Huh, yeah.
Long time ago,
I heard something.
Things about the islands
on the Gulf of Mexico.
What kinda things?
Things you don't wanna know.
Great.
That girlfriend of yours
is a real piece of work.
Oh she's not my,
my girlfriend.
I used to have one like that.
Back in the days.
Yeah?
What happened?
This what happened.
What do you think
our chances are
of getting off this island?
Fair.
Just got to be smart.
Greg?
Is that you?
Do you ever feel scared?
Me?
A guy like you?
I'm scared right now.
Um,
let's uh,
let's go that way.
Looks like there's
less stuff in our way.
I hope you have your gun ready.
Do you really think
there's jaguars out here?
I don't think they're jaguars.
Then what are they?
Open up Laine,
open up!
Where's John?
Greg, where's John?
They got him.
Oh fuck.
Those things.
Those beasts.
They got him.
My name is Laine Wells
and I'm the leader of,
I'm the leader of
the Cinema Verde
Documentary Group.
I'm not sure what fate
has in store for me but
should it be what I think
is going to happen then,
I only hope that
someone finds this tape.
I was told that
no one could make me happy but
they were wrong.
I was um,
thinking about...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, guys.
What are you doing, Laine?
I'm so sorry.
What?
I'm sorry I killed everybody.
No, no, no, no.
Don't, don't say that.
Don't say that.
Look at me.
Don't you quit on me, Laine.
Don't you dare quit
on me, you hear me?
I need you.
Please don't leave me.
We can't just sit here.
What else can we do?
Remember in
Rio de Janeiro when
Javier ate those
burrito looking things?
He must've went to the
bathroom at least eight,
10 times.
I know he stained his
underwear that day.
Javier never wore underwear.
Rollerblading in Spain.
Remember Christy's
dress flew up?
Beaver shot.
Why doesn't anyone in
our crew wear underwear?
I'm gonna get the flare gun.
I can't see it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
If something happens,
you run back here
and lock that door,
you hear me?
What do we do?
I'm gonna shoot the flare.
No, no, no, wait, wait,
we only have one flare.
This is our only chance,
we might not have another one.
What if they don't see it.
What do we do?
I don't know, I don't,
let's think about it.
I'm gonna shoot the flare.
No, no!
I had to.
You all right?
Thank you.
For the seven best
days of my life.
Let's go flag it down.
I'll go.
You stay in here.
I'll protect you.
Promise.
Greg!
Laine.
Get on, no,
they're pulling you.
Let go, Laine.
No.
No, let go, let go.
Lock the door.
Oh okay.
I know that we're gonna
need a lot of luck, so,
rub my boobs for luck.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
we don't need luck, okay?
We got Laine.
Laine,
Greg likes you,
he always has.
Shut up.
He always has.
Don't say that.
He's just too big of a
pussy to tell you, that's all.
That's all, what, what?
Don't move, you're
hurt pretty bad.
What do you think happened?
I don't know.
Heard stories about
these islands.
About people eating people.
What?
I never believed it.
Laine.
Where's Laine?
He's, he's asking
about some woman.
He was on
the beach by himself.
Don't move.
We're gonna get you some help,
you're gonna be okay.
Do you think it's possible?
Cannibals?
I hope to god, not.
Kevin, I'm scared,
get us out of here.
Okay.