(calm music)
(wind blowing)
(dramatic music)
- Well, hello.
- Hey.
- Thank you for accepting my offer.
I appreciate it.
Please, come in.
I just want you to relax, okay?
I'm just going to put some
drops in one of your eyes.
So if you just want to sit
down and tip your head back.
- You sure you wouldn't
want to rather screw, Doc?
'Cause I mean, like, my rates
are the same no matter what.
- (laughs) No, that's quite all right.
I really just want the
use of one of your eyes.
Okay.
Now you're going to feel a little warmth
when I put some of the drops in,
so if you want to just take a seat?
Just lean back a little bit for me.
Excellent.
Now don't move.
Okay.
Excellent.
Okay, now in a few moments,
when the solution starts to take effect,
I'm going to ask you to
look in this device, okay?
And then I want you
to very simply just
describe to me what you see.
Relax.
This is just an experiment in perception.
- Yeah, yeah, right.
- Through the use of these
chemicals and this device,
you may very well be the
first person in human history
to actually perceive the eighth dimension.
- The eighth dimension?
(thumping)
- Yes, the eighth dimension.
Oh, don't worry about
that, that's just my wife.
Now in a few moments,
the eye drops should start to take effect.
You're going to feel a kind
of warm tingling in your eye.
You listening to me?
- I have a warm tingling in my thighs.
Gotcha.
- Right in the middle of
something, sweetheart.
- He's cute.
I hope you don't blind
him like the last one.
- That was just a little, a little joke.
Will you excuse me for a second?
Just tip your head back
and tell me when it starts to tingle.
I told you, Rita, don't speak like that
in front of the subjects.
Besides, I promised you that
would never happen again.
- Yeah, well, it better not.
You know, I'm tired of paying
for this hospital shit.
Every time somebody gets
hurt, I have to pay.
Your experiments, I have to pay.
The assistant down the hall, my money.
I feel like I'm supporting
a third world country here.
- Yeah, well, it's an investment.
Besides, I told you,
it's all going to be worth it in the end.
(ominous music)
- Yeah, you were supposed to
be rich and famous by now,
you know, at least have that grant money
to pay me back for some of this shit?
- You know, first I
actually have to graduate
from med school, then I
have to win the grant.
- Doc?
Think I'm ready.
Let's look through this
lens thing over here.
- Well, Jesus, I'm close to
a major breakthrough, Rita.
I mean, what else do you want from me?
- What else do I want?
How about sex?
- We had sex last Thursday.
- Jordan, I told you when we
got married, I need attention.
- Rita, I'm under a severe
amount of pressure right now.
(thunder crashes)
(gasps)
- You know,
I don't think I've ever even
truly experienced an orgasm.
- Now?
I mean, you want to talk
about you and your orgasms right now?
- Well, we can't talk about
it in the bedroom, now can we?
- Look, Rita.
I'm working with a test subject right now.
(groaning)
- You know, all I know is is
you have a pretty hot wife
who pretty much pays your way.
All she asks in return
is a little attention.
- Listen, why don't
you go for a walk, huh?
Go and visit the neighbors.
That always seems to cool you down.
(energy crackling)
God, his eye.
(dramatic music)
- [Man] Dude, I bought this off this guy
with this killer van down by this beach.
- Man, that shit looks like Bufferin, man.
- No way, it's like crystal meth,
crystal meth if you like mixed it
with Flintstones chewable vitamins.
- Yeah?
That man is pretty cool, man.
He's a dope motherfucker, man.
- Anyways, let's you see
things no one else can see,
do things no one else can do.
- So how long's this shit last, man?
- All night.
(thumps)
Did that hurt?
- Yeah, it did.
But just, just the right
side, just the right side.
- It's working.
- Is that the door?
Or did I just hit myself again, man?
- Joe baby, Tom baby.
How are my two favorite
bachelors this evening?
- Bad, we're as stoned as stoned can be.
- Oh, business as usual.
- Hey, baby.
How about a little appetizer?
- Well, I'll just skip to the main course.
- Hello, Mrs. Grady.
Are you trying to seduce us?
- Well, I have a very special
favor to ask you guys.
- Another special favor.
- We did two special
favors for you last week.
- Well, I'm high maintenance.
- You sure your husband's okay with this?
I mean, the three of us?
- Well, he did say he
wants me to be happy.
So make me happy.
(ominous music)
(bed creaking)
- They're at it again.
- Yeah, but tonight we
don't have to hear it.
- So this is real.
We're really going to go out.
- A promise is a promise.
- Even if it is a month late.
- Look, I've been trying to get away
but you know Grady.
- Unfortunately.
- He helps pay the bills.
- His wife pays the bills,
but that doesn't make you his slave.
- Jane.
- Just remember who
you're married to, okay?
- It's not that bad.
You make it sound
like I'm at his beck
and call 24 hours a day.
- I need your assistance
up in the lab immediately.
- Dr. Grady.
Jane and I were just on our way out.
- Can it wait?
This is gonna take a couple of minutes.
- I'll be right back, I promise.
(kisses)
- Oh, Jane, have you
seen my wife anywhere?
- No, no.
- [Jordan] See, I just need
a couple pairs of hands
to help lift this, okay?
- What is that?
- [Jordan] What?
- That, the dead body.
- That's just a cadaver I
borrowed from the hospital.
- A clothed cadaver?
- Yes.
I mean, no.
I put the old work clothes on it
because I didn't want to embarrass Rita
by bringing a naked dead cadaver home.
You understand?
- Yeah, sure, it happens all the time.
What happened to his eye?
- How do I know what happened to his eye?
The guy came like that, didn't he?
Probably lost it in a
knife fight with Boxcar Bob
over a pack of cheese snacks
or whatever these street kids do nowadays.
- No, see, this is a recent wound.
Like the ocular cavity got burst outwards.
It's as if the eye got,
I dunno, pushed out.
- All right, well, thanks,
Morton, for the autopsy report.
But if you don't mind,
I'm going to pretend like this is my lab
and this is my cadaver and,
yes, you're my employee.
So let's just take it from there, okay?
- Sorry.
- Fine.
Just grab his feet and let's
hoist him into the crate.
Come on.
Okay.
(grunts)
No, okay, lift your end up a little bit.
There we go.
(slow music)
(energy crackling)
- Man, I need some rest,
I'm totally tapped.
- That's it?
- [Man] Me too.
- Amateurs.
- So how is the experiment
coming anyway, Doc?
Working pretty late tonight.
- No, well,
I probably shouldn't say
anything right now but...
- You had a breakthrough
with the apparatus?
- The tests are not conclusive
so, well, not yet anyway, but yeah, yeah.
- Wow.
Well, that's great.
Now you can get that five-year grant.
- At least, at least.
- Well, what did the subject see?
Did you open up a visual
path to the eighth dimension?
- I didn't get a chance
to ask him that yet.
- Well, how's the subject
doing health wise?
- I think he's doing great.
- Oh, shit!
- Oh, come on.
I mean, it's not like
I just said to myself,
hey, what am I going to do?
I might as well just kill
this guy for the hell of it.
Accidents happen and
you know that, Morton.
- What happened to his eye?
- I don't know what happened to his eye.
And maybe that's the tricky part.
Maybe the chemicals and the...
Maybe they dissolved it?
- Oh, and that's your big breakthrough?
- No, that's not my big breakthrough.
Look, Morton, something
happened in that lab, okay?
I mean, I had to step out for a while,
so I wasn't able to see what happened
but the scope showed that
there was a definite flux
in that dimensional wall
when the kid looked through the eyepiece.
I mean, a big flux.
- Wow!
- Jesus Christ.
- Scare you?
- Yeah, you did scare me.
You know, it's funny how when
you just walk up to an attic,
you don't sort of expect
to find someone there waiting for you.
- Oh, geez, I'm real
sorry about that one, Doc.
Just up here in my thinking place.
I hear voices, here I come.
- What were you thinking about?
- Please, don't ask him that.
- Death and life and
elective brain surgery
and how maybe, just maybe,
they all kind of fit together
like a jigsaw puzzle.
Hey, not the religious
type, just makes you think.
- (laughs) That's a doozy.
But if you don't mind,
Morton and I were just up
here delivering the crate,
so if you'd excuse us, please.
- Oh, yeah.
Let me give you just a
little something to chew on
on that, huh?
Get rid of it.
Throw the whole shebang in the trash,
let municipal waste take care of it.
Life's too short, you
know what I'm saying?
- Yeah, you know what, Bill,
is there not a wall you
could be staring at?
- Sure, sure.
- Yeah, we better be
getting back to the lab.
- See you around, fellas.
Should find that wall.
(dramatic music)
(energy crackling)
(screams)
- The hell are you screaming about?
What was it, a bug?
You know, you really need to
cut down on the drug intake.
- Tom?
Dude, you're wasted.
I'm seeing shit.
- Look, Doc, I appreciate
you making me your assistant
and all, you know that,
but I don't think it's fair
for you to make me an
accessory after the fact to a-
- One of the greatest discoveries
in the history of science.
You do understand that's what
we're talking about, right?
- All that mumbo-jumbo
about the eighth dimension?
Yeah, sure.
But meanwhile, you get a
dead kid's body stashed
up in the attic with Creepy Bill
and you don't even know if he
saw anything before he died.
- He did see something.
- Huh?
- Look, between 8:15 and 8:23,
I was out of the room, okay?
But at 8:18, so according to the scopes,
that kid felt the tingling in his eye
and he came and looked
through this device.
- How do you know that?
- How do I know that?
I'll tell you exactly how I know that.
Because at 8:18, the dimensional space
around this apparatus was
no longer perfectly curved.
There was a whole hole in it for,
I don't know, maybe five seconds.
- So you're telling me that
that kid punched a hole
through our reality with his eye?
- Yeah, and the chemicals
and the radiation.
I mean, you can't forget that, Morton.
But you know what?
That is not the sexy part.
You want to know the sexy part?
Something came through.
- Oh, shit.
- Absolutely.
And whatever it was triggered
those bioelectric scintillators
there on the table
and they act like sort of Geiger counters,
that track audible biofeedback.
Now, if that is the case, we can use them
to go and track down
our new little visitor.
And you and I, Morton, can
have empirical evidence
that the eighth dimension actually exists.
Now it went somewhere
through the vent, okay,
and if that is the case,
it's going to be anywhere
in this building.
Okay, so I want you to go
and check all the apartments
and I'm just going to stay here
and I'm going to start
processing the data we've got
since the dimensional wall was open.
- Whoa, just hold on a minute here, Doc.
This thing comes out of God knows where
and it probably ate the kid's eyeball.
- We don't know that.
- In any event, we're out of
our league here, Doc, way out.
- Look, whatever came through,
came through that eyepiece there.
It could not be bigger than a marble.
Okay?
How dangerous could that be?
(ominous music)
- Back in a minute?
(sighs) I'm gonna kill him!
(energy crackling)
(slow music)
- So I made a mistake.
I was looking for a couple of boys
when I should've been
looking for a couple of men.
- Yeah, Tom's really out of it this time.
What did you do to him?
- What did I do to him?
What about all that shit
you guys are always taking?
I mean, it's a wonder
you both aren't dead.
- No, see, I really truly saw something.
- You know, you guys are
always seeing something.
- Hi, everyone.
Sorry to barge in like this.
Didn't expect to find you here,
especially with all your
clothes on like that.
- Funny, Morton.
What's going on?
- I'm looking for something.
Hey, Joe, Tom, how's it going?
- Man, I think Tom's
braindead or something.
- Hey, that's great.
Two more satisfied customers.
- You know, you used to be fun, remember?
I mean, before Ms. Morton showed up?
- It's that pesky monogamy thing.
- It's just a ring and a license.
Nothing two people
can't work out somewhere
in a nice dark room.
- I'm working.
- Don't forget who writes
the checks, sweetie.
- Dude, she wants it.
- You just don't let up, do you?
- It's just part of my charm.
- As hard as this might
be for you to believe,
I actually love my wife, okay?
- Yeah?
So where's Janie now?
(slow music)
(energy crackling)
(Jane gasps)
- What do you know about
biofeedback radiation?
- About as much as I know
about going stag to the prom.
- Anyway, that's what me and
Dr. Grady are looking for.
Remember him?
- Barely.
- Well, I'll make you a deal.
You climb off my back and maybe
I'll forget I saw you here
with the doobie brothers.
- Hey.
Oh, I think I'm getting your
machine there all excited.
I think it likes me.
(slow music)
(energy crackling)
Why don't we ditch this toy
and we can play like grownups?
- What is that, a dope detector?
- Is he okay?
I'm picking up some
really strange readings.
(screams)
- Wow, was that weird.
I felt like something just tried
to suck the life right out of me.
- What?
- Something's probably broken.
I'm gonna go see if the doc can fix it.
- See you around, tiger.
- God, this is gonna complicate matters.
Fancy meeting you here, Bill,
just lurking around my apartment.
You know how much I'd
love to just sit down
and chew the fat with you,
but I'm afraid I just don't
have the time right now.
- We should talk, Doc.
- You know, maybe one day
we might just do that,
but just not today, okay?
- It's about that crate or, got
it, what's inside the crate.
- You looked in the crate?
- I'd say I had a little bit of a peek.
- Okay, let's talk.
- All right.
(energy crackling)
(slow music)
- A few minutes, you said?
Congratulations.
Another night shot to hell.
- Well, boys, the night's still young.
- Oh, baby, I'm really out of it.
- So?
It'll be like every other
time we get together.
- Don't think a little romance
is going to cheer me up.
I'm still mad at you.
(energy crackling)
Awfully sure of yourself.
It's not going to be that easy.
- Hey, what if that thing comes back?
- What thing?
- That thing that was
under the sheets with you.
I saw it.
- There was no thing, Joe.
- Forget it.
You're not going to touch this body
until I hear some begging and pleading.
God, you know just where to touch me.
(energy crackling)
Okay, you're forgiven.
- Look, honey, I know I
said I'd be right back
but you won't believe...
- What the hell?
What's behind me?
- Don't turn around.
(gasps)
(energy crackling)
- Dude, you're so fried.
- So are you, man.
(laughs)
- You know what?
Forget it.
You guys are hopeless.
Color me (indistinct).
(dramatic music)
(energy crackling)
(lamp crashes)
- What exactly are we saying here, Bill?
- Hey, Doc, I'm just saying,
finding a dead body in the attic,
that's some wacky shit, you know?
- So they say.
- And I was thinking that you
and Morton probably took it
up there in that big old crate
and maybe you had a reason.
- What have we got here, Bill,
a little bit of blackmail?
- Nope, no blackmail.
- What do you mean no blackmail?
- I'm just trying to clear things up, Doc.
You know, keep it copacetic.
- So you're just going
to go tell everyone?
- No!
Because when you tell on others,
you're really just
telling on yourself, Doc.
- How did I get here?
- Damned if I know.
The last thing I remember is...
Grady.
- We got to get one
thing clear then, okay?
We do not tell anyone.
- Anyone.
- Not just anyone.
Bill, we don't tell nobody.
- Nobody.
- And your lips are sealed?
- Lips are sealed, Doc.
- (laughs) You're okay with that?
- I'm as right as rain.
(energy crackling)
- Hey, where's that street
kid you brought home?
- Oh, he's up in the attic.
- Oh, thanks, Creepy Bill.
- Sure thing.
- What the hell did you tell her that for?
- Geez, Doc.
Thought she already knew.
- No, she does not know.
- Hello?
My name's Rita.
I'm the Doc's wife?
Remember me?
(gasps) Shit, God, you
scared me half to death.
Don't do that.
Are you okay?
What did my sicko husband
try to do this time?
God, you're cold as ice.
But you're kind of cute though.
- I.
I.
- Oh, you're shy?
That's okay, I like shy.
- I stranger.
Stranger.
- Well, that's okay.
I like strangers too.
You know, you get to know somebody
and you just get disappointed.
I like this.
Two people meet, they don't say a word.
- I.
I stranger world.
Need to make more.
Force to make more.
- (shushes) Just come to mama.
I like a man that gets right to the point.
You like that?
(dramatic music)
- My god.
- Well, he's alive.
- [Jordan] Well, maybe
he was pumped up on drugs
or something like that.
- That's good, drugs, that's good.
- But he could have been,
it's like angel dust
or something like that.
- Angel dust, every time.
- He can pump him up with angel dust
and you'd get someone who-
- Oh, oh, hey, Doc, isn't
that the guy you killed
and stuffed in the crate?
- [Jordan] This is nothing
like that, believe me.
- Hey, Doc,
what about the big son of a
bitch floating eyeball thing?
- What?
Rita.
Get away from my wife!
(energy crackling)
- Don't look into its eye.
- [Bill] Hey, it's all eye!
- Don't look at it.
- Does somebody have something to say?
Somebody who, oh, I don't know,
might have been doing
some eye experiments?
- You just wait a second, okay?
A few scarred retinas, some blindness.
Now that's the sort of stuff
I'm used to dealing with.
This whole giant eyeball
is a new one on me.
- Right, you're done.
- Hold on there one moment.
I think somebody needs a bit of time out.
- You know, I really thought
the Frankenstein was cute
when we got married, but frankly,
it's getting on my nerves.
- Morton, how did you find out
this thing was scared off by light?
- By accident after it
tried feeling up my wife.
- Well, that sure is horny, huh?
I mean, for an eyeball, sorry.
- I don't get it, Doc, what
the hell is that thing?
- It's a creature from the
eighth dimension, Morton.
- Oh, please come off it.
- Hey, look, I wish I was kidding, okay?
But I must've opened up a
dimensional wall in reverse,
allowing something to come
through into our world.
And the first place it went to
was into that kid's eyeball.
- Oh, a possessed eyeball, of course.
Well, hey, makes perfect sense to me, Doc.
- Good, swell.
Any idea what we do now?
- I'm all for getting the
hell out of here, kids.
- Amen.
- I agree, I think we
should call the police
or NASA or whoever.
We don't know what this creature is.
We do know one thing, it's not friendly.
- No, there's absolutely
no way we're going.
This is my experiment,
this is my discovery,
and I'm not letting some
greedy government glory hound
come in here and take it away.
- You know, it's been
nice knowing you, honey.
- Yeah, and you're not
going anywhere else either.
- [Rita] Yeah, just keep
telling yourself that.
- Oh, that would be a shame.
You'll leave poor old
Dr. Grady here on his own
when the cops show up,
oh, and they find the street kid's body.
God, that would be a shame, wouldn't it?
Because yes, if you stop to
think about it for a second,
you are in fact an accessory.
Of course.
It was all your inheritance money
that went towards financing
those so-called twisted
experiments and all.
Oh, damn.
Oh, and Morton, yes, it was
you who helped me lug the body
up into the attic.
And Bill, if I'm not mistaken, yes,
you were the one who tried to
blackmail me about the body.
So whether you like it or not,
we are all implicated in this.
And if the cops show up, we all go down.
- What do you want from us?
- No one leaves here
until I get my specimen.
Listen, it gets worse.
I did some tests on the ectoplasm
that I found by the vent
and I believe this thing
in its full form is a hermaphrodite.
That is to say that it
can reproduce asexually.
It's like an amoeba.
- So why is it attracted to the women?
- Maybe it's confused.
- Maybe it's just trying
to make little bitty, tiny eyeballs.
- Not if it's a hermaphrodite.
It could just split a piece of itself off
or be born pregnant,
which is all the more reason
we should stay away from it.
I mean, who knows what this
thing is going to do next?
- True, it is a hermaphrodite.
But maybe only a small
part of it came through.
Maybe that was the male part.
And if that is the case,
it's most likely to be looking for females
to reproduce with.
All the more reason why
we've got to find it,
we've got to put it in a controlled space.
- You know, Jordan, maybe
you should just marry it.
- That reminds me, where's Jane?
- Oh, she's safe.
She's asleep back at my place.
I don't think she really
remembers what happened
and I'd like to keep it that way.
(ominous music)
- What about the light?
- Well, that actually is the good news.
By possessing a human eye,
it's confined to the
limitations of an eye.
Now, as we all know, looking
into bright lights is painful
but it's exactly the same thing for it.
Looking into bright lights,
or rather the heat
generated by bright lights,
it can dry an eye out.
Now an eye needs to be
moist in order to function.
And it gets its energy
from living brain cells.
So what I'm thinking is prolonged periods
without active brain matter to nourish it
coupled with bright lights
and heat, it could just-
- Kill it.
- Possibly, yes.
- Oh hell, it's been floating around here
and fucking for hours.
It's gotta be getting tired.
(slow music)
- This movie's brilliantly directed.
- This is a movie?
Man, I thought it was real.
- Dude, you're so fried.
- Let me tell you something, man.
If I saw a monster coming
at me, I'd kick his ass.
- Damn right.
I'd shoot him.
- [Tom] You don't have a gun.
- I'd still shoot it.
- I gotta go to the bathroom.
- Then go.
Not here, in the bathroom,
go in the bathroom.
- Well, what about when it
was in the street kid's head?
I mean, didn't that like recharge it?
- No, no, the kid was already dead.
There was no active brain cells.
It needs active brain cells
in order to energize it.
- And how does it pull that off?
- Hey, Tom, this movie's
getting really good.
(dramatic music)
Hi.
Want some drugs, man?
(energy crackling)
(water running)
(ominous music)
- What'd I miss?
- Need female.
Need more.
- Yeah, right.
- Where's females?
- There's one on the tube.
Man, you are beyond fried, bro.
- Not real girl.
- If you want the real thing, man,
why don't you go find Rita?
- Where?
- Think she went upstairs, man.
Oh, man.
Hey, just make sure
you don't bring her back down here, okay?
Trying to watch this movie.
- [Joe] Okay.
- [Morton] How are we
going to catch this eye?
- Well, we're going to get Joe and Tom,
and then the six of us are
going to search this building
from top to bottom.
- All right, good, good, good, all right.
Do we get guns?
- No, I'm going to give
each of you a light.
- And then what?
- And then we either
trap it or we kill it.
- Well, why don't we just send
it back to its own dimension?
I mean, having something
that powerful hanging around
in our world might be dangerous.
- Nothing worth going after,
Morton, is easy or safe.
- Thanks for the fortune cookie, Grady,
but we don't know what this thing can do.
- Joe, what great timing.
We thought you could
help us on a little hunt.
We're looking for something,
actually a big something.
- No, wait, I got a better idea.
I think someone should be
with my wife just in case.
- Hey, I'll do it.
- Joe, I want you to go downstairs
and keep Jane company, okay?
Remember Jane, my wife,
the woman I live with?
Okay, good.
Here's the keys, go down to my apartment,
lock the door behind you,
and don't let anything in
until we come and tell
you it's safe, okay?
- Okay.
- Thanks, I appreciate it.
(ominous music)
- Who's that?
Joe?
Where's my husband?
- Upstairs.
- Did he say when he'd be back?
That's awfully sweet, Joe.
I think I'm all right now.
It's like I had some
kind of weird bad dream.
Do you think that you can get
me a glass of water, please?
(ominous music)
- Well, there is one
good thing about this.
- Yeah, what's that?
- Can't bite us.
- I guess that's true.
- Yeah.
Oh, can't shoot us either.
- Also true.
- Good, good, all right.
So therefore, I was thinking
that, you know, maybe we live
and let live and let the slimy
little creature do his thing,
we do our thing, ne'er
the twain shall meet.
- [Morton] Yeah, that's
a swell idea, Bill.
- [Bill] Maybe he's missed it.
- [Morton] I doubt it.
- Maybe he's hiding in
the best place of 'em all.
- Where's that?
- Right under our noses.
- It's not up here.
Let's split.
- All right, good.
- Hey, hey, quit that!
- See anything peculiar around here?
- Yeah.
- Right, dumb question.
- [Tom] What are you looking for anyway?
- [Rita] The killer eye.
- [Tom] The killer what?
- Killer eye.
It's this big eyeball floating
around, diddling everybody.
(laughs)
- I don't know anything
about a killer eye,
but right now I got a killer buzz.
- You're pathetic.
- Hey, you can't just come in here,
call me names like that.
I'm telling Joe.
Where is he anyway?
- He's next door keeping an eye on Jane.
(footsteps thumping)
(ominous music)
- Thank you.
What are you doing?
- [Joe] Massage.
- Something awfully familiar about this.
Morton would wring your
neck if he caught you.
Mine too.
- [Joe] Roll over.
- Listen, Joe, you're a really nice guy
but I love my husband, understand?
(screams)
Somebody help me!
Somebody!
- You killed my best
friend, you stupid bitch!
- It doesn't seem to be
growing very weak to me.
- Jane.
- I'm okay.
- But it's not any weaker
'cause he's got a recharge
on Joe's brain matter.
- [Tom] What's that mean?
- It means your friend's
brain has been sucked dry.
- Is he going to be okay?
- He's dead, you moron.
- This is serious.
It's killing people,
it's attacking the women.
We can't afford to play around
with this thing anymore, Doc,
we gotta call somebody, dead
body in the attic or not.
- What the hell is going on around here?
- Okay, okay, look.
Let's just head out
for the front entrance.
- I don't think we're going to make it
to the front entrance.
I mean, this eye could be
waiting for us anywhere.
- No, no, no, look, look.
We all stick together,
we keep the lights on,
and we definitely have the advantage here.
Oh God, what the hell is that?
- So much for the advantage.
- Oh my God.
- Very diabolical.
- No, wait, just relax.
Wait, I have a backup
power supply for the lab
and it's on its own separate line.
The breaker box is in the attic.
Okay, look, everyone, just
get, get back to the lab, okay?
- What about you?
- This is my mess.
I'm going to go and hit the breaker.
- Jordan.
- What?
- Take care, huh?
- I've got an idea.
- Thank heaven for small miracles.
(dramatic music)
(energy crackling)
- What the hell is this thing?
How did this all happen?
- It was a fluke.
The original experimental design
was to simply allow the eye
of the test subject to
see through the barrier
of our reality into the eighth dimension.
- Eighth dimension?
- It's a hypothetical plane of reality.
Alternate universe.
- [Bill] Like New Jersey.
- Anyway, Doc Grady
was working on eyedrops
that would allow us to see the other side.
But I guess somehow it all got reversed
and something broke into our
world from the other side.
- Sure likes our Earth women.
- Yeah, they killed my buddy Joe.
Why couldn't they have
just taken me instead?
- Are we just going to sit around here
until the lights go out again?
- No, I'm sure Doc Grady will
have a plan when he gets back.
But if he doesn't, then
I say we set a trap.
- A trap?
- Like a mouse trap.
- Like a light trap.
If we could somehow surround
it with a series of lights
all set at the right spectrum
and then keep it in that one
particular spot long enough
for it to dry out and destroy it.
- How are we going to keep it in one spot?
- I haven't figured that out yet.
- Hey, lookie there.
Hey, Doc, we're just
sitting around talking
about setting a trap for the eye.
- Oh, you don't say?
Just so happens I had
exactly the same idea.
And I have a little backup.
Cross dimensional time bomb.
- Come again?
- I didn't want to mention anything before
'cause it's a little bit
of a drastic measure.
But I believe if I can coerce
the eye into a small space,
set off the bomb, I can
destroy the creature.
Probably about five or
six city blocks as well.
- Yeah, but the thing we
couldn't figure out is
what are we going to use for bait?
- You.
- [Rita] What?
- We find somewhere dark like the attic
where we know the eye is sure to show up.
We know it's obviously attracted to you.
- Yeah, I'm real flattered but...
- When it does show up,
we exit, trap the eye,
lock the door, set up the bomb.
- [Morton] And run like hell, I hope.
- We'll have about five minutes
before the bomb goes off
and that should give us enough time
to be outside of the bomb blast radius.
- And what if it isn't?
- Quite frankly, the
explosion would be so huge,
you wouldn't even feel or see a thing.
So Rita and I are going
to go up to the attic.
I want the rest of you to stay right here
and don't move until we
have trapped the eye.
You got that?
- What if I got to take a pee?
- You hold it.
(ominous music)
- Jordan, I'm scared.
- Don't be afraid, I wouldn't
let anything happen to you.
- You know, I have a confession to make.
I mean, since we might be
getting blown to bits and all.
I haven't been the most
faithful wife in the world.
- I know.
- And you know, you haven't
been the most loving husband.
- I know that too.
- And I was thinking maybe
we should get a divorce.
(kisses)
Wow.
- That good for you?
- Real good.
(moans)
It's never been like this.
(gasps)
- Don't be afraid, Rita.
It's not an evil being.
It let me look into its mind.
- What did it just do to me?
- It has certain needs and
it asked me to help it.
And in exchange, it's going to help me.
And so I did it.
I did it, Rita.
It's going to show me how
to open up a real portal
to the eighth dimension.
I mean, isn't this great?
A whole world full of these
little guys everywhere you look?
- What are you talking about?
- This eye.
It's not here by accident.
I mean, he's here as an advance scout
from the invasion fleet.
These guys want to move in.
- Oh yeah?
You better tell your new
buddy the eyeball here,
it's gonna be awfully hard
for him to take over the world
with one of my three inch
spike heels sticking out
of his yucky fucking face!
(slurps)
(groans)
- Oh, yeah, there.
Hey, this looks like
that intergalactic bomb thing the Doc had.
- Not quite though, it's a stopwatch.
- Oh, well, like I said,
it looks like the bomb thing the Doc had.
- Oh my God.
- The whole thing was bullshit.
The Doc was lying to us.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are we going to do?
- Morton, what is going on around here?
- I don't know, but I got
a really horrible feeling.
We'd better find Rita quick.
- Don't fight it, Rita.
I promise I'm going to be
the world's greatest husband.
- Oh god, I want the world's
greatest divorce lawyer.
- Curses!
- This is for my buddy, you bitch!
(energy crackling)
- Your lights, hit it with your lights!
Don't let it get away.
- Wait, you're going to ruin everything!
(energy crackling)
- Bet you're wishing
for some Ray-Bans now.
- That's right.
You're gonna die.
There's no escape.
You only have one other choice
and that's to go back
to your own dimension.
Go back and stay back!
(energy crackling)
- Wait!
Take me with you.
(dramatic music)
(energy crackling)
- What happened to Jordan?
- I guess he's boldly gone
where no man has gone before.
- Do you think that he's okay?
- If he's into giant eyeballs,
I'd say he'll make out like a bandit.
- At least it's all over.
(ominous music)
(growling)
(energy crackling)
(ominous music)
(calm music)