TAINIES CO LTD
THE QUEEN barbarian II
The Empress Strikes Back
~ 1990 ~
No!
No one will make me
lady.
No! Daughter of King Alko.
Not going to show up
ahead in these bastards,
Anything less than
befitting a lady.
If you want me there should be
to accept so as I am.
And so as smelly!
You run away from the fire.
It's time to learn the protocol.
My only trouble you bring,
by little girl.
Now King is away and
Ankaris will make your life difficult
The King will come back.
And the daughter of the King will make his life
Ankaris very short.
Nampis!
Stay away from me.
You look beautiful Atheleia.
Have you heard from father Ankaris?
Unfortunately we have.
A battle took place at the border,
a week ago.
But we did not lose.
Never lose.
We won the battle.
But our beloved King
Alko lost.
True?
The power is mine now,
right? anyone disagree with that?
And spells the
protected.
The spell
protect the life of the King.
Wait at least until
bring his body here.
Kneel!
The Lord gave you a command.
This will be your guardian.
The body of your father
not found.
Then there is proof
that is dead!
Ma'am... you are very persistent.
Father you confided your
the secret of the magic scepter,
To surrender,
If something happens.
To finish the
skimming treasury
And change advisors
with your killers?
You would obey.
Until I see that the King is dead
I will not give away your
power.
You will see that I have enough
power to change your opinion.
Chofrax.
Treasurer!
I brought a little food.
Thanks.
I wondered if I had any friends left
I hate them.
The men do not understand
power.
They think that it is good to have
more and more.
You know the secret of
magic scepter.
Yes, but as my father is alive
I can not use it.
You know, I heard them talking.
They think it's really dead.
If not though?
And use the power of the scepter
Wherever you are going to die.
No risk to betray
my father.
You can not just sit here
.
I do not have much choice.
My Good girl!
I'm ready to go out.
Please.
Let's get away
from your father.
Trust the power of your
to the one daughter
Who held on
bygone times
The Trust me
that nobody can touch
Without the blessing of the female sex
.
You have the power now?
No, there are still some
words.
The know?
Yes, but I'm afraid...
For my father.
Chofrax!
You can not take the scepter with the
Chofrax violence. You know the power.
Then used the
to stop me.
Are you afraid?
You think your
father is still alive,
And not sacrifice his life?
Then sacrificed yours.
Atheleia.
Well done my girl.
And now.... Kneel!
Having scepter
does not mean that you have the secret of power.
Remain the guardian of
you and you remain mortal.
Will you give me the secret.
Or you die.
My father said you will become my slave
if you bring the scepter.
And it will actually happen.
It's mine.
Are not you?
You look so superior to everyone.
Kiss my foot.
I think your little daughter
become big queen one day.
And good husband with
suitable husband.
I told you I want to kiss my
the slave legs.
You can govern by force,
But the real power is not
will be yours ever.
Then that power will be sacrificed.
Why
secret will die with you.
Perhaps he is right my Lord
Without the magic scepter of the
enemies can fight back.
I feed them with it.
Prepare the execution of Atheleias
with the first light the next day.
Promised that will become my slave.
We will find you another.
Orion!
You 're her fiancé
my daughter.
Show me the spouse
a day will share the throne.
You're good!
Not sure
that likes me!
I'm not sure
likes anyone!
I always love!
You can be my King!
You could;
Not really
never thought.
One day I will become Queen
.
What if you want to marry me,
to be nice to me now.
Gladly!
My Queen!
Sprinkled!
Where do you come from?
In chasing the men in your places!
You know what I mean!
There are others!
Better to go from here!
I can not lose to them.
I never find gold
when someone knocks.
Really need to get out of here!
How waiting to doff
livelihood anyway.
This should be
a beautiful and peaceful forest.
But a few months ago
trouble come and go!
Here you live?
Yes!
I wish I could too!
Will appreciate what you did not have.
What are you?
I'm Zielona!
My name is Atheleia.
A! One that hung in the morning!
The news travels fast!
Better to gallop faster!
Go!
It's very "lady" for
be useful to us.
Just look at her!
When it's time
battle will see how useful I am.
Oh I would not want to spoil your
these beautiful clothes.
Fuck me!
Erigkina! It has already passed
a hard day.
Okay then, let the
pave the sheets.
I told you.
Leave me!
Yes Erigkina. Hit it!
Father!
Bring back!
Let go!
Do you want me.
We do!
You do not need to go immediately back
.
Come on, do not do nasty
... Come party like a man.
Ballas!
At last we caught one of them
damned rebels.
Flew t 'your weapon.
Let her go.
Grasp.
I will not try, even.
You really think that two of you
, can stop us?
You .
Betrays your royal blood.
You want to pour the
my royal blood.
Now let's see what
color is yours.
You ...
... You're a fugitive from
royal execution order.
Surrender now... and
regret their "friend you".
I do not think like you.
Flew t 'your weapons.
Old-rebels.
Chase them.
We have an army of our own.
An army of
people who lost loved ones,
Them stole their crops,
That got them their children,
Or worse
We had a King who ruled
fair, even the poor knew.
The justice was on our side.
If you need a leader to your
convince, then I learn to lead.
If this requires a stronger army then
,
I'll find the strength.
But I'll make a promise.
We will win!
Yes! We!
Atheleia!
So in
chased a handful of women.
I will go tomorrow with several men,
To clean the
forest for good.
If the find.
You are welcome to
to admire!
I doubt be helpful.
He always won in fencing.
My portion dislikes.
Give me yours, Orion.
Finish your food,
Gave it to me.
Do not fidget, otherwise
I will never marry.
I will come with you tomorrow.
My Lord .
In two days we will not stay
one rebel alive.
I did not know that aimed
someone else.
But I killed it.
Where you think you going?
Wait! Wait!
There are dozens of people to be fed.
You are welcome to share with us
.
How to say?
You can not speak?
Soldiers.
And now you are hiding here.
All alone?
There are others
share your match...
And welcome lunch.
You know what did the nobles
and to my own?
They killed!
Glad to escape.
I did so
took my father.
Tortured him to death.
It's time to pay.
Glad I leave this place.
I wish I could go with you
and killed out there.
Thee Nampis?
Who did you hurt?
I 'find someone.
If this child
become queen,
Not want to see it.
You know how to say now?
Old goat-midwife!
Sure grew.
You must first crawl
her legs.
Just have the crown in the hands of my
be waiting below.
I do not know what the King
And does not turn back on
to marry the Atheleia.
She would not ever marry!
Her I'd ask...
... Many times.
It's too late now.
Old goat-midwife!
The company is ready.
Nice.
Do the rebels to
walking faster.
Good afternoon, my Lords.
I see you keep a big company!
If you like both,
Then you are welcome to follow.
I used to think to ask them if they want to
to follow them.
This is the last thing
would ask anyone!
I'll never get used!
Do not kill him!
I made a mistake?
Cuff him!
To tie him? I have never
xanadesei anyone.
Why tell me
do these things.
Get in!
It's gorgeous!
Do not you dare touch
with your bloodstained hands.
No.
Take my cape off
of these vromopaida.
Not give you orders here.
Why simply not to kill?
Be finish.
I do not intend to kill.
Do not like those
get your fortune?
I will punish you as you did
with these poor farmers.
Perhaps I
I cut your hands.
Would not dare.
No.
Thinking that there are better ways of punishment.
Why so afraid of women?
I fear nothing!
Women are a waste of time.
But, you have so much time now.
All have their Achilles heel.
One night with me
may have been your end
You do not have even destroyed.
But now that I know.
What are you doing out here?
Food to throw away.
Only villagers
to hang out.
Best of friends I
you did last.
What is your favorite
little princess?
You know what I want.
And I know what I will do once I get
throne.
And to get him would be
as chilly as you are now?
And you...
... with your army.
Born in power.
Not need it like you.
No! Just
camp in the countryside for recreation.
For them!
You know how they live Orion?
A little food on their table
Few rags to keep warm
their children.
Knowing the future they have.
Life is already hard enough for them
no one like you.
I too am a man.
Every day less.
I learned something here, Orion.
That my life is more valuable than
others.
Do not you see that?
Is not that right;
It was the power in only
seeking.
I gave up long ago
believing that you do not love.
I thought it would
claimed forever.
I have to do with the logic
now.
I remember that
were very reasonable.
Let us return you something
old Chofrax!
I wish you a good return.
And Convey my respect
to Ankaris.
Kill!
No!
Now Ankaris will see that we are
strong enough to put...
... The "bravest".
And a warning, not
other slave caravans.
Otherwise the next time the
loop will be more firm.
There will be some more time.
And when he comes,
Loop is
around your neck.
Ethmpek!
It loons!
Peasants!
Were peasants who waited
but we found an army.
And your own army massacred
from villagers and a girl.
Girls
more loudly than you think.
It is possible to think
that at the end will win?
If you want to know what you think...
... ask him.
He is
strolled with her in the forest.
When you hostage strolled
when they tell you to lounge about.
Honestly believes that the villagers
is as good as we do.
Let's see if close enough
to take in the trap.
When you hang loved
of villagers in the square.
Hanging innocent people?
Villagers not people.
Or is soulatso together
changed your minds?
You know my devotion
my Lord.
Course.
And to be rewarded for it
will lead the first run.
And you?
...
... I will erect
trap Atheleia.
Why? What have we done;
Enough!
We did not do anything.
And to prevailing when you were a baby.
And Atheleia well.
The Ankaris
thinks he can help her.
Calmly with it!
- You will not come.
- You come.
My stomach
dies of anguish.
And if you do not come?
Come!
Came!
Seal the gates!
What if there are other nuns here
and ask us what we are?
Just say "bless"
and go!
Bless!
We came to bless
death row.
We came from very far away.
The nuns want to bless
prisoners.
Let the pass.
You came in very dangerous
part, Sister.
The risk does not employ those
serve a higher purpose.
Sister!
You can bless
my sword?
Sister!
He wants to bless his sword.
Bless on it, then.
May...
May this sword...
Do not pray for them
the old souls Sister.
Pray for the poor
to live...
Do not say anything my son.
May this sword
become...
Remember the blessing Sister?
I can not bless
in the hands of a soldier.
May the sword beating
only freedom.
What kind of blessing is this?
Grasp!
Let's get out of here.
Do not worry about me
turn the camp.
So you say?
Ethmpek no!
We can not lose you!
I told you that
will meet again.
You can slept well.
They do not torment
guilt at nights.
Always impressed,
They found on the wrong side
blame others
That they are guilty.
I'm sure you want to
open your eyes
And see what happens to you.
So that you decided
to win a woman.
I guess this is my chance
To repay your grace
And to see bare
from your dignity.
Oh! How beautiful
disgusting spectacle!
My father said that
I track.
Course.
You will hurt much?
There is
pain kneeling them.
It's fear.
Knowing how is absolutely helpless.
Are you helpless?
Is not that right;
Can I ask you
that pleases me.
And thou
you can not do anything.
I like this
when I become Queen.
You would never become Queen.
You better tell us
for the scepter now.
Kantin speak.
This looks wonderful inconvenient.
Is not Atheleia?
It is very inconvenient?
Old spoke then.
'll Talk again.
Very soon.
Now you want to tell us,
Atheleia is not it?
Tell us.
Tell us the scepter.
Please Atheleia,
not want to happen to you something.
May need a little more persuasion.
About falls so every time.
Say about three more times
and will become extremely more inconvenient,
Than it is now.
We'll let Atheleia
to think about what you want to tell us.
Before
pull this lever three times.
Come treasurer, we have dinner.
Come treasurer.
It is possible, my Lord,
but I am stronger.
Suffers too.
Take care so as not to die before
to tell us everything.
Okay!
We know what
want a couple of days.
But I have no intention to kill
either now or later.
No.
Will continue my
pays for too long!
Orion the Atheleia runs away.
I wish I had not trusted
never secret.
Father, give me a sign
if you're alive or dead.
Very touching
Do you really believe that?
What are you doing?
Get.
If you are afraid to save yourself
with the scepter,
Then you definitely will not give
his secret to us.
So the Ankaris
will not hesitate...
... Give me leave
to kill you.
I intend to do it very slowly.
The scepter
secret should remain a secret.
Someday someone will come
stop you.
Who?
Someone you tangible rebels?
My soldiers will march
an hour to hunt them.
Seems not to care.
But you at least
wish him good luck in Orion.
Who will lead
enterprise.
Much like
impatient to prove himself.
Where were you last night?
Where?... Here!
I came in looking for.
The Atheleia escaped.
I heard.
It was when I went out to walk a little
,
Over the ramparts.
You go there often?
I will come to walk
together overnight.
I have nothing to do when
miss.
Where are you going?
I go to the rebels!
Do not go!
Keep my little companion.
Out there is the last
place I wanted to be.
But I have orders to go to
Chofrax.
So simply I would tell my father
give you other orders.
Give me a kiss.
Stay at known path and
find yourself directly in the camp.
We will find them, sir.
Treasurer?
Your father told me
that will find you here.
There are spiders in here.
Is poisonous?
I do not know.
I was thinking of the
put on her.
Do not be afraid not to lose any, not after
know what room it goes.
Okay then!
I kinda hungry
anyway
You are so weak.
Come!
The last time
saw the royal escort,
Was just
30 km away from our castle.
To reread your message?
No
If the King has come back...
The
Atheleia not know this yet.
Maybe I can convince her
tell us the secret.
Sure, bold servant
Lady Treasurer will succeed,
More than me.
Let him try!
- I want to see.
- No.
What do you mean, no?
This should
do it myself.
Please forgive me.
I swear on my life that...
Will leave this castle now.
Or will die here together!
That sounds like a plan.
Orion!
Father! Father! Father!
Oh! Megalodyname...
Note.
Oh my God.
On the bed please.
Carefully Oh!
Out! Outside! Outside!
The took care of baby,
I can do it again.
Where are you?
It will be well?
I do not know.
It's possible.
Always be possible.
We did not find any trace of them, my Lord
.
Looked where I told you
the Orion to look.
It's one of those stupid!
We dash immediately.
This time will follow me.
I will bring him back, my child
.
I do not want him back.
On this
want because you want to be with her.
Never loved me.
Well of course she loves.
I wish I was dead!
Sure I wish you were dead.
The father believes
I want power.
But wrong.
Is yours.
You said will you give me
just growing up.
I have grown enough now.
Please, Mother!
Let me.
Let this be the day.
Trust your strength
To that daughter
The
held in bygone times.
The Trust in me
That nobody can touch
Without the blessing of the female sex
.
Use your power.
To do with a woman
Worthy of your majesty
Please, Mother!
I want him back or I want him dead.
Use your power.
To do with the woman
That will fulfill your destiny.
Zielona! Zielona!
Soldiers, I saw them in the woods.
Stay here.
Where are the others?
Ethmpek, come!
You're safe.
You, you're here.
I will be where you.
Always.
Oh My Lady!
Thank God!
My Lady!
Oh My Lady!
It is very weak, a little
food will help.
You do not need to tell me
how to do my job
But not with these dirty
pigs are out there.
Not my Lady!
I
a delicious breakfast will prepare you with my hands.
You just wait,
right here.
Well what do you expect?
You need food,
Little peace and quiet.
Open now open!
Go! Come on!
The Nampis!
But He's right, you know.
The reports say that King
turns. You have to rest.
- Rested enough.
- Not enough.
I was wrong.
Love is the greatest
strength than anything else.
Now it seems to be happening.
And I was the only
I wanted everything.
Rest my love.
Rest.
I see that you become better Atheleia
!
Thanks Nokia.
I'll see what it is.
I guard now.
The King turned...
... Dead.
In
brought back to be buried in his homeland.
Only not
own longer.
As far counted
lost the homecoming.
Die quickly?
And brave.
Your Majesty!
He buried on his own soil.
Bring me body.
Send message
then everyone everywhere.
To gather all here tonight.
It's time to fight!
You are not strong enough.
We waited the day you turned
King and now it!
This will give us the
strength to defeat his enemies.
Now I'm free to use
the power of the scepter.
- In a few days...
- In a few days I will be dead.
Anyone scepter
can not be killed by human hand.
It was the human hand that freed
the spider with poisoned.
The scepter is
my only salvation.
Going to live!
All are to live free!
So it will gather
10,000 swords.
We attack at dawn!
Yes! Ask!
What do you mean you can not find it,
it is only a little girl.
You are not worthy to find
a little girl.
Treasurer!
This is no time for games.
Why everyone follow me?
Do not follow me.
Find!
Treasurer!
Taaamis!
Our army is
strongest ever.
Coming
warriors from all parts of the province,
Help our cause.
The most important is to
get inside the castle.
Some of us will die,
must be sacrificed.
But the victory would mean
freedom for us all.
Yes! Ask!
... Sorry...
What happens?
Is fever of
spider venom.
Keep cool until the
to fetch some water.
You're unique.
... Your strength...
... Trust the...
... One man did not touch...
Atheleia?
... Without the blessing...
... The female sex...
Atheleia, something magical happens
I think you should see this
... Hold me now...
Scepter wins
And grasps the power
For whoever reigns.
Who's there?
Hey Nampis.
Not to know you.
What are you doing in this scene?
It is the scene of Orion.
Is not that right;
Whatever you're not
you have no business there.
Yet I have.
I can do what I want now!
What are you?
You do not need to tell you.
Old goat-midwife!
What do you want?
Just know the secret.
What secret?
His scepter.
What are you?
Let me must go
to the castle now.
The know those eyes.
Now I will become Queen and
after you marry.
Kiss me!
You ?
But how?
I will not let you to have!
Went to kill me.
Save the Nampis!
What is this?
Who understands
such magic.
You know what?
The cashiers.
I will tell my father.
If you recognize what you are.
Course will recognize me!
While you stand with
with the rebels?
Would not dare!
Ethmpek!
Change of clothes and
valtin on a horse.
Think it over Atheleia!
You will regret this!
When I become Queen will
to hang from the...
- I do not know the secret.
- Let's say it in Ethmpek.
Is everything ready?
My Lady fact.
Nice.
Ride!
What do you have here?
Transfer the body
King Alko,
Who died in battle.
Did you hear the news?
I want to see the
my own eyes.
You claim that this is the Alko.
It is indeed!
Your Majesty!
Open the gates!
Coming knights!
Get them!
Father! Father!
Help me!
We need to get the scepter.
A front, go
not waste time.
Will do training
the traitor.
Practiced enough?
Continued!
What shame?
To come so close to the scepter,
only to die.
I write in your grave
that killed woman.
You will be dust in your grave before you
read my tombstone.
Attack!
No!
Father!
Father?
What are you, that
call me Father?
I came here to give you the power of
scepter.
Treasurer?
Father!
Treasurer!
Taaamis
So soon.
"We all
our Achilles' heel."
Ankaris?
Was always the magic that held
rulers in power.
Instead of thanks
those who govern.
But this is the real magic
.
When people trust the
life of someone else.
This is the magic that govern
this kingdom now and then!
Yes! Ask!
TAINIES CO LTD
Editor Subtitle tainies@in.gr