[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
You thought you'd
win, didn't you?
That you'd live forever,
that you could beat death.
Well, sadly, death finds
everyone sooner or later.
Too bad for you it was sooner.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Well, perhaps death
was right on schedule.
I guess we'll never know.
[GHOSTLY LAUGHTER]
You'll know.
You!
When it's your time to die.
No!
You're dead!
You can't hurt anybody anymore.
Are you so sure,
my faithful lawyer?
Death isn't always
so neat and tidy.
Chat later.
[GHOSTLY LAUGHTER]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Shadows of darkness, spirits
within, harness the energy,
let it begin.
By the power of my will,
essence of my soul,
make this woman reveal her goal.
Cindy, my dear, draw
from the uncharted.
You're on the clock now so
I suggest you get started.
[CLICK]
[LOW MOANING]
Wow.
Can you really foretell
the future, Madam Zola?
That would be so cool.
Past, present, future.
All is known to those
who possess the powers
of the psychic world.
And you really
possess those powers?
Yes, I recently
repossessed them.
You know, I've never really
done anything like this before.
Zola already knows that.
Of course, you
know everything.
You came to the right place.
Now tell me, what
is troubling you?
I'm not sure if I should
tell you everything.
[SIGHS]
Please, in order to help you,
I must first know your desires,
your needs, your fears.
My fears?
Well, I'm afraid of enclosed
spaces, open spaces, hot food,
cold food, gluten-free
food, children,
vampires, birds, cornucopia--
OK.
Just give me the
"Reader's Digest" version.
[SIGHS] Well, I
don't have a boyfriend.
I can't pay my rent.
And I'm failing all my
most important classes.
I just suck at
animal husbandry 101.
Hm, really?
Let us consult the crystal ball.
Look deep into the crystal.
Tell me what you see.
I see--
I see a crystal ball.
Right.
Um, there must be a bad
connection to the spirit world.
Might be the weather.
We'll do this old school.
Let me see your palm.
Uh, front or back?
Front.
Well?
I see your fortunes are
about to change, very soon.
Soon?
How soon is soon?
Soon enough.
Will I be able to pay my rent?
I don't know that yet.
Will I stopped sucking
at animal husbandry?
Well, that's up to you.
What about romance?
What about passion?
Will I find it?
Close your eyes.
Passion will soon find you.
Very soon.
What do you feel?
Mm, I feel--
it kind of feels like a boob.
Hey, what are you doing?
Please, I can see your
future and it's a hot one,
filled with much passion.
You can't escape your destiny.
[SIGHS] Well, I have been in
a bit of a dry spell lately.
And I have to be
honest with you.
I can't pay you for today.
I'm flat broke.
But I'll give you my IOU.
Trust me.
Your credit is good here.
I really do know what's
about to happen next.
[SULTRY MUSIC]
[AMBIENT STREET NOISE]
[DOOR CLOSES]
SARA: Cindy, is that you?
Yeah, it's me.
Where have you been all day?
I know you're
going to laugh at me.
But I went to see Madam Zola.
Madam Zola?
She's a psychic advisor.
[SCOFFS] Oh, please, Cindy,
like you're not already
strapped for cash as it is.
I know.
I just-- I really needed
some good news right now.
And did you get
your money's worth?
I guess you could say that.
What's that?
Another note from
Mr. Catwhistle.
Ah, it's probably
about the rent again.
CINDY: It seems like we get
one of these every month.
That's because we're
always behind on rent
right every month.
Well, don't worry.
Madam Zola said a
change in my future
is right around the corner.
You can't be serious.
Of course I am.
Before you know it, good fortune
will come knocking at the door.
You can't be serious.
[KNOCKING]
See?
It must be Mr. Catwhistle
here to collect the rent.
Quick.
Run out the back.
I'll go distract him.
Oh, please.
That gag only works
on "Three's Company."
Miss Storm?
Who's asking?
My name is Cosgrove.
May I come in?
OK.
I am an attorney.
I represent the estate of
the late Lady Dracovich.
CINDY: Dracovich?
The late Lady Dracovich.
Late?
Late for what?
No, no.
I don't mean that kind of late.
What I meant to say
was, she's departed.
Oh, she farted.
Departed, Cindy.
Yes, dead.
Dead people fart?
Oh, no.
No.
OK.
Look, it is my
duty to inform you,
Cindy Storm, the
Lady Dracovich has
left you her entire estate--
everything, lock,
stock, and barrel.
What am I supposed to do
with stocks and barrels?
The estate consists of
Dracovich Manor, its content,
and the surrounding property,
plus a moderate source
of ready cash.
Money!
Here's the keys.
Yes!
Wait a minute.
Have you ever met this
Lady Dracovich before?
Well, no.
Well, then why would
she want to leave
you her entire fortune?
Ah, that's simple.
No one ever liked
Lady Dracovich.
And when she died, suddenly,
she left specific instructions--
the first person to push
Like on her Myspacebook page
would inherit her estate.
So you hit Like on
someone's death notice.
I thought it was Mr.
Malkovich, my history teacher.
Dracovich, Malkovich.
I didn't know vich was vich.
Why don't we meet later in
the afternoon at the house?
I can turn over the deed
to you and give you Lady
Dracovich's final instructions.
OK.
See you then.
There is one final thing.
This book.
You are to protect
this book at all costs.
Failure to do so would mean that
you forfeit your inheritance.
Do you understand?
Protect book.
Got it.
OK.
[SNAP]
But never read it.
The instructions
are very specific.
I'm not much of a reader
anyways so no worries.
Excellent.
I hope so.
Well, ladies, good day.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
I'm rich!
Woo!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
So you see, Professor Gordon,
it's absolutely imperious
that I'd be allowed a
short leave of abstinence
to gather my affairs.
You mean to tell me
that you, Cindy Storm,
inherited a vast fortune
from the late Lady Dracovich?
She's not late, she's dead.
And, yes, I
inherited everything.
Are you all right,
Professor Gordon?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
It's just this-- this
damn chair, it's uneven.
I think the base is uneven.
Now about your leave--
Oh, please.
I'll study extra
hard while I'm away.
I could do extra credit.
Ah, well-- well,
how would you do that?
The manor house has a bunch
of old antiques and stuff.
I guess I could write a
report on everything I own.
OK.
That is true.
Lady Dracovich had one of the
rarest collections of books
pertaining to the paranormal.
OK, Cindy.
You win.
[GASPS]
But I expect you to
report back every few days
and keep me up to
date on your progress.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
I really appreciate it.
Bye bye.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
[SIGHS] [LAUGHS] I
thought she'd never leave.
Now, where were we?
[SIGHS] I think we were
discussing how I could
best serve the student body.
Well, I was thinking maybe the
best way would be on your back.
And I thought it would
be even better on my knees.
Well, considering that you are
the head of the student body,
I guess we could
make a compromise.
[SULTRY MUSIC]
[GASPS AND MOANING]
Can you believe
that Lady Dracovich
left her entire estate
to that nitwit Cindy?
How is that even possible?
Some people have all the luck.
You know, Lady Dracovich had
a book, "Mysteries of the Worm."
Alone it's worth a fortune.
I'd do anything to
get my hands on it.
Maybe Cindy will
have a garage sale
and then you can
buy all her books.
I can't take that chance.
I need to have it now.
Well, how do you
plan on getting it?
There's got to be a way.
I've got it.
That old mansion is a hotbed for
our spooky stories and rumors.
Paranormal trickery, of course.
But Cindy doesn't know that.
If we could just convince
her that the place is overrun
with ghouls and goblins--
Then the book
will be all yours.
Precisely.
You know, I think we owe it
to Cindy to at least warn
her of the danger she's in.
From you?
No, silly.
From the supernatural.
Right.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[DOOR OPENS]
Madam Zola?
Hello?
Anybody there?
MADAM ZOLA: Who
summons Madam Zola?
It's me, Cindy.
From this morning?
MADAM ZOLA: Sorry, no refunds.
No, I owe you money.
I give you my IOU.
Of course.
I thought you were broke.
I was.
But now I'm rich.
Really?
Yes.
It happened just
like you had said.
Almost as if by magic,
my fortune's changed.
Fortune?
[LAUGHS] What?
How?
As soon as I got
home, an attorney
came by and said I'd
inherited the entire estate
of Lady Dracovich.
Lady Dracovich?
No, no.
Take your money back.
I don't want it.
Why?
I can't accept it.
Only bad can come of this thing.
Don't be silly.
I'm stinking rich.
What could be wrong with that?
You will never
live to enjoy it.
That house is evil.
I don't believe you.
There is no such thing
as an evil house.
Restless spirits roam the
halls of the Dracovich Manor.
Soon your spirit may join them.
As a matter of fact,
I'm on my way there now.
Well, if you don't
want the money--
Wait, wait.
Here.
Just take my card.
You may need my help later.
Heed my warning.
When the black cat
strikes at midnight,
the dead will walk again.
Cat, midnight, dead.
Got it.
[SIGHS] What a day.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Wow.
Double wow.
It's big.
It's expensive.
It's creepy.
It's mine!
I love it!
You do?
Let's look around.
- All right.
Which way do you want to start?
This way.
OK.
This place goes on forever.
A girl could get lost here
if she wasn't careful.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Look.
Do you think that's her?
Lady Dracovich?
Probably.
Madam Zola said
this house was evil.
[SCOFFS] Evil?
Look at that beautiful face.
She's a lot prettier
than I thought.
I do her.
What did you say?
SARA: I said I'd do her.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Good to know.
[LAUGHS] Impressive.
Like it?
Hell, yeah.
Check out this bed.
Who wouldn't?
This was her room.
Lady Dracovich?
How do you know?
I can feel it.
My senses are so
alive right now.
And what are your senses
telling you, exactly?
That I must have you.
Whoa.
Don't act like
you've never thought
about me in that way before.
All the times you've seen
me walk around the apartment
naked?
Well, there was that one time
when you were vacuuming naked.
What a better way to
celebrate our new home?
I guess it wouldn't hurt.
[LAUGHS] Not unless
you want it to.
[LAUGHS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[KNOCKING]
[CREAKING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Hello?
Is anybody here?
[DOOR CLOSES]
There's no need to shout.
You might wake the dead.
I'm sorry, Cindy.
I wasn't sure
anybody was here yet.
I knocked.
Sara and I have been
poking about some upstairs.
I see.
Well, if you're ready,
I have some papers
that require your signature.
Of course, Mr. Cosgrove.
Please follow me.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
This should
officially transfer
everything over to you.
All neat and tidy.
What did you say?
I said, all neat and tidy.
Why?
It's odd.
Well, it was one of the
last things she said to me.
Really.
It's a quite common expression.
No need to upset yourself.
Of course.
You're right.
It's very common.
I would say signed,
sealed, and delivered,
but I'm not sure your
heart could handle it.
Very funny.
But you didn't know
her like I did.
CINDY: Drink?
Sure.
Why not?
So what kind of woman
was this Lady Dracovich?
She was a sexual predator.
She had a way of
trapping people.
If you were a man, she
turn you into her servant.
If you were a woman, she
turn you into her slave.
She sounds like a free
spirit to me, someone who knew
how to get what she wanted.
She got it all right.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
She fell from up here.
She died here.
Here?
Yes.
Who pushed her?
I didn't say anybody
pushed her, Cindy.
That's right.
You didn't.
I think we've finished
with all of our business
for the time being.
Have we?
Have we, really?
Yes.
Yes, we have.
Goodbye.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Whoa.
What's with all the racket?
[ENGINE STARTS]
Wait!
Are you coming or going?
Going.
We're done, right?
Done what right?
Look, please feel free
to call me if there's
anything more I can do, OK?
What the hell was that about?
And why do I feel like
I've been licked all over?
[DOOR CLOSES]
Did someone just come in?
No, I don't think so.
It sounded like
the door to me.
Did you just take a shower?
Yeah, I mean, I had to
cool down from all of that,
you know.
All what?
You know, that.
You're acting
awfully weird, Sara.
Are you feeling OK?
Yeah, of course I am.
It's you that I'm
kind of worried about.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
Did you get it?
Right here.
What took you so long?
Uh, I had a little bit of
trouble with the message.
Kathy, it's supposed
to say Happy Homecoming.
[SIGHS] Spelling's
not my best subject.
Clearly.
Now, we take this
cake over to Dracovich
Manor as a housewarming gift.
And as soon as we get a chance,
we search the whole place.
Brilliant.
[LAUGHS]
Piece of cake.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
- Oh, no.
It's started already.
Cindy, what is it?
Tell me what's going on?
LADY DRACOVICH (ON PHONE):
Stay away from Dracovich Manor.
This will be your only warning.
Who is this?
LADY DRACOVICH (ON
PHONE): Can't you guess?
You're supposed to be a psychic.
Don't get funny with me.
And I don't frighten easily.
LADY DRACOVICH (ON PHONE): Good.
Because I'm not
into cheap scares.
Who are you calling cheap?
LADY DRACOVICH (ON PHONE): Just
stay away, or you'll regret it.
[CLICK]
What kind of person
just hangs up the phone?
Lady Dracovich, calling
from beyond the grave!
She wants me out of the way.
In the way I must get.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Hey, Sara!
Come here, quick.
What now?
It's this weird witch board.
[SCOFFS] So what?
It's just a game,
just to have fun.
It's all fun and games until
someone pokes their eye out.
I know, let's
contact Lady Dracovich.
No way.
Wow.
Did you see that?
Come on, Cindy.
It was the table and its weight.
It just slid on its own.
PROFESSOR GORDON:
Don't be so sure.
Professor Gordon!
You scared the life out of me.
Sorry, Cindy.
No one answered the door.
It was open.
That's OK.
Well, what are
you guys doing here?
We brought you a
housewarming gift.
Happy whore coming?
CINDY:
Oh, uh, yeah.
Stupid cake store.
That's sweet.
But you really shouldn't have.
Nonsense.
Besides I kind of needed to
talk to you about something--
this house.
Oh, OK.
In private?
All right.
Follow me this way.
Kathy, will you put
that in the kitchen?
Got it, babe.
Thanks.
Well, I'm going to stay here
and work on my stock tips.
OK.
I have to admit, Cindy,
this is a beautiful house.
I know.
I haven't really had the
chance to check it out yet.
But somehow I feel as if
I've always lived here.
[SIGHS] Well, it's
kind of actually what
I'm here to talk to you about.
This house, it's got
a strange history.
People think it's haunted.
They think it made
Lady Dracovich go mad.
Mad?
Who can say what madness is?
I just don't want to see
anything bad happen to you.
Why is that?
Because you're such
a promising student.
What a liar.
You think Cindy is a moron.
Excuse me?
The only thing you really
admire about her are these.
[LAUGHS] That is true.
Those are amazing.
They feel better than they look.
Touch me.
[SIGHS] [SIGHS] You've come here
looking for something special.
Now you've found it.
[SULTRY MUSIC]
[CLATTERING]
What?
Red drum?
[SIGHS] That's it.
I got to change bakeries.
Looking for something?
Oh, uh, me?
Well, you appear to be
searching for something.
No, you know, I was
just looking for something
to cut the cake with.
Will this do?
Woo!
Might be-- might be a
little bit overkill.
Who are you?
I come with the house.
If you tell me what
you're looking for maybe
I can help you.
Ah, you know,
really I'm just--
just the curious sort.
You know-- you know the type.
I think I do.
[GASPS]
You're looking for the book.
Book?
This one?
Oh.
Yeah.
You know, actually I am.
Funny story, but I forgot
to return it to the library,
and boy are they pissed.
I'll bet.
But I can't let you have it.
Unless, of course, I was
distracted in some way.
Distracted.
Hm.
Well, you know, in
high school, I did win
the John Deere distractor pull.
Oh, and how would you
go about distracting me?
Well, first I'd kiss you.
Where is everybody?
Come on, guys.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Holy shit, it actually worked.
This was easier than I thought.
Now you're all mine.
[EERIE NOISE]
[GASPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Kathy?
What's going on?
What-- where is everybody?
I don't consider that an answer.
CINDY: There you are.
[EERIE NOISE]
[LAUGHS] No, you don't.
Not yet.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
So Dracovich, you
really did manage
to return from the grave,
at least for a little while.
But you needed this and
a life force to possess.
Yeah.
But even that wouldn't keep
you hanging around for long.
I know that much.
Yes.
I did push you down the stairs.
Somebody had to.
Somebody had to stop
your plan from bringing
the evil into this world.
And I would have
succeeded to if it
wasn't for that silly kid
and her stupid Myspacebook
addiction.
Why do they have to click Like
every time somebody passes gas?
Yeah.
But I know how to destroy
you once and for all.
You're nothing without a
sacrifice, a male sacrifice.
And all you've got right
here is a handful of girls.
[MOANING AND GASPS]
Goddamn it.
[SULTRY MUSIC]
What's happening?
I think they're trying
to fuck him to death.
What a terrible way to go.
I know how to destroy Lady
Dracovich and foil her plan.
I've got all the
power right here.
SARA: If you say so.
I do say so.
But I'm going to need your help.
The hell with that.
I'm joining in on this.
[SULTRY MUSIC]
Please don't let
me screw this up.
OK.
Here goes nothing.
[EERIE NOISE]
[ZAPPING SOUND]
[SIGHS] Now that's a finale.
Professor Gordon!
Easy, Cindy.
Kathy, I-- I can explain.
You were possessed.
You guys tied me up.
I was forced into this.
Oh, you poor thing.
Well, I mean,
it wasn't all bad.
I'm the only one the knew
what Dracovich was planning.
The only one that
could stop her.
And you already did a
pretty good job with that.
So why the rush?
I think I set
the house on fire.
[FIRE ALARMS SOUNDING]
Fire!
Run!
[FLAMES CRACKLING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Can really foretell
the future, Madam Zola?
That would be so cool.
I thought I was Mr.
Malkovich, my history teacher.
Dracovich, Malkovich.
I didn't know vich was vich.
There's no need to shout.
You might wake the dead.
[SULTRY MUSIC]
[LAUGHS]
You'll know when
it's your time to die.
No, you know, I was
just looking for something
to cut the cake with.
Hm.
Will this do?
I've only got
one shot at this.
Please don't let
me screw this up.
Well, sadly, death finds
everyone, sooner or later.
Too bad for you, it was sooner.
Are you feeling OK?
Yeah, of course I am.
It's you that I'm
kind of worried about.
Am I some kind of mega loser.
This shit board.
Oh, please.
That gag only works
on "Three's Company."
Well, I was thinking maybe the
best way would be on your back.
Kathy, it's supposed to
say Happy Homecoming.
I think the base is uneven.
Now, about your leave--
[LAUGHS] I thought
she'd never leave.
We brought you a
housewarming gift.
You know, really, I'm just--
just the curious sort.
Uh, you know.
We were discussing how I could
best serve the student body.
Past, present, future.
All is known to
those who possess
the powers of the psychic word.
CINDY: I've got the money.
Oh, wait, wait.
Take my card.
Who are you calling cheap?
Your fortunes are about
to change very soon.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]