Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[speakers:
blues rock playing]
[woman]
♪ Got my bags packed up ♪
♪ Yes, sir
I'm ready to go ♪
♪ To the east
And on the 10 ♪
♪ Yeah, rollin' slow ♪
[song continues playing]
♪ Yeah, Coachella gold ♪
♪ Everybody wants
Coachella gold ♪
♪ Hurry up, now, hurry up
It's almost time ♪
♪ You know, I like to
Not to have to wait in line ♪
♪ Oh, hey now ♪
♪ Well, it's somewhere
Where the desert sun ♪
♪ Will shine, yeah ♪
♪ Coachella gold ♪
♪ Everybody wants
Coachella gold ♪
♪ And if they didn't know
They might as well be told ♪
[song continues playing]
Hey, baby.
You ain't from around here,
are you?
Mmm, let me guess.
LA.
No?
Mmm, Phoenix.
Am I close?
Don't act all silent.
Vegas.
Damn. Vegas.
All right, well...
I'm off at 1:00
if you wanna get a drink.
Hey, we could use
that bitch over here too, bro.
Fuck off, Bobby.
Let me talk to my new friend.
Hey, new friend.
Why don't you head over there
and meet my boys.
We're low on bitches.
Why are you always
fucking starting shit?
Get out of here, Jade.
I don't want to talk to you.
So what's your deal?
I was just leaving.
Good.
Why don't you
get the fuck out of here?
Otherwise you're gonna start
having to pay me fucking double.
Why would I do that?
Because I fucking
run this joint.
Do you know
who the fuck I am?
Bobby?
What'd you say, you smart-ass?
What'd you say?
[groans]
[song continues playing]
You fuckers done?
[song ends]
Put your hands
on the bar.
- Put your hands on the bar.
- Now.
- Hands.
- Bobby, you good?
- He broke my nose.
- Get in the car.
- I want his head.
Get in the car.
You two, out.
Let's go. Move it.
You heard him.
Hey, asshole, get outta here.
You got a name?
Wrong answer, stranger.
[girl's voice] Hi, Dad.
I don't know where you're at.
I don't know
what the hell you're doing.
who else to call anymore.
I want to get clean again.
Where the fuck are you?
Please call me back.
I'll talk to you soon.
Bye. I...
I love you.
I really don't appreciate you
manhandling my boy like that.
I take it kind of personally.
So who are you really?
Do we gotta
go through this again?
We don't like strangers
in this town.
I think you get that.
What I don't get is what a guy like
you is doing in a place like this.
It's a long way from Vegas.
Goddamn it,
I hate this tough guy shit.
Tough guys always think
it's best not to talk.
I never understood why.
He doesn't look so tough
to me.
He thinks he's tough.
- I think they'll get you talking.
- [phone buzzes]
Sorry. Excuse me.
I gotta get this.
- Maggie?
- Ben, where are you?
I told you
I'd be home soon.
You don't care
that I made you dinner?
- Of course I care.
- Do you want it to get cold?
- No, I don't want it to get cold.
- Okay, I'll see you soon.
- I'll see you soon.
- Don't drive too fast.
I won't.
- I love you.
- Okay, bye. Love you too.
My kid sister.
She likes to bake.
I gotta run.
To be continued.
[door closes]
This is all that was
on him, Mr. Nichols.
Give them
a few minutes.
Okay, so next time you wanna
start trouble in my town,
you might want to think
about taking the next exit.
[grunting]
Whoa, whoa! What the fuck
is going on in here?
Stop it right now.
I am processing him.
What the fuck?
You tell Nichols that
I'm the sheriff around here,
and you're not supposed
to talk to the prisoner.
- We're not. He's fine.
- For real.
You guys should go.
This isn't protocol.
- Spare me that shit. Let me do my job.
- Hey, hey!
I think he got the point, okay?
All right.
Nice talking to you, fella.
You good? You're okay?
Catch your breath.
I'm sorry about this.
This isn't how we do things around here.
This goddamn town.
[gasps]
Calm down.
Here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna
walk me out of here.
- Okay?
- Okay, okay.
You're fucking crazy.
Yeah, maybe.
- You know who those guys are?
- I don't give a shit.
Look, you're a good cop.
Nothing's going to happen to you
if you don't fuck around.
I'm just doing my job.
They work for Nichols.
They're not cops.
You know
who Nichols is?
Yeah. You wanna tell me
where he lives?
I ain't
telling you shit.
He's the shogun
around here.
We'll see about that.
[engine starts]
- Hey.
- What have you done?
- [chuckles]
- Smells good. [sniffs]
- Yes.
- So do you.
- Thank you.
Where's your nephew?
I don't know.
And I don't know how he's ever
gonna take over the family business.
- You know we have somewhere to be today.
- I do.
- We cannot be late.
- I will not be late.
- Please go talk to your son.
- That's where I'm going.
[speakers: music playing]
- Get that goddamn thing out of your mouth.
- [music off]
Why are you smoking
that shit all the time?
I've been trying
to call you.
- Who is he?
- Who's who?
This guy.
[groaning]
Oh, shit, Dad. Stop. Stop.
- How should I know?
- What did he say?
- He didn't say shit.
- Don't you lie to me.
Dad, I swear to God I've never
seen this guy in my fucking life.
Just let him go. Let me handle him.
I can take him.
Okay, like you
handled him last night?
We save your sorry,
spoiled little ass month after month.
You bring this shit
to our doorstep.
Like we need this
right now.
[Maggie]
Pie is getting cold.
Get up.
- How is it?
- Mmm.
Tasty. Very tasty.
Bobby?
I said, how is it?
It's good, Aunt Maggie.
It's really good.
Good.
Family is everything,
isn't it?
That's right.
I want you to tell me why that
man in holding has this picture.
Look at it.
Yeah, it's a real shame.
Isn't it, Bobby?
Son, I want you
to think really hard.
I want you to rack
that weed-soaked brain of yours
and tell me.
Who do you think that man
could be?
Oh, man.
Wow.
I'm lost.
I know.
How did you know
when it was time to quit?
It was ecstasy to me.
And I knew I was...
I was doomed.
[man] So I...
I turned around.
[engine off]
[sheriff on radio]
Hunter, you have to come in.
If you can hear me,
this isn't the way.
You have to come in.
Bring the car back.
We can talk about this.
I gotta find out
what happened to my daughter.
We can help you.
Just come back in.
[man] There you are.
- Hi, Burt.
- Ben, looking good as always.
- Thank you.
- Not as good as your sister.
- Maggie.
- Thank you so much.
Ben, Maggie, this is Chairman
Welmas of the Cabazon nation.
They own all of this.
Welcome to
Fantasy Springs Resort.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, Chairman.
I want you to know that your
interests are being protected.
Thank you.
And I want to introduce you
to my best friend,
Congressman Mike Ellis.
It's a pleasure.
- Congressman.
- Ben here.
My vice president,
my head of security.
Basically the brains
behind my whole operation.
Tell 'em what we got, Ben.
What we've got here is the
biggest aquifer in the Southwest.
Under all that sand,
just a giant river of water.
That's right.
This is what a billion dollars
looks like on a sunny day.
This water deal is what
we've been waiting for.
We have the tribe on board.
We're good to go as soon
as we get state approval.
Oh, you'll get
state approval.
We've taken care of that.
It's coming in days.
A month from now,
we're gonna be back here
popping champagne.
Hey, what's going on?
- Nothing.
- Yeah, right.
I know when my brother is fine
and when he's not fine.
Plus, that vein in your forehead
is popping out.
- So tell me what's up.
- You always take care of me.
- You bet your bottom dollar I do.
- Yes, you do.
- I take care of it all, don't I?
Listen, if that motherfucker is in
jail and somehow looking for Melissa,
we're gonna take care
of him too.
'Cause nobody's gonna come between
that water deal and us, okay?
- Right?
- Yes, ma'am.
I'll see you inside.
[shotgun cocks]
You are one ballsy fuck,
aren't you?
This is my home.
Yeah, I know that.
I'm here for your son.
Dad, what the fuck
is going on here?
Get back inside now.
Where the fuck
is my daughter?
- Who?
- Melissa. That's her bracelet.
- Bobby, get back in the house.
- We can take this guy. Fucking shoot him.
Tell me where she is right now, and I
won't drop your old man in front of you.
- Get back in the house now.
- What do you want me to do?
Get back in the house!
Bobby?
- I didn't...
- Bobby, shut the fuck up!
Wait. What did you say?
- What the fuck did you just say?
- I didn't want to do any...
Stop talking, Bobby.
- We were having fun.
- Who was having fun? Say it! Tell me!
- You didn't mean what?
- I didn't want to hurt her.
[speakers:
rock music playing]
I'm good.
- Mmm.
- Ooh!
I'm okay.
[laughing]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What is that? What is it?
- This?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Bracelet.
- Where'd you get it?
From no one. Do you want it?
Fuck yeah.
Can I have it?
Yeah. It's yours
with my blessing.
I love you.
Yeah.
- [chattering, laughing]
- [music continues playing]
Oh!
[chattering, shouting]
She almost spilled my drink!
Where the fuck
have you been?
Jimmy, you found it
and then you broke it?
That's what you get, Jimmy!
That's what you get!
[inhaling]
Wow.
- What do I fucking do?
- Why would you bring that?
That's a lot.
[laughs]
You think that shit's crazy?
You should see what I got
in the back.
[gasping]
- I didn't want to hurt...
- Bobby!
Bobby!
[Maggie shouts]
Bobby?
[gasping]
Is he dead?
Oh, G...
He's out there!
Go get that piece of shit!
I want his fucking head!
[man]
I see him. I see him.
Go! Go!
He's on the move.
[men chattering]
- [gunfire continues]
- [groaning, panting]
Move!
He's moving! He's moving!
[shouting continues]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
He's off!
He's running! He's running!
In pursuit.
Move! Move!
[men continue shouting,
faint]
[gasping, panting]
Fuck!
[grunting]
[chattering continues,
faint]
I don't see
the motherfucker.
- [grunting]
- [machine gun fires]
[gunshot]
[police radio chatter,
faint]
Mmm.
Steve said they were all out of bear
claws, so help yourself.
He stole my keys.
- Who?
- Jake Hunter.
He's on his way
to Nichols' place.
- I called CHP.
- [phone rings]
- County.
- Bartlett, this is Stone.
Get your ass down to Nichols' ranch now.
We have a situation.
And don't tell Ms. Sheriff
where you're going. Hurry up.
Okay, yeah,
I'll be there in five.
I gotta go.
[sheriff]
Bartlett, do you copy?
Go for Bartlett.
Hey, looks like this guy has been
making his way across state. Over.
Fucking give me that.
This is Stone.
Officer Kim, as opposed to fucking
around and playing private detective,
why don't you go write
some parking tickets?
Okay? Copy that?
This is under control.
[machine gun fire
in distance]
They got him.
He's around here somewhere,
I know it.
He won't last long
out here.
And if you get him in your sights,
you kill him. You understand me?
- I ain't never killed anybody before.
- It's never too late to learn.
Brock. Brock.
- [choking]
- [gasping]
Jesus Christ.
I didn't sign up
for this, Stone.
- Where are you going?
- To the station.
You're not
going anywhere.
- This is out of my jurisdiction, man.
- Goddamn it, stay here!
- No, good luck, man.
- Don't be a pussy! Get back here!
Stone, come in.
This is Sarge One.
He's not around here.
We don't know where he's at.
What do you have for me?
- I think we lost this motherfucker.
- Meet me at the tree line.
We need to send a drone up.
[grunting]
No! Don't fucking kill me.
Don't fucking kill me.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Tell me a reason not to put
one in your head right now.
Just a fucking cop. Fuck, that hurts.
Please stop that.
- You work with Kim?
- Yes, yes. She's my partner.
- I don't believe you.
- I'm not a dirty cop. I swear, man.
Nichols owns the town,
but he doesn't own me.
I'm just a fucking cop,
okay?
That's why I was leaving.
Please don't kill me, man.
I got a kid.
Okay, you go back to Kim.
You tell her I'm out here. No one else.
I-I won't say anything.
- I'll come find you.
- Okay, okay. I swear to God.
[Bartlett]
Okay.
Fuck.
Gotta get the fuck
outta here.
[grunts]
- [gunfire continues, faint]
- [police radio chatter, faint]
Fuck, we lost him.
Handle this motherfucker.
Don't worry about it.
We got an eye on him.
Fuck!
[muttering] Fuck.
[groans]
[exhaling sharply]
[panting rapidly]
[inhales, exhales]
Are you hurt? What happened?
What's going on?
I'm fine, okay.
Nichols' ranch. Shit went bad.
- He killed Bobby.
- Oh, my God.
He could've fucking killed me.
He let me go.
He has a message for you.
He wants you to know where he's at.
[police radio chatter]
We lost him.
It's just too dark out there.
We can't see shit.
- I know, I know.
- We'll have to resume the search tomorrow.
Just keep a perimeter.
Just two ways
out of these fields.
Okay.
[sighs]
So I was just telling her.
You need anything...
anything... I'm here.
We're family.
But I hate to say this.
This can't get out.
- It won't.
- It can't.
I know.
I mean, I need to know from both of
you, friend to friend,
is there anything else
you're not telling me?
- Anything I need to know?
- No, Vic.
This is my business here.
It's on the line.
- We're days away from the state funding.
- We know that, Vic.
If you know that,
and you two want your piece,
you better
clean this shit up.
I mean fucking clean.
'Cause kid or no kid,
nothing's getting in the way of
me making half a billion dollars.
Nothing and nobody.
You understand?
Christ.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about Bobby.
I'm sorry about what happened.
Fuck.
[vehicle door opens]
He told you that?
Yeah.
Why me?
I don't know.
We need to call in
the other counties.
This is huge.
This is completely insane.
Yeah, but then Nichols
will hunt us down too.
- Yeah, so what are we gonna do?
- Keep digging.
I'll head out there
in the morning.
Kim, what if
he's playing you?
None of this makes sense.
Why would he let you go?
- I don't know.
- And why would he let me go?
He said he was looking
for his daughter.
Yeah, well, I have a feeling Bobby
Nichols knows what happened to her.
She's haunting us, Mags.
That girl
wants her revenge.
No one's gonna
do nothing, okay?
We do what we do
for family.
That man's gonna die and no
one's gonna know the difference.
We built this business
from the ground up,
and I will protect that
at all costs.
Bobby was a fuckup
and you know it.
Look at this place,
man.
Do you think that he
could have handled this?
No. Why?
'Cause it was always
gonna be me and you.
Come here.
[gasps, panting]
[echoing,
indistinct voice]
Did you fail?
Yeah, did I fail you?
No, you didn't fail me.
I don't doubt
the job I'm doing.
I doubt my ability
to do it.
I'd prefer to be at home
with Melissa.
She misses you.
I don't have the answers
that you have.
I don't have answers.
I'm just comfortable with the question.
The home I have with my
family, I destroyed.
There's just so many times you can
take something precious like that away
before it cripples you.
[groaning,
panting rapidly]
How long
you been smoking?
None of your business.
I mean,
I don't remember.
You don't need
to take care of me.
I can go with Mom.
Mom's not better.
And you are?
I'm here.
Are you though?
You come back after being gone
from who-the-fuck-knows-where.
And then you're my dad
all over again?
That's not fair.
I'm 18, I have my own life,
my own shit going on.
You know, like,
you don't want to deal with that.
- I wanna hear it.
- No, you don't.
I don't need some in-and-out dad
telling me how to live my life
when he can barely
live his own.
Are you gonna take those shades off
and actually look me in the eye?
You gonna tell me
what happened?
You know I can't.
Well, then guess what.
I'm not gonna tell you where I've been.
How's that?
That's not right.
I'm your father.
I don't need a father.
I need a dad.
[helicopter whirring]
[helicopter continues whirring]
Okay, let's try it.
Stand by. We've reached the property
and dropping off the asset now.
Sir. Sir.
Sir, I'm here to escort you to
the property. Right this way.
Follow me.
- May I help you?
- Yes, I hope so.
- I'm looking for Ben Nichols.
- Okay, and?
And you are baking
something fantastic.
- Is there something you need?
- That smells good. Can I come in?
We have a lot going on.
A really full day.
We need to take care of some things.
Yeah, I think I can help you
with your present situation.
Oh, really.
What situation is that?
The man out in the field.
I'm the only one who's gonna
be able to bring him in.
So why don't you
call your brother, Ben,
and we'll have some muffins
and a little chat.
Okay?
Smells fantastique.
[Melissa coughing]
We can get you clean.
You just gotta trust this guy.
Trust. Right.
Like you... Can you...
[clears throat]
- Can you just take me home?
- You can't keep going like this.
- I just need some sleep.
- Listen, we can get you clean.
We'll do it together. It's gonna be
hell, but we'll do it together.
- You won't be alone.
- Okay.
- We can do this.
- Take me home, okay? Please.
Brother.
Hey, Jake.
[chuckling]
God Almighty.
Hey. Hey, man.
- Thank you for doing this.
- How are you?
Well, what's on your mind?
- What the hell's going on?
- You remember Melissa, right?
[man] I see.
- She grew up a little bit.
- Yeah, she did.
- Hey.
You probably don't
remember me, do you?
[Melissa] Nope.
- You were a little tiny thing last time I saw you.
- [clears throat]
She's sick now. We gotta get her
in somewhere, and I only trust you.
I can't handle it, man.
This was your world.
Yeah, yeah, sure was.
Um...
Can you do this for me?
It's out of my realm.
There's not too many things in this life
you could ask that I wouldn't do for you.
I know.
She needs it.
She doesn't trust me.
- [man] Get her in somewhere? What's going on?
- I'm right here.
Literally right here.
I know. And you trust him like me.
More than me.
- I don't know him.
- He's been through this.
Your dad and I been doing things
before you were even born.
Listen to what he's telling you.
He's been clean, what, 30 years now?
At least, yeah.
And he's helped people
get clean. I trust him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, got it.
For what it's worth, I know where
you're at, just looking at you.
And I've been there before
myself.
Uh, this ain't no intervention
or any of that stuff.
'Cause I don't even believe in
that, all right?
God bless the people that it
helped, but it didn't work for me.
And that ain't what I'm gonna...
that ain't what I'm thinking of doing.
Melissa, take the glasses off.
We're trying to help you.
Well, there you are.
[laughs]
[Jake] Okay, you guys are good, right?
I'll get going.
[Melissa] Whatever. He can leave.
He does it all the time.
[sobbing]
[gasps]
Well, first, my condolences.
There's nothing worse
than a parent losing a child.
How did you even know
about that?
Well... [chuckles]
let's cut to the chase.
Um, I don't think
you have any idea
who you've got
in that field out there.
Well, we can take care
of our own.
[chuckles]
I know your security firm
very well.
Okay.
I know you're aligned with
some really deep, deep pockets.
And you're in charge
of the security arrangements
for some pretty
important corporations.
- Am I right? Right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Well... Well, your interests
are going to crumble
if you let Jake carry this
to its inescapable conclusion.
He's not gonna stop.
He's not gonna stop
until you're dead.
Or he is.
Hmm.
He's dead.
You know,
you and I both know...
we don't have the security
clearances that we used to.
But his level of employment
has not changed.
[Ben] Hmm.
You got any questions
for me?
Not just now,
thank you very much.
- Appreciate the information.
- You're welcome.
Enjoy your muffin.
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
Wake the fuck up!
[grunting]
You piece of shit.
We found you
like the rat that you are.
Sneaking around and stabbing
guys in the back like a pussy.
Don't tickle him.
Make it hurt.
I oughta blow your fucking head
off, but it'll go too fast.
You fucking dirty bastard.
You fucking...
I'm gonna kill you.
[groans, coughs]
- [static buzzes]
- [Stone gasping]
Stone, you copy?
[groaning continues]
Call them off.
That's not how we do things
around here, Deputy Director.
Michaels. Michaels.
- Bring them in.
- Bring them in?
That guy deserves a fucking
bullet in his fucking head.
- No one's bringing him in.
- Mags.
I'm sick of sitting around
having a civilized conversation.
Either you kill him,
or we're killing him.
How is that working out
for you?
[door closes]
Bartlett, on my way.
I'll text you when I get there.
Slow down.
Slow movements, Hunter.
You gave my partner
coordinates.
Here I am. Why?
Stop. This distance is good.
If I wanted to kill you,
I would've done it back at the station.
So then what?
You're supposed to be
a good cop, right?
Yeah, I am.
Well, these fucks know what happened
to my daughter. Help me take 'em down.
- Nichols.
- Yeah.
So do you think they had
something to do with it?
His crew runs the whole town.
They're covering up some shit.
Think about it.
You know it's true.
You're hurt.
Let me help you.
I'll live.
Her name is Melissa.
Check
your missing persons.
- How will I get ahold of you?
- I'll find you.
[coughing]
[groaning]
Hunter, let me go.
[groans]
You fucking motherfucker!
I'll kill you!
- Bobby.
- What about Bobby?
Nichols' piece-of-shit kid.
You hang out with him.
He's a nut.
He picks up broads, he gets 'em high.
- That's what they want to do.
- You know these girls?
They're junkies.
They're pieces of trash.
You fucking motherfucker!
I'm gonna kill you if I get out of this!
Nineteen years old, brunette.
Melissa.
[Jake]
He said he loved her.
Melissa.
You fucking know who it was.
[Stone]
She was a junkie.
- You fucking...
- [screams]
I didn't kill her! Nichols killed her!
I didn't do shit!
[shouting, chattering]
How you doing?
- [man shouts, indistinct]
- Hey.
This is the fucking
Manson Family.
[chattering continues]
- What's going on in here?
- Hey, how you doing?
Where's Bobby?
Putting on a clinic.
- Get everyone outta here.
- Shut the fuck up.
Get everyone outta here!
[man] All right, guys, that's it.
It's a wrap. Let's go.
- Hey, Bobby.
- Everybody out!
Get off, man.
Show some manners.
- [Stone] Get off!
- Fuck you!
Get outta here.
- You fucking...
- I don't give shit.
- She's in there with me.
- I don't give a shit.
- Get the fuck out.
- You heard him, Bobby. Let's go.
- Fuck you! Fuck you!
- Everybody out!
Everybody! All y'all!
I didn't fucking do shit.
It was Nichols who killed her.
- She's not fucking dead.
- [groaning]
You're fucking lying,
you cocksucker.
She's fucking dead!
And I didn't do it!
[Stone moaning quietly]
[gasps, coughing]
I didn't do it.
You gotta let me go, man.
Let me go.
[screams, groans]
[no audible sound]
- Mr. Greenberg.
- Great to see you.
I can keep this
as tight as you like.
I know. What happens next?
Not sure.
I haven't decided yet.
But I like to leave those
kinds of things to chance.
I like chance.
Favors the prepared.
You know, I warned them.
I told them nothing was gonna get
in the way of this water deal.
What about your guy,
this, uh... this Hunter?
Hunter's my guy.
I'll take care of him. Don't worry.
Nothing's gonna get
on your skirt, okay?
All right.
Give my regards
to the tribe.
Thanks.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm good.
Oh. I'm Deputy Kim.
- This is the guy they sent in.
- Oh.
- Who are you with again?
- I used to be Jake's boss.
Oh.
So, uh, you got anything
you could share with me?
Nothing. I had to go
check on my daughter.
Ah.
Daughters are good.
I did call your cell phone,
and there was no answer.
Shit.
I must've
left it at home.
I hate when that happens.
So, does Jake have a sister,
a female family member he's close to?
Well, we do know that he's tried to
reach some members of his family,
and we're not
quite sure who.
And he did leave a text message
for his ex-wife. Why?
There may be a lead
I need to follow up on.
It could give us
some more answers.
How many people
know about it?
- No one.
- Great.
Let's keep it that way.
- Were you gonna tell me about this lead?
- [Kim] I was going to.
- Bill, where's Melissa?
- Oh. Hey.
Listen, I...
I knew you were gonna show up.
I can't get her on the phone.
Her mother's not picking up.
I didn't call you because I
figured she was coming back.
What do you mean? I left her with you.
I thought you had your eyes on her.
Yeah, you sure did leave her with me.
You left me with a big, heavy load.
I tried to help you out,
but I ain't no fucking babysitter.
And that's what
it was turning into.
You need a dose of reality.
You're running around
being a superhero.
Big shot. Yeah.
And you're good at it.
But where were you
when she needed you?
I should have told you,
but I didn't want to make it worse, so...
I know where she is.
Where?
Ever hear of a place
called the Salton Sea?
Yeah, I know it.
What the fuck is she doing out there?
She's with some drunken asshole
named Bobby.
Some fucking piece of shit.
And God knows what
they're doing over there.
I gotta go find her,
man.
She was trying.
[man] So, how many points of
entry are there into this area?
It's about five square miles
of connected fields.
And exits?
No, it's pretty contained. All farmland.
Only a couple access roads in and out.
Well, then
he's there for a reason,
and he's not
looking to escape.
Uh, me and Bartlett are
gonna follow up on something.
[walkie-talkie beeps]
This is Deputy Kim.
This is a restricted channel.
[Jake]
They're all dead.
Jake, son,
you gotta come in.
That's not gonna happen.
What do you want?
Answers.
[quietly] What are you gonna
do, son?
Wipe out the whole town?
- No, just them.
- Who's them?
Ask Sheriff Kim.
Jake, you're hurt.
You gotta come in.
Don't make me
call in the team.
Don't do that.
You do what you gotta do.
Murph, you know
who I'm here for.
You're gonna wanna know.
It's Melissa.
Okay.
They have Melissa.
They killed her.
I'm coming back
for all of them.
You're gonna help me
take them down.
He's coming in.
What?
He's bringing the fight
to us.
Gear up.
And under no circumstances
do you shoot him.
Amigo!
[speaking Spanish]
[engine starts]
What is it?
This town is plagued
with missing girls.
You think Jake Hunter
knows something about this?
Yeah, I do.
I think that's why he's here.
And I think his daughter's photo
is going up next.
[radio chatter, faint]
[police radio chatter]
[male dispatcher] White van.
Suspects are considered...
[officer] Be advised,
suspect is armed.
[police radio chatter
continues]
[female dispatcher]
Copy, westbound headed...
[police radio chatter
continues]
[whines]
Taking the shot!
[machine gun fire]
I told you no shooting,
goddamn it.
[shouting, faint]
[weapon cocks]
[shouting continues]
[machine gun fire]
[groans]
We have to move. Now.
- You two bring the car around right now.
- You got it.
- Go!
- Okay. You drive.
Goddamn it!
[gunfire continues]
[groans]
Three forward!
Two left, three right.
[groaning]
[groaning, grunting]
[men shouting]
- Okay, so...
- Sh, shh.
We're in full pursuit.
He's heading into an abandoned church.
That's it. Let's go.
Head to the church.
[gunshot]
Where are we going?
I don't think this is a good idea.
Stop the car.
Stop the fucking car!
[thud]
Shit.
[door opens, closes]
- You gonna make it?
- [coughs]
- Take me to Nichols.
- Okay.
How did we get here, Mags?
We had it so perfect.
There's no such thing as perfect.
There's just us.
She's out here.
I can feel her.
No, she is not out here, okay?
Let's go back home. Come on.
Okay, I'm headed back.
Lose the gun.
Sit down.
It's gonna be okay.
No, it isn't
gonna be okay.
What do you want?
I want to hear it from your mouth
what happened to my daughter.
I don't know
who your daughter is.
- [bones snap]
- [screams]
- I'll break every one of them.
- [groans]
You're a dead man.
Do you know
about Bobby and Melissa?
Do you know about
the drugs he gave her?
- Do you know that he raped her?
- I had no idea.
- [bones snap]
- [screams]
Okay! Fuck! Stop!
All I know...
All I know is
she was causing problems.
- [whimpering]
- So now you know who she is.
I want to hear how she ended up OD'd
and raped in this shithole town.
Bobby told me
that it was an accident.
My son had a drug problem.
Your daughter was an addict too.
And these kids were partying
and it went too far.
My daughter is gone.
So is my son.
No one
killed your daughter.
It was drugs. She OD'd.
That's fucking bullshit.
That's not how it happened.
It is how it happened!
[grunts] Yeah, go ahead.
Fucking do it.
Go ahead. Do it.
You will never know where her body
is, and you'll never find her.
That's gonna hold up in court.
Deputy Bartlett requesting
immediate backup to Nichols Ranch.
Immediate backup
to Nichols Ranch.
[sirens wailing]
[officer on bullhorn] Come out
with your hands up, now.
You let us walk out of here.
That's the only chance you have.
Fuck. Get the fuck up.
Let's go. Get the fuck up.
Okay!
Jake, don't hurt 'em. Don't hurt 'em.
Just bring 'em out.
Come on.
Move, you motherfuckers.
Bring 'em down.
All right, you fucker!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Jake, put the gun down.
- Put the gun down.
- Put your gun down, please!
Put the gun down!
- Shut the fuck up!
- [Murphy] Nichols, put it down.
- Do you know what they did to Melissa?
- Don't get hurt. Put it down.
Do you know what they did
to my little girl?
Holy shit. She's still
fucking breathing, Dad.
- We gotta fucking do something.
- It's too late.
Too late?
She's fucking alive!
- She's halfway dead.
- Halfway dead, my ass.
Are you shitting me? What do you
want to do? What's the game plan?
I want you to be quiet so I can think
for one minute. Can you do that?
- This isn't my fucking fault.
- She's dead because of you, asshole!
- Oh, my God.
- You sick... She's alive!
Let me tell you right now,
you fucking asshole!
- Look at her!
- Can you take it down?
You killed her,
you motherfucker.
[coughs]
- Did you fucking see that?
- All right, take him home.
- Dad, I'm fucking sorry, okay?
- Shut up!
Dad, I... Fucking...
Just go home, kid.
Goddamn kids.
[geese honking]
- [Jake] They fucking killed her!
- [Maggie] He's lying!
They're covering it up,
this whole sick fucking family!
No one killed your daughter!
She died!
She died
with a needle in her arm, man!
I will kill her
right in front of you!
- You're gonna get yourself killed!
- Go get him!
Put the gun down.
I will do it, Murphy.
I'll kill these motherfuckers.
Everyone has to know
what they did.
It's not gonna
bring her back, man.
Arrest the Nichols.
- Put your hands right there. Freeze!
- Go, go. Go!
- Me?
- Yes.
On your knees now!
- You are under arrest.
- [Maggie] Why?
- You have the right to remain silent.
- [Maggie shouting]
[shouting continues,
faint]
[no audible dialogue]
[shouting]
She's hurt her hand.
She's... Her hand is broken.
Let her walk.
[no audible dialogue]
Good work.
Jesus Christ,
you're a fucking mess.
Oh, God. You know,
help is on its way.
All right?
You're gonna be good.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Life's not fucking fair.
Melissa knows.
You weren't the bad guy.
I'll get a medic.
Stay right here.
[man]
Checking in on you.
I don't know where you ended up,
but I don't like how we last spoke, man.
I know life ain't fair.
I know what it's like
to lose my family to the job.
But you're a good man, and you know
that I know that you're a good father.
Nothing gets us ready
for that mission
of being a dad, right?
Melissa is a good girl.
She don't deserve
to be in the mess she's in.
But then whoever does?
Look, if you find her,
just hug her.
Tell her everything's
gonna be all right.
She just wants her dad.
You hear me?
Listen, don't let her go.
This world is a fucking cruel
and unforgiving place,
and that's why they send men
like me and you out there
into the dark places.
If anyone lays a hand on her
and hurts her,
then make sure they get what they
deserve, every last one of them.
- [vehicle door opens]
- [gasps]
[footsteps]
She's haunting me,
isn't she?
[weapon cocks]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull