(bells twinkling)
(swishing)
(bold orchestral music)
(fire crackling)
- Trick or treat, Sean. (laughing)
(owl hooting)
Mr. Jack will break your
back, cut off your head
with a whack, whack, whack.
(striking)
There's a story behind that
old nursery rhyme Sean,
would you like to hear it?
(owl hooting)
The Pumpkin Man will steal your soul,
snap it up and swallow it whole.
Then just as quick, before you die,
the Pumpkin Man will steal your eyes.
(bird calling)
(tense music)
Many years ago, on a night just like this,
the men of Oakmore
Crossing caught a murderer.
The killer was a wicked old wizard.
And before he was hung, he
put a curse on the town,
and told them a monster
would come for them,
Jack-O, Mr. Jack, the Pumpkin Man.
That Halloween, Jack-O came back.
A farmer got ready to fight the monster.
It was on this old farm,
right where we're sitting.
But before he left, he
said goodbye to his son,
a little boy, with the same
last name as yours Sean,
a boy named Kelly.
(tense music)
(metal bell ringing)
(gentle orchestral music)
- [Arthur] I told you to keep the boy
away from here, Eunice.
- [Eunice] Don't go, Arthur.
- I've got to, woman.
- If you can't do it for
me, do it for your son.
I can't raise him without a father.
- Are you gonna die, Daddy?
- Not if I can help it, son.
The Bible says know thine enemy.
He's cursed us all.
- I don't need you to remind me.
I watched two sisters die at his hand.
You and your brother hung him, he's dead.
Let his evil rest.
- He sent us a demon from hell.
It's killed the Barlows last night.
The streets of Oakmore
will run red with blood
if I can't be done with that thing.
- But vengeance is mine sayeth the lord.
- Then let him take his vengeance tonight.
Just before my daddy died,
he told me that the estuary
can protect folks against evil.
- Well what if he was wrong?
(footsteps clomping)
(somber, mysterious music)
- Take care of your mother, boy.
Always do what she tells you.
Always love her.
- Where you goin', Daddy?
- I've got somethin' to do, son.
- Can I come with you?
- No, I've gotta go alone.
But there is somethin' you can do.
Say a prayer for your
daddy tonight, you hear me?
(somber, mysterious music)
(birds chirping)
(thunder booming)
(Sean gasping)
(eerie music)
(thunder booming)
- Pumpkin Man.
(mysterious music)
(tense, suspenseful music)
(rhythmic banging)
(bus brakes squealing)
- Dude, did you hear about that guy
that got flattened by that car?
- No.
- (laughing) Looked kinda like roadkill.
- Can we talk about
something else, that's gross.
- Hey, I bet ya that's
the head of Mr. Jack,
the Pumpkin Man.
- No, it's not.
- Is too, it's the Pumpkin
Man and he's gonna get you.
♪ Mr. Jack will snap your spine ♪
♪ Cut you in half with a scaly vine ♪
- Cut it out, my dad said
there's no Pumpkin Man.
- How do you know he's not lying?
He probably didn't tell
you about the witch either.
- [Sean] What witch?
- Robbie says he saw a witch
walking around the neighborhood
this morning, he's so full of it.
- Oh yeah, well here she comes again.
- Witches have brooms and
they don't drive cars.
- They do now.
- She's stopping!
- Follow me!
(car engine humming)
Now do you believe me?
She's looking for kids to eat.
- That's just a lady.
- Then what's she looking for?
This is what they used to do to witches,
they threw rocks at 'em,
tied 'em up, and burned 'em.
- Robbie, don't.
(rocks clattering)
- I'll get her this time.
- Robbie don't, you'll get us in trouble.
- Ow.
(Sean groaning)
I'll get you, Sean Kelly.
(Sean grunting)
You're a wuss, Sean Kelly.
- Uh, Robbie, Robbie.
(Robbie yelling)
- Get off of him.
- [Sarah] See you later, Sean.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Thanks for saving my car.
- He can be mean sometimes.
- My name's Vivian, are you Sean?
- Sean Kelly.
- Can I give you a ride home, Sean?
- My dad won't let me ride with strangers,
I just live down the street.
- Can I walk with ya?
- Yeah.
- I'd like that.
(birds chirping)
- What happened to your clothes?
- Um, he stopped a boy
from vandalizing my car.
They got in a fight.
- Who with?
- Robbie.
Vivian pulled him off me.
- He's a lot bigger than you.
- Sean held his own quite well.
- Looks like you taught
him a lesson, Sean.
Go in and get cleaned up.
And don't tell Mom you got in a fight.
(chuckling) Moms sometimes
overreact to bloody noses
and scabby knees.
- He's a brave little boy.
- Sean's special.
- I'd love to see your spook house.
In fact, I'd really love
to help you with it.
- Well, we need all the help we can get.
I'd hate to impose.
(deep, scary music)
What brings you to our little burg?
- I'm doing some research on a book
for my great, great grandfather.
Actually, I was hoping to get
some perspective from you.
It seems your family was
connected to ours many years ago.
(car horn honking)
- Hey.
Honey, this is Vivian--
- Machen.
- She's doing a history of Oakmore
and she wants to know more
about the Kelly family.
And, she's offered to
help with the spook house.
- Well, you're gonna
have to stay for dinner.
We can't afford to pay you,
but we can at least feed you.
(scary music)
- [Walter] There's little
use in trying to resist me.
(footsteps crunching)
My will is much stronger than yours.
- Linda, where do you want this stuff?
(mysterious music)
(dramatic booming)
(tense, eerie music)
- Daniel, come on, we've
got the devil's work to do.
(scary music)
(cross thudding)
(tense music)
Daniel.
Jule, oh my god.
(tense, scary music)
(dramatic booming)
- Help, please, help us.
- Help.
- Please help us.
(deep, suspenseful music)
Please help us, please help us.
- Sean, are you all right?
You look like you saw a ghost.
- I had a scary dream.
- All dreams try to tell
us things, even bad ones.
Right now, your father tells me
your favorite television show is on.
Would you like to go watch?
- I guess so.
- Sean, baby, honey, are you okay?
- He had a bad dream.
I heard him call out so I went
in his room to check on him.
You're all right now, aren't you, Sean?
- So, what're you guys hungry for?
- I'm sorry, I'm afraid
I'm gonna have to pass
on dinner tonight.
I, I have a prior commitment
I completely forgot about.
- [David] Oh well, maybe
we'll see you tomorrow.
- You can count on it.
Bye, Sean.
(mysterious music)
(insects chirping)
(can clanking)
- This really sucks.
- What sucks, Brent?
- [Brent] The old Oakmore
Cemetery's suppose to be
right over there.
- I don't see any graves.
- Well, I guess we'll just
have to look, come on.
(insects chirping)
(deep, eerie buzzing)
I saw an old map at the library.
This used to be the Kelly farm.
They had a little burial
plot out here somewhere.
And we're gonna find where
they buried their dead.
- This is the suburbs.
There aren't any dead
people in the suburbs.
(Brent chuckling)
- The brain dead.
- Yeah, they probably moved the bodies
when they built the houses.
- Shannon, can I move your body?
(can clunking)
That had beer in it.
(insects chirping)
(deep, eerie buzzing)
- Come on Paul, quit screwing around
and help us find the grave yard.
(deep, eerie buzzing)
- Cool.
Think I found somethin', somethin' old,
and dead.
(Paul yelling)
(Brent sighing)
- Ever do it with a dead guy?
- I wouldn't like it,
you'd just lay there.
- You know you want me, don't fight it.
(Shannon scoffing)
(brush crunching)
- Hey, he did find something.
Daniel Kelly died in 1915.
- And there's two more over there.
I wonder what else we'll find.
- Evening folks, I'm a night
early but, happy Halloween.
(creepy music)
- Did you find that too terrifying?
I mean, has your mind ceased to believe
that which I've shown you to be true?
Let me remind you,
the human mind is capable
of almost anything.
From it, springs the
most wonderful of notions
and the darkest of evils.
Welcome to my asylum of horrors.
Oh yes,
the doctor is in. (laughing evilly)
(suspenseful music)
(creature groaning)
(deep, suspenseful music)
(television remote clicking)
- Almost time for bed, Sean Kelly.
- Can I watch Dr. Cadaver tomorrow
before I go trick or treating?
- We'll see, first you
have to try one of these.
- What are they?
- [David] Eyeballs.
- Gross.
- Nice, juicy eyeballs.
I picked 'em fresh for you.
- Come on Dad, what are they really?
- Grapes for our haunted garage.
Come on, let's go check it out.
- You guys are just in time to
help me put this stuff away.
Ah, Linda my dear, Sean
and I are going into
the haunted garage.
And then it's straight
to bed, right, young man?
- What all this stuff for, Mom?
- Supplies for the spook house.
I've got corn syrup and
food coloring for blood,
cauliflower for brains,
and spaghetti for--
- Intestines.
- Very good, we'll make
a ghoul out of you yet.
Did you get ahold of a babysitter, Linda?
- What do I need a babysitter for?
- Your father and I have
to watch the garage, Sean,
and collect the money.
I know you're getting
too big for a babysitter,
but it's just somebody
to keep you company.
- Why do you have to collect
money, we've got money.
- But some people don't, sweetheart.
The neighbors will give us
money for the spook house
and then we'll give it
to the homeless shelter.
It's important to help people
who haven't been blessed like us.
- We're haunting the homeless.
- [Linda] David.
- Come on, we got work to do.
Uh, who are you calling, Linda?
- Carolyn, I couldn't
think of anybody else.
- Carolyn's nice.
- I think she likes me.
- (chuckling) In your dreams, David.
Now get to work boys.
(tense, suspenseful music)
- Hey you guys, come here.
(tense, mysterious music)
- Cool, a killer old cross.
Shannon, don't say I
never gave you anything.
- Leave it alone.
- Afraid of ghosts?
- Maybe they didn't move all the bodies.
Just a little respect for the dead.
- Maybe he's right.
Let's go see what else we can find.
(tense music)
(Brent grunting)
(swishing)
(water splattering)
(mysterious music)
- I have a hit of your cigarette?
- No way.
- Jim, come on, please, just give me
a hit of your cigarette.
- No way.
- Come on.
- Buy your own.
(water splattering)
(phone keys beeping)
(telephone ringing)
(dog barking)
Hey, isn't that your sister's phone?
- She'll get it, don't worry about it.
(dog barking)
- You know,
I think she's in the shower,
maybe I should get it for her.
- No, you are not going in
the shower with my sister.
(telephone ringing)
(water splattering)
- Julie, get the phone!
(telephone ringing)
Julie get the phone!
Ugh, hello.
- Carolyn, Linda Kelly, everything okay?
- Yeah, my sister's home on break.
College education and I can't even get her
to answer the phone.
(motorcycle engine revving)
Um, babysit for Sean tomorrow night?
Linda, I've got this
Halloween party to go to.
- Carolyn, I was counting on you.
How am I gonna find another
sitter this close to Halloween?
(motorcycle engine revving)
- I'll uh, tell you what,
uh, the party's not till 10.
I'll bring Julie over
and show her the ropes,
I'll watch Sean until it's
time to go to the party
and then she can take over.
(engine revving loudly)
Oh you'll like Julie,
she's really reliable, very mature.
(dog barking)
(motorcycle engine revving)
- [TV Announcer] And now
with tonight's commentary,
Dr. Tom Mason.
- I am sick and tired of real Americans
having to apologize
for not being homeless,
disabled, or a minority.
(laughing) Where does this come from?
(motorcycle engine humming)
- Oh, pure white trash.
Carolyn Miller moves in across the street
and our property values plummet.
- She's a divorced woman,
Amanda, simple as that.
We're lucky she doesn't have children.
- If she were a dog, I'd have her spayed.
(deep, suspenseful music)
- You finish your prayers?
- Yeah.
- Get under covers.
(deep, suspenseful music)
- Dad.
- [David] Yes, son.
- Are monsters real?
- Well, monsters can be fun
like on the Dr. Cadaver show
or at Halloween, but there
aren't any real ones.
- What about Mr. Jack?
- Who?
- Mr. Jack, the Pumpkin Man.
Mr. Jack will break your back,
cut off you head with
a whack, whack, whack.
- Pumpkin Man will steal your soul,
he'll snatch it up and swallow it whole.
I haven't heard that in years.
That's just an old rhyme
my grandma used to tell me
to keep me from getting into trouble.
- You used to get in trouble?
- Sure did, and we're
both gonna be in trouble
if your mom finds out
you're not asleep yet.
Close them eyes, boy.
- Okay.
(mysterious music)
Then real quick before you die,
Mr. Jack will steal your eyes.
(scary booming)
(mysterious music)
(tense, scary music)
- Well that wasn't too bad.
- Now you have to catch me.
- Don't go there. (sighing)
(tense, scary music)
Paul, that is not funny.
(gasping)
- Boo.
(Paul chuckling)
(tense, mysterious music)
(thunder clapping)
(Sean groaning)
- No.
(eerie music)
(man groaning)
(scary booming)
(man grunting)
(man breathing heavily)
(thudding)
(tense music)
(man groaning)
(tense, eerie music)
- I am the judge of the hill.
Not everyone is lucky enough
to get my special attention.
(thunder rumbling)
(deep rumbling)
(bell tolling)
(laughing)
- What's the problem?
- [Brent] (chuckling) Shut up.
(deep rumbling)
(tense music)
(beer can tab popping)
(deep rumbling)
(bell tolling)
(fierce growling)
(suspenseful music)
(deep, tense music)
(Sean groaning)
- [Walter] I have found them guilty
and the punishment is death.
- Help me, Sean.
(static buzzing)
Help me, Sean.
(suspenseful music)
- [Walter] You must do as I've
found, kill them, kill them.
(tense music)
(rhythmic banging)
- What was that noise?
(tense music)
(rhythmic banging)
- [Paul] Brent burped.
(tense music)
(rhythmic banging)
- You guys, can we go now?
(swishing)
(slashing)
(gagging)
(yelling)
(thudding)
(Paul gagging)
(screaming)
(Shannon crying out)
(adventurous music)
(scary music)
Uh! (crying)
(tense, scary music)
(swishing)
(thudding)
(banging)
- No!
(eerie music)
(thunder rumbling)
(heavy thudding)
(tense, eerie music)
- I'm sorry you find my
justice so difficult to accept.
My power is much greater
than even I believed.
(thunder rumbling)
(mysterious music)
(eerie swishing)
(deep, tense music)
(motorcycle engine roaring)
- Carolyn.
- How's my boyfriend?
Ooh, you look so scary.
Yard looks great.
- Well, I try.
- You're like a little boy
about all this scary stuff.
- I guess it keeps me young.
- I like little boys.
- That's a nice bike
your friend has there.
- Can I go look at it?
- Look uh, but don't touch.
(Jim moaning)
- Neat bike.
- You like bikes, kid?
Go ahead, check it out.
- Well I guess I better
go talk to your daddy.
I get to be your babysitter too.
- Cool.
- So, you ever ridden one of these?
- No, not lately.
- Come on kid, climb aboard.
(motorcycle engine roaring)
- Seah, uh Sean.
(motorcycle engine revving)
- He's all right, Jim's a real safe biker.
(motorcycle engine roaring)
- Hi Carolyn.
- Hi.
- And you must be Julie.
What's that noise?
(motorcycle engine humming)
Sean, get off that bike right now!
- Don't worry, Mrs.
Kelly, he's safe with Jim.
- David, how could you let this happen?
- I, I said he could
look at the damn thing,
I didn't say he could ride it.
(Linda groaning)
- See you at seven, Linda, if that's okay.
(animal howling)
(doorbell ringing)
- Well hi Vivian, come on in.
- Hi.
- Ready for a spooky Halloween?
- Yes.
- What's with the book?
- This old family Bible got
me started on my project.
- [David] Oh, I love those old pictures.
(game beeping)
- Sean.
Come here, this might interest you.
- Who's he?
- Just some creepy lookin' old guy, why?
- I saw him in my dream.
- His name was Walter Machen.
- You must've seen his
picture somewhere before.
Isn't that right, Vivian?
(tense, suspenseful music)
- These are the kind of tales
that drove Edgar Allan Poe
to the brink of madness.
I'd better go easy on you at first,
I don't wanna scare you off.
I want you to sit back and observe.
Welcome to my asylum of horrors,
the doctor is in.
(deep, suspenseful music)
- Our grandparents never talked
much about the good old days
and we weren't allowed to ask.
Were our families close?
- In a way.
Walter Machen was accused of sorcery.
He was linked to the disappearance
of many innocent townsfolk.
81 years ago this night,
Arthur and Daniel Kelly
led the mob that lynched Walter Machen.
- That's terrible.
- Before the rope bit into his
neck, Walter vowed revenge.
He said the streets of Oakmore Crossing
would run red with the
blood of the Kelly clan,
or anyone connected with
them, within one year's time.
According to legend, his
prophecy almost came true.
Halloween night, 1915,
something came out of the ground
and took Machen's bloody revenge.
- You said almost.
- Arthur Kelly stopped the evil thing
Machen raised up from hell,
he stopped its mission of vengeance,
but at the cost of his own life.
Mind you, most of it's just legend.
I'm just trying to
separate fact from fiction.
- What about my ancestors,
you said they lynched Walter Machen?
- Oh that part's true, but don't worry,
time heals all wounds.
- Quiet, I can't hear the movie.
- [Woman On TV] Blood running
red down my soft skin.
Always the blood and the terror.
My soul cried out for release,
but for release into a
world of fire and torment.
And I knew that they were
there, clutching, grasping,
tearing at their own flesh and
the flesh of their victims.
And I would soon be--
- David, honey, could you
give me a hand, please.
- [Woman On TV] Left
my body, as the fire--
- Let me know how it ends.
- Can I go trick or treating now?
- As soon as Carolyn and Julie get here.
- [Woman On TV] My flesh
nourishing their twisted souls,
my death bringing life to the coven.
(somber orchestral music)
- I've come to drink your blood.
- David, how long is she gonna be here?
- Oh I don't know, I guess till
we close the haunted house.
- She makes me really uncomfortable.
All this talk about curses
and blood in the streets.
- That's just the stuff that sells books.
It's Halloween, lighten up.
- Linda, can I help you with something?
- Oh, Vivian, uh, no, no
thanks, we're all set.
(tense music)
(insects chirping)
- They say that there are
only two things in life
that are certain, death and taxes.
(laughing) What a load of
liberal crap, I tell you.
Why should I give my
money to the government
when they aren't giving me any of theirs?
- That's so true, that's what
I've always said, Richard.
(TV audience applauding)
Why are people so blind?
(creature growling)
- What's the matter?
- Dad says the Watsons are mean.
- Mr. Watson owns a grocery store,
he's gotta have the best candy.
(knocking at door)
(TV audience applauding)
- Oh, little monsters.
- Did you leave the porch light on?
- Must I do everything for you?
- Yes.
(thudding)
- [TV Announcer] Learn
how to play the guitar
the Glenn Miller favorites style.
- [Richard] I'm coming
you little parasites.
- [Both] Trick or treat.
- You looking for a handout?
- Yes sir, we'd like some candy.
- Oh, you want some candy.
Does this look like a candy store?
I make my living selling food.
You want something from
me, you pay for it, got it?
Good, now get outta here.
(insects chirping)
- Man, that guy's creepy,
creepier than Dr. Cadaver.
- He's just mean.
- Hey, I got an idea.
No treat, so it's time for a trick.
(insects chirping)
(Richard groaning)
- Learn from an expert,
learn from Del Bugercasher,
he's been playing guitar
for over four years (muffled
by footsteps crunching).
But you'll learn favorites
just the way he learned--
- What was that sound?
- [TV Announcer] And you'll love 'em.
(deep, mysterious music)
- That's it.
(kids laughing)
(deep, tense music)
Hey, hey I know who you
are and I saw what you did!
(scary music)
Hey, get outta the yard!
Damn kid.
(door clicking shut)
- [Ghostly Voice] The realm dies.
(howling)
(eerie music)
The realm dies.
- We aim to spook.
(hissing)
(scary music)
(dramatic banging)
(tense, suspenseful music)
(banging)
(smoke hissing)
(deep, tense music)
(mysterious music)
- Ah, ah, ah!
(tense music)
- [Woman On TV] Anyways,
the ancestors made sentinels
out of the charred, rotting bodies
of those ancient sorcerers.
Yet to me, they still lived on,
the voices of the dead
coven called out to me.
(dramatic swishing)
(deep, mysterious music)
(scythe clanging)
(howling)
(doorbell ringing)
- Sounds like our first
batch of trick or treaters.
Everybody look spooky,
let's go get 'em. (laughing)
The door is stuck again.
(door handle jiggling)
Oh, there it is.
Carolyn, Julie.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
Sorry we're late, but
Julie and her boyfriend
just had to fit in a game of pool.
- [Sean] You're not trick or treaters.
- Sure we are.
- Come with me.
(insects chirping)
Carolyn, Julie, you don't mind taking Sean
trick or treating for awhile, do you?
- No, not at all.
- Good, 'cause Linda and I've
gotta open the spook house.
Come on Vivian, you're in for a treat.
- (laughing) You guys help yourself,
it's open season on the fridge.
- Got any beer?
(Linda chuckling)
- Okay, Pumpkin Man, are you ready?
- I'll go get my mask.
- [Carolyn] Okay, hurry up,
'cause you're burnin' moonlight.
- Oh, this is so white-bread.
- I know, but just play
along with me, okay.
- Maybe if more children
were taken away from their unfit parents.
I think it's time that we
try a little hard love.
Not all of us were born with love
and respect for fine things.
No, we aren't all born with it, hardly.
You've seen the world we are in today.
We're hardly born with that,
some have to learn in the hard way.
Oh, love all your neighbors,
certainly, love your neighbors,
if they're real Americans.
But if they're bleeding
heart liberals, huh,
then they don't deserve to live,
they don't deserve to breathe the air
that you could be breathing.
Just think of that,
they're stealing your air.
(static buzzing)
- Oh, Richard.
(Richard sighing)
- The antenna must be down.
- We should get cable.
- Tool of the liberal media, Amanda.
We'll get cable when
they prior the antenna
out of my cold, dead hands.
- Shut up.
(laughing)
On your knees, hell pigs.
Duck!
(hubcap clanging)
- Oh, they're back for more.
- I'll make some more toast
while you answer the door.
(door clicking open)
(suspenseful, scary music)
(dishes clinking)
Damn rug.
(suspenseful music)
(toaster buzzing)
Oh!
Richard, you have got to get that fixed.
(suspenseful, scary music)
- Where's my hubcap?
All right you yellow rat bastards.
I don't care how long it
takes me, I'm gonna find you,
and I'll make your parents pay.
(brush crunching)
(scary banging)
A little big for trick or
treating, aren't you, bucko?
(tense, scary music)
Get outta my yard or I'll cut your belly--
(scythe thudding)
(Richard gasping)
(hubcap clanking)
Ah!
(tense, scary music)
(Richard gagging)
(deep, scary music)
(thudding)
(tense, scary music)
- Richard?
You gonna be out there all night?
Richard?
Richard.
(tense, scary music)
(yelling)
(scary, adventurous music)
I've gotta get away.
(Amanda crying out)
(toaster sizzling)
(Amanda yelling)
(tense, frightening music)
(motorcycle engine revving)
- What's Julie doing in the bathroom?
- Girl stuff.
Julie, come on, Sean wants
to go trick or treating,
and I've got places to go.
(motorcycle engine humming)
Julie.
Julie?
(motorcycle engine humming)
Beer run, bye.
Great.
(Sean growling)
(Carolyn gasping)
Okay, let's go trick or treat.
- [Sean] Yes!
(insects chirping)
- Ooh, the Watsons put
up decorations after all.
- That's not scary,
maybe they just want kids
to come up to the door
so they can yell at 'em.
Come on, the haunted garage'll be better.
(deep, scary music)
(door clicking open)
- Trick or treat. (laughing evilly)
I've been expecting you,
Sean. (laughing evilly)
Evening, Carolyn, happy Halloween.
Sean, didn't you forget to say something?
Trick or treat. (laughing)
- Don't hold me so tight, baby,
you're cuttin' off my circulation.
- Really?
I thought you could
handle a little bondage.
- Maybe I can.
(deep, scary buzzing)
You playin' rough, baby?
- Maybe.
- Just remember somethin', I bite back.
(deep, scary buzzing)
(tense, mysterious music)
Hey, what're you doin',
what's the matter, baby?
What's the matter?
- I think somebody's out there.
I think we should go back to the Kelly's.
- No, come here, come here.
- Not right now.
- Come on, what's the matter with?
I'm goin' to get beer,
get your own ride back.
(motorcycle engine roaring)
- Jim.
(deep, mysterious music)
- Welcome to the Kellys' haunted
garage, enter if you dare.
- Hi, Mr. Kelly.
- [David] That's Count Kelly, kid.
- This better be good.
- Ah, children of the night,
you are either very brave or very foolish.
Esmarelda, more children.
- Mm, I love children,
especially flame-broiled.
(deep, scary music)
(insects chirping)
(deep, tense music)
(eerie music)
(scary swishing)
- Let's go see the man turned inside out.
- That's gross.
- Feels fake.
(scary growling)
(Robbie yelling)
- (laughing) I guess we got him good.
- Perhaps it was something else.
- You know, she's right, David,
maybe those kids wrecked something.
You better go check it out.
- [Ghostly Voice] Welcome
to realm, join us.
- That could've been the Pumpkin Man.
- It wasn't, now can we please go home?
- No, I want more candy.
- [Ghostly Voice] Come join us.
- It's dark and scary in here, mommy.
I can't see a thing.
- That's the whole idea.
- [Ghostly Voice] Welcome
to the realm, join us.
Join.
- The heart's still in the right place.
- David, what are you doing in there?
- I'm feeling my guts.
(chuckling)
No damage, maybe it just scared 'em,
scared 'em real good. (laughing)
(scary booming)
(objects clattering)
Well I didn't find any body parts.
At least not real ones.
(fabric ripping)
(glass clinking)
- Something's been here.
- Yeah, David.
Uh, what a neighborhood
full of kids couldn't do
in one night, you managed in two minutes.
Well, I guess I gotta
close the spook show.
(tense, creepy music)
(bird howling)
(tense, scary music)
(tense music)
(mysterious music)
(thudding)
(frogs croaking)
(mysterious music)
- I wanna go home, I think we're lost.
- No, we're not.
The old cemetery's down the road.
That's where the Pumpkin Man lives.
(muffled growling)
- I think I heard something.
- It's just somebody trying to scare us.
(creepy music)
Is that you, Sean Kelly?
You're still a wuss.
(muffled growling)
(tense music)
(laughing evilly)
(Robbie and Sarah yelling)
- What'd you do that for?
- Come on, baby, it ain't Halloween
if you can't scare a
few kids once in awhile.
(brush crunching)
Hey, you still mad at me?
- No, but can we go
back to the Kelly's now?
- Just a second, I gotta check
my throttle, it's sticking.
(insects chirping)
- Uh, no.
Slow down, Mrs. Stephens,
you're saying Sarah and Robbie
saw dead bodies and a monster
all over the neighborhood.
It's Halloween.
No, no, I'm sure it's just,
no, Sean went trick or treating.
Okay, I'll check it out, thanks.
- Is there a problem?
- Hm, some of the neighborhood kids
saw dead bodies and a monster.
I better go track down Sean.
Tell Linda I went to look for him.
(tense, suspenseful music)
(swishing)
- What was that?
- Huh?
- I heard something.
- Give it a rest, Jim.
- No, really.
(tense, suspenseful music)
(swishing)
Huh, nice costume, butthead.
You're scaring my girlfriend,
now get the hell outta here.
(tense music)
I said, get the hell outta here.
(scythe thudding)
(tense, scary music)
(Julie gasping)
- Oh my god.
(truck engine humming)
(footsteps clicking)
- What?
- It got Jim, it got,
we've gotta get outta here.
Come on.
Would you get in the car?
There's something out there!
Would you please just get in the car!
Would you just get in the car!
- Hey, calm down, there's
nothing out there.
(Julie screaming)
(scythe thudding)
(gagging)
- Oh my god! (yelling)
(tense, somber music)
(rhythmic banging)
(Roscoe whining)
- What's the matter, Roscoe?
You hear the boogie man? (laughing)
(Roscoe whining)
(scary swishing)
David, you nearly scared me to death.
- Couldn't find you out front.
Some of the neighborhood
kids said they saw monsters
and dead bodies out here.
I'm trying to find
Sean, have you seen him?
- He was here with Carolyn
early this evening.
I scared the hell outta them. (laughing)
- They say where they were goin'?
- It's Halloween, David,
I figure they're out lookin'
for candy. (laughing)
- Thanks.
- Trick or treat.
- [Woman] How much you got in there?
- Where are you, Julie?
- What?
- Oh nothing, Sean, what'd
you get at the last house?
- Just juice.
- Well you'll need that to
wash down all that candy.
(juice thudding)
Oh, come on.
(growling)
(insects chirping)
(knocking at door)
- There's no sign of Sean.
- Someone's been in his room, look.
Where have you been, I've
been looking all over for you.
- I've been out looking for Sean.
Didn't Vivian tell you?
(mysterious music)
- It's gettin' late and I
don't see any other kids.
- We waited too long.
- Well let's start back, it's a long walk.
- I know a shortcut through the park.
(mysterious music)
(Carolyn yelling)
(Sean groaning)
(Carolyn grunting)
- Run, Sean, run!
(adventurous music)
Run, Sean, run.
Get away from him!
Get out of here!
(scythe swooshing)
(thudding)
(eerie music)
(adventurous music)
(Sean panting)
(deep, frightening music)
(mysterious music)
(Sean gasping)
(slow, suspenseful music)
(Sean groaning)
(scary music)
- You know what's going on here.
Now what the hell is happening?
- Walter Machen cursed
your family and mine
when he raised his demon.
Your ancestor, Arthur Kelly,
thought he killed the monster,
but he was wrong.
- You know, I've had
enough of your fairy tales
and spooky stories.
Where is our son?
- He's out there, drawing
the monster to him.
I let Sean be a decoy.
It's the only way to find
the monster, flush it out,
and destroy it.
- Linda, this is pointless, she's insane.
- Why do you think I'm here?
I'm hunting this demon.
A family prophecy says that
only the fifth male descendant
after Arthur Kelly can
destroy this creature.
That would be your son.
- Sean.
- I knew the demon would rise again,
and seek out the fifth son after Arthur.
It has to kill Sean before Sean kills it.
(adventurous music)
(Sean grunting)
(scythe thudding)
(adventurous music)
- Maybe I oughta check
the neighborhood again.
There's a few houses I might've missed.
- David, call the police.
- The police can't help you.
They're powerless against the demon.
- Vivian, shut the hell up.
(tense, somber music)
(adventurous music)
- Help, help!
(thudding)
- That was Sean.
(adventurous music)
- [Sean] Let me in.
Pumpkin Man's coming.
Let me in.
- [Linda] Is it stuck?
- [David] The damn door's stuck again.
- [Sean] Don't let him get me.
(adventurous music)
(scary music)
(blood splattering)
(tense music)
- My god, where's Sean?
- There's no sign of him.
How could he disappear?
- No.
(insects chirping)
No.
- It's not blood.
- Where is our son?
- You're wasting your time, Linda.
She doesn't give a damn about anybody,
certainly not Sean.
- You're wrong, David,
I'll help you find Sean.
But you're going to need to
do exactly what I tell you.
(Linda crying)
- Let's go.
(thunder rumbling)
(mysterious music)
That's Jim's bike.
(Linda screaming)
(scary music)
(mysterious music)
- Poor Mr. Jack, you can't be saved.
- Vivian, please.
- No, no, let her finish.
- It's like you were in a shallow grave.
I know where they're going.
(adventurous music)
- These are ash.
- Get the hammer.
(tense, frightening music)
(deep, scary music)
(bell tolling)
(adventurous music)
- Please no.
- Let's go.
(adventurous music)
- No.
(scythe clanking)
(tense, suspenseful music)
- You know me, don't you?
(mysterious music)
I'm the last of the ones who
brought you into this world.
Now go, back to hell.
- [Linda] Whoa, where did she go?
- Over here.
(scary music)
(scythe thudding)
(Vivian grunting)
(tense, scary music)
(Vivian groaning)
(Vivian gagging)
(thudding)
(deep, scary music)
(scary banging)
(tense, scary music)
(deep rumbling)
(swishing)
(Linda yelling)
(adventurous music)
- Give us the boy back.
(thudding)
(Linda yelling)
(adventurous music)
(Linda grunting)
(Sean groaning)
(adventurous music)
- Leave my mom and dad alone.
- David! (groaning)
- Come get me, Pumpkin Man.
(crunching)
(eerie music)
(deep rumbling)
(exploding)
(insects chirping)
(rooster crowing)
- It's almost dawn, let's go home.
- I have something to do first.
(birds chirping)
(gentle music)
- [Boy] Where you goin', Daddy?
- [Arthur] I've got somethin' to do, son.
- [Boy] Can I come with you?
- [Arthur] No, I've gotta go alone.
But there is somethin' you can do.
Say a prayer for your
daddy tonight, you hear me?
(gentle, somber music)
(birds chirping)
(Julie groaning)
- Carolyn?
Carolyn.
- Oh.
Oh!
Julie.
Julie, where's Jim?
- Um, that thing got him.
The one the kids call the Pumpkin Man.
- Sean.
- Sean?
- Oh my god, we've gotta find Sean, Julie.
Come on.
Sean?
(gentle, somber music)
(Carolyn laughing)
- Do I have to go trick
or treating next year?
- Not if you don't want to, honey.
(gentle, somber music)
- [David] Let's go get
some breakfast, I'm buyin'.
- [Carolyn] I guess I need a sugar fix.
I'd like a big slice of pie,
with a scoop of vanilla
ice cream on the side.
- [Sean] What kind of pie, Carolyn?
- [Carolyn] Mm, anything but pumpkin.
(mysterious music)
(rhythmic banging)
(adventurous music)
(mysterious orchestral music)