All I wanted,
all I ever wanted
was for my husband to love me.
That wasn't meant to be
because that's not
how we've made the world.
No, that isn't...
No, he promised...
Yeah, typical.
Yeah.
- Everything okay?
- I'm late.
Oh, a guy from the insurance
company is gonna come by today
with some papers
for you to cosign.
Oh, we don't
already have insurance?
Of course, but Ron wants us
to update our policy.
Sent a emissary by the office
the other day,
new kid,
had all the ladies swooning.
Sounds like you'll love him.
What does that mean?
He's good-looking, that's all.
Ooh, I got us
a tri-tip for dinner.
Oh, my favorite.
But I'm supposed to meet
Councilman Peck tonight.
- Oh.
- I'll call you.
I love you, Ste.
Why'd you say that?
'Cause I love you?
If you get yourself
knocked up,
that's all gonna change.
Yeah, I... I appreciate
what you're saying, Mama,
but it's... it's not as easy
as that, okay?
Can we just... can we just talk
about something else?
Uh, there's a new dollar
machine down at the casino.
If you win a free spin,
the horses run.
Okay. Okay, Mama.
Mama, I... I got to hang up now.
I... I got to go.
I love you too.
Mrs. Stevens?
Jake Walters, Vertex Insurance.
If you prefer,
I can come back later,
or you could go up and change.
No, uh, oh, this is only
gonna take a minute, right?
Right.
Would you mind if...
Could I have a glass of water?
Yeah, yeah, okay, yeah.
- Ah, thank you.
- Sure.
So what do we do here?
Since the insurance is held
in your trust,
you need to cosign.
- What kind of insurance?
- Life.
It's been increased
to $15 million.
- For my husband?
- For both of you.
Stunning view.
Can we?
If anything happened to him,
he wanted you
to be provided for,
and God forbid, well,
he asked me not to say this,
but if anything happened
to you, it would destroy him.
He wouldn't be able to work.
- He said that?
- Mm.
How sweet of him.
So where do I sign?
Uh, well, actually,
there's a bit more to it
than just that.
You need to check
your medical history here.
Oh.
Okay.
So, uh, why is the
insurance in our trust?
I don't know.
It's what rich people do.
They're either flashing it
or hiding it.
Some lifestyles are expensive,
not that I would know.
Both:
Oh.
Your name is Sue Anne
but people call you Brooke?
- Long, boring story.
- I'd love to hear it.
May I say this?
You have
a very compelling quality.
Do I?
This is a...
This is a very
unusual insurance meeting.
Yes.
May I ask another question?
I don't see how to
stop you at this point.
Does your husband know?
That you're not
completely happy?
Ah, right. Mm.
Um, why... why would I
answer that?
Even... even if that were...
The next step,
you and your husband
will need to get physicals,
and I'll generate
the final docs.
Uh, and then you'll have
to come back for me
to sign the papers?
No, no need
to bother you again.
We can do it all electronically.
I see it a lot.
Couples, they start taking
each other for granted,
and obviously you're
a very gorgeous woman,
but sometimes people
stop communicating
in an intimate way,
you know, talking and so on.
I don't know you.
That's right.
You shouldn't be talking
to me like this.
You're right.
I shouldn't.
It's perfectly safe.
We'll never see
each other again, and I find,
don't you, it's much easier
talking to a stranger?
What you're selling,
the insurance, what does it do?
Nothing.
Nothing can ward off despair,
but insurance
does provide financial
and emotional protection
against the unthinkable.
Of course, once
you've thought it,
it's not unthinkable anymore.
- Good morning, Mrs. Stevens.
- Oh, good morning, Carlita.
- Pleasure meeting you.
- Pleasure meeting you too.
You're a remarkable person,
Brooke.
You need to accept
that and decide
what you want from your life.
Wow, that was so cool.
Let's ride it again!
No, no, we're going
to the arcade.
- Yay!
- Yay.
Oh, Jessie is so cute.
She's making your ovaries
hurt, isn't she?
That obvious?
We've... we've stopped
trying for now, I guess.
Stopped trying to get
pregnant or stopped screwing?
Well, one does
cause the other.
Oh, it's nothing a good
BJ can't fix.
That's Tara's solution
to everything.
Yeah, I'm sure the night
you conceived started
with one of those.
No, that night started off
with one too many martinis.
Sexy underwear, communication,
and BJs are the key
to a happy marriage.
Not in that order.
Okay, I'm gonna start
with the sexy underwear.
You need to find a young man
to get the job done.
I could never do that to him.
Sparking life back
into unused parts
is the best thing
you can do for a marriage.
And Tara knows
what she's talking about.
Mm-hmm.
That's right, I totally
forgot about that night
with your Italian model.
Nights, plural,
and I regretted it.
Oh, you did not.
You spoke about those orgasms
for weeks.
Maybe we should all
get divorced,
pool our money,
and run off to Capri.
Mm-mm, that would not be
fair to you guys.
I'd get zip in a divorce.
- You signed a prenup?
- I didn't have to.
Ste doesn't actually
own anything.
It's all tied up
in his family's trust.
I thought you were rich.
Thank God
I don't have to envy you
anymore.
Money makes everything
so much more complicated.
Being poor sucks.
Well, I could certainly use
a little less complication
in my life.
This is the weirdest upsell
I've ever seen.
I offered to buy you a drink,
and you want
to sell me insurance?
Bad things happen.
You got to protect your kid.
How do you even know
if I have a kid?
I read people.
Oh, that's bullshit.
All right, I'll prove it.
You were married, young,
to a woman, one kid.
Lasted a few years, she had
no idea your wandering eye
was for the mechanic
that serviced your car.
Two old-fashioneds, please.
What... what are you,
clairvoyant?
Your dad,
he died before you came out,
didn't he?
And you came out, what, like,
three, four years ago?
You been talking
to my ex-wife?
Just give me a sec.
Ah.
You know, you're cruel.
Effective and profitable.
That's what credit
cards are for.
I'm sorry.
You hit a nerve.
You had my dad pegged,
all right.
I was an idiot
not to tell him who I am.
He loved you.
Parents always know.
Ah, um, when you, uh,
get serious about insurance...
Want to get out of here?
Hey.
There's another
three policies.
Oh, you're amazing.
These guys,
they have art collections.
They have wine collections,
real estate holdings.
They're supporting
elderly parents.
Someone needs to be
protecting their interests.
And they want to hook up.
Wong, who knew you were
so small-minded?
Since these guys got the shaft
from the insurance industry
during the '80s,
they trust us just about
as far as they can throw us.
I'm just non-judgmental.
I remind them
that they share the same risks
as everyone else.
Just not sure that your father
would approve of your methods.
Let's just say dad
was old-school.
I'm more reform school.
Okay, well, be careful.
There's a fine line.
Remember,
you are not invincible.
Oh, my God, I'm not?
Mrs. Stevens.
Oh, hi.
- Wow.
- What are you doing here?
Nice to see you again.
You look...
Good thing I bumped into you
'cause, uh,
I have your policy,
and I was gonna, like I said,
email it to you,
but I'm old school.
With a big policy like this
I prefer getting a real check,
real papers.
Would you mind
if I dropped by again or...
- Yeah, sure.
- Excellent.
Then it's a date... uh,
an appointment.
Hey.
Hate to do this to you.
What?
Last-minute trip with
some buyers to New Orleans.
It's a backup plan
if the rezoning falls through.
I'll be back tomorrow night.
I made you snickerdoodles.
You want one?
And add an extra
hour onto the treadmill?
Yeah, no thanks.
I don't know if it'd be fun
hanging out on Bourbon Street,
but you don't want to go?
Uh, yeah, I would...
I'd love to,
but, uh,
real estate exam's coming up.
Yeah.
- I should study.
- Yup, no, that's good.
Oh, don't forget we have
that charity thing on Sunday.
I won't.
Councilman Peck is
supposed to be there.
I want you to look great.
I'm gonna go pack.
"Oh, no, no,
thank you, sweetheart.
"It... it was so nice of you
to bake them for me though."
Hi.
Hey.
Wow, you look stunning.
Thank you.
Well, the truth is you don't
have to wear anything.
Anything special, I mean.
You're always breathtaking.
I mean, literally, when I look
at you I forget to breathe.
You're smooth.
We're drinking?
We're celebrating.
Veuve Clicquot?
Kind of a hip place
for an insurance meeting, no?
Yeah, I lied.
I thought it would be more
adventuresome to meet here.
We work so hard, don't we?
To be in control.
To do what we're supposed to do.
But we can't, and we're not.
How would you feel
if Stevens died?
I'm... I'm sorry.
What?
It's a natural question
with life insurance.
Most married folks have
a wish disguised as a fear.
Their spouse
is in a car accident
or has a heart attack
or something like that.
Yeah, Ste's death
would... would be a disaster.
My... my life would be over.
No.
This life would be over,
but yours would start again.
Things happen, Brooke.
Things that we don't anticipate,
and if we're alive,
if we're still alive,
then we have to be open
to those things.
I think that there's
someone else in there.
In you.
Someone that you don't
let out very often.
Someone who's
a little dangerous,
someone who wants
very much to be alive.
That's why I had
to see you again.
In fact, I...
I can't remember
when I wanted something
quite so much.
I've rented a room.
- I lo... I love my husband.
- Of course you do.
When we were first married,
we would go...
We'd go on getaway weekends,
and we'd go hiking together,
and he was so doting...
- Do you want to go upstairs?
- I can't.
I... you should not... you
should not be asking me that.
That's not what I asked you.
Have you seen my iPad?
Uh, check my nightstand.
Carlita.
Oh.
Pepper spray?
What's this?
For protection.
From me?
No.
What's-her-name,
purple slacks, three doors down,
intruder broke in,
tried to rape her daughter.
Well, if you're
that concerned,
I'll get you a gun.
I'll sleep on it.
You know, you said something
the other night in your sleep.
- I was dreaming?
- Maybe.
You said,
"Of course I love you,
but I also hate your guts."
That's funny?
It's funny 'cause you think
I was talking about you.
I was probably talking
about my mom.
Yeah.
Of course.
Silly of me.
But is there something
you want to tell me?
Anything buried deep
in your subconscious mind
that you're just
dying to get out?
Oh, hey, did the insurance
thing get taken care of?
- Mm-hmm.
- Good.
Ste, I want you to touch me.
Hey.
I want you to touch me.
Hey, you know
that charity ball
you're going to tonight
at the museum?
Mm-hmm.
Wong gave me two tickets
for employee of the month,
so I'll see you with Stevens.
Oh, God.
That'll be awkward.
Maybe we'll disappear
for five minutes.
Jake, no, don't joke.
If he caught us,
he would kill us.
- Maybe.
- You met him.
He's old-school macho,
territorial.
Well, it's gorgeous territory.
So you say.
You know, the point is he,
uh... he thinks he owns it.
- Doesn't he?
- Not anymore.
Hey, you, uh... you
remember the hotel?
Of course I do, vividly.
You said something,
almost as if you were implying
that Ste should have
an accident.
No, just that...
That it'd be natural
to have that kind of fantasy.
Mm.
Well, if you're
speaking of fantasy.
Well, three's my lucky number.
Yeah?
Councilman Peck at 3:00.
Between Angie's Louboutins,
private schools,
office overhead, I'm drowning.
Mayday.
Hey, Brooke, looking fancy.
If I disappeared, nobody
would care except you and Tara.
That's not... Buck would care.
Care?
He wouldn't even notice.
"Sure is sleeping a lot.
Maybe she's depressed."
Brooke, what I really want
to talk about
is a certain someone
who was sighted
at the No-Tell bar
with a handsome stranger.
- Dish, Brookie.
- I don't know what you mean.
- Brooke.
- I was signing papers.
Brooke, you're not.
No, it's... it is not
what you think.
- Mm-hmm.
- No judging here.
We're your friends, and we know
how unhappy you've been.
I think it's great.
Get some while you can.
Brooke, are you okay?
Brooke, I don't mean
to freak you out,
but Ste is walking this way.
- Ladies.
- Hi, Ste.
Ste, I'm sorry, but this is
a ladies only conversation.
The mysteries I could learn
from that.
Both:
But unfortunately,
I'm going to have to
steal my wife.
Oh, uh, how'd it go
with the councilman?
- The prick is avoiding me.
- Mm.
- I might need your help later.
It's a disaster since
Mom learned how to text.
- There's Wong.
- Oh.
Ste, good to see you.
Looking good.
Thank you.
You better hope so.
You got 15 mil riding on it.
Mr. Wong, my beautiful wife.
Great to finally meet you,
Mrs. Stevens.
Heard all about you from Jake.
He is such a sweet boy.
Will you excuse me though?
I need to use the ladies' room.
Are you waiting for someone?
Maybe.
Isn't Cinderella
waiting for you?
Ah, I forgot to ask you.
Are you wearing any panties?
Excuse me?
Looking for a woman
who isn't wearing any.
Ah.
That must be hard to find.
The hunt is the best part.
- Are you?
- Wearing?
Mm.
You'll, uh... you'll have
to see for yourself.
Oh.
Oh, my, you're not wearing any.
- Good.
- Have you ladies seen Brooke?
Well, maybe if you paid
more attention to her,
you wouldn't have to look.
She hasn't been
herself lately.
She's fine.
If you say so, but if there's
anything I can do for her,
please let me know.
Well, maybe it's what
you should do to her.
- Sounds good.
- Shall we?
Well, yes.
I can't... I can't stand this,
not having you.
I need you every day,
every night, every minute.
Divorce him.
So what?
We'll have nothing,
but we'll have each other.
I came from nothing, Jake.
If I go back, I'll die.
I will wither and die.
You'll wither and die
if you stay with him.
Who's texting at this hour?
Mom just figured out
what emojis are.
Oh, God.
She's losing at the slots.
She wants to come visit.
No. Hell no.
Write her a check.
I cannot handle a visit
from your mother right now.
No way.
I have to go to Miami tomorrow.
- Again?
- For Christ sakes,
it's one night.
We need this.
It's another backup deal.
That's why you went to...
To New Orleans.
God!
Everything we have is tied up.
What do you want from me?
If you want to talk...
There's nothing for you
to concern yourself about.
Just trying to be here
for you.
I want to help.
Okay, well, when you get
your real estate license,
you can go out and work,
and I'll stay home.
You know, sometimes I think
you just want me gone.
Divorce, new life,
new wife, is that it?
Really? You want to have
that argument right now, huh?
Next do you want to talk about
why we don't have kids, hmm?
Hmm?
Maybe you want an affair, hmm?
New man, new life.
Do you want to be married?
I want you to tell me
we're okay.
We're okay.
When you texted,
"What do we do?"
what did you mean?
What did you think I meant?
We're talking about
something, Jake.
What are we talking about?
A better life for both of us.
We can't go on this way,
and yeah,
we're talking about something,
and you know exactly what it is
even if you can't
say it out loud.
Hey, hey, it's me.
Can... can Sylvester
watch the kids for a while?
I need to come over and talk.
Can you call Ang?
Okay, bye.
What am I doing?
Okay, spill it.
I think I'm gonna ask
Ste for a divorce.
Are you sure?
It's it because of that guy?
No. Well, yeah...
Yes, maybe.
I... I don't know.
You don't want
to get divorced.
You really think
your little sex toy
is gonna stick around
once you're broke?
He's just looking for
some rich bitch to pay his way.
Okay, that's not true.
Ste doesn't love me anymore.
I... quite frankly,
I am done pretending.
- Ang, if she's not happy...
- Happy's a relative term.
But if you're not willing
to work and sacrifice for it,
then it's time to move on.
Make a clean break and end it.
I got to go.
Ste's a sure thing, Brooke.
Don't forget that.
Oh, you okay?
I got you a gun.
Be sure to go to a gun range
and learn how to use this first.
I slept with someone.
I think that means
we should get a divorce.
Wh... why?
You're not happy, Ste.
I don't... I don't make
you happy anymore.
I love you.
I don't want to lose you.
This is my fault.
It's not your fault.
I haven't been paying enough
attention to you.
- Ste, that's not...
- No, don't say anything.
This land development deal,
it's... it's killing me.
I'm sorry.
I got us into this mess.
I got us into this whole mess.
It's my fault.
You did not... this is
not your fault.
This whole... whole baby thing
has completely messed me up.
I do not want
to lose you, okay?
I don't want to lose you.
Let's... let's go
to the mountains this weekend,
just you and me, okay?
Like old times,
we'll forget about everything.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Jake, you look like...
- Yeah, I know, thank you.
I look... I'm fine. I just didn't
get a ton of sleep last night.
I'm feeling a little burnt out.
My hotshot hadn't sold
a policy in...
Please don't worry.
I got a couple leads tonight.
That'll get me back up to speed.
All right.
Hi, honey,
I'm gonna go check in
with the concierge.
Oh, you,
uh... you want me to go?
No, no, no, you stay, relax.
I want this weekend
to be perfect.
I'll see if they have
any trail maps.
- Wh... what are you doing here?
- You texted me.
Why would you tell me
where you're at
unless you wanted me
to come find you?
Oh, my God, that is not why.
Jake, you can't be here.
You have to go.
You...
No, this can't work.
Hmm?
Has it occurred to you
how much older I am?
Ooh, I like
an experienced woman.
You know what you want.
We... we can't go on
like this forever.
Why not? Maybe great sex
is your fountain of youth.
I... I told him, and he
doesn't want to let me go.
Come here.
Tomorrow, spread out.
You take the lower trail.
Let him take the ridge trail.
There's an abandoned lodge
up there
on the overlook.
I'll take care of it.
It'll look like an accident.
Tomorrow she'll be dead,
and the money will be ours.
Wonderful.
This is fun, reminds me
of our honeymoon.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
I'm such an idiot.
I left my headphones.
Oh, let's go back.
No, that's okay.
I'll go get them.
I'll run down real quick.
I'll meet you at the top
at the ridge.
I'll be right back.
God, Jake, pick up.
Pick up, damn it.
Oh, my God, it's you.
Did you do it?
- No.
- Oh, thank God.
Jake, we can't, okay?
It just is a mistake.
We would live with it
for the rest of our lives.
We'll do what you said, okay?
I'll divorce him,
and we can run off together.
What? What is it?
Jake? Jake?
What'd she look like?
Her expression
when you pushed her?
You said she hated you,
and she would jump
at the chance to kill you.
Yeah.
She was sleeping around
all over Buckhead.
She changed her mind.
You didn't do it.
Why?
Are you in love with her?
Oh, Christ almighty, you are.
She got to you.
- Did she?
- You're not thinking clearly.
I think I'm thinking
very clearly, thank you.
It's time, Jake.
She used me.
She married me for my money.
She never loved me,
not one single minute.
She cheated on my
any chance she got.
You proved how easily
she would do it.
You married her.
That is what
we are trying to fix.
God, I need that 15 million,
otherwise I am ruined.
Fifteen?
Oh, come on.
Of course we're gonna split it.
That goes without saying.
If it goes without saying,
why did you
just say something different?
Oh, my God.
What does it matter
who has the money?
We'll be together.
You having qualms, Jake?
Hmm?
I didn't think they were
in your repertoire.
- I didn't think so either.
- You liar!
Before Jake I never slept
with anyone but you.
- No.
- I loved you.
That's not true.
You only married me to get away
from your trailer trash mother.
That's not true.
You're a whore,
and I loved you.
Hey!
Jake.
He didn't... he didn't love me?
He... he was gonna kill me
for money to save his... his...
We were killing him for money.
He was just being
honest about it.
We were doing it
for love, Jake.
And the money
to enjoy our love.
Love?
Is that what this is?
Yes. I don't usually
feel things, Brooke,
but with you, with you I do.
I really... I do.
Okay, all right, okay.
The police will think
he leaned too far over the edge
for the good shot, and he fell.
Remember, he was crazy about
getting the best shots.
You need to go now,
to the other trail,
and remember if you see anyone,
say something memorable.
Go.
Just...
Ah.
Damn you.
Thank you.
You have a package.
- Yes?
- Hey, it's me. What is this?
It's a precaution.
It's disposable,
cheap, untraceable.
Yeah, but why? Why now?
We cannot see each other,
not for a while.
They're doing due diligence
since the policy
was taken out so recently.
It's nothing that
I didn't anticipate.
Well, if you anticipated it,
you would have
given this to me sooner.
You miss me?
Jake?
Do you miss me?
Yes.
Of course, terribly.
Ah, Jake.
Corporate's not happy.
Yeah, I'll bet.
What's your angle, the wife?
Got to be.
Are there any scratches on
him from her fingernails or...
No, just from the fall, but
there's an autopsy in process.
Hey, Jake?
You didn't sleep
with her, did you?
I flirt, Wong.
Past that, things get messy.
Yeah, it's me.
I need you back at the office.
Oh, Brooke, oh, my God.
I'm so sorry. I can't imagine
what you must be going through.
One moment someone
you love is there,
and then...
how could this happen?
You're here.
That's what matters.
Angie didn't even call.
Oh, sweetie, don't think.
She just doesn't deal
with death well.
And what am I, a pro?
She's got a touch
of the stomach flu.
She loves you, 'kay?
She'll be at the memorial.
You don't find it strange
that a man
with so much hiking experience
could just fall like that?
- What are you saying?
- Well, hypothetically,
what if... what if
it wasn't an accident?
Yeah, who would want Ste dead?
We all have secrets.
Oh, you mean a lover?
Yeah, maybe if Ste
were interested in sex.
Or maybe it was money,
gambling problems,
a bookie, a creative hit man?
I mean, we...
We are facing
bankruptcy, so who knows?
I am so sorry.
I didn't mea... I'm just trying
to protect you.
From what?
The thing is if it wasn't
an accident,
people on TV
always suspect the wife.
- Okay, so what's my motive?
- Is there life insurance?
God, do you... do you have
a reason to believe
that this wasn't an accident?
Of course not.
No, I'm just thinking like
they do, and there was
a car parked outside.
It drove off when I came up.
I know.
Hey,
I'm not as helpless
as you think I am.
Uh, Jake, this is Mike Wall,
investigator
on the Stevens case.
- It's a case now?
- There's been a development.
A button on Stevens' vest
had a partial print.
Not his?
Well, the feds are checking
the database.
I got a friend.
All right, well,
if I can help in any way.
See you at the funeral.
Seems like a nice guy.
Yeah, I wouldn't
take it that far.
But he's good at his job.
Go comfort the wife,
see what you can find.
I'm sorry for your loss,
Mrs. Stevens.
They are trying
to deny your claim.
The police gave it
the all-clear,
but the bastards in Hartford
hired an investigator
to look into it.
How are you holding up?
- I'm holding up.
- They're watching us.
Do not contact me
under any circumstances,
and be careful
of that investigator, Wall.
- Mrs. Stevens, condolences.
- Thank you.
I'm Mike Wall
with the insurance company.
Sorry to interrupt,
but let me explain.
Your husband had what's
considered a suspicious death,
and if in the event
there was foul play,
we're hoping you can help.
- I... I don't understand.
- Well, people at his office
say he was talking
about disappearing.
Perhaps he was
going into hiding,
or maybe he was afraid
for his life.
No, that's... that's crazy.
Well, we'd like to come
by your home
and check his computer.
Oh, by any chance,
have you seen his iPad?
I mean, who knows
what we might discover?
No.
Uh, what do you hope to find?
Well, an email
on his cell suggests
there might be another account,
another email address
that isn't in his name
or on his phone.
We think he downloaded messages
on his iPad or home computer.
Well, his iPad is... is
not at home,
but I can look for it
and get back to you.
Well, may we come by
and look for it?
Strangers pawing through
my underwear drawer
on the day
of my husband's funeral?
No, thank you.
Yeah, well, people
who die accidentally
don't first dispose
of their electronics.
- I said I'd get back to you.
- Yes, and if you don't,
I'll see you at your home
with a warrant in hand.
This is inappropriate.
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
You went to Venice with Irene?
Who the hell is Irene?
Oh, hey.
Robert Lange?
Okay, let's try this again.
Brooke, if you're getting this,
that means that
I've left it for you,
and if I left it for you,
that means I've left you.
But not... not just you.
I've left myself, our life.
When I heard about your
affairs, it devastated me,
but I don't blame you.
I'm a failure in everything.
In marriage, in business,
in everything.
No, no, it's too humiliating.
Yes.
Oh, there, buddy.
What the hell?
Carlita, can you
take the trash out?
Brooke?
We pray to thee,
our God, this day
for the blessings you provide.
You haven't answered my texts.
I hate you.
I don't know why I'm here.
You're here to renew
our sacred vows.
No, I'm not
doing this anymore.
I'm being followed.
We shouldn't even be meeting.
- Beneath thy almighty wing.
- You sure?
Jake, did you not hear
what I said?
Oh, God,
the spirit of all our joys,
the cause of our delights,
the glory of our darkest nights,
the comfort in times like these.
There is only one way to live
for people like us, Brooke.
We have to risk everything.
That risk is what we crave
to feel alive.
It turns you on.
We need to feel something,
and we need it desperately.
Jake, we can't do this.
What, God doesn't
approve of sex?
He invented sex.
Both:
This is crazy.
We could get caught.
Mm-hmm. That's why you
don't want me to stop.
You filmed yourselves.
Jake, I watched it all.
Not me, him. I didn't know.
Whenever you weren't together,
you were with me,
and he was with this Irene.
She was just loose change,
his words, not mine.
You two just screw whatever.
Man, woman, don't matter.
That matters.
They're different.
Yeah, I'm aware.
What about Ste?
Closeted?
Bisexual?
What is the difference?
I mean, we're all
just the same, right?
We're just trying desperately
to connect to someone, anyone.
I was married to someone that
I didn't have a clue about.
And I don't know
who the hell you are.
I'm not sure you're
still with me, Brooke.
I need to trust
that you and I are together.
I am sorry about this.
Insurance in case you... I mean,
you know,
I am in the insurance industry.
- You have killed 12 people?
- Give or take.
Say what the job is.
If you're arrested
on her word, I kill the bitc.
What's your weapon of choice?
Glock and silencer.
I said I was sorry.
If it's any consolation,
the insurance scam was my idea.
I put Stevens up to it.
He was desperate.
When I realized that
he was planning
an "accidental" suicide
to leave you the money,
I figured out a way for me
to make money in the process.
Look, Brooke,
things turned out this way
because I fell in love with you.
I chose you.
- My coffee cup's missing.
- Maybe it's in the sink.
I, uh, like to visualize.
Possible third person,
mystery man or woman.
Looking at the way
that Stevens was found,
forensics thinks
that he fell backwards.
Meaning?
More than likely
he was pushed.
Or he was taking a selfie.
The view up there really
is quite something.
Is it really?
That's what I hear.
I wouldn't know.
I prefer tarmac to trees.
Mm.
Hello?
Of course
there's a liability hazard.
The signs were obscured.
There was no railing,
and it's your property.
Wh... then make me a good offer.
Thank you.
I accept.
Mrs. Stevens,
we have a warrant
to search these premises.
You were right.
It was in the sink,
only I didn't put it there.
Jake, where were you
the morning that Stevens died?
I tried to reach you.
You didn't
come in till mid-afternoon.
- When do I usually come in?
- Afternoon.
- Why is that?
- Well, the thing is that
the policy you gave me
was dated the night
before the murder.
Murder?
Oh, sorry, sorry, not proven.
The night before Stevens died,
that policy.
You know, I, uh,
had to call the insured.
Couldn't read his handwriting.
Yeah, well, with computers
now, no one can write anymore.
Your insured said he bought
the policy earlier.
The night in question
he was with his sister.
Maybe I accidentally
entered the wrong date.
Come on, boss,
are you really accusing me
of being involved in this?
Check my phone records.
That'll tell you where I was.
- We did.
- Mm.
Thank you for your faith in me.
You know corporate's
first thought,
agent is co-conspirator.
We had to get you
off their radar.
Tell them to do something
anatomically impossible.
Look, Wall took your prints
off that cup.
That's why it was in the sink.
Again, only to eliminate you.
Thank you for saying that.
How's the real
investigation coming?
The police checked
Mrs. Stevens' phone records.
Shows calls coming in and out
from the cell phone
and a disposable.
Like this?
The calls stopped
when Stevens died.
Why don't the cops
just trace the phone?
The SIM card was removed
and the phone destroyed.
Convenient, huh?
Jake, they're on it.
I thought you needed to know.
Told you it wasn't here.
You can let yourselves out.
Hey.
Hey, honey,
I was thinking about you.
Do you need me to come over?
No, I'm fine.
You really shouldn't be
alone right now.
You know what? You're right.
Hey, Tara, do we know an Irene?
- I don't think so.
- Hmm.
Yeah, remember your trip
to Italy?
Is that where you met
that model?
Why?
Just, uh... doesn't matter.
I'll see you soon.
Angie, what are you...
What are you doing here?
You startled me.
- We need to talk.
- Okay.
About what?
How'd you like Venice, Irene?
A lot.
It didn't seem like
a bad thing to do
to one of your best friends?
- Were we ever really friends?
- Well, I did think so.
You know, the... the
funny thing is I,
uh... I thought
that Tara was Irene.
Venice was a scouting
expedition to see where we'd go
once we had the money
and the baby was born.
Remember, stomach flu?
I'm eight weeks in,
and it is not Buck's.
Believe me, he couldn't
get it up with a forklift
and a bottle of blues.
I want half for me and the baby.
Otherwise I make a claim,
and you get nothing.
I'm sorry, how's that?
The claim would be
for Stevens' child.
In a few weeks they can do
a DNA test to prove paternity,
at which point little Stevens
would be the beneficiary,
not you.
Check the policy.
Trust me, that's what it says,
and here's the kicker.
The policy pays us
even if you killed Ste.
And being the mother,
you would get
a generous living allowance.
You create a trust
to receive the insurance.
Once paternity's proved
that it's Stevens' child,
you and the baby
will split 50/50.
Is Tara in on this?
No, no,
she's your actual friend.
I just told her.
She's my insurance if
you attempted to kill me too.
Okay, I didn't kill Ste.
You will let me know
by tomorrow.
Otherwise I make my claim.
And, uh, thanks for the cookies.
They were delicious.
- I don't know, Brooke.
- Please, Tara?
For old time's sake?
Yeah, I don't want anything
big, just the three of us.
- Well, okay then.
- You're an angel.
Tomorrow at 5:00?
Bye.
Angie, it's me.
We have a deal.
Mr. Wong,
this is Brooke Stevens.
Jake, uh, you'll never guess
who's here to see you.
Judging by your excitement,
it wouldn't be Mrs. Stevens,
would it?
Oh, you're good.
Oh, and Wall's fingerprint
report will be here today.
Hi, Mrs. Stevens.
Can I get you something,
coffee, water?
You and the police have
searched my husband's office,
my house, watched my house,
had me followed.
Why?
It's all perfectly normal.
You're the beneficiary
and the spouse.
Statistically speaking,
you're doubly suspect.
You think I killed my husband?
Conjecture's for amateurs.
I simply explore
secondary explanations.
Now, I'm glad we're having
this talk, Mrs. Stevens.
I admire a forthright person.
Do you mind if I ask you
an equally direct question?
Sure. I mean,
you haven't answered mine,
but I'll go first.
How long after you're paid,
if you're paid,
do you intend to leave town?
Well, I... I don't
remember the word
for the smallest
possible increment of time.
The reason why I ask,
Wall's found evidence
of a possible accomplice.
As of now we've come
to no conclusions,
but if we do,
it could implicate you.
Yeah.
The resort has already
paid $1 million in negligence.
I'd appreciate if you could
expedite your payment also.
I'll see what I can do.
Have a good day.
Hey.
Thanks again for doing this.
What are we eating?
I'm starving.
Oh. I wasn't expecting you.
Surprise. I thought
we could celebrate.
Damn, I'd have
brought balloons.
Angie, you did me a favor.
You know, you took
Ste off my hands,
or to be more specific, my body.
My pleasure.
Well, I hope so
'cause it wasn't mine.
Look, as... as weird as this
may sound,
you two are kind of
my only friends here,
so I can hold a grudge,
or I can remember
the good times.
Is this for real?
I'll just give you
two a moment.
If she tries to kill you, shout.
Half a million,
cashier's check.
I can't void it.
We got the fingerprint
final report.
Looks like a match.
- Really?
- Yes.
Unfortunately, it's a partial.
It's the tip of a forefinger.
It would never
stand up in court.
- I guess it's a washout.
- Apparently.
Oh, by the way, Mrs. Stevens
settled her case
against the resort.
Really? How much?
A million in cash, tax-free.
What?
I know you, Jake,
since you were five.
I know your tells.
I see your tells.
Angie miscarried.
They found drugs in her system.
I know.
It's really easy
to get prescriptions
from Canada in the mail.
What? How could you?
Yeah, it's like... it's
like we don't even know
who the other is anymore.
You never thought to ask what
was in those cookies, did you?
You're one coldblooded bitch.
Well, that is a compliment
coming from you, Angie.
Don't feel too special though.
I'm, uh... I'm not the only
one that Ste played.
When he was with you,
he was screwing another man.
Wrong.
Ste wasn't smart enough
for all of this.
What are you saying?
It was me.
Stevens adored you,
so much he was actually willing
to kill himself
to leave you insurance money.
He wanted to save you
from his shame of bankruptcy,
but that would have been
a waste of good money,
so I convinced him
that you were
a philandering bitch,
and that broke his heart.
No, Jake said
this was his idea.
I'm sure he did.
I didn't figure
that shit would seduce
Ste and cut me out,
but obviously
he was willing to do anything.
Ste was weak and easy
to manipulate.
You bitch.
You did this.
You did... you did all of this.
For money.
You're no different than me.
You murdered the one man that
was willing to die for you.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't even know
she was pregnant.
Brooke?
Brooke!
Brooke, where are you?
911, what's your emergency?
Help, someone's broken
into my house.
I know you're there.
You got insurance money,
and you didn't split it?
I thought that
might bother you.
And if you don't split
that with me,
you can't even tell me about it?
That's why I told Wong.
That makes me insecure about
that life insurance payout.
I won't split the money.
You seem to have forgotten
something, Brooke.
Who killed him?
I can't remember.
- You did.
- Yes, of course I did.
- But I told you not to, right?
- Right.
- And you did it anyway.
- And that's my point.
If I hadn't have done that,
if I hadn't have done that,
you would have nothing
right now, just like me!
Is that what you want,
to shoot me?
Maybe.
Or maybe I'll wait.
The Earth is small, Brooke.
It is too small to hide.
One day you'll turn around,
and you will see
my smiling face.
I loved you, Jake.
God, I loved you so much.
Then why didn't you pay?
'Cause I was
doing it for love.
You can't love anyone.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about that.
Do you have kids?
Mm-hmm.
Do not leave this laying
around the house.
Mr. Walters planned
to blackmail your husband?
About the affair, yes.
Until he had a better idea.
To kill Ste and blackmail me.
We're not fools,
Mrs. Stevens.
That isn't exactly the
most credible scenario.
That's precisely
what Jake said,
and how he...
How he blackmailed me.
Who killed him?
I can't remember.
- You did.
- Yes, of course I did.
But I told you not to, right?
Right.
And you did it anyway.
And that's my point.
If I hadn't have done that,
you would have nothing
right now.
I couldn't risk anymore.
I had to shut it off.
So you knew he was
gonna kill your husband.
Of course not.
Yeah, but you knew afterwards,
and you didn't come forward,
and that makes you
an accessory after the fact.
Yes, but Jake was strategic.
He showed me a video,
which you will find
on his cell phone,
of him threatening to kill me
if I went to the police.
CSI just fished parts
of two pink cell phones
out of your disposal.
Want to explain that?
Not really.
This should take care
of your family for a while.
Oh, thank you, Ms. Brooke.
Mom, I've been thinking.
Those Vegas slots,
they really are something.
Well, pack your bags 'cause
we're going to Vegas tonight.
I love you.
Bye.
Hope you don't think
I'm incompetent.
Not at all.
Well, I'm impressed by...
In a horrified way...
By the way you've been able
to manage all this.
I, um, wired the money
into your account.
Here's your copy.
I like the personal touch.
Largest amount I've ever seen.
You may not believe it, Mr.
Wong, but I didn't want this.
All I wanted, all I ever wanted
was for my husband to love me,
But that wasn't to be
because that's not
the world we've made.
In this world
we're born alone, we live alone,
and we die in an even more
desperate state of loneliness.
Sometimes,
for brief moments, we have
the illusion of connection.
Grab onto it, cherish it.
You can judge me.
I know you do.
Growing up, were you hit
every day instead of kissed?
How about adolescence?
Girls stare at your crotch
the way boys leered
at my breasts?
Probably not.
See, I found out that
it doesn't matter
if you come from nothing
or you're born into luxury.
The secret,
the secret is to
always wear a big, wide smile
and hide your real self,
'cause if you don't,
if... if they see
who you really are,
they will destroy you.
So you give them what they want,
your body, hide the rest.
And then one day
you look around,
and where is it,
that poor little self
that you were protecting,
that troubled soul or
whatever you want to call it?
It's gone because, sir,
like our DNA, our souls
are in every cell of our body.
It's kind of a two-fer.
Sell your body, soul comes with.
Do you have any notion
of what I'm talking about?
No, you just want a confession.
That would be nice.
I didn't ask to play
their game,
but when I did,
I played it better, and I won.
So I confess
that whatever you think I did,
Probably did,
but if you want regret,
remorse,
it's gonna be
a little harder to come by.
Thanks for the money.