(grand orchestral fanfare
playing)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ ♪
- (wind whistling)
- (insects chittering)
(birds chirping)
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
(whooping)
We found gold, boys!
(wind howling)
(busy chatter)
(horse neighs)
(busy chatter continues)
- MAN: Lucky seven.
- (men laughing)
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh!
Oh, this is it. Uh-huh.
I have the number.
- I have the number.
- Yeah.
Who do you think is gonna get
a turn with her tonight, boys?
- Yeah, come on!
- Number one?
Never been number one before.
Number one!
(horse neighs)
Yeah, boys!
Winning number, I got 15!
- It's gonna win!
- (excited chatter continues)
- Fun tonight, boys.
- (men laughing)
- Hey. Give it back!
- No, no, no.
That's the winning ticket!
- (men laughing)
- Oh, Angel.
- Angel.
- My Angel!
Angel!
♪ ♪
(door opens, closes)
MAGOWAN (in distance):
All right, all right!
- (men whooping, cheering)
- Vagabonds,
show me your tickets!
(excited cheering)
One more charmed man,
then she's done shagging
for the day.
- (men groaning)
- She's all worn out!
(clamoring)
I have plenty of other girls!
Chinese, African, Spanish.
Dealer's choice.
But if you want Angel...
(cheering)
...you'll have to
come back tomorrow.
And by guess or by golly,
it could be your lucky day.
(clamoring continues)
MAN:
I have the lucky number!
Forty-one!
- Yeah! (laughing)
- (men groaning)
(clamoring)
Get off me!
(laughing)
♪ ♪
(girls laughing)
- (laughter echoes, fades)
- (birds chirping)
♪ ♪
Sarah!
I'm down here.
Child, your mama wants to know
if you got the flowers.
Is he here?
He'll be here soon.
You must hurry.
I'll pick more now.
MAE:
Thank you for getting these.
You know how much
I love flowers.
I do.
Now, blue is
his favorite color.
Remember to stand straight up
and act like a lady.
(horse neighs)
MAE:
Sarah?
(exhales slowly)
Isn't she beautiful, Alex?
Did you pick blue
on purpose, Mae?
Because it brings out
the color in her eyes?
- Cleo!
- She's not here.
I sent her to town.
Well, that leaves us in a fix.
Doesn't it?
- Papa...
- Don't call me that.
Uh, I-I wanted to thank you
for the gifts you send me.
- Hush, Sarah.
- What gifts?
Tell me.
I like the candies you send me.
The best of all
is the crystal swan.
Indeed.
I'm so pleased to know
how much my gifts mean.
MAE: Darling,
go outside and play now.
Find Cleo when she returns.
Can't I stay?
I want you to go outside
to play.
I want to talk
with your mother alone.
Can I come back
once you're done talking?
Your mother will come get you
when she's ready.
Now, run along.
As you've been told.
ALEX: I brought back that swan
from Europe for you,
and you throw it away
on a child.
She is your daughter.
I have enough children
by my wife.
Legitimate children.
MAE:
Do you know what it's like
for me to walk down the streets
in this town?
- I gave up everything for you.
- (crying softly)
ALEX: She should never
have existed, Mae.
I sent you to a doctor
to get rid of that mess!
You son of a bitch.
- (Alex grunts)
- (blow lands)
- (objects crash)
- ALEX: You ungrateful bitch!
- (slap)
- (objects clatter)
MAE:
Where have you been, darling?
I've been looking
all over for you.
Is he coming back?
Maybe not for a long time.
Maybe not ever.
I don't want him to.
We'll have to wait and see.
You father is a very busy
and important man.
What if I got sick and died?
You're not gonna
get sick and die.
You're far too young
and healthy for that.
But, Mama...
...if I did, would he come back
and stay with you?
No.
Don't you ever ask
that question ever again.
- Do you understand?
- But...
Never again.
None of this has anything
to do with you.
I love you more than
anything or anyone
(echoes):
in this whole wide world.
LUCKY:
Angel?
Angel!
(people laughing, chattering)
It's break time.
LUCKY: My mother ran off
when I was five.
And my aunt took me in.
Auntie Priscilla.
She used a switch on me
at least twice a day. Look.
- The bitch with a switch.
- (Lucky chuckles)
She was the meanest woman
I ever knew...
meaner than the Duchess.
She would make me cut
a fresh switch
from the tree in the front yard
every day.
So, one day,
she was out having tea
with her phony friends.
So I took an ax,
and I chopped the tree down.
It went through the house,
crushing her fancy-ass parlor.
(laughter)
Yeah.
God, I just wish
I had've stuck around
to see the look on Priss's face
when she got home.
And sometimes I wish
that I could go back
and say that I'm sorry.
Maybe my life
might've been different.
How so?
Well, might not
have ended up here,
you know...
...just being a mattress hole
for whoremongers.
Just collecting gold dust
that isn't mine.
My father sold me
for three ounces of gold.
And he told me that I was
going to stay in a palace.
I thought he meant
a royal palace.
Like a princess.
(laughter)
It's bad.
- MAI LING: Angel.
- Hmm?
You got any big plans?
- ANGEL: Plans?
- Yeah.
LUCKY:
You got to have plans, Angel.
You got to hope for something
more in this world
outside of this... paradise.
Hope for what?
You can't get by without hope.
I get by.
How?
Never look back,
never look forward.
("The Stable Song" by
Gregory Alan Isakov playing)
(dog panting)
- (sheep bleating)
- MICHAEL: Come on.
- ♪ Remember when our songs were ♪
- Come on.
- ♪ Just like prayer? ♪
- (dog barks) - Come on.
- ♪ Like gospel hymns ♪
- Come on.
♪ That you called in the air ♪
- ♪ Come down, come down ♪
♪ Sweet reverence ♪
♪ Unto my simple house
and ring ♪
♪ And ring ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Ring like silver,
ring like gold ♪
♪ Turn these diamonds
straight back into coal. ♪
- (vocalizing)
- Come on, boy.
Great job.
Come on.
(song ends)
(hawk screeching in distance)
MICHAEL:
Lord,
thank you for blessing the land
that you have given me.
May I always know,
as I tend to each crop
and creature,
you're the one
that helps them grow.
Grant me strength and wisdom.
Please protect the farm
from harm.
And thank you, Lord.
Amen.
Lord, I was, uh...
I was hoping that...
maybe you might give me a...
(chuckles)
I mean, provide me...
...with someone
I can share this with.
Some guidance.
A sign.
Anything. (chuckles)
Maybe she likes fishing.
(chuckles)
You know,
maybe she has long legs.
Anyway, you...
you know the kind I need.
I trust you.
(door creaks)
♪ ♪
(hawk screeches in distance)
(wind howling)
(dog whines)
What?
Walk on.
- (excited chatter)
- MAN: There she is.
- Ma'am.
- (whoops)
Ma'am.
(whoops) Look at that!
Hey, back up.
Stand back.
(excited chatter continues)
(chuckles)
She's something to see,
ain't she?
Who is she?
JOSEPH:
That's Angel.
Finest girl
west of the Rockies.
Every Monday and Friday
afternoon,
she takes walks.
They all come out to watch her.
I can see why
her husband is armed.
Oh, that ain't her husband.
Bodyguard.
No one gets within
a foot of her for free.
I have to meet her.
You'll have to get in line.
The Duchess holds
a daily lottery
to see who gets to spend
quality time with her.
MICHAEL:
A duchess?
She owns the brothel up there.
Palace.
Hey, what,
sh-she's a prostitute?
Uh-huh.
Lord, you most certainly have
a sense of humor.
That's the girl?
What's that?
Uh-uh-uh, nothing.
- Been on that farm too long.
- Yeah, let's settle up.
Come on. Take it in the back.
♪ ♪
(busy chatter)
Whoa.
♪ ♪
CLEO:
I'm gonna tell you God's truth.
(Sarah grunts)
All men want to do is use you.
- (gasping)
- Your papa only
cared about
what your mama gave him.
(crying)
And she gave him
everything she had.
(Mae gasping)
And now he kicks her out
and cuts her off.
When you give them your heart,
they tear it to shreds.
(register bell dings)
None of them care.
RAB: These stones are
green glass, not emeralds.
You got anything else?
No.
(sighs)
CLEO:
Nobody cares about anybody
in this world.
RAB:
There is another way.
(gasps)
Just you and, uh...
five easy dollars.
(gasps softly)
(seagulls squawking)
- (waves sloshing)
- (bell clanging)
(thunder rumbling softly)
(sniffles)
(coughing)
Let's hop on one of those ships
and sail away.
(Mae chuckles)
Where would we go?
Far...
far away from here.
MAE:
Mm.
Far away.
That sounds nice.
RAB:
Mae!
You got company.
(sighs)
Why don't you think about
where we would go, hmm?
(thunder rumbling softly)
RAB: Come on, now.
We don't have all day.
(clears throat, coughs)
(coughing)
(shivering)
(murmurs)
(coughing, wheezing)
(sniffles)
(breath shuddering)
MAE: Say my... my prayers
with me, baby.
BOTH:
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
(Mae stops):
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done
on Earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day
our daily bread...
(exhales slowly)
...and...
Mama.
(sobbing):
Mama, wake up, please.
Wake up.
(seagulls squawking)
♪ ♪
(panting)
CLEO:
That is God's truth.
Best you know that now, child.
(pounding on door)
MAN:
I paid! Let me in!
(chuckles):
Go to hell.
(lively chatter)
Come on! Angel!
Go to hell!
(keys jangling)
(lock clicking)
I said go away.
(sniffles)
Fill the tub.
(indistinct chatter)
(water splashing)
- You hiding something from me?
- (objects clattering)
Huh?
Think you're so special?
(door closes)
Better than me
and everyone else around here?
(Magowan breathes deeply)
(gasps)
(panting softly)
I know you're hiding something.
Duchess said
I'm off-limits to you.
You pig.
- (grunts) Let's go!
- (screams)
Put me down!
Put me down! Duchess!
- (grunting)
- (gurgling)
No, no, uh-uh-uh.
Stay down! Huh?
(coughing, gasping)
- Enough?
- (gasping): Enough.
Huh?
- Come on, fight me! Come on!
- (gasps)
(grunts, coughs)
You have no idea how much pain
I'm gonna wreak on you.
- Do it. Do it!
- DUCHESS: Stop!
She needs to be
taught a lesson.
(gasping)
I heard her screams
from the hall.
Men knew what you were
doing to her, they'd hang you.
(chuckles softly)
I have extra rope
if they're short.
Not another word.
Sober her up and talk to her.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
DUCHESS: Coffee and bread
are on their way up.
Make sure she takes it in.
I need her ready to work
in two hours.
Not a mark on her.
Not a mark.
(sniffles)
(knock on door)
ANGEL:
It's open.
(door closes)
What's your pleasure, mister?
(clears throat)
Doesn't matter in here
if you're married.
Doesn't matter if your...
(chuckles)
Christian mama doesn't approve.
There's no guilt in here, okay?
Just pleasure. So don't be shy.
Tell me what you want.
You.
I'm all yours.
(Angel sighs)
Why don't you come over here
and I'll wash you.
(chuckles)
I'm not gonna hurt you,
I promise.
(Michael stammers)
That won't be necessary, ma'am.
"Ma'am"?
Do I look like your mama?
No, ma'am. (chuckles)
No.
You do not.
The truth is, I...
I didn't come here for... that.
ANGEL:
Yeah?
MICHAEL: I just came here
to talk to you.
You want to talk?
There's a nice barkeep
named Murphy downstairs.
He'll talk your ear off.
(chuckles)
(clears throat)
Y-You-you... you live
in this room?
No.
My little white house
surrounded by roses
on top of the hill
is where I prefer to stay.
I shouldn't have come this way.
(chuckles)
(chuckles):
What other way is there?
Uh, I ain't sure.
How old are you?
I'm real old. How old are you?
T-Twenty-six.
Ancient for a gold miner.
Oh, s... no, no, see.
I-I ain't a miner.
I-I work on a farm.
Angel your real name?
(chuckles)
You can call me
whatever you want.
Well, my name is...
I don't want to know your name.
Michael Hosea.
(sighs)
Are you afraid of
what your wife might think
if you have your way with me?
Wife. (chuckles)
No, see, 'cause, uh...
(clears throat)
I'm not married.
(sighs)
But I will be soon.
Then come over here and get
your last taste of freedom
while you can.
Oh, no, I can't, you see,
'cause I'm...
- gonna marry you.
- Mm.
You're gonna marry me?
Take me away from here,
give me the life I deserve?
Mm-hmm.
You're my fifth proposal
this week.
How about we do what's on
your mind and we call it a day?
I'm gonna give you a good life.
Come on. Come away with me.
(indistinct chatter, laughter)
Time's up.
Come on.
(chuckles)
I'm coming back.
All-all I ask for is-is-is
one honest half hour.
Five minutes with me,
you'd run like the devil.
Angel, Angel...
(sighs)
(women giggling)
- (crickets chirping)
- (indistinct chatter)
Next time I pray to God
for a woman to share my life,
I'm gonna be
a lot more specific.
ANGEL:
So you won
- the lottery again?
- (Michael chuckles)
I paid double again.
(Angel laughs)
Lucky me.
I do hate to see you just waste
your time and gold dust
just... just chatting.
Do you want to stay here
for the rest of your life?
I don't think that's really
any of your business.
It was my business the minute
I saw you on the street.
Yeah, love at first sight,
right?
Right.
(yawns)
Oh, sorry. What, am I
putting you to sleep now?
All this talking is exhausting
to be honest.
So you'd rather
I join you on the bed?
At least you would've
left having gotten something
- for your gold dust.
- (chuckles softly)
Let me get you
out of this place.
I'm serious.
Marry me.
(pounding on door)
MAGOWAN:
Time's up.
Get your boots on. It's...
- (indistinct chatter)
- (piano playing)
It's time for you to go.
Nice talking to you.
(indistinct chatter)
She said no, again.
- JOSEPH: Shocking.
- (chuckles)
MICHAEL:
I don't know.
Got enough gold dust
for one more try.
JOSEPH:
Maybe you need a new plan.
- (Michael laughs)
- Buy some cattle.
It might've been cheaper.
Go home, Michael.
Work your farm.
Ain't no woman worth
that amount of gold.
Mm.
REBECCA: Angel, who's the man
you were with last night?
Which one?
The good-looking one.
- All look the same to me.
- (chuckles)
Six feet, dark hair, blue eyes.
- (chuckles softly)
- When he smiled at me,
I could feel it
all the way down to my toes.
LUCKY: A pot-marked midget from
Nantucket could smile at you,
and you'd feel it
all the way down to your toes.
Drink your brandy, Lucky.
- No one was talking to you.
- (laughs softly)
I've had one untried boy
after another.
I would like to give
a real man a go.
RENEE: Duchess said
one glass per girl.
Milk's expensive.
So, you really don't care
about him, Angel?
You can have him.
You'd be doing me a huge favor.
- (lively chatter, laughter)
- (piano playing)
- Hey.
- (chuckles)
(clears throat)
Don't bother with Angel
tonight, sugar.
She wanted me to tell you that
you'd like me a lot better.
(chuckles)
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
What else did Angel say?
That I'd be doing her
a huge favor
to take the farmer boy
off her hands.
She said that?
Yes.
Never been with a woman
like me before.
And as far as I can tell, I
never been with a man like you.
(scoffs softly)
(sighs)
(knock on door)
(Angel groans)
You again.
Your, um, your friend
just met me downstairs.
Told me you asked her
to take me off your hands.
(chuckles) I told you
you'd be wasting your time
and gold dust on me.
(chuckles)
Don't worry about me.
I'm leaving town.
Headed back to the valley.
Back to the farm.
(scoffs) Well, go ahead.
I'm not stopping you.
Do you like the view here?
Slapped-up shacks?
Drunk boys fighting in the mud?
Men paying money
to put their names into a hat
so they get the chance
to have sex with you?
- I didn't ask you to care.
- No, you didn't.
No, 'cause you don't
ask anything, do you?
need anything. (chuckles)
Or maybe-maybe it's just
'cause you don't feel anything.
That it?
Wh-Why don't I just go
to your friend's room, hmm?
- Maybe she'll feel something.
- That's a great idea.
No, it is. She costs less, too.
You might as well leave
with a smile on your face.
Oh, you want to see me smile?
- Just say my name.
- What is your name?
Hmm?
'Cause I don't remember.
♪ ♪
(whispers):
It's Michael.
Well, it's about time.
No, stop.
Hey, hey, stop.
Hey, stop. Stop.
We can't, we can't do this yet.
- What do you mean "yet"?
- Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
We should wait till
it means something to you.
You're a damn fool.
I feel nothing for you.
Absolutely nothing.
You're a dirt farmer.
Yes, I am.
(door opens)
(door closes)
♪ ♪
RAB:
Ain't Boston a grand city?
Told your mother
I would take good care of you.
(busy chatter)
Come on.
(indistinct chatter, laughter)
Upstairs.
Second door on the right.
My name is Sally.
What's yours, honey?
Oh, she's shy.
Don't mind her.
Take her home, please.
Just get her out of here.
RAB:
Her mama's dead.
She'll be better off here
- in this fancy place with...
- No.
No, she won't.
♪ ♪
(sniffs)
Oh, yeah.
(exhales sharply)
(smacks lips)
Oh, my. That's fine.
(door opens)
♪ ♪
(clock ticking)
Are you enjoying my brandy?
RAB: Well, it's the best
I've ever tasted.
She's all yours.
As soon as you pay me.
What's her name?
You can call her
whatever you want.
Take care of him.
(gasps)
- Come here.
- (grunting)
No, no. Don't move. Don't move.
(choking)
Don't move.
Don't make a sound.
Look.
(gasps softly)
- (choking)
- (straining)
(exhales slowly)
(gasps)
(breath shuddering)
(glass clinks)
(drink pours)
You'll drink
when I pour you a drink.
(grunts)
(sobs softly)
Go through the pockets before
you dump the body, Colin.
There might be something
in there for you.
(breath shuddering)
(sighs softly)
Come here.
(shudders)
Don't make me ask you again.
You have the look
of intelligence about you.
What's your name?
Never mind.
You'll be my little Angel
from now on.
And as long as you do
exactly what I tell you,
we'll get along.
YOUNG ANGEL:
"'He may live in my memory
"'as the most amiable man
of my acquaintance,
"'but that is all.
"'I have nothing
either to hope or to fear
"'and nothing
to reproach him with.
"'Thank God.
I have not that pain.
"'A little time, therefore...
"I shall certainly try
to get the better.'
"With a stronger voice,
she soon added,
"'I have this comfort...
imm-me...'"
"Immediately."
"Immediately"?
"'I have this comfort
immediately
"'that has not been more than
an error of fancy on my side...
"'...and that
it has done no harm
to anyone but myself.'"
(indistinct chatter)
"'Do not give way
to such feelings as these.
YOUNG ANGEL and ANGEL: "'They
will ruin your happiness.
ANGEL: "'It's very often
nothing but our own vanity
that deceives us.'"
♪ ♪
Alex.
This is Angel.
You are stunning.
(chuckles softly)
Have we ever met before?
Could be.
You look like...
someone I used to know.
(crying softly)
(gunshot echoes)
COLIN: Alex Stafford
blew his brains out last night
when he found out he had sex
with his own daughter.
Don't look back.
Go.
COLIN:
Now Angel's gone.
- (ship bell clanging)
- (dogs barking in distance)
She was last seen
heading for the docks,
and Captain Sorenson's ship
left harbor yesterday.
DUKE: And who helped her
get out of the house?
Sally.
Well, before you kill her,
bring her to me.
(horse sputters)
- (indistinct chatter)
- (seagulls squawking)
♪ ♪
We could make a heap
on this voyage to California.
Look at them all.
ALICE:
We might as well sell it.
Better than having them
take it for free.
I have a guy
who can handle our money.
His cut is ten percent.
You okay with that?
I don't think I have a choice.
- (ship creaking and rumbling)
- (waves sloshing)
(indistinct chatter)
(men coughing)
(seagulls squawking)
♪ ♪
(laughter)
(indistinct chatter)
ALICE:
Put her down!
(groans, coughs)
Found it.
Let's go.
Hurry.
(seagulls squawking)
Here. You need a drink.
No.
You sure you're not sick?
I was just thinking
about my mother.
What was she like?
Beautiful.
Shattered.
You're clammy.
I have a headache.
How long's it been aching?
(sighs)
Ever since that...
- farmer started badgering me.
- (chuckles)
And you're sorry
you didn't go with him?
(whispers):
No.
No. No man is gonna own me.
(sighs) Yeah.
The Duchess wouldn't have
let you go anyway.
(scoffs)
She can't keep me here.
(scoffs) Like hell she can't.
No, we have a deal.
She holds my money, and then
when I'm ready, I walk.
The only girls
who leave here are too old,
too sick to work or dead.
(knock on door)
DUCHESS:
Who's there?
Angel.
Come in. (sniffles)
You look dreadful.
Something troubling you?
You've been
working me too hard.
(scoffs) Nonsense.
Sit down, darling.
I heard you missed breakfast.
Would you like something?
I want my gold.
(chuckles)
And why do you want it?
- Because it belongs to me.
- Mm.
Pour yourself some coffee.
I don't want coffee.
I want my gold.
(sniffles)
Tell me,
why do you want your gold?
I would like to leave,
get my own place.
DUCHESS:
Mm.
Getting ambitious, are you?
Trying to compete against me.
(chuckles):
No.
Be a hundred miles
from this place.
You don't have to worry
about me.
I just would like
to be left alone.
I take good care of you,
don't I?
Huh?
You'd be one woman
fighting off a hundred men.
How long would you last?
Maybe I'll get...
- married or something.
- (laughs)
(laughing):
You fancy doing laundry
and cooking for a man
and giving him sex whenever
and however he wants for free?
You know how to make a man
happy for 30 minutes.
That's all you're good at.
I want my gold, Duchess.
You are forgetting
what I do for you.
Everything costs money.
You wear silk in a mining town.
I provide protection for you.
I feed you.
You live in a nice building.
Is my name on the deed?
- What did you say?
- You have coffee
with cream and sugar,
pastry from
that baker down the street
and three eggs
and a steak on your...
...your fine china.
I had oatmeal for breakfast
with two glasses of milk,
rationed.
How many men...
...did I have to have sex with
so you could have this?
You stuff yourself like a pig
and you dress up like royalty!
A duchess?
A duchess of what?!
Men don't even pay
to have sex with you anymore.
You have to pay Magowan
to have sex with you.
(Angel gasping)
You forget where
I found you, missy.
In an alley, covered with mud,
broke and beaten bloody.
I made you a princess.
I can take it all away.
I'm sorry. (gasps)
(panting)
(Angel crying)
You're ungrateful.
ANGEL:
I don't know what I'm saying.
I can't do this anymore.
I have to get out of here.
That teacup came around
the Horn from England.
I'll add the cost of it
to your debt.
My debt?
Magowan will take you
to your room
so you can discuss further
those thoughts you have
banging around that
pretty little head of yours.
You will be as obedient
- as a street dog when I'm done with you!
- (pained groaning)
You have no idea
how much I am gonna enjoy this.
(laughing)
(sighs)
(laughing continues)
What's so funny?
You.
(laughing)
(laughing):
You're just...
You're just one of
Duchess's lapdogs.
She rings a bell
and you just come running.
- (sighs)
- And she owns you, too.
You're no different than
all of us.
You're just one of Duchess's...
girls.
- Hmm.
- (laughing)
I'm gonna kill you.
Do it. Do it!
- (Angel laughing)
- (blows landing)
(coughs, grunts)
- (Angel sobbing, grunting)
- (blows landing)
(gasps)
(panting)
- (horse neighs)
- (busy chatter)
♪ ♪
(lively chatter)
DUCHESS:
Murphy, get him a drink.
- On the house.
- Yes, ma'am.
No one goes up the stairs
without paying me first.
♪ ♪
Who did this to her?
Magowan. I made him leave.
(Michael scoffs)
Don't look at me like that.
It's her fault.
She pushed him too far.
(groaning)
I'm taking her with me.
She's not leaving
until she pays me
every penny she owes me.
Okay, well...
well, then...
Fine.
(exhales softly)
Good luck with her.
♪ ♪
(Angel sighs)
(sighs softly)
Listen, I...
I-I know the timing
ain't perfect.
(chuckles softly)
But, uh...
Will you marry me?
(whispers):
Sure.
(chuckles softly)
(Mai Ling laughs)
- We'll get the preacher.
- Yeah.
He's down the street.
(laughing)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
(rooster crows in distance)
(fire crackling)
(pants softly)
- (door opens)
- (Michael sighs)
Good morning.
(Angel sighs)
Looks like you...
...got me after all.
- (chuckles softly)
- Lucky you.
Whatever Duchess had you pay,
you got cheated.
Well, you're beautiful, but
that's not why I married you.
I'm gonna work off my debt,
and then I'm going back
to get what's mine.
(grunts, inhales sharply)
Oh, uh...
you can wear these.
For now.
Where's the wife
that goes with this dress?
Hope she isn't buried
under the house.
Oh, those belonged
to my sister Tess.
She, uh...
She-she-she died last year.
Her husband Paul, we, uh...
...we all came west together.
How far away is Pair-A-Dice?
A lifetime. (chuckles)
In miles.
About, uh, 20.
20 miles.
(sighs)
Well, I hope you don't mind
waiting a few days to...
exercise your conjugal rights.
Listen, uh, that...
that's not why
I brought you here.
Mm-hmm.
Well, you can take this back.
Marriage is over. (sighs)
Where did you get
a ring so fast?
It, uh... (clears throat)
...belonged to my mother.
Y-You gave me
your mother's ring?
Yeah.
(grunts)
Okay.
- Whoa, hey. Oh.
- (groans)
You know, shouldn't be
up for longer than
a few minutes at a time.
- Now, what hurts most?
- Nothing I want you touching.
(grunts softly)
I'm not staying here for long.
I'm not playing into your
little marriage slave fantasy.
Marriage is not slavery.
(thunder rumbling softly)
(horse neighs)
(rooster crows in distance)
(horse nickers)
(hoofbeats galloping)
♪ ♪
(breathes sharply)
Bad, bad dog.
Go home. Shoo.
Get!
(whines)
Go home! Go!
(whimpers)
Go home.
Go get the stick.
- Go on.
- (barks)
♪ ♪
Ha!
(panting)
(whispers):
Ow.
(grunting)
Leave me alone!
I'm going back.
You don't own me!
You'll need water.
It gets cold at night.
That way is Pair-A-Dice.
19 more miles.
Duchess and Magowan waiting
for you at the end of the road.
That way... is home.
One mile downhill.
Fire, food...
...and your husband.
Your choice.
(sighs)
Ha!
- (fire crackling)
- (crickets chirping)
(door opens)
(grunts)
(sniffles)
(coughs softly)
(dishes clinking)
(liquid pours)
(pot clanking softly)
♪ ♪
(grunts softly)
Why are you doing this?
One mile can be harder to walk
than 20.
♪ ♪
Can you help me?
(birds chirping)
I think it's time
to pay you back.
- Pl-Please don't.
- Hmm?
(breathes deeply)
Can I ask you something?
Yeah. I, uh...
Does your God
talk to you a lot?
He talks to everyone. I mean...
My mama prayed.
She prayed,
but God never heard her.
'Cause he doesn't care.
So if you're telling me
that your God said marry me,
you know he's punishing you.
'Cause that's what he does.
Grinds people into dust.
- (birds chirping)
- (sheep bleating)
Go on. Go on.
(birds chirping)
(Angel clears throat)
Listen, um,
this whole wife thing
isn't for me,
but I will play along
until I pay you back
what I owe you.
MICHAEL:
Hmm.
Well, we'll have to get
your strength back.
Then we'll have you
out plowing the fields.
(laughing)
("Love Is a Wild Thing"
by Kacey Musgraves playing)
- You like eggs?
- (chickens clucking)
Mm-hmm.
Well, these ones belong to us.
Go ahead, eat all you want.
- Go on.
- I...
- You...
(clucking)
ANGEL:
Hey.
Hey, Mr. Chicken.
- (squawks)
- Oh!
- (laughing)
- (chuckles)
I'll teach you how to cook
roasted chicken, too.
(both laughing)
MICHAEL:
Uh, no, no.
Right here.
♪ But they'll try to... ♪
- Like that?
- Just like that.
♪ Trying to find the ocean... ♪
(Michael grunting)
Weeding is constant.
We're getting rid of the bad
and keeping the good.
Mm, so subtle.
Talk, talk, talk.
♪ Coming through the melody
when the night bird... ♪
(whooping)
(hushed):
Not too fast.
(Angel whooping)
- (line snaps)
- ♪ Love is a wild thing ♪
(chuckles)
(laughing)
♪ Oh, I can feel it ♪
- ♪ Magic in your... ♪
- (Michael clears throat)
All right, give me the axe.
I-I don't think
that's a good id...
Give me the ax.
Okay. (clears throat)
- Wait. O-O-Okay, now. Steady yourself.
- Shh.
Sorry.
♪ So don't try to... ♪
Oh. Whoa. (laughing)
- Come on.
- No, the wood is just too stiff.
- Come on, I'll help you. Oh, the wood?
- (laughing)
That's the problem?
- Come on, I'll help you up.
- (both laughing)
- Look, it's still stuck.
- That's true, that's true.
Come on.
(both sigh)
♪ Places that you can't see ♪
Come on.
There's room for two.
(sighs)
I'm fine right here.
I owe you.
Come on.
We're not ready.
(chuckles)
I don't understand you.
I don't understand you either.
(laughs)
Uh, uh, I think, uh,
I think Maverick needs a walk.
(grunts) Uh, Maverick?
- Come on.
- (Maverick groans)
(gasps)
(whimpers)
What are you looking at?
- ♪ Love is a wild thing. ♪
- (Maverick barks)
(song ends)
- (horse neighs)
- (Michael sighs heavily)
I'm gonna go saddle the horse
in the barn.
Okay.
- (inhales deeply)
- (Maverick barking)
(sighs)
(crickets chirping)
(door creaks)
(night bird calling)
♪ ♪
Did you think
I couldn't find you?
(gasping)
- You belong to me, Angel.
- No! No!
No!
Angel, Angel! It's me.
It's fine.
It's me, okay? It's me.
It's just... just a nightmare.
(Angel panting)
You want to talk about it?
No, I don't, I don't remember.
(sniffles)
Your heart's beating so fast,
it's gonna come out your...
Don't... touch me, please.
Okay, come on.
Get your boots on.
We are going for a walk.
It is the middle of the night.
I'm not going anywhere
with you.
Well, you're going
whether you want to or not.
Now, you can go like that...
or dressed.
It's your choice.
But you're going.
(laughs)
Come on, Angel.
What are you so afraid of?
Nothing.
Michael, where are you
taking me?
You'll see.
This is ridiculous.
I want to go back.
We're almost there. Come on.
(sighs)
- Trust me.
- (grunts softly)
♪ ♪
MICHAEL:
We're here.
(birds chirping)
(whispers):
Look.
♪ ♪
(chuckles softly)
That's the life
I want to offer you, Angel.
One full of color and warmth
and beauty and light.
(whispers):
Just give me a chance.
If you knew half of what I did,
you'd send me right back.
Uh, listen, you did not choose
the life you had.
Okay? But you can choose
the life you want.
I chose to die.
(sighs) Well, you...
do you still want to?
No.
- No, but...
- But?
I don't know why I'm here.
Why...
You say that I'm your wife,
but you won't even...
And it's... I don't blame you.
- I don't. I-I...
- (sighs)
I've just been waiting.
♪ ♪
(Angel gasping)
(both panting)
♪ ♪
(Angel gasping)
(both moan)
(moans):
Oh, Michael.
(panting)
♪ ♪
(echoing exhale)
(wind whistling)
(birds chirping)
- (man groaning)
- (objects clinking)
(crows cawing)
(panting)
♪ ♪
(sobbing softly)
(crying)
Michael.
(chuckles):
Paul.
- It's so good to see you.
- Good to see you, too.
- (laughing)
- I-I've missed you.
I miss, I miss you, too.
- Look at you.
- (both chuckle)
Yeah, yeah. (chuckles)
Yeah. (sniffles)
So, uh, so how was it
out there?
Uh, it-it was awful.
Yeah. (laughs)
(sniffles) Yeah, it was
a lot of hard work, uh,
finding nothing and, uh...
...you know,
drinking to forget. (laughs)
No gold, then, or...?
No, no, no. No.
Not enough to buy a pot
to piss in at least, you know.
Just... (sniffles)
fighting for survival
out there, mostly.
(chuckles, sniffles)
What about you?
- Uh...
- You look, uh...
Well, you always look content.
I got married.
You're married?
That's right.
Yeah. (chuckles)
Well, uh,
congr-gratulations, Michael.
(laughs) Thank you. Thank you.
Well, am I gonna meet her?
You... What's she like?
Wh-Where is she?
Angel?
(Michael clears throat)
This is, uh...
This is Paul.
Paul, meet my wife, Angel.
- Hello.
- ANGEL: Hello.
PAUL:
Um, uh...
I'm sorry to gape
at you, ma'am.
Those are, um...
Those are T-Tess's clothes,
uh, the ones she made?
- MICHAEL: Uh, yeah, uh...
- PAUL: Mm-hmm.
- Angel needed clothes. I...
- Mm-hmm.
I thought Tess
would approve, so...
Hmm.
Well, you must be hungry.
MICHAEL:
Three weeks on that trail?
- PAUL: Mm. Mm.
- My God.
That was just on foot.
(chuckles)
Yeah, it was about seven total.
MICHAEL:
Brutal.
Come on outside.
I'll show you what I did
to the barn since you left
- to make your fortune.
- All right.
Mm. I'm-a get a refill.
- (door opens)
- MICHAEL: Sure.
PAUL:
I'll be right there.
Okay.
So Michael doesn't know
what you are, does he?
- Should I remember you?
- Mm.
Well, I suppose all faces
start to look alike,
someone in your business, huh?
Yeah, and everything else, too.
(sniffles)
Yeah, seeing you
in my wife's clothes
makes me sick to my stomach.
- I'd like to rip 'em off you.
- (chuckles): I bet you would.
Michael is the best man
that I know,
and he deserves
a decent girl, not...
...you.
(clicks tongue)
Wh-What'd you do to get
your claws into him, huh?
Well, Michael came to the
Palace, he paid for my time,
- and then he begged me to marry him.
- (silverware drops)
That's a lie.
I know Michael, and
Michael would never step foot
inside of a whorehouse.
Well, the whore is here now.
So I guess you're just
gonna have to deal with that.
(Angel sighs)
(Paul sniffles)
Oh, no, I don't.
(Maverick barking in distance)
(hammering)
MICHAEL:
Look at the new hayloft.
(hammering continues)
Yeah.
Come on, give me a hand
with this. (grunts)
- (rooster crows in distance)
- (chickens clucking)
(Michael sighs)
I-I-I need to talk to you
about something, Michael.
It's about Angel.
Sh-She's not
who you think she is.
(chuckles)
She's exactly
who I think she is.
She's my wife.
Michael, before
she was your wife...
...she was the highest priced
whore in Pair-A-Dice.
I know all about that.
Y-You know?
- Yes.
- Michael, listen to me.
She has been with
thousands of men.
She just does not love you.
She is using you.
You have no idea who she is.
Well, maybe you should
look at your own life
- instead of judging hers.
- Well, what do you think
your mother'd say about
marrying a piece of trash
- like that?
- Yeah. "Trash."
If you love me like a brother,
then you will love her as well.
Understand?
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
(sighs)
Uh...
I mean, Tess was my sister.
Okay? You're not, you're not
the only one suffering.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
I'm sorry. Come on.
Come on.
(grunts)
(Paul sighs, sniffles)
You need supplies.
Okay, go to Pair-A-Dice.
Uh, I'll give you enough money
to get what you need.
You can, you can borrow
Shadrach and the wagon.
And buy another horse
while you're there.
(Paul grunts softly)
Listen, the town
has a preacher.
Go to church.
Try to remember
the man you were...
...when you married my sister.
(horse nickers)
MICHAEL:
Paul needs to sort things out.
He's coming over tomorrow
for the horse and wagon
to go into town.
He was mad because
I didn't remember him.
The truth is I don't know.
(chuckles softly)
Every man looks the same
without clothes on.
You're not that person anymore.
I'll always be that person.
(Michael sighs)
I don't care what you've done.
See, I...
I just want
to build a life with you.
I want to have children
with you.
(chuckles softly)
- Michael...
- A new beginning. Hmm?
(whispers):
A family.
- (chuckles)
- (match strikes)
♪ ♪
(dishes clinking)
I taught you how to be careful,
so this wouldn't happen.
Dr. Smith's gonna
take care of the problem.
So it never happens again.
(screaming)
- No!
- (yells)
No! No! Please don't take...
Please don't take...
Please, my baby!
My baby! No!
- (man grunting)
- (Angel gasping)
I told you what would happen
if you disobeyed me.
(gasping) Please.
(sobbing):
Please!
(echoing scream)
♪ ♪
Wait! Wait.
- Wait, wait. - Whoa.
- (Shadrach neighs)
What do you want?
I want a ride.
(laughing)
Yeah, 'cause you're running
off on him, aren't you?
Oh, you want me to stay?
Well, come on.
Gonna take us all day
to get to town.
- (birds chirping)
- (insects chittering)
(crows cawing)
You, uh... you want a drink?
- Yeah.
- Hold on, now.
(sniffles)
You got to say "please"
if you want one.
Please.
(Paul sniffles)
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
(sighs heavily)
(sniffles)
Tell me something.
How'd you really meet Michael?
Hmm?
- I already told you how all of this came about.
- Liar.
Michael didn't go into
any brothel.
There's no need to be jealous.
Now that I'm gone, you can have
Michael all to yourself.
(sighs)
You owe me for the ride.
(sniffles)
What exactly
did you have in mind?
You know, I never did make it
upstairs to the Palace.
But I have always wondered
what it might be like
to make it inside Angel's...
...inner sanctum.
And now you want to know.
Mm-hmm.
Maybe I do.
♪ ♪
Well...
might as well do it now
or we'd...
...never get there before dark.
What'd you have in mind?
Whatever you want, mister.
Long as I can get a ride.
Or was that all a bluff?
♪ ♪
(sniffles)
(Shadrach sputtering)
(Angel coughing)
(coughing continues)
(sniffles)
(retches)
(spits, sniffles)
(spits)
(sobbing softly)
(panting)
PAUL:
Let's go!
Come on.
♪ ♪
Whoa. Whoa.
Go on. Get down.
I don't want
to be seen with you.
You know, I never pretended
to be anything but what I am.
But you?
You took Michael's money,
you took his...
his wagon...
his horse,
and then you took his wife.
Call yourself his brother.
- (brake clicks)
- Walk on.
♪ ♪
(busy chatter)
MURPHY:
It burned down, Angel.
When?
About five weeks back.
Last real excitement
we've had in this town.
(panting softly)
It's good to see you, Angel.
Assuming that marriage thing
didn't work out.
Where's Duchess?
I came back
to get what she owes me.
She didn't even have
a thimble to spit in.
Magowan burned the whole thing
down around her.
We caught up with him,
hung him.
Two of the girls died
in the fire.
Which ones?
Mai Ling.
Little Chinese flower.
I liked her.
And the other?
Loudmouth drunk.
What was her name?
- (voice breaks): Lucky.
- Yeah, that's her.
They were trapped upstairs.
Screaming.
Awful way to die.
Come see my place.
- Whiskey's fine.
- (sniffles)
(indistinct chatter)
Got a spare room upstairs.
You could be back in business
in five minutes.
Just say the word.
All we got to do
is figure out the cut.
What do you say, Angel?
(Angel clicks tongue, sighs)
Fifty-fifty.
They pay me, I pay you.
Mm. Fair enough.
(Murphy sighs)
Providing you give me
what I want whenever I want it,
and it's free.
(laughter, lively chatter)
♪ ♪
(horses sputtering)
Hey, whoa. Whoa there.
I stopped by my place,
you know,
un-unload the supplies
is why it took me so long.
You took her back.
She asked me to, Michael. I...
I-I tried to,
I tried to warn you.
I'm-I'm sorry.
Go home, Paul.
Now.
Before I kill you
with my bare hands.
♪ ♪
All right, come on.
(laughter, lively chatter)
Hey. Hey!
Hey, where you think
you're going?!
MAN: ...your eyes like that,
I don't know any...
- Get out!
- (groans)
Do you want to stay here?
Come on. Come on.
(people murmuring)
- She stays here!
- MAN: Yeah.
Stay there.
(grunting)
MAN:
Jesus!
(groans)
Let's go.
♪ ♪
Did Paul tell you about
what we did?
He didn't have to.
The guilt was written
all over his face.
Then why did you come for me?
- Why didn't you just leave me where I belong?
- Because...
I love you.
♪ ♪
(Shadrach neighs)
(crickets chirping)
♪ ♪
(crying softly)
(crying)
(groaning)
(crying continues)
(grunting, sobbing)
(straining, gasping)
Stop. Angel, stop.
- I'm not clean.
- Angel, hey.
Don't-don't touch me.
I'm not...
- Hey, hey, stop, stop.
- I'm not clean.
Let 'em go. It's okay.
It's okay.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- (crying continues)
- Come on.
- I'm not clean, Michael.
Hey, hey. Hey.
- Look at me, okay?
- (sobbing softly)
I forgive you.
Come on.
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
You have to stop thinking
that I'm gonna be
something that I'm not.
I don't know how to love.
I've got too many demons.
My father was my demon.
He was a plantation owner.
Slaves.
I told him when he died,
I'd free them all.
So he beat me bloody...
...dragged me down
to the slaves' quarters.
Said I should see
how animals live
since I loved them so much.
Ezra...
...an old slave,
took care of me, and, uh...
...mm, taught me about God.
And forgiveness.
So I took Ezra
down to the bayou and, uh...
set him free.
What about your father?
What did he do?
He wanted me to learn
the benefits of ownership,
so he sent a young slave girl
to my room.
Told me she was there
for me to, uh...
...to do with what I pleased.
I packed up and left
that night.
- Never looked back.
- And the girl?
Did... did you?
No, I did not.
See, sometimes
you have to leave behind
what you were born into
to become who...
...who God meant you to be.
Been thinking about
planting fruit trees.
(chuckles softly)
Over there.
What about walnuts?
Mm. Good idea.
♪ ♪
Fruit all summer,
nuts in the fall.
(Michael chuckles)
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
(sighs)
(creaking)
- (Angel gasps)
- (Maverick barking)
(gasps)
(exclaiming)
(laughing)
I got a fish!
Ah!
I got a fish! (gasps)
(laughing)
♪ ♪
MICHAEL:
Whoa now. Whoa now.
- (John groans)
- Whoa now.
JOHN:
Damn wheel.
Need some help?
That'd be mighty kind
of you, sir.
- What'd you hit?
- Hi.
Can you please help us?
My mom's in so much pain.
When is the baby due?
About this time last week.
MIRIAM:
She's not doing well.
MICHAEL:
Where you looking to settle?
- JOHN: I really like Oregon.
- Oregon?
We have the best farmland
west of the Rockies right here.
- I have 300 acres.
- Let's go give this to your ma.
And Paul's got just as much,
and-and there's more
available land next to him.
- Thank you.
- See, the thing about the California soil...
ELIZABETH: Thank you so much
for your kindness.
We've been living in that wagon
for over a year.
I'd forgotten what it feels
like to be in a real bed.
I don't know what we would have
done if you hadn't come along.
Mama wasn't doing well.
This baby can't stay
in the womb much longer.
Hey, uh, hold on. I got it.
- MICHAEL: Attach it down there.
- JOHN: Okay.
Just connect it down there.
PAUL:
Michael, do you have...
How did you and Michael
come to California?
Oh, he came by land,
and I came by ship.
(chuckles)
How did you two meet?
He rescued me from
a brothel in Pair-A-Dice.
(Miriam laughs)
Oh, you mean it.
I'm-I'm sorry.
Mama always says
I shouldn't pry,
but I just want
to know you better.
I like you.
You like me?
Yes.
Can you forgive me?
I want us to be friends.
Why do you want
to be my friend?
(chuckles):
Well-well, you're kind
and you're certainly honest.
(chuckles)
(banjo playing "Dry Bones")
♪ Old Enoch, he lived to be ♪
♪ Three hundred
and sixty-five ♪
♪ When the Lord came
and took him ♪
♪ Back to heaven alive ♪
♪ I saw ♪
♪ I saw the light from heaven ♪
♪ Shining all around ♪
♪ I saw that light
come shining ♪
♪ I saw that light come down ♪
MICHAEL: Paul came to me
asking for forgiveness.
He's still tortured
by what he did.
He knows how wrong he was.
That doesn't change anything.
♪ When Moses saw
that burning bush ♪
♪ He walked it
round and round ♪
♪ Well, the Lord
said to Moses ♪
♪ "You're treading
holy ground" ♪
♪ I saw ♪
♪ I saw the light from heaven ♪
(Michael and Miriam talking,
laughing)
♪ Shining all around ♪
♪ I saw that light
come shining ♪
♪ I saw that light come down. ♪
- (song ends)
- (others whooping, laughing)
Well, I have an announcement.
Elizabeth and I have decided
on a name for our youngest son.
(baby cooing)
Michael.
Michael Benjamin Altman.
(chuckles)
Well, I'm honored, truly.
Th-Thank you. (chuckles)
I have another announcement.
We're staying.
- (chuckling)
- With Michael's help,
I bought the land
just east of Paul's,
and he's rounded up a few men,
and we'll have a cabin up
in a few weeks.
(laughter)
Thank heavens.
If you'd put me back
on that wagon,
- I'd have shot ya.
- (laughter)
- MIRIAM: We're staying.
- MICHAEL: Congratulations.
Michael. Yeah.
♪ ♪
PAUL: Welcome to
the neighborhood, partner.
- Thank you.
- (chuckles)
- PAUL: It's right over yonder.
- MICHAEL: It is.
I'm, uh, I'm glad
you came, Paul.
PAUL:
Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
Miriam is... (sighs)
she's a beautiful girl.
Mm, she is.
And you two have
a lot in common.
- You get along so well.
- (chuckles)
You jealous of her?
(both laugh)
No, that's not it.
You have no reason
to be jealous.
I'm not jealous.
She can just give you
more than I can offer you.
(chuckles) I want you.
No one else.
Well, you want children.
- Mm-hmm.
I can't have children.
(Maverick barking in distance)
You can't know that.
I got pregnant once.
And Duke, um, he had a doctor,
and he said
that he would make sure
that it would never
happen again.
JOHN:
Michael! I need help!
The sheep are loose!
Listen to me.
I love you.
Nothing's gonna change that.
Nothing is impossible.
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
(sighs softly)
♪ ♪
(door closes)
(chuckles softly)
What are we celebrating?
- Us.
- Hmm?
Dinner first.
MICHAEL:
That was delicious.
Mmm.
(Michael chuckles)
Let's go to the hilltop
where you first showed me
the sunrise.
♪ ♪
You know,
I never paid attention
to sunrises and sunsets...
...till you brought me here.
(chuckles softly)
What's gotten into you?
Just want you to have
a good night.
(both panting)
♪ ♪
(whispers):
I love you.
♪ ♪
Excuse me. Mister? Hey.
- Uh, can I get...
- Yep.
Are you going into town?
Mm-hmm.
Get in.
There you go.
Hyah. Hyah.
(door opens)
(panting)
Wh-Where's Angel?
Gone.
Sh-She, um...
she left this for me.
You have to go after her.
She has free will.
It has to be her choice.
(busy chatter)
(man groaning)
Mister?
(man coughing)
I think you need a better cook.
We hired one, but he left
for the goldfields.
Well, hire me.
I can bake pies
and bread and biscuits.
You can call it
"Mama's Home Cooking."
Name's Virgil Harper.
Mama's Home Cooking.
You got yourself a job, missy.
Well, I need a place to stay.
You can have
the cook's quarters.
It's right off the kitchen.
There's a good lock
on the door.
You're gonna work yourself
to death.
(chuckles)
Keeps me from thinking
too much.
Paul says Angel's probably
in Sacramento or San Francisco.
What else did Paul say?
Just go after her, Michael.
Bring her back
where she belongs.
You want to help?
Pray for her.
That's what I'm doing.
(lively chatter, laughter)
- Are you doing all right?
- Oh, yes, ma'am.
All right. So this is yours.
♪ ♪
- Pass it down!
- Got it.
- Hurry!
- (panting) Here, here.
(clamoring continues)
(wood creaking)
- Hurry up! Let's go!
- Hurry!
Come on, bring up the next one!
Let's go!
- Hurry up!
- Keep it coming!
(men grunting)
There you go!
- Come on!
- Keep it moving!
♪ ♪
Jesus, let me go after her.
Let me, Lord, please.
(sighs)
Or just give me the strength
to hold tight.
(sighs)
(indistinct chatter)
DUKE:
Hello, Angel.
♪ ♪
It's been a long, long time.
It's fate that I find you
only a couple of blocks
from my front door.
Did you come to... all the way
to California just to find me?
Well, circumstances
changed in Boston,
but then there are fortunes
to be made here
and few laws on how it's done.
Shall we go?
All that I have to do
is scream,
and a dozen men will come help
a lady in distress.
Open your mouth,
and I'll have Colin kill Virgil
Harper some dark foggy night.
You...
...a cook?
Ah, it's a pity
the café burned down.
♪ ♪
- (lively chatter)
- (piano music playing)
Leave us, Rosie.
- (whimpers, gasps)
- Take the key.
Lock her in the room next door.
- Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
- ROSIE (whimpers): No.
(door closes)
How old is she, Duke?
(sighs softly)
I need you to get cleaned up.
You're going onstage tonight.
I need to put
my best prostitute on display.
How old is she?
Eight?
Nine?
- You jealous, Angel?
- (chuckles softly)
You never could handle a woman,
could you?
What's happened to you, dear?
What's it gonna take
to bring my little Angel back?
Fill the bathtub up
with warm water.
(whimpers)
(buckets creaking)
- (door closes)
- (lock clicks)
♪ ♪
Don't push me, Angel.
As fond as I am of you,
you're not indispensable.
(knocks)
If she gets away again,
I'll hold you accountable.
I'll be next door
with the girls.
(lock clicks)
(door opens and closes
in distance)
- DUKE: Come here!
- ROSIE: No!
- DUKE: Get over here!
- (Rosie shouting)
I said now!
(girls screaming, shouting)
- Get over here! Come here!
- (Angel sobbing)
- (clattering)
- (girls shouting)
- (slap)
- (girls screaming)
(sobbing)
ROSIE:
Please stop now! Please!
- ANGEL: Please.
- (Duke grunts, slaps)
(Rosie screaming)
ANGEL:
God!
- (lively chatter, laughter)
- (piano music playing)
(whistling)
(cheering, whistling)
(lively chatter
and laughter continues)
(chatter and music fade)
♪ ♪
(whispering):
My God.
God, I want to believe.
I do.
(breath trembles)
If you're real,
please just help me.
♪ ♪
If you want revenge
for everything I've ever done,
then so be it,
but those girls need you.
I need you.
Help me.
(echoing):
Please.
SARAH:
Wake up.
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
I want to believe.
MAE:
Sarah.
♪ ♪
Tell them the truth, darling.
I give you an Angel.
♪ ♪
(crowd cheering)
(whooping)
Feel the power, Angel.
We can share it.
We'll bring them
to their knees.
(cheering continues)
(crowd quiets)
Duke fancies little girls.
- What? - What?
- (crowd murmuring)
ANGEL: He has two locked away
upstairs right now.
He abuses us until we do
anything to survive.
♪ ♪
I was eight years old
when he bought me.
(murmuring continues)
I escaped when I was 17,
but he found me
and he forced me here.
- DUKE: Lies! All lies.
- (crowd jeering)
A scorned woman
tells lies, gentlemen.
Lies!
And you're the father of lies.
(grunts) Get over here!
(crowd clamoring, jeering)
Let-Let's dance. Let's dance.
Let's dance. All right.
- (grunts)
- (gasps)
I should've killed you
when I had the chance.
(both grunt)
Goodbye, Angel.
(grunting)
- Stay down.
- (screams)
Go. Get out of here. Go.
- Colin!
- Go.
(Duke screams)
MAN:
That's enough.
DUKE:
Colin!
MAN:
Quiet. Don't you dare.
(girls whimpering)
Okay, I'm-I'm gonna
get you girls out of here.
DUKE:
Colin!
COLIN:
Coming!
(girl gasps)
- (Colin groans, coughs)
- Come on.
(crowd murmuring)
There are little girls in here!
(crowd clamoring)
Hang Duke!
(clamoring swells)
(Angel panting)
(clamoring continues)
MAN:
Godspeed.
(clamoring continues)
♪ ♪
- There he is!
- (crowd clamoring)
(Duke panting)
(grunting)
(rope creaking)
(coyotes barking in distance)
(indistinct chatter)
(horses neighing)
♪ ♪
Oh, well,
she-she definitely did.
(continues talking
indistinctly)
(Angel laughs)
I'll see you. (laughs)
(horses sputtering, neighing)
SUSANNAH:
...30, we got 2.648,
divided by 22,
multiplied by 60.
Don't forget the...
Ma'am.
Can I help you, sir?
I'm looking for a girl.
I bet you are.
(laughter)
PAUL:
Uh, she went by the name Angel.
Uh, I think I saw her
come in here yesterday.
ANGEL:
Paul.
- Wh-What is this place?
- (sniffles)
It is a shelter and a school.
For women like me
who want a new life.
Do you, um...
ever go back to the valley?
Miriam told me you wanted
to go back to the goldfields.
She talked me out of it.
How is she?
Well...
...she's in a family way.
Wow. That's...
Well, that is...
that's wonderful news.
Well...
guess you're gonna have to
help him build an addition
to the cabin.
He'll need it.
(chuckles) What for?
For the baby. He and Miriam
definitely need more room.
Miriam is my wife.
Not Michael's.
♪ ♪
He's still waiting for you.
(whispers):
What?
Why would you do that?
Why would you get in the way?
- Miriam is perfect for him.
- I didn't.
She's-she's innocent.
She's pure.
She's intelligent.
She knows how to love.
- She chose me.
- She loved him.
Like a brother, she loved him.
You need to go back
and you need to tell him
that you found out I was dead.
Do you hear me?
Cholera, consumption, anything.
Michael has to find a nice girl
that can give him children,
Paul.
I can't.
Did...
- Did he know?
- Yes.
I told him.
So that's why you left?
You thought he would...
he would go to Miriam,
and they...
(smacks lips)
(voice breaking):
I was wrong about you, Angel.
'Cause I hated you.
But what you-you said to me
that day outside
Pair-A-Dice, I...
(Paul sobs softly)
I knew you were right about me.
(sniffles)
I'm a scoundrel and I betrayed
my brother and... (sobs)
Angel?
Angel, will you...
will you forgive me?
(sniffles)
I forgave you
a long time ago, Paul.
How could I not...
(chuckles softly)
...with all the forgiveness
that I've been given?
Uh...
Come back with me.
Michael is suffering.
This has already been
hard enough.
I'm needed here.
The carriage
leaves my hotel at 4:00.
Please come with me.
He loves you.
(bell tolling)
- (indistinct chatter)
- (tolling continues)
(horse neighs)
♪ ♪
What are you thinking about?
(Miriam gasps)
I've missed you so much.
I missed you both.
Did you find her?
Go on.
(sheep bleating)
- (plow clanks)
- (Shadrach neighing)
(wind whistling softly)
("Rescue" by Lauren Daigle
playing)
♪ You are not hidden ♪
♪ There's never been a moment
you were forgotten ♪
♪ You are not hopeless ♪
♪ Though you have been broken ♪
♪ Your innocence stolen ♪
♪ I hear you whisper ♪
♪ Underneath your breath ♪
♪ I hear your S.O.S. ♪
♪ Your S.O.S. ♪
♪ I will send out an army ♪
♪ To find you ♪
♪ In the middle
of the darkest night ♪
♪ It's true, I will... ♪
My real name is Sarah.
And I've never told
anyone that.
Until now. (chuckles)
Because it was
the only thing that I had
that no one could take from me.
I came here to tell you
that I love you.
And I am so sorry.
I'm so sorry
for all of the pain
that I've caused you, Michael.
(sniffles)
It's your pain that brought us
to this moment.
♪ There is no distance ♪
(birds chirping)
♪ That cannot be covered ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ You're not defenseless ♪
♪ I'll be your shelter ♪
♪ I'll be your armor ♪
Keep it on this time,
will you, please?
I'll never take it off.
♪ I hear you whisper... ♪
As long as I live.
(chuckles softly)
Welcome home, Sarah.
I've always loved you.
♪ I will ♪
- Welcome home.
- (laughs)
♪ Send out an army
to find you ♪
♪ In the middle
of the darkest night ♪
♪ It's true ♪
♪ I will rescue you ♪
(both laughing)
♪ I will never stop marching ♪
♪ To reach you ♪
♪ In the middle
of the hardest fight ♪
♪ It's true... ♪
Come.
Come on, baby.
Yeah. Right here.
Okay, come.
Do you want to fish?
Ready? Ready?
(gasps)
Oh, oh.
- (Stephen grunting)
- Good! Yeah!
(Sarah and Michael laughing)
Here. Come here. Okay.
Okay. Go that way.
- ♪ Oh, I will rescue you. ♪
- (Stephen babbling)
- (Sarah laughing)
- (song ends)
♪ ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ ♪
(music fades)