(whooshing)
(dramatic music)
(somber piano music)
(inspiring instrumental music)
- That's what you fucking
said the last time.
- You're making a big
deal out of nothing.
- Oh, you can just go to
hell, you motherfucker.
- It's just Melony Proctor.
She's a fucking whore anyway.
It's her job.
- How am I supposed to have
a real conversation with you
when you're dressed
like this fucking Bozo?
- Bitch, don't you
ever fucking mock me.
- Why not?
Who else is laughing?
Except maybe Melony Proctor.
- You come back
here and take it.
Come on.
So you think I'm a joke, huh?
I'm the man around here.
I'm the fucking man.
Fuck.
(somber music)
What you doing?
- Nothing.
- I don't know.
Doesn't look like nothing to me.
Here, let me see.
- Hey, give it back!
- Wait.
- Give it!
- This ain't so impressive.
(laughing)
Calm down, why don't you?
Just calm down.
Wait a minute.
Nah, this is shit.
Don't get all weepy now.
You don't want to be labeled
a cunt like your mother.
Do you?
(laughing)
What do you think, Larry?
You think I'm funny, right?
What's the matter with you, kid?
You never laugh.
All the times I've known you,
I can't even get you
to crack a smile.
You must be as fucking dense
as these ignorant pig
fuckers around here.
- You're the worst clown ever.
- Really?
Not funny?
Not funny?!
I'll show you funny, kid!
- Let me go!
Stop!
(ominous music)
- Give me that.
- Let me go.
- You want funny? You got it.
(laughing)
- Get off me.
- Am I touching you?
Am I touching you?
Coochie, coochie-choo.
Coochie, coochie, coochie-coo.
You wanted funny! You got it!
(laughing)
Coochie, coochie, coochie-coo.
Coochie, coochie-coo.
I work so hard.
I slave away for you bastards
to get a descent wage.
You'd think I'd get
a little support.
A little kindness?
A little glad?
(laughing)
Look at this bullshit.
I don't know what's
going on here.
What is this?
(gasping)
Hey, what's going on here?
(gagging)
There's something
wrong with the kid!
Lyla!
- Larry!
What did you do to my baby?
Oh my god.
God damn it, call 911.
- All right.
- Baby, look at me.
Baby, it's okay, honey.
- Yeah, is this the police?
Yeah, this is Dale again.
We've got a bit of an emergency.
It's my girlfriend's kid.
He's having a
brainstorm or something.
I don't know.
Look, we need an ambulance.
Maybe he's dying or something.
I don't know.
I told you before,
the kid's a tard.
Yeah.
A few minutes?
All right, I'll
be expecting you.
All right.
(dramatic piano music)
- Hey.
I thought I'd try
you one last time
before I leave in the morning.
I know.
Peyton, I know.
Would you cut me some slack?
We're just chilling
one last time
before I leave in the morning.
I'm flying out first
thing in the morning.
No excuses.
(radio rock music)
Hey, I gotta go.
Yeah, I'll call you after--
- You ready to roll?
- I love you too, bye.
What's up, guys?
- [Guy] What up, dude?
- How you been, man?
Good to see you.
- Good to see you guys.
What's up?
- All right, before we go,
I got some shit
you guys gotta see.
- He's been going on and
on about this shit all day.
- Well, what is it?
- You know my cousin upstate?
He's being paroled.
- Paroled?
- Come on, fucker,
get to the point.
- All right, don't
rush me, Jesus.
You're fucking up my story here.
- Story?
You're not exactly Hemingway.
- Hemingway?
Whatever.
Before he got taken away,
his crew
they planted some shit
out here, you feel me?
Some good shit.
- No shit.
- No shit, indeed.
- Listen, it's your
call, college boy.
You're the one whose gotta
catch a flight in the morning,
but if you say the
word, we'll split.
- Come on, man.
Xbox and beer our last night?
Fuck that.
Come on, for old times sake.
- I guess.
Why bother flying if you
can't fly high, right?
(laughing)
- That's my boy.
Tony, you better be right
about this shit though.
- Follow me.
(somber piano music)
(enchanting instrumental music)
Motherfucker.
- What is that?
- That guy over there.
He's pissing all
over the product.
- Fuck it, let's
just get out of here.
- No, fuck that shit.
That's your cousin's
legacy, right?
You're gonna let some
asshole come out here
and piss all over his legacy?
- Fuck no.
- Yeah, that's right, boy.
You go get that shit
and while you're at it,
show that fucker who's boss.
- Fucking right.
Hey, asshole.
What the fuck you
think you're doing?
- Taking a piss.
- You asking or
telling, old man?
(ominous music)
You ain't going nowhere.
- I didn't realize
you wanted to watch.
I could try to take another
pee if it'll make you happy.
- You motherfucker.
(intense music)
- Tony, what the fuck?
- You motherfucker!
You fucking scum!
Fucking ruined the fucking
shit, you motherfucker!
You fucking pissed on my shit!
You hear that guy?
He's a fucking fag or some shit.
- Calm down.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
(intense music)
(eerie music)
- Whatever.
When you two are done
stroking each other's cocks.
You know, fuck both you guys.
- What the fuck? Fuck you.
- You're fucking psycho.
I didn't think you'd
actually do it.
- Did you hear?
He called me a fucking
fag or something?
He's just a fucking old man.
- You okay?
(gagging)
(ominous music)
(screaming)
(foreboding music)
(laughing)
(knocking)
(coughing)
- Fuck.
(knocking)
- [Man] Professor Hanson?
- Be right there.
- Sorry I'm late, professor.
I was finishing that
sketch last week.
I have some cool
stuff to show you.
Check out this cool pen.
Doesn't it look very
Marquis de Sade?
(ominous music)
This sketch.
(foreboding music)
Nathan said that he was
gonna come around six.
Something to do with his
mom and pills or something.
Professor, what happened here?
What happened to your eye?
- Long night.
(ominous music)
(stepfather laughing)
- [Stepfather]
Think I'm funny now?
I'm funny, right?
You gonna laugh?
You think I'm funny?
(laughing)
(foreboding music)
- Professor?
(somber piano music)
(eerie music)
Professor, are you okay?
(ominous music)
Professor?
(eerie music)
(exciting video game music)
(knocking)
- Go away.
Not coming.
(knocking)
It's open! Fuck!
- All right, motherfucker.
Where is he?
- Good morning, Peyton.
- Morning?
It is five in the
afternoon, dick fingers.
(video game music)
Where is he?
- He, as in?
- My brother.
- Brad's gone. You know that.
Now, you don't have to make
excuses to come see me.
He didn't get on the plane,
he never called and
he's not at school.
So where the hell is he?
- Your guess is as good as mine.
- And your guess would be?
That's what I thought.
- You can't just.
- We have a problem.
- I guess so.
Hey, where you going?
- To Troy's.
If anybody knows where
he is, that bastard will.
They were supposed
to hang that night.
- I'm coming with you.
- Why?
- You know.
Protection.
- Please.
(ominous music)
(moaning)
(evil laughing)
(giggling)
(groaning)
(foreboding music)
(gasping)
- Why are you doing this to me?
Please stop hurting me.
What are you doing?
- Coochie, coochie, coochie-coo.
(laughing)
Coochie, coochie, coochie-coo.
(knocking)
- Help!
Help me, please!
Please help!
- Coochie, coochie, coochie-coo.
(groaning)
(gagging)
Coochie, coochie, coochie-coo.
(knocking)
(gasping)
(reggae music)
- Knock, knock.
What are you doing?
- Get the fuck in here.
Close that door.
What the fuck you two
think you're doing
busting into people's
homes like that?
- The door was open.
- Where's my brother?
- Shit.
What makes you think?
- Cut the shit, Troy.
- What the fuck did
you say to me, bitch?
- What the fuck is going on?
- You wanna see a bitch?
You were with him last
night and yet here you are.
So where the fuck is he?
I'm not gonna ask again.
- Yeah?
Then what?
You gonna cut me?
Please.
You have no motherfucking clue
the shit I've seen little girl.
- Where is he, Troy?
- Tony's in there.
He was the last one to see him.
You with her again?
- Never kiss and tell, my man.
- Yeah.
(heavy metal music)
(Tony moaning)
- Come on, now.
(yelling)
Shit!
Jesus Christ, get out!
- Where's Brad?
- How the fuck should I know?
- Enough!
Show me.
- No, I'm ain't
showing you shit.
Let me go get my pants.
- Professor.
(foreboding music)
Sam?
Come on, is this a joke?
Get up.
Sam, come on.
(foreboding music)
- This is a bad idea.
- Keep moving.
- Tell us again about
this killer clown, Tony.
- Shut up, Conner.
- Shut up!
- All of you, shut the fuck up.
When I find Brad, I
am whooping his ass
and then I am
whooping all of yours.
- Damn, girl.
Fucking sexy.
- Shut up.
- There.
- Okay.
And?
- That's where we last saw him.
I'm out of here.
- Wait.
- What happened?
- Just tell her already.
- Well, we came here looking
for my cousin's stash
and there was this guy,
this creepy motherfucker
and he attacked
us and we ran off.
We left Brad behind.
When we turned around
he was gone.
(ominous music)
- Listen,
you gotta understand.
What we saw was...
Crazy.
We weren't thinking.
- Yeah, he changed
right in front of us.
The way his hair, his eyes,
I will never forget
the look in his eyes.
- Turned into a clown?
- Call it what you want, man.
- I'm calling it
what you guys said.
You did say a clown, right?
- I never said a fucking clown.
- You chicken shits.
You ran and you left
my brother to die
so that someone wouldn't
find your stash.
- No.
It wasn't like that. No.
- I will kill you.
If he is dead, you're
next, motherfucker.
You're both fucking next!
(yelling)
- Shit.
There goes our ride.
(intense music)
- Shit.
(somber piano music)
- We're gonna find him.
I mean it.
- He's dead, Conner.
(crying)
- Come on.
Don't say that.
We can go to the cops.
They'll have every officer
in the city looking for him.
- They know his history.
They know his rap sheet.
If he's dead, they're
not gonna give two shits.
They'll throw a fucking party.
He was a bad kid.
A kid.
And this was finally it.
Was finally his chance
to get out of here
and to make
something of himself.
I knew it.
I knew I should've stopped
him from going out.
He was so fucking close, Conner.
He was so fucking close.
(crying)
- It'll be okay.
I'll help you out.
- I have to go.
- I'll come with you.
- No.
I'm fine, really.
Tomorrow, okay?
- Yeah.
Sure.
- Thanks.
For everything.
(car engine starting)
Hey.
It's me.
I just need to freshen up.
Be half an hour, all right?
All right, I'll see you soon.
- God, I need this.
I really need this.
- What is it you need, baby?
- She's the only thing
that calms me, mom.
I can't help it.
Whenever I'm with
her, I feel so alive.
(stepfather laughing)
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
but if this bitch is the
only thing you need, buddy,
you're more fucked
up than we thought.
- You shut up.
- Or what?
- Leave him alone, you monster.
- Monster, aye?
That's cute.
Your precious baby boy kills
three people in cold blood
and I'm the monster.
- I didn't do that.
Did I?
- Oh, you bet you did.
Tickled them.
Weird, right?
Except for that first one.
You ripped his
throat out real good.
Now that was a mad
kill, if I ever saw one.
- No, no, no.
- Baby, calm down.
Dale's just messing.
Dale, tell Larry
you're just messing.
Dale.
Tell Larry.
- This can't be happening.
Not again.
- Oh it is.
Over and over and over and over
and over and over.
- What the hell
did you do to me?
Answer me!
(foreboding music)
- I believe thank
you is in order.
- Stop it! Stop it!
Stop!
Please, stop it.
Stop it!
(somber music)
- Don't act like
you can't remember.
You can fool her.
You can fool yourself.
But you can't fool me, boy.
(laughing)
- What am I?
- You're a killer.
(knocking)
- Hello, Cherry.
- Why the long face, baby?
Let's get this party started.
- I had this one
student in art class.
One day she wanted to
be like Salvador Dali
and the next day René Magritte
and the next day she thought
she was like Van Gogh.
She didn't know what she wanted.
- So that's why
you quit teaching.
- No, I quit teaching because
she wouldn't drop my class.
- You do some really great work.
- Thanks.
- I think when I quit teaching
it really got my creative
juices flowing again.
I still teach.
A few local kids
from the neighborhood
come here for art classes
a couple times a week.
Nothing that pays the bills,
but at least I get to
interact with people.
- Not a lot of interaction
in your life, Larry?
- Sadly, no.
Listen to me.
I'm rambling like a madman.
Tell me about you, Cherry.
- Nothing much to tell, really.
- Can I assume Cherry
isn't your real name?
- Next subject.
- Sorry.
It's just that I
really care about you.
You come here so often,
I feel like we're more than just
customer and client.
I almost feel like we're...
- Friends?
We're friends, Larry.
If you really wanna know.
I recently lost my brother.
The only family I had left.
- What happened?
- He was murdered.
- Oh my god.
- At least, that's the
story that I'm getting.
But the ones telling that story
are a couple of burnout losers
with a sketchy track record
and an even sketchier
relationship with the truth.
- Did they tell
you what happened?
- Not exactly.
Just that he was
attacked in the woods by
a guy possibly dressed
like a clown or some shit.
It's all fucking
bullshit if you ask me.
- A clown?
- Yeah.
Like I said.
Bullshit.
They did something to him.
I know they did
and when I find out what,
let's just say...
Fuck it.
Got anymore?
- Actually, that
was my last bottle.
Cherry, I hate to do this.
I've been fighting a cold
or allergies or something.
- I get it.
Let's do this another night.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
- Yeah, no problem, really.
- Okay.
I apologize.
- For what it's worth,
I had a lovely evening.
It was a nice distraction.
Till the end, of course.
Thanks.
See you soon?
- I'll call you.
(somber music)
- I told you.
A killer.
- What do I do?
- Trust in me.
(eerie music)
It's the only way out.
- What're you doing, Larry?
Give me the knife, baby.
(menacing music)
- Very nice.
(giggling)
- Diablo?
- My friends call me Diablo.
You haven't paid me
in two months.
Name's Mr. Sanchez to you.
- I'm on it.
I swear, I swear.
- You are a nice piece of ass.
Why do you mess around
with that old fuck?
- Larry's a nice guy.
He doesn't need sex.
We both win.
- You're not here to win.
You're my whore.
Whores fuck.
Start fucking him
and stop fucking me.
I want my money.
You get it from him
or you get a bullet
to the brain.
(foreboding music)
Tomorrow night.
(exciting video game music)
(knocking)
- Yeah, coming.
(somber music)
What're we doing?
- Don't make me beg.
After all the shit I've been,
I need to feel loved again.
Just one night. Can you do that?
Good.
Now shut up.
(somber piano music)
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- Some night, huh?
- Yeah, I'd say so.
- I love you.
- Conner, this isn't.
We can't do this.
- This is what you wanted.
This is what you asked for.
I'm here.
I'm right here, Peyton.
- I wasn't thinking last night.
Shit just got out of hand
and I needed someone.
- And I was there.
- Exactly.
And I still need you, Conner.
I need you to help me find Brad.
- And then?
- Then, I don't know.
- That's not a no.
- It's not a no.
But...
- But?
- I am in big fucking
trouble, Conner.
Big fucking trouble.
- Go on.
- No, fuck it.
I've got it, really.
- What?
- Hey!
- Who's Larry?
- Fuck you, Conner!
- It's Diablo, isn't it?
He's got you again, doesn't he?
(dramatic music)
Spend the day with me.
Tell me everything.
I'll just shut up and listen.
(crying)
It's gonna be okay, Pey.
But as punishment,
you're gonna be second player.
(laughing)
(reggae music)
- Hey.
Go get us some food.
Come on.
- Fuck you, pot boy.
You get us some food.
- Fuck you.
Go get food.
- Fuck.
- Make it snappy.
- "Make it snappy."
(reggae music)
- Ah!
(somber music)
(phone chiming)
- This is your big chance.
Take care of her, that's one
less loose end to worry about.
- She's not a loose end.
- She starts playing Scooby-Doo,
the cops get involved.
The cops get involved,
we're fucked.
- I suppose you're right.
- Yeah.
I'm always right.
You know what to do.
- I know, I know.
- Just make sure you get rope.
Nylon.
Not that cheap kind that
sheds shit everywhere.
And tape.
Lots and lots of tape.
Duct, not masking.
- Why would I get masking tape?
I'm not a complete moron.
- Really?
Where'd you stash
the bodies, Larry?
- That's a valid point.
- After we take care of
your little fuck ups,
we hit the road.
New town.
New identities.
New kills.
This time,
we'll be unstoppable.
(somber music)
- Shit!
Shit! Shit!
(engine puttering)
Fuck!
Yeah, motherfucker.
I know who you are.
No, you ain't getting in here.
Fuck!
(engine puttering)
Fuck.
(ominous music)
(coughing)
(foreboding music)
Fuck!
(eerie laughing)
(yelling)
What the fuck?
- Coochie coochie.
Coochie.
Coochie
Coochie coochie, coo.
(laughing)
(foreboding music)
- Is that all you got, man?
Holy shit!
(laughing)
- Coochie coochie, coo.
Coochie coochie, coo.
(laughing)
(eerie music)
(gagging)
(somber music)
(Dale laughing)
- Get the address.
We need to check the place.
More loose ends, I'm sure.
(eerie music)
(foreboding music)
(screaming)
- Who are you?
What the fuck?
Let me out of here.
Fucking kill you.
Let me go.
Just stand there,
you fucking freak.
(creepy laughing)
What the fuck are you doing?
What is that?
(creepy child-like laughing)
Shit, man.
- Coochie coochie, coo.
Coochie coochie, coo.
(laughing)
- Stop!
Please.
Stop, please.
Please, cut it out.
Please, stop.
Stop. Stop.
Stop, please.
(gasping)
- Coochie coochie, coo.
Coochie coochie, coo.
(intense music)
- What the fuck?
Stop.
Stop!
I swear.
Stop.
Let me go, you fucking freak.
(eerie laughing)
(intense music)
(gasping)
What the fuck?
I'm gonna kill you.
Put that down.
No.
Oh, fuck. No.
Please, no! No!
Oh god.
(intense music)
Fuck.
(laughing)
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh my god.
Oh fuck.
(booming)
(ominous music)
- Now,
the girl
and we're home free.
(laughing)
(somber music)
(video game music)
- You're going down.
- I gotta go.
This isn't up for discussion.
I have to, Conner.
- Why?
Why can't you just stop?
- Because if I don't
get him his money,
I will have bigger problems
than Tony and Troy.
You know how serious he is.
- Let me take care of him.
- And do what?
Kill him?
His people will find you
and it won't end
until we're all dead.
Or I can end it now.
I can get him his money
and I can get him
out of my life.
- You think it'll be that easy?
- There are no other
options for me.
- I love you.
I've always loved you.
But I can't let you
kill yourself for money.
- Bye, Conner.
(somber music)
- Wow.
You look terrific.
- Thank you.
- You know what to do.
The bitch dies.
- I know.
- I'm sorry?
- Nevermind.
I was just thinking
of something.
Sit down.
Well, here we are.
- Here we are.
- Can I get you something?
- Just these clothes off me.
- I thought you'd never ask.
Let me get the room ready.
I have a surprise for you.
I want this to be special.
Make yourself at home.
(dramatic music)
- You really like the moon.
- You're wasting time.
(foreboding music)
(ominous music)
- Brad.
(gasping)
- Get her.
(yelling)
- No! No!
(intense music)
Get off me!
- You let her go,
we're done for!
(screaming)
- Peyton!
- No! No! No!
Conner!
(booming)
- Shit.
(tire screeching)
Stop it, please!
- Shut up!
- Let me go! Let me go!
- Sit down.
- Diablo, wait.
- Hands behind your back.
- Let me go and I will
get you your money.
Let me go, please.
- It's too late begging.
- Let me go!
Diablo!
Diablo, please.
I will get you your money.
- All right, bitch.
You die.
- Let me go.
I will get you your money.
- Too late, bitch.
Now you'll know
the fires of hell.
- Diablo, listen to me.
Listen to me.
Just let me go
and I will get you your money.
Please.
Don't do this. Just let me go.
- Shut up, bitch.
- Just let me go!
You let me go!
Let me go!
- Burn in hell.
I'll roast marshmallows
on your tits.
- Look at me.
Don't do this and I
will get the money.
I will get you more
than your money.
I will get you so much money.
I will be your best girl.
- You die!
- No! No!
(screaming)
Stop!
Diablo!
- Burn, burn, burn!
I smelled a cunt.
Dirty whore.
No one messes around
with Diablo Sanchez.
Shit!
Forgot my matches.
Sorry, I'll be back.
- Help!
Help!
- Hey! Hey!
- Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
- I'm moving. I'm moving.
(creepy laughing)
- Larry.
(eerie music)
- What the fuck?
- What're you doing?
- I love you.
- [Peyton] What?
(intense music)
(eerie music)
(creepy laughing)
(exciting music)
(intense music)
(yelling)
- What?
(carnival music)
(foreboding music)
- No!
(gasping)
(somber music)
What do you want from me?
You wanna kill me?
You wanna fuck me?
Do it, Larry.
I'm tied up.
I am a helpless little girl.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, that's
what us whores like.
- What are you doing?
This is no time
to fuck with her.
That guy's gonna come back
in here again any minute.
Could be another loose end.
Do you want another loose end?
- Come on!
What are you waiting for?
I'm here for the taking, right?
(crying)
Abuse me.
The others did.
(laughing)
(dramatic music)
I hate you.
(laughing)
(screaming)
(yelling)
(laughing)
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
("Lunatic Dreams" by
The Dirty Blondes)
* I can't believe
I'm here with you
* It's a fantasy come true
* I know just what I wanna do
* I hope you're
feeling that way too
* The pressing
moon is on the rise
* I see it shining in your eyes
* And as the sun sinks into dusk
* My emotions turn to lust
* Lunatic dreams
* Can come be true
* Nightmarish screams
* Fade in to blue
* Maybe I'm seeing
visions in my head
* Lunatic dreams
float above my bed
* I'm your vision in the night
* I just might give you a fright
* Your my midnight rendezvous
* I think I'm gonna come unglued
* Lunatic dreams
* Can be true
* Nightmarish screams
* Fade in to blue
* Maybe I'm seeing
visions in my head
* Lunatic dreams
float above my bed
* Come to me, my little one
* I'll take you
to my land of fun
* Don't be scared
* Don't be afraid
* It's not just a masquerade