(laid-back music)
- [Man] Hey, Jimmy, Jimmy!
(gunshot banging)
(engine revving)
- [Narrator] That's funny, I
didn't expect to die today.
(dog barking)
♪ You could've rubbed me out
and filled in the blanks ♪
♪ You're the one that wants
to be the one to thank ♪
♪ But my body up and left me ♪
♪ While I was waiting to be filled in ♪
♪ I'm someone else ♪
♪ I'm not myself, I'm someone else ♪
♪ I haven't been seen, so I'm not myself ♪
♪ A light bulb went off in my head ♪
♪ Suddenly, I'm none of
the things you said ♪
♪ Did my body up and leave me ♪
♪ Or did someone finally fill me in ♪
♪ Still feel like a fake ♪
♪ I still have to lie ♪
♪ Lie still, like a fake ♪
♪ Like I could disappear
before your eyes ♪
♪ You could've rubbed me out ♪
(melancholy music)
- [Narrator] Maybe if I just hadn't got
out of bed yesterday,
maybe a lotta things.
You gotta hold on here, think.
Yeah, now that I think on it,
yesterday started seriously fucked up.
You didn't exactly wake up feeling
like some way cool dude, did ya?
Nah, you had one of those hangovers
you wish you could just die from.
- Get up, man, Chris is here.
Did you drink so much, you
can't even fucking wake up, man?
You're gonna make the old man proud.
Get up, man!
- Get off!
- What the fuck's wrong with you,
pushing me away like that, man?
Just telling you to wake up.
- It's weird.
Once my older brother,
Brandon, and I were like this,
and now we drive each other crazy.
He is right about things.
There just isn't anything
I can do about it.
The craziest story I ever heard
is how our mom named us Marlon Brando Ray
and James Dean Ray, her
two favorite actors.
You can't be any more American than that.
Now we're just Brandon and Jimmy.
Everything would've been
different if Mom hadn't died.
At least, I think so.
We've always kicked back
by the local airport,
watching the planes take off.
We even got up once
with some uncle of ours,
our mom's brother, or something.
That was five years ago, when I was 18.
Sometimes, watching the birds
take off is the only way
to see people get out of this
piece of shit little town.
Yeah, newcomers always complain
about the sound of planes taking off.
Me, I like it.
It's comforting, and as close
to heaven as I'll ever get.
- Just get Chris in here, okay?
- [Brandon] Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry man.
I guess you don't need to hear all this
when you have a hangover, huh?
Bro, just take it easy, all right?
- Yeah, goddamn right, take it easy.
I just should've last night.
- Yeah, I'll just let Chris on in.
Hey, maybe when I get
home from school today,
we can hang out, or something.
At least we'll go to that party together.
- [Jimmy] Yeah, maybe.
- I'm not telling you your
business, or anything,
but if you wanna keep
Alyssha as your girlfriend,
you better show at that
party tonight, man.
- [Jimmy] Fuck that, we'll see.
- Later.
- [Narrator] Before all
this shit went down,
we had a great time, when
it was just Brandon and me.
He was almost as crazy as I was, almost.
God, I used to look up to
him, my big brother, still do.
The TV always gave me ideas,
hot thing to do, easy crime to commit.
I guess it keeps 'em in
business, I don't know.
It is funny how sometimes in life
things are just handed to you.
- Excuse me, I wonder if you could tell me
how I can get back onto the motorway.
- Oh yeah, I can help you.
Where you from?
- From England, Gloucestershire.
- Oh, uh-huh, and where's that?
- Oh, it's a long way west of London.
- You're from England or
Ireland, or something?
- A little of both, I think.
- Well, there sure are enough of us here.
It's a great country.
- It sure is.
You can show us that map, or something?
- Yeah, thanks.
- Yeah, why don't you put it
on the hood, or something,
so we can tell where you're going?
- All right, thanks very much.
Thanks.
- Yeah.
- [Englishman] I came off here.
- Oh, uh-huh?
- Mm.
- [Narrator] I wish I hadn't done that.
It seemed funny at the time.
Poor bastard probably thought he was safe
with a couple of white boys.
We should all be safe, but we ain't.
(Englishman groaning)
- Shit, bloody hell.
(slow rock music)
- [Narrator] Chris Hollins
has been a good friend
since I met him in kindergarten.
Old man has always hated
him for being black.
He has no reason, he just does.
Chris was trying to warn me.
I just wouldn't listen.
- Josh Brawly told me Ford
Davis is looking for you, man.
But I told him you were out at the
kosher market, or something,
man, I made some shit up.
- He can't find me, man.
- Dude, what's up with that?
Josh said you skipped on Ford, man.
I told him that ain't like you.
- Yeah, well, I'll take
care of it later, all right?
- All right, dude.
(metal clattering)
(brooding rock music)
- [Narrator] Yeah, I should've
just pulled the covers
over my head for a day,
till it all flew over,
but that's never been my style.
I always wanted to be
like my old man, Nick Ray,
but it was best if we
just ignored one another.
He hated me, and I didn't give a shit.
Maybe I did.
It's sad, I wanna remember
something good about him.
I can't.
All I can remember is his
hand coming down on my face
when I was too small to fight back.
(melancholy rock music)
- Come on, man.
Come, there we go, Pop.
- [Jimmy] Come on.
- Oh shit, you fuck! (laughs)
- [Nick] Jimmy.
- [Brandon] Come on.
- [Jimmy] Steady.
- [Nick] He fucking spilled
beer on me, the son of a bitch.
- [Narrator] As much as I've
hated him my whole life,
that's how much now I see we're alike.
- Hey, good to see you
could make it up here today.
- Hey, man I really
tied one on last night.
- Tell me, Jimmy, do you have any idea
what you're doing with yourself, man?
- Well, at least I ain't getting
drunk here in the morning.
- When I was your age, I
at least had a goddamn job.
I had a wife, and I had a kid.
And I fought a fucking war,
so don't start with me, Jimmy.
- Yeah, see, I am smarter than you, right?
- Why?
I can see you didn't learn shit
from your little visit to County, did you?
- Oh yeah, I learned one thing.
- What's that?
- Never get caught.
- Ooh.
Is this the best you can do?
- It's better than you, old man.
- Oh, Jimmy, I don't feel
like arguing this morning,
so why don't you just go?
Go on, get outta here.
- Hey, man, you always
have time for arguing.
- Have a good one.
- Yeah.
- I got a hundred-and-something
channels on this thing,
and I can't get shit on any of 'em.
(brooding rock music)
♪ Seems I have been a clown ♪
- [Narrator] I wasn't really
worried about owing money yet.
I figured I'd sell what I had,
and come up with a plan for the rest.
The only time I can think
sometimes is when I'm driving.
I have this fog over me,
especially since I got out
of County about a month ago.
(siren blaring)
What others call trouble,
I've always called fun.
- Okay, and then another
here, over here, over here,
down here, down here.
- Come on, man, you patted me down before,
and didn't find nothing.
You know me.
- Yeah, I know you.
Have a seat in your favorite chair.
Is this your weed I found in the car?
- Yeah, it's my bud and marijuana.
What's Mr. Handycam here doing?
- Oh, he's from the Junior College.
He's doing a short film
on cops and arrest.
- Shit, man, I was hoping
I was gonna be on TV.
- Yup, meet Jimmy, an
out-of-work drug dealer,
this week on "The Real World".
Now, is there anything else in this car
you wanna tell me about before I find it?
- Yeah, I got nothing to hide, officer.
- You should've just told me.
- Ain't my weapon, man.
- We both know you carry a
weapon, you fucking scumbag.
Hey, edit that part.
Get a shot of his dope
or gun, or something.
Let's go.
Fuck, get up!
- No, no!
- Get up!
- No!
- Now, fuck!
You have the right--
- All right!
- Let's go.
- [Narrator] When you're dealing drugs,
you don't have to put out the sign
that most who don't last do.
It's as if customers can
smell you out themselves.
But look at me, I fucked up.
I guess we all do sometime with this.
- Dave, dude, come on man!
- He's not here, man.
- It's Jimmy.
- What do you want?
- I go something for him.
- Yeah?
- How's it going, Krystal?
- Okay.
So, what do you got?
- What I have.
- Why don't you just give it to me,
and I'll get Dave to pay you later?
Come on, dude!
- Nah, I need 60 bucks.
- I'll give you part of the money.
I'll give you 40, and Dave will
pay you later for the rest.
Come on.
- Come on,
just score me another 20.
- Come on, man!
Hand it over.
- Nah, another 20.
Come on, I need it.
- Hold on.
Shit, man.
It's all I can do.
- It's all right.
So, see you later, all right?
Thanks.
- Okay, dude.
- [Narrator] Poor Davis,
I've known him my whole life.
He's always been a little ahead of me,
with him being Brandon's age.
I hung out with him more
than Brandon did, though.
Ford's been dealing local
shit since he was born.
He farms it out.
He made the mistake in spotting me.
I messed up, and used the
most of what he gave me.
(pager beeping)
(phone ringing)
- [Ford] Hello?
- Hey, Ford, it's Jimmy.
- [Ford] Hey, Jimmy, where you been?
I've been looking for you.
- You know, here and
there, doing business.
- [Ford] Cool, we need to get together,
get things straightened out.
- Yeah, sure.
- [Ford] You didn't use all
the shit, did you, Jimmy?
- What, now, who said that?
- [Ford] That's what I hear.
- Yeah, well, you heard wrong.
- [Ford] I hope so.
- It ain't about that, you know me.
- [Ford] Okay, look, let's meet
in the grove by the old boat
in about 20 minutes, and talk about this.
- Okay.
- [Ford] See you there.
- Yeah, see you there.
- [Narrator] Looking back,
I let it all go too far.
Geez, why did I keep going deeper,
when I was already drowning?
It seems ridiculous now
that I went to meet Ford at the old boat
that was once our fort
when we were little kids.
Brandon and I used to
play with Ford there.
We never did know who owned that boat.
Isn't that funny?
- Lotta memories here, huh, dude?
- Yeah.
I remember, I learned about this place
from you older kids, man.
- This is the first place
I ever got stoned, dude.
- Yeah, me too.
In fact, you were there.
- That's why I wanted to meet here, Jimmy.
It's like we all come from the same place.
- From the rack?
- I guess so.
So, why are you packing?
- Hey, man, I just didn't take
it out before I came over.
- Not too cool for a
man who just got busted
for a concealed weapon.
Besides, old Brandon would
kick your ass if he knew.
- Hey, this ain't got
nothing to do with Brandon.
- Easy, dude, relax.
- Hey, man, he don't know
shit about what I do now.
He's a schoolboy, and
that's that, all right?
- You've always been a
temperamental kid, Jimmy.
So, how are you gonna pay be me back?
I mean, ain't nobody
spotting me a thing, dude.
- I'll get it to you.
- I need it today, Jimmy.
It's been too long, and too
many people have been talking.
- So, are you fucking threatening me?
- Look, we don't have
to play like this, dude.
This isn't the big city, man,
so we don't have to play like that.
There's just not that much competition.
Get the money by today.
- Yeah, I'll have it by tonight.
- Just don't make me
look like a fool, dude.
I always wondered what she'd
be like on the ocean, man.
- She'd be like a boat, man.
- You know, you've always
been a weird one, Jimmy.
Maybe you're the one who
should be at school, man.
Some kind of philosopher,
or something like that.
Sure you couldn't give me
a little something, dude?
- Yeah, I got things
going later, all right?
- It's gotta be today, thought, Jimmy.
Keep me informed, all right?
Call me.
I don't want this to become a problem.
(brooding rock music)
- [Narrator] I wish this was all a dream.
Maybe that's all life is, is a dream.
If I could wake up, then
my life would start.
But it's not.
When did this safe place
become so dangerous?
You know what they say,
when everything goes wrong, that's right.
(heart pounding)
- You're fucking nothing.
Go on, cry, you little piece of shit, cry!
Here, drink up,
'cause that's all the fuck
there is in this life, boy.
You either drink it the fuck down,
or it's gonna fucking drink you down.
Oh, no?
Yeah, boy.
(lively rock music)
♪ You should've seen
the one that got away ♪
♪ It must have weighed about 110 ♪
- [Narrator] He's the
only person I've felt
truly close to most of my
life, my brother Brandon.
I should've followed him
out of all this mess.
It got a friend of ours, Frankie, killed.
But I always felt like he
left me, but he really didn't.
It's sort of crackup to think this guy
that has sold drugs and done drugs
is sitting there taking a college test.
Why not, right?
I wish I coulda talked to him.
I miss all the fun I had with him.
We had such good times at the old boat.
- I wanna take this boat
with us, though, man.
I dig this boat.
It's like--
(Brandon laughing)
What the hell you
laughing at anyways, man?
- You, man.
I swear, Pop beat your ass too many times
when we were growing up, dude.
- Man, I used to think about all the ways
I could kill him when I was little.
I was too scared then, though.
Most of the time, I wish I would've.
- Yeah, I thought about it, too, man.
I don't know, he's our
old man, though, you know?
Sometimes I wish he'd died in
the war, and that Mom hadn't.
- Fuck, man, half the time
I wish I wasn't even born,
you know?
I got no reason for fucking anything.
- No, man, you can't think like that.
It'll drive you crazy.
Besides, it don't do no good.
Everybody thinks like that sometimes.
- Yeah, but where are we going?
- Anywhere but here.
In fact, I tell you what.
Put a hitch on your car,
and we'll take this boat
wherever we go, man.
- Cool, we could just go till
we like somewhere, you know?
- [Narrator] Yeah, that
boat wasn't going nowhere,
and neither were we.
- Hey, Jimmy.
- Hey, Erica, how's it going?
- What's up, you looking for Aly?
- Nah.
- Looking for Brandon?
- Hmm-mm.
- Enrolling in class?
- Hey, maybe I just came to see you.
- Coming to the party tonight?
- Nah.
- Well, then you won't see me.
- Huh, yeah, see you later, all right?
- That's were I'm gonna be.
(brooding rock music)
- [Narrator] Yeah, that's when I really
should've thought of a game plan.
Instead, I was headed over
to Chris' to get stoned,
get me to relax, help me think.
Duh!
- What you think, man?
- Shit, it's the best in the country, man.
- I'm finally relaxing, man.
You want some more?
- So, are you gonna
tell me what's going on
with you and Ford, or what, dude?
- Wanna buy my car?
- Just ain't got no money, man.
- Yeah.
Me neither, man, that's the problem.
- Ah, so you do owe Ford.
- Yeah, man.
- Jimmy, man, don't fuck with Ford.
Dude, he's out trying to make
it big in this shit, man.
Watch your back, dude.
- Check this out, man.
I'm carrying.
- Shit, dude, put that thing back, man,
before my mom comes back and
has a heart attack, dude.
I got enough problems with her thinking
I'm too old to be living
here and all, man.
- Hey, I'm sorry, man.
- It's cool.
It's just, you know, she will
get weird about that, man.
- Yeah, your mom has always
been real cool to Brandon and I.
- Yeah, you guys did an
awesome snow job on her, man.
She says to me,
"Why can't you be more
like Brandon and Jimmy?"
- Yeah, well, at least like Brandon.
- So, how much you owe, dude?
- Eight.
- $800?
How much you got?
- Well, I got about
100 I can come up with.
- You gotta come up with $700, dude?
- No, man, don't worry about it.
- Shit, dude, you'll get
your ass kicked, man.
Even worse if you don't
so something about it.
Ford's got too many friends
to be starting that shit, man.
I'll see what I can come up with, man.
But you see what you
can come up with, dude,
and I'll fucking get you some help, man.
- Man, you're fucking
stoneder than me, man.
- Dude, so at least
I'm thinking here, man.
- Yeah, all right, Super Fly.
- Man, fuck you.
I am trying to help you,
and you get fucking racial
and shit on me, man.
- I'm sorry, man.
- That's better, dude,
show fucking gratitude.
- You got any more of this shit?
- Fuck, dude, I'm floating here, man.
- Yeah.
Well, I guess I better get
up and get myself going here,
and look for this money.
- I'll get you half by tonight, dude.
- How much is that?
- I'll get you 400 tonight.
- Thanks, man.
- No problem.
Dude, I can't wait for
that party tonight, man.
- Catch you later, man.
- All right, amigo.
Take care, dude.
- [Narrator] Pride?
I don't know.
Alls I know is that
was $300 I didn't have.
That's when I started getting
some real stupid ideas.
I've always found more trouble
to get me out of trouble.
(ignition whirring)
(brooding rock music)
- [Cashier] Howdy.
- [Jimmy] Give me your fucking money!
- What?
What?
- I ain't gonna hurt you.
Give me your fucking money.
Do something!
- I can't help you.
- Fuck, give me the money!
- What are you talking about?
- Give me the fucking money!
- I can't open the drawer.
- Do something!
- What's your member number?
I can't open the drawer without a number.
- Fucking do something!
- I'm sorry, I can't help you.
- Ah!
- [Narrator] I always dream
what it would've been like
to have my mother.
I envy everyone that has one.
(melancholy music)
I love playing with Alyssha's dogs.
The collie's name is Dusty,
and the Australian
shepherd's name is Clint.
Pretty cool, huh?
Everybody should have a dog.
They're better than people.
♪ It drains the blood from your veins ♪
- [Narrator] Boy, we've
had some good times here.
I remember, when I first met Alyssha,
Brandon and his girl, Kim,
were thinking I might go to school
if they fix me up with
some sexy college girl.
It didn't work, but it was a helluva try.
♪ Everyone needs something ♪
♪ If they're gonna survive ♪
♪ This one needs a soul ♪
♪ Just to keep it alive ♪
♪ In the moment at hand ♪
♪ In the shrapnel and the dirt ♪
♪ Vows are exchanged ♪
♪ And pleasantries rehearsed ♪
- [Narrator] Sometimes I
didn't treat her right,
and yet, other times, there's
no one I'd rather be with.
♪ This one don't move or breathe ♪
♪ Till you give it a fix ♪
♪ This one goes to market ♪
♪ This one went to bed with
someone that you know ♪
♪ This one keeps you warm at night ♪
- [Narrator] I like sneaking
over to Alyssha's house
to crash during the day.
It's such a quiet, comfortable place.
Nobody's ever there.
Alyssha's a girl from a
small Australian town.
Hmm, that's what I like,
that she's different.
♪ This one eats souls ♪
♪ All souls alive ♪
- [Narrator] Her room always
smelled so good, felt so good.
Why was I always so angry with her?
- I'm just trying to talk to you.
- Shut up.
- You won't even listen to me.
- Shut the fuck up, Alyssha.
- Fuck you!
- Go ahead.
- I'm really getting sick of this, Jimmy.
- What, are you getting sick of me?
- I didn't say that!
- Well, what the fuck did you say, then?
Don't talk down to me.
- Look, why don't you leave?
- What, you can tell me when I can leave?
- Just--
(melancholy music)
- [Narrator] I wanted to love
her, but I never knew how.
I still don't entirely.
I mean, she's so beautiful,
and I can be mean, even without trying.
I had a way of shutting her
down, shutting everyone down.
(brooding rock music)
How could I be mad?
It was loving, everyone I wish I was.
Showing your real self.
I don't know, lesson learned.
♪ I am feeling ♪
♪ Just a little down ♪
♪ Nothing I can ♪
- Anyway, he's just too
young to understand.
- He understands, you just
don't understand, old man.
- Hey, I ain't no old man!
(brooding rock music)
Hey.
- Hey, what's up?
- I guess your brother
should be coming home
pretty soon, huh?
- Yup, pretty soon.
Why are you dressed like that?
- Would you believe, an old friend of mine
got me a job interview today, Jim?
I mean, there's no openings.
Maybe a couple of weeks, a month or so.
At least I still get my checks, huh?
- Yeah, Pop.
Maybe soon, huh?
- Yeah.
Yeah, this country, they don't
care about the vet, Jimmy.
I mean, it's a joke.
I mean, you can see Vietnam vets standing
on every street corner, man,
with a sign, begging for money.
It's a joke.
- Yeah, I've seen 'em, except,
you know, I always figured
about half 'em were faking it.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, some probably are.
I mean, that's what even makes
it a bigger joke, eh, Jim?
- You want a beer, Pop?
- Yeah, yeah, give me a beer, Jim.
Yeah.
- Okay.
- [Narrator] I can't believe
I missed the best chance
I ever had to talk to my father.
He wasn't drunk.
He was open, I can see that now.
I guess I was still too worried
about the money and shit.
Could I have told my dad?
No, never, not in a million
years would I do that.
- You know, I didn't ask
to be your father, Jimmy.
- Yeah, ditto.
- What the fuck does that mean, ditto?
What does that mean?
- Man, you wanna know what that means?
- Yeah, I wouldn't have asked if I didn't.
- Why is it always a question,
and never an answer from you?
You wanna know what it means?
- Yeah, I wanna know!
- Hey, man, it means,
you ain't never had time
for me, so I'm never
gonna have time for you.
- Hey, fuck you.
I brought you into this world.
- Fuck you!
Some luck, huh?
- Hey, son.
Come on, sit down.
Jimmy over here was just telling me
how much he doesn't need
me, ain't that right, Jimbo?
- That's not what I said.
- What's going on?
- The same old shit.
Every time we try to start talking,
he jumps all over me, man.
He's crazy, I told ya.
- Yeah, I'm crazy, so the fuck what?
- You see?
I'd have never talked
to my father that way.
Never, no matter what age.
- Just drop it, okay, Pop?
- And who in the fuck are you?
Hey, come on, sport, I'm only kidding.
- Yeah.
- Come on, get back here.
And you can get the hell out
of my house any time, you know?
Hello, is anybody listening over here?
Is anybody listening?
- [Narrator] What is it with my family
that makes us all so
cruel with each other?
I guess it was the lack
of a mother's hand.
Closest thing I had to a mother
was a few different girlfriends Pop had
while we were growing up.
I guess my real mom was Brandon.
He'd be sore if anybody said that,
but he was a pretty good mom.
- Hey, what are you doing in my room?
- This was my room first, man.
- Yeah, well, it's mine now.
- No, no, I'm just letting
you borrow it, man.
It's really still mine.
- Yeah, right.
- You ever think about giving
him a break sometimes, man?
- Hey, I gave him a break my
whole life, you know that.
- Yeah, I know that.
But he's older now,
man, he's not the same.
- Look, I know what you're trying to do,
but don't defend him.
- I'm just tired of all the fighting, man.
It's all bullshit.
- Yeah, well, I've been
fighting for 23 years.
You know what they say, we're
like that MTV generation shit.
Immediate gratification.
- Oh, man, don't give me that bullshit.
- I was just fucking with you.
- Yeah, I know.
But next, you'll say some shit
like my fucking professors
about our generation again.
- Hey, man, give me all
the credit, why don't you?
- Credit, shit, no, I
ain't giving you no credit.
- What the fuck is a generation, anyways?
Brandon, um, I need to
tell you something, man.
Tonight, you know, after
I see how things work out.
- Yeah, sure.
If you don't go to that
party, then whenever, man.
All right?
- Yeah.
- Is it good news or bad news?
- Is your girlfriend going to the party?
- Of course.
I saw Alyssha today at school.
She still thinks we're gonna
get your ass there, man.
- Yeah, well, you can
believe in some things.
It's just, I believe some
things ain't ever gonna happen.
- You're so fucking smart to
say things like that, man.
I don't get you sometimes.
- Yeah, nobody does.
Hey, man, don't hurt yourself.
- Yeah, I'll try not.
You know, things would
be a whole lot easier
if you'd just help me out a little, man.
- Yeah, well, I learn all
I need to on the radio.
- [Brandon] Yeah, I guess
you probably can, at that.
Later.
- Yeah.
(Jimmy laughing)
- [Narrator] If I ever was to be a father,
I'd never say half the stupid things
my father has said to us
daily while growing up.
It's just some shit that will never end
if some just don't stop it.
(Nick laughing)
- Oh, man, I don't want no
fucking niggers in my house.
Not in my fucking house!
God, what the fuck are
the neighbors gonna think?
I don't want the fucking
niggers in my fucking house!
Man, I don't want the fucking world
knowing about what I'm doing,
just because you're gonna be
smoking some wacky tobaccy
with these black motherfuckers.
Get 'em the fuck outta here, now!
I don't fucking want 'em here.
(pager beeping)
- Damn!
Yeah, it's Jimmy.
Yeah, I'm working things.
Hey, look, man, I said
I'll get your money, man.
Yeah, I said I'll have it.
Look.
Come on, man, why are you
fucking with me like this?
What?
Hey, big deal, I haven't called you.
You fuck, you wanna
threaten me, you fucking?
What, kill me?
You wanna kill me?
Why don't you try, you
fucking pencil dick?
Hey, man, fuck you, don't
call me again, all right?
Yeah, I said I'll get your money.
(phone beeping)
Boom!
Boom, boom, boom!
- What are you fucking doing?
- Nothing, man.
- Are you tripping on me?
- Nothing, I was just playing, man.
- Come on, is that shit loaded?
- No.
- You need a hobby, bro.
- Shit, I got a hobby, man.
I'm a cowboy, and you're an Indian.
- You watch way too much TV, man.
You oughta try reading some time.
- You ever think about living and stuff?
- As little as possible
when I'm studying, man.
- Yeah, but what are you studying for?
I mean, you're just gonna die
in the end anyways, right?
- Slow down, man.
Look, I gotta get back to
my studying, all right?
You know, man, you shouldn't
say things like that.
You know, it's like bad karma or something
to say shit like that.
- Yeah, you better get
back to your studies.
Hey, sorry.
- [Narrator] I've always
been a daydreamer,
even when I was little.
It's the place I always wanted.
I always got the girl, always
was the hero, whatever.
I really dig thinking wild like this.
(brooding rock music)
- I've always been faster than you, dude.
- Yeah, at least I hit what I aim at.
And your momma's faster than both of us.
- Oh, that's.
(gunshot banging)
You missed me, you missed me!
(gunshots banging)
- [Narrator] I think of
some crazy shit sometimes.
I just wish it was all so simple.
Brandon and I had fun when we were little.
We were always playing cowboys
and Indians, and stuff.
Reality hit when a friend of ours died,
messing with all the same stuff we were.
Frankie OD'd, some said it was suicide.
I can't say I haven't thought of it too.
I never cried so hard in my whole life.
But instead of going like Brandon,
who turned his shit around in a heartbeat,
I just got deeper.
I started using all my own stuff.
I haven't been clearheaded for so long.
What good is it anyways?
I should've done it like Brandon,
and got the hell outta Dodge.
I went around that afternoon
and called on every favor I could,
borrowing money to pay for borrowed goods.
I came up with $350, and with Chris' half,
I should've been home free.
I thought Ford would
even spot me the cash.
Yeah, I just never took to
being threatened very well.
(lively rock music)
♪ I'm looking back on
stupid things I've said ♪
♪ Was that really me or was I misled ♪
♪ Not even a smile 'cause
it's been done before ♪
♪ And you don't think it's funny anymore ♪
♪ Crying, "I'm sorry,
I'm out of my head" ♪
♪ End up fixing junk instead ♪
♪ Taken too much, I got nothing to give ♪
♪ I got no reason left to live ♪
♪ Stupid kid, you don't really know ♪
♪ I'm a time bomb, and I'm ready to blow ♪
♪ Is it really fair it's
not up to you to decide ♪
♪ But hitting your arm is slow suicide ♪
♪ Crying, "I'm sorry I'm out of my head" ♪
♪ End up fixing junk instead ♪
♪ I've taken too much,
I got nothing to give ♪
♪ I got no reason left to live ♪
- You gotta relax, Jim.
What happened, man?
- Man, he's fucking just pulled up on me,
and just drove me off the road, man.
- Damn!
- Dude, it's fucking crazy, man.
He got out of his car, came running back,
and I just fucking drilled his ass.
- Dude, you beat him bad?
- Fuck, man, I kicked his ass bad.
- Fuck.
- Fuck, this tastes good.
- No problem, man.
- Thanks.
- Look, dude, I got your 400,
but it looks like we need
someone to talk to Ford,
and calm him down now.
I mean, it's a whole nother thing, dude.
Dude, maybe we can have
Brandon talk to him.
- No, no, man.
I can't fucking bring
Brandon into this shit again.
I'm always bringing him into this.
- But that's your brother, though, man.
I mean, he should be able to do something.
- Lay off, all right?
- Yeah, sure, man.
Dude, let's just go to the party,
and have a good time tonight, man
Come on, man, this shit'll pass, dude.
(brooding rock music)
- [Narrator] I should've just left town.
I got some help from those who
coulda helped me out of this.
Shit, everybody gets in
over their head sometime.
- You're not really thinking
about carrying your gun
to the party, are you, Jimmy?
- Hell, no, man, I'm just making my bed.
- Uh-huh.
Shit, I know this makes
you uncomfortable, man,
but she is your girlfriend, and besides,
Chris and I will be there.
What could happen?
Dude, something like
bringing a gun to a party,
and you're bound to find trouble.
Shit, it might even find you.
- Yeah, what could happen?
- I know you're still mad at
me for going to school, man,
but one of these days,
we gotta talk this out.
Something's going on with you.
I know it and you know it.
Still, you won't tell me.
- Come on, I said, later, let's talk.
- Well, it should be a
good party tonight, man.
- Yeah, well, any party's a good party.
- You got any money on
you for tonight, man?
- No, not very much.
- Now, don't go weird on me now.
And don't sweat that, I'll
catch the beer tonight.
(heart pounding)
(Jimmy coughing)
- Hell, the only time it matters
what people talk about you
is when you die.
Do you wanna know what
they'd say about you
if you died today, huh?
They'd say you're a fucking loser.
A smart-ass, fucking
slopping dressing, slacking,
no-good fucking drug-dealing loser.
(heart pounding)
(Jimmy coughing)
(upbeat music)
- Yeah, Brandon, man,
you said you were gonna
introduce me to Erica
when we get to that party, man.
- Yeah, man, I'll take care of it.
- Hey.
- Thanks.
- Ladies first.
- Yeah, well, get your
ass in the car then.
(engine roaring)
Yo, man, listen to this,
I love this song, man.
(upbeat rock music)
Hey, man, keep your beers down.
I don't need to get no DUI, man.
- Yeah, Jimmy, you gotta
watch getting a DUI.
- You guys are crazy.
Just keep your beers down, all right?
- Hey, Brando, why don't
we just go up to the hills,
and have a few beers, fuck the party?
- No, man, we do that, we'll
have a couple of chicks
really pissed off at us
when we show up, man.
- Hey, hey, hey, Jimmy.
You tell him yet, dude?
- Tell me what, man?
- Hey, it's nothing.
- No, come on, tell me what?
Look, some bullshit's been
going on all night, man.
Tell me what?
Look, you can't tease me like that, man.
- It's nothing, dude.
We just got ahold of this,
this huge doobie today, man.
We smoked it this afternoon,
homes, it's nothing.
- Yeah, right.
♪ Do right, you do right,
do right, you do right ♪
♪ Right, you do right,
♪ Do right, you do right,
do right, you do right ♪
♪ Do right, you do right ♪
- Man, let's kill these
beers, and get in there.
- I knew there was
something good about summer.
All the women wear less.
- Dude, there's nothing more beautiful
than women in bathing suits, man.
- Yeah.
- I mean, a naughty one, too.
- Yeah, I think I'd rather have
my women naked in the pool.
- Dude's got a point there, man.
- Naked women in a pool, man, that's hot.
(engine revving)
- Well, what do say we do this thing, huh?
Tell you what, why don't
you put the empties
in the bag back there,
and I'll take in the rest of the beer.
- Oh, yeah, Brandon gets
the good stuff, man.
We get to carry empty bottles.
- Yeah, well, that's
'cause I'm older, man.
- Dude, you're a mean old man.
- Well, if you guys are good,
I'll let you share some.
(upbeat rock music)
- Will you stop worrying,
he's gonna be here.
- I know, yeah, yeah, I know, I know.
I don't care, it doesn't matter.
- He's even been pretty cool lately.
I mean, he took us to lunch last week,
and he gave you a card.
- Well, that sounds really good to me.
And Brandon will make
sure he comes anyways.
Chris is never gonna miss a party.
- That's true.
- I just think something's
up with Jimmy, you know?
Something wrong.
I just feel it.
- Listen to her, she can just--
- Shut up!
(girls laughing)
- Wait, she's got a fluke
coming down into her.
(girls laughing)
He's gonna be here.
- I don't care, I don't care.
- It has been nice lately, huh?
- Sorry, Jimmy, you think I'm stupid.
- No, that's all right, thanks.
- Hey, how's it going, Chris?
- Hey, it's going great, Kim.
- Oh, I'm sorry, Erica, this
is Chris, Chris, this is Erica.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- It's good to meet you.
- [Erica] I've heard a lot about you.
- Thanks.
I hear there's gonna be a really
cool band playing tonight.
- [Erica] Yeah, they're
supposed to be really good.
They're gonna start in a few minutes.
- Well, this is a cool party.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- Does anybody need another beer?
- Yeah, I could go for one.
- Yeah, let's get another beer.
- I'm up for that.
- So, is everything okay?
You just seem a bit uptight.
- Yeah.
- You didn't even call me, though.
- Well, I was busy.
- Do you wanna talk about it?
- Look, later, okay?
- You okay with all these
strange people you don't know?
- Yeah, well, they are kinda strange.
- You're strange.
- Thanks.
It's a nice party you
got going here, you know?
Your parents are pretty nice to do this.
- I'm old enough, and they trust me.
- Why?
- Yeah, well, what they don't
know won't hurt them, right?
Don't you think?
- Yeah.
- [Narrator] Nobody appreciates life
till it's taken away from them.
We don't treat it with
love, respect, you know?
I knew big trouble was coming,
trouble that I made myself,
my own worst enemy.
And watching all these people
seeming to have so much fun,
I wondered why I always
felt alone, an outsider.
Thinking about it, maybe I was wrong.
Maybe we're all outsiders,
maybe we're all alone.
Maybe the beauty is those
very few moments we're not.
(gunshot banging)
(brooding rock music)
(upbeat rock music)
- What are you doing smoking that?
Will you hurry up and
finish that off, please?
- I'm sorry.
I'm mean, we were having a few beers.
I thought it'd be a
nice time to get stoned.
- Well, I'm sorry, but, you know.
- It's cool, I mean, like,
you're not into that scene.
- Well, it's just--
- No, that's not it.
- She's just concerned that the cops
will show up, or something.
- Well, the cops aren't
gonna bother you too much
about one joint.
It's how many people here have them.
- See, now, that's what
makes me nervous, you know?
I mean, look at all these people here.
- Just kidding.
As long as you're not selling,
you don't have to worry about it.
- Yeah, we'll see.
- Which is good anyway.
- Cool.
- Just don't do it here, you know?
Did you talk to him?
- Where's Jimmy?
- I think he's playing pool, I think.
- He seems really sad.
Is there something wrong with him?
- Nah, he'll be all right.
- He's okay.
- I hope that it's not me
that's making him act that way.
- It's not, you know that.
It's just, we haven't totally
gotten along in a while.
But I don't even think it's
me that's bothering him.
It's something else.
- He won't talk to anybody.
- [Brandon] He's a survivor,
he'll make out whatever it is.
- Man, I can't be quiet anymore, he's,
he's--
- He's what?
- [Brandon] Chill, man.
- Yeah, it's getting pretty fucked up.
Thanks, bro.
- Anytime, man.
- Here.
- Sorry, Jimmy.
- I need a soda, or something.
I'm getting a little too buzzed.
- Hey, no problem.
♪ I like the way you bleed ♪
♪ It brings you to my knees ♪
♪ It really breaks my heart ♪
♪ The way you fall apart ♪
♪ We tried to say goodbye ♪
♪ It's no good, you and I ♪
♪ I know we've had it hard ♪
♪ Taking things too far ♪
♪ I need a new thrill ♪
♪ Make me a deal ♪
♪ I can't sit still ♪
♪ I need a new thrill ♪
♪ Make me a deal ♪
♪ I can't sit still ♪
♪ I need a new thrill ♪
(crowd cheering)
- You're not gonna leave me, are you?
- Yeah, well, you'd be
better off if I did.
- So, you are gonna leave me?
- Come on, I didn't say that to you.
- You won't talk to me, or anything.
It's like you're mad at
the world, or something.
- It's not you, all right?
- Well, I'm glad you're not leaving me.
- Stop it!
God!
That's always the fucking answer?
- Well, I can't believe I'm
standing here telling you,
"I don't know what I'll do without you,"
and you say, "Stop it."
- I don't want you to depend on me
forever.
- You're so fucking cruel.
- I don't want you to
depend on me forever.
- I open myself up to you, and
you just slam the door shut.
I'm just a piece of ass, aren't I?
- No, that's not it.
That's not it.
- Why do I stand here and listen to you?
Do you know how many guys
would kill to be with me?
- Hell, I'd kill to be with you, too.
- Well, you're not
making any sense, Jimmy.
I'm confused, do you like to
confuse women, is that it?
- No, that's not it.
Hell, I don't even know
what's going on, I mean...
A lotta shit.
- What?
- A lotta shit's...
I don't know.
- Great.
- I'm sorry, okay?
- Yeah.
- You're so temperamental.
- Screw you!
- Yeah?
- You wanna spend the
night with me, Jimmy?
- You want me to?
- Yeah.
What's wrong?
- I gotta go somewhere
with Brandon to make this,
all this shit turn out right.
I'll come back, though.
- Good.
It's gonna be okay.
- So, why don't you talk to me?
- Hey, man, I owe Ford money.
- What for, shit?
Hey, why are you messing
around with a loser like that?
- I don't know, man, I was
trying to make some money.
- Don't sound like it.
How do you deal and owe, Jimmy?
- 'Cause I was buying more
than I was selling, man.
I don't know, man.
This fucking shit,
it got way outta hand, you know?
And you've been going to school, and shit.
- No, fucking don't blame this
shit on me, man, all right?
- I'm not.
- Well, how long you owed Ford then, huh?
- Hey, man, I kept thinking
I'd get ahead of it,
and it got way ahead of me.
- Why didn't you come to me, man?
- Hey, you know we haven't
been close for a long time.
- Yeah, maybe, but I am your
fucking older brother, huh?
- Yeah.
- So, what, you been using
since I went to school?
- No, I've been using since
Frankie killed himself.
- Man, why?
- I don't know, man,
maybe I fucking like how
it makes me feel, you know,
or doesn't make me feel.
What, man, fucking look at me.
- I'm fucking looking at you,
don't fucking be like that.
- You fucking worried what
other people are gonna think?
- Don't fucking be like that, all right?
- Fucking worried they're gonna
say I buy and sell cocaine?
- I don't give a shit about anybody else.
So, how bad is this with Ford, man?
- Yeah, well, it's real fucking bad.
- All right, how much
do you owe him, then?
- Hey, man, that's not
all there is to it, right?
- All right, well, what else then, huh?
- Hey, wait a second, man.
- What?
- Hold on.
What?
- Fuck.
- What, man?
You wanna fuck with my girl.
- Hey, Jimmy, please!
- Out of my way!
(lively rock music)
- Hey!
- Cut it out!
- [Alyssha] Wait, no, Jimmy!
Please, stop it, stop it!
- [Man] All right, come on,
right now, right now, let's go!
- Can you tell me why you did that?
- Hey, what am I supposed to do?
- A lotta guys would just be
proud, you know, it takes two.
Man, I didn't do anything.
Gimme some credit.
- Forget it, man.
- You can't just do stuff like that!
- Hey, leave me alone, man.
- [Narrator] I almost never cry.
I just bite the bullet,
however hopeless it is.
I mean, how hopeful is
a drug dealer after all?
I can't make excuses.
Why me, God?
Why couldn't I have been
rescued from all of this?
(melancholy rock music)
♪ Why are you here ♪
♪ Couldn't you tell him ♪
♪ Were you afraid he'd hear ♪
♪ You should've been
thankful to be alone ♪
♪ You took off your shoes ♪
♪ Said, anything further
would be bad news ♪
- [Narrator] I'd never been there,
but something told me to
go to my mother's grave.
I've always been too afraid to go.
I guess I was searching
for something last night.
Myself, my soul.
- Hey, Jimmy.
Jimmy!
(gunshot banging)
(dog barking)
- [Narrator] Is this all life is about?
I wish I could do it
again; I'd do it different.
I just realized, the big joke is,
we all wanna be immortal, and then die.
What about living our time here?
God, forgive me.
- Mom?
Fuck it.
Take the money in my pocket,
and spend it on your kid.
- [Woman] No, don't go.
(melancholy rock music)
- [Narrator] Death beckoned,
and I answered the call.
It ain't fair, but it's not so bad.
Life is for the living,
and I wasn't living.
I know that now.
Hey, don't forget me.
(gunshot banging)
(brooding rock music)
♪ Well, I woke up on the gravel ground ♪
♪ At the feet of a long, tall train ♪
♪ Rememb'ring not where I was from ♪
♪ Rememb'ring not my name ♪
♪ I thought of friends from years ago ♪
♪ In a youth I'd thrown away ♪
♪ And a girl who used to love me so ♪
♪ Though I couldn't recall her face ♪
♪ Then I realized I was only drunk ♪
♪ And the years were stripped away ♪
♪ I felt like a widower,
stoned, and watching ♪
♪ A film of his wedding day ♪
♪ She ran to the car with a T-shirt on ♪
♪ Her face as sad as the moon ♪
♪ Well, I was lost, and I was bummed ♪
♪ By the ghost of yet to come ♪
(upbeat rock music)
♪ There's a love we know ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ There's a love we know ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ And if you ever feel it ♪
♪ And you don't know what it is ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ There's a love ♪