[women] Get down now.
Get ready.
Let's do it, let's do it!
[radio DJ]
Our special guests,
ladies and gentlemen.
-In the studio,
the Queens of Comedy.
-Woo!
It ain't nothin' but a queen
thing this mornin', baby.
Hey, Memphis, this is Mo'Nique.
Interstate, this is the house
of the skins. Can I help you?
What's happenin', home biscuits?
This is Laura.
Oh, my God! Oh, shit!
Memphis, Tennessee,
Adele Givens. I'm such a lady.
Somethin' inappropriate
about taking off your skirt
with a picture of your baby
in your hand, isn't it?
-And this is Sommore again.
-What do they call that? Yeah.
And we are the Queens of Comedy!
And I'm table dancin' here!
-This is my table dance.
-That ass work, Mo'Nique.
That's how big girls dance.
We don't play that bullshit
all up in here.
Let's go!
-Let 'em have it!
-[Mo'Nique]  Tonight,
we're makin' history.
This is the first time
four women has been on stage
at one time makin' a movie.
[announcer]
Welcome to the Orpheum Theater
in Memphis, Tennessee!
And now, show your love
for the one and only Ms. Laura!
[cheering]
Hey!
What's goin' on, Memphis?
-[cheering]
-All right!
How good to see y'all again,
and, man, what a
beautiful theater.
Go ahead, y'all.
Y'all big-ballin' up in here.
Man, you better be glad
this ain't the '70s.
I'd be boostin' all this shit.
Woo, I guess y'all been doin'
all right, huh?
You're lookin' good.
Man, I been in trouble.
I got three grandchildren now.
Moe, Larry, and Curly.
Or should I say,
Leelee, Monie and Woowoo?
[laughter]
We be giving' 'em some names,
don't we?
Man, they came through the house
like little Tasmanian devils.
I got one, twelve,
who's forever on the telephone.
"Grandma, I got business."
I got one that's eight years old
that's forever askin' me
every question in the world.
Then there's that little ol'
15-month-old,
who can't say nothin' but...
[mimics baby]
Who thinks he's a gymnast
and is forever climbin'
and runnin' all over stuff.
And that little one
right in the middle,
Little Monie...
boy, I'm tellin' you she asks
a bunch of questions.
Always wants some money
for somethin'.
You know, I used to say "no"
to my kids easy, but sometimes
it's kinda hard to say "no"
to your grand-babies, you know?
She come walkin' up to me,
"Grandma...
can I have 30 dollars to see
pay-per-view?
I wanna see The Rock."
[cheering]
I'm not knowin'. I didn't know
who the fuck The Rock was.
I know he was a grown-ass man.
I was, like, "Baby, I'm not
givin' you thirty dollars for
no damn pay-per-view."
She said, "But, Grandma,
he is fine!"
I was, like, "What the fuck
you know about 'fine'?"
"Grandma, don't cuss.
That's not nice."
"You right, baby. You right.
What the hell you know
about fine?"
"Grandma, I'll go get you
a picture, okay?"
"Well, go get the damn thing,
then."
She come back,
showed me the picture...
I say, "Goddamn."
"This motherfucker is fine."
"Well, look,
Grandma got thirty."
I'm gonna have to take this time
to just talk to y'all
for a minute, Memphis,
'cause I need to tell y'all
how much I appreciate you.
Because only in Memphis...
Oh, this is so emotional.
Only in Memphis,
can a bitch like me
walk into a hair salon
where they do hair and nails,
and make a request like...
My two big-toes is ugly,
and I just wanna know,
as my sister,
will you put two
fake fingernails
on my big toenails
-so my feet will look good?
-I sure will. No problem.
See?
Did you ever take a class
in puttin' fingernails on toes?
Just that--
Was you ever trained?
That never happened, did it?
-But you know what?
-That-- You ain't never
done that before.
You're a goddamn,
guinea-pig monkey. Pig!
They just mad.
See, they already have
pretty big-toes.
I don't.
She gave me the finger
with the monkey-feet.
I'm talkin' to you
as a friend...
and a Queen of Comedy.
I want you...
[laughs] to take them
monkey feet...
[both laughing]
...out of the bucket.
Please?
Can we have security
on the property?
How about this?
I'm gonna be able
to bat my eyes like Bette Davis.
Ms. Laura's goin' through
the change of life
and she wanted to try
a new experiment
and get single eyelashes.
Nobody's eyelashes
are that long.
You look crazy!
You look like a bunny.
They ran out of short,
black ones in the store.
They have ran out of lashes.
Did you hear that?
Cut them down off of my sister
and glue 'em on that eye.
That's what this is all about.
Feelin' good about yourself,
even if you got one eyelash.
You don't come over here 'cause
I don't trust you. [laughs]
Get away from me.
Hold up. Wait a minute.
Hey, is the security
still out there?
The two by the door?
Okay, cool.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
Ex-husband in town.
[laughter]
Motherfucker get
a Vietnam flashback,
come lookin' for me.
I don't know why
he'd wanna fuck with me.
I come from a big
family of girls.
My daddy didn't play.
He raised us tough, baby.
He was like, "I ain't raisin'
no punk bitches."
And you couldn't go to my daddy
with what he called
"sissy shit," you know?
"Daddy, can we go outside
and play with Barbie?"
"Fuck Barbie."
"Better get your ass out there
and build me a sofa."
And he taught us
to stick together, too.
You marry one of us,
you marry all of us.
Okay? And when
there's some problems,
we'll get together, baby.
'Cause Moms is the Dispatcher.
My little sister got in trouble,
she had to call Mama.
[crying] "Mama, this--
this nigga hit me."
Woo. Mama was cool, though.
She's like,
"Don't worry about it, baby."
Moms hung-up the phone,
dialed one number,
all our phones rang.
"Bertha, Laura, Uela, Ruthie?
Get on over to Alice's house.
That nigga done gone crazy."
That's all we needed.
We jumped in the car.
We rollin'.
We slappin' five over the seat.
"Here, bitch. Hit this. Shit!"
Get to the house,
screech up real fast,
walk in the door.
The nigga just about
to hit my sister. We go,
"No, not tonight, motherfucker!"
"Nigga, what?"
"Nigga, what? Nigga, who?"
Uh-uh.
We ain't play that.
No, baby.
I have no shame in my game.
I got 40 or 50 of these at home.
Oh, baby, yeah.
I'll fix it up better
when I get in the back but...
I was young and wild.
Now, I could do this shit
in the dark.
My drawers might be on backwards
but this hair gonna be straight.
Memphis!
Yeah!
Coming to you,
all the way from
the queendom of Chicago.
From The Tracy Ullman Show,
the Queen of Comedy
from Def Comedy Jam.
-She's such a fuckin' lady.
-[audience] ...lady!
Memphis...
welcome...
Queen Adele!
["Three Strikes"
by Kelly Price playing]
What's up, Memphis, Tennessee?
Yeah! Do I look like
a fuckin' lady or what?
[all] Yeah!
I am so glad
y'all decided to join
The Queens of Come  tonight!
So glad I see so many queens
in the house
with me tonight. Hey!
See?
Now, ladies, that love
that y'all just gave me,
I want you to give it
to your damn selves.
That's right, 'cause y'all know
we been bullshittin'
for the last few years
and we gonna stop that.
We've been trippin' about flaws.
A flaw ain't shit but a unique
identifyin' mark.
Everybody got a flaw.
If you get a big belly,
rub that motherfucker.
Love it.
Ladies, let me tell you
somethin' tonight. I don't care
what's wrong with you
or how fucked up you think
you are, somebody love yo' ass.
Hear me?
That's right.
So, if you're buck-toothed,
bitch, relax.
Chill out, bucky baby,
you gonna be all right.
'Cause I bet there's a man
in the house right now
don't want nothin' less
than a bitch who can
bite an apple
through a picket-fence,
I swear to God.
That's right.
I want you to quit
disrespectin' yourselves,
ladies.
Quit trippin'
'bout little bitty flaws,
all right?
I don't give a shit
what's goin' on.
If you're cockeyed, find a man
who had a stroke, goddamn it.
That's right.
You cockeyed, he's sideways.
Y'all the perfect
goddamn couple. What?
Shit.
We can't trip no more.
Know that you are beautiful.
I don't give a damn what.
Understand that.
You know what happened.
We started gettin' tricked
by these magazines and these
televisions.
These bitches is
trip-trickin' you.
You think you can live up
to them celebrity bitches,
don't you?
Well, it can't happen
'cause the hoes ain't real.
You know,
they build them bitches.
You know that.
Buyin' titties,
which I don't understand.
Why you go and buy titties
when you got socks at home?
Ladies, these hoes are not
made out of the same stuff
you made out of.
You a real woman,
them bitches are not.
They there to entertain
your ass.
You know they ain't made
outta your shit
'cause you read about 'em
goin' to the hospital
for shit like
exhaustion and dehydration.
Now,
what bitch you know so tired,
she gotta go to hospital?
I know some exhausted bitches.
I know some women got two jobs,
six kids, no man.
The bitch got things to do.
You hear me?
She gotta go to PTA meetings,
after-school programs,
football practice,
riverboat casino...
This bitch is exhausted.
She ain't goin' no hospital.
She can't. Who gonna watch them
bad-ass children when she gone?
In the real world, when you
get exhausted, you take
a fuckin' nap, don'tcha?
You stop lettin' them
bitches trick you,
'cause they will trick you,
and they'll use
your kids to trick you.
You see these commercials
where they got kids
now tryin' to fuck
with your self-esteem.
But it's all about attitude.
I saw this one
Jenny Craig commercial,
this woman comes out there
all distraught and fucked up
talkin' about,
"I knew I had to do something,
because I woke up one morning
and my daughter said,
'Mommy, you're fat.'
And I knew
I had to do something.
So, I picked up that phone
and I called Jenny Craig."
You know, they flip the screen,
she come back, like,
two weeks later.
"I lost 15 pounds on Jenny Craig
and I feel great."
I say "Yeah, that's good, bitch,
but you need a new attitude."
'Cause had that been me
on that commercial,
it would've went the same way
with a different attitude.
I'd a said, "Well, I knew
I had to do somethin'
because I woke up one morning
and my daughter said,
'Mommy, you're fat.'
And I knew
I had to do something.
[laughter]
So I picked up that phone
and I knocked that little bitch
down a flight of stairs.
I whupped her little ass
that day.
Told her, 'You're the reason
why Mama's so fuckin' fat!
Carryin' your little
bald-head ass around
for nine months.'
I beat her so long,
I lost 15 pounds
and now I feel great."
Right foot!
Left foot!
-I don't know how to do it.
-All right, now.
Now, cha-cha now.
Turn around.
You don't wanna go to work
all messed up. You want
your shit lookin' good.
Now, we gonna need us some
Versace housekeepin' outfits.
Yeah, this is the shit.
Now, watch.
Watch this come in style, y'all.
People gonna be wearin' it,
talkin' about,
-"Girl, this the
housekeepin' shit."
-Okay.
Remember the 11th commandment.
-Finders keepers,
losers weepers.
-[all] ...losers weepers.
-Have a happy
housekeepin', ladies.
-Yeah.
Ooh, he threw a kiss at me.
Back to you, sweetheart.
They so nice in Memphis.
Or is this is the ho-stroll?
Is this the ho-stroll?
Am I a hooker?
Men throwin' kisses at me
and offerin' me money.
They might not recognize me.
I might just be
where the hookers be at.
Is this where they buy
the coochie at?
Music is pure entertainment.
Sometimes,
they got a good message. Great.
But a lotta times
it's just for your
fun and enjoyment.
Now TLC made "No Scrubs"
and we treated
that bullshit like
some sort of national anthem,
didn't we?
Man tryin' to talk to you
and you got your hand
all in his face,
No, I don't want your number
Y'all gonna fuck around,
miss your man
with that bullshit.
[laughter]
That's what's gonna happen.
You can't listen to TLC.
How you gonna take love advice
from a bitch named Left Eye?
You ask that ho about
a contact lens or somethin'.
Don't ask her about no man.
It ain't like she got a history
of harmony in her own
goddamn relationships, is it?
Ain't that the same one
that burned up her scrub-tub?
Don't fuck around with TLC.
They contradicted
their own selves.
'Cause I know they singin'
they don't want no scrubs.
That's 'cause they got
this 10-million-dollar
record deal,
but a few years ago
when their ass was bankrupt,
they wasn't too proud to beg,
was they?
They was creepin' and shit,
wasn't they?
You caught them hoes
on the right day
at the right time.
You got the red-light special,
didn't ya?
I wasn't impressed, no way,
'cause that shit sounded
like a joke that I wrote.
All you have to do
is break out them old
Def Comedy Jam  tapes.
I'm the bitch on there sayin',
"Hey ladies,
why is it when
there's two brothers in a car,
it's always the one
on the passenger side
that says,
'Hey, baby. You want a ride?'"
And I say, "What the fuck
I'mma do, take your place?
Ain't you gettin' a ride?"
These heifers put music to it,
got a hit record,
they ain't gave me
a fuckin' nickel.
When they find Left Eye,
I'm suin' the bitch
for that right eye she got.
That's what's gonna happen.
Crazy-ass people,
crazy-ass world.
I know why this world crazy,
too. I been checkin' this
bullshit out.
You know why we fucked up?
'Cause we eatin' them fuckin'
Oodles of Noodles, that's why.
Ramen noodles, Roman noodles,
you know what the fuck
I'm talkin' about.
That shit ain't lunch.
When you had spam,
you didn't do no crazy shit.
Now you got some bullshit
that all it takes is water,
three minutes,
only cost a dime a pack.
That's a trap,
that ain't no fuckin' meal.
And it ain't just the kids,
you know.
That's why I'm glad
my grandmother was here
until she was 92,
'cause she balanced
this crazy shit out
for you, you know.
When you got somebody
in your life 92 years old,
that's a wisdom you can't
buy nowhere. You know what
I'm sayin'?
And I know what she mean now,
'cause my grandmother
used to always say,
"You know, we livin'
in our last days."
She used to say that
all the time.
"We livin' in our last days."
She fucked me up as a child.
You don't say no bullshit
like that to a five-year-old.
Every day, I woke up scared
than a motherfucker.
"Grandma, this it?
Can I ride my bike
one more time?"
I love my grandma,
but she scared the fuck
out of me for years.
When I grew up
and she was older,
now, when she was 92,
she said that same shit.
I just grabbed her ass
in the car and said,
"Hey, Grandma, why the fuck
we gotta be livin'
in our last days?
That's your goddamn fantasy.
You're 92, you done did
all the fuck you wanna do.
I bet you when you was 20
and fuckin' Granddaddy,
we wasn't livin'
in our last days, was we?
'Cause you think about it.
Why would you wanna
share that kind of shit
with somebody anyway?
Say you knew we livin'
in our last days?
Why the fuck you gonna fuck up
my last few days with the news?
Just buy a bitch a pizza
and surprise a ho.
[giggles]
That was my heart, though.
That was my heart.
-She was--
-[woman in audience] Tic-tac!
Ain't no tic-tac tonight,
baby, but...
we'll talk about some more shit,
you know.
Motherfuckers who open
their mouth with teeth
that look like tools
and shit, you know.
I saw 'em.
Them motherfuckers look like
some goddamn...
Look like she can
walk into Sears
and put Black & Decker's ass
right on out of business.
But I love you.
'Cause I love my grandma.
I need to tribute to her
'cause I love my grandma. She...
In fact, she's the reason
why I'm still standin' here
doin' comedy.
-[applause]
-For real. She is.
Because, you know,
I had gotten discouraged.
I said I wasn't gonna do it,
because I did a show
and I gave it my all.
I don't know if y'all know
but I use y'all for therapists.
I talk to y'all 'cause I know
y'all can relate
to the shit I'm talkin' about,
you know?
So, I talk to y'all
and I put my heart into it,
and I gave a great show
one night, and a lady
came up to me after the show
and she said,
"Adele, we loved you.
You were funny as shit."
She said,
"But you have a filthy mouth."
And I was all fucked up
'cause I wasn't thinkin'
at the time
that that's a control issue.
When somebody tell you
how you should talk,
that's a motherfucker
that wanna control you.
But I wasn't thinkin' that, see?
I was just discouraged
that one of my fans
thought I had a filthy mouth.
And I said,
"Fuck it, I'm through.
I'm quittin'. Shit."
-My grandmother...
-[laughter]
My grandmother talked to me,
said, "Look,
you don't quit, bitch,
unless you wanna quit.
You don't let nobody
make you quit."
I said, "But Grandma,
that lady said
I had a filthy mouth."
She said, "Come here, baby.
Let me tell you somethin'."
She said, "The next time
somebody tell you you got
a filthy mouth,
you let 'em know,
it ain't what come
out your mouth
that make it filthy,
it's what you put in there."
She said, "Then you tell 'em
you wash all the dicks
you suck, hear?"
I said, "Yes, ma'am."
Be careful, y'all. Ladies,
when you're havin' a baby,
make sure you name 'em some shit
that they can live up to.
'Cause I got friends ain't gonna
never live up to their names.
I do.
I got a friend named Alexis,
look like a Buick.
Not a regular Buick.
One of them old,
fucked-up 1973 Buicks,
one of the doors a different
color than the rest of the car.
All fucked up.
I got a friend named Champagne.
Look like a '40.
Not a regular '40.
One of the kind
you grab the bottle
and bust it on the curb,
then cut a bitch with, you know.
Ol' roughneck '40.
[laughter]
And I don't wanna see what I saw
in the airport today.
This shit was scary.
Now, y'all know it's hard
to find a ugly baby.
[audience] Ooh.
-But they out there.
-[laughter]
And they a hell of a sight
'cause you don't see 'em often.
Most babies is cute.
But I saw this
little motherfucker
in the airport today.
Oh! That big-head motherfucker.
He had a big, giant-ass head.
He was leaning
'cause he was tryin' to
keep up with that motherfucker.
He was cross-eyed, knock-kneed.
He had a Pamper swollen
about six times its size,
where he done pissed.
His T-shirt was dirty
with a sucker stuck on it
with lint.
He tryin' to run and play,
his mother talkin' about,
"Come here, Denzel!"
Who, bitch?
Bitch, he gonna need a nickname.
How about "Head"?
Let's call that motherfucker
"Head".
Hey, Memphis, Tennessee,
thank y'all so much for joinin'
The Queens of Comedy!
We love y'all!
["Three Strikes"
by Kelly Price playing]
Can I just please
speak to the folk
in America?
See, this is what's happenin'.
You know, see,
because me and Adele,
we ain't made up.
We just flew in.
-Bad flight.
-Right, right.
-That bitch there.
-She right at home.
She prime like a bull.
She went to bed
and woke up ready.
Ain't this some bullshit?
She got on pumps and heels.
Look at my motherfuckin' shoes.
I got on big Herman shoes.
That bitch got on
three-inch heeled spikes.
You don't do that bullshit.
Matter of fact,
she ain't a Queen of Comedy.
She has just been dismissed.
I am Diana Ross of the Supremes,
bitch, and you will not
be tourin' with us.
I want Mary Wilson
out the fuckin' group!
[laughs] She brings. She...
She brings problems.
I want her dismissed right now.
-We was on schedule
till we picked your ass up.
-Ain't nobody gonna say the shit
'cause they
my motherfuckin' friends!
Your trick-ass is back there,
lookin' like a goddamn
beauty queen
at six o'clock
in the motherfuckin' mornin'!
And that's why
we're not on fuckin' schedule!
Now let the truth
really be said!
You two scared bitches
ain't gonna say nothin'.
Yours and that bitch
that's sat back there,
she already been
to the fuckin' beauty shop!
And I don't play it!
Damn, brothers,
y'all got some good lines.
Don't act like you don't know.
You know how we be
at your apartment, house
wherever you live,
and you be tryin'
to get a little pussy.
And that's okay, that's okay.
That's cool.
It's normal. A man is gonna try.
But we ain't ready
to give you none
and we got to go.
But you don't want us
to leave, so you'll try
to make us feel guilty.
"Uh...
Girl, you leavin'?
How you gonna leave?
You gonna leave me like this?"
[laughter]
"Touch it. It ain't never
been this big.
It ain't never been this hard."
And this has got to be
the best line of all:
"Just let me put the head in."
[laughter]
Just let you put the head in.
Do you know how many times
I let a nigga put the head in?
I got two babies by the head.
[laughter]
Memphis!
Yeah!
From the queendom
of Trenton, New Jersey.
She was the first host
of BET's Comic View,
she hosted Def Jam.
You've seen her on
The Hughleys,
The Oprah Winfrey Show.
You don't know money
like she knows money.
She's the diva of comedy!
Welcome, Memphis, Queen Sommore!
[cheering]
["Da Baddest Bitch"
by Trina playing]
[music stops]
Now, y'all know
a bitch just got out of jail.
Y'all need to act
like you're happy
to see me in this motherfucker.
[cheering]
Baby,
I'm tellin' y'all right now,
first, they started lockin' up
football players,
then they started
lockin' up rappers.
Now they lockin' up bitches
with good pussy.
All y'all better hide!
Baby, they put a bitch in jail!
[shouting] Lord, I thought
they was playin'!
[laughter]
Baby, they put a bitch in jail
for five motherfuckin' days!
And, you know, when you in jail,
five days feel like 50 days.
But I was strong.
A bitch was strong.
You know what I'm sayin'?
I tried to hold it together.
I felt like Tupac...
when I went in there.
"Keep your head up."
[laughter]
Baby, but when the reality
that a bitch was in jail...
set in...
-I felt like Miss Sophia
on The Color Purple,  Lord!
-[laughter]
"Please help me!
I don't like the devil!
Lord!"
Woo!
I ain't never seen so many dykes
in my life.
Baby, the dykes was on me!
Lord, there was this one dyke,
the bitch was aggressive.
One dyke wouldn't
leave me alone.
I said, "Bitch, leave me 'lone.
-Leave me 'lone."
-[laughter]
I figure,
since I was incarcerated,
I talk like a slave.
"Bitch, leave me 'lone."
"Look, I has got a man.
Leave me 'lone."
That bitch looked
at me and said,
"Eatin' ain't cheatin'."
[laughter, shrieking]
I said, "Well, bitch,
we gonna be fightin'
'cause I ain't dykin'."
Baby, I'm tellin' you!
And the worst thing
you ever wanna do in jail
is you don't wanna look sexy.
I was tryin' to look
as un-sexy as possible.
You know,
the ass is already
a little flat.
I was smashin'
that motherfucker
way in walkin'.
[laughter]
Baby,
I'm gonna tell y'all one thing.
Any place where dick
ain't runnin' free,
ain't for me! Fuck it!
[laughter]
Woo!
I'm tellin' you. I said,
"Lord, please don't
let my one time..."
'Cause I got this one prayer
I say all the time every night,
just for my ass to swell up.
I say, "Lord, whatever you do,
don't let my ass
swell up this time
while I'm in here."
I'm for real.
That's my number one prayer,
to get me a big ass.
The titties is all right
but the ass is kinda flat.
The bitch is wide
but it ain't got
no weight on it!
I see the brothers
know what I mean
when I say "some weight on it."
I want me one of them
ball-a-call asses, you know.
I want a ass so big that
when I'm walkin'
through the club,
a man could just take his drink
and lay it up on my ass
and I don't even know
it's there.
I'm just movin' on
through the club and shit.
Knockin' drinks
off the tables and shit.
Movin' tablecloths over
and shit.
I want me a big ol' ignant ass.
The kinda ass you just frown up.
You be like, "Damn."
[laughter]
I want a ass so big
that if I'm on top,
he roll me over,
I'm still on top.
It's a wrap-around ass.
I hate to see other women
with big asses. I seen a lady
down on Beale Street
had a real big ol' ass.
She gonna try to be
friendly with me.
Now, she got a real big ol' ass,
a real flat stomach,
but she was flat-chested.
Came over to me
askin' me questions and shit.
Talkin' about,
"Sommore, you know,
what can I do to make my
titties look really, really big
without gettin' silicone?"
I said, "Bitch, get you
some toilet tissue
and rub it
in between your titties."
She said, "Well,
how is that gonna help me?"
I said, "I don't know, bitch,
but it's done wonders
for your ass."
I'm for real!
Well, I'm gonna
get me a big ass.
I'm for real 'cause science
and medicine is
a motherfucker nowadays.
You know, they got a pill
for any fuckin' thing you want.
Do you realize that science
and medicine has got together
and created so much bullshit
that we spend money on bullshit
like Viagra and breast implants
and we ignore important shit
like Alzheimer's Disease?
Do you realize by the time
we all get old,
we're gonna be walkin' around
with big ol' titties
and big ol' dicks
and don't remember
what to do with 'em?
I'm for real!
I know a motherfucker bought
some bootleg Viagra.
Everything swelled up
except his dick.
But you gotta remember one thing
when you buy this medicine.
-All that shit has a
side effect.
-Yep.
All that shit has a side effect.
And they try to sneak
the side effects past you.
You ever notice,
like on a commercial,
they'll have you believin'
this sinus medicine
is a bad motherfucker.
Then right before the commercial
go off, here come
the motherfuckin' side effects.
They go, "Warning.
This medicine will give
you a headache, insomnia
and constant diarrhea."
Now, you got to decide
whether you wanna have
a runny nose or a runny ass.
Which one it gonna be?
But I like that type of shit.
I wish everything came
with a fuckin'
side effect label.
Especially men.
I wish men had a motherfuckin'
side-effect label right on
the side of your asses.
That's the truth!
Let a bitch know up front
what your ass is all about.
Let's say you in a club.
You in a club, you chillin'.
He walk in. You lookin' good
and he lookin' good.
He checkin' you out,
you checkin' him out.
Right before he walk past,
you see his motherfuckin'
side effects.
"Warning. This nigga is subject
to run up your credit,
fuck about two or three
of your girlfriends,
and has a tendency
to whoop a bitch-ass
every now and then."
[laughter, applause]
"What you gon' do?"
You know,
a bitch like me will go ahead
and fuck with him anyway
if the dick is good.
You know that.
"Nigga might change,
nigga might change."
I had a dream
that I was standing
at the gates of Heaven
and got into a fight.
Wasn't my fault. They was
fuckin' with me in line.
Let me tell y'all how
this shit happened.
No, they was fuckin' with me.
They was fuckin' with me.
Now, I'm standin' in line
at the gates of Heaven.
Foxy Brown, the rapper,
is standin' in front of me.
Monica Lewinsky
is standin' in back of me.
So, Foxy Brown gets up
to the gate. She say,
"How you doin', St. Peter?"
She said,
"My name is Foxy Brown.
I'm a rapper.
I've done some sins in my life
but I'm still a good person."
He said, "Foxy Brown, my child,
what part of your body
have you sinned with?"
She said, "My hands."
He said, "Go over there
and rinse your hands out
in the faucet,
and you may enter
the gates of Heaven."
Next, it was my turn.
I went up to the gate.
I said, "How you doin',
St. Peter?
My name is Sommore.
I'm a stand-up comedian.
I've done some sins in my life
but I'm still a good person."
He said, "Sommore, my child,
what part of your body
have you sinned with?"
Before I can say
any fuckin' thing...
Monica Lewinsky pushed me
out of the way and said,
"Excuse me, but can I rinse
my mouth out in the faucet
before this bitch put her ass
in the water?"
[laughter]
I said, "Bitch!
You don't know
me like that, bitch!"
Don't shit with me!
I'm not gonna have any children
unless I'm married.
I'm for real. Fuck that.
A bitch might dress
like a Power Ranger
but I need help!
I ain't no strong motherfucker
when it comes to bein' strong
like that.
'Cause, y'all women kill me
when y'all bein'
too motherfuckin' strong.
Y'all be walkin' around
talkin' about, "I don't need
a man for shit.
I pay my own bills.
I pay my own rent.
I don't need a man for shit."
Well, as soon as a man
fuck you real good, you give him
a key to all your shit.
I know you have.
Fuck that.
I need help from the gate.
I'm for real,
and I see the reality
of marriage.
See, marriage to me
is a lot different
than other people see it.
See, marriage to me
is a lot like going to
an amusement park.
You know
how you go to an amusement park
and you get inside,
-and you're ridin'
all the rides.
-[laughter]
Just havin' yourself
a real good time.
Just ridin' all the rides.
Then all of a sudden,
you start walkin' around
and you start seein'
all these big, pretty,
fluffy-assed animals
that you could win.
So now you decide that you got
to have you one.
So, now you play all the games
that you have to play
in order for you to get you one.
Then you spend up all the money
that you have to spend up,
in order for you to win you one.
Finally, you got you one.
Now you're walkin' around
the fairground
with this big,
pretty motherfucker,
and everybody see ya.
But after a while, you realize
that you can't ride
no more rides
'cause you got
this big bitch with ya.
[laughter, applause]
See, I just wanna ride
all night long.
[chuckles]
Trust me, I tried!
I tried to look for a man.
I go to all the
celebrity parties and shit.
The celebrity men,
they don't fuck with me,
'cause they know
I'm just like Velcro.
You fuck with me,
you stuck with me.
-We ain't breakin' up for shit.
-[laughter]
I'm for real!
We ain't breakin' up for shit!
[laughter]
But I think I'm a
smart motherfucker. I got
good money management skills.
There's some of them
that could really use my help.
I wouldn't waste their money.
I know for one thing--
like, let's say Stevie Wonder.
If Stevie Wonder was my husband,
if Stevie Wonder
was married to me,
he wouldn't have
but one fuckin' outfit.
[laughter]
What the fuck does he need
with more than one outfit?
I'd take him
to the closet every day,
let him feel all my shit,
and say, "That's all your shit.
That's all your shit."
[applause]
I'd tell him every day,
"You sharper than a
motherfucker."
I'd be Febreze-ing
his shit every day.
[mimics spraying sound]
[laughter]
He think he wearing suede.
He wearin' brushed cotton
like a motherfucker.
See, I see the reality
of a lotta shit.
That's why now,
since I'm approachin' 30,
once I turn 30 years old,
I ain't fuckin' no more
men over 30.
I'm not! I'm sick and tired
of fuckin' niggas named Charlie
and Greg and them.
And Bruce and Rufus.
I wanna fuck some Hakeems,
some Taquons,
-some Deshawns.
-[laughter]
I'm for real! I'm sick of men
in dress-socks trying
to get the pussy.
He's slippin' and slidin' fit
to bust your lip.
[laughter]
I want a man with some
Timberlands on
that's gonna be all up
in that ass, just ridin'.
And now, since we talkin'
about dicks...
'Cause I wasn't gonna
bring up dicks,
but since y'all brought it up...
[laughter]
Let me ask y'all a question.
Why is it that men
with little dicks...
act like they don't know
they got little dicks?
Like the dick just got small
on the way to your house.
Nigga, you knew
what this dick was
on the phone! On the phone!
I blame women.
I blame women for men
with little dicks walkin' around
thinkin' they got big dicks.
Y'all just need
to tell 'em the truth.
Shut 'em down.
[laughter]
I'm for real!
I had a guy come to me one day,
talkin' about,
"Sommore, you know, well,
what's your favorite position?"
I said, "Well, it depends
on the size of the dick
'cause if you got a little dick,
my favorite position is
with another motherfucker."
I ain't got time
to be bullshittin'.
Balls all big,
dick hidin' behind the balls.
No!
That's some bullshit!
[laughter, applause]
I'm for real!
Dick is a beautiful thing.
Y'all don't know dick
like I know dick.
Do you realize that
if a man is fuckin' you right,
you can spot his ass
at the Million Man March.
"There he goes."
Oh, dick is a beautiful thing.
'Specially if you fuck around
and get you some good dick.
Oh! And you don't know good dick
like I know good dick!
You know how you can tell
if you got a man
with some good dick?
When you let him drive your car.
And you know
he ain't got no license.
[laughter, applause]
You say, "Go, fool!
Fuck with the law."
Say, "Nigga, you can drive now!"
But I say this to my sisters.
Just don't get dickmatized.
You ever just see somebody
that's dickmatized?
That's when the dick
is just too good
that they can't see the reality
of some shit.
[laughter]
Oh, no, no, no.
People that's dickmatized
be sayin' stupid shit like this,
"No, no, no, no, no.
He don't be fightin' me.
I be, like, walkin' into
the punches and shit."
"No, no. I be, like,
walkin' right into the punch."
Now, that's dickmatized.
"Well, why you always
gotta be talkin'about dicks?
Why you always..."
You know why
I always talk about dicks?
'Cause I believe,
especially in the United States,
women, we are exploited. We are.
I don't give a shit
which movie you wanna see,
Pocahontas  or Die Hard 3,
you're always willing
to see a woman
in any movie that's willing
to show her pussy
and her titties.
I think they should start
making men show their dicks.
-[woman in audience] All right!
-[cheering]
That's right!
From now on, if I pay my money,
I wanna see if Wesley is nestly.
All right?
Damn it, for 6.50, damn it,
Denzel better swell, okay?
As a matter of fact,
I think we should just
lock all the doors
and make all the men in here
just pull their dicks out.
Now, look at the men
with little dicks.
They sittin' there like
"Now, this bitch
ain't funny worth a damn.
This is some bullshit."
But you know
there's one big-dick,
country motherfucker sittin' way
at the top like this,
"Lock the door."
"Lock the motherfuckin' door!"
Oh, 'cause ladies,
it's the new millennium,
and I don't know about y'all,
but this is how I feel.
Fuck your bling-bling.
Nigga, can you swing-swing?
Woo! I'm for real.
Women, we go through
a lotta shit. We do.
We go through a lotta shit.
But the amazing thing
about us ladies,
we have the ability
to bounce back
'cause we're made like that.
That's right!
We have a certain... Man,
let me tell y'all somethin'.
We have a certain rhythm in us
that no matter what
we go through,
we gonna be all right.
And see,
when we was little girls,
your mother knew
that you had that certain
rhythm in you.
So, when you was about
eight years old, she gave
you one essential toy.
She knew that with this toy
you would get a swivel
in your hips
and an attitude to match.
Ladies, when you was
about eight years old,
your mother put you outside
on the front porch
and she gave you a hula hoop.
You didn't quite understand
why she insisted
that you learn how
to do the hula hoop.
You got outside with the
hula hoop rockin'
around your waist...
And, at first, it was
a little bit difficult for you,
but you kept on tryin'.
After a while when you
got it rockin' to your own
certain pattern,
it made a certain sound.
It said...
[mimics swishing]
And when you heard that sound,
you knew you was the shit!
[mimics swishing]
Then your girlfriend hollered,
"Put it round your neck!"
[mimics swishing]
So I say to my sisters
here tonight in Memphis,
the next time that you have
to remind him
of just who you are,
the next time that he forget
just your powers,
the next time that you gotta
put it down on him,
the next time that you're up
on top and you're ridin' him
real good.
You're ridin' him so good
that his toes is curlin' up.
His eyes is rollin' up
in the back of his head.
You're ridin' his dick so good
that he can't even close
his mouth!
I want y'all to do me one favor.
I want you to look at yourself
in the mirror,
wink one eye at yourself
and just say...
[mimic swishing]
-[laughter]
-Yo, my name is Sommore.
Y'all been wonderful.
Thank y'all for comin' out.
[cheering]
["Da Baddest Bitch"
by Trina playing]
A. Schwab. Established in 1876.
Watch out, now.
The oldest family-owned
and operated workin'
general store in the South.
Pigs fuckin' from the back.
This is the type of shit I like.
Yeah.
This is a big slave bell.
Just in case some shit
come back.
-Okay, I got you.
Hurry up. Okay.
-Hold on. Hold that.
Is this son of a bitch
stickin' out?
-Let it stick out.
-Push it down in my...
Push it down.
-You got it.
-Push it down.
This is weed. All day long
I don't care what
they got on here,
this is marijuana.
Two dollars a bag.
It's legal on Beale Street.
This some shit right here.
This some shut-your-
motherfuckin'-mouth potion.
You take this shit
and you won't talk.
She's puttin' on
her tap shoes, baby.
Black folk know how
to entertain.
And for those of you who are
watching her,
this ain't for free.
Fuckin' move girl.
Watch her slide.
Now, I'm y'all manager,
so I get ten percent.
We gonna...
I wanna welcome y'all
to show business.
This is how it goes.
Now, we made a few dollars
so far now.
There we go. All right.
Thank you so much.
Y'all give it up
for Michael and Jasmine.
Entertainin' y'all.
That's right.
From Givens Management.
If you need to contact us,
call me, Adele Givens,
or email me
at suchalady1@aol.com.
Now, come on. Let's cut this up.
Y'all gonna get
a dollar apiece...
'cause y'all tapped really well.
There you go. There you go.
-Now, we're gonna put this
in our fund...
-[Mo'Nique] Right.
...to buy us some
tapping costumes,
so we can look alike.
-We got a plan.
-[Mo'Nique] I'm the attorney.
Now, my fee,
she ain't paid me yet,
so I'm gonna have to sue y'all.
All right.
Memphis!
-Yeah!
Coming to you...
all the way from the kingdom
of Baltimore, Maryland.
What can I say about this sister
'cept she the sweetest,
craziest woman I know?
From The Parkers...
welcome as only you can,
Memphis,
Queen Mo'nique.
[cheering]
[R&B music playing]
Hi.
Memphis. Goddamn it.
This is some wonderful shit.
Y'all better make some
motherfuckin' noise
for my ass up in here tonight,
baby!
Yes! Yes!
And I'mma tell you somethin',
now see, all the fat girls,
all you fat bitches
should have got up out your seat
when my fat-ass pulled around
in that goddamn pyramid.
Goddamn it,
stand your fat asses up
and take a motherfuckin' bow!
Get your fat asses up,
big girls. Get it up!
Get your fat ass up!
You ain't chubby.
Get your asses up!
Do it, do it, baby!
Goddamn it, big women.
You all right, big girl.
You better represent it,
goddamn it.
You better do it, you fat ass.
I love you, baby girl.
You handle your shit.
Fuck you skinny bitches. Now!
Fuck you skinny, anorexic,
bulimic motherfuckers!
What?
[laughs]
Big women,
it's our goddamn time, baby.
Fuck these skinny bitches.
Look at her shakin', bitch.
'Cause you hungry!
Get a motherfuckin' two-piece
and a biscuit.
[laughs]
Big women, handle your shit!
You hear what I'm sayin'?
Y'all look good from the top
of your head to the bottom
of your motherfuckin' feet.
I watched your fat asses
come in on the monitor.
I said, "Look at my big sisters
handlin' their shit."
Fuck these skinny bitches.
Y'all are some hateful bitches!
Skinny women are evil
and they need
to be destroyed, baby!
You hear what I'm sayin' to you,
big girls?
If you're sittin' next to
a skinny bitch,
take your fist...
[laughs]
...and hit that bitch in the top
of her motherfuckin' head!
Let that bitch know you're here.
Right in the top of the head.
Say somethin'.
[laughter]
[Mo'Nique laughs]
Big women,
handle your shit, baby.
Yes! It's a new goddamn time.
I'mma tell you somethin', too.
See, at one time,
you skinny bitches...
[laughter]
...you didn't respect us.
A skinny bitch
did not respect...
a fat bitch,
and she didn't feel threatened
by a fat bitch, either.
She was real confident
with her shit.
When she had a man,
she'd see a fat girl
come in the club,
she didn't even blink twice.
She'd say,
"Look at that fat bitch...
[laughter]
...She goin' right
to the little buffet table.
Mm-hmm."
[laughs] And she was right,
but that bitch didn't need
to say that cruel shit.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Look. Look, skinny bitch.
[laughter]
Look at 'em.
Look at 'em. See,
a skinny bitch is a
confused bitch.
It started at 10:30, bitch!
You hungry.
It fuck up your thinkin'!
Gonna walk your skinny ass
through the middle of my
motherfuckin' show.
Eat something!
I don't like that bitch.
Back up!
[Mo'Nique laughs]
That's right!
[laughs]
And sit your black ass down!
-[cheering]
-[Mo'Nique laughs]
Like he doin' somethin'!
[imitates man mumbling]
Sit your country ass down.
[laughs]
[kisses] I love you, baby.
But I'mma tell you somethin'.
And, see, you know what?
You know, sometime,
little skinny bitch felt like...
she wasn't threatened.
That her man would never, ever
want a fat bitch.
Well, I got news for you, baby.
It's a new motherfuckin' day.
You hear what I'm sayin'?
Every man wants
to fuck a fat girl
one time, baby.
One time, and once you go fat,
you never go back.
Once you get some fat pussy,
it's all over, baby.
[laughs]
See, you skinny bitches,
y'all complain
when you're fuckin'.
You don't have enough meat
to hold shit together.
When you fuckin'...
"Oh, oh! My leg bendin'!
My kidney hurt!
My neck crooked!"
Big girl be like, "Nigga,
you ain't said nothin', nigga!
What you say, nigga-boy? Pop!
[laughter]
I got you, nigga.
Stop cryin', boy.
Stop cryin'. Stop cryin', nigga.
Hold on, nigga! Hold on!"
[laughs]
Woo, baby!
Handle your shit, big people.
I like being a big old
healthy girl.
And big men?
Let me tell you somethin'.
You keep eatin'...
your shit.
Fuck these
muscle-bound motherfuckers.
Got veins poppin' out
of their goddamn neck.
They're gonna fuck around
and shrink their dick up
liftin' all them
fuckin' weights.
You stay a big, fat old pig.
I just can't fuck with ya.
[laughter]
Woo, baby!
Two fat motherfuckers cannot...
get together.
Baby, I have tried.
Oh, shit!
I have tried to fuck a fat man.
It's too much! Uh!
It's too much shit
goin' on, baby.
Both of y'all layin' there.
He's looking for your shit,
you tryin' to find his shit.
Y'all breathin' and sweatin'.
[heavy breathing]
I can't breathe, nigga!
Get off my stomach!
Let's go get a fish-box.
Shit, fuck it.
[laughs]
Oh, baby.
You know what, though?
What I'm most proud of?
I don't give a fuck
what size we are,
just bein' a sister.
-You hear what I'm sayin' to ya?
-[all] Yeah!
Black women got some
special shit with them.
We are some
special motherfuckers,
and if you look around,
every sister in here
is so pretty,
and we age so gracefully.
You see what I'm sayin'?
You don't never know
how old a sister is, baby.
Because black women,
we have a motto about life.
We have a motto.
Black women don't give a fuck.
[laughter]
We don't give a fuck.
We don't give a fuck about shit.
Girl, you goin'
to work tomorrow?
Girl, fuck that job.
[Mo'Nique laughing]
We don't give a fuck!
Girl, how're your kids doin'?
Girl, fuck them kids.
Shit. Fuck that.
Black women got some shit
with 'em, and brothers
y'all know that.
That's how come y'all don't go
all the way over the line.
'Cause y'all know
we some crazy motherfuckers,
and y'all are a little scared
of us from time to time.
Some shit done went down
at home, your boy come over,
and you nervous. You're like,
"Man, don't look at her."
[laughter]
"Don't say nothin' to her.
She done fucked up my shit."
[laughs]
That's why I love us, baby.
But see, sisters.
That's how come we can learn
from the white girls.
We can learn some shit
from a white bitch,
'cause a white bitch
-knows when to just
shut the fuck up.
-[laughter]
She knows when the argument
has come to a
motherfuckin' close.
She knows when to back up
and say, "Hey, hey...
Hey, Peter."
[Mo'Nique laughs]
I'mma leave this shit alone.
Not our black, evil ass.
We don't give a fuck.
-A sister will get the last word
on your ass, baby.
-[woman in audience] Yeah!
We can be in a goddamn coma,
we gonna say our shit.
He be like, "Bitch,
don't you say nothin' else."
Mm-hmm
Fuck you, nigga,
and your mother, too.
Now, take that.
Baby, we just got some shit.
See, a little white couple.
Little white couple have
a argument in the
mornin' time,
she gonna cut that shit short
She don't want to fuck with him,
he gotta go make that paper.
She's gonna say, "Hey, hey..."
[laughter]
"Hey...
All that shit I said...
I'm sorry...
and I love you.
And have a wonderful day
at work,
and I'll call you. [kisses]
It's wonderful."
Not our black ass.
We don't give a fuck
about havin' no argument
in the mornin' time
and you gotta go
make that motherfuckin' paper.
We gonna say our shit.
Then your black ass
try to walk out the door
like you done ended
the motherfuckin' argument.
No, nigga. It ain't over.
I'm comin' to
your motherfuckin' job.
"Can I speak to James, please?
Bring your ass, nigga!
Bring your ass!"
And, baby,
a sister will not apologize.
Now, James done lost his job.
'Cause we done been up there
six times in two days,
just tellin' him how the fuck
we was feelin' about some shit
that could have held off
for a minute.
And we ain't gonna tell him
"I'm sorry".
We-- Fuck that!
He sittin' on the edge
of the bed cryin'.
He lost his job.
[laughter]
You shoulda let me say
what the fuck I had to say.
[Mo'Nique laughing]
Baby! Black women, baby!
Black women. But you know...
you know who I totally
take my hat off to,
and she ain't a sister,
is Ms. Hillary Clinton.
I take my hat off to that bitch
'cause she knew how to
be a fuckin' wife
under pressure.
And you know what, baby?
Right now with all
this election shit comin' up,
I wish Clinton could run again
'cause I would put his ass
-right back in fuckin' office.
-[cheering]
He was runnin' the shit
out of this country.
You hear what I'm sayin'?
And everybody got mad,
White America got mad
because he got his dick sucked.
So the fuck what?
That comes with
runnin' the country.
That's a privilege
when you are the
President of the United States.
You supposed to get
your dick sucked,
seven motherfuckin' days a week!
That comes with
your goddamn job!
Y'all better be glad
I'm not president.
[laughs]
Line these niggas up!
Your turn, your turn, your turn,
your turn, your turn, your turn.
I'd be doin' electric slide
on the nigga!
Wait a minute, nigga!
Back it up!
Woo! [laughs]
Baby!
And I'm tellin' you,
when all this shit broke,
when it broke,
and I'm sittin' and I'm
watchin' news, I'm, like,
"Clinton, hold your shit.
Hold your motherfuckin' shit.
You are the president.
Fuck them! Kill 'em!
You the
motherfuckin' president!"
Hear what I'm sayin'?
Don't become a bitch.
Hold your shit.
And I was like, you know,
for about a month,
he was like "Fuck y'all.
Fuck y'all.
I didn't fuck that bitch.
I don't know that bitch.
Fuck y'all."
I'm like, "Yeah, baby.
Do your shit. Fuck them.
Fuck them."
And then...
the whiteness kicked up
in his ass...
and he came back on TV
and got to cryin' and shit.
And he broke...
America.
[giggles]
"I-- I wanna say I'm sorry.
I got my cock sucked."
[laughs]
They call it "cock." [laughs]
We're like, "Nigga,
you got your dick sucked.
Clinton."
That's how come brothers,
y'all could never be president.
Not 'cause you don't
have the skills,
but we ain't gonna
stand still that long, baby.
We gonna show our motherfuckin'
ass on ABC, NBC, CBS,
CNN, the animal channel,
the Discovery Channel, baby!
And we gonna try to be cool.
We gonna try to be cool
while the media's sayin',
"You know, hey,
he got his dick sucked."
We'll be like...
[laughter]
Mm...
"Y'all go to commercial.
Go to commercial.
Nigga, you got your dick sucked!
Nigga!
Nigga, what! Nigga!"
Fuck that, baby.
-Let's go, baby.
-All right, this is
Interstate Bar-B-Q,
up here in Memphis, Tennessee.
You know when you're in
black-folk establishment.
This shit's the real
damned bologna,
with the red band.
-Wait a minute!
-See that?
White America don't know nothin'
about this!
[all laughing]
Interstate, this is the house
of the skins. Can I help you?
We got two bags of skins left.
How far are you away?
Who in the hell calls
a restaurant and say,
"Hey, y'all got any skins?"
We working on first come,
first served.
Now, if you don't come down here
to get Emma's skins,
then both of y'all
are out of luck.
You hear what I'm sayin' to you,
Russell?
And that's a coincidence.
That's just what I wanted
for lunch.
A smoked sausage.
I like it hot, too.
We ate a couple of the skins
out of the bag, but you come on.
Tell him we miss him
and we're sorry, hear?
All right, player. Later.
I'm gonna take their order.
Come on out here,
Mr. Interstate.
-We takin' their order.
-[Adele] Oh, she goin'.
My name is Mo'nique.
I'mma be your server today.
-Yes.
-Okay, I'll tell you
what y'all do.
When y'all decide
what you want to eat,
write it down on the pad.
-I'll come back and get it.
-[all laughing]
-I need to get my drinks.
-We got it. We got your order.
We got your order.
-Let me hold the phone.
-We want ten more.
-Now see, we just
posted a memo today.
-Come on and pass ten more.
We are gettin' sick of y'all
callin' in when it's time
for you to come to work.
If you don't show up today,
don't worry about showin' up.
Now, the decision is yours.
I'mma give you time
to think about it
and you call right back
[laughter]
[Mo'Nique laughing]
Oh, baby! But you know what?
Sisters, we got common sense.
That's the one thing about
a black woman,
baby, that I cherish.
We got
common-motherfuckin'-sense.
See, a white bitch...
-Remember that shit
Lorena Bobbitt?
-[cheering]
Right, right.
That was white women shit, baby.
Cut that boy dick off.
Why?
What in the fuck was she
thinkin' about?
She cut his dick off...
[laughter]
...and then she threw it...
up on the forest...
and drove the fuck away.
We ain't never
that motherfuckin' mad, baby.
I don't care what his black ass
did, that dick ain't goin'
nowhere, ever!
You hear me?
That nigga coulda whipped my ass
and closed my right eye.
Mm-mm
And I'm standin' over the top
of his dick
with the scissors...
lookin' at it.
Hm! Hm!
-Oh, Lord, Lord!
-[laughter]
And it's in the mornin' time!
Jesus!
And he ain't peed yet!
[Mo'Nique laughs]
You ain't beat me that bad,
motherfucker.
Call me Left Eye. Shit.
It's all right.
Black women, you better
get yourself a black-ass man
and hold on to him,
'cause you can't
make it without him.
Fuck what you heard, baby.
I love and worship the ground
that a black man walk on.
I don't give a fuck.
And it don't have
nothin' to do with the money.
I am the breadwinner,
and I'm married to what I think
is the best black man
on the face of this earth.
You hear what I'm sayin' to you?
Oh, baby.
But I am the breadwinner.
He does not work
because he have
a problem readin'.
[all laughing]
But we gonna work with that
illiterate motherfucker.
He be embarrassing me and shit,
orderin' shit he can't pronounce
in a restaurant.
"Can I get
a strawberry daq-why?"
What the fuck is a "daq-why",
you ignorant bitch?
Point to it!
You order shit else.
[Mo'Nique laughs]
But he's mine, baby.
You hear what I'm sayin' to you.
He's my
non-readin' motherfucker.
He is mine and I will
kill a bitch if she step to him.
I ain't fightin' over no man.
I ain't gonna fight you.
I'm gonna kill your
motherfuckin' ass,
'cause that's my shit.
-[laughter]
-That's my shit, baby.
I will hit you in the
back of your throat
with a goddamn hammer.
Say, "Bitch, I told you.
Now you can't talk,
you mad with me."
I don't play that bullshit.
For all you women out here
who's got a man
and you got a single girlfriend,
fuck that bitch.
Don't you let that bitch
up in your house
when you ain't home.
-[cheering, applause]
-You hear what I'm sayin'?
Don't even let that bitch go
to the movies with y'all.
"Bitch, I don't know what
to tell you. I get you the DVD
when it come out.
You ain't goin'
to the motherfuckin'
picture-show with me,
you lonely bitch."
I don't trust no woman.
When I first got the show,
The Parkers...
You know, all my
little girlfriends
out in Hollywood say,
"Bitch, you gotta get a maid.
You're a star.
Don't be cleaning your shit."
So I ain't never had nobody
come in clean my shit.
So I got tickled,
and I called
a little maid service. "Hey,
I need a bitch over here...
[all laughing]
...to clean my shit up."
So they kept sendin'
these real pretty,
perky white girls.
I said, "No, no.
I got a motherfuckin' husband.
Uh-uh.
This bitch has got to be 65,
a Mexican who can't speak a bit
of motherfuckin' English,
with one tooth
and two strands of hair.
And that bitch
can't even spend the night.
When I leave,
every bitch in the house leave.
When I get my coat
and pocketbook,
Mama, you grab your shit, too.
I don't trust your ass either.
Sit out on the front
till I get back." [laughs]
Fuck what you heard, baby.
But see, as a wife...
As a wife, and a lot of the
youngsters say "What you mean?"
As a wife, I know my place
with my husband.
You hear what I'm sayin'?
Even though I make
all the money,
he's still the king
of my castle.
I give him what he wants
when he wants it,
and the bitch is on time
when he say "Be there."
'cause I'm not losing that man
over some shit
I would not do.
Especially,
when it come to that bedroom.
My husband calls me the F.B.I.A.
The Freakiest Bitch in America,
'cause I give it to him
however the fuck he wants it.
You hear me?
And for you crazy bitches
sittin' out there,
talking about,
"I ain't gonna
do that nasty shit,
I ain't gonna
do that freaky shit.
He wants me to do
some old nasty bullshit."
Well, let me tell you somethin'.
What you won't do,
another bitch will.
And she will do that shit
so swell, his ass ain't
comin' back home.
So, if your man wants you
to do some nasty, gutter-butt,
triflin', slutty,
whorish, pornographic bullshit,
you better get
with the motherfuckin'
program, baby.
If he wants to stick his dick
in your ear,
lend that nigga your ear.
-I hear you comin', nigga,
I hear you comin'.
-[laughter, applause]
[Mo'Nique laughing]
Fuck what you heard, baby.
Handle your shit.
Keep your man happy.
Now, see, some shit...
some shit...
I can't...
fuck with.
Some shit physically
I can't fuck with.
Like sometime,
Mark be wantin' me to do,
you know,
little-skinny-woman shit.
[laughter]
Like he like me
to swing across shit.
I done fucked three
dining-room tables up
tryin' to be motherfuckin' Jane
up in there,
and fell through the goddamn
table and the chandelier
and fucked my back up.
I can't fuck with that.
I can't do that.
Then he be talking about,
"Mo'nique, look.
Take your legs...
and wrap 'em up
around your neck." No, nigga.
I can't breathe like that.
Pull my motherfuckin'
stomach muscle, nigga.
Put me the fuck down.
And then,
some shit that fucks with me.
Black men,
I don't know where y'all got
this bullshit from
but you take it back
'cause it is some unnatural...
horrible bullshit to put on
one individual.
You're in the bed
and feelin' real sexy
and wonderful,
and then he fuck up
the whole vibe,
talkin' about, "Let me poke you
up in your ass."
[all laughing]
"Let me stick you up in
the ass one time."
No, nigga! No, no!
That is horrible to fuck
in the butt.
And if there are any homosexuals
in Memphis, Tennessee,
God bless your nasty,
faggoty asses,
because that is
some painful shit
to fuck in the butt!
And every sister in here
has tried that shit
at least one time, baby.
And men, y'all ain't worth shit,
'cause y'all be tryin'
to coach us
through that nasty shit.
[laughter]
"All right. Now, look.
Check this out, right.
Check this out.
I want you to just bend over...
and relax all your muscles."
Okay, okay. Okay, okay!
-Hoo! Shit!
-[laughter]
[screaming]
Nigga, my eyebrows burnin'!
Take it out!
"I got some K-Y Jelly."
Put it on a biscuit, nigga.
We're eatin'. Shit.
That is some pain...
That is some painful,
horrible shit,
to fuck in the butt...
but I like it now.
-[audience exclaiming]
-[laughs]
You gotta grip some shit
real tight and breathe.
[heavy breathing]
[laughter]
[Mo'Nique laughs]
And I'mma tell you somethin',
baby. I'mma tell...
I'mma... [laughing]
I'mma tell ya...
And, you know,
every man has
a little bit of bitch.
Every man, baby,
has a little twinkle
of a bitch...
up in 'em.
Now, I'mma tell you sisters
how you bring it out.
You gotta be careful.
'Cause if he ain't secure
with his shit,
you might fuck around,
and he punch you
up in your mouth.
"You be like, wait a minute,
nigga. I was playing. Damn.
What the fuck's...
goin' on here?"
I've been hit a couple times,
but you gotta be
persistent with your shit.
You know, aggressive and...
"Fuck it."
Get you some new teeth
and you just keep going back...
to do the shit.
But when you're in the bed...
with your man.
When you're in the bed...
with your man,
and y'all doing your shit...
Mm...
[laughter]
[gargling]
[laughs]
That's called "The Slow Roll."
Mm... Uh.
[giggles]
Then you tell him, you tell him.
You say, "Come on, baby.
Come on, come on.
Lay on your stomach for me.
Lay on your stomach."
Now, he gonna get
a little nervous.
"Look. Hold up."
[laughter]
"I ain't into that
faggoty bullshit.
I don't play that nasty shit."
"Nigga, I just wanna
rub your neck."
"Yeah. Yeah, Daddy. Yeah, yeah."
Now, you gotta kiss him gently
on the neck.
You gotta break him down
'cause he's a little tensed up.
[kisses]
"Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah."
Now begin to work your way down.
Now, when you get to the middle
of his back, sisters,
he gonna get
a little nervous again.
"Look. Hold up.
Don't make me rip your ass
up in here. I don't play that
faggoty punk bullshit."
"I know, Daddy, I know. Mwah."
[chuckles]
Keep on going, sisters.
Now, when you get to the crack
of his ass,
watch him.
He gonna try to hold on...
to his manhood,
but that bitch gonna twinkle
right out his ass, baby.
Give him one good kiss
on the crack of that ass
and watch that nigga break down.
[kisses]
"Look.
Hmm.
Look.
Look!
Hmm."
[screams]
[laughter]
"Don't tell nobody, hear?"
Now, sisters.
If you know,
you gonna give him
a special treat,
make sure you bathe his ass
thoroughly.
For you fuck around
and get a treat--
What the fuck?
You nasty motherfucker!
Go wash your ass!
And you know what, sisters?
I gotta share some shit
with y'all.
Now...
ever since I came
out here tonight,
I have used this one word...
about 9,000 times...
and that's "bitch".
From the time I came out here,
I been using that word "bitch".
We give that word
so much motherfuckin' power.
We are willing to leave
our husbands and our boyfriends
because he called you a bitch.
It's a motherfuckin' word.
But if at that time,
if that's what you
was representing,
that's what the fuck you needed
to be called, ya bitch.
You just get
the motherfuckin' point.
Sometime, baby,
it helps close the sentence out.
Shut the fuck up...
-bitch.
-[all] Bitch!
[all laughing]
You understand me better
when I put that closin'
on there.
And if the word is used
at the right time,
at the proper time,
oh, it's a wonderful word, baby.
If it's used
at the right moment.
Like when I'm with my man,
we doing our shit.
Y'all know I'm a nasty,
freaky bitch.
I like all that old nasty shit.
Talk that filthy,
pornographic shit to me,
while you gettin' it.
I like that shit.
And when he hittin' it
from the back,
he ain't in the ass.
-He just hittin' it
from the back.
-[laughter]
It makes a difference, baby.
Trust me.
And we doin' our shit,
we doin' our shit.
And I'd be like,
"Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Call me a bitch, nigga.
Call me a bitch.
Call me a bitch."
"All right, ya bitch."
[screaming] "Oh, shit!
That's my shit!
Call me a bitch!
Call me a bitch!"
"All right, ya bitch!"
"I'm gettin' ready to come,
Daddy. Take me home!
Take me home!"
"All right, you fat bitch."
Wait a minute.
Memphis, my name
is Mo'nique, baby.
God bless you. Keep supportin'.
[cheering]
I really enjoyed all
of the women.
They're truly queens.
They was just off the hook.
-Queens of Comedy,  number one.
-We loved the show!
-Sommore!
-Mo'nique. I loved Mo'nique.
-Go see Mo'nique.
-All of 'em. All of 'em.
-We like Adele.
-Adele Givens.
I've not laughed that hard
in my life.
It was wonderful. It was superb.
See you next year.
I loved all of 'em, but Sommore.
Daddy, when she did
the hula hoop thing...
[mimics swishing]
Queens of Comedy  better
than Kings of Comedy  any day.
[man] This is not Baltimore,
it's Memphis, because what?
It's a lotta black folk.
That's Memphis, yeah!
This is called the wave,
side-dip, and a curl twist.
That's what that's called.
Seven hundred dollars
for the ponytail. Right.
Now, why you wanna come up
on the back of me
in that big-ass truck,
and then try to blow the horn?
I will slam on these...
You move your ass around!
Go around!
Cuss that motherfucker out!
You take your ass on,
you crazy motherfucker!
The last hotel we was in,
y'all know what happened
in my room.
Had a little accident.
How you call somebody
to tell 'em
-you fucked up
their toilet system?
-[all laughing]
Girl, shit. I said, "Help me.
I'm having an emergency!
Please!"
So they say...
How you call somebody
to help you flush the toilet
when you done shit?
That's bullshit.
I said, "I don't know
what's happening.
There's some floodage."
I'm not gettin' that bullshit.
We was in a six-star hotel.
I didn't give a fuck.
I was bein' fabulous.
Look at that. Look at that.
Look at how that's holding.
That is a wonderful...
Hold that for me, baby girl.
Mama you hot
Tell me do you got
Just a little time
You look thirsty
Can I get you
a glass of wine
This is how black folk
are very creative.
He's out here
workin' his ass off.
He needs to take his drunk-ass
and drink that beer and go on.
So why don'tcha come
with me to my place
[all] Oh!
Can you do that?
That's skills. Right.