[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
[WOMAN] Here you go.
Here you go.
- [FOLDERS THUD]
- All yours, Sofia.
- Sorry, what am I supposed to...
- Not my problem.
Mm.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS SADLY]
Miss Dunham.
Oh, Sofia. Wonderful.
Can you get me an espresso
before I pass out
looking at the god-awful logos
that corporate sent over?
I don't know why
they insist on doing my job for me.
There's not a creative mind
in the entire bunch.
Yeah. Yeah, Miss... Uh, yeah,
I can do that for you. Um...
Before I do that, I...
I was also wondering, uh...
[SPUTTERING] I... I thought that I...
- I thought that...
- Oh my God, spit it out.
So, I've been your assistant
for, like, two years now?
Or a little over two years, and, um,
I just thought it was time
to talk about, you know, the fa...
the fact that my job
is, um, answering phones
and proofing and scheduling,
and I don't actually get
to do any graphic design.
[SIGHS] I hired you to be my assistant,
not my protégé.
And I thought you understood that
when you took the job.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I did. Uh...
I just thought that if I could show you
that I could handle more responsibility
then something might fall to me.
There's an entire office
full of people with master's degrees
waiting for something to open up for them.
So I don't think anything is going
to fall to one of my assistants.
Yeah, okay, uh...
So, what do I do?
[SIGHS]
Hmm.
Oh, love.
I'm gonna do you a favor.
Thank you. Oh, wow.
I really appreciate it.
I'm gonna let you go.
[CHUCKLES]
Sorry, what?
Yeah, two years is way too long
to be somebody's assistant.
Most people leave the job
after six months.
How old are you?
I turn 30 tomorrow.
Ew. You are way too old
to be answering phones.
[CHUCKLES] You know,
there's something for you out there,
but it's not here.
So, I'm going to ask you to reconsider.
I don't think you...
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- Yeah, go for Becky.
[KNOCKS ON DESK] Yeah, I'm ready.
[PANTING] Up, up, up, up.
- Okay.
- One. Yeah, yeah. Down, down, down.
Up, up, up, up.
Seize the day.
What?!
Also, thank you
for the birthday card, guys.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[WOMAN] What's her problem?
- Ow!
- [OBJECTS CLATTER]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN] Zooey.
Zooey, get your butt in the seat.
- [CHILD BLOWS RASPBERRY]
- [WOMAN] One, two...
Thank you. Would you like your juice?
No.
It's apple juice, honey.
It's your favorite.
[ZOOEY] I don't like it.
[WOMAN] Oh.
Well, yesterday,
you really liked apple juice.
All right, well, I think
it's nap time when we get home
with the way you're acting.
- [ZOOEY] Nope. I'm going somewhere else.
- [WOMAN] Where might you be going?
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Richard, are you home?
[RICHARD] Sofia?
Hey.
I have kind of a funny story.
I quit my job today.
[OBJECTS THUDDING]
Wanted me to sign my own birthday card.
[SMACKING LIPS]
- [OBJECTS THUDDING]
- Richard.
Honey, are you okay?
Hey.
Hey, baby.
You go back to bed?
No, I was, uh... I was just...
No, that's not...
[CHUCKLES] What's going on?
Also, why are there
two sandwiches out here?
- Oh, I...
- [CLATTERING]
[CLEARS THROAT] I, uh, didn't...
I didn't know what I wanted, so I just...
- I got... two.
- [CLATTERING]
Is that a puppy in there?
[CREAKING]
That better be a puppy, Richard.
[RICHARD SIGHS]
[WOMAN GRUNTS]
Hi.
Were you gonna jump out of that?
'Cause I would love to see you try.
- I probably shouldn't.
- [SOFIA] Yeah.
Babe, I... [SIGHS] Uh...
[VOICE BREAKS] Um,
I'll be back in an hour.
Tell your girlfriend to go home
and don't be here when I get back.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh my God. Damn it!
[GRUNTS]
Damn it! [SHRIEKS, EXCLAIMS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[SOFIA] God.
Oh my God, Sofia, are you okay?
Do not! Do not come down here!
I was just gonna come down and help you.
You've got one hour, dick!
- [SHUDDERS]
- Okay.
- Go!
[SOFIA GROANS]
Oh, this is not my day.
[EXHALES SHAKILY] It is not my day.
[GENTLE SWEEPING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENING]
[NAIL TAPPING]
[GASPS] You know
what my favorite time of day is?
When I get to say good morning to you.
Good morning, Mother.
Oh, honey. Good morning, my dear.
How is my little baby bird today, hmm?
- I'm still stuck in the nest.
- Mm?
You know what? I made you some breakfast.
You got a big day ahead of you.
No, I don't remember
seeing anything on my schedule.
You know, you've been
in your little poop place long enough.
And I want you to come
to my Zumba class today.
Mom, the doctor, I think, is gonna have
something to say about me Zumba'ing.
I told all the girls that you're in town,
and they're just dying to meet you.
- Mom.
- Honey.
No, no, no, no. Don't "Mom" me.
You're going to go, honey.
- We gotta get you back up on your feet...
- [SIGHS]
Your foot. Your f...
[CHUCKLING] Your crutches.
Come on, honey. You know what?
Your new life is not going
to find you under the covers.
- Okay, okay.
- We gotta grab it.
- Okay.
- They're gonna absolutely adore you.
[GIGGLES]
["LA FIESTA SOY YO"
BY ENZO VILLAPAREDES PLAYS]
Five, six, seven, and over. There ya go!
Two. I mean four.
[LAUGHS] Six.
Okay. And now it's touch time.
When you feel ready, add the shoulders.
Pat yourself on the back.
- [WOMEN LAUGH]
- [CHUCKLING] That's it. You deserve it.
If you get lost, follow Julietta.
And now we're going to merengue!
- This is something like that. [LAUGHS]
- [WOMEN LAUGHING]
Keep your hands up high.
Take 'em down low, low.
Yeah, I know.
So we'll see you next time, hmm?
[SOFIA] I work
as a graphic designer in the city.
Oh, my goodness. Who do you do that for?
That's a... That's a good question. I...
She's between jobs so she can spend time
with her lonely mother in Sonoma.
- How long are you staying?
- Uh, I don't know. I...
Probably until I can put
some weight on this ankle,
'cause it's just kind of hard
to get around the city in crutches.
Yeah. I'm gonna have her dancing Zumba
next to you, Julietta, before you know it.
Well, if anyone can put
a little salsa in your butt, it's her.
- Mm, a girl can dream, right?
- [LAUGHS]
- Oh! She is such a cute darling.
- I know.
- Thank you.
- [SIGHS]
Well, I gotta go shower off
before Alejandro gets home.
He and I have this
little post-Zumba ritual.
It's the only way
I can get rid of the extra energy.
[CHUCKLES] That's my girl.
[JULIETTA LAUGHS]
Bye.
Oh my gosh. She and Alejandro have sex.
I got that.
Well, you survived.
Yeah. Your old guys and gals
really got it goin' on.
Thank you for that view
into my very, very near future.
[LAUGHS] Oh, stop.
Oh, look.
- What?
- It's a... a cooking class.
"Learn Spanish summer dishes
at El Corazon."
- Oh, I love that place.
- Mm-hmm.
- You should sign up.
- No, I'm good.
- But why? Why not?
- 'Cause I know how to cook.
What? What do you make?
I make anything.
I make chicken, steak, fish, rice...
- That... No, that...
- Noodles, potatoes. I...
That's not cooking,
that's just heating things up.
- Yeah, that's cooking.
- No, no. Cooking's more creative.
It's... It's... Okay.
How do you prepare your chicken?
- How do I prepare my chicken?
- Mm-hmm.
I warn it that the pan
is going to be very hot.
- [LAUGHS]
- And then I drop it in.
I'm signing you up.
Mom, that's a couples cooking class.
- Do I look like I'm in a couple right now?
- Well, I can be your couple.
I can't think of anything
more tragic than what you just said.
[CHUCKLES] Oh, don't be silly.
Mom, seriously, the idea of being
in a couple literally gives me hives.
I don't want to be in a kitchen
staring at a bunch of lovebirds
making tapas and googly eyes
at each other.
- So, please. Come on, just do it for me.
- No, Mom. Don't sign me up.
- I'm serious.
- Okay.
[PAPER TEARS]
[FLAMENCO MUSIC PLAYING]
[NAIL TAPPING]
Good morning, Mother.
Good morning, my dear.
Come on. Wake up.
We're going to have fun at the spa today.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay. All right. We're here.
Oh, this isn't the spa.
Oh. Oh God, I forgot. Spa's tomorrow.
- [INHALES SHARPLY]
- Okay, then what are we...
Mom... I said no.
Oh, come on, honey, please.
I specifically said no.
Just, you know what? Just one class.
If you don't like it,
I swear we'll never come back.
Do you see what I'm wearing right now?
This is child abuse.
[SCOFFS] You're 30.
- Then it's grown human abuse.
- [MUMBLES]
You know, you're being so dramatic.
It's just one stupid class.
Mom. I'm not going in.
- Oh, Sofia.
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
This is stupid.
You take the class by yourself,
see how you like it.
Okay. Okay, let's go.
No, you go. I'm going to wait here.
It's a couples class. I need my couple.
Mom, I'm not going. No.
- Honey, come on. Get your butt out.
- I...
- No, you get your butt... Don't! Mom!
- Get...
- Stop pulling me!
- Don't talk like that.
- You're gonna break my other ankle.
- No.
- Get your butt out of the car.
- Mom, stop!
Excuse me, excuse me. Do you, uh...
Did you need some help?
Oh my God.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, you know what? I think we might.
I can't seem to get
my daughter out of the car.
- And she's got a bad ankle.
- It's... Mom!
Okay. Oh, okay, uh,
here let me try. It's okay.
- No, I can do it myself. Look.
- No, no.
- I'm just being...
- This'll... This will be easier.
Um, just put your arm around my neck.
[CHUCKLES]
- Okay.
- Okay?
Okay. And now, ready?
- We'll just... There you go.
- Aw.
And we're just gonna hop up nice and easy.
- Okay.
- There you go, there you go.
There we go.
Uh, and these, uh...
- These are yours, no? [CHUCKLES]
- How did you guess?
- Oh, thank you so much.
- Yes, of course.
I just couldn't... couldn't get her
out of there. [CHUCKLES]
I don't know why the car was giving her
such trouble. [INHALES SHARPLY]
[CHUCKLES] Anyway,
I think we've got it now, so...
Okay. Glad I could help.
- Yup. Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Yeah.
- [GROANS] Sorry, sorry.
- No, it's okay. Sorry, sorry.
[CHUCKLES] Thanks again. Thank you.
- Mom, I don't know where to go.
- Okay. We're gonna go this way. Come on.
Hi.
Hello, welcome to El Corazon.
Uh, how can I help you?
Oh, are you here for the class?
- For the cooking class, yes.
- Oh.
Uh, you... you do know
it's for... for couples?
Okay...
- [SOFIA] Yeah, yeah.
- Mm. Um...
No better couple than mother-daughter.
Okay.
Of course!
- [CHUCKLES]
- [LAUGHS] Yes, please join them inside.
Oh, okay. Looks fun already. Come on.
Hi, sorry. [CHUCKLES]
And yes, I see we have our final couple.
Venga, venga.
- This is your spot right here.
- Thank you.
- You must be, uh, Lainie and Sofia, yes?
- Mm-hmm.
Which is which?
- I'm Lainie. This is my daughter, Sofia.
- I'm just gonna... Hi.
Ah! Que monada.
So wonderful. Yes.
- Oh, I got this. It's okay. Thank you.
- You sure?
Are you gonna be okay
with that, uh, chair, my dear?
- Yeah. Is it okay that I sit?
- Oh, no, no, no. That's fine. [CHUCKLES]
You put these on and we begin, yes?
Let us start with
the quick hellos of the couples.
Um, you go first. Yes?
Okay, I'm Kerala.
- This is my husband, Frank.
- Hi.
We run the, um, bed-and-breakfast
up on West view.
Oh.
And we just thought we'd find something
to get our butts out of the house, right?
[LAUGHS] That's about right.
[ALL LAUGH]
Of course. Perfect.
And, uh, you next.
Hi, I'm Todd.
Uh, hi, I'm, uh, David.
Um, we own the Sonoma Creamery.
- Ooh, I love your cheeses.
- Yeah.
Oh, thank you. We cheese to please.
[ALL LAUGH]
- [DAVID] Todd, please. No.
- [TODD] Okay. So...
Uh, we do a lot of cooking together,
and we wanted to learn,
uh, new Spanish dishes.
Mm.
So here we are.
[SNAPS FINGERS] Olé!
[ALL LAUGH]
So wonderful.
[CHUCKLES] And, uh, you?
Uh, we're Chad and Brittany.
We met online.
Hi, everyone.
And we thought, what's more romantic...
- [MOUTHING]
- ...than taking a cooking class together?
Maybe get to know
each other a little better.
Cooking can be very romantic and intimate.
Yes. And so can eating.
[LAUGHS]
Okay, you two ladies.
- Oh, um, we're not dating. No.
- [STUDENTS CHUCKLE]
- Surprise.
- No.
We're... We're, um, Lainie and Sofia,
the mother-daughter couple.
And, uh, normally Sofia lives
in San Francisco,
but she's going through
a little life change. Yeah?
And, uh, so she's staying here
in Sonoma with me now.
And right at this moment,
I wish I was dead.
- [LAINIE] What? Aw.
- [GUILLERMO] Oh!
No dying here, please.
Only cooking. [LAUGHS]
Well, we have lots to do so, um...
As you know, uh, I am Guillermo
and I am a couple, too.
My wife, she is busy today,
but I am joined by my nephew
who is here from Spain for the month.
Uh, where is Matias?
Matias?
Tío, Tío. Sorry, uh...
Sorry, Tío, I had to get
something from my car.
Matias... Oh, I'm sorry.
- Isn't he...
- Mm-hmm.
Matias has studied with some
of the finest chefs in all of Europe.
But now he gets to learn from the best.
His tío Guillermo.
[LAUGHS]
Nice to meet you all, um,
officially.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- Hi.
So, we will be making
delicious dishes for the summer
leading all the way up
to La Noche de San Juan.
This is the celebration
of the summer solstice,
the longest day of the year.
This is when, um, friends and loved ones,
they gather on the beaches
of Spain with big fires
to welcome the arrival of summer.
- Oh, how lovely.
- That's lovely.
- Oh! Jinx!
- [ALL LAUGH]
And, uh, today we will start
with, uh, one of the most popular dishes
in Spain, the tortilla Española.
What you call the Spanish omelet.
- [LAINIE] Ooh!
- Ah?
Oh. [CHUCKLES]
- Egg.
- [GUILLERMO] Ah, huevos.
- Muy bien.
- Thank you, huevos.
- So fun, so fun.
- Oh, yeah, eggs.
Cut your potatoes into quarters
and then you slice them
into little triangles.
[INTRIGUING CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Watch your fingers, honey.
You watch yourself
while I'm holding this knife.
- Oh.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
They should be about this thick
for the best taste.
How's Sofia doing?
Yeah, those look, uh, very good actually.
Uh, lucky you do not need
to use your foot for this, huh?
[LAUGHING]
[TODD] He's so cute.
And then you sprinkle
a little truffle salt on your potatoes
once they are cut.
Kerala, those look wonderful.
- Thanks, Guillermo.
- I... I put the salt on.
[GUILLERMO] Oh! Well...
[BRITTANY] Hey, cut it out.
[KERALA] That's a no-no.
- [GASPS SOFTLY] Oh!
- No. It's not gonna last.
[PAN SIZZLING]
[GUILLERMO] Keep on beating them
until they are good and mixed.
Take out all of your frustrations
out on those eggs, huh?
This is gonna be a killer omelet.
Oh. You seem very, uh, angry
at those eggs.
[LAINIE CHUCKLES]
Yeah, I've got, like,
a lot of frustration to take out.
So, just...
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Seems healthy. Safe. Yeah.
- What? Stop.
- What? What?
- Focus on your potatoes.
- [MATIAS] Very mediocre. Good job.
Now, this is the fun part.
You will take your tortilla flipper,
or a plate or a lid
if you are not from Spain
and do not have a tortilla flipper,
and you will cover the pan. Mm?
And then you will flip
your tortilla quickly, like so.
Eh?
Oh, just like that, huh?
- Oh, you can do this! I promise.
- [TODD] All right, all right.
- [EXCLAIMS]
- [GUILLERMO] Yes!
- [LAUGHS]
- Okay.
[GUILLERMO LAUGHS]
- [SOFIA] And then...
- [GUILLERMO] Yeah!
- That's not terrible.
- Oh!
- I'm a chef! [LAUGHS]
- Right? We made it.
Now what? Now what?
Uh, you just put it back in the pan
and, uh, you cook the other side.
- [SOFIA] Slide it?
- [LAINIE] Yeah, slide it.
Oh, a little of that.
[CHUCKLES] Yes!
- Okay. Oh, we got a runner!
- [SOFIA] Oh, shoot!
- Sorry, sorry. Get right there.
- It's okay. See, look.
No, no. Oh, it's okay. There. No worries.
- So exciting.
- There, good as new, okay?
- Okay, okay. We can take it from here.
- Okay. Of course.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Make sure it's nice and round.
Matias, is this... is this a problem?
That can be saved.
- Oh, yay. Okay.
- Oh, good.
Be nice.
I am being nice.
You be less nice. How about that?
Double flip.
[ALL EXCLAIM]
And now for the best part.
We get to eat what we have made.
[LAUGHING]
And you can put a little, uh,
salt and pepper on it, if you like.
- [LAINIE] Okay. Looks great.
- Bit of salt.
I like more truffle salt. [LAUGHS]
Oh my God. Oh my God, this is fantastic.
Guillermo, I love it.
[LAUGHS] So wonderful.
Uh, this is the perfect dish
for any tapas party,
and you should not have one without it.
That's true, that's true.
[LAINIE] Oh, God, well, I... I love it.
It's not not good.
"Not not good." Ooh, and the onions...
- It's actually...
- Truffle salt.
- It's the truffle salt.
- Okay, I'm good after this.
That was fun.
I know I had a really good time.
- We'll see you all next week, yes? Yes.
- Oh, you can count on it!
- [GUILLERMO CHUCKLES] Thank you.
- That was fun. Bye!
- Oh, bye. Nice meeting you.
- Good night.
- This was better.
- Uh, thank you.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Bye, see you.
[MATIAS] Bye. Thank you, man.
[EXCLAIMS REPEATEDLY] No, look.
When you cook at home, you clean up.
But when you cook here,
we clean up. Right, Tío?
- [LAUGHS]
- Que claro.
- Oh, I love the sound of that.
- Yeah, you do.
- Yes.
- Ah.
- Oh, I can...
- Here.
No, but would you be needing help,
uh, to your... to your car?
No, my mom and I have got it.
Thanks.
[CHUCKLES] Yeah. I'll be outside.
I...
Uh, let me help. This... here.
- No, no, no, I... I can grab...
- No, it's okay. I can help, it's okay.
No, it's nothing. Don't worry, no trouble.
- Thank you.
- Hey, de nada. Yeah.
- Then let... I can carry.
- I can grab it.
It's okay. It's... Please. Oh.
Thanks.
So did you enjoy the class?
- Honestly, not really, no.
- Why not?
'Cause I just spent an hour
making eggs and potatoes.
Yeah, but that is just the basics.
It's... It's the personal touches,
the flavor, that make it, um, special.
- Mm.
- You know, like my uncle's truffle salt.
Which, between you and me,
is always the secret ingredient.
Well, between you and me,
it's a pretty simple dish.
Yeah, well, many of the old recipes
began with the simplest of ingredients
because it was all that people
could afford at the time.
It's not exactly fine dining, is it?
[CHUCKLES] N... No.
No, it's... it's traditional dining,
which is, uh, in many ways, harder
than having everything you want
to make a dish.
I don't know,
I think IHOP kind of crushes it
with the Rooty Tooty
Fresh 'n Fruity breakfast.
Is that fine dining?
No, but it gets the job done.
Yeah, of c... Eating is not a job.
Eating is one
of life's greatest pleasures, you know?
Yeah, sometimes it's life's only pleasure.
What... What... What does that mean?
I think I hear my mom calling me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Do you wanna follow me to the car?
- Yes, of course.
- Or should I hobble with the box in hand?
- No, no, I will help you.
So, uh, you will be back
next week though, yes?
- Oh, yes. Oh, we'll be back.
- I...
- Okay, okay.
- You can count on that.
I guess we will.
Uh, just, um, promise me,
between now and then,
no, uh, Rooty Tooty-whatever.
- No more Rooty Tooty?
- Yeah.
It's gonna be hard, but I'll try.
- Uh...
- Thank you.
Great job. Hasta la próxima, Lainie.
- Hasta to you, too.
- [SOFIA CHUCKLES]
- Thank you.
- Oh, I can... I can help you if you need.
- I... Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- Here, let me.
- I... Thank you.
Yup. Careful. Okay.
- Okay, uh, you can just shut the door.
- Okay. Sí.
Yup.
- Hasta luego.
- [SIGHS SOFTLY] Okay.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[SIGHS] What?
Did you make a friend?
I walked two students to their car.
I was being polite.
Incredible. You've only been here
a few days and you already captured
the heart of an American girl.
That's not the message I was getting.
- Trust me.
- You know I'm dating Irina.
Oh! Irina. Yeah, she's dating you.
- And half of Europe.
- You don't know that.
Anyone with an Instagram account
knows that.
Go out with the American girl.
She's cutie.
I have a job to do. You do yours.
Papa! Matias was born with no huevos.
Viviana, leave your cousin alone.
He is alone.
That's the point.
He seemed nice, huh?
Mm. Seemed Spanish.
What's wrong with that?
Spanish men are players, Mom.
Everybody knows that.
[CHUCKLES] No, I didn't get...
I didn't get a player vibe.
Mm-hmm, and that's
because Spanish men are charmers
with their... accents and their big smiles.
Well, I like big smiles, so...
Hey, let's go... let's go back
to the restaurant and have dinner tonight,
just see if he's working.
Mm.
Yeah, okay, so you want to stalk him.
No... No, he's... He's new in town.
- He might need a friend to hang with.
- So go hang with him, Mom.
You need to get out of the house, honey.
I am. I'm gonna go have dinner
with Olivia on Friday.
Oh, well, why didn't you tell me?
- I have to tell you when I make plans?
- [VOICE SQUEAKS]
Okay, yeah. That's just...
That's really rich because you made plans
for us to go to a cooking class today
and nobody told me about it.
Honey, I just was happy to hear
that you're feeling better, that's all.
Mom, I'm not some sort of basket case.
Well... [CHUCKLES]
You were a bit of a basket case.
- Mom.
- You... And now that's over and yay.
- Yay.
Okay.
[GROOVY MUSIC PLAYS]
[OLIVIA] How much longer
do you need those?
[SOFIA] Um, I find out later this week
if I can start putting weight on it.
And that is one last gift from Richard.
God. I would like to break
both of that boy's legs.
You're welcome to, you have my permission.
[LAUGHS] Honey, why were you
with him for so long?
[SIGHS] I don't know.
He was there and he was safe,
and we could hang
our prom photo up in the living room.
- Mm, barf.
- I know.
I was just scared
of moving to San Francisco.
It was just easier to do it with him.
The wedding vows
just write themselves, huh?
- Shut up. I know.
- [LAUGHS]
[INHALES SHARPLY] Anyway,
how are you and your little family?
- Um, Dennis has been good.
- Yeah?
Yeah, he, uh, actually
just got a small promotion.
- Really? That's amazing.
- Yeah.
- And Ella won't stop being a chatterbox.
- Oh! What is she saying?
Gum and teeth, gum and teeth. [BABBLES]
Oh, okay. This... She's an intelligent one.
She get it from her mama.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
- Yes, she does.
You know, Dennis has actually
been really good with Ella. Surprising.
Yeah.
God, you're so lucky. He's...
He's honestly one
of the only good ones left.
None of them are good ones, Sof.
You have to train them all
and retrain them.
- Oh, right. Retrain them. Yes.
- And then retrain them and retrain...
Hi, ladies. Uh, what can I get you?
- Um, we'll have a volcano bowl to start.
- Yeah.
Do you know what you wanna eat?
Do you have omelets?
[CHUCKLES] No, sorry.
- Seriously?
- Just asking.
Chicken fingers for me, please.
Me, too.
Good choice.
I'll be right back with your drink.
Thank you.
You want an omelet at a bar?
- No, not really.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
I... I just can't stop thinking
about this cooking class
that I'm taking with my mom.
Um, we made Spanish omelets this week.
- You took a class to make an omelet?
- I did. Yes.
Okay, uh, let me guess.
You put eggs in a pan.
- Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
- You put stuff in it and you cook it.
No! That's why it's funny.
- What?
- This was different. It was different.
This was super, super simple, but...
special somehow.
And so now you can't stop
thinking about omelets.
Yeah, something like that.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYS]
I need that, uh, paella, Matias.
It's coming, coming.
So?
Wonderful?
So wonderful.
Thank you.
- What's next?
- Uh, well, we can finish up, Matias.
- Why don't you call it a night, eh?
- No. Are... Are you sure? I'm still good.
No, no, no.
There's only a few tables left.
You did good work tonight.
- ["JULIANNE" BY EVERLY PLAYING IN BAR]
- ♪ And his name was Henry ♪
♪ A man without a mother... ♪
[SIGHS] Uh... Hey, miss.
Ew.
♪ Let me tell you about Henry ♪
♪ Henry was born in a travellin' band... ♪
I will be so happy
when going to the bathroom
is not a full-body workout.
[CHUCKLES] I bet.
- All right, where we going next?
- Ugh, I can't, I have to go home.
What? I finally get a night out with you
and calling it quits?
Girl, Ella wakes up at the crack of dawn
whether I am hungover or not.
I prefer not.
- God, she's... She's so needy.
- [OLIVIA CHUCKLES]
Uh, excuse me.
I'll be right with you.
[CRUTCHES CLACKING]
I saw some really cute guys in there.
You know what? Maybe that's what you need,
is to find yourself a new man.
Oh, God!
That is the last thing that I need.
Men suck and they betray you
every chance they get.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
- [PHONE CHIMES]
Oh, that's my car. Uh, you good?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm good.
Mine's, like, a couple minutes away.
Okay. You know, boys suck.
I'm talking about finding you
a real man, okay?
That's our top priority
next time we hang out.
Okay. Let me get through the summer
without getting
completely heartbroken again,
and then we'll re-evaluate
that whole situation.
- [SPEAKS SPANISH]
- You gotta give me a minute, man.
Love you, be safe. Bye.
Tell Ella I say hi.
[OLIVIA] You got it.
- Sofia?
- Yeah.
Matias.
Hi. I did not see you there.
Oh, I just... I just, um, stopped in
to... to get a drink. Yeah.
How was it?
I don't know.
I couldn't get the bartender's attention.
[SNIFFS]
[LAUGHS] Okay, so
what? You just... gave up?
I guess I did.
Okay. I think
I'm going to have to teach you
to be, like, a little more rude
if you're going to survive in America.
[CHUCKLES]
So, tell me, how was, uh,
Ducey's Tavern for dinner?
It was good.
They have the best chicken fingers.
Chickens do not have fingers.
I'm sorry, are you telling me
that Spaniards don't have chicken fingers?
Okay, so then tell me what, um...
What spices do you put
on these chicken fingers?
Uh, whatever's in the ranch dressing.
Your chickens have fingers
and now they're getting
dressed on the ranch, right?
- [BOTH LAUGH]
- So now I have heard it all.
This is America, we're full of surprises.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
- [PHONE CHIMES]
My ride's here.
Um...
So, when will I learn
how to order a drink in, uh, America?
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
I should probably get home.
Yeah. Yeah, of course, of course.
But I will see you in class, yes?
Yeah. Yeah.
Um, oh, good.
- Okay.
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
No, no, after you. Go. I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
- De nada, querida.
Wait, what does that mean?
Um, de nada is thank...
"You are welcome," um, "my dear."
Of course.
Buenas noches, Sofia.
Buenas noches, my dear.
Sorry! Bye.
- [CRUTCHES CLACKING]
- [SOFIA GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- Hi, are you Sofia?
- That's me.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ALARM CLOCK BEEPING]
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
[LAINIE] Any luck?
No, there's... there's seriously
not a lot out there, and...
I'm realizing that leaving my job
right after all the design graduates
hit the workforce
was not the greatest idea.
[CLICKS TONGUE] Aw.
What is that?
Might have to consider
getting my master's degree.
Oh, that's... that's a commitment.
Yeah, I don't know
if I have a future without it.
[TYPING]
Is that a good school?
Yeah. It's close. So that's good, right?
[CHUCKLES] Well, you know
I love having you around.
Yeah.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[TENDER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Ugh.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[LIGHT COMIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[VIVIANA SIGHS]
Well, at least when she dates other men,
you get to see it happen.
Those pictures are from her work.
They don't mean anything.
Oh. So, where does she work?
A kissing booth?
Go away.
[SCOFFS] Matias, you're stuck.
You need to release that fish
to catch the prize.
She is not a fish.
No. No, no, no, no. She's a shark.
- [SCREAMS] Get out of the water!
- Oh my God. Leave me alone!
["LONDON SHOW" BY AMELIA RAE
PLAYS ON SPEAKER]
♪ London, show me how to love the rain ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm pouring and I feel insane ♪
♪ Silky smooth but flooding up inside ♪
♪ Keep it pouring
And pouring and pouring ♪
...John's wort.
Hey, Mom, can I borrow the iron?
- Oh, I'll do that for you, honey. Here.
- Oh, thanks. Oh!
- Ooh... Ooh...
- Are you okay?
- What's wrong?
- I have... [GROANS] ...these stomach cramps.
Oh, Mom, sit down. I can iron a dress.
Oh God.
- You okay?
- Oh. Yeah.
- Okay.
- [INHALES SHARPLY] Oh my gosh.
Oh gosh, honey, I don't... I don't think
I can go with you to the class.
Mom. No, I'm not going alone
to the couples class.
- We paid for it and somebody should go.
- Mom. Forget it. No.
We're gonna survive
not knowing how to make pancakes.
[LAINIE] Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[TENDER MUSIC PLAYS]
We have truffle salt.
Yeah.
You know, I'm thinking
what if you just went... just went
for a little bit of the class,
stayed for...
I'm gonna go.
What?
Yeah, I'm gonna go.
Wait... You're gonna... You're gonna go?
Yes, ma'am.
So we made the tortilla Española
for our, uh, bed and breakfast guests.
- You made it. Mostly.
- I... Okay, good point. I totally made it.
- They loved it.
- [KERALA LAUGHS]
- Hi, everyone.
- [KERALA] Hi!
[SOFIA] Hi.
[BOTH] Where's your mom?
- Oh!
- [BOTH LAUGH]
Uh, she does not feel very well.
So she encouraged me
to hobble here without her.
[DAVID] No crutches?
No, thank God.
Apparently the bone is mostly healed now.
- So, it's exciting stuff. Yeah.
- [ALL ENCOURAGE]
Okay, my good people.
Let's settle in, eh?
Uh, I see we are short one chef today.
Yeah, sorry. She doesn't feel very well.
Oh, well, that's good.
I mean, it's not good, but este...
Matias. Matias will be
your partner for today's class.
Are you sure he can keep up?
[STUDENTS LAUGHING]
Just kidding. Just kidding, Matias.
He's coming along quickly this one,
I... I'm sure he'll be just fine.
Oh, thank you, Tío. Thank you.
Okay, today, we are going
to make gazpacho. Mm!
Nice.
[GUILLERMO] It is the perfect dish
for the summer
'cause when it is hot
and... and everybody's sweaty,
and you give them a little gazpacho,
and everyone is much happier. Eh?
The secret to gazpacho
is ripe tomatoes.
[ROMANTIC FLAMENCO MUSIC PLAYS]
- Honey, the... Your fingers.
- Yes.
- I'm doing the knuckle thing.
- [KERALA] Yikes!
Do not lose the juicy seeds.
They give depth to the flavor.
- How am I...
- What?
How am I not supposed
to lose the juicy seeds?
- Quick, quick cuts, clean and fast.
- Not... Okay.
[MATIAS] Be careful. Okay?
- Yeah, that's perfect. Perfect. Good.
- This is so much work.
That's... Why do you think this is work?
It's not. Look, it's a...
it's a joy to cook.
I... No, I don't... I don't think
I have the cooking gene.
It's just not in there.
- What is this gene?
- [CHUCKLES] I'm not born to do this.
We are not born to do anything.
We're just born to lie there and cry,
and we learn everything we do.
And you can learn this.
Look, you're learning it.
- Wow.
- What?
I've just realized why
I'm so good at lying around and crying.
I... I've been doing it my entire life.
Oh. [CHUCKLES]
- Yes. Okay.
- I'm a professional lier around and crier.
Okay, now you're going to be
a professional tomato cutter.
[GUILLERMO] You need
a good coating of olive oil
to give your dish a creamy flavor.
And then,
sherry vinegar from the hills of Spain.
[SNIFFS AND SIGHS]
It's a strong complement
to the flavors of your ingredients.
And remember,
no balsamic vinegar ever in gazpacho, eh?
Do you smell that?
Now, we will mix the ingredients.
We will get our hands dirty.
[GUILLERMO AND KERALA LAUGH]
- Do you want to dive in first?
- No, no.
You are the one
with frustrations to get out, no?
- Yeah. No, I was just asking.
- Go on, you try it.
Go, go. All right.
- Ew.
- Go. Go, go!
But get in. Get in, get in.
Eh? [CHUCKLES]
- [SOFIA GRUNTS]
- [MATIAS] Ah.
Keep going. Squeeze. Uh-huh.
Now, pat down. Now, pat down.
Pat down. Get it out, get it out.
- Keep squeezing?
- Then I turn. Yeah. Keep...
- You were very angry the other day.
- [GRUNTING]
[GUILLERMO] Now, you must let
the juices marinate for at least an hour,
but overnight is better.
Yes.
So all that is left now
is we blend the soup and we are done.
And when do we cook it?
[CHUCKLES] Oh, no, no, no!
No, we do not cook gazpacho.
- Oh.
- [GUILLERMO] No. No.
- It is done when it is the consistency...
- Sure.
...of how you would like to eat it.
- I'm a chunky monkey myself.
- [ALL LAUGH]
I'm taking the class
for a reason, I guess.
[WHIRRING]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYS]
[BOTH SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[MATIAS] That goes to the side. Twist.
- Do you want to press the button?
- [CHUCKLES] Yeah.
[WHIRRING]
[MATIAS] Mm?
Mm, mm.
[MATIAS CHUCKLES]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
That's so good. We did that.
[DIALOGUE IMPERCEPTIBLE]
Thank you for being my partner today.
- It was my pleasure.
- [LAUGHS]
My mom's actually gonna love this.
You should give that to her
with some summer sangria.
Absolutely not. No.
Why not?
Boxed wine, apple slices, and 7 Up?
- Mm, that... No, no. That is not sangria.
- I'm gonna pass on giving that to her.
- That's definitely sangria.
- Okay. No, no, no.
- You're gonna sit and you're gonna try.
- Like right now?
Yes, yes! Right now is always
the best time for sangria.
Go, come on. Come on.
- Okay.
- Please, sit. Okay?
[GENTLE SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MATIAS CLEARS THROAT]
- Oh, okay.
- Okay. Okay, now wait.
- [VIVIANA] I'll get your menus.
Okay.
Is this a chicken finger?
- Mm. [CHUCKLES] No.
- You sure?
No, that is a croqueta
for you to try with your sangria.
- Okay.
- Okay? So, look, look, look.
The fruits have been marinated
in brandy and sugar.
Okay? And then combined
with a Spanish Rueda,
and now you top it
with a nice crisp dry Cava.
- Mm.
- Okay?
- Great.
Yeah.
Please don't tell me
you're going to stand the whole time.
- Oh, no. [LAUGHS]
- 'Cause that's...
- No, no, no. I sit, I sit.
- Okay.
Okay, so go.
- Now you try a bite of your croqueta.
- Okay.
Uh-huh.
A-ha.
And now a sip of the sangria.
- Salud. Salud.
- Salud.
Yeah, that's, uh...
that's really delicious.
- You see?
- Yeah.
You see, when food
is done in just, um, the right way,
it can be the most, um,
sensual experience that there is.
- Sensual?
- Uh-huh.
Yes, it's like licking
whipped cream off of boobies.
Um...
That is sexual.
- Oh!
- No, no.
- Okay, sorry. [LAUGHS]
- What I mean is sensual.
In the sense that all five
of your senses are... are triggered.
The look and the smell...
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS]
...of the food.
The taste...
of course.
And... the way it feels...
in your mouth.
Actually, no, that's... that's
not all five senses,
'cause I can't hear the food.
No, not the food itself,
but the sounds of joy
and laughter and "Mm!"
- Okay.
- Should be a part of every meal.
- I can feel the joy.
- And that is how you trigger the ears.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Salud.
Ah, salud. Yes, yes. Salud.
[CLEARS THROAT]
So, um, what is it that you do, Sofia?
Me? Um...
Sorry.
I'm a graphic designer.
What is this?
Um...
Okay, like, see this label here.
Um, someone has to decide,
- "Oh, I'm gonna put a señorita on there."
- [CHUCKLES]
"And I'm going to give her a basket,
put a flowery hat on her head,"
and make her super happy
"as though collecting fruit
is the coolest job in the world."
That's a graphic designer's job.
So, it is like cooking.
- No, it's not at all like cooking.
- Of course it is.
Look, you... you take all the ingredients
and you put them together,
and then all the flavors
make a final dish.
No. Because in design,
there's no recipe to follow.
Mm. And where do you think
recipes come from? From the stars?
[CHUCKLES] No, okay?
People have put together
all the flavors over many years.
Making many works of art.
And you are a chef of pictures.
Okay. Well, you make it sound, like,
way more romantic than it actually is.
It's actually, like,
really hard work sometimes.
And do you think of many things as work?
Yeah. When it's my job, I do.
But does it not bring you, um, happiness
to design these pictures?
Yeah, of course it does. It's just...
My entire life has been me
trying to, like, prove myself
in one way or another,
'cause people look at me
and they judge me because I'm a woman
or because I'm young or because...
'Cause you are beautiful.
[CHUCKLES] Uh...
Thank you, um...
- Because of how I look, I would say. Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
But your pictures, they...
they speak for themselves, no?
Not always, no.
What would you, um...
What would you design for me?
- For you?
- Yes, for my restaurant.
- Oh, do you have a restaurant?
- Oh, no. No, no. I'm still learning.
But, uh, my dream is to one day become
a master chef and have my own restaurant.
Okay, um...
Well, I'd have to get to know you.
- Like, a lot better.
- Mm-hmm.
I'd have to know what kind of food
you're serving at your restaurant,
what kind of atmosphere
you want to create.
- Um, you know, all that stuff.
- Mm.
Hmm, yeah,
that does sound like a lot of work.
No, I don't think that would be work.
I think... I think that'd be quite fun.
[LAUGHS] Okay.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Papa!
- Matias is giving away the best Cava.
- [MATIAS] Hey. Oh my God.
- Por favor, Viviana.
- He must really like you.
- Save me some.
- Okay.
Ah, you leave them alone.
This is my star student.
Salud, Sofia.
Uh, de nada, querida.
[ALL LAUGH]
Sorry.
So is there, um, anything else
I need to know about you?
Do you have a girlfriend
back in Spain or...
Oh, is this going to be part of the logo?
- Just doing my research.
- Ah.
You know what? I have a better idea.
Uh, Tío, Tío, I... I think
that your, um, star student
needs some extra schoolwork.
Sorry, I... I what?
[LIVELY CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DIALOGUE IMPERCEPTIBLE]
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[SOFIA] Mom, I'm home.
[LAINIE] In here, honey.
Hope you're feeling better
because we've got
some gazpacho to finish... eating.
[RICHARD] Hi.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
Hi.
I, uh, never gave you
your birthday present.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
I forgot how nice it is here. Good times.
Mm-hmm.
Your mom seems... seems good.
You know, my... [CHUCKLES]
My... My parents actually,
they turned my room
into a yoga studio now.
- Mm.
- So, yeah.
And Kristie,
she's graduating high school...
Can you just say
what you came here to say, please?
Okay, I'm... I'm...
I'm really sorry for what I did to you.
And us.
You know, it was selfish and I just wish
I could take everything back.
It didn't mean anything.
- It obviously meant something.
- No. I don't even know that girl.
I will literally never see her again.
No, I'm saying
it meant something about us.
It meant that something
was very, very wrong with us,
and you couldn't talk to me about it.
That's not true.
I was being stupid.
Okay.
So, what? You want me to just forgive you?
I just want you to know that I realize
that I made a really big mistake.
And I truly am sorry.
[TENDER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Of course.
What, honey? It's pretty.
I don't wear necklaces.
Ever.
He doesn't even know that.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[OLIVIA] Shut up!
He thinks you're gonna forgive him?
- He seemed pretty sincere.
- No.
Sofia, when someone shows you
who they are, believe them.
Everybody makes mistakes, Livy.
Meanwhile, you've got Antonio Batatas.
He's literally wining and dining you.
No, he's just being nice.
There's nothing going on there.
I don't know, doesn't sound like it to me.
No, he's Spanish.
It's in his genetic code to flirt.
Girl, he is fine, okay?
You gotta find out.
No. He's going back to Spain
in a few weeks anyways.
So? You're not trying to find true love.
You're trying to avoid
falling back in with true evil.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Yeah.
Right? True evil.
[CHUCKLES]
Here you go.
Liv, I'm tired.
I'm tired of making these big decisions.
What big decisions?
Like quitting my job
and moving out of my place with Richard.
- Those are big decisions.
- Wait, wait. You didn't quit your job.
- Did you?
- Ish.
Oh. Quit-ish.
Yeah, just like you dumped-ish Richard
after he cheated on you?
- Ish.
- [SCOFFS]
Sofia, honey,
you didn't make those decisions.
They were made for you.
Now, you keep letting yourself stay
in these horrible situations
and then you lose a piece of yourself.
And if you get back with Richard,
he's going to be making
that decision for you too.
Because that's what he wants.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYS]
Okay.
Mm? Hmm.
[SIGHS]
Oh, God.
[IN SING-SONG] Hello.
- Oh! Hola, Sofia.
- Hi.
Oh, wow. Your dress is so pretty.
- I love it.
- Thank you, thank you.
Um, is Matias here?
Oh, he got into a little bit of trouble.
What happened?
Well, he's been distracted
the last couple of nights,
and I think I know why.
Mm! No idea.
[VIVIANA LAUGHS]
- He messed up one of the dinners.
- Oh, okay. So, what now? Is he fired or...
You cannot fire family.
You can only torture them.
- [SOFIA] Oh.
- So, he's on lunch shift today.
Oh, okay. That doesn't sound that bad.
That scared me for a second.
Oh, but I do not think
that is the end of Papa's torture.
[MATIAS] Sofia.
- Hi.
- Buenos dias.
Uh, are... are you here to eat?
No, uh, I was gonna see if you wanted me
to show you around, maybe. Um...
Later, I can show you
how to get that drink.
- I would love that. Um...
- I mean, if... if you're free.
Papa!
Uh, Matias is done for the day.
- Ah, my star student.
- Hello. [LAUGHS]
You put my boy's head
back on straight for me, yes?
Yes. I will try.
[GUILLERMO IN SPANISH] Boy's hopeless.
[IN ENGLISH] Sit outside.
I'll be right there.
- Okay, thank you.
- Okay.
Take this off. Take...
Give it here.
One crema Catalana,
compliments of our visiting chef.
Mm. You made this?
I made a batch earlier.
- Yes.
- [VIVIANA] It's delicious.
Yes, he does do some things well.
- [SOFIA] Aw.
- Okay. [LAUGHS]
- [SOFIA] Thank you.
- Thank you, Viviana.
This looks like crème brûlée.
No, except this not like crème brûlée,
crème brûlée is like it.
Meaning what?
That we did it first
and the French stole our recipes.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Eh, ta... taste.
Oh my God, that is, oh, so delicioso.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Uh, I also made something for you.
It's just a prototype.
Oh, this looks, uh...
very pro.
[CHUCKLES] I was just, like,
messing around with some designs.
I love it. [LAUGHS]
Is... Is that me?
It's a version of you, yeah.
I will have to grow more mustache
for this restaurant. [LAUGHS]
No, no, we can shave him
as well, if you want to.
No, no, no. I will...
I will grow it, I will grow it.
So, where is... where is your logo?
- Mine?
- Yeah, your logo for Sofia's Designs.
I don't have one.
Oh, so you are
like the cobbler with no shoes.
Sadly, yeah.
[LAUGHS]
You are very sweet.
So are you.
But you have to be
sweet to yourself too, no?
Yeah.
You're right.
So have you, um, ever been
to, uh... to Spain?
No, it's really embarrassing.
I've... I've, like, barely left California.
But you went to university, no?
In San Jose, yeah.
In Costa Rica?
Santa Clara.
[BOTH LAUGH]
- Is that far?
- No.
Not at all.
Uh, well, there's no...
there's no greater, um, collection
of art in the world
than in Madrid, you know.
There's, um, the Prado.
There's the... the Reina Sofia.
There's even an... an American museum.
Wow, is that just, like,
a bunch of paintings
of cowboys and Mountain Dew?
[CHUCKLING] No. No, not this America.
Um, um, South America.
Oh, okay. I think...
I think I've heard of that.
Uh-huh. [LAUGHS]
And then, my city,
we have El Museu Picasso.
You have heard of Picasso, right?
Yeah, it, like, slightly rings a bell.
Uh-huh.
- What city is this?
- [IN CASTILIAN ACCENT] Barcelona.
- Sorry, what?
- Barcelona.
- Why do you have a lisp all of a sudden?
- No, it's...
It is called distinción,
and, um, it's because, in... in, uh, Spain,
it's different than in Latin America.
No, so... so, in Latin America,
you say "gracias"
and in Spain we say...
[IN CASTILIAN ACCENT] ..."gracias."
Okay, I thee.
[LAUGHS] Oh!
- Hurts the brain.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
["ONLY LOVE (SEASIDE WOUNDS REMIX)"
BY HUMMINGBIRD HOTEL PLAYS]
♪ Or are we all
Just on our way back home? ♪
♪ Only love ♪
♪ Oh ♪
- Sorry, I shouldn't have done that.
- No, I... I, uh...
I liked it. I liked it a lot. Um...
It's just... back home...
You have a girlfriend.
No, no.
I have somebody
that I thought I wanted as a girlfriend.
Eh, she is not, um...
She's not so sweet. [CHUCKLES]
Well, then you've got
to be sweet to yourself, no?
Yeah.
- Come on.
- Where are we going?
Come on. Come with me.
♪ When your eyes
Can only find the ground ♪
♪ Angels, they don't make a sound ♪
♪ Grab a hold of my hand ♪
♪ In your soul's darkest night ♪
♪ I'll be ahead to shine a light ♪
♪ You'll never feel alone again ♪
♪ Only love ♪
♪ We're in this together
And it's only getting better ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Only love ♪
♪ We're in this together
And it's only getting better ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Only love ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh... ♪
[KETTLE WHISTLES]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- Oh!
Oh.
Early morning?
Late night.
Oh, you want some tea?
Yes, please.
[LAINIE] You seem to be feeling better.
- [CHUCKLING] Yeah, I am.
- Oh.
So, um... [CHUCKLES]
Were you making some gazpacho?
[CHUCKLES] Yeah. Yeah, you could say that.
[CHUCKLES] Honey!
Guillermo is a married man.
- [MOCK GASPS] What did I do?
- [LAUGHS]
Why didn't you tell me?
I thought you knew.
Oh, honey.
You deserve to have some fun
after everything you've been through, so...
Yeah, beats crying every night.
- [CHUCKLES] Yeah.
- Mm.
Just don't know what
I'm supposed to tell Richard now.
You don't have to tell Richard anything.
Well, he still wants us to be together.
What about Matias?
What about him?
He goes back to Spain in ten days.
Well, do you like the way
he makes you feel?
A lot, yeah.
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
Well, Matias doesn't have to be
your escape hatch from Richard,
honey, but he can certainly help
you realize that you're gonna have to
create your own escape hatch.
I think I know what you mean by that.
I'm gonna go deliberate.
[LAUGHS]
- Yeah. Deep thoughts.
- [SOFIA] Thank you.
[SWEEPING CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[STUDENTS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- [LAINIE] I hope so.
- [SOFIA] Yeah, seriously.
[LAINIE CHUCKLES]
- Buenos dias, Lainie.
- Aw.
Oh, Viviana, buenos dias.
Oh, we missed you last week.
[SOFIA CHUCKLES]
- Hi. Good to see you.
- Hola, Sofia.
Good to see you.
I did not think you would be here.
- Oh, no, no, I'm fine now.
- Yeah, she's all good.
Not only because of that, because of him.
[DISAPPOINTING MUSIC PLAYS]
Oh my God.
What is with you
just showing up at places?
Sorry. I just... You know.
Look, we're... we're having
a party at the house
for Kristie for her graduation,
and she'd really like to see you.
I'll see.
Everyone would love to see you.
I would love to see you, too.
Richard, this isn't
the time or place for this.
I just wanna watch,
you know, it looks fun.
You're gonna have to ask
if you can do that.
- I did. They said it was no problem.
- You did?
Mm-hmm.
- Great.
- Okay.
- Cool.
[RICHARD CLEARS THROAT]
Vi, Vivi, is Matias here?
Oh, he is. Still being tortured.
- What does that mean?
- Oh, you will see. [CHUCKLES]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYS]
Okay, all my lovely peoples.
Let us settle in, yes?
[TODD] Yes.
Today, I have a treat for you.
We are going to make one
of the most well-known Spanish dishes.
[MOUTHING]
[SWEEPING MUSIC PLAYS]
Paella!
[ALL EXCLAIM HAPPILY]
[GUILLERMO] Eh? [LAUGHS]
But first, we must
have a glass of rebujito.
Uh, rebujito is a summer drink
to take away the heat, and...
it will be served
by a traditional Spaniard,
dressed in traditional festive wear.
[LAINIE] This is so fun!
Matias.
Oh!
[FLAMENCO MUSIC PLAYING]
[DAVID] Oh boy!
[STUDENTS LAUGH AND EXCLAIM]
Ho-hoy!
- [FRANK] Wow! Oh my God!
- [STUDENTS LAUGH]
[ALL CHEER AND APPLAUD]
Matias is our jotero for today.
He will entertain us with song and dance.
- [VIVIANA] Ta-da!
- [STUDENTS LAUGH]
I do not know any song or dance.
[ALL LAUGH]
Everyone knows a little.
♪ Hear me, ye who know so little ♪
♪ And I'll tell you somewhat more ♪
♪ Of the knowledge essential ♪
♪ De la cueva de Salamanca ♪
[ALL LAUGH AND CHEER]
[SOFIA WHOOPS]
Whoo-hoo!
- No. No!
- [STUDENTS] Yes!
- [SOFIA] No, no, no.
- Yes, yes, yes!
[ALL LAUGH]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS]
Yeah!
Okay!
♪ Hear me, ye who know so little ♪
[LAUGHS]
♪ And I'll tell you something more ♪
[STUDENTS LAUGH]
♪ All the knowledge that's essential ♪
♪ De la cueva de Salamanca ♪
Matias?
[STUDENTS LAUGH AND CHEER]
- [IRINA] Matias?
- Hola, Irina.
I am Viviana, Matias' cousin.
Hello.
[HESITANTLY] Irina?
Well, at least
some people here have manners.
[VIVIANA] Ahem.
- [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
- Hello.
[MATIAS] I did not know
you were coming here.
Well, that's what makes
it a surprise, isn't it?
It... [CHUCKLES]
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
Is this how you do cooking in America?
No, this is, uh... This is for my, uh...
A class that my uncle is... is having.
Oh! For the silly little bunches
of Americans.
- Hello!
- Uh, yeah.
You must be exhausted from your travels,
so we should let them do their class.
- Come, come. Come on.
- Dasvidaniya.
Have good day. Irina out.
Okay. Okay, peoples!
La Noche de San Juan is still coming, yes?
Back to the paella, yes?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm gonna give you two
a couple minutes, okay?
- Hey.
- Hi.
I did not expect Irina to come here.
Yeah, I figured that.
Maybe she does care
more about you than you thought.
No. She just likes
to be the center of attention.
I think, uh, she was afraid
that I could actually survive without her.
Well, I didn't expect
Richard to be here either.
I thought maybe that was your Richard.
He doesn't really know
when to call it quits, but, um...
[SIGHS]
...but I do.
Sofia, I don't want this to...
[VOICE BREAKING] I just really can't
be the other woman for Irina.
'Cause my life's completely
just been blown up by one.
- And I can't do that to her.
- No, no. She's...
only here for, like, a couple of days
and then she's flying somewhere.
- I don't...
- And then you leave right after that.
Matias, this has been good.
Really, really good.
This has barely just yet begun, and...
Gotta be sweet to myself.
And to do that,
I've got to keep my heart safe.
Adios, Matias.
[SAD MUSIC PLAYING]
Ouch.
Ah, maybe it's time to step off, Matias.
Sounds to me like she's starting
to finally see you for who you really are.
Yeah, and, uh...
who am I?
Come on, man,
you don't really care about her.
I get it. You're just trying
to get laid while you're in America,
and then you're just going
to take off when you're done.
But you care about Sofia?
Yeah, I've been
with her since high school.
On and off.
We moved in together, so...
And you cheated on her.
That was a mistake.
She knows she's still mine.
Doesn't sound to me like she's anyone's.
Not mine.
- And certainly not yours.
- Well, you don't know her. I do.
That's good.
Then you know she doesn't like necklaces.
Everyone likes necklaces, okay?
[SCOFFS]
[SOFIA] Yeah.
- Do you like this one or that one better?
- [ELLA] I like this one.
- [SOFIA] Yeah? Should we color it in red?
- [OLIVIA] Oh my.
[SOFIA] Is there red or orange in there?
- [OLIVIA] Jesus.
- [ELLA CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
- Yikes.
- Yeah.
Yo, she put the "super" in supermodel.
[SOFIA] I know, right?
Maybe she has a eating disorder.
[CHUCKLING] Stop. That's not funny.
- Okay.
- Say, "Mom, you are in time out."
I'm just saying. She's not perfect.
She's just... pretty.
Yeah, and she's here.
Yeah, not the best timing.
- Nope.
- [CHUCKLES]
But hey, that's not on you.
You put yourself out there
and it paid off.
Yeah, it paid off for one little night.
- Just one.
- [OLIVIA] So?
That's a start.
Yeah.
Right? Toddler attack?
[BOTH] Toddler attack!
- [ROARING PLAYFULLY]
- [LAUGHING]
You're so yummy. Yum, yum, yum! I got you!
- [LAUGHS]
- [SIGHS]
She likes koalas.
- Baby steps.
- Aw!
Huh?
Sometimes you just gotta
celebrate taking the baby steps.
["STANDING TALL" BY DARKMINDS PLAYING]
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Looking for a reason ♪
♪ So burned out ♪
♪ Everybody need it ♪
♪ Something to believe in ♪
♪ So tired of running down our demons ♪
♪ We've gotta face 'em ♪
♪ We are reflecting
Reckon with scars ♪
♪ All that we've been seeking ♪
♪ Lies deep in our hearts
That are beating ♪
♪ Let the rain come down ♪
♪ Wash it all away ♪
♪ We are not afraid of the dark ♪
♪ Change don't come easy ♪
♪ Following the light of the stars ♪
♪ We'll find a whole new way out ♪
♪ We all got our part ♪
♪ Even mountains will fall ♪
♪ But when the dust settles down ♪
♪ We'll be still standing tall ♪
♪ Running out of patience ♪
♪ Chasing a ghost
Invisible and faceless ♪
♪ If we're gonna make it ♪
♪ We'll need a new motivation ♪
♪ We're lost, never alone ♪
♪ Head first, into the unknown ♪
♪ Life could be amazing ♪
♪ If we open our eyes
And invite an awakening ♪
♪ Let the sun shine down ♪
♪ Never fade away ♪
♪ We are not afraid of the dark ♪
♪ Change don't come easy ♪
♪ Following the light of the stars... ♪
[LAINIE] Oh...
- [SOFIA] Got it?
- Yup. Oh, boy.
This is nice. See? Now that's cooking.
I mean, we are the class couple, now.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Aw, where's Matias
to clean up after us, though?
- I know.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Um, so I was wondering...
- Mm?
How would you feel
if I applied to some schools
that weren't in California?
Oh, sure. No, I think you should.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Oh yeah.
You'd... You'd be okay?
Yeah. What do you... What do you mean?
Of course, honey. Don't be silly.
Okay. It's just, we've never lived that
far apart from each other before, so...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Oh, honey, are you worried
about, uh, me being okay, or you?
Little bit of both, probably.
Oh, sweetie, you know what?
All I have ever wished
was for you to go as big
and as far as your wings would take you.
I can take care of me.
- [CHUCKLES]
- I promise.
Okay.
Mm.
Gracias, Mama.
De nada.
- Oh, that sounded very good.
- [LAUGHS]
Did I? Was it close?
- Yeah.
- De nada. I don't know.
You look so much happier, little angel.
Oh, yeah,
I'm definitely feeling better. Thanks.
- Well, sometimes love will do that.
- Huh?
Julietta.
What have you been saying about me, Mom?
I can tell when there is love in the air.
And Matias is a wonderful boy.
You... You know Matias?
He's my grandson.
[CHEERFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
I'm gonna get... get my purse, and, uh...
- Yeah.
- You ready?
Bye.
- Let's stop on the way for dinner.
- Mom. Stop right there.
Matias is Julietta's grandson?
[CLICKS TONGUE] How about that?
How about that?
"Oh, hey, let's take a cooking class."
"Oh, hey, such a cute guy is teaching.
Oh, hey, can't make it to class."
Hey, you're making it sound sinister.
I don't need my mom
trying to fix my love life.
- I wasn't, honey.
- You were.
- No, I wasn't. I wasn't!
- Stop, you're so much.
No, honey. I wa... I...
Okay. Well, maybe I was.
- Just... Just a little bit. Okay?
- Yeah.
I had a Matias, too.
What?
- Yeah.
- When?
Whe... Right about the same time
that I met your father.
- His name was Henry, of all things.
- [CHUCKLES]
Your Matias was a Henry?
Yes. And Henry and I fell...
We fell madly in love
and my parents did not approve.
Why not?
Henry wanted to travel the world.
He wanted to seek adventure
and live by the seat of his pants and...
He... He just wasn't the kind of person
that my parents pictured for me.
So your father, he was a safe choice.
God rest his soul.
- And you chose safe.
- Yeah. I did.
And I often wonder
what my life would have looked like
if I'd followed my heart
instead of my head.
Huh.
I had no idea.
Yeah, well, you know, you're not supposed
to have all the answers when you're 30.
- But... You know?
- Yeah.
But life isn't something
that you should just fall into.
You've got to...
You gotta jump in, both feet.
Even if you don't know
where you're gonna land.
Yeah.
[TENDER MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, for what it's worth,
I am very, very happy that you chose safe.
[CHUCKLES] You are?
Yeah, you wouldn't
have had me if you didn't.
Oh. Oh, no. No, honey.
No, you were meant to be in my life
and you would have found your way to me
one way or another, that I am very sure.
Okay, yeah.
So tell me more about this Henry.
And yes, you should make
all of the different kinds of coca,
but for La Noche de San Juan
we have finished...
- [STUDENTS CHEER]
- [LAUGHS]
- ...La coca de San Juan.
- [STUDENTS] Ooh!
[GUILLERMO LAUGHS] Eh?
You like that.
[GUILLERMO] Hey!
Let us celebrate!
- [TODD] Yes.
- Yes.
I don't have any more room.
- Gonna have to loosen... loosen the apron.
- You'll make some.
- [GUILLERMO] Eh?
- It's delicious!
- Bueno?
- It's delicious. Yeah.
- [VIVIANA LAUGHS]
- Oh, thank you.
[DAVID] Gimme that one.
Thank you. [LAUGHS]
- You're welcome.
- Hey, hey. Um, where's Matias?
Uh... Come with me.
Uh, okay. Mom?
- Hmm?
- Mom, I'll be back.
Okay. Honey. Go, go, go.
[VIVIANA SIGHS]
- What?
- We miss you.
- I missed you too, but you guys had Irina.
- [SIGHS]
Oh, Irina. She was a nightmare.
All she wanted to do was be pampered and...
God, I'm so sorry.
You know.
Well, she and Matias are no more.
Really?
He told her he was done
being her puppy dog.
Oh. How'd she take that?
Well, have you seen
a wild boar devour a small reptile?
Not that specific combination, no.
- I have.
- Oh, no.
[BOTH LAUGH]
He said that you helped him see
how foolish he was to stay with her.
Mm-hmm.
I did that, huh?
And I, for one,
am so thankful that you did.
Uh, hey, where is he?
He, uh... He's leaving today for Barcelona.
No, I thought he was staying
through the weekend.
He moved his flight up a few days
because he wanted
to get settled for the new job.
Okay, okay. Um, do you think
I can still catch him?
[LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING]
- We can try.
- Yeah?
- We need to try. Where? Uh, where? Okay!
- [LAUGHS]
[VIVIANA] Let's check
his apartment first, no?
Yeah, his apartment.
We can try and catch him at the airport.
Vi, you really don't
have to do this for me. It's okay.
Of course I do. You're family.
- I love you.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
[PANTING] Okay, so I... I can drive.
Okay, uh, I should
let my mom know that... that we're...
We need to hurry.
Okay. Yeah.
No, she'll be fine. I'll be fine.
Uh, thank you.
- [GROANS] Just...
- Jeez!
Uh, okay. Are you... Where are you gonna...
- Go, go! Go find him.
- Okay.
All right. I'll come... I'll come find you.
I'll look for you.
I'll look for you. Thanks!
- [GROANS] Ooh! I'm sorry. Sorry!
- Scusi.
[LIVELY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sorry. Excuse me. Sorry.
[MUSIC FADES]
[MATIAS] Sofia?
[TENDER MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES] Hi.
Oh my God, you're still here.
Oh. I thought you left.
No, I... I, uh...
I couldn't leave
before trying chicken fingers.
Chicken fingers.
I like it.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
You know, I don't know
how you do things in Spain,
but here in America we actually say
goodbye to people before we leave.
Yes, um...
I wanted to, but...
you're a very...
strong person.
Wow, no one's ever
accused me of that before.
You knew what you wanted, so...
I thought I should respect your wishes.
Well, then,
I guess this is a goodbye present.
What is this?
- This is a Cabernet Sauvignon.
- [CHUCKLES]
It's the pride and joy of Sonoma County.
- Yeah, I have heard of this. [LAUGHS]
- Oh, yeah? [CHUCKLES]
I was...
hoping that we could drink it together.
To celebrate.
To celebrate... what?
I got accepted into a master's program
for graphic design.
I start in August.
- Sofia, this... this is amazing!
- Yeah.
- Felicitaciones, mama.
- [LAUGHS] Thank you, thank you.
- I'm assuming that that means congrats?
- Yes, yes.
Oh, I'm getting so good at Spanish.
Which, actually, will come in handy
when I start school.
Why is that?
Because I'm going to be
at the Institute of Design
in Madrid.
Wait. [LAUGHS]
That's the... No, that... that...
There's not one of those
in Santa Clara or whatever, right?
No, no. Just the one in España.
That's amazing, mama.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Mm, thank you.
Perhaps, maybe you will let me
come and, um, visit you sometimes
while you are there.
I think I'll have to sign up
for every single one of Matias' tours...
that Matias' Tours has available.
I wish you didn't have to go.
Uh...
I can't...
leave now.
I have to try the pairing
of chicken fingers and this wine.
[LAUGHS] Come here.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- No, it's... I have... It's an emergency.
- Move the car, lady.
No! No, no, no, no! This is an emergency.
- I'm gonna move the car, they're...
- I don't care. Get!
Why are you being so mean?
Hey.
[GASPS] You found him!
- [SOFIA CHUCKLES]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
Did you miss your flight?
- [VIVIANA CHUCKLES]
- Yeah, just barely.
- [LAUGHS] So happy.
- [SOFIA LAUGHS]
- Thank you, Vi.
- "Vi"?
Yes. Now I'm Vi.
Yeah, we're, like, really close like that.
Oh boy.
[VIVIANA] We got him!
[MATIAS] No, I know, let's...
I'm surprised you guys survived the car.
[ALL LAUGH]
[MATIAS] Can you please open the trunk?
[ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYS]
- [SOFIA] So, you can come.
- [LAINIE] Okay.
- Help me move in.
- Okay.
- But...
- But what?
I get to decide
what goes in the apartment.
- [LAINIE] Oh, yeah. Of course.
- Okay. I thought you were...
- I thought that would be more difficult.
- No! No.
- Buenas noches, ladies.
- Wow. Hi.
Come.
Follow me.
- Come on, Mama.
- Okay.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
- You ready to have some fun?
- [SOFIA] Behave yourself.
[LAINIE LAUGHS]
[MATIAS] Here.
- Welcome, guys.
- [GASPS]
- Hello.
- [CHEERING]
Lainie and Sofia.
My favorite cooking couple.
The special guests have arrived.
Ah! Welcome to la Noche de San Juan.
- [APPLAUDING]
- Gracias.
No, no, no.
[IN CASTILIAN ACCENT] It's gracias.
- [MATIAS] Ah!
- Oh!
[MATIAS] She's learning quick. Okay?
- She is ready for Spain, querida.
- I think so, I think so.
- [GUILLERMO] I think so.
- Yeah.
Well, come on in. I have some jamón.
- Yes. Okay.
- And I have some quesito manchego...
- [MATIAS] Oh, wow, I love manchego!
- [SOFIA] I think I know what that means.
And we saved the gazpacho from...
- ["FOR THE CROWD" BY EVERLY PLAYS]
- ♪ Go fast, slow down ♪
♪ What planet am I on now? ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ I show the world only pieces of me ♪
♪ Get high, feel low ♪
♪Hide pain under my pillow ♪
♪ Have it all ♪
♪ It's only when I'm here ♪
♪ That I just wanna sing... ♪
All right, I'm gonna grab
an appetizer. [CHUCKLES]
[MATIAS] I think it's fine.
I think it's fine.
I mean, I think it's time, Tío.
- You think we should do it?
- Yes. It is time now.
All my lovely peoples,
please pay attention.
Yes!
Now...
we will write our wishes
for the coming year, and we will...
[IN MONSTROUS VOICE]
...burn them in the fire.
- That was terrifying.
- Every single year.
- Why is he saying it like that?
- He does it every time.
- It's his thing.
- I hate that.
And our couple of honor
will jump over the fire.
This will cleanse you
of all your bad energy
and give you a fresh start
to the coming year.
We? We have to jump over that?
- Oh yes.
- [ALL AGREEING]
- Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, no.
- No.
- You can do it.
- No, no, no.
- I can't do that. My ankle just healed.
- Yes, you can.
- I can't do that.
- It's okay, it's a little fire.
- It's not even that big. Okay.
- That's a huge fire! No.
- Or...
- You can use this.
- [ALL LAUGH]
- Okay, yeah. Very funny.
I hate you guys. That terrified me.
[TENDER CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, I guess
I'm officially jumping in with both feet.
- Right, Mom?
- Give it, give it.
Right.
- [MATIAS] I want that. I want that, too.
- I don't know why I'm nervous.
- [LAUGHS] Okay, um...
- It's okay.
- I guess so.
- On three.
One.
[BOTH] Two.
- Three. Come on!
- Three.
- [SOFIA SQUEALS]
- [ALL CHEER AND LAUGH]
[JULIETTA SPEAKS SPANISH]
- Okay, Mom, now you. It's your turn.
- No, I'm not gonna do that.
- Yes, it's your first time.
- I could get burned!
Yes. Mom.
You gotta use your Zumba muscles!
- Mom, remember.
- I can't... What?
New beginnings.
- Okay, new beginnings.
- Come on.
- Thank you. Ready?
- All right. One...
- Okay. [EXCLAIMS]
- Two...
[ALL CHEER]
Okay? [LAUGHS]
[MAN] Bonjour, ma chère.
Oh my God.
Is it Henry?
Hi, Lainie. It's good to see you.
I figured since
I'm going to be so far away,
you shouldn't be here alone.
Love you, Mom.
Oh my God, Henry.
- I hope I'm not too late.
- Oh!
No such thing.
[IN FRENCH] You haven't changed.
- [BOTH LAUGH]
- [IN ENGLISH] Oh, my God.
To new beginnings.
To happily ever afters.
["CALIFORNIA WEATHER"
BY JONATHAN TINNÉ PLAYING]
♪ Let's take this road ♪
♪ Around every bend ♪
♪ 'Cause you know my love ♪
♪ No, it has no end ♪
♪ And in the rain ♪
♪ I know you'll hold my hand ♪
♪ 'Cause yesterday's pain ♪
♪ Doesn't venture this land ♪
♪ Show me the moon ♪
♪ From your hillside ♪
♪ Please be my view ♪
♪ On every ride ♪
♪ You are the light ♪
♪ In my firefly ♪
♪ Oh, you are the stars ♪
♪ Every night ♪
♪ Ride out to the beach, come with me ♪
♪ Only if we drive on the breeze ♪
♪ Only if you won't fall asleep ♪
♪ Next to me ♪
♪ Lie down, look up at the sky ♪
♪ Let's thank the stars in the night ♪
♪ Only fall asleep here tonight ♪
♪ Next to me ♪
♪ California weather with me ♪
♪ Tell me all the places you need ♪
♪ Show me all the love that you feel ♪
♪ Flow through me ♪
♪ California weather with me ♪
♪ Show me all the places you've been ♪
♪ I just want to be by you
Near through the years ♪
♪ I know that there's ♪
♪ A forest in me ♪
♪ And you carved your name ♪
♪ Into every tree ♪
♪ Do you know somewhere ♪
♪ Where flowers all bloom? ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanna spend
All of my sunsets with you ♪
♪ Show me the moon ♪
♪ From your hillside ♪
♪ Please be my view ♪
♪ On every ride ♪
♪ You are the light ♪
♪ In my firefly ♪
♪ Oh, you are the stars ♪
♪ Every night ♪
♪ This must be ♪
♪ What poets talk of ♪
♪ Yeah, you are the reason ♪
♪ I believe in love ♪