Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Michael!
Michael!!
Excellence,
education, faith.
These are the foundations of the
religious formation and strong education
that Holy Name Episcopal High
School
has been providing young women for
nearly one and a half centuries.
Hello.
I'm Reverend Warren Peters,
President and Principal of Holy
Name Episcopal High School.
Our mission is to educate the
young women entrusted to our care
with the immaculate teachings of
the Word
and nurture them into productive and
spiritually rich members of society.
You have expressed an interest
in attending Holy Name.
I'll be your host through this
video tour,
a chance for you to view the
magnificent facilities
and beautiful campus of Holy Name,
to help you decide if our institution...
There're ants in the
wildflowers you had me pick.
There's Raid in there.
Maybe we should order
some.
There's a place on the mainland
that ships for free.
You know, every penny I get,
goes to getting you into Holy Name.
Can you collect the mail on your
way through?
We have the liturgy tonight.
No, you moved the
liturgy for the vigil tonight.
The men are still trolling for
him.
Yeah, I know.
Stupid thing.
What a waste.
That's why you're not supposed
to swim there.
God bless him.
You want to begin?
- No, you.
- All the way up.
Proverbs, chapter 3, verse 5.
Trust in the Lord with all your heart
and do not rely on your own insight.
Trust in the Lord with all your
heart and do not rely on your own insight.
Be not wise.
Be not, in all your
ways, acknowledge.
In all your ways, acknowledge Him
and He shall make straight your path.
In all your ways, acknowledge
Him and He shall make straight your path.
Be not wise in your own
eyes.
Be not wise in your own eyes.
In the Proverbs it says train up a child
and the way he should go and when he
is old, he will not depart from it.
The question is, what is the
right way
and how do we know if something is right
for our children or even ourselves?
From Matthew, every good tree
bringeth forth good fruit,
but a corrupt tree bringeth
forth good fruits.
Every good tree doesn't bring
evil fruits.
We have a small orchard here on
Lacquesset Island
and when one of our fruits go missing,
we all lose some of our fruit.
So, so let's pray for the men and women
who are looking for Michael Quinn,
that their search is fruitful.
Amen.
As a mother stills her
child
Thou canst hush the ocean wild
Boisterous waves obey Thy will
When the Saints can then be
still
When at last I near the shore
And the fearful breakers roar
'Twixt me and the peaceful rest
Then, while leaning on Thy
breast
May I hear Thee say to me
"I will pilot thee."
Launched by NASA's jet
Propulsion Laboratory in 1977,
Voyager 2 and its sister probe,
Voyager 1 were designed as space travelers
to reach the furthest unknown
areas of space.
This August Voyager 2 will pass within
3,000 miles of the planet Neptune.
Using its television cameras, Voyager
2 will send back pictures of Neptune...
- Thomas!
- What?
You know what?
Why don't you move up to this
chair here, please.
Thomas?
I don't want to; make
someone else do it. Make her do it.
- No, Thomas.
- I don't mind.
Then you take Hannah's
seat.
Michael.
- Wow.
- Look at that!
Got it?
See what love the Father
has bestowed on us,
that we may be called the
children of God.
Yet so we are.
The reason the world does not know
us is that it did not know Him.
We are God's children now.
What we shall be has not yet
been revealed.
We do know that when it is
revealed, we shall be like Him,
for we shall see Him as He is.
We pray for Michael's family,
that the Lord will fill the
present emptiness in their hearts
with the love and prayerful support
of many friends, we pray to the Lord.
Lord, hear our prayer.
For each of us here present,
that God will bless us richly
with the gifts he knows we need
to fully celebrate life
and recognize the new beginning, which he
offers us each day, we pray to the Lord.
Lord, hear our prayer.
We remember Michael today
for his life has touched each of us.
We know him as our brother here
in this congregation.
We know him as a good student in
our school
and we know him as Lacquesset's
youngest lobsterman,
as his father, Herb's sternman.
For a moment, let us be with our
own memories of Michael.
On a note of new beginnings, I
have an announcement.
Our, our own Hannah Newcomb,
has applied for Holy Name High
School in Shore Springs,
which she hopes to be attending
this fall.
There's a contribution box at
the door.
This is a great honor for her and
it's a great honor for our island...
What did you just say?
...to attend this great
institution.
I hope, I hope that, I encourage you
all as you leave, to leave some...
This is my son's funeral!
Not a sideshow for that orphan!
Fuck your school, honey.
It's nothing personal, but fuck
you all the same.
That's enough.
Rejoice in the fact
that we do see
a great deal of decency and
heroic virtue in our lives.
And priests especially don't
thank the people enough
who make our priestly ministry possible
with their presence and generosity...
the servants who are serving the
Father,
serving the decent Son as an
important part of their lives.
But also the Word of the Father.
The servants have to be open and
willing to welcome home...
Hello?
Hannah? Is that you?
What are you doing out here?
I heard a sound.
Is something wrong with
you?
It's past 5:00.
You probably should start your
chores.
Jerry?
I'd like to work for the Quinns
this summer.
I could go out and haul lobster
traps for him.
Absolutely not.
Michael was a stern man
on Herb Quinn's lobster boat
and now he has nobody to help
him.
Please, put that out of
my face.
We could talk about it later.
Give and it shall be
given to you.
For whatever measure you deal out to
others, it will be dealt to you in return.
Will you be paid?
Yes.
Your chores.
I'm going out for a smoke.
These are my dad's.
He was 81.
Yeah?
I'm really sorry about the
service.
I didn't ask him to say any of
that.
Yeah, well...
I could come work for
you.
I could go on the boat, I could
help you.
I need the money.
I don't think so.
Sean is...
I could use the help,
but I don't think it would be a good idea.
Here we go.
Bonnie brought them over.
Hmm... hmm.
They're really good.
They're made from honey,
she said.
I don't know.
From the bee lady?
I found this the other day.
I haven't much to give you, you
know.
Pinching pennies for that school,
but I wanted to give you something.
When you first came here,
people said you were a gift from God.
Of course, I don't have any
children of my own,
but I've come to think of you
like that.
You ought to have nothing but
the best opportunities.
You deserve that school and I'm
going to make sure you get it.
Excellence,
education, faith.
These are the foundations of the
religious formation
and strong education that Holy
Name Episcopal High School
has been providing young women for
nearly one and a half centuries.
Our mission is to educate the
young women
entrusted to our care with the
immaculate teachings of the Word
and nurture them into productive and
spiritually rich members of society.
Hello?
Herb?
Sorry.
You sure about this?
Truck.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Over here and down here.
You got it?
You OK?
Yeah, good.
Hannah.
OK.
These five traps are yours.
Whatever they catch, you keep
the profit.
That'll be your pay.
Do you have any other work
clothes?
No, not really.
Here you go.
These were Michael's.
Some of them should fit you.
He was a little dude.
There's weeds growing
around the flowers here.
Those aren't weeds;
mint.
I planted it, remember?
How was your work today?
All right.
We just hauled out some traps
from the storage area.
What about your pay?
He gave me some traps of
my own.
And what if you don't
catch anything; what then?
For nearly one and
a half centuries.
Hello.
I'm Reverend Warren Peters,
President and Principal of Holy
Name Episcopal High School.
Our mission is to educate the
young women entrusted to our care
with the immaculate teachings of
the Word
and nurture them into productive and
spiritually rich members of society.
Holy Name fosters empathy and
responsibility for self
and others in a fully
residential community.
Students are encouraged to think
creatively, work collaboratively,
develop individual passions and
celebrate talent.
Those fit you OK?
Yep.
OK. You ready? All right.
This guy right here is your
throttle.
I can't see.
You're doing fine.
Look behind you.
See the landing? See that rock?
I want you to turn right,
throttle up.
This one right here.
It's OK, you're doing great.
Do it again.
Open yours right up, you
got to check yours, too.
Is that what I keep
doing?
Nope.
You got to put these in there.
Hannah?
Yeah?
Didn't forget, did you?
No.
You've still got evening
chores.
Hannah?
Yeah, I will.
There's dinner when
you're finished.
OK.
Did you gather all of the
donations from today?
Yes.
Did you put them in the
den?
Yes, Jerry.
Fishing isn't an excuse
for neglecting your duties here.
Remember?
Aren't you forgetting something?
Dear Lord, thank you for
this food
and for giving me the chance to help Herb
Quinn and his family and their son, Michael,
who you took from us for reasons
we're not to know.
Amen.
Hello?
Who is it?
Well, safe.
Want a sandwich? I made
two.
Sure.
No, no!
What the hell you doing?
No.
Come on.
I'm not going to eat it.
Why not?
Needed salt.
Marcy!
Herb.
I'll have a stout and a
soda for her.
Sure, dear.
I'm sure you all know
Hannah.
So what's shaking
today, Herb?
I'm showing Hannah the art
of the haul.
How you liking it out
there, Hannah?
Good.
No luxury cruise,
though, is it?
No, it's not.
You all done with school,
Hannah?
Yeah. I graduated last
week.
That's great.
You were the one and only, the
one and only graduate, huh?
Congrats.
I remember...
So Hannah, what do you know about
this old timer you been working for?
Ever hear any stories?
I could tell you some
stories.
You save your stories,
Marcy.
Just go back there and do what
you're good at doing.
Well, Herb always was a
tough son of a bitch.
Don't mind my swearing.
The only problem was you couldn't
get him ornery enough to fight.
He's always kind.
Yep.
His old man was like that, too.
That's why we were all a bit
surprised when Sean fell for him.
We always thought the biggest
prick gets the chick.
Hannah, you're going to
have to pardon Lemann.
His language gets a little
colorful.
Turns out, turns out, even young
women sometimes go for a man of substance.
Night they met, we were over at
Jake's place having a few barley pops
and Sean and Herb, they lost
some kind of bet.
Card game, cards.
Cards.
Something like that,
something like that.
They lost the bet.
They had to snowmobile from one
end of the island to the other,
just the way God made 'em.
You mean like ...?
Nude, honey.
Naked!
It was love at first
sight.
I missed the evening
service.
You want me to talk to
Jerry?
This is my fault.
No, I got it.
Hey, Jerry.
I'm sorry I kept her out late.
I wanted to repay her hard work
with a soda.
Yeah, well, money would
be better.
Yeah, well, we should be
getting to her traps tomorrow, right?
Go in, Hannah.
Hey, Herb. Hey,
Lori.
Jerry, she's been a really
big help.
I can't thank you enough.
OK.
Goodbye.
Herb took me to the
Squall.
Look at you.
They're my bib pants.
What do you think?
What if the girls from Holy Name
saw you?
Do you think they would let you
in?
Do you think you're worthy to
represent this church there?
Because of how I'm
dressed?
I want you to give a
confession.
What?
What do you mean?
Come on.
Where?
In there.
That's the closet.
It'll do.
Come on.
Jerry, no.
Why?
In there.
Jerry.
Go in.
Hannah?
There's no light.
It's blown.
You can start.
I don't know what you
want me to do.
Say, bless me, for I have
sinned.
OK.
Bless me, for I have sinned.
The Lord be in your heart and
on your lips, that you may truly...
Jerry, this is stupid.
Why am I in the closet?
...to in the Common
Prayer...
Can I come out?
Most merciful God.
Hannah?
What did I do wrong?
You haven't kept your
promise to me.
I've done everything I
used to do for you.
No, you haven't.
You told me I could work
for him.
I told you, you could
work for him, that is all.
I'm just trying to help.
There are people who need
our help.
If you want to help, find
somebody...
He lost his son.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Jerry, please.
Jerry, can I please come out?
Hannah?
Yeah?
It's Thomas.
Wow, this is cool.
Is this your room?
No.
Are you camping?
It's so small.
What were you watching?
I have to be quiet.
What movies were you
watching?
A video from Holy Name.
Oh.
Holy Name?
Oh, yeah. Cool.
I don't know where I'm going
yet.
Maybe I'll go to Holy Name, too.
I don't know.
Well, it's for girls
only, so...
Thank Bonnie for me.
She gave me a buck.
How'd you get this in here?
This is so cool, you have TV.
What's that?
Is that... let me see that.
Holy shit, it is.
This is Michael's hat.
It was in the bag of
stuff Herb gave me.
You're wearing Michael's
clothes?
No.
I was going to give it back
anyway. I don't need it.
Oh yeah?
Well, how about right now.
Now?
No, I have to study.
I think they would want
it back right now.
Thomas! Thomas!
Come and get it, cow!
Whoo!
Thomas?
Thomas, we shouldn't be here.
Why?
Come on, just check it out.
Just wait.
Don't you think we should give
the hat back?
She probably wants it.
Just give me the hat and
let's go.
Why don't you go knock
on the door?
What?
The door for the hat,
the door for the hat.
OK, give me the hat.
Hello?
Who is it?
Michael?
Dad?
Fuck!
I'll kill you, you fuck!
Herb?
- What was it?
- No, no, no.
It's nothing.
No, nothing.
Herb, I heard you say Michael.
What was it?
Come on, come on, let's go
inside.
Come on, it's nothing.
Come on, it's OK.
It was only a joke, come
on.
Let go!
I'm not holding you.
Hannah, what is this?
What are you doing?
I'm camping.
Put this on and join me
out here.
Good morning.
What the hell is this?
We need a charter over to
Ram Island, can you help us?
What do you need to go
there for.
It's a church matter.
Yeah, well, have a...
We're going to see Kay
Goodall.
What for?
It's a church matter.
Yeah, you said that.
Yeah, all right.
She's sick, you know.
Yes.
The bee lady?
What?
Like the honey?
Why are we going?
Can't hear you.
We're going to anoint Kay
Goodall.
I'm going to give her the Last
Rites.
I'm not ordained.
It's a little surge-y out
there.
My brother Paul's a sword
fisherman.
My cousin worked on a trawler
until he retired.
I could never do it.
I could never spend more than
half an hour on a boat.
We should be in the clear;
not much farther now.
I don't know how you
fisher folk do it.
I mean, the work, the endless
trapping and killing.
You spend so much time doing
something of no substance.
You gotta raise a family
somehow.
God bless you for it.
Fathers are fathers.
Hannah!
Mrs. Goodall!
Why don't you go around back?
Here.
Mrs. Goodall!
Mrs. Goodall?
Mrs. Goodall, are you all right?
Spooky, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
You're a little spooky
yourself.
It's a border stone.
My husband found it at the base
of the Himalayas in Rasuwa.
That's where we met.
He took it with him.
Are you Mrs. Goodall?
Wherever he moved.
He's buried right underneath it
now.
And I swear to you, that thing
is still moving.
It has moved three feet in as
many years.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Now where do you suppose he's
off to now?
Kind of thought I'd be
getting more visitors
after Bonnie brought me all
those birthday cards.
Here you go, girl.
So, priest, to what do I owe the
pleasure of this visit?
Are you here to talk me into
dying?
No, Mrs. Goodall.
My ward here hopes to be
ordained one day...
Ooh!
How's the tea, ward?
It's from the An Hui province.
You know where that is?
I was there in 1947 with the Red
Cross, see?
Queen can't get enough of this
stuff.
And here I am in Abyssinia two
years later, which is now...
Kathleen, if you don't
mind, this will only...
What's your name, dear?
Hannah.
Hannah what?
Hannah Newcomb.
Ooh, not much of a
name.
Of course, Kathleen Goodall
isn't much better.
Goodall was Raymond's name.
My maiden name is Plummer.
Imagine.
Well, now, priest.
What's it gonna be?
Anointing of the sick?
The Eucharist or just a good old
fashioned spanking?
This will only take a
minute.
Here, take this.
Take the book.
Why?
Take the book, come with
me.
Come with me.
Take the oil.
What good is the ritual
if she's not ordained?
The oil is blessed.
It'll still work.
Jerry...
Now say after me...
The grace of our Lord
Jesus Christ...
Magic oil.
My soul needs no cleansing,
priest.
And if God has anything on me,
you just send him down.
No offense, child.
Would you help me,
please?
Hannah.
You should have seen Hannah
today, Herb.
The work of God.
I'll bet.
I'm proud of you, Hannah.
You did good work today.
Sorry. We got to haul this
one in since we're here already.
This looks like one of yours.
Look at that.
Well, it'll come out with a
little soap and water.
It's not good work for a girl.
It's not good.
In a month you'll be with the other
girls and they'll look at you.
I want to make sure that you're
right up there with them.
We just about got enough for the
first term.
Enough money.
And you spend all your time hauling
lobsters out, going around with fishermen.
Who's going to be around to show
them the way when I'm not here?
Judgment will wrack their bones.
I can't go to Holy Name.
What do you mean?
I'm not going.
I don't want to.
Go get ready for service.
I'm not going and I'm not
going to stay here with you anymore.
Oh, no?
And what are you going to do?
Fourteen years old, pull bugs
out of the water
and slosh that water on you for
the rest of your life?
Fourteen years old!
They brought you out here, so I
could raise you as a Christian.
And as long as I'm around,
you'll do what by me.
Do you understand?
Now get that cleaned up for
service in an hour.
If you mess up one more time,
you will not leave this island!
That'll be my charity on you.
I want it cleaned up!
Excellence,
education, faith.
These are the foundations of the
religious formation and strong education
that Holy Name Episcopal High
School
has been providing young women for
nearly one and a half centuries.
Hello.
I'm Reverend Warren Peters,
President and Principal of
Holy Name Episcopal High School
in Stockton Springs.
I want to personally congratulate
you on your acceptance to Holy Name.
I'm sure you probably have lots
of questions.
Future students want to know what a day
in the life looks like here at Holy Name.
Well, that's what this
acceptance video is for.
Let's step inside the hallways
of Holy Name
to give you a better idea of what to
expect when you come here in the fall.
Hello?
Hello.
Thomas!
What are you doing?
Church is that way.
Can I ride that?
Want to drive it?
You can ride it if I drive.
Where?
Stand up on the pegs.
Hold on to me.
Hold on tight.
It's not even that high.
I'll bet he's not even dead.
Why do you say that?
It's deep right there.
I could jump that.
Do it.
For what?
I'll let you kiss me.
When?
After.
OK.
But if I die, it's your fault.
What are you waiting
for?
Nothing.
You're in deep shit!
Fuck off!
What are you doing?
What's happened?
What happened?
Trust in the Lord with all your
heart and do not rely on your own insight.
In all your ways acknowledge Him
and He will make great your path.
Be not... let go!
Mrs. Quinn!
I'm sorry.
Come on!
What are you doing?
Calm down, it's OK.
What'd they send you?
Did they let you in?
Hannah!
Open the door!
...School in
Stockton Springs.
I want to personally congratulate
you on your acceptance to Holy Name.
I'm sure you probably have lots
of questions.
...far from the light and warmth
of the Sun and the life of the Earth,
Voyager 2 passed over the cold
blue clouds of Neptune tonight,
its cameras snapping pictures
and its sensors gathering data
on the composition and dynamic
forces of the giant planet.
The rendezvous was the culmination
of the most far-reaching exploration
of the planet in the history of
the space age.
As Voyager 2 approached Neptune at
a speed of 38,000 miles an hour,
it transmitted...
Hannah, please come out.
...showing sharper
deeper details of the swirling clouds
in Neptune's great dark spots, a
storm system the size of earth.
Hannah, I'm sorry.
I'm not going, Jerry.
We can talk about it.
Please come out.
It's... It's my fault.
I should have never let you work
with him.
He couldn't even take care of
his own son.
That doesn't mean
anything coming from you.
You never loved anything.
Hey.
Come on, come on inside.
What's going on?
What happened?
I need to stay here
tonight.
Wait here a minute, OK?
Hi.
He isn't going to save
you, you know.
Hey.
Let's get out of here, OK?
Fred stills this stuff.
You ever have homemade spirit?
Me and Michael used to come here
all the time.
Learned how to swim right out
there.
He was a good swimmer, looked
like a monkey.
Did you know your daddy?
No.
I think I remember my mother,
though.
Why did you come to live
here?
I don't know.
Did you ever ask?
Nope.
Jerry said, Jerry said it was
ungrateful
to look past the path that God
had set for me.
Yeah.
Well, I always, I always thought
you made your own path.
It was in the bag with
all the other stuff.
No.
It's OK.
No, no.
Please, please, please,
please.
Please, don't.
Please, please, please.
Herb.
Please, please, please,
please.
Herb, stop it.
Please, please, please,
please.
Stop.
Please, please...
Michael.
No!
Michael!
Herb!
Herb?
Here.
I'm all right.
Shut that off.
Look at them all.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull