Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[car horns honking]
[Jane singing]
♪ Hell yeah, I love you ♪
♪ Never going to rub
You the wrong way ♪
♪ Go with the grain ♪
♪ Hell yeah, I love you ♪
♪ Never going to rub
You the wrong way ♪
[text message beep]
♪ Go with the grain ♪
[continues singly softly]
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
[door thuds]
[body thuds]
[woman screaming]
[tires screeching]
[car horns honking]
[dog barking]
[crowd yelling]
[pants] Fi?
[Jane panting, sobbing]
Fi!
[screams]
Help her!
[Jane crying, siren wailing]
[drumming music]
[Jane laughs]
Okay.
[Fiona] Oh.
[Jane and Fi laughing]
Oh my gosh!
Oh wow.
It's so beautiful.
[Jane] It really is.
I love you.
[Fiona] I love you.
[laughs]
[Jane] Oh man,
I have to pee so bad.
[Fiona] Are you serious?
[Jane] Yes.
Hold it, hold it!
No... I can't!
You are ruining
this moment for me.
[both laughing]
I think that's ours.
I think that one's ours.
[man cheering]
[Jane] There's so many.
[Fiona] This is so much fun.
- Oh!
- Hey!
- Sorry.
- We couldn't find you.
I'm sorry.
No, that's okay.
[laughs]
What did you wish for?
- Wait, what?
- Sorry, what did you wish for?
To meet you.
I wished for us.
I wished for...
I'm Fiona.
I'm Gemma.
Nice to meet you.
Do you wanna dance?
[Gemma] My wife's love
for life was infectious.
[bird cawing]
Her curiosity was enlightening,
and her care for her family
and her friends was admirable.
- You know there's no body.
- Yeah.
[Gemma] While our questions
may never be answered...
- Wait what?
- [Gemma] One day they will...
Gemma refused to bury her.
This is the compromise,
an empty coffin.
Thank you for being my rock.
[Ruth] She claims Fiona
wanted to be cremated,
and do you know what
an empty coffin costs?
- [Gemma] And my wife.
- Is it less?
- I don't know.
- [Gemma] And my everything.
What's the right answer here?
Please join me
in the Jewish tradition
of placing the earth
on the grave.
[gentle piano music]
How much longer?
Come on, let me
see your brave face.
Let's go too, Bubbe.
[birds singing]
[soft, indistinct chatter]
Here's Jane,
Fiona's best friend.
Hey.
I'm so, so sorry,
so sorry, Jane.
Thank you.
[woman]
How are you holding up?
Thank you.
[Ruth] Jane?
I feel really bad.
These containers
aren't microwavable.
Where are the containers
that are microwaveable?
Bailey's halfway to starving.
- Glass containers.
- They've got green lids.
I bought them for Fiona
two Hanukkahs ago.
I don't know where they are,
but they're here, we have 'em.
Did we prepare enough food?
I don't think we
prepared enough food.
Oh.
He's going through a hot
dog and broccoli phase,
likes a lot of melted
cheese on his broccoli.
Go be with your friends.
[soft, tense music]
[Ruth] Where's the microwave?
There's no microwave
in this kitchen.
Where's the microwave?
[sighs]
[water rushing]
[exhales]
[soft thud]
- Hello?
- [Bailey] J-dog?
B-boy?
Did you wrap a fruit
snack around your waist?
Mm-hmm.
I made a mess.
What's the backstory?
I wanted to see how many times
I could fit it around me.
- And?
- Well, five-ish.
Whoa, that's impressive.
All right, what are
we working with?
Oh buddy, this snack
is, like, stuck.
Forever?
Nothing's forever.
Let's get this off you.
[door opens]
[Kayla] Yeah,
it's just tragic.
[Greg] I know, I mean,
was it depression?
Is that confirmed?
[Kayla] I'm just guessing.
Okay, our ride will
be here in five.
She didn't seem depressed
at Lily's fairy party.
I mean, she bought
the glitter confetti.
Well, I'm not
saying that she was.
- I'm just saying that that's one reason.
- Mm.
What did she have
to be depressed about?
You know, she gets
to mess around
with her friend
at her little startup,
and Gemma provides
financial security.
Oh yeah, her little startup.
Oh, screw you, Greg.
I only wish I had
a job to escape to,
stuck at home with two kids,
one on the way,
and a husband
that's having an affair.
[Greg] Oh my God, really?
Oh no, I'm just being
a little dramatic,
but my point is that life
is hard, Fiona's wasn't.
- Who are you?
- Hi, I'm Greg.
This is Kayla.
Our kids go to
school with Bailey.
You're Fiona's
business partner, right?
Cool, cool, cool, awesome.
So you guys are trying to figure out
if she had enough
reason to kill herself.
Oh no, no, no,
no, we are friends...
How would you feel if your
husband fucking killed himself,
and I was ripping apart the
superficial aspects of his life?
Oh my gosh,
no, I'm so sorry.
One, none of my business
how he offed himself,
and two, there is
no two; that's rude,
- you're rude people.
- Is everything okay?
No, everything's not okay.
You have garbage friends.
- Yeah, I...
- Excuse me?
They're trying to put
on their Nancy Drew hats,
see if they can solve
the mystery of Fi's suicide.
Look, I would never
call myself Nancy Drew.
You know what?
Go fuck yourself, Kayla!
- [Greg] We are seriously sorry.
- It's fine.
No, everything's not fine!
- It's fine, Jane.
- No, look, I am so sorry.
You know what?
You have no idea
what we're going
through, no idea.
- [driver] Are you Kayla?
- Yeah, sure.
- I'm sorry.
- That was just...
[Gemma] I'm sorry you guys.
Unlock your fucking door.
- That was our ride.
- She didn't mean that.
I need to change the address.
["Little Whip" by Daggy Man]
♪ Oh my ♪
[Jane crying]
♪ Get your heartache
Out of my sight ♪
♪ Said your mother
To you as a child ♪
♪ It never felt right ♪
♪ Never felt right ♪
♪ But me like a little
One got to admit ♪
- I'll be right back.
I'll be.
Right back.
I'll be right back.
♪ But me like a little
One got to admit ♪
♪ I can feel... ♪
Oh, shit.
♪ With a shovel ♪
♪ And I'll dig, dig, dig, dig ♪
[music continues]
[phone vibrating]
♪ But me like a little
One got to admit ♪
♪ I confused that
Whip with a shovel ♪
♪ Me like a little
One got to admit ♪
♪ I confused that
Whip with a shovel ♪
[Gemma] Hi Jane, it's Gemma.
Rent is past due
for Paper And Bliss.
We haven't discussed how you
want to proceed with the company,
so call me back as soon as
possible at the office, thanks.
♪ Dig, dig ♪
[birds chirping]
[gentle music]
Viola!
[gentle guitar music]
[laughs]
What's wrong?
I don't know,
I just didn't expect it
to be so four walls and boring.
Well, yeah,
it's boring, asshole.
[both laughing]
We have to make it us.
What, like plants and shit?
Yeah, plants and shit.
Artwork, maybe a splash wall.
I don't know.
I like it.
I mean, I like the idea of it.
You're nervous, huh?
If I say yes, will
that make you nervous?
[laughs] Of course
I'm nervous.
This is insane!
[laughs]
I don't know anything
about running a business.
Um, you may have wanted
to lead with that.
Probably should have, right?
[sighs]
Who gives a shit?
If we fail, we fail together,
hm?
[laughs]
Whatever, right?
I mean not whatever, whatever.
- If you don't want to do this...
- It's not that.
It's just...
this is your dream.
- It's our dream.
- Your money.
[Fiona sighing]
- One moment.
- [Jane] Okay.
- Oh!
- Can we celebrate now?
- Is this real life?
This is happening, mama.
Okay.
- [Jane] Okay.
- Do I need to shake this?
- [Jane] No, no, no, no, no.
- Okay, do you want it?
Absolutely not,
it'll pop my eye out.
You know what happened
to my aunt, right?
Yeah, she wears
a patch, right?
- Okay.
- Okay, just aim it away.
Okay, okay, here?
- Okay, yeah.
- Okay.
[cork popping]
[upbeat music stops]
[car horns honking]
[sirens wailing]
[tense music]
Gemma, how we doing?
Good, I'm just working
on the terms of agreement
for the Kilian West merger.
Listen, the partners
and I have been talking,
and we think it might be best
if you'd lay off the project.
Why?
Given the current
circumstances,
it's just best not to
overload you right now.
I brought this merger
to the firm, Larry.
I've got it under control.
What's your issue?
Is it my personal life?
Because if you want
to bring that into it,
that's a different conversation,
one that involves HR.
Sorry to interrupt.
Gemma, I have Jane Collins
here to see you.
Send her in.
Let me know how you want
to move forward, Larry.
Hey, Gemma.
I got some of Fi's stuff
from the office.
Um, yeah, have a seat.
How are you holding up?
Sorry, I hate that question too.
Never been better.
[laughs]
Hey, me too.
Oh, I had one
of the lawyers here
draw up a dissolution contract.
In layman's terms, it just
says that all of the assets
in the Paper And Bliss account
will be transferred to you.
Wait, what?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, you should take Fi's
portion and split it.
We don't need it, that's okay.
Anyways, it'll help
keep you afloat
until you figure out
what you want to do next.
So how's being back
at work treating you?
Well, I didn't really
have much of a choice.
Just keep swimming.
[Gemma] What?
Oh it's just a line
from Bailey's favorite movie.
[Gemma laughs]
So is Ruth staying in town
to help you with Bails?
No, no, no.
I have him in
an afterschool program,
and then I'm hiring a babysitter
to take him
to therapy and help out
when I'm tied up in meetings.
Where did you get that?
Oh, I found it on Fi's desk,
I didn't want to lose it, so.
Here.
[gentle music]
She never took this off.
I know.
Thanks, Jane.
Take care, yeah?
Call me if you need anything.
[phone ringing]
Have a nice day.
Hey, I have an idea,
hear me out.
You shouldn't have some
rando watching Bailey.
They're not randos.
They are professionally
trained babysitters.
No, that's not a real thing.
Don't you want
someone who knows him
like you do like, like Fi did?
I can't ask that of you.
You didn't.
I'm offering.
[gentle music]
[groans] Agent 455,
I thought I'd find you here.
Did you bring the package?
Meet me round back; I'll
give you all my secret money.
How do I know you're
not trying to trick me?
Trust me.
[laughs]
Is this your backpack?
Let's roll.
Let's roll?
I heard it when I said it.
Okay, that was too much.
You're like the
smartest kid in class?
- I guess.
- I bet you are.
- Can I have some?
- Yeah, sure. - Thank you.
Are you picking
me up every day?
For now, yeah,
like or don't like?
- Like.
- [Jane] Sweet.
Oh, you have to
meet my pet lizard.
Oh, shit!
He's from the
imaginary pet shop.
- His name's Dragon.
- Oh, got it.
Where'd he go?
There he is.
He just got a little startled.
Oh, whoa, did you see those
fire breathing skills?
Whoa, smells like cinnamon.
It does.
Do you want to put him back?
- Yeah, sure.
- So nice to meet you, Dragon.
- Okay.
- Oh, give him a goldfish.
- Yep.
- I hear they love goldfish.
Let's go.
[gentle music]
[Jane] Your mom used
to think she was a stunt...
- You know what a stunt person is?
- [Bailey] Yeah.
She, like, fell down
the stairs on purpose.
- Oh, man.
- Hi, checking in Bailey Flack.
Hi, Bailey.
He'll be out in a moment.
Cool.
- Let's go sit.
- [Bailey] Tell me another one.
Okay, uh, ooh...
have I told you the one
about your mommy
and me, and Scientology?
No, what's Scientology?
- Do you know what bullying is?
- Yes.
It's bullying in
the form of religion.
Stay far away.
- I'm Jewish.
- That's great.
So your mommy and I
are on this road trip, right?
And we're driving to LA,
and we come across
this giant castle,
but they're giving
away free breakfast,
and like, who turns down
free breakfast, right?
That was the summer after
your sophomore year, right?
Alec.
Oh my God, how are you?
What are you doing?
Wait, are you Bailey's...
are you Bailey's doctor?
Yeah, we've been seeing
each other since the funeral.
- You were at the funeral?
- Oh, yeah.
We spoke for a second.
Oh, like yeah, I literally
have no memory of that.
I'm helping Gemma with Bails.
She's not a real babysitter,
so I'm gonna call her my Jane.
Aw, I like that.
You ready, Bailey?
[Bailey] Yep.
What does Gemma normally
do when he goes in there?
- Oh, she comes back in an hour.
- An hour?
Sometimes, she stays.
Okay, I'll do that.
[laughs]
Sounds like a better plan,
because I, um,
I don't have anywhere to be.
[phone clicking]
- Jane.
- Hey.
Has it been an hour already?
Almost.
You have a second to chat?
Yeah, sure.
You cool to be out
here for a sec, B-boy?
Sure.
Are you seeing anyone?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I got too busy
to date, you know,
after you and I broke up,
Paper And Bliss starting,
and then Fi getting pregnant,
a lot of responsibility, so yeah, no.
[laughs]
[Alec laughs]
What?
[laughs]
Let me rephrase.
Are you seeing
a therapist or a counselor?
- Oh, my God.
- [Alec] Since Fi died.
I feel like a God damn idiot.
No, no, not at all.
I mean, you're still
aggressively self-deprecating.
Aggressively determined
to make a fool
out of myself,
that's for sure.
It might not be a bad
idea to see someone.
Wait, are you
suggesting that I see you?
Is that what you're saying?
Because wouldn't that be...
- Unethical, yeah.
- [Jane] Right?
No, I could never
be objective enough,
but I could make some calls.
Yeah, no, I'm good, I'm good.
Thank you though.
Yeah.
How's he doing, by the way?
Well, imagine being seven,
your mom is gone,
and you can't
logically comprehend why.
What do I do, or not do?
[scoffs]
I literally have no
idea what I'm doing.
Just be his Jane.
If you listen, you'll know
what he needs from you.
Has he mentioned any changes
in Fi's behavior before,
you know?
I guess what
I'm saying is, like,
did he notice
or, like, allude to any...
Jane, I'm a psychiatrist,
not a mind reader.
Besides, I can only speak
to a parent
about Bailey's sessions.
Yeah, never were much
of a rule breaker, were you?
Okay, blink once for yes,
raise an eyebrow for no.
I don't know if
you're having a stroke
or trying to be funny;
it's cute though.
[Alec laughs]
Hey, you can call me
if you need anything,
as a friend or whatever.
Little advice though.
Uh-oh.
You need to work
on your winking abilities.
[girl in video] So you're gonna
wanna make sure
that you ask questions.
The parents will like
that because, you know,
it'll make you seem
interested and professional,
and like you're on the ball,
and you know the kid's needs.
You're also gonna wanna
have fun with the kid
and do something funny,
because they like that.
You want to make sure that
they know you mean business.
I said you're not
the boss of me!
- Wow.
- You're not the boss of me!
Hey, hey, oh, off the couch.
You get down right now.
Bailey, I mean business.
What are you doing?
Oh!
Get down.
What are you doing?
Whoa, hey!
[gasps]
I told you,
you're not the boss of me!
Okay, okay, all right,
no I see, here we go.
I'm a mean kid, I'm a mean kid
that's having a tantrum.
I'm such a baby, baby,
baby tantrum, baby.
[sighs]
How'd that look?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
[insects chirping, dog barking]
[door opens]
[Gemma sighs]
I'm so sorry I'm late.
Oh, no worries.
Do you want a glass of wine?
Oh, um, okay.
[Gemma] So how was he today?
Oh, he was a little...
he ripped up his homework.
Oh, he's been doing that.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, it was intense.
[laughs]
[sighs]
- Alec diagnosed him with ADHD.
- Oh.
He suggested I put him
on medication.
Oh.
He's just a kid, I mean,
there's gotta be other
ways to handle it.
You ever read those
advice articles?
They always pop up
on my social media.
It's like I survived cancer
without using chemo,
that kind of stuff.
What's happening
with your hair?
Oh, um...
I... we played hairdresser
and I was the customer.
You were really lucky that he
did not actually cut your hair.
- Yeah.
- He did that to Fi once.
Oh I remember that.
Yeah, I think it's gonna
be a little difficult
to brush out, but I don't know,
it's just hair.
I'll cut it;
it'll grow out.
Hold that thought,
I'll be right back.
What?
I was kidding
about cutting my hair.
Not getting scissors.
What happened
to Fi's painting?
Ah, that's a brush.
It's good.
What do I do with this?
[gentle music]
[Jane] Oh, um, just don't
throw it away.
Yeah.
So what... what happened
to Fi's painting
that was by the piano?
Ruth.
Ruth happened.
She also asked me
to bring over Fi's ashes
for her to keep, when we
come to visit for Passover.
Ruth, I mean she's
Fi's mom, so.
She was just so
against you even...
It's fine, it's fine,
it'll be fine.
You're gonna keep
some of them though, right?
Yeah, um...
I was thinking of turning
them into a tattoo,
and, like, putting
a little bit of the ashes
mixed in with the ink.
- Say what now?
- I know.
My receptionist
gave me the idea.
She took some of her cat's ashes
and made a paw print tattoo.
Okay, that is somet... I never thought
of you as, like, a tattoo person.
Yeah, well,
I never had a reason.
How're we doing back there?
Uh...
We're doing.
[Jane laughing]
It's going really
well, actually.
[Ruth] You're so
good to him, Jane.
Hopefully Gemma's appreciative.
¿Cómo estás?
[man on app] Bien, gracias,
¿y tú?
[both] Bien, gracias, ¿y tú?
["Atlas" by Daggy Man]
[both speaking jumbled Spanish]
- Yeah, I have no idea.
- No clue, all right.
[music continues]
♪ Bent breeze
On exhausted fire ♪
♪ Oh, to know, to know ♪
[Gemma] Honestly, I think
he's falling asleep
during these meetings.
Yeah.
You're doing it wrong, give it to me.
Hold on a second.
What are you, like a snot
connoisseur or something?
Yeah, kind of.
You have to go in
circles like this.
Is this, like, a thing now?
Yeah, it's been a thing.
I don't know why
he's doing this to me.
Thank you.
Yeah, make sure
he gets the email.
Yeah, he's, like,
warming up to me.
It's been a good
couple of months.
I feel like I'm, like,
getting the hang of it.
Hey Ruth, I have another
call coming through,
I'm gonna call you back, okay?
- [Ruth] Love you, dear.
- Hello?
[Miss Sue] Hi, is
this Jane Collins?
Oh, thank you.
I'm not interested.
[Miss Sue] Wait, wait, wait.
This is Miss Sue
at JT Elementary.
Are you able to pick up Bailey?
Gemma isn't
answering her phone,
and you're
our emergency contact.
Wait, what, is he okay?
[Miss Sue] Yeah, yeah,
no, I mean yeah.
I would rather talk in person.
Okay, I'll be right there.
♪ I guess you never ♪
[knocking]
Come in!
Hi, I'm Bailey's...
I'm his Jane.
- Thank you so much for coming.
- Yeah.
Bailey had an accident today.
Is he okay?
What kind of accident?
- Incontinence.
- Oh.
Yeah, he refused to wear our
in-case-of-emergency clothes.
[sighs]
Poor baby, okay.
I'll take him home.
Here's the problem.
He did it on purpose.
[laughs]
Come again?
At morning break,
the kids were swapping food,
and Arthur didn't want
to swap his pudding
for Bailey's carrots, so
Bailey threatened to pee on it.
- He didn't.
- He did.
Did he, like, unzip
and, like, bring it out?
No, no.
No.
He grabbed the pudding,
sat on it, and peed.
Jesus, okay.
So we're looking
at a three-day suspension.
Okay, okay, is that necessary?
We don't condone this sort
of behavior at JT Elementary.
Right, right,
but his mom just died,
so, like, I mean,
can you even imagine
what that's like for him?
Things like this
are bound to happen.
Of course.
However, we think some time
off of school would be best.
Right, for the school, maybe.
So wait, your guys'
way to deal with it
is to not deal with it,
that's awesome.
Awesome system you got going on.
You guys teach kids,
you know that, right?
There's no need to yell.
So?
So...
Yeah, I got nothing.
Let's get you home.
Bailey, please buddy, come on!
Let go!
Oh, my God.
Just get in the tub, buddy.
It's just the bathtub.
Bailey, come on.
You are covered in pee.
Here we go,
my foot's in.
My foot's in.
Bailey, get up.
Bailey, you got it, you
got it, I got you, okay?
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
Good, there you go.
There you go, hey
look, hey, you did it.
You did it.
I'm really proud of you.
You got it.
Look at you.
We did it, we did it.
Oh, my gosh.
Wait, Bailey.
Bailey, did you hear that?
It's the bubble monster,
and it's coming to get you.
[both laughing]
[Miss Sue]
I wanted to speak to you
before the babysitter did.
Understand our side
of the situation.
Yes, of course.
I will talk to him,
and I'll decide
on the course of discipline,
alongside the suspension.
[Miss Sue] Thank you, Gemma.
So why did you pee
on the pudding?
There's no right answer,
I'm just curious,
'cause it wouldn't have
been my go-to move.
It is creative.
I give you that.
Mommy always used
to put them in my lunchbox.
Why don't you ask
your mom to get you some?
I did, but she forgets.
Well, why didn't you ask me?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
I'm your Jane.
That's gotta count
for something, right?
I wish I could
swap mom for mommy.
[Gemma sighing]
[Jane humming]
Hey, Gem.
Gem?
Wha... I'm sorry... this is
ridiculously inappropriate.
- What the hell is going on?
- What is wrong?
Get out now.
Seriously, get out of the tub, Jane.
[Jane] Okay.
Okay, can you cover
yourself up, Jane?
Okay, I'm looking for a towel.
[Bailey yelling]
He's got soap
in his hair, Gemma.
Gem, wait.
Do not tell me how
to take care of my kid.
Come on.
Go get changed, okay, Bailey.
You call me when something
like this happens.
I tried, you were in meetings,
I couldn't get ahold of you.
You can't talk back
to a teacher.
You can't take a bathtub
with a seven year old.
You can't just come around here
and do whatever we wanted to do...
What can I do then, huh?
Because he wouldn't bathe,
he had piss all over himself...
- Oh, my God. You're not a parent.
- He was having a fit.
You couldn't possibly
understand; I don't know why...
He just wanted pudding.
He wants something
new every week, Jane.
He wanted a pony last week.
Well, this isn't a pony.
It's the pudding.
It's the pudding that
she put in his lunch box.
I don't know, I don't know why...
You're supposed
to be helping me.
I thought I was!
Sorry.
Call Alec.
[phone ringing]
[Alec] Hey, Jane.
Hey, hi.
You said I could call,
so I'm calling.
Hi, it's Jane.
[Alec laughs]
Hey, what's up?
I need your advice.
Are you doing anything tonight?
[Alec] Going to Milton's
with a few friends.
You still go to Milton's?
[Alec] You know what they
said, if it ain't broke.
- You want to join?
- Yeah, I do.
All right, let's...
I'll see you there.
[gentle upbeat music]
Whiskey ginger, thanks.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
Happy Friday.
Fuck Friday.
What are you drinking?
- A whiskey ginger.
- Awesome.
[bartender] There you go.
What can I get you?
- Mm.
- Okay?
I hate whiskey.
Hi, Jane.
Oh, shit.
I haven't seen them since...
The night you
broke up with me.
- Yeah, this is gonna be weird.
- Yeah.
Oh no, it's been a long time.
- She'll be fine.
- [sighs]
- Come on.
- Okay.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, girl.
Do we know you?
Yep, still hate me.
I'm kidding, it's a joke.
I'm so sorry about Fi.
Thanks, Suz.
So I'm gonna go... I...
No, hey, come on.
One drink.
Thanks.
So how naked were you?
Because I don't think this has
anything to do with Bailey.
[Jane] Wait, what do you mean?
Well, she's a lesbian, right?
[Jane] Uh, so?
So let's say Gemma was a man.
Would you have been
that unguarded?
[Jane] With a man, no.
[Suz] Yeah, but she's
attracted to women, right?
I mean perky nipples
through a soaked T-shirt.
- [Paul] Ooh, say more.
- [Suz] No, no, no.
[Alec] On a scale
of one to ten,
ten being the absolute
worst, it's about a six.
[Paul] Need a nanny
for dummies book.
Wow, cheap shot, man.
[Paul] Sorry, lesbian
for dummies.
Paul!
Okay, okay, how about this?
I used to undress in front of Fi
all the time, never an issue.
[Paul] Well that's different.
Lesbians don't have
sex with their friends.
They're far more
intellectualized than that.
Guys, take it
from the lesbian.
[Paul] That's right.
[laughter]
[Jane] Okay, Alec.
Help me out.
You're the professional.
No, I am off the clock.
[Jane] Come on.
I understand why
you did what you did.
[Jane] So why am
I the bad guy?
Because Gemma had no context.
[Suz] How close
are you with Gemma?
I mean, if Fi
and I weren't friends,
I don't think Gemma
and I would be friends.
I don't know; it's a gray area.
Okay, see,
therein lies the conflict.
I mean, take Paul for example.
He sleeps with girls
he can't stand.
Oh yeah, there's something
in the aggressive dislike
that turns him on.
Sexual desire
isn't built on love
or the need to build a future.
- Not always.
- Sometimes never.
[Jane] Hold on, so you sleep
with people that you hate?
- [Suz laughs]
- I do.
I do do that.
[Jane] You're an honest bunch.
I'm not mad at it.
[all laughing]
This was fun.
Yeah, it was.
Look at you, Alec.
You're a doctor now.
You're a mother fricking doctor.
That's cool; you're cool.
And some would say sexy even.
When Fi became a mom,
what did I become?
Still figuring it out.
Well, yeah, but there's
nothing sexy about that.
[both laughing gently]
[Jane sighing]
[Gemma] Hi Jane, it's Gemma.
I've decided to hire
a professional babysitter.
Thank you for your help
the last couple of months.
I hope you have a good day.
Bye.
[gentle guitar music]
Hey, girl.
Hey... Hannah.
- How's life?
- Never been better, you?
Oh, my God, me too.
It's crazy, right?
Are you gonna be
around this weekend?
Can't imagine
where else I'd be.
Oh my God, yes.
Do you think you could
water my indoor plants?
I'm going home for a week,
slash Sundays for Passover,
slash my sister's having a baby.
I could leave a key for you.
- Wait, it's Passover?
- Today.
Like today, today?
Uh-huh.
Pick a lane,
any lane, pick it.
Oh, you're not gonna
use your blinker.
Oh, that's great,
that's smart,
'cause you know
that's not for you, right?
[music continues]
Hey.
What are you doing here?
You weren't returning
my messages,
so I made you this;
it's a Ruth survival kit.
It's got Advil
for when she drones on,
mini vodka bottles when she's
being passive aggressive,
coloring book for Bailey.
It's stupid, I didn't...
oh, just take it.
[Bailey] Jane's coming?
Oh, B-boy.
[groans]
Get in here, hi.
Jane, you know how
I always tell you my dreams,
but you haven't been here,
so I have all these
dreams to tell you.
- Do you want to hear one?
- Absolutely.
I have so many dreams
to tell you too.
Get in the car.
You can tell Jane on the way.
- Come on!
- What?
- Come on.
- Go get your bag.
- Come on!
- I don't have a bag; how did...
- Get your bag.
- How did you know?
Okay.
You're good.
You're coming with us.
We're stealing with you.
Okay, all right,
you can steal me.
- [Bailey] Come on Jane!
- Hold on!
- [Bailey] Hurry up!
- Okay.
- [Bailey] J-dog?
- [laughs]
I'm coming.
Get in your seat and buckle up.
[gentle guitar music continues]
[music fades out]
That was
the second worst dinner
I've ever had ever.
- Bailey.
- In my whole life, what?
What do you expect?
You two never introduced
him to anything kosher.
Hey, Bailey,
show Bubbe your lizard.
Gemma, you did not bring
a lizard into this house.
[Gemma and Jane]
It's imaginary.
Well, I would love
to meet him.
He's in my backpack
and doesn't want to come out.
Oh, that's nice,
sweetheart, that's nice.
The most important thing
to me is that Bailey
gets that money that
is in a trust fund...
- This is all pretty standard.
- And that it's safe in there.
I'm aware,
so I completely understand.
If you just tell me
where to sign, I can.
- Cool!
- [Jane beatboxing]
♪ I'm Bailey ♪
♪ I'm here on the daily ♪
♪ I'm a dancer ♪
♪ A thug, like prancer ♪
♪ I'm J-dog ♪
♪ I hiphop like a frog ♪
♪ We spit a mean track ♪
♪ Always have each
other's back ♪
♪ We're friends ♪
♪ We put on a good show ♪
♪ You wish you had our flow ♪
Drop the mic, B-boy.
Woo!
That was awesome.
[Jane] We are friends.
Mm-hmm.
[insects chirping]
You getting in?
Thinking about it.
[both laughing]
- Here.
- Ugh, thank you.
How's it going in there?
- Uh...
- You okay?
[Gemma sighs]
[Jane] Ah.
[laughs]
Can I ask you something?
And I just want you to be
totally honest with me.
I'm not gonna get all Gemma
on you or anything.
Am I failing him?
[soft, emotional music]
How so?
I don't know how to love him
through all of this.
Like, I look at him
and I just see her.
You know, she made
it look so easy
and it's...
it's not.
It's really not.
And, like, I know that I'm
letting him down, you know?
I don't know how to change it.
[music continues]
Do everything
you can to make it right.
Even if you make it wrong,
keep trying, right?
How did she do what she did?
Like what, her being her?
Yeah, that.
I don't know.
She had this way
of making you feel safe,
like she was shielding you
from the outside world.
Who was shielding her?
I thought I was.
Yeah.
Me too.
Sorry.
Thank you so much for
helping out with Bailey.
- He's finally down.
- Yeah.
Yeah, no problem.
I'm really sorry you
have to sleep down there.
That can't be comfortable.
Oh, it's not,
but I have survived worse.
You know what?
Yes!
Let's see.
Oh, yeah.
[Gemma] Oh, my God.
I wonder if it's still hits.
Is that joint
from high school?
[Jane coughing]
Shh!
[Jane laughing]
It still hits.
It's nasty though.
It's really nasty.
[laughs]
[Gemma] Okay.
Wow.
Ruth is definitely
gonna smell that.
What's she gonna do,
ground us?
God damn, I miss her so much.
Me too.
I miss her every day.
I don't wanna cry again.
That's okay.
- [Gemma] Do you cry?
- [scoffs]
No.
Why?
'Cause I won't stop.
That's why I can't start.
Scoot over.
[Gemma sighs]
I'm so mad at her, Jane.
Like, I am so mad.
Sometimes I feel that more
than I feel anything else.
[gentle music]
Show me.
[music fades out]
- Dragon's dead.
- What?
- [Jane] What?
- He's dead; he's gone.
No, no, no, I just saw him.
He came in here
and he was happy.
You're lying.
I got up and he was dead.
Shh.
What's going on?
His lizard died,
his imaginary lizard.
- Oh, my goodness.
- It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
[Gemma] It's okay, sweetie.
Mom, you have
to say those words.
About Dragon?
Dragon, thank you
for being such a good pet.
You were the bestest.
And we hope you're
happy wherever you are.
- Bubbe?
- Hm?
[Bailey] Can we do
that dirt thing now?
Of course, honey.
[gentle music]
[Gemma] Alec, no, he didn't
say how he died,
just that he died.
I don't... I don't...
Jane, do you know
when Bailey got the lizard?
Oh, I met Dragon when I first
picked him up from school.
Okay, so it was,
like, six months ago.
I think he needs
a better therapist.
- No, Alec's good.
- No, I did.
- Trust me.
- I started him
on the low dose
like two weeks ago.
Wait, low dose?
What low dose?
[Gemma sighs]
Okay, all right.
Thank you, Alec.
What did he say to do?
You put him on the meds?
Alec thinks that this
is normal behavior,
considering the circumstances,
and he's going to bring
it up in his next session.
Okay, and the meds?
- What meds?
- Yes, Jane.
I thought that it was a good
idea to start him on the meds.
What meds?
Bailey has ADHD.
- [Bailey] Mom?
- Bailey doesn't have that.
- He's rambunctious.
- Well Alec thinks...
That's not clinical.
That's a typical seven year old.
Alec thinks that it's
going to level him out, Ruth.
I cannot believe he
would do that to a child.
It was recommended.
Numbing him?
All that's gonna do is help you.
Ruth, that's not fair, okay?
Parents drug up their children
to make their own lives easier.
- Mom!
- Fiona would never
have done that.
Wow, Ruth, you are
being unreasonable.
Oh, and what you're
doing is any better?
You're kidding
yourself if you think
you're all of a sudden gay;
give me a break.
Wait, what?
Janie, I see
everything you're doing
to make this family
stay together,
but Bailey's life
is upside down.
This is gonna make
it a whole lot worse.
I would never do anything
to hurt him...
And if you ever smoke
dope in my house again,
you will not be welcome back.
Yeah, you think that
was the first time.
Come on, Ruth.
You're smarter than that.
[Ruth] So are you.
[gentle music]
So, in light
of Dragon's death...
maybe you could come back
and help us out a little bit.
I mean, if you even want to,
or if you even can.
I don't know what
you have going on.
Yeah, no, yeah.
I can pick him up tomorrow
and take him to therapy.
Thanks.
Thanks, Jane.
And Jane, I...
Are we home yet?
Yes, sweetheart.
[Jane] I'm gonna go.
- You good?
- [Gemma] Yeah.
Okay, awesome.
[laughs]
Yeah, you too.
- Bye.
- [Gemma] Bye.
♪ I never thought eyes ♪
♪ I never thought to change ♪
♪ And now I look around ♪
♪ And now I see what's plain ♪
♪ I am the one who shuts
The door and my shutters ♪
All right.
Ask Vanessa.
Can I please have a lollipop?
You sure can, mister.
Hey, can I talk
to you real quick?
Yeah, sure.
My next client's in 30.
Vanessa, is that all right?
Uh-huh.
Um...
Holy shit.
I'm only telling you because I
need your professional opinion.
[laughs]
Well as your friend, holy shit.
Okay, but like, what do I do?
As a therapist,
tell me as a therapist,
and I know, I know,
I know that you're like,
"It's unethical Jane, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah,"
but, like, seriously,
I've no idea what I'm doing.
Tell me what to do,
and I'll literally... I'll do it.
Here's a question for you.
Did you enjoy it?
Well, don't give me that look.
Sorry, yeah, I just...
I did not see this coming, okay? Um...
Am I like a lesbian?
Can it switch like that?
I don't think you
have to label it.
Well, you labeled Bailey ADHD.
That's an actual disorder
with criteria for diagnosis.
Then give me
your professional diagnosis.
There's nothing to diagnose.
You're exploring bisexuality.
No, that's gray area.
Could this be like
a symptom of something bigger?
Sexuality isn't a symptom;
it's a human experience.
I need more, okay?
Fi used to help me out
with this kind of shit.
[gentle music]
I can't... I can't go it alone.
I mean, you think I wanna
be asking you for advice?
At some point in my stupid life,
I forgot to make friends,
and forgot to, like, date.
I hear you.
Do you?
Are you sure you aren't
interested in talking to someone?
It's obviously up to you,
but I think it
would be beneficial.
There's a lot to unpack here.
Then start unpacking.
Sorry, Alec.
Please... give me something.
Maybe you slept with her because
you really miss Fi; you both do.
It was a very...
Gemma's a part of Fi for you,
and you're a part
of Fi for Gemma,
so you two had each other.
So you're saying
I'm not a lesbian?
[laughs]
Come on, Jane.
I can't define that for you.
You might just have
to be okay with that.
Oh, that's asking me
to do the impossible.
Oh yeah, well,
that is my specialty:
taking the impossible,
making it possible.
You're welcome.
You're a good friend,
and, like, an okay therapist.
[upbeat pop music]
[door opens]
Hey, Gem.
You didn't have to do that.
Oh no, I know.
I wanted to.
And there's also,
like, a warm plate
of food in the oven,
if you want it.
Thank you.
How was your day, sweetheart?
[laughs]
Kidding, sorry.
Don't mean sweetheart.
That's weird.
It was a long day, darling.
The partners are just waiting
for me to make a mistake,
just to prove I'm off my game,
and it's really exhausting.
I can imagine.
It's sometimes how I feel
when you get all Gem on me.
Really?
It's the last thing
I want you to feel.
I mean, I don't... I don't
take it personally or anything.
I was thinking I could
maybe stay the night?
Yeah.
Was kind of hoping
you'd say that.
[Jane sighs]
[gentle guitar music]
[together] One, two, three!
[Bailey] We made it for you.
It's called Dragon's Looming.
Oh, man.
I forgot to bring a book.
You wanna read to me?
I'm not reading to you.
Oh, why?
Too romantic?
Absolutely.
[Jane laughing]
[children chattering
indistinctly]
He'll bite your hand off.
Never touch shark.
He lives under the monkey bars.
He'll eat you and your parrot.
Hey, I wanna jump, hey.
Hey, you have to share!
- Ow, stop.
- Watch out.
This is a park for sharing.
- Ow!
- B-boy, ease up.
- Let me try.
- No!
- Bailey!
- This hurts.
B-boy, not cool,
man, not cool.
Bailey, hey, hey!
Ow, get off!
Bailey, hey!
- We're playing.
- That is enough.
- We were playing.
- We are leaving.
Hold on, hold on.
Can't he just take
a timeout or something?
Yeah, timeout.
I am trying to teach
him a lesson here.
Yeah, but you're being
a little harsh, don't you think?
What?
Gem.
"Now Diego was met
with a familiar feeling,
"a flicker of passion."
- Gem.
- "If only she could..."
I thought you wanted
me to read to you.
Am I done with timeout yet?
[both] No!
Listen, there are boundaries.
I'm literally just doing
what Fi would have done.
Exactly.
That's why
it's so weird, okay?
What are we doing?
Should we stop?
If that's what you want,
you have to say it to my face.
Me neither.
Do you ever think about her
when we're together?
Like think, think about her.
I think about
her all the time...
but no, not like that
when we're together, no.
Sometimes when I feel happy...
I feel terrible,
like we're betraying her.
Oh, well...
I mean, if that's
how you feel, then,
I mean, maybe we should stop.
No, no, no, no.
I take it back.
Go back to bed.
Are you sure
we have enough space
in the garage for all this?
[Gemma] I hope so.
I don't really wanna get rid
of all this stuff just yet.
Yeah.
[gasps]
Oh, I love this one.
Oh, my gosh, Gemma, smell it.
It smells like her.
[Gemma] You want
to smell, Bailey?
This one stays.
So is there anything
in this box
from Paper And Bliss
that you want to keep?
I don't know.
Let me go through it.
Okay, I'm gonna go
grab some more boxes.
Okay.
[kissing]
Lollipop.
[tablets rattling]
What do you got there, buddy?
Alec.
Bailey, where did
you find these?
There.
Hey, Gem, can I talk
to you privately?
Yeah, sure.
What's up?
Bailey, go play
in the living room, okay?
Yeah, but I wanna
be here with you.
Hey bud, ten minutes,
and then you can come back.
I promise, okay?
Babe, you're freaking me out.
Fi was on anti-depressants?
What?
Where'd you get these?
Bailey found 'em over there.
Was she depressed?
I mean, I didn't even
know she was taking these.
You swear?
Yeah, I swear.
Were you guys, like, having
problems or something?
[Gemma] I'm sorry.
What are you saying right now?
Why would Alec
prescribe these to her?
Fi was a little bit
stressed out.
I mean, I wouldn't say
that she was depressed.
She was stressed out?
She didn't seem stressed out to me.
Yeah, well we were trying
to have another baby.
A second baby?
Yeah.
[Jane] Since when?
I mean she did the
insemination two weeks before...
She never told me that.
I mean, you don't
need to know everything.
Why haven't you told me that?
You don't need to know
everything about our lives.
You don't know everything
about our relationship...
Yeah, but you're supposed
to tell me these things.
I'm supposed to tell you
every detail about my marriage?
She said that you were
gonna have the next baby.
Wasn't that the plan?
Well, we tried,
and it didn't take.
Did you force her
to have the second child?
[laughs dryly]
I didn't force her
to do anything.
Are you sure?
Because maybe she wasn't ready.
[Gemma] We were ready...
Yeah, but you're not the one
that has to have
the baby, right?
Oh, my God!
She had such a hard
time after Bailey.
She had PTSD
or whatever that's called.
- Post-partum?
- Yeah.
She had that, I'm pretty sure,
right after Bailey.
So what... what is it
that you're saying?
- You worked all the time.
- Are you saying that, what?
Maybe she was
scared, I don't know.
Are you saying
that it's my fault
that she killed herself?
Oh, my God, no, no.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm not... sorry, I'm just, like,
I just need to, like,
think through this.
So you're saying that you guys
wanted a second baby,
and that stressed her out so
much that she killed herself?
No, no, no, that's not Fi.
That's not my Fi.
Your Fi.
You know what I mean.
That's not what I'm saying.
You know what?
She was a little bit hesitant.
[Jane] Okay.
[Gemma] Because of you.
Because of me?
Okay, yeah, so you're just gonna
spin it around
on me now, uh-huh.
If the insemination took,
she was going to leave
Paper And Bliss
and stay home with the kids.
No, maybe that's
what you wanted,
but she never would
have done that.
It wasn't an easy
decision, Jane,
but you depended on her.
I would have
been happy for her.
That's why that doesn't
make any sense to me.
She didn't want
to let you down.
So you're saying that she
was so worried about me,
and that depressed her, so she
killed herself because of me?
I don't know.
You know what?
I think that's a story
that you tell yourself;
that doesn't make it true.
I knew her.
- Why do you do that?
- Do what?
You are constantly
competing with me!
You knew her better,
you two were closer,
you loved her more.
Do you know how
ridiculous you sound?
I have never once
made you feel
- like I knew her better...
- [Gemma] You constantly do.
That's not even what
I'm talking about right now.
And it's hurtful,
and it's childish,
and it's pointless.
She was my wife, Jane, my wife!
I can't go here with you.
Only when it's
on your terms, right?
Get the hell out of my house.
Get out.
[Gemma sighing]
[gentle music]
Where are you going?
I just have to go out
for a little bit.
How long is a little bit?
Just, like, a little bit.
I don't want you to go, Mommy.
Hey.
You know what?
Your mom asked
if you could go in
and give her
a really big Bailey hug.
Can you do that?
Go do that.
[gentle music]
[Jane sighing]
[car horns honking]
[woman on phone]
I can conquer anything.
I just need some help.
[narrator] Some of the
most common side effects
of Miderol are diarrhea
and loss of appetite.
Miderol may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions,
or unusual changes
in mood and behavior.
[video rewinds]
Suicidal thoughts or actions,
or unusual changes
in mood and behavior.
[video rewinds]
Miderol may cause
suicidal thoughts
or actions, or unusual...
[video rewinds]
Suicidal thoughts or actions,
or unusual changes
in mood and behavior.
If you're allergic to Miderol,
do not take Miderol.
Ask your doctor
if Miderol is right for you.
[phone beeps, video stops]
[tense music]
[engine turns over]
[indistinct bar chatter]
- Hey, guys.
- [Alec] Hey.
- Hey.
- Jane!
- Whose team am I on?
- Mine, and we are losing.
- That sounds about right.
- You're up.
You normally need a plan.
what ball are you
trying to pocket?
- All of them.
- It's not how you play.
Okay, my turn.
Well...
Nailed it.
Wow, okay.
Wrong ball, but good try.
Let's see.
- Jane.
- Why'd you give these to her?
- Jane, not here.
- Why did you give these to her, Alec?
Jane, come on, please.
Just come outside, okay?
Hold on, Alec.
Tell me.
About a month before she...
she started seeing me
as a patient.
She was having trouble
sleeping, some anxiety.
- Miderol is a common...
- Why didn't you tell me?
Doctor patient
confidentiality.
Alec, it's me.
I followed up with her,
and she thought they were helping.
Okay,
what was the exact conversation?
I don't remember
it word for word.
- Well then tell me the gist.
- That's basically it.
What was her tone?
Her tone, her tone
was calm, casual.
Okay, but what
about the side effects?
The most common
set of side effects
of Miderol include loss
of appetite, diarrhea,
but Miderol might also cause
anger, suicidal thoughts...
Yeah I know, but
the percentage of suicide
while taking
antidepressants are slim.
Slim, but it has happened.
There's always
two sides, Jane.
Millions of people
take them and it helps.
There are people
killing themselves...
- Why do you think she did it?
- That if they had access to medicine...
- What do you think happened?
- And therapy.
I've prescribed them
to many of my patients,
- and it has been proven...
- God Alec, please, please.
As my friend, tell me
your honest opinion.
I won't get mad, okay?
I just... I need to know.
Could these pills
have caused it?
Uh...
There's always a chance that
the chemicals
in the brain don't...
If you knew that...
if you knew that,
then why did you
let this happen?
Why did you risk it?
- I wanted to tell you, I...
- What?
Stop crying, stop it.
- You don't get to cry.
- I'm sorry, Jane,
Jane, I wanted to tell you,
I'm sorry, okay?
Had I known that
she was suicidal,
- I would have treated...
- Isn't that your job
- to know though?
- I'm a completely...
- Stop crying!
- I'm trying, please.
- Jane, Jane.
- Don't touch me, stop!
I want to sue Alec.
- Jane.
- We can do that, right?
[Gemma] We wouldn't be
suing Alec.
We'd be going up against
the pharmaceutical company.
They're ready
for lawsuits like that.
Our lawyers would likely spin it
so that our relationship
was the cause of Fi's suicide.
But we weren't
even together then.
It doesn't matter.
They'll do anything to keep
their side of the street clean.
But...
I have to get up early.
[Jane sighs]
[door thuds]
[Jane screams]
How are you feeling?
Pretty terrible.
I'm running late.
You're acting like yesterday
didn't happen.
Oh, it happened.
Talk about it later, okay?
[Fiona] Oh yeah, I really
like the lavender one.
- I do too, and I like this one.
- Oh that one's cute too, yeah.
Oh, oh!
[laughs]
Fi, Fi...
- [Fiona] What?
- Oh, damn.
That came out of your body.
Oh, my God.
[laughs]
I think I'm getting
a stomach bug.
Leave me alone.
[laughs]
To be honest, you should
be the one leaving me alone,
like Fi farts for my fall.
Ah, jerk some Janerism
generating Jamesom jiner.
Jameson jiner
with the Fi farts.
[Jane talking gibberish]
[Gemma]
Your passport's arrived.
Yes, good timing.
Where are you going?
Mexico.
Who, both of you?
Yeah, and Bailey.
Uh, no, I figured that
he was old enough
to stay at home
and fend for himself.
Five is way too young.
Gotta wait 'til he's six,
he'll be self-sufficient,
then he can be our chauffer
and our chef.
Oh, I like that.
Looking forward to next year.
- [Fiona and Gemma laughing]
- So when are you going again?
- Monday.
- Oh, shit.
So we should
reschedule the pitch.
No, no, absolutely not.
You got this.
Gem could only
get this week off,
so you know, who knows
when we can get away again.
No, totally, but like,
we should, like, reschedule it,
because I'm not
gonna do it right.
You've worked
really hard on this.
I wouldn't leave you with it
if I didn't think
you could handle it.
I can't handle it.
Okay, I'm gonna
go take a shower.
Okay.
[kissing]
- You're salty.
- Mm-hmm.
[Fiona and Gemma
laughing and kissing]
You know I suck
at the talking stuff, Fi.
Jane, you were
great last time.
No, I wasn't.
I, like, fumbled my words.
No, no, you were fine.
You got this, you got this.
[Bailey] Mommy!
[Fiona] Shit, okay.
I don't have time
to worry about this.
You will surprise yourself.
You always do.
[scoffs]
[Jane sighs]
[Gemma on baby screen] Why didn't you
tell her that we were gonna be gone?
[Fiona] Because
she gets in her head.
[Gemma sighs]
Well, maybe we should
just reschedule this
for later in the year.
[Fiona] No, no, she needs
to learn to be okay on her own.
[gentle music]
[monitor beeps]
Do you believe
in heaven or hell?
Why, what do you believe in?
That's why I'm asking you,
because I don't know
where mommy went.
Well, um...
Come here.
[sighs]
I believe that we have
many, many, many, many lives,
and we're given
a test in each life,
and hopefully, we pass it.
Some of us do.
Some of us don't.
Some of us make mistakes,
you know?
Some of us keep
making those mistakes,
so we have to come back
and take the test again.
You think mommy
didn't pass the test?
Oh no, no, no, buddy.
I'm sorry.
That's not... that's not
what I meant.
I'm saying it wrong.
So, mommy's learning
new lessons?
Maybe.
Like a baby, or a squirrel,
or a child,
or a turtle, I don't know.
A baby, maybe, but...
So, like, there's a baby
out there that's her?
No one really knows, Bails,
and we never will.
It's the most...
beautiful and tragic
part of life.
I feel like we
should know though.
Do you think you're
going to pass the test?
I have no idea, B-boy.
No idea.
[Bailey] You okay?
Yeah.
[door opens]
[Gemma] Hello?
I'm out here.
[slowly approaching footsteps]
Gem, we can't do this anymore.
We're always gonna choose her.
I know.
I don't know.
I'm not sure how
to do this without you.
Me too.
I mean, I don't know why I...
[gentle piano music]
I don't know why
I can't say the words.
Please, don't say them
because...
if you say them,
I won't want to go.
And I need to go.
I do though.
We need to think about Bailey.
I love you.
I love you too.
[emotional piano music]
[Bobby]
Ma'am, one second, hold.
I need permission.
Hello?
Landlord.
Hey, Bobby.
What are you doing?
Uh, there's a woman
here to see you.
She says it's an emergency.
- Is it Gemma?
- You also haven't paid rent.
I told you to wait outside.
Are you smoking
in the apartment?
Not that I know of.
Hi, Ruth.
What are you doing here?
You need to get
your act together.
[Jane] I don't need
to do anything.
Okay.
Come on, up.
Up, you get.
Take a shower.
You stink.
And then we're gonna
get your puppy.
What?
I got one; his name is Cookie.
He's very lovable.
Well, I don't need a Cookie.
Gemma's having
a hard time too.
Been staying with them
for a couple of weeks.
She's worried about you.
Just tell her I'm fine.
Oh, good God,
stop feeling sorry for yourself.
We all lost her.
You're the only one acting
like it was personal.
I can't help how I feel, Ruth.
You know, every day
I wake up and I decide...
I decide I'm gonna do my best.
I put my feet on the floor.
That's the first win.
And then I feed Cookie.
It's the second win.
They're little wins,
but they matter.
Living in the past,
it's the worst thing you can do.
People that live in the past
are clinging to their one dream.
Life is for moving forward.
Moving forward is hard,
but oh, boy,
we all have to do it.
Up, up, you get.
[dog barking, siren wailing
distantly]
[Jane sobbing]
["Terrified" by Daggy Man]
♪ Super, I guess I'll
Stay home tonight ♪
♪ Home tonight ♪
♪ Kamikaze bird
Is taking flight ♪
♪ Taking flight ♪
♪ When the wings come off ♪
♪ I'll say I can't make you
Different than you are ♪
♪ But I liked you much better ♪
♪ Back when you were
Terrified and scarred ♪
♪ You were sad
And so leathered ♪
[Jane] Dear Fi.
Where do I start?
[sobbing]
Where we began,
or when you left me?
I loved you with everything
I had to love,
and I loved you that way
because you loved me
with everything you had too.
That's what made us, us.
I've gone over everything
and I still can't
make sense of it.
You couldn't tell me
why your soul was breaking,
and I wish I had
the chance to fix it.
I'm forever broken now too,
but I forgive you.
I'm finally okay
with being okay
that I'm not okay.
There's something
liberating about that.
[sighs contentedly]
Thank you
for sharing your family,
sharing your wife, your son.
While I never saw it coming,
it will forever be our story.
[Daggy Man]
♪ Don't mean I won't ♪
♪ To get into their pants,
To talk's enough ♪
♪ But when the words run out ♪
♪ You'll say I can't make
You different than you are ♪
♪ But I liked you much better ♪
♪ Back when you were
Terrified and scarred... ♪
[Jane] You are my best friend.
I never imagined that
I would get this lucky.
Thank you for making me, me.
[music continues]
My wish is to see you again,
but until then,
thank you for choosing me
to share your life.
Love, Jane.
["Denial" by Daggy Man]
[Daggy Man] ♪ The more I overthink It
over, it makes sense ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ This doesn't need
To change much ♪
♪ It could be life
If life is fucked up ♪
♪ Don't cry now, silly,
He's a willing child ♪
♪ Stuck in a fascination
With denial ♪
♪ Don't cry now, silly,
He's a willing child ♪
♪ Stuck in a fascination
With denial ♪
♪ Now, now, now, now ♪
♪ I make a movie based
On truly sad events ♪
♪ This doesn't need
To change much ♪
♪ It could be life
If life is fucked up ♪
♪ The more I overthink it over,
It makes sense ♪
♪ I don't think I can hack it ♪
♪ What is a life
Without the habit ♪
♪ Don't cry now, silly,
He's a willing child ♪
♪ Stuck in a fascination
With denial ♪
♪ Don't cry now, silly,
He's a willing child ♪
♪ Stuck in a fascination
With denial ♪
♪ Now, now, now, now ♪
[gentle music]
[gentle guitar music]