[intro music]
[uplifting orchestral music]
[upbeat rock music]
♪ I've got something
Very strange ♪
♪ It's my karma boomerang ♪
♪ Boomerang ♪
♪ Comes back again ♪
♪ Send it spinning
Through the air ♪
♪ Comes back to me
From somewhere ♪
♪ To share ♪
♪ It's only fair ♪
[mouthing music]
♪ Instant karma ♪
♪ Karma takes the wheel ♪
♪ When it comes back ♪
♪ Karma counts for real ♪
♪ Waiting on it ♪
♪ But it's bringing more
Than I could ever need ♪
♪ Yeah, oh ♪
Sandy?
Hi, um, can my friend come with?
Uh.
It's my first day.
I don't really know
all the rules.
Yeah, sure, why not?
Okay.
So I'm guessing
you all are students?
Wow, you must be smart
for a U-Lift driver.
[laughs]
Come on, give me a break.
Hey, I did let your friend
come along for free.
Sorry, we had a big test
and it kicked our ass.
No worries.
- What are you studying?
- [Latisha] Marketing.
Oh, that's cool.
That's what I studied.
And now you're a U-Lift driver.
Wow, we are totally screwed.
We might as well
just drop out now.
[girls chuckling]
Marketing is a good major.
I just hit a string of bad luck,
but it's only temporary.
You will for sure get good jobs
when you graduate.
We'll worry about that
some other time.
We're gonna hit some shrooms.
Do you wanna join?
[chuckling] Um, I wish,
but I have a big marketing job
interview to get to.
Plus, it might be a little hard
to explain to my girlfriend.
All right, here we are, ladies.
[Latisha] Well,
thanks for the free ride.
- Have fun with the shrooms.
- [Sandy] We will!
[murmuring patrons]
You probably thought I wasn't
gonna show up, didn't you?
Look, I got you something
to drink.
It's okay, Mom.
I'm fine, thanks.
You know you need
to stay hydrated
or you'll get your headaches.
Yeah, Mom, I know.
Okay, I'm an adult, remember?
Well, if you acted
more like an adult,
then I wouldn't have to
remind you of so many things.
This is what
you should be drinking.
It not only hydrates you,
it boosts your energy,
it aids your digestion,
it provides you
with antioxidants,
it detoxifies your liver,
improves your eyesight,
and it will even help you
with your constipation.
Jeez, Mom!
Why don't you say it louder
so everybody can hear?
Sorry. You know I worry.
I just wanna make sure
you're okay.
I know, and I appreciate that,
but sometimes you just need
to dial it back a little bit.
Oh, my God.
Mom...
Why didn't you tell me
that it tasted like...
licking somebody's underarm?
Well, it is fermented.
You know, like sauerkraut.
And it's
the fermentation process
that provides you
with all the health benefits.
Great.
Never mind.
Tell me, how are you doing?
How's the new job
at the computer company?
What's wrong?
- I got laid off.
- You what! Why?
You just started there
last month.
Does it matter why?
Maybe.
- Did you do something wrong?
- No, I didn't do anything wrong.
- Was it the hair?
- No, Mom!
Okay, just calm down.
They were making cuts and I
was the new guy, so it was me.
But it's okay, relax.
I already have a new job.
Really?
That was quick.
Where?
U-Lift.
[groans]
U-Lift?
Driving people around?
Jeff, you know
that's not a real job, right?
It is a real job.
And, actually, I have to
get back to work.
So thank you for the fermented
sauerkraut drink,
- but I'll see ya later.
- Jeff!
I... I didn't mean that.
You know I love you.
And I know it's a real job,
but it's just temporary, right?
[door opens and closes]
Oh, hey babe.
Hey!
Oh, that looks good.
Hi.
Mmm.
Oh, I missed you.
How was your day?
Uh... it... it was a day.
Okay.
But I think I made over $100,
so that's not too bad
for my first day.
- I don't care about that.
- Mm?
Well, I do, but...
how was your day?
How about some wine first?
Yeah.
[wine bottle thuds on table]
[sighs]
All right, where do I begin?
Okay, well my first riders
were these college girls
who invited me
to do mushrooms with them.
Uh, did you?
No, of course not.
- Come on.
- I... I just...
Okay, well, then, things
got really weird after that.
There was this couple
that I picked up
and they were... they were
dressed all in black clothing.
They had this like goth type
makeup on
and... and what I hope
was fake blood
just dripping from their chins.
I tried to talk to them.
I said their costumes were cool,
but they just grunted
and growled at me.
- Weird.
- Oh!
And guess
where I dropped them off.
A cemetery.
What?
That is so creepy!
Uh, they left me five stars
and a pretty good tip, so... eh.
Was that the worst of it?
No.
I wish it was.
The worst part was meeting
my mom at the coffee shop.
You know,
I think she cares about me,
but I don't know,
sometimes she can just be
just so condescending,
and she told me today
that she doesn't think
U-Lift is a real job.
And it just made me feel
really crappy, you know?
Yeah.
I'm just happy
to be home with you.
So, do you travel a lot?
To some people
it might seem like a lot.
To me, it's not too bad.
- I still enjoy it.
- Cool.
Do you have a favorite place?
Oh, do I!
Yeah, that would be India.
Wow, India.
And why's that?
[Sighs] Wow,
where would I start?
To me, India is just... the
natural beauty is just awesome.
The diversity of people.
The sheer nature of it.
And the people there,
wow, just so amazing.
[engine sputtering]
Whoa, whoa, hey, whoa!
What the hell?
- [Jeff] Ugh!
- [engine turns off]
- Crap! Could it get any worse?
- What's going on?
Because of you,
I'm gonna miss my meeting.
- Have you ever gotten a zero star rating?
- Oh, come on, man.
What happened to all that peace
and love and friendship stuff?
All that stuff
was left back in India.
I need to get to my meeting now.
Okay, look, I'm sorry.
I...
I tell you what.
I'll take off the charge
for the ride, and...
You can have this too.
That's all the money I have.
Please don't give me a
bad rating. I need this job.
How are you gonna be
a U-Lift driver
with a piece of junk of a car?
You need some help?
Shouldn't I be asking you that?
[laughs]
With the car, I mean.
You need to move it.
Um, yeah, thanks.
Thanks man, I...
I really appreciate the help.
Sure thing.
I'm sorry, I just gave
my last cash to the rider.
[Sam] So, what's the news?
I lost my job.
You got fired from U-Lift?
No, I can't drive U-Lift anymore
because my stupid car
broke down.
And the mechanic said it would
be $1,000 to fix, which I can't afford.
I see.
Sam, I don't think
you understand.
If I don't work,
we can't afford rent.
And we'll get kicked out
of our house.
We can't afford
to live together,
so I'll be forced to go move in
with my mom.
There's no way in hell
that's happening.
So, basically we're done
and I'm going to be homeless.
And you don't think you're
overreacting like just a little bit?
No, no, I don't.
My life is shit right now.
I am on the worst string
of bad luck.
Nothing is going right, everything is
falling apart, not just my stupid car.
- I think I'm cursed.
- Maybe so.
But you know what they say,
"It's always darkest
before the dawn," and all that.
So, um, who knows?
Maybe today is the day
that everything changes.
What does that even mean?
Are you gonna give me
some positivity pep talk?
[laughs] No.
Remember my friend
from work, Kumar?
Uh, yeah,
he's the IT guy, right?
Yeah, well, he told me
this morning
that he's going to India
for three months
to visit his home city
of Baroda.
Okay, so how is that
good news for me?
Because...
he gave me his car
and said that I can use it whenever I want
while he's gone so it doesn't just sit around.
And it's a really nice car.
Much better than the old smokey
that you were driving.
So...
you can use it, if you want,
until yours gets fixed.
[funky music]
♪ Keep it all
Under lock and key ♪
♪ On a test and a mystery ♪
♪ Pull down those shades
Quietly ♪
♪ And move along
Nothing here to see ♪
[female passenger] Then he says
he's been sleeping with my sister,
but still wants
to go out with me.
Can you believe that?
Jeez.
Is that when you punched him
in the face?
I should have.
Instead, I just threw my beer
at him and left.
[chuckles]
Well, good for you.
But, still, that really sucks.
It does.
But it's all right because
when I left his place,
I went to his brother's
and slept with him.
Nice sign.
Hey, I know that guy.
Wave him over.
[passenger] Hey, come here.
Hey, man, thanks again
for the help with my car.
You're welcome, sir.
I really appreciate it.
You did me a favor.
You deserve this.
Thank you, General.
Your Majesty.
[light music]
Well, I'm sorry things didn't
work out with his brother,
but I hope things work out
with his cousin.
- I've got a good feeling.
- [chuckles]
Thanks for listening.
Oh, hey, you dropped some money.
Not mine.
[ethereal music]
Huh.
I can't even describe
how happy I was all day
after finding that money.
I felt like I was floating.
What'd I tell ya?
I know, but... [sighs]
What's wrong?
[sighing]
I'm really happy right now.
I can't even describe it.
But I'm also excited
and... and scared too.
Scared?
Why? What's wrong?
Well, this is the first bit of good
luck I've had in awhile, and...
I hope it's a sign
of things to come,
but I'm scared it'll all
be over before I know it.
So, I'm worried and wondering
how to keep it going.
Jeff, honey, relax.
Luck, good fortune, magic...
whatever you wanna call it,
you can't keep it going
any more than you can keep
a wave going.
You just have to ride it
for as long as it lasts
and then, like surfing,
keep an eye out for the next one
and get ready for it.
[light music]
- Can you pop the trunk?
- Sure.
- Do you need a hand?
- Nah, I got it.
[trunk opens]
- [suitcase thuds]
- [trunk beeps]
Hey, hope you didn't put
a dead body in there.
Not the entire body.
Just some parts.
Just kidding.
It's just some gear I'm using
for a workshop I'm doing.
Hey, do you mind if I make
a stop real quick?
[passenger]
Sure, go ahead.
Hey.
- Are you following me?
- [Jeff chuckles]
- Busted.
- [laughing]
What are you doing
all the way over here?
What?
I can't come downtown because
I'm currently without a residence?
No, you're just a long way
from where I saw you last time.
You must be tired as shit
from walking all that way.
I don't have any money on me
right now, but, um... hold on.
That's mighty nice.
Thanks.
I gotta run, but I can come back
and give you a ride
after I drop my passenger off.
Not necessary.
But thanks for the lunch.
[trunk beeping]
Uh, can I help you with these?
I should be able to carry it on
if you just wanna hand it to me.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, sure.
And what about your bags?
Um, they're not mine.
Gotta go.
Don't wanna be late.
[ethereal music]
Huh.
[trunk beeping]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Wow...
What are all these?
I mean, I am hungry.
- What are you making me for dinner?
- [sighs]
I haven't even thought
about that yet.
Are you sure you didn't leave
some groceries in the car?
Mm-hmm, I'm sure.
Why do you keep asking?
Well, if you didn't leave
groceries in the car
and none of my riders did,
I didn't buy this stuff.
You know you shouldn't drink
on an empty stomach.
Come on, let me make you
some dinner.
- Come on. Come on.
- Yeah. [giggles]
I know I can't make luck
continue...
but I sure would like to know
what's causing this.
You know, like how waves
are caused by the wind?
Isn't it enough to know that maybe
you're just having some good luck
and things are finally
going your way?
Yeah, I guess.
But if I could just figure out
what's causing this wave, then...
maybe I could get
in the sweet spot
- and ride it for as long as possible.
- Mm.
Hey, hold on, hold on, hold on.
- I need your help on this.
- Okay.
I'm in. I'll help.
Okay.
So I found money and a
bunch of groceries in my car...
Well, in your friend's car...
After I dropped off
two passengers.
And it didn't belong
to your passengers?
Correct.
Then you dropped off
other passengers,
but didn't find anything
with them, right?
So, what did those two
passengers have in common
that wasn't true
for the other passengers?
[slams table]
I got it. I got it!
[laughs]
Okay. You gonna tell me?
I got it!
You'll know tomorrow
if I'm right.
Jeff!
Well...
[birds chirping]
Hey.
- Hey.
- Hmm.
I'm gonna go do
some early driving
so we can hang out
later this afternoon, okay?
Okay.
What did you want me
to pick up for you?
Um, some running shoes.
Mine are getting worn out.
Okay, what kind?
Uh, just the kind
that I have is fine.
Where are they?
- Under the bed.
- Okay.
Now go back to sleep.
[sizzling]
- [doorbell ringing]
- Hmm.
Hey... babe.
[Jeff] Hi.
[Sam] Uh...
[Jeff grunts]
Excuse me.
[Sam] Okay.
Oh, my gosh.
What did you do?
[Jeff] I have a little bit
of a surprise for you.
- [Jeff grunts]
- What did you do?
[laughs] I hope you like these.
Uh... [laughs]
Um.
Babe, these are awesome!
Why are there so many?
I mean, I'm not mad,
I'm... that's great,
but why'd you buy so many?
I didn't buy these.
What do you mean?
I found all these boxes
in the back of the car.
And I think I know now what's causing
this wave of good luck for me, you know?
Well, what is it?
It's a homeless guy.
I... I mean,
can you believe that?
It's a homeless guy.
Okay, so when you say
"homeless,"
you mean like...
I don't know exactly, but... but
every time I give him something,
I get back 10 times as much.
So I gave him $20
and then I got back $200.
And one day I gave him lunch,
and we got all those groceries.
So today I gave him
your old pair of running shoes
and found all these boxes
in the back of my car.
I think he's like a magical
good luck charm.
Or a... a magical wave.
Well, I think that
we should ride this wave
for all it's worth.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
[laughs] Okay.
- To Homeless Guy.
- [Jeff laughs]
Mm.
Oh, this is
some really good wine.
I found it in the groceries
that were in the car.
But I think we only have
one bottle left.
I sure would like some more.
How about you?
You wanna give wine
to a homeless guy?
I mean...
- To Homeless Guy.
[light music]
Josh West?
Dude, are you kidding?
Man, I've been a fan of yours
since you were on The Voice.
And I love your band
Vanilla Aardvark.
Thanks, man, I appreciate it.
No, I'm serious.
I listen to your music
all the time.
Awesome.
Are you ready to go?
Yeah, sorry, man.
I didn't mean to go
all fan boy on you there.
No worries.
Hey, uh, Josh,
sorry to bother you, man.
Mm-hmm.
Can I ask you a big favor?
Sure, what's up?
Would you mind singing
a song for me?
Well, not for me,
but for my girlfriend.
She loves you too.
But she's not here.
Not a problem.
[line ringing]
Babe...
guess who I have
in the car right now.
[Sam] I don't know.
Your mom?
[chuckling]
Not even close.
It's Josh West
from Vanilla Aardvark.
- Yeah, right!
- No, I'm serious.
And guess what.
He said he would
sing a song for you.
Hey, can you do that one
about magic?
We love that one.
Sure, man. Why not?
♪ Take a carpet ride
Through the skyline ♪
♪ Above the city streets ♪
♪ Where the cardboard signs
By the roadside ♪
♪ Walk on worn-out feet ♪
♪ To the traffic speed ♪
♪ All the red signs
Gather all at once ♪
♪ On a two-way design ♪
♪ Stop the spinning wheel ♪
♪ Make a quick deal ♪
♪ For a stranger's smile ♪
♪ To the traffic speed ♪
♪ Where fortunes meet ♪
♪ It's a supernatural display ♪
♪ Something that I can't
Explain away ♪
♪ It's the ebb and flow
The give and take ♪
♪ A simple change
That I can make today ♪
♪ As I go my own way ♪
♪ On a magic trip ♪
[rock music]
♪ Like a magic show
It goes up in smoke ♪
♪ Then it comes back ♪
♪ Right before your eyes
Comes a surprise ♪
♪ A rabbit from a hat ♪
♪ How about that? ♪
♪ Nothing up my sleeve
Do you believe me ♪
♪ Enough to try? ♪
♪ Take a car now ♪
♪ And I'll show you how ♪
♪ Make it multiply ♪
♪ How about that? ♪
♪ That's where it's at ♪
♪ It's a supernatural display ♪
♪ Something that I can't
Explain away ♪
♪ It's the ebb and flow
The give and take ♪
♪ A simple change
That I can make today ♪
♪ As I go my own way ♪
♪ On a magic trip ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, nah ♪
♪ It's a supernatural display ♪
♪ Something that I can't
Explain away ♪
♪ It's the ebb and flow
The give and take ♪
♪ A simple change
That I can make today ♪
♪ As I go my own way ♪
♪ On a magic trip
[light music]
[Jeff] To riding the magic wave.
To riding the magic wave.
And... to getting more.
[Jeff chuckles]
To having more.
Anything else?
Well, I have been thinking.
And I think that we need
to be more strategic.
What do you mean?
Well, don't get me wrong.
I love getting all the things
and the fact that we've been able
to make a couple thousand dollars
from selling the surplus
is great.
I just think it's time
that we got back
to the way that you started.
You know, by giving him money.
Okay.
That makes sense.
But it won't be as fun.
Since when is more money
not fun?
Okay, good point.
To more money.
How much are you gonna give him?
I was thinking $1,000.
That would give us $10,000.
Yeah, okay.
[female passenger] So how long
have you been working for U-Lift?
Uh, a little over a month now.
You like it?
It didn't start off too well,
but lately it's been
very rewarding.
[passenger] That's good.
What's up, buttercup?
[laughs] Hey, it looks like this
corner's getting pretty crowded.
Probably my fault.
I've been talking too much
about the good luck
I've been having on this corner.
What's going on?
Is there a convention in town?
Oh, no, I'm just trying
to do a good deed
for someone less fortunate.
Don't tell anyone about this.
[Jeff] Hey, sorry for
the detour back there.
Maybe it was
just a fender bender.
Have a nice day.
[passenger] You too.
[Jeff] Oh, yeah,
I definitely will.
Can you meet me
at the coffee shop now?
[Sam] Sure, hon.
On my way.
Well?
Jeff!
[funky music]
This seems really quick.
Why? Look, if we just give him
this money,
we'll have $100,000.
Yeah, good point.
Hey, um, do you know
where the other guy is?
I don't know his name, but he
usually stands on this corner.
You got a better description?
Um, well, he...
Yeah, he's the guy
with the funny signs.
We all got signs.
What, you don't think
my sign is funny?
Not bad.
You're not gonna give me
something?
Sorry, man,
you're not the right guy.
Cheap bastard.
[light music]
[whirring]
You lost your good luck charm.
He's a person, Sam.
Mm, a person.
- Whose name you don't know. Nice.
- [phone ringing]
It's been less than a day.
Okay, I saw him
yesterday morning.
- I'll find him, don't worry.
- Mm.
Yeah, well, you're not taking
the 10 grand with you until you do.
Okay.
Let me just get a shower
and some coffee, -[phone rings]
and I'll get back out there.
He's gotta be
out there somewhere.
Hey, Mom.
What's wrong?
Yeah, okay, sure, I'll meet you.
But then I have to
get out there and drive.
Okay, U-Lift is my job, Mom,
and it's a real job.
I'll see you later.
[sighing]
Come, sit down.
How's my boy doing?
Mom, you know
I don't like that stuff.
Remember what I said?
It's an acquired taste.
You won't like it
until you drink enough of it
so your distaste for it
goes away.
- That doesn't make any sense.
- Really?
Think about the first time
you drank a beer.
So, what's the big 911?
Oh, I just wanted to see you
and see how you're doing.
It's been so long.
I'm sorry I don't call you
more often.
But I am thinking about you
all the time.
I just wanted to see you,
see how you're doing.
And you don't look too good
right now.
Well...
everything was going fine
until yesterday and then...
You can tell me.
It's a long story.
[light music]
And that's how I lost
my lucky charm.
I'm sorry you feel that way,
but...
I really don't think
that's what happened.
What do you mean?
I... I can't find the guy.
Well, I mean, I think
it wasn't luck at all.
I... I don't think
you need that guy,
though it was nice
that you helped him.
I actually think
it was instant karma.
I read about it the other day
on the "inter web."
It's fascinating.
Have you heard of it?
Instant karma
is when you do good for anyone
and something good
immediately happens for you.
That's what happened,
I'm sure of it.
All you need to do now
is go back to work at your job
and do good to anyone.
Did you just say
what I do for U-Lift is a job?
I sure did, honey.
I'm sorry about the other day.
I also read about U-Lift
on the "inter web"
and now see it is a valuable
part of our new gig economy.
Mom, you're incredible.
I don't care what anyone
says about you.
- What are people saying about me?
- [laughs]
Nothing.
Nobody's talking about you, Mom.
I have to get back to work,
but thanks for the drink.
It wasn't as bad as last time.
See, what did I tell you?
Just like a beer!
[door closes]
Mom, I can't talk right now.
I have a passenger
I have to pick up right here.
I know, honey, it's me.
I'm your passenger.
How can I tell all my friends
how much I love and support you
if I don't support you?
You're awesome, Mom.
Hey, man.
You look thirsty.
Do you want something to drink?
Uh, not really, no.
I knew I should've gotten water.
Just relax.
The universe will bring you
the right person
at the perfect time.
[Jeff] Are you thirsty?
Yeah.
Can I have that?
You know what this stuff is,
right?
- Yeah, I've had that before.
- All right. [laughs]
Sorry, I don't have some food
to give you too.
Aw, thanks, man. But like
my sign says, anything helps.
[Mom] Wait a minute.
Let's give him this.
Wow.
Wow!
Thanks, man. You don't know
how much this is gonna help.
It's not a problem.
Hey, what's your name,
by the way?
Charles.
But my friends call me Chuck.
All right, Chuck.
It's nice to meet you.
I'll see you around.
Oh, thank you so much.
God bless you, God bless you.
That's it, we did our part.
Now we just wait for it
to come back to us.
Thanks again, Mom.
I'm sorry it didn't work out.
I guess everything you read
on the internet
isn't always true.
That's okay, Mom.
It was just fun
to hang out with you.
[door closes]
Where have you been all day?
I was with my mom.
Oh, great.
Bet you didn't even try
to look for your lucky charm.
Correct.
I told you not to waste
your time with her.
You know she doesn't
even believe in you.
Well, right now it seems like
you're the one
who doesn't believe in me.
Well, can you blame me?
It seems like
you're pretty tired right now.
Maybe you should just go to bed.
Who are you
to tell me what to do?
You were failing at one thing
and then another thing,
and I'm the one
that stood by you
when no one in their right mind
would have.
You know, sometimes
I wonder why I even did that.
Wow, thanks for the vote
of confidence.
You stumbled upon
the biggest lucky charm
that I've ever heard of,
and then right before
we can hit it big, you blow it!
You lose him,
and now you're acting
like it's not even a big deal!
Hey, will you calm down?
I know it's a big deal.
And I'm sorry
that I "lost the homeless guy."
But did you ever think
that maybe he wasn't
the lucky charm
that we thought he was?
Of course he is.
What are you talking about?
How else do you explain
all of the magical stuff
that's been happening?
What if it wasn't him?
What if it was...
instant karma?
Did you ever think about that?
Instant karma?
What is that?
My Mom told me about it today.
She read about it online.
It's the act of doing
a good deed to anyone
resulting in good
coming back to you.
Seriously?
It's a real thing.
I looked it up.
So Mom and I drove around
all day giving stuff
to another homeless guy.
Well?
Did it work?
No.
Are you sure?
Yeah, we checked everywhere
in the car and...
and didn't find anything.
What about the hatchback?
[light music]
[trunk beeping]
[male passenger]
So how is your day going today?
Oh, pretty good.
I got in a big fight
with my girlfriend last night,
but we've already made up.
Wow, that's impressive.
What did you do?
Well, I have to give her
most of the credit.
But I did make her pancakes.
So that's your secret?
Pancakes.
Sorry to bother you, but...
you look really familiar.
Should I recognize you
from somewhere?
Well, maybe you've seen my photo
in the post office on the wall there.
- America's most wanted.
- [chuckling]
I don't think
they do that anymore.
But, seriously,
where do I know you from?
You got me.
So, I'm the Mayor of Chandler.
I knew it. I knew it!
That's pretty cool.
It must be a tough job.
Everybody wanting
something from you.
[Mayor] That it is, my friend.
That it is.
Hey, before you go,
can I give you something?
Sure.
A stick of gum?
Should I take this personally?
No, no, I'm just giving a
small gift to all my riders today
to celebrate me
making up with my girlfriend.
That's just what I grabbed
from the bag,
but you can take
something else if you'd like.
No, this is good.
Maybe I do need it.
Thanks.
Hi there.
Let me help you out.
Oh, one second.
Let me move this.
[ethereal music]
Sorry about that.
Just right here.
So, how's your day going so far?
Who are you
and where are you taking me?
- Gotcha!
- [laughing]
Seriously, it's been
a great day so far.
We got two new residents
and they're both men.
Oh, so you're not married.
Not currently.
But check back with me in a week
and I'll let ya know.
[both laughing]
So are you meeting some
of your girlfriends for lunch?
I'm meeting my boyfriend
for happy hour!
Wow.
Well, he's a very lucky guy.
This is for you.
This is so beautiful.
Thanks so much.
And if things don't work out at
lunch, I may have to call you later.
[laughs] Have a good time.
- Hey.
[both lightly moan]
It is bigger and better
than I had ever imagined.
What?
Babe!
- Oh, my God.
- Ah, ah.
Let's go in the backyard, okay.
I'll tell you all about it.
- Okay?
- [groans]
[trunk beeping]
Okay, so anytime
you give anybody anything,
it magically comes back to you
ten times?
Yep.
Passengers, homeless people,
random strangers on the sidewalk
or in parking lots, anyone.
But did it work with money too?
I didn't have any on me,
but I'm sure it will.
Hopefully.
But I think
that we should try it
before we go in
for the big score again.
Copy.
Mm! I almost forgot.
That guy Frank called
and your car's ready.
- Jeff, what is happening? How are you?
- Frank.
Life is great.
Life is great?
Wunderbar!
You should put the
"Life is Great" on a shirt.
- There's an idea.
- Yeah, let me show you your car.
[tools whirring]
I thought it was fixed.
It is,
but it's not what you thought.
You thought your engine
was blocked and locked up.
It wasn't.
You had plenty of engine oil.
We had a simple
fuel system cleaning.
That took care of it.
You're good to go.
Wow.
Thanks.
But so you know, I don't
know what any of that means
that you just told me
about my car.
Except that...
you could have ripped me off
and charged me
for a big repair that I
didn't need, but instead...
you looked out for me.
- Thanks.
- It's not about me.
If I take care of you,
I've got a business model.
It's all about you.
Let's get you checked out.
Would you mind
sitting in the back seat?
[door closes]
Let's go!
Do you hear me?
- We gotta hurry!
- Yep.
On our way.
Should I ask
why you're in such a hurry?
I just knocked out
my stupid boyfriend.
And I stole his drugs.
[chuckling]
Well, that's something
I don't hear every day.
I wouldn't even know
how to knock someone out.
Well, it's easy
when you got one of these.
[chuckling]
Wow.
That's a big gun.
Oh, damn!
Something wrong?
I forgot my damn ChapStick!
Oh, um, I can help you
with that.
I... I think I have some
in my bag here.
- Hold on a second here.
- [horn honks]
Watch it!
Are you trying to kill us?
Yeah, sorry.
Um... sorry.
Here.
Just take the bag.
You can find it yourself.
[sighing]
- Did you find what you were looking for?
- Yes.
I can't live
without my ChapStick.
Glad you had the good stuff.
So, what else you got up there?
You got any money?
Here, take whatever you want.
Oh.
All right, here we are.
[kisses, blows]
So, did you really
pee your pants?
Yeah, a little.
Anyway...
I have a coworker
that also drives for U-Lift,
and he tells me the craziest
stories about passengers.
Yeah, involving guns?
No.
Which means that
this was probably just a one-off
and won't happen again.
Did you have any problems
with your other passengers?
Didn't have any.
Just drove around for the
rest of the day and jammed out.
Can we just change the subject?
Okay, do you know
what you're gonna give next?
Not really.
- Do you think you'll wanna drive tomorrow?
- Okay, stop, please.
I feel like
you're interrogating me.
Let me just go get the stuff
from the car.
Can I help?
[mouthing]
Sam, we... we have a problem.
What? What happened?
I went to get the stuff
out of the car,
and I opened up the back,
and it was empty.
I gave that lady a whole bag of
stuff and I didn't get anything in return.
Shit.
Am I losing the magic already?
It's okay.
There's gotta be
some kind of explanation.
Let's just talk it out.
What happened differently
with this passenger?
Well, there were multiple items.
But we did that
with the homeless man, so.
Can you think of anything else?
Um, she was in the car
when I gave her the stuff,
but, well,
we've done that before.
So that's not it.
Okay, relax.
There's no pressure.
I think I know what it is.
I didn't actually give her
anything.
I thought you said she took,
like, two bags of stuff.
That's just it,
she... she took it.
I didn't give her anything.
I put the bags in the back seat
and said she could take
whatever she wanted.
I think that's it.
Hey, I came as quick as I could.
What's up?
What is that?
This all made sense at the time.
Babe, I don't know what you're
thinking unless you talk to me.
Think about it.
I was... shit out of luck.
Every day
my life was getting worse.
Not counting you, of course.
And then I met the homeless guy.
I gave him $20 and I find $200
in the front seat of the car.
And I get to keep it.
Then I gave him lunch,
and we scored
all those big bags of groceries.
So we're thinking he must
be my lucky charm, right?
Yeah, that makes sense to me.
But then I lost him.
Then Mom showed up.
And she said
that it wasn't him at all.
It had nothing to do with him.
She said it was instant karma.
So we drove around
the rest of that day
and we gave drinks and money
to a different homeless person.
Turns out...
it was instant karma.
[Sam]
Sounds good to me.
Of course it does.
Then I gave the mayor
a pack of gum.
I find ten packs of gum
in the back seat of the car.
I met that really nice old lady,
gave her that beautiful scarf.
And so on and so forth
until the back seat of the car
is filled with stuff.
Ten times as much
as I had given away.
It was so fun.
Until I gave that stuff
to the crazy lady.
No, she took that stuff.
And I didn't get anything
in return.
Okay,
so if it's not instant karma,
then what is it?
I think it must be
your friend's car.
Think about it.
Before that showed up,
I was on the worst string
of bad luck.
You were ready to leave me.
And you probably should have
if things didn't change.
But they did change, big time...
as soon as I started driving
your friend's car.
And then when I tried
to do the same things
while driving my car,
it didn't work.
I think you're right.
But why would Kumar
give me a magical car?
[Jeff]
I don't know.
I think what we need
to do first is test this out
to see if I'm right.
And then we need to make a plan
on how to maximize
using this while we have it.
Yeah.
So, did you go to church much
when you were growing up?
Yep.
Sorry to hear that.
What do you mean?
Well, I've heard
so many horror stories
of people who were
earnestly searching for God
and got totally turned off.
Some were even hurt or abused.
Oh, none of that for me.
I just lost interest
in high school.
I discovered girls.
Well, that'll happen.
And how about now?
Um, you know,
I guess I just try to live
by the golden rule.
"Do unto others" and all that.
Like karma.
Give to others
and receive gifts in return.
That's all good.
"Give and you will be
given to."
Exactly.
Hey, you know what,
let me show you how it works.
Hey, come here a second.
Okay, you got a deal.
Who's first?
Uh, no, you have the wrong idea.
You don't have to do anything.
That's a gift.
Thank you.
I was a little nervous
for a bit there, young man.
[passenger] I was little worried
about this.
[rock music playing]
[Jeff] Well, it's clear that
you only reached out to me
so that you could have someone
to beat up on in tennis.
Well, I always remember you
being better than me in college, so.
Okay, then either one of us
hasn't played much since then,
or one of us has played a lot.
- Or maybe both.
- [chuckles]
Anyways, thank you
for letting me beat up on you
and being a good sport about it.
Of course, man.
This has been a lot of fun.
I can't remember the last time
that I had some guy time
since I started dating Sam.
Yeah, it's been a while
for me also.
It's great to catch up.
You know,
I never would have pegged you
for a U-Lift driver.
But it sounds like
it's working out for you, so...
that's cool.
Yeah, and I'm really sorry
to hear about your mom's cancer.
Yeah, well, at least she's getting
great care here at the clinic, so.
That's all you can hope for.
But I hear
that's really expensive.
How's her insurance?
Let's just say
it's not the best,
but I'm working on a way
to supplement it, so.
I'm glad to hear.
Well, this has been
a lot of fun.
The beer drinking part,
not so much
getting my ass kicked
on the tennis court.
But I gotta run.
Let's get together again
while you're in town.
Yeah, definitely.
And let me pay for the beers.
It's only $1,000, but...
I want you to have that
to help your mom.
- Dude, I can't take your money.
- Don't worry about it.
There's plenty more
where that came from.
And don't even worry
about paying me back.
[chuckles]
You know that karma's
spelled with a K, right?
Yeah, but we have a magic car.
- So I had it made with a C.
- Oh. [laughs]
I love you in pink,
but this is really pink.
Yeah, I know.
It was the only color
they had left.
Maybe it'll fade
if I wash it a couple times.
[laughs]
Wow, that shirt sure is pink!
You get it at Goodwill?
[laughs]
First time I see you in a month
and now you're a comedian?
What can I say?
I'm trying to expand
on my comedic signage.
Speaking of which...
What if I could change things?
For you and Jennifer Aniston?
Are you serious?
Tell me more.
Not here.
Can I get in?
Where to?
Thanks for bringing me here.
I love this place.
It's a beautiful stadium.
Have you ever been
to a game here?
I wish.
I never had the money.
When I was a kid
growing up in Chicago,
my dad used to take me
to Wrigley Field all the time.
I even used to dream
about playing for the Cubs.
Can I ask you something that I
should have asked you a long time ago?
Harry.
Harry Swayne.
How'd you know
I was gonna ask that?
No one ever asks me my name.
Well, like I said, I've been
meaning to ask for a long time.
Sorry, Harry.
I'm also curious...
Why did you disappear
after the last time
I gave you the money?
You're not going to like it.
Well, why not? You think
I'll be upset that you...
spent it on booze,
drugs, and women?
I wish.
Never had the chance.
What do you mean?
One of the guys
on the corner that day
saw you give me the cash
and told a few of his friends.
I... I tried to downplay it
and act like it was no big deal,
but when I left,
three guys followed me,
jumped me, and...
beat the shit outta me.
And took all the money.
And even worse, all my signs.
Sons of bitches.
Don't be mad at 'em.
It's just how it is out here.
And... anyways, I spent
a few weeks in the hospital.
Then they got me
into a rehab center to recover.
I'm just getting back to work
this week.
[Jeff chuckles]
I'm glad you mentioned that.
I've always been curious.
How does that work?
Do you have to clock in?
- [chuckling]
- Do you get to pick your corner
or do you have like a supervisor
who assigns those to you?
You're funny.
I should get your help
with my new signs.
Seriously, what if I could
help you with your sign today?
If you can get Jennifer Aniston
to go out with me, sure, I'm down.
Well, I don't know
if I have that much money.
But what if I did have enough
to get you off the streets?
At least for a little while.
That'll work too.
Okay.
Fiesta Town Apartments.
They're close by to here.
I looked 'em up online
and they seem okay.
They have
fully furnished apartments.
You can get a six-month lease,
and that should give you enough time
to get back on your feet,
find a job.
And if you need anything else,
you have my number.
I'll even go to Goodwill
with you.
We'll get you some blankets,
sheets, kitchen stuff.
Whatever you need.
Maybe we'll even find you
a cool shirt like this.
[chuckling]
I don't know what to say, man.
You don't have to say anything.
I've been in your shoes before.
Well, not homeless, but...
I did hit a string of bad luck
and someone helped me out.
So I'm just paying it forward.
Thanks, man.
We'll have to come back here
and go to a Cubs game
next season.
Deal.
I look forward to it, Harry.
- Just don't wear that shirt.
- [chuckling]
[engine starts]
I just really don't like that
the money's just in the car.
It's fine.
I parked right out front.
No one's gonna take it.
I don't know, I really think
you should just
either do the next giveaway
or take it home or something.
The next giveaway?
- Already?
- Sure. Why not?
We're gonna be millionaires.
Well, that's the plan.
All right, how about this?
I'll take the money home,
hide it...
but leave a little bit out
so we can go
on a spending spree.
That way, if we get
comfortable having money,
maybe it won't feel as scary.
Hmm.
Yeah, I like that idea.
I like that idea a lot.
[light music]
♪ I'm breaking the rules
And ♪
♪ I'm cutting the wire ♪
♪ I'm warming myself by ♪
♪ A deeper fire ♪
♪ I'm silencing sirens ♪
♪ That come from outside ♪
♪ And calming the waters ♪
♪ That flow from inside ♪
♪ Oh, say don't hide ♪
♪ In neon light ♪
♪ Hold the line ♪
♪ Don't close your eyes ♪
♪ Hang tight ♪
♪ In the stillness
Of your mind ♪
♪ Till the building hides ♪
♪ The question lies behind ♪
♪ Static kissing ♪
♪ Something missing ♪
♪ Pull the plug and hear
The song it's singing ♪
♪ A reflection ♪
♪ No reflection ♪
♪ Break the mirror
Now it's getting clearer ♪
♪ Oh, look at us ♪
♪ Looking at us ♪
♪ Look at us
Looking at ourselves ♪
You need help?
[Jeff] No, I got it.
[Sam]
You can put that over here.
- [Jeff] Right here?
- Yeah.
[Jeff] Okay.
[grunting]
Oh!
Whoo!
I can get used to this.
Are you kidding me? I'm
ready to go back out right now.
No, we need to pace
ourselves, okay?
- [groans] Do we have to?
- [laughs]
Mm-hmm.
[phone ringing]
- Oh, sorry.
- Who is that?
Eh, it's Emilio.
I should probably get this.
Hey, man, what's up?
Um, no...
Okay.
All right, man,
I'll see you later.
Okay.
What was that all about?
It's crazy,
but it might be perfect too.
He's in a real bind.
But... how is that perfect?
Well, I can help him.
And by helping him,
that could help us big time.
Okay,
so you're Mr. Riddle man now?
No, sorry, let me explain.
So, when I saw Emilio,
he said that he had a plan
to pay for his mom's
medical bills.
Okay.
It turns out that the plan
was to gamble
and win the money.
- Let me guess.
- Exactly.
He lost, big time.
So what does he want?
Well, that's the crazy part.
He needs $100,000.
Right away, tonight.
Does he need $100,000
for his mom's medical bills
or for like a gambling thing?
Says he needs it right away.
I'm assuming the latter,
but I didn't ask.
I just told him I'd help.
He said he'd pay me back, but...
I don't think he'll have to
because of the magic.
Wow, this is crazy but perfect.
[chuckling]
Mm!
Clint?
[trunk beeping]
I'll take that for you, sir.
Welcome aboard, Clint.
How's your day been so far?
It's been a long day.
At least I didn't have to
kill anyone, so.
[laughs]
Yeah, right, me neither.
I'm kidding.
You do a lot of these
night shifts for U-Lift?
Uh, not too many,
but I like the variety,
so I do them every now and then.
You should be careful.
Crazies come out at night.
Yeah, I know you said that
you've had a long day,
but are you in a hurry now?
That depends.
Can you make it worth my while?
[laughs] Probably not.
I have a buddy
who lives along the way
and I have a bag
that I need to drop off to him.
Would you mind if we stopped
on the way?
Shouldn't be a problem.
Thank you.
You got it?
Right here.
The whole amount?
Yeah, just like we talked about.
Seriously, you have no idea
how much this means.
Listen, I'll...
Listen, I'll pay you back
every cent.
Why'd you bring somebody,
though?
Don't you trust me?
Yeah, of course I do.
He's just my U-Lift rider.
Don't worry about it.
See, I told you
that wouldn't take long.
Easy peasy.
In and out.
Bada bing, bada boom.
Should I ask
what that was about?
Please don't.
I've got a U-Lift driver
who's a spy.
[chuckling]
But seriously, I could use
a guy like you.
How'd you like to make
some extra money?
Um, no, thanks.
Um, I'm good.
I'll grab your bag for you, sir.
For making my ride
entertaining, kid.
Hope to see you around.
[door creaks]
- Surprise!
- Oh!
Are you ready to celebrate?
Well, don't you wanna see
what we're celebrating first?
[funky music]
Sam...
- We're millionaires.
- [gasping]
Oh, my gosh.
We're millionaires.
Whoo-hoo!
♪ I bring my A game ♪
♪ But we're no way the same ♪
♪ And she moving,
Lay down, yeah ♪
♪ If you only see me
When I'm falling ♪
♪ I'm a Sisyphean roller
Baby ♪
♪ I'm a gun, not a chump ♪
♪ See the billings ♪
♪ Wax up,
'Cause I'm still swinging ♪
♪ Oh, I'm... ♪
- [vacuum whirs]
- ♪ Jammin' ♪
[funky music]
Good as new.
Hey, It's a good thing
Kumar texted you
to let you know
he's coming home tomorrow.
I am so glad that we got
the money last night.
- We're freakin' millionaires!
- [chuckling] Yeah!
- [Jeff] Ugh, it's probably my mom again.
- [phone rings]
- What are you doing there?
- Don't worry about it. I'm working.
[phone ringing]
[dings]
Who called?
I'm not sure.
[over phone]
Jeff, this is Clint.
Yeah, you remember giving me
a ride last night.
You need to give me
my bag back now
or you're in deep shit!
What's he talking about?
I literally have no idea.
He had one bag,
I put it in the hatchback,
and then I gave it back to him
when I dropped him off.
So you're positive
that you did not switch
that dude's bag with the giant
bag of money you brought home?
I mean, the bags
looked similar, but, no, no, no.
- There's no way that I switched 'em.
- All right, Jeff, calm down.
- Let's figure this out.
- [phone ringing]
Hello?
[Clint]
Did you get my message?
- There must be some mistake.
- That's right, and you made it.
You put my bag in your car.
It had a million dollars in it.
And now, my money's gone.
But I gave your bag back to you.
Listen, you little shit!
I'm not fucking around.
- I didn't do anything.
- Quit lying to me.
You're really starting
to piss me off.
I know you have my money.
I saw you looking at it
on the security camera.
Well... well,
what if I don't have it?
If you don't have it, then
your little friend Emilio here
is in for a world of hurt.
And then I'm coming after you.
I've got Emilio at a warehouse
north of downtown.
I'll text you the address.
Come around back.
Bring me my fucking money
or you're both dead.
You have two hours.
Put Emilio on the phone first.
- [stammers] If you want your money.
- [Clint laughs]
Playing hardball, are ya?
If you want me
to bring you your money,
I need to know
that Emilio's okay.
[Emilio] Oh, Jeff, Jeff,
you gotta help me.
This guy's crazy.
Please, please, Jeff, just...
- [punch lands]
- [Emilio grunts]
[Clint] Better hurry.
I don't think he'll last long.
We've gotta get outta here.
But we can't just leave Emilio.
Did you hear that guy?
Okay, before we do anything,
we have to figure out
why this is happening.
Everything was going so well.
Maybe we messed up the magic
when we were cleaning the car?
[ominous music]
[crickets chirp]
Ugh!
[ominous music]
Sam, where are you?
I'm right here.
What the hell?
Just in case.
- Have you lost your mind?
- No!
I'm being practical.
That guy sounds like
a total psycho.
What's to stop him from killing us
both after you give him the money?
Okay, just stop for one second.
You're right, Clint is a psycho,
but we have to at least try
to save Emilio.
It's my fault
he got sucked into this anyway.
And first we have to figure out
why all of this is happening.
Do you recognize this?
Yeah, it was in the car,
next to the console.
I took it out
while we were cleaning.
Do you have any idea what it is?
No.
[Jeff] It says that the statue
is the God Shani.
And Shani is the God of Karma.
Yeah, and Shani is the
most powerful of all gods
and has the power to reward
and to punish.
So, this is the reason
for everything.
It wasn't
Harry the homeless guy,
or instant karma,
or even the car.
It was Shani, the God of Karma.
[phone ringing]
[Jeff]
Maybe he got away.
Emilio?
[Clint] Emilio's a little
under the weather right now.
Clint, you better not
have done anything to him.
He has nothing to do with this.
Okay, it was a mistake,
a misunderstanding.
I'm on my way right now
to make things right.
The clock is ticking.
You have one hour left.
- I have to go.
- Let me come with you.
No.
I'm not letting you go
by yourself.
[ominous music]
Should we bring the money?
I think we should leave it
here for now.
- [ominous music]
- [garage door creaks]
Emilio!
[ominous music]
[Clint] Well, well, well.
Hello, Jeff.
You son of a bitch.
Why are you doing this?
He didn't do anything!
You're right.
But you know what?
He had to pay 10% interest
on your loan.
Which he was unwilling to do
until I applied
a little pressure.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Jeff, you stole
my fucking money!
[gasping]
Hey,
who's your little friend there?
You leave her out of this.
Then why the fuck
did you bring her?
You know what?
Don't answer that.
Glad she's here.
[Sam] Oh, no!
- No!
- [grunting]
What are you gonna do to us?
[Clint] Well, it depends.
Did you bring my money?
- Oh...
- [Jeff] No.
No?
No, we didn't bring the money.
We hid it.
So if you kill us...
you'll never find it.
- [Emilio grunts]
- [Sam] No, no!
[Jeff] Listen!
We'll trade you the money.
For our lives.
All three of us.
So you give me my money
and I let you go.
Is that right?
No.
You let us go,
and then
I'll bring you the money.
[Clint laughing]
Do you think I'm stupid?
[Jeff]
No, I don't.
But I can clearly see
that you're a tough guy,
so I'm appealing
to your sense of fair play.
Just give us a chance.
I promise,
if you let us go,
I will promise that you get
your money.
Fair play?
You want me to trust you
after you stole my money?
[laughs] Okay, sure.
Tell you what I'll do.
On one piece of paper
I'll write "Let you go."
And on the other...
"Kill you."
And you pick
which piece of paper.
That way, you decide
what I do to you.
Now choose one.
Untie me first.
Okay, but no funny business.
[snaps fingers]
All right, you...
But you have to promise
to be a man of your word.
If I choose the one
that says "Let you go,"
you have to let us go.
Oh, Jeff, I cross my heart
and hope to die.
What are you doing?
You said that you wrote
"Kill you"
and "Let you go" on the papers,
right?
Well, let's see
which one's left...
and we'll know what I chose.
You little shit!
It looks like I chose the one
that said "Let you go,"
so you have to let us go.
[Clint]
I'm not letting you go!
- Don't let them get away!
- [muffled shouting]
[Clint]
I'll be back for you later.
[engine starts]
[tires screech]
Go, go, go, go!
[dramatic music]
- [Jeff] You see 'em?
- Yes, I see them!
- They're still there.
- Shit.
[tires squeal]
[Clint] Keep close.
Step on it.
- Can we go any faster?
- I'm trying! I...
Let's go, catch up.
- You're driving like your mom!
- Oh, my God.
- I'll go up there.
- Take it. Take it, take it!
I don't even know
where this goes.
- [Sam] No, no, no, no.
- [Jeff] Shit. Uh...
- It's okay, just turn around.
- Yeah.
[Jeff] Oh, my God,
I think we lost 'em.
[Sam]
Where are they?
Oh, shit! Oh, my God!
What do we do?
- What do we do? What do we do?
- Sam, run!
[Sam grunts]
Come on.
[gunshots]
There's nowhere left to go.
That was a good one back there...
Eating the fucking paper.
I didn't see that coming.
But now your time is up.
If you both come out
with your hands up,
I might let one of you go.
Okay.
Coming out.
[Jeff]
Don't shoot.
- [grunts]
- Oh!
Where's my money?
[cocking gun] -Wait,
wait, wait, wait. Wait, wait.
Jeff, if we just... we just tell
him where it is, it'll be... it'll be...
He's gonna let us go, right?
- Right?
- Okay. [groaning]
Okay.
Okay, I'll...
- I'll tell you where it is.
- Where is it?
[groans]
It's in the car.
Let's go!
Show me!
- It's in the back of the car.
- I said let's go!
[groaning]
Here.
That wasn't so hard.
- [engine starting]
- [car door closes]
[brakes squeak]
Can you pop the trunk, please?
[trunk beeping]
You okay with this, sir?
[businessman] Yeah,
it should be fun.
[trunk beeping]
First ride share, huh?
Yes, sir.
What kind of work do you do?
I used to sell books online.
Now I sell
just about everything.
I've probably bought
something from you... before.
Let me help you
with your bag, sir.
[light music]
Here you are, sir.
[businessman] Thank you.
- [Jeff] What about this one?
- [businessman] It's not mine.
[dramatic music]
[ethereal music]