(insects buzzing)
(whooshing)
(soft, upbeat acoustic music)
- Jodi.
(bangs)
Come on, we gotta get out.
- [Jodi] Get out?
What are you doing?
(rock music)
(tires skid)
♪ Funhouse 69 ♪
♪ Taking it all ♪
- Southwell!
You're gonna die, Southwell!
You're gonna die.
(laughs)
(glass shatters)
(thugs laugh)
I'm the fire starter!
Hey, guys!
I'm gonna kill you!
- [Jodi] Oh no.
All our stuff, all our stuff.
No, no, no, no, no.
- What are you do-
Oh, your bear.
Sorry.
- Who cares about that?
All our stuff was in there.
- We'll get new stuff.
- Yeah, where are we gonna sleep?
Where are we going to live?
- I'll figure something out, all right?
- I just did the laundry.
(flames crackling)
(soft, melancholy music)
(dogs grumbling)
(dogs barking)
- Sherman, Peabody. Stop it.
(soft, melancholy music)
(dogs barking)
- [Barbara] Dearest Gordon,
it's my fifth day at sea
and I've been giving our
life together lot of thought.
For years we've been
living two separate lives.
Your depression and
hopelessness has shut me out.
Gordon, no matter how
difficult things have been,
I do miss you,
but living without love,
affection or communication
has taken its toll.
I can't do it anymore.
I would like to think you still believe
there is something worth living for,
something that would make
you want to fight, for us.
But deep down, I know it would take
an act of God to turn
this marriage around.
- Peabody, Sherman. Let's go
(dog grumbling)
Who is it for, Peabody?
- [Barbara] My cruise ship
will dock in San Diego.
If there's any chance of saving
what's left of our marriage,
I pray you'll be there.
- [Neighbor] I hope you're
going to clean that up.
(soft, melancholy music)
- Actually, I'm not.
You want to save our marriage?
I'll save our marriage.
Oh.
(sighs)
Well, I tried.
(people chattering)
(upbeat Christmas music)
- [Celeste] I just keep thinking how long
it's been since we had a real Christmas.
With a man around the house.
Oh, Jodi, honey, I have
a feeling you're really
going to like Cliff.
He's going to make a great husband,
even though he's turned your
kid brothers into army brats.
- So send me a ticket and I'll fly down.
- [Celeste] Oh yeah, so you'll...
- It's my mom, my mom.
- And by drugs
for your friends?
- Thanks, ma, I love you, too.
- [Celeste] Oh, come on.
What do you expect from me?
You run away from a good home-
- Good home?
What are you, high?
- [Celeste] Jodi.
The door's open.
You do what you want. You always have.
(line drops)
(upbeat Christmas music)
- 50 bucks?
Where did you get that?
- Donation. For abused kids.
Hey, it's Christmas, right?
(bright, upbeat Christmas music)
- All righty.
- No, that's okay. I don't have to see it.
- Okay, then.
If you just want to sign right here.
We'll have you on your way.
Now if you're interested
in a good shooting range,
there's a place just-
- It's a gift.
For myself.
- Okay, well, in that case...
(bullets rattling)
(clicking)
(softly sobbing)
(bright, upbeat music)
- Excuse me. Can you spare some change?
It's actually for a good cause, my, my...
Merry Christmas.
(people chattering)
(laughing)
(soft, upbeat Christmas music)
- It's freezing out here.
What are you doing?
- Nothing.
(sighs)
So have you figured out
where you're staying tonight?
- I don't know. Maybe the
Ramada or the Hilton. (chuckles)
- Yeah, right.
- I'm serious.
Somebody gave Cam 50 bucks.
- Seriously?
Wow.
I wonder what he had to do for it.
(sighs)
- Ho, ho, ho.
Santa's got some stuff.
(Crystal laughs)
You ready?
All right.
Lamb's wool sweater
straight from Scotland.
Heated socks, nine volt
battery included for you.
- I always wanted these.
- Yes.
Ear muffs and gloves.
Ooh, one last thing.
Close your eyes, please.
(sighs)
Okay, open 'em.
- All of that for 50 bucks?
- [Cam] Yeah.
(Jodi chuckles)
(bright, upbeat Christmas music)
(insects buzzing)
- Excuse me, mister, um...
Me and my sister have
been calling our parents
to give us a ride, but
they're not home and um,
we were wondering if maybe
you can give us a lift?
- Sorry.
- Please, mister.
It's getting late and it's cold
and we have no way to
get home, so, please?
- Well, where do you live?
- [Crystal] Just a few minutes from here.
- Well, I'm heading to Lockesburg.
- That's perfect.
- That's good.
- Well okay, but uh...
Brush off your shoes first, please.
- [Crystal] Oh, um, this is our brother.
Can you give him a ride, too, mister?
Wipe your feet off first.
(insects buzzing)
- Well, one thing, kids.
When you drive in this
car, you wear a seatbelt.
(soft, mysterious music)
Feet off the dash.
Hey.
Hey, hey.
(Cam grunts)
- Hey.
- Knock it off.
Do you have a problem?
- [Jodi] Stop.
(laughing)
- Pass it up, just give me the broom.
Give me the broom.
- [Cam] Give me the broom.
- Are you a wise guy? Give me the broom.
So uh...
Were you doing some Christmas shopping?
- No, sir.
We went to a movie.
- [Gordon] Really? Which one?
- I don't remember,
'cause we, we left early.
(laughing)
(clattering)
- All right.
Out of the car. Now!
Come on, out.
- What's with you?
- All right, let's go.
- [Jodi] Hey, stop!
- Out.
- [Jodi] Stop it, that hurts.
- [Gordon] Enough with the shenanigans.
That's it.
- Get your hands off me.
Look, we didn't do anything.
- Get out, out of the car.
- [Jodi] Stop it, let go of me.
- [Crystal] Listen,
you're really hurting her.
- [Jodi] Come on, stop!
(tires skid)
(insects buzzing)
- I don't believe this.
- Stupid idiot, what are you doing?
- Watch it, I'm trying to drive.
- [Jodi] Cam, I am not kidding.
You gotta turn this car around right now.
(Crystal grunts)
(Cam laughs)
- Sit back and put your seat belt on.
- Oh great.
(tires skid)
(insects buzzing)
(tense music)
(tense, dramatic music)
Hey.
- [Jodi] I can't believe this.
Cam.
- Come on.
We were just kidding around.
- [Jodi] Hey, don't hurt him, okay, Cam?
- [Cam] Just get back
in the car, all right?
- [Crystal] Don't listen to her.
- [Cam] Come on!
- [Jodi] Cam? Hey!
Cam, what did I say?
- Wow, it's freezing.
- [Gordon] Can I say something?
You kids are making a big mistake.
(rock music)
- [Crystal] 12 bucks? That's it?
- That's a short trip in this gas duster.
And I bet you use super, don't you?
- Where's the rest of your money?
- Hey, will you cut it out?
This is stupid. I don't want
to do this anymore, Cam.
- You started it.
I didn't hit him in the
head with any goobers.
- That was just having fun.
- [Crystal] Well so is this so chill out.
♪ If the truth be known ♪
♪ Truth is more than to each his own ♪
♪ There'll be more to answer for ♪
♪ Everybody gets a shot ♪
♪ It'll cost you everything you got ♪
Here's his credit card.
- Don't you try nothin'.
- He won't.
(Gordon coughing)
- Ow, ow, ow, ow.
(Gordon groans)
- [Crystal] Are you hard of hearing?
- [Gordon] Ow.
- Because you will be.
Mrs. Forrester used to
do that to us. (chuckles)
Works pretty good, too. (chuckles)
- We are mobile.
(car starts up)
One thing, kids.
When you ride in this
car, you wear a seatbelt.
(electronic rock music)
(laughing)
Woo!
(electronic rock music)
♪ I thought distinctly ♪
♪ Different than now ♪
♪ Wonder dramatically ♪
♪ All about everything always ♪
♪ Jump over on ♪
♪ Everybody now ♪
♪ And drive over in ♪
♪ Come on, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause it's just not enough yeah ♪
♪ To stand at the edge ♪
♪ You gotta dive over in ♪
♪ Jump over on ♪
♪ Everybody now ♪
♪ Dive over in ♪
♪ Come on yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause it's just not enough, yeah ♪
♪ To stand at the edge ♪
♪ You gotta dive over the edge ♪
(laughing)
- Hey!
Careful.
- Here.
(Cam burps)
- That really hit the spot.
You guys want to do anything else tonight?
- Not me.
Thanks, mister.
- So Jode, I guess you figured out
where you're staying tonight, huh?
- There's always the bus station.
- I think I got a better idea.
We got a car, right?
I don't know, why don't
we like head down south,
all the way to Mexico.
Get some sun, get out
of this freezing cold.
What do you think?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm all for that.
What?
Ah, come on, your mom
lives down south, right?
Arizona.
- Yeah, that's right.
And you know what? You could
even be there by Christmas.
- Nah, I don't wanna.
- Okay.
You think you can give us a ride downtown?
(hits)
What was that for?
- "You think you can
give us a ride downtown?"
- What?
We just stole this guy's
car with him in it.
What do you think?
He's just going to go
home and go to sleep?
We have a serious problem, Cam.
- That's right.
That's right.
And it's going to get worse if you don't
give me those keys right now!
- Do it, Cam.
(keys rattling)
- All right, I don't want
any hassles, all right?
- No, give me the keys!
- [Jodi] Crystal.
- Ow, ow!
- Hey!
- Ow!
- Stop it.
- Hey, leave her alone!
- [Cam] Knock it off.
- It hurts.
- Don't hurt her.
- Get off of me!
- Come on,
you're hurting her.
(grunting)
You're out of control.
Fucking psycho.
- Oh great.
Can somebody get me a tissue?
(Crystal sniffles)
- He took the tray.
Check the glove compartment.
All right, Santa.
- [Biker] Hey!
Get back here, old man!
I'm gonna kill you.
(Gordon grunting)
(gun cocks)
- Down, boy.
(tense music)
- [Jodi] Arizona by Christmas.
Right?
(dogs barking)
- Is everything fine over here?
(gun clicks)
More coffee, sir?
(hits)
(waitress gasps)
Looks like somebody woke up
on the wrong side of the bed today.
- All right, you can have the car.
Just let me go.
- Can't do it, Fish-Man.
- Why is that?
- 'Cause I need you to
sign the credit card
in places like this.
- I'll give you the
credit card. You sign it.
(Cam laughs)
- Right, that'll work real good.
Card member since 1982,
when I was freaking born.
- Don't you want to eat something?
You should really eat something.
- [Celeste] Well, isn't that a kick?
To have my baby home again,
and just in time for Christmas.
Your kid brothers will be thrilled.
I hope you're not bringing
any of your friends.
- What? Ruin their Christmas?
I was just kidding, ma.
- [Celeste] Well, I hope so,
because that was pretty mean, Jodi.
I want you to come home, honey.
I can't tell you how much I miss you.
And hey...
- [Cam] Come on, Jodi. We're gotta go.
- [Celeste] Wait till
you see our new house.
- Ma, I got to hang up now,
but I love you and I'm coming home.
- I love you.
- Bye.
(upbeat music)
(dog grunting)
(window shatters)
(dog barks)
- Oh my goodness.
Oh.
Oh! You naughty dogs.
You...
Shoo, shoo.
(dog barking)
Mr. T!
(dogs barking)
(upbeat pop rock music)
♪ 14 kids in an old church van ♪
♪ With a light in their eyes ♪
♪ And some tracts in their hands ♪
♪ 60 miles an hour feels way too slow ♪
♪ When you got the Chevy
pointed down to Mexico ♪
♪ We all want to run ♪
♪ The race to win ♪
♪ Never more giving up or giving in ♪
♪ Coming at you like a blitz ♪
(car honks)
♪ Like a blitz ♪
♪ They've had three flats
and the radiator's leaking ♪
♪ Ain't nothing gonna keep 'em ♪
♪ From the prize that they're seeking ♪
♪ They're riding all together
and it's in God's hands ♪
- I gotta take a whiz myself.
How about you Fish-Man?
- No, but I could use Bromo.
- A Bromo?
What's that?
- Just ask the clerk.
- Keep an eye on him, all right?
Here.
- Forget it.
- No, just take it, and be careful with it
because I loaded it again.
- Wait.
You know, I also could use a toothbrush.
Medium bristle.
I mean, don't get me the
firm, and some toothpaste.
Colgate.
Not the gel.
The original.
- Anything else?
Six pack of prune juice maybe?
I don't know, a box of adult diapers?
(Jodi laughs)
- Man, he's so immature.
You think so?
- Do I think so what?
- That your young friend is immature?
- I don't know.
- Well, it just seems that
you're more reasonable
than your friends.
You're smarter.
- Everyone's smarter than Cam.
- Is he the one that broke your arm?
- Um, no.
No, that, that was some jerk
who thought he was my boyfriend,
you know, with all the privileges.
Cam was the one who chased him off.
Okay.
Go.
- What?
- Go on, get outta here.
What are you doing?
- I need the gun. Give me the gun.
- Are you mental? Get out of here.
- I'm not leaving you kids
with a gun. Give it to me.
- [Cam] Woo hoo hoo!
You're not gonna believe what I got.
(Jodi sighs)
- You're not too swift, are you?
- Woodstock, man.
Only 99 cents in The Dead, Fish-Man.
The Dead rule.
And...
They even gave me these for free.
It just might be Christmas after all.
(tense, strange music)
- [Man] This is one thing that I was going
to wait a while before we talked about,
but maybe we'll talk about it now
so you can think about it because you all,
we all have to make some
kind of plans for ourselves.
It's a free concert from now on.
(audience cheers)
(rock music)
One major thing you
have to remember tonight
when you go back up in
the woods to go to sleep
or if you stay here,
is that the man next
to you is your brother
and you damn well better
treat each other that way
because if you don't, then
we blow the whole thing,
but we've got it right there.
(bass guitar strumming)
(electronic rock music)
(Crystal laughs)
(laughing)
- [Crystal] Stop, Cam. (laughs)
- What?
I thought we were going to party.
- No way.
- Oh, come on.
(Jodi laughs)
- [Jodi] No.
- Come on.
- Get off of me.
(laughing)
- You know, I'm just trying
to have a little bit of fun.
- Just stay away.
(Cam scoffs)
- Where am I supposed to sleep?
- That's your bed.
- With Fish-Man.
He's a little more your speed.
(Jodi laughs)
(television blaring)
(Jodi grunts)
- Cut it out, idiot.
(Cam chuckles)
(chuckles)
(Gordon grunts)
- What the?
- Sorry.
- What's wrong with you.
- Okay. I said I'm sorry.
- Oh.
Ah.
Oh.
(Jodi gasps)
- Oh my.
Get some water!
Get water.
Oh, god.
(splashing)
- I got it.
I got it, I got it, I got it. Don't worry.
(splashing)
- God, I can't believe you.
That's it. I'm outta here.
- Oh.
- Jodi, come on, what are you doin'?
- I hate him.
I hate him.
- Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
All right? I'm sorry.
- You're always saying you're sorry.
This time it's not enough.
Get out of my way.
- What? It was a joke.
It was funny. I was
kidding, right, Fish-Man?
Tell her.
- Sorry for all the trouble
we caused you, mister.
Really.
You're a nice man. You don't deserve this.
- [Cam] No, come on, please.
- Cam, get out of my way.
- Please, please.
(Cam sighs)
What's that all about?
- 'Cause you're a moron.
- You're not going to
leave me here, are you?
- Just chill out.
Do me a favor?
Try not to set the whole place on fire.
(television blaring)
(insects buzzing)
(cars passing in the distance)
♪ On something you can't find ♪
♪ So tell me how do I wrap
my heart up for Christmas ♪
♪ I wanna give it to you ♪
♪ Pretty bows and ribbons ♪
♪ Won't fit the gift I'm givin' ♪
♪ Your loving arms will have to do ♪
♪ At first I thought of giving you ♪
- Jode, you have to come back.
- [Jodi] Not with Cam.
- Okay.
What about me?
I mean, you can't just forget
about your friends, you know?
We have to stick together.
- I don't know who my friends are anymore.
- Right.
Forget about Cam and all the
times he watched out for you.
I mean, you're right.
You got your family now.
What do you need us for?
- Come on, Crystal.
- I don't know why I ever
thought you were any different.
Everybody just uses everybody else.
That's the way it works.
And if I don't know that
by now, then joke's on me.
- Well what do you want me to do?
- Without you and me to
keep Cam out of trouble,
the cops would pick them up in a second.
They will.
And you know what that means?
It means we're next.
I mean, where do you
want to spend Christmas?
At home or in jail?
- What about Gordon?
(Crystal laughs)
- Are you kidding?
He's our main man.
Give me one sec, okay?
- Something special I can do you for?
- Well I saw you selling to that guy
and I thought maybe we can make a trade?
You do trade, don't you?
- I think we can probably
arrange something.
- There's one problem.
My friend, she's a little shy,
so maybe you could talk to her
while I make myself
comfortable in your rig.
(man chuckles)
- Well, it's that one right there.
(tense, strange music)
- It's gotta be here, come on.
Where is it?
(tense, strange music)
- Don't get mad at me.
It was your friend's idea.
- You're lying. Where is she?
- She's in my rig, behind those trucks.
(tense, strange music)
- Crystal?
What are you doing?
Get out of there, he's coming.
- [Crystal] Just stall
him, I'm almost done, okay?
- All right, little lady.
Up you go.
(chickens clucking)
Well.
See you found the little hen house.
Big cock'll walk.
(mimics chicken)
(laughs)
All right.
That's the way you wanna play it.
- Get ready to run.
(chickens clucking)
- Woo hoo hoo hoo!
(Crystal grunts)
- [Crystal] Now!
(chickens clucking)
(tense, dramatic music)
- [Jodi] Cam!
Cam!
(tense music)
- [Cam] Don't move.
(chickens clucking)
- [Crystal] Stop it.
(Crystal grunts)
(hits)
(Crystal sobs)
- [Jodi] Did you kill him?
- No.
He was still breathing.
Head wounds bleed a lot, you know.
- Ow.
Bunion. (sighs)
(Crystal sobbing)
- [Detective] How do you spell that?
- [Man] T-R-O-U-T.
- Like the fish?
Well...
The first thing that we have to establish
is if in fact he's really missing.
I mean, how do we know he's
not over at a friend's house?
- What friends?
- My father rarely leaves the house.
Besides, look at this.
He's been gone for three days now.
- Well, this doesn't
necessarily mean anything.
I mean, he could have got
tired of your mother's cooking.
Any marital problems?
- Not that I know of.
- Excuse me?
- He wasn't happy about her going off
on a cruise by herself.
(woman gasps)
What?
What else do you want me to say?
- My father-in-law
tried to commit suicide-
- That was 15 years ago.
- Well, excuse me, Donald,
but isn't that the
reason we're so worried?
- His business failed, his partner,
his best friend in the world
screwed him up the wazoo.
- All right. I get the picture.
Depression, the holidays, weather.
Willis, check the hospitals.
(train horn blares)
♪ Driving that train ♪
♪ High on cocaine ♪
♪ Casey Jones you better ♪
♪ Watch your speed ♪
♪ Trouble ahead ♪
♪ Trouble behind ♪
♪ And you know that notion ♪
♪ Just crossed my mind ♪
(Cam laughs)
- That's my name.
Cameron Casey Jones Southwell.
It's my dad's name, too.
You know, he was an
engineer, at Central Pacific
before he got busted.
Yeah.
Garcia wrote that song for him.
He and my dad were like
real tight, you know?
And you see this?
Garcia gave it to him.
(Crystal scoffs)
- [Crystal] Bull.
- What?
- You heard me.
- Hey.
Hey.
My dad doesn't make stuff up, all right?
- Yeah, right, that's
why he's in the state pen
because he's so pure and honest.
- Hey Fish-Man, take the wheel.
- What?
- You heard me.
Take the wheel. I don't feel
like driving anymore, man.
- Whoa.
(Cam laughs)
- All right, all right.
Now we're talkin'.
Let's have a little but of fun.
Lay on the horn.
- What?
- I want you to lay on the horn.
(horn beeps)
Oh, please.
You can do better than
that. Lay on the horn!
Lay on it. Train men love that, man.
Lay on the horn.
(horn blares)
All right!
Woo!
(train horn blares)
All right!
(tires skid)
(Crystal and Jodi laughing)
- That was so...
You are too much, Fish-Man.
- Yeah, I mean, really.
It was an accident.
There was a, there was a, a pot hole.
(Crystal laughs)
Yeah, I mean really.
There was a huge pot hole.
(police sirens wailing)
♪ Trouble ahead, oh ♪
♪ Trouble behind ♪
♪ And you know that notion ♪
♪ Just crossed my mind ♪
(police radio chatter)
- [Cam] Give him his wallet.
- Can I see your driver's
license and registration, please?
(police radio chatter)
Take it out of the wallet.
Thank you.
You kids okay?
- Yeah.
- Officer, aren't you going to ask me
to step out of the car?
- What for? You drunk?
- You're not going to arrest
our grandfather, are you?
'Cause he doesn't always drive this fast.
- No, I uh, I slow down to
85 when I'm in a school zone.
- Okay. Mr. Trout. Let
me smell your breath.
- Don't I walk a straight line?
- Come on.
(Gordon blows)
No.
You're not drunk.
Sign here.
(police radio chatter)
Now because you're from out of state,
you're going to have to show
up in court tomorrow morning.
- Officer, wait.
Where do we show up tomorrow?
- It's on the citation.
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
- [Cam] And a happy new year.
- Bye.
- Yeah, thanks.
- [Cam] That was close.
- You can say that again.
(Cam laughs)
- You're a wise guy,
aren't you? (chuckles)
(soft, tinkling Christmas music)
(Cam snoring)
(soft Christmas music)
- I can't believe this is happening.
I was just robbed last week.
- I told you you're not being held up.
I just need to use the phone.
- Right.
Just over here.
- Quick, dial 911.
- What?
- I'm kidnapped.
My name is Gordon Trout.
Do it.
- Grandpa.
- These are my kidnappers.
- Grandpa, what are you doing?
Please don't tell me that
you're calling the police again.
- He always does this.
- Stay away. I'm warning you.
- Grandpa, come on.
You're scaring us.
- The Res-Wel Motel.
Guy here claims he's being kidnapped.
- I am being kidnapped.
- All I know is he's got a gun
and he's pointing at two kids.
Now hurry.
- Why did you say that?
Where's Cam?
Nobody's going to hurt you, grandpa.
- Enough with the grandpa bit.
Don't move.
- [Employee] Okay, fella.
Drop it.
- You heard the man. Do what he says.
- Not him, you. You, old guy.
- What? What?
Now wait, wait a minute.
You've got it all wrong.
I'm the victim here.
- We'll let the police decide that.
Now drop it!
(gun thuds)
(Cam clicks tongue)
(employee sighs)
(gun cocks)
- All right, drop it.
- Hey, what are you doing, kid?
- What does it look like I'm doin'?
Me and grandpa here were having our way
with these fine young poodles.
Now, unless you want
to get into a contest,
drop the gun and get out of here.
I said drop the gun!
- Okay.
All right.
- I told you.
- [Crystal] The cops are on their way.
- Come on! Let's go!
- No!
It's over.
This whole cockamamie charade is over.
Finished.
- Really?
All right, come on, come on.
- Go ahead.
Do it.
- Cut it out.
- What's the matter? No guts?
- Cam, don't.
- I'm trying.
- Come on.
What do you think I bought this gun for?
Come on, take your best shot.
Punk!
- No.
Do something!
(hits)
(Gordon grunts)
(Gordon thuds)
♪ Papa I think I messed up again ♪
♪ Was it something I did ♪
♪ Was it something I said ♪
(hits)
- Hey!
Cut it out!
- You're driving too fast.
And you, I'm not gonna say it again.
- Stop it!
- Feet off the dash.
- You're hurting me.
- You touch her again, I swear to God-
- What?
- No you don't have it.
No you don't.
(slaps)
(Cam grunts)
- Are you deaf?
- Ow!
- I said slow down.
- [Crystal] Ow!
♪ That it's time to get
down on my knees and pray ♪
♪ Lord undo me ♪
- No, come on.
Get out of the car.
Get out of the car!
You wanna kill yourself,
you go right ahead.
♪ This spirit through me ♪
♪ Lord ♪
- [Jodi] You need to eat.
♪ Undo me ♪
♪ But I never meant to hurt you ♪
I'm not feeling so good.
What if he really does it?
- [Crystal] Don't talk about it.
- Yeah.
We saved that guy and his
bunions too many times.
It's what he wanted anyway.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- Maybe we should go back.
- Are you nuts?
No way.
(wind blowing)
(laughing)
(body thuds)
(soft orchestral music)
- [Man] Morning.
(upbeat pop rock music)
- What is this?
Where am I?
- You're on God's good earth.
Fresno, California.
- Did I have a heart attack?
- No.
Just shorted out from exhaustion.
Wife's a nurse.
- Oh.
What kind of a place is this?
- Look up there.
See anything?
- A ceiling painted with clouds.
- That all?
Scoot over.
Don't worry. I'm a minister.
Eddie Corbett at your service.
Go on. Give it a try.
- Frosty the Snowman, I don't know.
(Eddie chuckles)
- You see the chin?
The line in the nose.
The eyes.
Right there.
Pure Odalis.
Just goes to show things
aren't always what they seem.
Here you go.
Eat up.
We'll have you back on
your feet in no time.
- How did I...
(soft, midtempo music)
- Kinda bored.
(sizzling)
- Ow!
Freak!
- [Cam] Ouch.
- [Eddie] You forget how
to tie your shoes, kid?
- No, no, no, no, hey,
hey, whoa, I'm fine.
Hallelujah.
- So let's talk about Mr. Fish.
Who wants to tell me what happened?
Cameron?
Come on, big man.
Tell me what it's like to be
taken away from your life,
your home, your loved ones.
- We messed up.
- That's right.
You messed up.
What do you have to add to that, Crystal?
- He was asking for it.
- If you hurt somebody else,
does that make you feel
better about yourself?
Look at me.
You can stop this.
You can change this
self-destructive path you're on.
You don't think you have it
in you, but I know you do.
So what about you, Jodi?
You know you did wrong, don't you?
There you go.
(sizzling)
Ow!
(Eddie grunts)
(Cam laughing)
Now just remember, what
goes around comes around.
- [Employee] Res-Wel Motel.
Yeah, a guy here claims
he being kidnapped.
- [Gordon] I am being kidnapped.
- [Employee] Now hurry.
(banging)
- [Gordon] Now why did you say that?
- Well, that's it.
- I don't understand.
What was that?
- I take it those weren't
his grandchildren?
- Of course not.
Clearly he was in fear for his life.
- This is a registration for a hand gun
purchased December 2nd by your father.
Same gun you saw him
holding on those girls.
- So just what exactly
are you trying to say?
- He probably was kidnapped.
- Probably? What else could it be?
- Well, there is some confusion.
Your father was stopped in Southern Oregon
and there were three very
nervous minors in the car.
- Oh my god.
- Now we're running a
check on them right now.
In the meantime, we're
not ruling anything out.
Well I guess we can rule out suicide.
Anyway, I'll be in touch.
You know, I wasn't gonna
to say anything about this,
but the guy who shot this
said that he wants $5,000
or he's going to sell
it to Primetime Crime.
- What?
- I think it's just a bluff.
I mean, what would Primetime
Crime want with this?
(soft, midtempo music)
♪ Hope and prayin' ♪
♪ I've been waitin' ♪
♪ Everybody needs somebody to love ♪
♪ There's no question ♪
♪ Straight from heaven ♪
♪ You're my angel ♪
- Hello?
Hello? Anybody around?
Mr. Corbett?
- You can call me Eddie, Mr. Fish.
- You can call me Mr. Trout.
- Hey, I was close.
You want to go for a walk?
It might do you some good.
- Well I was trying to use the telephone
but I couldn't find one
anywhere in the house.
I must've left my cell phone
up where I was chopping wood.
Come on. I'll take you to it.
I spent most of my youth
getting in and out of trouble.
Followed it up with 36
years of serious drifting.
And then bam, I was convicted by the Lord.
I've only been a full senior
pastor for about a year.
Proof that it's never too late to change.
- Where is this phone?
- We're almost there.
You holding up okay?
- Yeah, yeah. I just
have to call the police.
- There it is.
(Jodi and Crystal chuckle)
- There's something you
don't see these days.
Straight out of Norman Rockwell.
Just kids being kids.
(laughing)
- [Cam] Push me higher!
- It's them.
They're the ones who kidnapped me.
Give me the phone. Quick.
- You mean Crystal and Cam and Jodi?
- You know them?
Do you have any idea what they did to me?
- Well yeah.
I think it's great you're
sticking with them.
- I'm not sticking with them.
Did they tell you that?
How do you work this cockamamie thing?
- Push send.
- [Cam] Higher!
- Gordon.
(Cam thuds)
If there's one thing these
kids need, it's consistency.
God knows they didn't get it at home.
- How would you know?
- I ran a halfway house
for runaways up in Seattle,
right after I got out of seminary.
- [Gordon] Well I can't
vouch for your work, Eddie.
- They could have left you up
on that mountain top to die.
That kid, Cam?
He gave you mouth-to-mouth resuscitation.
You didn't need it, but
he didn't know that.
- What's wrong with this thing?
I can't get through to 911.
- Call the operator. They'll connect you.
I don't know, maybe you're right.
Maybe they would be better off in jail.
Tried as adults, put in
with hardened criminals.
Can't be any worse than
what they grew up in.
Crystal learned the meaning of hot
when her mother burned
her with cigarettes.
- [Operator] Hello, this is the operator.
How may I help you?
- Hello. Uh, yes.
Could you please connect
me to the local police?
This is an emergency.
- Look.
Those kids did a terrible
thing kidnapping you,
but they're young and they can change.
They're at a critical point now.
So I'm asking you, Gordon.
I'll beg you if I have to.
I want just one adult besides myself
giving these kids another chance.
I'm finished.
- [Man] Fresno Police, please hold.
- [Eddie] It's up to you and God now.
- [Man] Fresno Police
Department, may I help you?
Hello?
- Hello.
Yes. I'd like to...
Nevermind.
(Eddie sighs)
How do you hang up this thing?
- God bless you, Gordon.
Where would any of us be
without a second chance?
- [Cam] Hey, Fish-Man, back from the dead!
- [Crystal] Fish-man,
Fish-man, he's our man.
If he can't do it, no one can!
- Gordon!
Where are you going?
- Listen.
I know you're anxious to get going,
but how'd you like to join me for a soak
in my healing waters?
- Thank you,
but I really must get home.
I must.
- [Eddie] Well your car's in
the driveway behind the garage.
It's been a pleasure.
- Hi.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
- Yes I am.
- I bought you this.
It's kind of a get well present.
- It's not necessary.
- Bottle of aspirin, extra strength,
Dr. Scholl's bunion pads,
tube of Colgate, and a toothbrush.
Medium bristle, not firm.
- No Bromo?
I am dying to brush my teeth.
(brushing)
Blegh.
- She's a good one.
- [Gordon] Well she's a lot
different than the other two,
I'll give you that.
- This reunion with her mother...
I pray that it's going to work out.
But I got to tell you,
I have serious doubts.
She's just not going to
make it on the street.
If it wasn't for Cam looking after her,
God knows what would've happened.
Something's bothering me, brother.
Why were you kidnapped?
- What?
- Have you thought about that?
I mean, in the deeper sense.
- What are you talking about?
- Bear with me here a moment,
'cause I've been giving
this some serious thought.
Now I don't know what's
been going on in your life,
but it's my belief that somehow,
some way God came through for you.
It's something to think about.
- You're some operator, you know that?
But you're wasting your time.
I'm not about to be baptized
here in your hot tub.
(Cam yells)
(splashing)
I think you better let him up.
(Cam gasps)
- Sorry, kid, I scare ya?
(splashing)
Good.
Just a little private matter.
He reminds me of me at his age.
- I can see that.
I don't know which one of you is worse.
(Cam gasping)
(Cam laughs)
- It's a long haul, Fish-Man,
so I thought you could
use some driving music.
- What about my credit cards?
- [Jodi] Hey, wait, wait.
You didn't sign my cast.
(smacks)
(Crystal chuckles)
- Sorry.
I guess you weren't such a dud after all.
- Thanks again, Gordon.
You sure you don't want to trade?
This baby would make a terrific
prize for the church raffle.
- I don't think so.
(soft music)
(police siren wailing)
- [Officer 1] Three kids, right?
(police radio chatter)
I don't see 'em.
- [Officer 2] They're probably
armed. Watch yourself.
Okay, check the floor.
- [Officer 1] They're not in here.
- All right, you can
put your hands down now.
You want to open the trunk, please?
- Can I ask you what you're looking for?
I'm on my way back to Seattle.
I've got a long trip ahead of me.
- All right. Where'd the kids go?
- Well they're not in there.
- Where are they?
- I've decided not to press charges.
- Let me explain something
to you. Mr. Trout.
Interstate kidnapping
is a serious offense.
Now just because you've decided
you don't want to press charges,
that doesn't mean a crime
hasn't been committed.
Now you're going to have
to come down to the station
and answer some questions.
- How long is this going to take?
- You want to ride with us or
do you want to follow behind?
(soft, tense music)
(police radio chatter)
(train track bell ringing)
(train horn blares)
(soft, mysterious music)
- [Gordon] Changed my mind.
- You want to be baptized?
- I want to trade. My Cadi for your truck.
But it's got to run.
- [Eddie] It runs all right,
but it's still not an even trade.
(soft, upbeat music)
- [Gordon] Now, let's
say we get this started.
Get Jodi by Christmas.
- [Jodi] Thanks.
♪ All I know is there is a piece to find ♪
♪ Can I fight the fear ♪
♪ Can I find a way to fly, yeah ♪
♪ And be free to hope
just a little taller ♪
♪ Free to hope just a little more ♪
♪ Free to fly so much higher ♪
♪ Than I ever thought I could before ♪
♪ Free to laugh just a little longer ♪
♪ Free to love like you want me to, Lord ♪
♪ Take me to that place ♪
♪ Where I'm free to be free ♪
(bright, upbeat Christmas music)
- Your little brothers are
gonna flip over these guys.
(Gordon laughs)
- Can you give me the paper
with the shiny gold trim?
They're for my mom.
- [Employee] Certainly.
- I'd like to have this
engraved, if I could.
- [Employee] Of course.
- And uh, this is for everything.
(bright, upbeat Christmas music)
- [Photographer] Okay,
everyone, and smile.
Great. One more.
♪ Dashing through the snow ♪
♪ On a one horse open sleigh ♪
♪ O'er the fields we go ♪
♪ Laughing all the way, ha ha ha ♪
- Donald, I'm fine.
The reason I'm calling is to
tell you that I'm all right.
- [Donald] But dad, you're
wanted by the police.
They said to me-
- I don't care what
they said to you.
- [Donald] You ran away from them?
- Does your mother know?
- She called here when you didn't
show up in Puerto Vallarta.
She's cutting her trip short.
She'll be docking in
San Diego on the 26th.
- [Gordon] San Diego?
- You're putting your mother in danger.
- [Gordon] Hold it, one second.
- Dad?
- Is that the 26th?
- Yeah.
- At what time?
- I don't know. Morning.
Look, where are you?
- [Gordon] I don't wanna tell you.
- But...
What do you mean you
don't want to tell me?
- [Gordon] I've gotta
go. The kids need me.
- What?
You're still with them?
Uh, listen, you're not
suffering from that, uh,
Patty Hearst syndrome, are you?
You know, identifying
with your kidnappers?
- [Gordon] Stop that.
They're just kids.
- Come on, dad. You can't believe that.
This girl is wanted for prostitution.
She cut up her foster father
the day you were kidnapped.
And the boy's got a rap
sheet you can't believe.
- Donald, son...
- If they're caught, they're going back
to juvenile hall or worse.
You can bet on that.
- Donald.
- And then-
- Do I tell you
I love you enough?
- [Donald] What?
Dad? Dad?
(phone thuds)
Dad?
(sawing)
(air dryer whirring)
(knocking)
- What?
- [Gordon] Crystal, what are
you doin' in the men's room?
(sawing)
- Come to the party.
- What do you think you're doing?
- It's okay.
I asked him.
I can't go home with a cast on my arm.
- Here, take this.
Give me the saw.
- Cool, snacks.
- Hold very still.
(sawing)
(gentle music)
- 12412.
Okay, 12418.
This is good, you can let me out here.
(gentle music)
- Now remember we'll be at the
Quality Court till tomorrow.
Room 420. Just in case you want
to reach us for any reason.
- She won't need to.
We're going to miss you.
You kept us, ah, well, you
tried to keep us honest.
We'll send you a pinata from Mexico, okay?
- Thanks.
Bye, Cam.
- Yeah.
Take it easy.
- Don't I get a kiss?
- Yeah.
(kisses)
(gentle music)
- I'm sorry for what we did.
But I'm sorta not, you know?
(gentle music)
- [Boy] She's here!
(boys chattering)
- [Celeste] Let me look at you.
- [Cliff] You outdid
yourself this time, Celeste.
- Thank you.
- Mom, it was fantastic.
- And you never told me your
daughter was such a looker.
- Well, of course she's a looker.
I mean, after all, she
takes after her mama.
(kissing)
(laughing)
You tired?
- No.
- How about a now?
I gotta get goin'.
Come on, Jenny, get your sweater, sweetie.
- What do you mean?
- I told you, Jenny and I are going
to her mom's for Christmas Eve.
Get your coat. Come on, Jenny.
- No, Jenny, wait a minute.
You didn't tell me that.
This is the first time
I've heard about it.
- What did I tell you
at the base? Remember?
After the party, I said that we're going
to come back here and have
dinner with your daughter
and then I was going to take Jenny,
I was going to take Jenny
over to her mother's for Christmas Eve.
I told you.
- No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, please.
No, it's too much for me.
Um, look, my daughter is home.
I have not seen her for almost a year.
You're not just gonna walk out like this.
- Listen, Jodi and I
will have plenty of time
to get to know each other, right?
Huh?
- Well, here's your
jacket and I'm wearing it,
so you can't go.
Cold in here without you. Don't go away.
- Come on.
- No.
- Come on, baby.
- Come on, please.
Just stay.
- Give me my-
- [Celeste] Just stay with me.
- [Cliff] Just give me the coat.
- I'm not giving you the
coat. I want you to stay.
Please.
- Give me the coat.
- No!
- Now, Celeste.
Don't act like this in front
of your daughter, okay?
- I'm sorry.
- Now come on.
- Come on. Jenny.
- Look.
Please-
- March.
- Grab your sweater, Jenny.
- Just tell me when
you're gonna come back.
When can I expect you back?
When are you coming back?
Just...
- Don't push me, Celeste.
- I'm not pushing you.
I just wanna know when you're
gonna come back, just...
- Mom?
Mom, did you see what I
got you for Christmas?
You want to open it now?
- No, I don't want, no.
I don't wanna open anything.
Just leave me alone.
Just leave okay?
Look, I just want a drink, that's all.
You know what I mean.
Don't bug me when I'm drinking.
I've told you that.
- You know, she might not take me back.
It might be too late.
But I'm going to be there.
And the moment she walks off that boat,
the first thing she's going to see is me.
(Gordon laughs)
- That is so rad, Fish-Man.
- Yeah.
- That's awesome.
- So, what are your plans?
- We're going to Mexico to enjoy
a lovely burrito by the water.
- Burritos rock.
(Crystal laughs)
- That's not a plan.
- Yeah? What do you
know about it, Fish-Man?
- Nothing, but running
away from your problems
doesn't solve anything.
That much I do know.
- You know, Fish-Man,
you might want to leave
the preaching up to the preacher man.
You kind of stink at it.
(Gordon laughs)
- Yeah, I suppose I do.
(laughing)
- [Crystal] Yep.
- Waiter.
Sir.
I think there's a mistake here.
Shouldn't that be 47?
- Mm-hm.
That is a seven.
- Oh.
Sorry.
Thank you.
- [Waiter] You're gonna need bifocals.
- [Crystal] Wow.
- Man. (scoffs)
I thought only I got treated like that.
- Well...
- No, I got it.
I got it.
No, I got it.
See, the guy is wrong.
It's not seven.
It's ate.
- Crystal.
(laughing)
Uh oh.
- Come on,
let's get out of here.
- Uh oh.
- Come on.
Let's go.
(laughing)
- Mom?
Mom, are you all right?
- Just, just close the door.
I want you out.
Tonight.
- What did...
What did I do?
- You think I didn't see
what you were up to tonight?
You think I didn't see the looks
you were giving to my fiance?
- Mom?
What are you talking about?
- Don't act stupid with me, Jodi.
- I know you.
And you're not going to pull any
of your dirty little tricks on Cliff
the way you did with Jack.
- My stepfather raped me and you know it.
- Shut up.
I don't want to hear that!
You're a liar and you're
not going to drive
another husband out of my life!
- I need you, mom.
I spent eight months on the
street and I am not going back.
- That was your choice.
- This is my home, too.
- No.
It isn't your home.
It's my home.
So get out.
Get out now.
Get out!
Get out now!
Just get out!
Get out!
Get out.
(glass shatters)
(insects buzzing)
(train horn blares)
- Woo!
(tracks rattling)
- You think he's safe?
I mean a gust of wind could,
could suck him under or something.
(Crystal laughs)
- [Cam] Woo!
- He'll be fine.
(Cam laughs)
I don't know, Jodi said that he didn't
even know his father, but,
supposedly he sent him a toy
train for Christmas once.
Pathetic, isn't it?
- Woo!
(train tracks rattling)
- And then when his father dies,
James Stewart inherits
his savings and loan
and then it runs into financial problems
and then see, the banker is played
by Lionel Barrymore and
he's a mean guy and anyway,
he won't lend him the
money and then he gets
into all kinds of trouble.
And then when he, when he says
I wish I was dead, then
the angel says to him
okay, I'm going to show
you what it will be like
if you were never born.
So then he takes him out and then uh,
and if he was never born,
then he wouldn't have a wife
and he wouldn't have, you
know, any relatives or any,
any friends in the town
and he can't understand it.
And he goes through this emotional thing
and he winds up on the top of a bridge
and he's about to jump off.
And, and it's, I shouldn't tell you
too much about it though,
because I'm ruining it for you, you know?
Well anyway.
I can't believe you haven't seen it.
It's on every year.
- Do you have any quarters?
- Quarters?
Yeah.
(change rattling)
- Thanks.
(Crystal laughs)
- I don't know, you'll
probably think it's dated
but Donna Reed, I was
in love with Donna Reed.
- [Crystal] Jodi?
Jodi, what are you doing here?
- [Gordon] Jodi.
(soft music)
- I, I thought I'd stop
by and surprise you.
The manager let me in
- What happened?
- What did she do?
- It's not worth talking about, so,
what are you guys up to?
(melancholy music)
- I'm so sorry.
What can I do?
- Jodi, what's going on?
What did you do?
(melancholy music)
- This girl has taken
an overdose of pills.
Her pulse rate is way down.
- Someone will be right up to take her in.
Meanwhile, I can start
filling out these forms.
Um, her name?
(tense music)
Sir, are you a relative?
We're going to need a parent
or guardian's consent.
- I'm her grandfather.
Shoved in line ahead of me, Jodi.
Should have been me lying there, not you.
Last thing I expected is to be
woken up by some crazy kids.
I just wish I could take it all away.
Of all people, I should know
the right things to say, but,
I never was very good with words.
Hey.
We were one crazy family
though, weren't me?
(Gordon sniffles)
(melancholy music)
You're a good kid, Jodi.
Don't let anyone ever
tell you that you're not.
I have to go.
But I'll be back in a few days.
That's a promise.
Okay, you guys...
- She's going to be all right.
We should get going.
You coming or not?
- Who's going to stay with her?
- Fish-Man.
I mean, unless you want to
hang out here and get busted.
- Eh...
(Crystal chuckles)
All right.
Drop me off to the bus station.
- Excuse me?
- Fish-Man's covering my
bus fare back to Seattle.
- What a loser.
So um...
What's up in Seattle?
- Eh...
Eddie knows this guy who
runs this place, and uh,
he thought maybe we could hook up.
- You? You're going to work at a job?
- Why not?
(Crystal laughs)
- Yeah, that'll last.
- What?
(Crystal laughs)
- Son of a gun.
(soft acoustic music)
♪ Now I've been high ♪
♪ And I've been low ♪
♪ I've been some places
that you would not go ♪
♪ I never thought there
would come the day ♪
♪ When I wish I never
would have left this way ♪
♪ But I've been searching
for a long, long time ♪
♪ I thought the devil
was a friend of mine ♪
♪ I turned my back on
everything that was true ♪
♪ I wasted years that belonged to you ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Some people gotta learn the hard way ♪
(Crystal laughing)
- [Officer 1] All right,
step out of the car.
- [Officer 2] Out of the car please.
(Crystal laughs)
(soft music)
- You're going straight through?
I'm supposed to meet my wife
at the pier tomorrow morning
at 10 o'clock.
- [Man] Cutting it
awfully close, aren't ya?
- I must be there.
(soft music)
(police radio chatter)
- [Man] Hey, he's got my jacket.
- Yep, that's him. Let's go.
- Suspect is on foot
entering the north gate.
(soft, tense music)
- [Woman Over PA]
Attention all passengers,
please proceed now through....
(woman speaking indistinctly over PA)
(soft music)
(people chattering)
- Okay, we've got him heading
towards the gangplank.
Be cool, just follow my lead.
- [Woman Over PA] Please
proceed now through customs.
(soft music)
(people chattering)
- Barbara!
Barbara!
(laughs)
(soft music)
- [Barbara] Dear Crystal,
you don't know me, but my husband, Gordon,
has told me all about you.
We've been praying that your release
from juvenile hall will be soon.
A lot has happened lately.
Jodi is officially the newest
member of the Trout family,
and Cam's got a job working as a mechanic,
thanks to Eddie.
Cam is also helping out with a
street ministry for runaways.
Eddie hopes to get Gordon baptized
in his hot tub before summer.
You know, I think he
might actually succeed.
I know the world's been
tough on you, Crystal,
and I understand how
it feels to be hopeless
about the future, but God does love you.
Don't give up.
And when you get out, come
stay with your extended family.
Gordon would like that.
(soft, upbeat music)
♪ Mm, don't mess with Jesus ♪
♪ Jesus ♪
♪ With Jesus ♪
♪ Go ♪
♪ Run away ♪
♪ Don't look back ♪
♪ Leave behind confusion ♪
♪ Seek ♪
♪ Find a place ♪
♪ To rest my head ♪
♪ A place to call my home ♪
♪ In a world without trust ♪
♪ Selfish and unjust ♪
♪ Now where am I to turn ♪
♪ Last night I felt so far from home ♪
♪ Like me, the moon seemed so alone ♪
♪ Could have used some love
to wrap around this heart ♪
♪ But now my soul has found a place ♪
♪ The smile's returning to my face ♪
♪ With you beside me ♪
♪ I'm no longer so far from home ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ With Jesus ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ Close ♪
♪ Hold me close ♪
♪ Don't let go ♪
♪ Make me feel so wanted ♪
♪ Touch ♪
♪ A warm embrace ♪
♪ Can erase ♪
♪ A lifetime of despair ♪
♪ In a world without trust ♪
♪ Selfish and unjust ♪
♪ I know now where to turn ♪
♪ Last night I felt so far from home ♪
♪ Like me, the moon seemed so alone ♪
♪ Could have used some love
to wrap around this heart ♪
♪ But now my soul has found a place ♪
♪ The smile's returning to my face ♪
♪ With you beside me ♪
♪ I'm no longer so far from home ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ Oh so far from home ♪
♪ No longer, no longer ♪
♪ So far from home ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ I wanna thank you, Jesus ♪
(soft rock music)
♪ One to another ♪
♪ Do you remember me ♪
♪ I feel so small ♪
♪ Well are you listening tonight ♪
♪ So temporary ♪
♪ The things that I have seen ♪
♪ I ran so far ♪
♪ Will you take me back again ♪
♪ Entertaining angels ♪
♪ By the light of my TV screen ♪
♪ 24/7 you wait for me ♪
♪ Entertaining angels ♪
♪ By the time I fall to my knees ♪
♪ Host of heaven, sing over me ♪
♪ One to another ♪
♪ The feelings in between ♪
♪ I won't let go ♪
♪ Of all you taught me ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Close as a brother ♪
♪ The way we used to be ♪
♪ I'll hold my breath ♪
♪ And I'll wait for you to breathe ♪
♪ Entertaining angels ♪
♪ By the light of my TV screen ♪
♪ 24/7 you wait for me ♪
♪ Cover me, Lord ♪
♪ Entertaining angels ♪
♪ While the night becomes history ♪
♪ Host of heaven, sing over me ♪