[music playing]
CAPTAIN: Good afternoon,
this is your captain again.
We're about 80 miles north
of Miami International.
We are about to begin
our final approach.
I'd like to take this time,
on behalf of the crew,
to thank you for
flying with us today.
And we hope you'll
include Carnival Airlines
in your future travel plans.
[music playing]
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Miss Hamilton?
Miss Hamilton?
We'll be landing in
just a few minutes.
ANNOUNCER: Carnival
flight 770 from JFK now
Lauren, welcome.
You look fabulous, as always.
Raul?
Thank you.
Are you blind?
No, I always carry
this one myself.
Raul remembered.
So are you happy,
healthy, psyched?
We've got a full night's
work ahead of us.
Now the good news--
no more hotel.
Daddy bought this nice little
villa for clients to stay.
She's our 9:15.
The Italian blonde's our 9:30.
But you have got to see Heidi.
She'll be by as soon as she's
off her shoot in Key West.
You'll see her, you'll
want her, you'll grab her.
Excuse me.
Let's leave the ladies alone.
I swear this city's
going to the dogs.
[horns honking]
Don't you want to make
sure it's all there?
I'm sure it is.
I see you're still not shaving.
My father lets him
get away with it.
See if you can avoid
the traffic, will you?
We are not running
on Spanish time.
LAUREN: I'm not using the
perfume bottle in these shots.
I'm going for
something different.
Right, right, right, right.
Nothing but beautiful babes
lying in the Palm Beach sun.
Don't you worry, Lauren.
I'm going to keep you
up to your ears in them.
I only need one--
the right one.
Now, Lauren, you're not
going to get picky on me again,
are you?
I mean, last time
was bad enough.
This isn't just
another job, Jennifer.
Oh, please.
All they ever want is
something sleek and sexy.
No, that's just it.
They don't want slick this time.
They want it real, provocative.
Not glossy, but raw.
Raw?
Yeah, they want it passionate.
Something that strikes a nerve.
You know, I don't even know
myself how to get it yet.
So, is the husband
taking a later flight?
No, Stephen is
staying in New York.
JENNIFER: Oh, really.
[speaking spanish]
LAUREN: I love it.
JENNIFER: It's
gorgeous, isn't it?
Mrs. Spencer will show
you up to the bedroom.
Hi, it's me.
Yeah, well we'll be
there within the hour.
As soon as she's changed.
Order in some dinner
from next door.
Any calls?
Yeah.
Is that it?
[phone ringing]
Should I get
that, Mrs. Hamilton?
No.
But do me a favor-- hang
up the things in that one.
Hello?
Stephen.
Yeah, just now.
Fine.
How did you find me?
Well, you're being awfully
attentive all of the sudden.
How do you expect me to be?
Yeah, well, maybe you should
have thought about that before.
Yes, you said that.
But over for you and whoever
she is is one thing, for me--
Stephen, I don't want to have
this conversation now, OK?
I've got work to do.
Yes.
Bye.
Thanks, that's a great help.
I thought you'd like
it a little cooler.
Yes, that's-- thank you.
I don't need anything else.
I mean, you can tell Jennifer
and Miss Perkins I'll
be down in about 15 minutes.
Thank you
Yeah, cooler.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Shu wop,
shu wop, my baby.
Shu wop, shu wop, shu
wop, shu wop, my baby.
Shu wop, shu wop.
Mama say, mama say.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Good and plenty, I'm not ready.
Sleek and sexy, she's not ready.
I don't care, I don't care.
Will she find it?
She shall find it.
Mama say, mama say Don't
cry Mama say, mama say.
Don't cry.
Mama say, mama say.
She's coming.
You better shop around.
Ooh yeah.
Ooh.
Good and plenty, I'm not ready.
Sleek and sexy, she's not ready.
I don't care, I don't care.
Will she find it?
She shall find it.
Mama say, mama say.
Don't cry.
JENNIFER: If you ask me,
Heidi's all you really need.
LAUREN: All right,
put an option on her.
Well, we've got another group
coming in the studio tomorrow.
We're more than covered.
Thanks for being so on
top of this, Jennifer.
I really appreciate it.
Hey, only the
best for you, babe.
What did I tell you
about the new car?
[music playing]
[SINGING] You
better shop around.
LAUREN: Why do you take it?
RAUL: Excuse me?
Jennifer.
She always gives you
such a hard time.
But it doesn't mean anything.
No?
Well, it's a job.
I work for Mr. Perkins.
If he wants me to drive
his daughter around,
that's fine with me.
Yeah, he's an interesting guy.
There's some great faces here.
Fabulous houses
with nobody home.
What are you looking for?
LAUREN: I wish I knew.
It's usually pretty simple.
I see the face I want,
I know what to shoot.
But it's not about
a face this time.
It's about an image that's sexy.
For real, not just flash.
It can't be fake.
It has to be felt.
Raul, let's stop.
I want to see this club.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Get on with it.
Get on.
Get on with it.
Get up.
Hey, Raul.
[inaudible]
Hi.
LAUREN: Very pretty.
Alena?
She's beautiful.
I guess it runs in the family.
My sister.
Oh.
She's studying
business management
at the University of Miami.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Time to
come right over.
The coast is very clear.
So I'm a [inaudible]
Get on with it.
Get up, get on with it.
Whoa.
Ooh yeah.
Can you feel it, can you
feel it, can you feel it.
Get on with it.
Get up, get on with it.
Whoa.
Get up, get on with it
Get up, get on with it.
Whoa.
Oh, Alena, can I
have my camera bag?
[inaudible]
I've got to get
her name and number.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Would you like
to come, come with me.
Would you like to have, have me.
Would you like to
play, play with me.
come, come with me.
Would you like to have, have me.
Would you like to
play, play with me now.
[screams]
[music playing]
[laughs] Come on.
[laughs]
Wait.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Come on let
me move your body.
Move you in our private party.
Come on let me move your body.
[screams]
[music playing] [SINGING]
Come on let me move your body.
Move you in our private party
Would you like to
come, come with me.
No.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Would you
like to have, have me.
Would you like to
play, play with me now.
Ooh would you like to
come, come with me.
Ooh would you like
to have, have me.
Ooh would you like to
play, play with me now.
No.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Ooh you like to
play in my private party.
Party.
Ooh would you like to
come to my private party.
Party.
No.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Ooh would you like
to come to my private party.
Party.
Come on let me move your body.
Move you in our private party.
Ooh would you like to
come, come with me.
Ooh would you like
to have, have me.
Ooh would you like to
play, play with me.
play in my private party.
Party.
Ooh would you like to
come to my private party.
Party.
Come on let me move your body.
Move you in our private party.
[moans]
[music playing]
[SINGING] Ooh would
you like to play.
Ooh would you like to play.
Mm yes.
Mm yeah.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Come on let
me move your body.
Move you in our private party.
Come on let me move your body.
Ooh would you like to
play in my private party.
MARISSA: [moans]
[music playing]
[SINGING] Come on let
me move your body.
Move you in our private party.
Come on let me move your body.
Do me a favor.
Get this developed first
thing in the morning.
Goodnight, Raul.
Miss Hamilton.
[music playing]
[heavy breathing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
STEPHEN: Hey, sweetheart.
Did you just finish up?
No, I got finished
a while ago.
We didn't come straight back.
I took in some sights.
Stephen, what it this?
[inaudible]
You said I wasn't
paying any attention.
So here I am,
attentive as can be.
Hey, how'd you like
the new luggage?
Yeah, it's lovely, it's fine.
Stephen, this is just
her guilt talking.
Are you alone?
Of course I am.
It's a terrible thing,
because now is when you and I
should be with each other.
You've run off on
your own again.
Lauren, let's leave
this behind us.
I have.
I want us to be together again.
Isn't that what's important?
What's important is
that things change.
Things have to get
better between us.
STEPHEN: It will be.
Lauren, you know you can have
everything you want with me.
You know that-- the
best of everything.
But to have it, we've got
to be there for each other.
I'm committed to that
now, more than ever.
The question is, are you?
I've got to go.
Bye.
All right, good night.
[music playing]
Good, now straight.
Beautiful.
[inaudible] camera.
[shutter clicks]
Good, thank you.
Brinig in the next girl, please.
Clifford, can we lose the scarf?
[music playing]
OK, let's take a look at her.
[shutter clicks]
Good, give me profile.
Head back.
Good.
OK.
[shutter clicks]
Ah, lose the dress.
And play with the scarf.
OK, get down.
Good, there.
[shutter clicks]
Come alive.
Good.
Beautiful.
[shutter clicks]
Arch your back.
Put you head back.
Turn.
Come on, turn, move.
OK, back to me.
Look at me.
[shutter clicks]
Get rid of the scarf.
Lose the scarf.
Good.
Go down.
Turn your back to me.
Good.
Over your shoulder.
OK.
[music playing]
This is it, dammit.
This is what I'm looking for.
So are we cooking, or what?
Heidi's ready.
Oh, good.
Where the hell have you been?
I need those dresses
picked up at Finerlooms.
[speaking spanish]
Yeah.
You have a good time?
OK.
I want you thinking about that.
I want you to think about
the way it was last time.
OK.
Turn your back.
Look at me, all right.
And run your hands
down your body.
Imagine they're his hands.
It feels good, doesn't it?
His hands feel good
on your skin, huh?
Good.
Imagine his fingers
touching your breasts.
He's taking your dress
off down your hips.
Good.
Lower.
That's it.
[shutter clicks]
Feel, he knows just
how to touch you.
He's making you hot, excited.
You can come in a minute.
[shutter clicks]
That's it.
[sighs]
It feels good.
Move with it.
[shutter clicks]
He's behind you now.
His lips are over your ear,
telling you every nasty thing
he's going to do to you.
You feel him inside.
You feel him getting harder.
That's it.
You're so hot, so excited.
You could come now.
What?
Why are you stopping?
JENNIFER: So, where
the hell is he?
LAUREN: It's only five after.
I swear one of these days
I'm going to kick his slick ass
back across the Bay.
[laughs] Jennifer.
What is bothering
you about Raul?
He seems perfectly nice to me.
He just--
I don't know.
Ever since daddy let him start
working with art collection,
he acts like he knows something.
Well, he's not dumb.
No, but God, a few years ago
he could barely speak English.
And now he runs around our
estate like he owns it.
Daddy just promised him
a piece of sculpture
that's worth a small fortune.
It's ridiculous.
Look, I got to book, babe.
Are you sure I can't help you?
- No, it's OK.
I'm sure he'll be here.
Well, if he's not here in
five would you let me know?
I'll see you at Dad's
Speak of the devil.
[horn honking]
LAUREN: Wait a second.
Raul, where are we going?
RAUL: You'll see in a minute.
[horn honking]
[inaudible]
[speaking spanish]
What did you say to them?
I said, don't
even think about it.
[speaking spanish] Marissa?
Here, ask her anything you want.
She's perfect, perfect.
The real thing,
she's got it all.
Talk about raw passion.
The way she was on the roof.
The look she had
on her face when
she lifted her
skirt for that guy,
if I can just get that on film.
Of course Jennifer will have
a fit, she's so high on Heidi.
I'll use them both.
Besides, once Jennifer
sees her she's
going to sing her up for life.
As long as she
shows up tomorrow.
Oh, she'll be there.
Yeah.
OK.
Thanks, Raul I owe you one.
It's nothing.
What?
Nothing.
I just have never seen
you without your--
Nikon bag, I know.
I feel naked without it.
But I've got my little
Canon right here.
Wait, I have an idea.
You'll be my date.
Mrs. Hamilton.
Lauren.
Come on.
[music playing]
The guest of honor.
Raul, [speaking spanish]
I'm sorry we're late.
Oh, as if cared.
We simply started without you.
You look exquisite.
Thank you.
Raul, are you joining us?
Well, I couldn't show up
without an escort, now could I?
Oh, we'll just get
another setting here.
There you are.
Thank you.
I'll get another chair.
Fine.
Jennifer, we have found
the perfect blue girl.
You're going to love
her, Jennifer I know it.
JENNIFER: But, how can you tell?
I saw her dance, if
you could call it that.
It was more like foreplay.
I've never seen a woman
taking so much pleasure
in her own body, and in public.
It was like nobody was
there but her and her lover.
And I wanted to talk to
her, so we followed them.
Then, they really
started getting into it.
Oh.
Squeeze it right here.
Did they know that
you were watching them?
No.
But it looked like
she was on fire.
But she was still in
control, taunting this guy.
How do you mean?
Well, she took down her
dress, and she's teasing
him with this magnificent body.
And she's letting him
kiss her, and then she's
pushing him away.
I mean, even when he
got her panties off,
she wouldn't let
him go any further.
It was like, not yet.
He got so excited.
It was like he was a slave.
And then?
Well, then finally,
he took her from behind.
STAN PERKINS: [laughs] That
sounds my idea of a night out.
Dining, dancing, and a show.
[laughter]
Daddy.
You watched all this?
LAUREN: I couldn't
take my eyes off her.
I couldn't take my eyes off her.
Is this your husband?
LAUREN: No, Mrs. Perkins,
my husband isn't here.
It's Raul, Mom.
You remember.
You make a lovely couple.
LAUREN: Grandma,
he's the chauffeur.
STAN PERKINS: Mom,
you remember Raul.
Eduardo's son.
[music playing]
RAUL: I saw you looking at this
in the cafeteria this afternoon
Thank you.
It's good with coffee.
You want some more?
Yes.
I'd like one of those, too.
[music playing]
STAN PERKINS: This is an
Indonesian piece-- from Bali,
actually.
They passed this technique down
from generation to generation.
See the detail work here?
Amigo.
A new shipment just came in.
When can you work on it?
I'll start this week.
Thank you.
Nice having you.
[music playing]
That's the collection.
I'll show you.
[music playing]
Mr. P hired me to open
crates when I was a teenager.
It started as a few
days work, but it
turned into a full-time job.
I got into the
old man's passion.
It's a private world of his.
He opened the door
for me, you know.
And now I'm helping him
organize the entire collection.
Mr. P gave me this one.
Beautiful.
It's from the Pacific Rim.
[inaudible] The
silverfish lovers.
This one-- he's a young
fisherman who hunted
silverfish.
He found this cove
where the fish lived
No, stay there.
Go on.
Oh, you don't mind, do you?
It's just for fun, for me.
Go on.
He found this cove
where the fish lived.
He was in the water.
[shutter clicking]
He had the fish cornered,
with a spear raised.
But he waited.
He couldn't do it.
And the full moon, seeing
this, turned him into a fish.
And they spent the night
together in that cove.
And the next day, the fisherman
returned to his village
with a beautiful maiden,
with hair of shining silver.
She only stayed with him
until the next full moon,
then she disappeared.
The fisherman searched
the river and the cove.
He never found the silverfish.
He never was able to hunt again.
Wow, that's a beautiful story
It's my turn.
No, really.
I'm better behind the lense.
It's only fair.
All right, you can take one.
Focus with this.
[shutter clicking]
[laughs] My turn.
[music playing]
[shutter clicking]
Now.
- Mm mm.
- Oh yes.
Put your hand behind
your shoulder.
That's good.
[shutter clicking]
Move your fingers.
Let's go on.
[music playing]
[moans]
LAUREN: [moans]
[music playing]
[dialing phone]
[dog barking]
I'm sore.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, in the morning--
Yes?
Could you come
by a little earlier
and help me with the equipment?
Sure.
It's going to be
a long day tomorrow.
And you're sure she'll show up--
Marissa?
She'll be there.
Sleep well.
You too.
[birds chirping]
Mrs. Spencer, I'm ready
for that omelet now.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Who do you love?
Who do you love?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Who do you?
Baby, baby, baby,
baby, baby, baby.
[knocking]
Good morning.
I couldn't wait for
you to come home.
So, what?
Aren't you going
to invite me in?
God, I'd forgotten how
hot it would be down here.
Whew.
I knew you'd be surprised.
But I was just kind of hoping
for pleasantly surprised.
Wow, this is nice.
You should have
called, Stephen.
Ah, shoulda, coulda, woulda.
Look, you're still
a little upset.
I think I still
rated a little kiss.
Just one?
Stephen, I've got to get ready.
[knocking]
Ah, allow me Can I help you?
It's Raul, Stephen.
He works for the agency.
Of course.
Oh, how goes it?
LAUREN: And he's here to
help me with the equipment.
And these must be
from the agency.
Yes, they are.
How pretty.
[phone ringing]
I bet that's Jennifer now.
Stephen, could you
Absolutely, absolutely.
I didn't know he was coming.
We have to talk because--
[phone ringing]
STEPHEN: Hello?
Hey, yeah, I flew
in this morning.
Yeah, she was surprised.
Hold on.
Lauren, Jennifer
wants to know if you--
if we need more time.
No, we're on schedule so far.
STEPHEN: No, no, no.
Your manservant, Raul.
The bags are over
here, Raul, if you
can take them downstairs.
Certainly, Mrs. Hamilton.
They're beautiful.
STEPHEN: OK, we'll
see you in a bit.
[hangs up phone]
Scrambled, lucky me.
You don't mind, do you?
[music playing]
[SINGING] [moaning]
I can see through this.
I can feel it.
And I can feel it in your kiss.
I've felt this all before.
Or maybe I read it wrong,
but I can't wait that long.
This love's weighing heavy
on my heart, on my heart.
I'll carry the weight of
the world for your love
for your love, all, the
weight of the world.
I just can't carry
this love on my own.
I can't carry this
love on my own.
Weight of the world, just can't
carry this love on my own.
I know you have a job to do.
I just couldn't leave
things unsettled between us.
Well.
I admit that I was wrong.
Maybe it's all been
too much for me.
I was feeling a
little threatened.
You're just so good
at everything you do.
And for me to be with
someone so talented,
so smart, so damn beautiful--
well, a man just
starts to feel--
Good, Stephen, blame me and
flatter me at the same time.
I'm not blaming you.
I'm saying that I did what I did
because of my own insecurities.
It wasn't you, babe.
As for this other totally
inconsequential encounter--
LAUREN: It didn't mean anything.
I know.
I've heard this once
before, Stephen.
STEPHEN: I bought
the Kornsby place.
LAUREN: You what?
STEPHEN: That's right,
the entire 23 acres.
You said that old barn
would make a dream studio
[laughs] Oh God,
this is so like you.
Something's wrong, so you
just throw money at it.
No, no, this is different.
This is what you wanted.
I did it for you, for us.
So we could have a
place, and the time
to make a new beginning.
All right, Stephen.
You say that you want us
to be there for each other.
Well, that means all
the time, not just
want a crisis like this
forces you to pay attention.
Yes.
Yes, absolutely.
You know, these daytime
assignments have done
wonders for your self-esteem.
I've never seen
you so assertive.
It's really attractive
Stephen.
A chance, that's
all I'm asking for.
Just say you'll think about it.
All right?
Come here, come here, come here.
All right, Stephen, all right.
[sighs]
JENNIFER: Ahoy maties.
Morning.
Hi, cookie.
LAUREN: Clifford, did you
pack the extra umbrellas?
You decided to
work on your tan, eh?
I do hope you brought
some swimwear.
Raul, you finally shaved.
What's the occasion?
So, where's wonder girl?
She's supposed
to meet us here.
She's late.
Where is she, Raul?
I took your word on this.
Well, who can you
trust these days?
Stop it.
She'll be here.
We've got to get this
show on the road, babe.
So we'll use Heidi.
You won't even miss
this flake of yours.
You've got 10 pieces on board.
11, if you count your bag.
Yo, yo, yo.
Where do you think you're going?
I've got you for
the day, don't I?
I'm going to need your
muscle on the island, Raul.
Get back on board.
Hey, hun, did you
pack the sunblock?
Ask Terry.
[horn honking]
[music playing]
You have got to be kidding me.
Just look.
Yeah, I see you're
going to need a cattle
prod to keep the crew back.
All right.
Time is money, folks.
Come on, let's get
this show on the road.
[music playing]
Raul, how about a cold one?
Let's stick to
soda for the talent,
at least until after lunch, OK?
[music playing]
LAUREN: [inaudible]
Let's go, Heidi.
[music playing]
[inaudible] Heidi [inaudible]
[shutter clicking]
Good.
Look over your shoulder at me.
[shutter clicking]
[inaudible] That's it.
Have fun with it.
Good Yes, beautiful
[shutter clicking]
Perfect OK, Heidi, play.
Ho, ho, ho, they are so hot.
[shutter clicking]
LAUREN: Good.
I'm hot.
Do me, will you?
LAUREN: Yes.
I love when you
talk like that.
Thanks for the phone call.
I needed a good
exuse to come down.
You missed a spot.
So, you really think
there's something
going on between them?
Something, yeah.
They're acting
awfully strange today.
Just keep watching, you'll see.
LAUREN: All right, you
take a break, Heidi.
Let's just shoot this.
I want to get more
coverage for her.
Yeah.
Marissa, take a dip, get
wet Good How's that feel?
Enjoy yourself.
Good.
I need a hand.
Yo.
Yo, a hand, an
arm, in the shot.
OK.
Raul, I need to use you
in this shot, please.
About there, about there.
A little to the left, Raul.
Can we lose the shirt?
[shutter clicking]
[music playing]
We're going for the
tension here, Marissa.
Good.
Now, do what you did
that night, Marissa.
Yeah.
[music playing]
Warm her some more.
85.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Would you like
to come, come with me.
Ooh would you like to play.
LAUREN: Yes, Marissa, yes.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Would you like
to play, play with me.
[shutter clicking]
Oh, he's playing it cool, huh?
Make him care, Marissa.
That's it.
Make him hard.
Yes, Marissa.
Yes, that's good.
Don't stop, don't
stop, I'm getting it.
That's what I want, don't stop.
More, Marissa.
More. more.
Yes.
Yes, Marissa, keep moving.
Move, Marissa, perfect.
I'm getting it.
Yes.
Rub your breasts on his body.
Touch him everywhere.
[shutter clicking] Make him
know you want him, Marissa.
That's right.
That's it.
Love it, love it.
That's it, Marissa.
I love it, Good.
[music playing]
[SINGING] Mm, mama
[inaudible] excited baby doll
and I just can't fight it.
You and I united with a kiss.
[shutter clicking]
You know you want
it now, Marissa.
Now.
[shutter clicking]
[laughs]
All right, break.
Well, if that wasn't
blue, I don't know what is.
Do you want to go talk to him?
No.
- Hey, Marissa?
- Hmm?
The guy I saw you
with the other night,
is he the same one that
drove you here this morning?
No.
What?
You think there's
something wrong with that?
LAUREN: No, no, I
was just curious.
Me too.
I'm a curious person.
And when I want to know
something, I explore.
Wow.
I see.
Whatever I want.
What my heart needs,
that's what I listen to.
I go for the things
I want, you know.
I want to live every
day all the way.
I don't want any
regrets when I'm old.
You know what I mean?
Huh?
[thunder]
[wind blowing]
STEPHEN: How about a
little refreshment, huh?
Woo.
[laughs]
LAUREN: Has anybody
seen my camera bag?
My bag's missing.
Clifford, where's the Nikon?
[sighs] Shit.
You heard what he said, hon.
We can't go back in
the middle of this.
It's not safe.
It's too shallow.
Screw this shit.
I want a dinghy.
All right, all right.
He needs both of his
crewmen up on deck.
My shot is in
that role, dammit.
I'm not going to stand
around here and do nothing.
You just have to wait it
out, sweetheart This should
blow over within an hour.
I'll send Raul after it
the minute this lets up.
I'd go back for
you myelf, but I'm
not familiar with those motors.
JENNIFER: Lauren?
Yes, yes, I hear you.
JENNIFER: I'm with
you, babe You better
stay where you are for now.
Kiefer says it's going to
get worse before it lifts,
and it's going to have a hell
of a time getting you moored up
[inaudible] again.
So just stay put, will you?
All right.
We're lucky.
You know, I was
depending on you, Raul.
And you just disappeared
like that today.
Listen, everybody else is
into their own bullshit Raul,
I would like to think that you
and I could play it straight.
Straight?
Right.
I'm sorry, OK.
I'm sorry that
Marissa went too far.
I'm so sorry Stephen showed up.
I'm sorry we haven't
had two seconds
to just talk to each other
about what's happened.
It meant nothing.
It doesn't matter
Raul, no
What is there to talk about?
You belong to him, right?
You had an itch.
You scratched it.
Yeah.
And now?
It's over.
It is over.
Stop it.
Don't.
It doesn't matter, right?
[music playing]
[SINGING] More than a
dream, closer than a shadow.
I can feel you near.
Oh something you're
saying is touching me.
There's a ringing in my head.
All along I tried to prepare.
Nothing comes close to how
we feel when we're together.
And when you touch
me, I keep holding on.
I pray forever is
one day you'll come.
It's more than words.
Now that I found you,
I'll never let go.
All of my nights
Were empty and shallow,
but now filled with tears.
Ooh reach out and hold
me, let your love control
me till the river is here.
Tonight I cure all our fears.
I want you so much, I need
to feel our hearts together.
And when you touch
me, I keep holding on.
Hold on.
I pray forever is
one day you'll come.
It's more than words.
Now that I found you,
I'll never let go.
Ho ho.
And when you touch
me, I keep holding on.
I pray forever is
one day you'll come.
It's more than words.
Now that I found you,
I'll never let go.
I won't let go.
Oh no no.
And when you touch
me, I keep holding on.
RAUL: So, what now?
Now you go back to
your husband again?
He says he's changed.
Me, I don't have to change
Oh, so I'd be
better off with you,
is that what you're saying?
I can make you very happy
Yes, for now.
Is that all?
You don't want more.
I know you.
Yeah, I do.
What, you really want
a future with me?
I don't think so.
You just like what's
going on right now.
And you?
Forget about it.
I'm completely confused.
But I should thank you.
Thank me?
Yeah.
You taught me something.
You taught me how to
just let myself be.
And that's a freedom and a
feeling I didn't even know
existed.
And you got me there.
You got your shot.
Yeah, and what did you get?
What do you want, really?
How long are you going
to live like this.
And don't give me,
it's a good job.
Well?
Well, what?
You could have so much more.
Mrs. Hamilton, are you there?
Yeah.
Is the camera OK?
Ah, it survived.
Good.
The coast is clear.
We're heading back in.
OK, we're on our way.
We better go.
My silverfish.
You got it?
Great.
JENNIFER: Yeah, I'm
sure it was nothing.
Look, that might be the kind
of line you feed your wife.
[inaudible] Hey, babe.
We were just about to
call out the Coast Guard.
JENNIFER: Um, did you--
did you find the camera?
Uh huh.
STEPHEN: Quite a storm, huh?
God, I missed you.
I need to get out
of these clothes.
JENNIFER: Of course.
Sure.
I'll um-- I'm going to get Terry
to pull one of the garment bags
for you.
LAUREN: No, I can manage.
Don't.
How you feeling?
Fine.
You look a little beat.
I guess the extra
trip overtired you.
I thought it was a bit much, you
and Raul, going in on your own
like that.
It was something you had to do.
I understand that.
[music playing]
[laughs] Thank you
Oh, you know the one
across form the Biltmore?
Oh, it's perfect for drinks.
Terry, Marissa can
come in your car.
Mm, gracias.
No, thank you, Marissa.
You really made it happen.
She certainly did.
Now, you know, I can
invest that for you
and practically double it.
Really, Marissa, this
is only the beginning.
Now, if you come with
my agency, I can have
you working whenever you want.
No, thanks.
One day with you guys
is enough for me.
I'm out of here.
Hey, babe.
Oh.
JENNIFER: Can you
believe this girl?
Flake.
What did I tell you?
An absolute, total flake.
Thank you.
JENNIFER: Raul, is my
phone still in the car?
Well, then must
still be on board.
Honestly, I shouldn't
even pay him for the day.
He can't keep track of anything.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Go back on and get it.
Get it yourself.
JENNIFER: What?
What did he say?
You heard me.
Look, I've had just
about enough of this.
No, I've had enough of you.
I quit.
And I'll turn in the
keys to your father.
JENNIFER: You slimey little--
STEPHEN: Hey, hey ignore him.
It's been a long day.
We'll go for a drink.
It's over, forget about it.
Well, who the hell
does he think he is?
It's over.
Come on, let's go.
We can fit in one car.
LAUREN: Raul?
Hey, babe?
You two enjoy yourselves It
won't be the first time, right?
Hey, Raul, mind
giving me a ride?
STEPHEN: Wait a second.
Lauren?
Like you said
Stephen, it's over.
Hey, hey, hey, come on.
What are you doing?
Something I should have
done a long time ago.
I just didn't know how.
Lauren.
Stephen, you hurt me.
And words don't
make that disappear.
This doesn't.
Now, I've got to go.
And where is it that
you think you're going?
I don't know, babe,
but don't wait up.
[engine starting]
[music playing]
[laughter]
[SINGING] More than a
dream, closer than a shadow,
I can feel you near.
Ooh something you're
sending is touching me.
There's a ringing in my ear.
All along I tried to prepare.
Nothing comes close to how
we feel when we're together.
And when you touch
me, I keep holding on.
I'll pray forever is
one day you'll come.
It's more than words.
Now that I've found
you, I'll never let go.
I'll never let go
All of my nights were empty
and shallow but now filled
with tears Ooh reached out and
hold me let your love control
me till the river is here
Tonight I cure all our fears.
I want you so much.
I need to feel our
hearts together.
And when you touch
me, I keep holding on.
I'll pray forever is
one day you'll come.
It's more than words
Now that I've found you,
I'll never let go.
And when you touch
me, I keep holding on.
I pray forever is
one day you'll come.
I need to hear
you say the words.
Now that I've found
you, I'll never let go.
I won't let go.
Oh no no.
And when you touch
me, I keep holding on.
I pray forever is
one day you'll come.
It's more than words
Now that I've found you,
I'll never let go.
Whoa ho.
And when you touch me,
I'll keep holding on.