[children yelling]
♪♪ [orchestra]
Come on. Right here.
[Boy]
Hey, Joey! It's your brother!
[Man]
There he is!
There's the guy!
Hey!
Ah, how you
doin', buddy?
[all chattering]
Playin' ball?
Yeah!
Want to play ball?
Can I play ball with you guys?
Yeah!
Oh, all right!
Let's play some baseball.
All right.
Okay, Joey?
You ready, buddy? Okay.
Here we go.
There it is! Okay,
go now, go, start runnin'!
Here we go! You're comin' in,
you're comin' home!
There it is!
Perfect, perfect!
Throw it back to Bob.
First base, over there.
All right, Joey.
Here he comes now!
Joey!
Run him down, run him down!
Yeah, that's it!
That's how it's done.
That's excellent.
Come here, all right!
That's the way it's done.
You guys understand
everything was explaining?
Come on, Ma!
We're gonna be late!
Come on!
I'm coming.
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
Do you have all the tickets
and everything?
How's your face?
Let me see that face.
Mrs. Vancucco, remember
today's the day!
We're gonna win this game,
I just know it!
[Man]
Get your programs!
1957 World Series Programs!
[Announcer]
...New York, to open
the World Series,
against
the heavily-favored Yankees,
led by Henry Aaron,
Eddie Matthews,
and Brooklyn's
own Frank Torre,
the Braves are looking
for their first World Series
title since 1914.
What's the name?
Tickets for Torre,
Joe and Margaret.
Joe and Margaret Torre!
You related to Frank?
Yeah, he's my brother!
And I'm his mother.
Pleased to meet ya.
You don't think Frank
can hit off
Whitey Ford, do ya?
Hey, just wait and watch.
[laughs]
Come on, Eddie!
Hey, looks good!
[Stadium announcer]
Number 24, Henry Aaron!
At first base, number 14,
Frank Torre!
You wanted to see me,
Mr. Cashin?
I don't know how
to say this, Joe.
We're looking to go
in a different direction.
I don't know how
to tell you this, Joe.
We're gonna be going
in a different direction.
Pack up your things, Joe.
We're going in
a different direction.
So? Change much?
It's smaller.
Hey, Joey! Gotcha!
Surprise, Joey!
Surprise!
Well, hey.
[excited chattering]
Hey, what are you doing?
Leaving the baby out here?
[all chattering]
Surprise!
Joe looks great!
Oh, he looks beautiful.
Look at this!
Here you go!
And you, look at you!
So wonderful
to have you back!
Okay, let's get a picture!
Let's get a picture! Get closer.
All right. Hey!
Come on!
Just got to pull the plug.
Two, three, provolone!
[laughing]
Did you do this?
Are you responsible for that?
Yes, I am.
♪♪ [accordion]
[Old Frank]
Yeah, she sang that for you,
she didn't sing it for me.
Because Poppy's tall,
and you're small.
Because I was the baby.
Yeah!
[laughing]
She spoiled ya, Joe.
She spoiled you.
Joey. Joey, Joey,
I got to tell you.
I think you're
out of your mind.
Frankie, leave him alone.
Why are you bothering him?
He just got here!
I'm not bothering him!
Joey--
Come on, you got a wife.
You got a kid on the way.
Why are you doing this?
I thought it was over.
I got a shot now.
I gotta take it.
You come home!
I don't think they realize
he's a grown man.
Hey, it's the law
of the neighborhood.
They never grow up.
They just get taller!
Is he all right?
You okay?
Hey, Rocco.
[chuckles]
Yeah. Just sittin'
down for a minute.
Hey, come on. Don't make
a Federal case out of it.
I'm okay.
♪♪ [Italian accordion]
Martinez is fine.
But he's no Mattingly.
I'll tell you what you
got to do. You gotta
bat Boggs leadoff.
It don't matter
who bats leadoff.
What you need
is more pitching. Now.
Who you got after Cone?
I'm just about getting into it,
but I think we got
a pretty solid staff.
Joey, the man canned
Billy Martin 12 times.
Bob Lemon. Lou Piniella--
He fires everybody!
It's his team, I guess
he can do what he wants.
Joey! Do you and Ali
have a place to live yet?
Well, she's starting to look.
You buying or renting?
Buying?
You'll be out of
here by August!
Joey, rent.
I'm not interested
in honorable finishes,
or close seconds.
This is New York!
I've won a few
World Series, Joe.
And I think I have
a pretty good idea
what it takes:
Focus. Dedication.
The right people.
They produce,
or you replace them
with people that will produce!
If there's anything
you need, you let me know,
or you let Bob know.
All you got to do
is win.
That's what I came here
to do, George.
Fine. Fine.
I've been divorced twice
and fired three times.
You never get used to it.
Look at this.
Oh, my God, Joey!
[Frank laughing]
[Radio announcer]
We're on the air.
What do you want to talk about?
[Caller]
What do I want to talk about?
What do you think
I want to talk about?
The one thing
I'll give George credit for,
maybe he drives people
crazy, but the man don't
sit still for losers!
He's giving Torre a shot,
fine. But unless he delivers--
[Announcer]
Tony from Tenafly.
You're on the air.
[Tony from Tenafly]
Hey, I'm happy for Joe, right?
He's a New York guy,
he's got a new baby, great!
I give him April,
I give him May.
By June he's gone.
Baby or no baby. End of story.
She's beautiful, Dad.
She's beautiful.
Yeah, Joe, Joe!
You didn't win with the Mets,
you didn't win with the Braves.
You didn't win
with the Cardinals.
What's different now?
This time it's the Yankees.
[laughter]
Next month, I'm gonna be 65.
I think that had
a lot to do with it.
Sixty-four years old,
and I never earned a nickel
in all those years
that didn't come from baseball.
When I was a kid,
I didn't have a paper route,
anything like that.
I was playing ball.
Day after I graduated,
I went to play A Ball.
Seventeen, I was
playing professional ball.
[laughs]
You know, I can tell you
what I did...
every 4th of July
from 1948 to 1995.
I was at a ball game!
[snickers]
Every Memorial Day:
at a ball game.
Every Labor Day:
At a ball game!
So what happened?
Why'd you quit?
Too many ball games.
[laughs]
Well, how do you feel about it?
You sorry you quit?
Well, am I sorry I quit?
The last six months
have been heaven!
Last six months
have been heaven.
[laughs]
Because if you're interested
in some more ball games...
I'd like to hire you
as my bench coach.
All right, wait a minute.
Did George put you up to this?
Don, this is my idea.
Well, it's a damn good idea.
Great.
Good.
Well, guess what, ladies?
You know, when I think about it,
it's really kind of amazing.
My second season
with Milwaukee, what happens?
I make it to the World Series.
Took it for granted.
I said, "Well, this is
the way it's supposed to be."
Easiest thing
in the world, right?
Yeah! I was arrogant.
What the hell did I know,
that most Major Leaguers
never get a shot like that?
I waited all my life for that.
That's what I'm sayin'.
What?
Joey...
You're gonna do it.
I won a batting title once.
Most Valuable Player once.
But when you're an athlete,
you play to win.
Win.
In baseball, that means
the World Series.
I played 2,209
baseball games,
and never made it
to the World Series.
I managed 1,901 games,
and never made it
to the World Series.
I played 18 years as a player,
19 years as a manager,
never made it
to the World Series.
Some guy looked it up,
and it turns out
that I'm the one who spent
more days in a baseball uniform
than anyone else in
the history of the game...
who never made it
to the World Series.
Now, how the hell
would you like to have
that on your epitaph?
[softly]
You know, this is not just
some kid with a couple years,
that's your boy--
this is Dwight Gooden, skipper.
Dwight Gooden!
Yeah, I know.
Was he a great pitcher?
Yeah, sure.
This is what I got to know.
Well, this is one
of the premier pictures
of all times.
Yeah, I know what.
Listen: what about
the drug suspensions?
He's clean now.
You know this?
Absolutely.
Hmm.
You know, he hasn't pitched
in a year and a half.
Joe, this is a guy
that really wants
to make it back.
Bottom line, Joe T.
The boss wants this guy.
Are you going
to use him or not?
Don't worry about it, Doc.
It's only spring training.
[bat hits ball]
All right.
Still spring training.
There's two weeks to go.
You'll get him next time.
It's only spring training.
I've lost Mélido Pérez.
He's gone for the season.
Jimmy Key has had surgery.
It takes a whole year
to come back from that one.
Kenny Rogers is banged
all over the place.
And Andy Pettitte
is inexperienced,
and that is four out of
my five starting pitchers.
What about Doc Gooden?
Doc Gooden.
He's a good pitcher,
isn't he?
1986, he was a great pitcher.
How they going?
Great. Almost ready.
Not the hamburgers,
the team!
Great.
Almost ready.
[Radio announcer]
Sal from the Bronx--
you're on the air!
What's on your mind?
[Sal]
Are you kidding?
It's gonna be a long year!
And I don't mean
into October!
It's simple!
It's so simple!
You know it, I know it,
everybody knows it
except Clueless Joe!
The Yankees got no pitching.
None, zip, zilch, nada.
[Tony from Tenafly]
Hey, I wish 'em luck,
you know what I mean?
[Sal from the Bronx]
Yeah, right. What good's
luck gonna do 'em?
Wasn't exactly
a great pre-season, Joe.
Pre-season's for football.
It's spring training,
that's all it is.
Not any more, Joe.
So, are the Yankees
ready for the season?
Well, we're about
to find out, aren't we?
[crowd groans]
[Radio announcer]
You're on!
[Caller]
Twenty-one games,
they lost ten.
They can't pick up the ball,
they don't know
where to throw it,
no pitching, no hitting--
they lucky they haven't
lost all of them!
[crowd booing]
I left my purse
out there on the field.
Focus, man.
They're pretty upset, Joe.
Better talk to 'em.
[bats clattering]
How's your arm, Doc?
It's fine, and you?
Good. Real good.
We'll get it back.
Paulie?
Yeah?
You played some
football in college, right?
Yeah, some.
How many games
in a football season?
Twelve.
How many games
in a baseball season?
A hundred and sixty-two.
Joe's right, boys.
We got more games,
let's get the focus back!
Let's dig in!
[smattering of applause]
[chattering]
Come on!
Joe? Joe.
Telephone.
Yeah, would you tell him
I'll call him back, Zim?
Joe, it's George.
[Steinbrenner]
How ya doin', Joe?
Uh, fine, George.
Well, this is one of those
I thought we could win,
but sometimes they
just get away from ya.
No, no, no, I meant
you, your family.
You settled in,
got a nice place?
Lovely place.
And there are no problems,
because, uh,
if there are...
No, not at all, George.
And no distractions,
I mean, nothing is
preying on your mind?
Nothing.
Well, that's all I want
to know, Joe.
[beeps]
You know what's wrong.
We haven't got any hitters!
You're the trading genius.
Why can't you get me
any hitters?
We've got hitters,
Mr. Steinbrenner.
That's not the problem.
If you're looking for
an area where you want
to make personnel changes,
you've got to consider the fact
that in our last four losses,
we gave up six, seven,
eight, and ten runs!
Unless we get some
pitching help, we've got
to find some hitters!
If you're gonna give up
that many runs, you got
to score runs!
A lot of them!
Where's all
these olives come from?
Are these Greek olives,
or Italian ones?
[Woman] No, no, no, no.
Italian.
These are Italian olives.
You sure?
Has it got a lot
of salt in there?
Kalamata?
All right,
what's this all about?
Beats the hell out of me.
I didn't call this meeting.
Joey, this is
not a meeting.
All right,
so it's not a meeting.
But what's it all about?
Yeah, Rae.
What is it all about?
It's about your brother.
Frank? What did he do?
He didn't do anything.
Why isn't he here?
He's in Florida!
Exactly... and
why is he in Florida?
Uh, because he lives there?
[laughs]
With his brother managing
a baseball team
practically across
the street from where
he has an apartment!
He doesn't want to get
in my hair! It's very
thoughtful of him.
A-Are we talking about
the same brother here?
Come on, please!
Ah, this is crazy.
Come on, hey,
gimme a break!
So pick up the phone,
and ask him why he's there!
Yeah!
You guys, listen
to your sister.
[Rae]
Thank you.
Now, Frankie lives
for baseball, right?
Yeah.
Every time there's a game,
he calls you
whether you are playing,
whether you are managing,
whether you are broadcasting--
whatever, right?
Has he been calling you?
No.
How soon can you go?
Soon as is humanly possible.
[booing]
Let's call it
a night, Doc.
Don't know what's the matter.
The ball's straight.
Stays up.
It's a long road.
We're gonna need you.
He'll come around.
[knocks]
Joe?
Doc! Come on in,
have a seat, will you?
Doc, it's only temporary
until you get it worked out,
but for now, I got to
pull you out of the rotation.
You'll work out of
the bullpen for a while,
low pressure situations,
it'll come around.
You know, I--
I have eighteen long months
to think about how bad
I screwed up my life,
you know,
I let my dad down,
and when I got that
suspension letter--
You know, I just kind
of bottomed out,
I really got down,
and I was just kind of numb.
Then I said to myself,
"I can make it back."
You are back.
You're in the major leagues.
You just gotta do
a little more work.
I threw all last year, Joe.
I threw all winter,
getting ready to come back,
and my arm is fine, Joe.
It's just um...
It's just--
Just--
It's just not there.
Don't give up.
Don't give up on yourself.
Hey, Joe. Come here.
I want you
to see something.
This is Doc in '85,
and this is him now.
Now, I been looking at these
over and over again,
tryin' to see
what's different.
I can't find anything.
Yeah.
I don't know what
the problem is, Joe.
Well, maybe
that's the problem.
He is trying to do
what he did when he was 21.
Can you imagine if
we tried to do the stuff
that we did when we were 21?
[grunts]
Good night.
Get some sleep, pal.
Yeah.
Hey, Doc?
Like you to try something.
I want to see if
we can eliminate some of
the parts of your motion.
Like, simplify it.
Bring your hands up slowly.
No, no, no.
Not that high. Down.
Good, good.
Now pull back a bit.
All right.
You okay there?
Mm-hmm.
All right.
Try a couple.
How'd that feel?
Good.
Good?
[laughs]
All right, here.
There you go.
Throw a couple more.
Oh!
Hey, Frankie.
Hey, Rae!
How are ya?
[laughs]
I got a little dizzy
for a second. I'm fine.
Oh!
You all right?
Yeah, hey. No problem.
Hey!
Come on, let's get
a cup of coffee.
How are you?
I'm good.
You look beautiful.
You always look beautiful.
Ahh!
Well, you do. Come on!
[cheering]
[Announcer]
It'll be a 2-2 to Tartabull.
Struck him out swinging!
Breaking ball away!
Well, Coney's been great today.
I think that's gonna
do it for him.
Ends with 12 strikeouts!
He looked phenomenal
today out there.
Great game, Coney.
I don't know where
we would be without you.
How long has
this been this way?
Not long, Joe.
What does that
feel like?
It's okay. Doesn't hurt.
Which is it?
Doesn't hurt? Or okay?
What do you mean?
Can you feel
what I'm doing?
Yeah, you're moving
my fingers.
Honest answer, Coney.
[sighs]
After about
the fourth inning or so,
sometimes later, I guess,
I can't feel
my fingers at all.
So this isn't
the first time it's happened.
Last couple of games.
Goes away in about an hour.
I shook his hand.
It was ice.
Ready, Joe.
I must have done something
right in a previous life.
I have never seen
two more beautiful women.
Did you hear that?
I guess he likes your dress.
[chuckling]
What were you thinking about?
When?
Just now.
When I walked in.
You looked so lost.
Well, I was lost,
and then you came in,
and how could I be lost?
[coos]
Aw.
That's such
a beautiful thing to say.
I read it somewhere.
[chuckles]
[laughing]
[phone ringing]
[yawns]
Hello?
Ali, it's Rae.
Is Joe there?
Can I talk to him?
Um, well,
he's still sleeping.
He didn't get in
till 2:00 a.m.
I hate to wake him up.
He's not been
sleeping very well.
It's kind of important, Ali.
Okay.
Joe?
It's Rae.
She says it's important.
What?
It's Rae.
She's on the phone.
Oh.
Hello, Rae.
What's the matter?
Frank's sick.
He won't go see a doctor,
and I can't get him
to do anything about it.
Put him on.
He does not know
that I'm calling you.
It's okay.
Put him on.
Oh.
Frank?
Hmm?
It's Joe.
He wants to talk to you.
Ohh.
This another one
of your brainstorms?
What brainstorms?
This is your brother.
Your brother who loves you?
He wants to talk to you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, Joe, how you doing?
Go to a doctor.
Yeah. Hey, how about
that game last night, huh?
This Cone--
hell of a pitcher.
Where the hell would you be
without him?
Well, we're about to find out.
He's got a problem
with his hand.
Yeah? Is it serious?
I don't know if it's serious,
but I do know that he's got
enough sense to go
and see a doctor.
What are you doing, Frank?
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, Joey, thanks.
I really appreciate it.
I'm busy right now.
What the--
Bye.
I love ya.
[sighs]
[players chattering]
Fellas.
Everybody, listen up.
Joe's got something
he needs to tell ya.
All right.
First things first.
I want you to hear it from me
before you hear it
from anybody else.
Coney needs surgery.
Oh, come on.
He's got an aneurysm
in his pitching shoulder.
We hear "aneurysm,"
we get scared,
but it's not like that.
It's not life-threatening.
He's gonna have
the surgery this week,
and it's all gonna
get taken care of,
so we have nothing
to worry about on that score.
I think I only
have to say this once,
'cause I know you all know it.
This is a 25-man game.
Will it be harder to win
without Coney? Absolutely.
Which means each
and every one of you
has to pull that much harder.
So let's not waste
time and energy
lamenting on
what we don't have.
Let's concentrate
on what we do have--
each other.
Yeah.
Right.
You got it, Coach.
You got it.
All for one.
That's right.
All right, guys, let's go!
All for one!
Let's go play.
Let's go have fun!
Come on!
[chattering]
Come on, come on.
Go back, back.
Doc.
What's up?
Feel like starting tomorrow?
Yeah. Where? Columbus?
I need somebody
to start tomorrow
against Seattle.
It's yours if you want it.
Yeah.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[grunts]
Let's hope
he can pitch like that
with his clothes on.
Shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh! Shh!
I don't know
what to do, Joe.
I mean, if this is gonna be
his last hours,
I think I should
be there, right?
Have you talked to him?
I didn't know
what to tell him.
I just kind of wanted
to make up my mind first.
I mean, he always said
that if...
[stifled crying]
He said he never wanted me
to lose my turn.
So...
[paper rustling]
[mutters]
[phone buttons clicking]
Dan Gooden.
Dad, it's Dwight.
How you doing?
'Cause you know
I'll be on the next flight.
Because I'd like
to be there with you,
that's why.
Right.
Okay. Right.
First thing in the morning.
I love you.
He says, uh, the operation
is first thing in the morning.
They're gonna give him
something to sleep,
and he'll be knocked out
all night,
and he don't want me
sitting in some hospital room
looking at him.
Well, you knew
what he would say.
You know,
when I messed up,
the thing that hurt me most
was the hurt I caused him.
Uh, yeah.
I knew he would say that.
Then you're pitching for him.
Is it time?
Yeah. It's time.
Oh.
Uh, thanks.
[crowd cheering, applauding]
[TV announcer]
One on, one out.
Top of the first inning.
Doc Gooden facing the great
young star of the Mariners,
Alex Rodriguez.
The pitch. Swung on and driven
to deep center field.
Gerald Williams back.
Going way back.
He makes a great
one-handed catch!
Fires back toward the infield.
They have a chance
to double-brag.
It's a double play!
[TV announcer #2]
That is about as good a play
as you will ever see
by an outfield.
Oh, baby!
The pitch to Griffey.
Swung on and missed!
Struck him out. Fastball.
Here's the two-two to Buhner.
Swung on and missed.
He got him with a strikeout.
The pitch.
Strike three is called.
Fastball inside to Bragg.
I don't know what the hell
you said to him, but he's
really popping the ball.
Oh, I haven't seen his fastball
rise like that since '89.
That-a-way, Doc!
[cheering]
Two outs,
top of the 7th inning.
Gooden staring into Girardi
for the sign.
He winds, kicks, and deals.
Wilson, fly ball
to center field.
Going back is Gerald Williams.
He's there and puts it away.
And Gooden is just
six outs away from history.
Indeed.
He's got a no-hitter
through seven
as he walks to the dugout,
where, obviously, Mike,
no one's gonna talk to him.
Baseball tradition.
You cannot jinx this man.
And, you know,
the eyes of the world
are on him right now,
but he might be
the loneliest person on earth.
[cheering continues]
You ever caught
a no-hitter?
You ever manage one?
I don't think
I can stand to watch.
Will you shut up?
One inning to go
for the no-hitter for Gooden.
In the 9th
with Rodriguez leading off,
the three-one pitch
from Doc.
It's low outside.
He walks him.
How many pitches is that?
113.
He's tired.
Get Wetteland warmed up.
So, Gooden alone
with his thoughts.
Trying to win the game.
Trying to pitch a no-hitter.
And the tying run
at the plate,
the dangerous Edgar Martínez.
It'll be a 3-2 pitch.
Rodriguez leads.
And Gooden deals.
Breaking ball, outside.
[crowd groaning]
He loses Martinez.
And now the worry isn't
only about the no-hitter,
but about the game.
Is Wetteland ready?
Yeah. He's ready.
Two on, one out
in the 9th inning.
Gooden trying to win
the ball game,
leading 2-nothing,
and earn his place
in baseball history.
The pitch to Buhner is low.
Gets away from Girardi.
A wild pitch,
and the runners move
to second and third.
And now a base hit
not only breaks his heart
but ties the game.
Wanna talk to him?
You go.
[crowd cheering]
[blows]
[exhales forcefully]
I'm just here
to give you a breather.
Uh-huh.
Joe says the game's yours.
So just try to relax
as best you can, hmm?
Mm.
If this guy's
gonna hurt you,
make him hurt you
on your pitch.
All right?
Mm.
All right.
[pats back]
[cheering continues]
It's great.
One out to go.
One out in the bottom
of the 9th for Gooden to get.
The left-hand hitting
Paul Sorrento,
and it'll be a one-two pitch,
with tying runs
at second and third.
Now Gooden is set.
The pitch.
He pops it up!
He's gonna do it!
Yes!
In short, left field!
Jeter back on the grass.
Back on the outfield grass,
waiting, looking.
Jeter makes the catch!
Yeah!
Dwight Gooden pitched
a no-hitter!
And the Yankees are mobbing
Gooden on the mound!
This team is going wild.
Dwight Gooden
with his first no-hitter
of his long,
illustrious career.
Remember, this is a guy
who suffered
in the depths of drugs,
and right now,
here in the grass,
he is sitting
on top of the world.
[crowd cheering]
[no audible dialogue]
[cheering fades out]
Last night,
Doc Gooden used baseball
the way I've used baseball
all my life.
It shuts everything else out.
There's the game,
right there in front of you,
and then there's everything else
you don't have to think about,
if you can only play
the game hard enough.
Hey, Zimmo?
Yeah?
Did you buy
these cigars for me?
Damn sure did.
I feel bad.
I've been telling everybody
you're a cheap bastard.
[laughter]
What's on your mind,
Duncan?
We play today, we win today.
Dassit.
[caller on radio] That's what
I've been telling you.
They got the right guy.
Slow start,
and he didn't panic.
Torre's a winner.
[radio show host]
You're next.
[caller #2]
I mean, Gooden's on fire.
He's on fire!
And what about Jeter, huh?
And Martinez?
Tony from Tenafly.
[Tony]
I don't know
how the guy done it,
but he got 'em
half a game out!
They take Cleveland
in this doubleheader,
they're in first place, man!
First place!
Look at this place.
How come we don't have
a place like this?
They won a league championship,
and we didn't.
All right, guys.
Hey, Mariano,
you got any thoughts today?
We play today,
and we win today.
Dassit. Twice.
[players whooping]
Let's go, man.
Let's go, guys.
Come on.
You see the washrooms?
They're fantastic.
Really?
Yeah.
[Announcer]
The Yankees need one out,
one out-- and they'll
go into first place
in this first game
of a doubleheader
against the Indians.
John Wetteland
trying to get that out.
And he has a one-two pitch
coming to Kenny Lofton.
Now Wetteland is set.
He deals.
Breaking ball hit on the ground
towards second.
Duncan backhands.
He throws.
In time! Ball game over.
Yankees win.
[cheering]
The Yankees win!
I told you
they'd be in first place.
Don't count your chickens.
It's a doubleheader.
Yeah! They haven't beaten
Cleveland all year.
There's always a first time.
What would you like
for dinner, honey?
You wanna go out?
You wanna cook something h--
Uh, honey?
Rocco?
That's what I wanna
see you keep doing.
No problem.
No, it's a problem,
because if you don't
keep reminding yourself of that,
you're gonna go back
to trying to pull everything.
Joe. Joe, Ali's on the phone.
Listen, I think I'm gonna
sit Paulie for the second game.
Yeah. You need to think
about Girardi too.
He took some bad foul tips.
Yeah.
Hi, sweetie.
What's up?
Joe, are you sitting down?
Frank?
It's Rocco, Joe.
He, uh--
He had a heart attack.
Christ.
What hospital is he in?
No hospital, Joe.
[phone clicks in cradle]
Roc...
we won the second game 9 to 3
behind Mendoza.
It was a blowout.
We're in first place.
This is the lineup card.
I wanted you to have it.
And all the guys
signed this.
I'm gonna win it this time.
Christ, I wanted you
to be there.
[knock on door]
Come in.
[door opens]
You wanted me, boss?
Where's Darryl Strawberry?
We didn't sign him.
You mean he's available?
I mean, he's out of baseball.
Nobody wanted him.
Find him.
What the hell am I
gonna do with him?
Who am I gonna sit down?
DH, I guess.
You could put him
in the outfield.
Hell, I don't know.
I got no room
for him, Zim.
Well, he was a hell
of a hitter.
We could sure use
some good offense now.
Can he still hit?
Do you know?
I don't know.
[chattering]
Hey, Darryl.
What's up, brother?
[laughs]
About time, cuz.
It's good to be here, Doc.
Hey, welcome to the zoo, man.
Welcome to the dark side, man.
You gonna do some banging
for us, huh?
Maybe later.
Right now I gotta
go see the man.
See you later, man.
See you later.
[chattering]
Hello, Darryl.
Hey, chief.
I just wanted to say
that I'm here to do
whatever you need me to do.
I appreciate that.
I don't know what
you've heard about me, but--
I've heard it all.
But I just wanted to say that--
Darryl, as far
as I am concerned,
history starts today.
[shaking hands]
Thanks, skipper.
[TV announcer]
The pitch.
Strawberry launches one!
[crowd cheering]
It is high, it is far!
It is gone!
A long home run
for Darryl Strawberry!
[radio show host]
You're on the air.
What do you wanna talk about?
[radio show caller]
I'll tell you what it is.
Joe Torre's got these guys
playing together like a team.
No stars, just a team.
You're up.
[caller #2] I'll tell you
what the difference is.
It's Joe Torre.
They're playing for this guy
the way he used to play.
[cheering fading out]
Rae, it's Joe.
What's happening?
I'm-- I'm worried sick, Joey.
I thought he was going
to the doctor.
He's gone to everybody--
this doctor, that doctor--
and it's getting
worse and worse.
I think-- I think
he just gave up, Joey.
Rocco dying seemed to just
take everything out of him.
You just listen to me, Rae.
We lost Rocco.
We are not gonna lose Frankie.
Do you hear me?
What's she doing?
Is she talking to Joey?
Mm.
What's she bothering him for?
Rae, put him on.
Tsk.
[sighs]
Hey, Joey.
What the hell
do you want from me?
I'm getting old, that's all.
There's nothing
anybody can do about it.
You are so stupid,
you know that, Frankie?
Hey, Joey, come on now.
I'm your older brother,
remember?
A little respect.
I show you respect.
But I'm not gonna
take it easy on you.
Did you ever take it easy on me?
When I was just
out of high school and no team
would take a look at me,
did you take it easy on me?
Joey.
Let me talk!
You made me take off the weight,
you made me into a catcher,
and it worked out good,
didn't it?
Yeah. What the hell
does that got to do with it?
It's got everything
to do with it.
You didn't let me quit,
and I'm not gonna let you quit.
No way. If the doctors
down there can't help you,
then you'll come up to New York.
We have the best doctors
in New York.
But I got nothing in the tank.
What the hell is the point?
The point is, I have lost
one brother this year,
and I am not gonna
lose another one.
[sighs]
[sirens wailing]
[radio show host]
Tony from Tenafly, you're up.
[Tony]
These guys are trying
to drive me crazy.
They sweep the Orioles,
they got a 12-and-a-half
game lead.
It's all over, right?
Wrong.
They lost five games
this week.
Here come the Orioles.
Unless these clowns
get their act together--
Sal from the Bronx,
you're on the air.
What's on your mind?
[Sal]
Hey, come on. What's
everybody panicking about?
They're still in first place,
ain't they?
Mm. Hi.
Hi.
I was trying
not to wake you up.
I've been waiting for you.
Yeah?
Come.
[sighs]
Tired?
Been a long time.
I've been on the road
too long.
Mmm.
Skip, it's just a strain.
He should be able to throw again
in ten days, maybe two weeks.
If we had to pick one guy
we couldn't afford to lose...
Yeah. No kidding.
Well, it's gonna
screw up the bullpen
for a couple of weeks,
but I think we can handle it.
They damn well
better handle it.
Okay.
[chattering]
[bat smacks ball]
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
[exclaims]
[crowd cheering]
What?
The Orioles
just tied it up.
Are we playing 'em?
No.
Then what do you care
what they do?
We were 12 games up.
Now it's only seven.
We are seven games up,
they are seven games down,
and we're the ones
who are worrying?
They must be about ready
to kill themselves.
[chuckling]
Hey, how you doing?
[Woman on P.A., indistinct]
Oh, there's Rae.
Where's Frankie?
[no audible dialogue]
Hey, Joey.
How are ya?
Good to see ya.
Hey, Joey.
[laughs]
How are ya, kid?
Hi.
How you doing?
How am I doing?
Eh, I don't know, Joey.
I don't know.
It's all right.
We're gonna get you fixed up,
okay? Okay.
Yeah?
Yeah. Come here.
Give him to me.
Hey, lookit...
We have him stabilized.
I wish I could tell you more,
but we don't know yet.
I'll be running
some tests tomorrow.
I'll have
some answers for you
in a couple of days.
Thank you.
♪♪ [rock]
[chattering]
Hey!
All right!
Hey, Doc.
Looking good, man.
[mutters]
Hey, Coney, you here
to save our asses, man?
[laughter]
Coney, Coney, Coney, Coney.
I miss you so much.
[laughter]
All right!
We got ourselves a Coney.
He's back.
He's back, and he's bad.
He's badder than ever.
♪♪ [continues]
What do you think of that?
Don't push it, Coney.
[grunts]
It's coming back, Joe.
I'll be back
before the season's over.
Five more minutes,
then shut it down.
What do you think?
Kid's got guts.
Is that a yes?
I don't know, Joe.
I don't know.
[TV announcer]
Left-hander Lloyd
on the mound.
Stares in for the sign.
Working out of the stretch,
he sets up the letters
and delivers.
[bat smacks ball]
[crowd cheering]
Driven deep
to right center field.
O'Neill giving chase.
And he pulls up.
[crowd groaning]
That's a ball that O'Neill
really should catch.
[crowd jeering]
[grunts]
Am I out?
You're hurting, Paulie.
I'm gonna put Ruben in.
Take the rest of the day off.
Paulie...
we got
a long way to go.
Your brother
needs a new heart.
A new heart?
Actually, Joe,
the surgery's the simplest part.
The hard part
is finding a donor.
We have to wait.
Well, how long
does that take?
There's no way to tell.
If we're lucky,
we could find one tomorrow,
but it really could take months.
What?
Two, three, five?
I'll be honest
with you, Sister.
I don't think your brother
has that much time.
You wanna talk about it?
Nothing to talk about,
really.
Not talking about it
won't make it go away, Joe.
No.
See, I was this little kid
from Brooklyn.
But it's like
I grew up too late.
My brothers and sisters
were already grown up.
And the house was a madhouse.
My father was always
hitting my mom.
You know that.
Scared the shit out of me.
You know the story
about how Frank threw him out?
He had a lot of guts.
He was everything
I wanted to be.
He was my hero.
He was a major leaguer.
He was in the World Series.
You will be too.
Yeah.
But here's the thing, Ali.
I get this shot
out of nowhere...
and just as I'm
about to get there,
my brothers...
Rocco won't be there,
and probably Frank
won't be there.
It's like I wake up
out of one nightmare,
and I'm in the middle
of another one.
Let's go to bed.
Come on.
Joe, Paulie's all upset
about that piece Al Post did
on his radio show last night.
Said you benched him
for not hustling after
that ball in the 7th.
Post is a son of a bitch.
Yeah, but you're gonna
have to talk to Paul.
I'll talk to Paulie,
and I'll do more than that.
[laughing]
Al, where'd you get
the information for that piece
you ran last night?
Well, I, uh, covered
a lot of stuff last night.
Relief-pitching home runs
are way down.
I talked about that.
Don't get cute with me.
You know what I'm talking about.
No. Tell me.
I benched Paulie O'Neill.
That's what you said.
Yeah, I know.
I was watching the game, Joe.
You took him out, I didn't.
Don't mess with me!
I don't appreciate you
trying to stir up something
in this clubhouse.
Well, he could've caught
the ball on the fly.
Instead, he one-hops it.
Next inning,
you sent Rivera out to play.
Now, tell me,
what part of that
did I get wrong?
Except for sending Rivera out,
all of it.
The next time you wanna talk
about why I did something,
you come to me and you ask me,
and I'll tell you.
Paulie O'Neill is playing
on legs that would
have you lying in bed,
moaning for somebody
to bring you soup.
He's out there every day
busting his ass!
And if it weren't for him,
we wouldn't be in first place.
You understand?
He's a team player.
That's something
you would know nothing about!
I took him out
'cause I could see his legs
were hurting, and I need him
the rest of the way!
Those are the facts!
And if you were
doing your job,
you'd have got it right
before you went on the air!
That's it right there.
Tell him, Coach.
[chattering]
So, what do you hear
from Steinbrenner?
He's gotta be on your case
now that Baltimore's back in it.
I hear nothing.
That's worse.
Why is it worse?
He already decided
to fire you.
I know it.
[chuckles]
Frankie, the last time
that Joe Torre was fired,
he was finished.
It was over, done.
This thing is all
a big gift to me.
They give you an extra life,
and you live it
as long as you can.
And then when it's over,
it's over.
What the hell
are you talking about,
managing the Yankees
or a heart transplant?
[chuckling]
Joey.
[radio show caller]
The last thing this team needs
is playing the Mariners
in Seattle.
Ever since
the play-offs last year,
those guys hate each other.
They just hate each other.
Come on, man.
That was last year.
They're out
to get us every year.
If they throw at
another one of our hitters--
"Hitters"? Me.
They throw at my head
every time I go up there.
Man, what you
gonna do about that?
[TV announcer]
O'Neill gets knocked down.
[crowd groaning]
It happened again.
Seattle has done this
repeatedly to Paul O'Neill.
And he gets up.
He doesn't like it a bit.
The umpire gets between O'Neill
and the Seattle catcher.
[crowd shouting]
Now they go at it.
O'Neill knocks him down.
And the benches
start to empty, Mike.
We're gonna have a brawl.
[Mike]
We are gonna have a brawl.
It's going to be nasty too.
These two teams
hate each other.
They've hated each other
for a long time.
That's awful.
Sometimes that's all
a team needs to get fired up.
Something better
get them fired up.
They've lost four in a row.
Hey, do you have to remind me?
That's not good
for my heart condition.
Oh.
[thud]
[chattering]
What the hell is this, huh?
They throw at us,
and we do nothing to them!
Relax, man.
Wasn't his fault.
Oh, no?
Our pitchers
have to protect us.
Come on, man.
There was nothing he could do.
He got warned.
Warned? They throw
at Paul O'Neill twice,
and you don't do nothing!
[overlapping shouting]
The enemy is out there!
On the ball field!
[door opens, closes]
[chattering]
Oh, she walked?
[laughs]
Yeah, well-- Oh, I see.
Held onto the wall,
but it's still walking, right?
Yeah.
Ali, I love you so much.
These road trips
are just tough.
They're tough.
I miss you.
I miss you two.
All right.
Kiss her for me.
I love you.
Talk to you tomorrow.
Bye.
The pitch.
Hit on the ground
toward short.
Jeter boots it.
Fields, fires low and wide.
Past Duncan
to shallow right field.
Two runs will score
for the A's.
And the Yankees are
playing terrible baseball.
Okay. Let's go,
you bathing beauties.
Joe wants to talk to you.
[chattering]
What's going on?
All right.
Run your ass, boys.
It's not gonna be pretty.
[scoffs]
All right.
We have
a two-and-a-half game lead,
and we are gonna win this thing.
That's not a guess.
That's not a promise.
That is a fact.
We are gonna win this thing.
And I wanna tell you
how proud I am of each
and every damn one of you.
Go and get some dinner.
I don't wanna see
any one of you here sooner
sooner than an hour and a half
before tomorrow's game.
No batting practice.
Damn straight
we gonna win it.
New York Yankees!
Come on!
Yeah!
All the way to October!
[chattering]
Charlie Hayes?
That's the best you can do?
He's a solid third baseman.
He's got a little pop
in his bat.
He's got ten home runs.
Boggs is tired.
His legs is bothering him.
His back is bothering him.
He's not driving the ball.
We need help at third.
The Orioles just
signed Eddie Murray.
Eddie Murray
is a great ballplayer.
He's got 3,000 hits,
1,500 RBI's,
500 home runs.
And I'm just looking
for a good, solid ballplayer
who can play third base.
You're the general manager.
I don't need a statement, Bull,
just a confirmation or a denial.
If you wanna talk,
let's talk about the trade.
Charlie Hayes?
We got that.
That's yesterday's news.
Klapisch is citing
an anonymous source
in the Bergen Record
that says that George
has decided to replace you.
I am still here, aren't I?
Isn't my statement enough?
So you're denying it.
You say you're not
gonna be fired.
I don't think about that.
The club's still in first place.
The lead's down
to two and a half.
It is still a lead, isn't it?
That is still first place.
What happens if you fall
out of first place?
If we blow a 12-game lead,
then we deserve to be fired,
Joe Torre and I.
You don't blame the passengers
when the plane crashes.
We fly the plane.
[overlapping questions]
It's over there.
[car horn honking]
[Ali]
Hey!
Hey, guys, I'll catch up
with you later, okay?
Hi.
How are you?
What are you doing here?
Well, I had to
get out of the house.
The phone is ringing
off the hook.
What phone?
What are you talking about?
You haven't
seen the papers?
No.
Not only is George firing us,
but we're gonna fire ourselves.
[laughing continues]
I'm not gonna talk about that.
Do you wanna talk baseball?
I'll talk baseball.
Just one thing, Joe.
Did you talk to Watson?
Did he clear
that statement with you?
That's two things,
and it's not baseball.
I gotta check on some people.
[overlapping chatter]
Hey, Joe.
Off the record, if you want.
How's your brother?
I've got an aunt
in the same hospital.
How's he doing?
He's okay.
He's in good spirits.
He's got a bad heart.
Clock is ticking.
[chattering]
[bat smacks ball]
[players exclaiming]
♪♪ [rock]
Talk to you a minute,
Boggsy?
Take it easy, man.
Charlie Hayes is coming in
this afternoon.
He was playing
out on the coast.
I want you to know
that you're my third baseman.
Right.
It's not a platoon thing.
I'm gonna give him
a little playing time
because I know you're tired.
We got a month to go,
and then the play-offs.
You okay with this?
Oh, don't worry about me.
It's not like that, Boggsy.
We're just trying to give you
a little rest.
We're gonna need you
in the stretch.
[player]
Wait up!
Hey, Ray.
Would you help me carry
this bat out to the field?
I'm a little too tired
to take it myself.
[chattering]
[crowd clapping rhythmically]
[chanting]
Let's go, Yankees!
[clapping]
[mutters]
Let's go, Yankees!
[Man]
Hey, Joe!
[crowd]
We're praying for Frankie!
We all are, Joe.
Thanks.
I kept telling myself,
"This time I got the horses.
"This time I'm gonna do it.
"All right.
The lead is cut down,
but that's okay.
We're gonna hold on."
But it really wasn't
until this week
when I began...
[snoring]
It's so up and down.
Some days he seems
so much better.
I'm afraid there'll be fewer
and fewer of those days, Joe.
There's gotta be something
we can do.
We can't do anything
until we locate
a suitable heart.
What are we gonna do,
just watch him slip away?
That can't be right.
There's gotta be something
we can do.
We're looking for
a healthy heart in a person
who has just died.
That doesn't happen
every day.
Well, how long can he wait?
If we're lucky,
if he's lucky,
maybe a month.
Any pain?
None.
David Cone checks in
to get the sign.
Now off the stretch, he deals.
Struck him out!
Looking great.
He has great movement
for a guy who's been out
three months.
Eighty pitches?
Eighty, ninety.
Somewhere in there.
No more than that.
He knows?
He knows.
Cone checking the sign.
He'll deal
to Terry Steinbach 2-2.
The pitch.
Struck him out swinging!
Is this an incredible story
or what?
Can you believe this guy?
Hasn't pitched in three months,
and look at him.
Yeah, I believe him.
I've known him a long time.
[Announcer]
Two outs in the 6th.
Cone deals Larado.
Cut and a miss
by Terry Steinbach.
He struck him out again.
[2nd announcer]
Mike, do you believe this?
How great Cone is pitching?
I'll tell you what:
this is bad fiction.
Three months ago,
you had to wonder if
the guy was going to live--
he had an aneurysm,
and now he's on the mound
for the first time,
and he's pitching
a no-hitter!
You really have to
wonder, though,
how long does
Joe Torre let him go?
Sixty.
[Announcer]
Two out, bottom of
the seventh inning,
Cone pitching
a brilliant game,
his first game back
from aneurysm surgery.
He stares in
for the sign, sets,
and deals to Berroa.
Swung on and hit deep
to center field.
Bernie Williams on the run.
Going back, on the track.
At the wall, he leaps,
and what a play
by Bernie Williams!
And he keeps
the no-hitter alive!
Am I done?
You're at 85, Coney.
You're done for today.
You know it is possible
I could have a quick 8th.
Even if you do,
you won't pitch the 9th.
You know I never pitched
a no-hitter before.
You leave it up to me,
I'm going back out there.
It's your call.
Get Mariano warmed up
for the 8th.
Coney, great game.
Good one, Coney.
Good job, Coney.
Way to go, Coney.
Coney! Good job, man.
These guys are gonna
win it all. I know it.
[Announcer]
A packed house
at Yankee Stadium,
and the Yankees need
one more win
to clinch the American League
East championship,
and Mike, it would be
the first time in 15 years
the Yankees would
have won a pennant.
[Mike]
And these fans
are starved for it.
The Yankees always
used to win, and now
there's been a long stretch,
a lot of dry land,
between the last time
and now.
The pitch to Fernando Viña
is popped up to center field!
Bernie Williams is there.
Bernie... makes the catch!
And the New York Yankees
have won the 1996
Eastern Division championship.
And the team is around
Jeff Nelson.
[announcers fade]
[cries, laughs]
[wild cheering]
All right.
Yeah.
Ali, it's like someone's
playing a joke on me.
I used to think,
if I wanted it hard enough--
but that never worked.
So I say,
"Give me another chance.
Just one more chance."
And now that
it's almost there,
it's like they're saying,
"How much do
you want it, Joe?
Take your brother away?"
Oh, Joe, it's not like that.
You know that!
[cheers, whistles]
♪♪ [country]
[chuckles]
Hey, come on, guys.
We're not here to talk about me.
I'm just a guy
with a bum ticker.
If you want me to talk, you
want to talk about my brother.
I mean, we just won
the first round of the playoffs!
How 'bout that?
That was great baseball.
Tremendous baseball!
[cheering]
[radio announcer]
Sal from the Bronx,
you're on the air!
What's on your mind?
[Sal]
Fielder, Jeter, Bernie,
O'Neill--
No way the Orioles
can beat these guys!
[loud cheers]
Do you know
what I believe?
Do you want to know what
I believe in my heart?
When that boy
touched that ball,
that was my brother Rocco
reaching down to help Joey.
[Rae]
So, what can I tell ya?
Joey made 'em
into a real team.
Not just a bunch of
strangers playin' a game,
but-but people.
[cheering]
[Announcer]
Yankees lead 9-3, 2 out,
bottom of the 9th,
and Cal Ripken up.
For the Yankees, it all
comes down to one out.
If they win, they go
to the World Series
for the first time
in 19 years.
For Joe Torre, he'll go
to the World Series
for the first time
in his long, 36-year career
as player and manager.
What a moment for Joe:
his brother Frank,
the memory of
his brother Rocco.
One out to go,
Wetteland deals--
Ripken hits
a ground ball to short.
Jeter fields, throws--
low and dug out by Martinez!
In time!
And the Yankees win!
The Yankees win!
The New York Yankees
have won the American
League championship,
and they're on their way
to the World Series.
Doctor. How are you doing?
Congratulations.
You got to find him a heart!
Yeah, Joey's been MVP,
but, uh,
he's never been on
a world champion team,
either as a player
or as a manager,
so he's waited
a hell of a long time.
Makes it all the sweeter,
believe me. [chuckles]
[New Yorker #1] The Yanks!
The second-best thing in my
life, next to marrying my wife.
[New Yorker #2]
It's the best!
It's a dream come true!
It's fantastic!
The Yanks are back!
They're back!
Sweep! Four games!
All over! Gone!
[TV announcer]
Here we are in game one
of the World Series,
and the Yankees
are getting clobbered.
The Bomber bats
are asleep tonight,
and Atlanta is on fire!
[Yankee crowd booing]
[ball hits pole]
[Steinbrenner]
We're up against
Maddux tomorrow.
Do these guys
know what this is?
Thirty million people, and
we get our butts kicked, 12-0.
Ten.
That's not just losing.
People lose.
This is being humiliated.
Hello, George.
[sighs] They tell me
that's the worst clubbing
in World Series history.
Yeah, it was pretty ugly.
[deep sigh]
Tomorrow's a must game, Joe.
Tomorrow we will probably lose.
But then, we'll go to Atlanta
and sweep three,
and clinch it
here on Saturday.
Judas Priest.
[TV announcer]
Well, the Yankees
come down to Atlanta
trailing the World Champion
Braves two games to none,
about to face the best
pitching staff in baseball
in their own back yard.
[Stadium announcer]
...the American League Champion
New York Yankees...
number six, Joe Torre!
[cheering]
[TV announcer]
Swung on by Leyritz, and
driven to deep left field.
Jones back to the track,
he's at the wall,
he leaps, and it's gone!
Bernie heading home,
he slides, he scores!
Right center field, Grissom...
drops the ball!
He dropped the ball!
Drilled to deep right field.
It is high! It is far!
It is gone!
Another...
[fading]
Like you said, Joe.
We're taking the series home.
[laughing]
You taste it, Joe?
I can taste it.
We play day after tomorrow,
we win day after tomorrow.
Dass it!
Hey, what are you?
A wizard or something?
That's exactly what you said!
Sorry, I didn't see you on--
No, I was just trying
to reach my brother.
There's no answer in his room.
Maybe his phone's just turned
off. Try the switchboard.
I'm afraid to.
[Ali] Great win, Joe.
Congratulations!
You did it! I just knew...
[beeps]
[Frank]
You did it, Joey.
You did it.
Congratulations, kid.
Joey, I'm gonna do it too.
They found a heart.
[sensors beeping]
[motor chugging]
Hey. Joey, Joey.
Joey!
I need...
six tickets
for tonight's game.
Um, I would, but I didn't
think you were gonna make it,
so I sold 'em.
[laughs, winces]
[laughing]
[TV announcer]
There is no greater setting
for a World Series
than Yankee Stadium.
The Yankees have won
22 World Championships
and they are poised
for number 23
in front of a jam-packed
Yankee Stadium crowd.
This is really
the Home Office for baseball.
[crowd going wild]
It's all set up right here,
the Yankees are one out away.
[2nd TV announcer]
One out away, but Wetteland
has a tough out,
with the tying and
go-ahead runs on base.
Facing Mark Lemke.
It'll be a 2-2 pitch
to Lemke,
as Wetteland deals--
popped him up!
Off-third foul!
Does Hayes have a play?
Hayes toward the dugout--
Hayes reaching in...
and he can't make the catch!
As Hayes falls down
in the Braves' dugout.
[crowd groans]
The Yankees were
three inches away
from winning
the World Series!
Now Lemke gets
another crack at it.
Well, that's
baseball etiquette.
Nobody was
helping Charlie Hayes
in that Braves' dugout,
and now they have to do it
all over again.
That guy can give you
a heart attack.
Hector, would you
shut the hell up!
I'm sorry.
[TV announcer]
What drama. They were so close,
a couple of inches away,
and they would have
won the World Series,
and now Wetteland has to
throw at least one more pitch.
[player]
Come on, Johnny!
Ten years ago,
I was one out away from
winning the World Series, Dunc.
I can't take it,
I can't take it!
Give it to him!
Come on!
What do you think?
He's gonna get him out
with this next pitch.
And Wetteland deals to Lemke--
swing, and he popped him up!
Get it, son, get it!
The ball's in foul territory.
Will this one stay in play?
Hayes, waiting.
Charlie Hayes waiting
for the ball to come down.
[cheering]
Yeaahhhh!