(crickets chirping)
(deep tense music)
(dogs barking in distance)
(slow eerie music)
- [Vivian] Don't worry, Zach.
(slow mysterious lullaby music)
(Zach coos)
See, Zach, everything's okay.
Yeah.
(slow mysterious music)
Sh, sh-sh.
(glass shatters)
Aaron?
- [Aaron] Almost done.
(slow mysterious music)
(creature growls)
(slashing) (Zach
squeals, cries)
(mirror shatters)
(haunting music)
- Zach?
(gasps)
Oh, god.
No! (sobbing)
No! (screaming)
(gentle mysterious
lullaby music)
(creaking)
(Papo cooing)
- [John] Opa.
Oh, yeah.
Okay. Hey.
- [Rachel] There it
is, my little prince,
it's your kingdom.
Here we go.
(gentle inspiring music)
Hey, buddy, this is your room.
Hm.
(Eli cooing)
Yeah, these are all
your new friends.
You gonna say, "Hello, jaguar.
Hello, alligator.
Hello, giraffe."
Oy.
Asleep.
- You ever have one
of those moments,
just like you imagined it?
(knocking at door)
- This little kid
sleeps through anything.
(chuckles)
(cooing)
- Hi, uh, Schoenberg?
- It's Guerrero.
Ah, yeah.
It's my mother-in-law,
that explains it.
Schoenberg's my wife's
maiden name. I can sign.
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah.
- There you go.
- Great. Thank you.
- Oh.
All right.
Hey, Papo, wanna
say hi to baby Eli?
Hey, Papo, look.
It's your little brother.
Yeah.
That's Eli.
We gotta look after him, yeah.
- It was my sister's stuff.
- Toys that, uh,
belonged to a baby who...
- Who died.
- I'm not superstitious,
I'm just saying.
You know, what
happened to her son,
and the whole accident
with her husband.
(Papo squawks) (Eli cries)
What happened? Papo
scare you, huh?
Oh, come on, let's get you
over here, put you down.
Okay? Yeah.
(Eli cooing)
(ticking clock echoes)
Papo's a friend, Eli.
It's okay. (Eli coos)
Yeah, it's all right, buddy.
(book creaks)
(ticking clock slows down)
- Got your ear.
- Oh, my god.
- And I
got your nose.
- Look at this.
It's got writing on it.
It's got music.
It's Hebrew.
All right, Hebrew school,
let's put you to work.
(John chuckles)
- Got jokes, all right.
- Yeah, come on.
See what you got.
- Um...
(John speaks Hebrew)
It's like a prayer, but not.
Hm.
Hang on, I got-I got
something for that.
(Papo squawking)
- That's good.
You need a cheat sheet.
See, you probably don't
even speak Hebrew.
I think I need to
call my mother.
- Wow, wow, I mean, I think
what you mean to say is
thank you, my love, for
getting my mother off our backs
and proving your undying
love for me and Judaism
by converting, maybe?
- Thank you, my love.
- Mm-hm.
- What was it again?
Ah, look, here it is.
It's a zemer. Yeah.
- Right.
(clears throat) It's a zemer.
- Mm-hm, zemer, it's like
a hymn, a religious song,
also like a lullaby.
It's actually beautiful.
- It's classic Vivian.
- Can you make out the tune?
- Um...
(Rachel vocalizing)
(telephone rings)
Okay, we don't need a lullaby.
Hello.
Thank you.
Yeah, he came out so
cute, the little munchkin.
I can't even tell you,
he's like a perfect
little soufflé.
Um, hey, so, right...
Where are we on reservations?
(gentle somber music)
You think this is too easy?
- We got this.
- You know, I bet I won't
even need the full month.
(Eli crying)
- Oh.
(car horns honk)
(Eli crying)
- Please, Eli, just work it out.
- Okay, I'll take him so
you can, uh, get ready.
Come on, buddy.
I'm, oh, let me get this first.
- I know. I know.
- There we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
All right now.
(Eli crying)
- Yeah.
- I can't do this.
I can't... Look at me,
I'm a freaking mess.
I can't, I can't, I
can't go in like this.
I've had, what, 45
minutes sleep this week?
- Okay, all right.
- I can't, I can't do it.
- How can I help?
- I don't know. The
restaurant was also my baby.
(Eli fussing)
I just feel like it's
slipping through my fingers.
(Eli fussing)
- Okay. (Eli coughing)
Okay. Okay. Up, up.
- Oh.
- Up, up, up.
- Hey.
- Rach, love,
I saw you build that
restaurant, okay?
- Yeah.
- It's not going anywhere, okay?
- I know.
- You're amazing.
- Well, I'm amazing at that
'cause I know how to do it.
I just, I don't
know how to do this
and that at the same time.
(Eli fussing)
- I have no doubt.
(Rachel sighs)
Oh.
Okay, look, um, I'll
call the gallery.
I'll tell the guys,
oh, you got my...
Did you get my nose now?
I'll let them know that
I'm gonna stay home.
- I'm not even gonna...
- It'll be me and you.
- No. No.
- Yeah, me and Eli.
- No, no, you can't.
This is your biggest
exhibition ever, baby.
- Oh. (Eli cries)
- You gotta go to the gallery
and make sure your psychedelic
chicken is on point.
- It's a phoenix.
- Well, you know,
at least one of us
can rise from the
ashes. (John chuckles)
I'm gonna stay with you.
- We're gonna work it out.
- Yeah? You sure?
- I got pretty close to getting
out the door today, buddy.
- You did. You certainly did.
- I did. I got close.
- I did.
- You'll need that.
- We're gonna work
it out, buddy.
Get outta here. Get out
before it's too late.
- Okay.
- Hi.
- All right, we a team,
we a team, we a team.
- We a team, we a team.
Yeah, we totally a team.
We got it. Oh, god.
(Eli crying) Yeah.
I, uh, I thought we
agreed on white truffles.
- [Woman On Phone] What?
- On white truffles. Sh, sh.
Yep, but you're
still gonna sit down.
You can cry about it.
Hi. Hey, baby.
Oh, this one, oh, look,
it's fun, it's fun.
Be happy. (Eli cries)
Look, look at the bird.
Look at the bird. Yeah.
(Papo squawks)
(Eli cries)
It's okay.
Look. (clapping)
You wanna clap?
You wanna do this?
I just need five minutes, okay?
Okay?
You're a good guy. Yeah.
You're a good guy.
(Eli cries)
Please, I just need to poop.
Eli.
(Eli cries)
No, don't eat that,
don't eat that.
No, don't eat that. No.
That's right.
We're gonna... Oh.
Okay.
Okay, we've got this.
Clean?
Vivian, Vivian. Vivian?
Oh, Vivian.
Thank you, sis.
Gold up in here. (Eli cries)
There's some gold up in here.
What is that?
Look, what's that?
(Eli wailing)
(wailing continues)
Stopped crying.
It works.
(Eli fusses)
Is that a little bit of drool?
(foot thuds)
(soft eerie music)
(indistinct distant whispering)
Oh...
Johnny.
(Eli crying)
(Papo squawks)
Sh, sh, sh.
(Eli crying)
(Rachel sings softly)
(Eli stops crying)
(Eli cries)
(Rachel sings softly)
(Eli stops crying)
(mirror cracks)
(Rachel sings softly)
(crickets chirping)
Baby,
you did it.
I love you so much.
(wind howling)
(ghostly voices whisper)
(door latch opens)
(John sighs)
Hey, honey.
Can you hear that?
- I hear...
absolutely nothing.
- Not a peep.
Not a snort.
Not for hours.
(John sighs)
It was the lullaby.
- Ah, your, uh,
your sister's book.
- Mm-hm.
- So, you were able to
read my translations?
- Mm-hm.
It, I don't know, it
put him right to sleep.
(both sigh)
- Thank you.
- How is this even possible?
You just got in the door.
- Ah, baby puke.
It's inevitable.
(towel snaps)
Hmm.
(gentle mysterious
lullaby music)
(zipper opens)
Oh, uh, your dress is unzipped.
- Really?
Oops.
(gentle mysterious
lullaby music)
(baby monitor buzzing softly)
(baby monitor crackles)
(scary startling music)
(tense haunting music)
(door squeaks)
(deep tense music)
(baby monitor crackling)
(baby monitor thuds)
(Papo squawks)
(metal grinding, tinkling)
(Papo squawking)
(knock)
John?
(Papo squawks)
(Papo squawking)
(steady knocking)
(tense scary music)
(exterior door
handle ratcheting)
(Rachel gasps)
Fuck this.
(mirror cracking)
(soft eerie music)
(Rachel groans)
Mom face.
Great. (mirror cracking)
(Papo squawking)
(tense suspenseful music)
(birds chirping)
(water splashing)
(shower door opens)
Guess who's still asleep?
- Elias Samson Guerrero?
- Yep.
- What a good boy.
- Yeah.
(Crone growls)
- Shit!
(scary music)
Rach.
- It's fine.
(sighs)
- Look, I'm sorry. I saw...
- You don't have to apologize.
You had an honest reaction,
that's just life.
It's what happens.
- Hey, no, look...
Wait a minute.
- We need a new baby monitor.
I'm gonna be back soon.
(door shuts)
- Hey, Papo.
Hey, buddy. (Papo squawks)
Hi.
Yeah.
Hey.
How you doin', bud? Yeah.
I know. Yeah, hello.
You're not mad at me, are you?
Look at yourself.
(Papo squawks)
(speaks Spanish)
What is that?
(Papo squawks)
Huh.
(people chattering)
(monitors crackling)
(creature growls)
(echoing knock)
- Okay, let's get outta here.
Hello?
(Rachel breathes heavily)
(scary music)
(Rachel cries out)
- Are you okay?
(haunting music)
(mirror cracking)
(Papo yells)
(thunder claps)
- Stupid bird, I swear to you...
(Papo squawking)
I'm gonna make a
pillow outta you.
(Papo squawking)
(baby cries in distance)
(thunder crashes)
(electricity buzzes)
(baby crying in distance)
(panting)
(thunder rumbles in distance)
(baby crying)
(Rachel shudders)
(Rachel gasps)
(Rachel whimpers)
(Rachel gasping)
(door creaks open)
(scary boom) (Rachel gasps)
- Hey. Hey.
Hey, what-what's wrong? What
happened? What happened?
- There's, I think
there's someone,
there's someone in
the apartment. I...
- What do you...
What do you mean?
- So, so, okay, so
there was a blackout,
and then I...
There, I think there's
something or someone, I...
- Did you call the police?
- No, I didn't. I... I didn't.
(thunder claps)
(Papo squawking)
(thunder rumbles)
(Papo talks indistinctly)
- Hello?
- [Papo] Hello.
(Papo squawking)
(thunder crackles)
- If someone's in
here, come out.
(metal rattles)
Hey!
(Papo squawks)
(thunder crashes)
- [Rachel] Baby,
is everything okay?
- Yeah.
Stay in the hall.
(Papo squawking)
(thunder rumbles)
(John breathing heavily)
(Papo squawks) (John grunts)
(Papo thuds)
(John gasps)
Oh, god.
Oh, shit, no.
No, Papo. No, no, no.
Papo. No.
My mom got him for me.
Had him since I was 11.
- I'm so sorry,
baby. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- Don't be.
It's not your fault.
I did it.
(eerie music)
(John sighs)
- I, I'm...
I'm not okay.
I'm trying really,
really hard to be okay,
but I think I'm not
okay, I think I'm...
I think I'm actually
losing my mind.
I mean, Vivian lost her mind,
she tucked her dead baby
into his crib for,
like, two weeks.
- Rach, you're not Vivian, okay?
You know, we're just...
stressed.
Parents of a newborn baby.
- I'm seeing things.
I'm seeing this woman,
this old,
hag witch woman
in the darkness, in the mirror,
in the freaking baby
store. I'm going...
(chair clatters)
Well, I suppose, wife's
going bat-shit crazy,
that's how I'd react too.
- No, Rach,
you are not going crazy.
Did you see... Is
that what you saw?
Did you see something like that?
- That's her. That's her.
- Yeah, okay.
The other morning,
in the shower,
same creepy image
got in my head.
- Right.
So, we're just, what, like...
sleep-deprived,
freaking cabin fever...
- Yeah, probably.
Most likely. Yeah.
- But that's not
what you believe.
No, you, no.
We're seeing... Come
on, we're seeing...
- Look, Rach, I believe
in us. Okay, that's all.
Whatever this is,
whatever's happening,
we're gonna get through this.
Together, okay?
We a team.
- Yeah.
Yeah, we a team.
- Yeah, and this is
going where it belongs.
- Yeah.
And Eli's sleeping
with us tonight.
(baby crying)
- Baby's crying.
(John sighs)
I'll get it.
I'll get it. You sleep.
(tense suspenseful music)
(baby crying)
Okay. Okay, buddy.
(door closes)
(baby crying)
I'm comin', Eli.
I'm comin'.
(baby crying)
(door slams shut)
Eli?
(baby crying)
Eli? Eli!
What the...?
(baby stops crying)
- Hey, hey! (scary bang)
You steal from me, man.
That's bad karma, man.
(door clicks open)
That's bad juju!
(door clicks shut)
(slow mysterious music)
(Eli crying)
- Hey, do you have
an alarm snooze...
Snooze button here?
(Eli crying)
(Rachel sings softly)
(ghostly voice echoes)
(eerie music)
Eli?
(baby crying)
Eli, Eli.
Eli. (scary whooshing)
(baby cries)
Eli.
(baby crying)
(scary music) (Rachel screams)
(panting)
(Rachel gasps loudly)
My baby, my baby, my baby.
(Rachel laughs with relief)
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- You gonna be okay?
- Absolutely.
We're long overdue
for some father-son
bonding time anyway, right?
In the meantime,
Eli, he says he wants
you to relax, okay?
- Okay. Thanks Eli.
- All right, bud, here we go.
Opa. (sighs)
- Let me get that.
Okay. I love you.
- I love you more.
Bye.
(slow haunting music)
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Vivian Brown,
please. I'm her sister.
(birds chirping)
(door clicks open)
- Hey, John.
And the little monster. Hi.
Hey. Hi. (laughs)
What's happened?
(exhales sharply)
Do Jews have exorcists?
- Come. Sit.
(slow somber music)
(John sighs)
(birds chirping)
- Hey, Viv.
(slow somber music)
- Hi, Rachel.
- Can I sit?
- Of course.
- Rachel's sister,
Vivian,
came to me with the same story,
the same questions.
- Vivian did?
What did you tell her?
(scoffs)
You thought she was crazy.
- Mom sent your
stuff, from storage.
- No. No, no. No, no.
I locked that stuff up.
Mom...
Mama should not have done that.
- I found the lullaby book.
- Did you sing from it?
Rachel, listen to me.
Zachary was taken.
I sang that song, and she came
and she took him.
- Who came?
Who is she?
- Lilith.
- Lilith
was the first woman
made by God to be Adam's wife.
- They would lie together
in Eden,
and he would sing her a song.
It was their special song.
And whenever Lilith
heard that song
she'd come running.
She loved Adam,
but she was a strong woman
and she refused to submit.
- The legend says
she was banished from the
Garden of Eden by God.
She roamed the wilderness.
She lay with wolves.
And gave birth to her own
race of imperfect creations.
- Deformed,
hungry, half human, half...
Half something else.
Lilith saw Adam and Eve
and their perfect babies,
and then she looked at
her own broken children.
And that's when she started
stealing their children.
Our children.
- And so it went
for generations,
until God listened
to the prayers of
Adam's progeny,
and he sent her
to the underworld.
- You know the word lullaby
comes from Lilith-abi.
It means "Lilith begone."
Mothers sing lullabies
to keep Lilith away.
But Lilith, (chuckles)
Lilith took her and Adam's song,
their special song,
and she twisted it.
She turned it into a lullaby
that does the opposite.
It summons her.
I sang that song,
and she came.
She took my Zachary,
and that corpse they found
that had been dead for who
knows how long, that...
That was not my son.
I can help you, Rachel.
I can help Eli.
I need to help Eli.
- How?
- You have to get me
the fuck outta here.
- Rabbi, this woman, Lilith...
- She's a myth.
What I'm telling
you are legends,
fables used for
lessons and guidance.
- Yeah, I know,
that's why I'm here.
Lilith, she's in your
stories, your fables.
(scoffs)
I'm telling you,
something's happening.
- And I wanna help.
- Then help.
There has to be something.
A-a-a prayer you can give
me. I don't know, something.
- That isn't how
our religion works.
- Is this what you told Vivian
when she came to you
looking for answers?
- There was nothing I could do.
(Rabbi Simowitz sighs)
(John sighs)
(eerie music)
(music fades out)
- Rach, we're home.
Hey, bud.
What do you say we
get out of that, huh?
And now we go opa.
Oh, yeah, we're not gonna
forget this thing, right?
Yeah. (chuckles)
Yeah, huh? Rach?
(water splattering)
Shit.
Okay, buddy, I need
you to hang here, okay?
Opa. There we go.
You have the toy.
Okay? Just for second.
Shit.
(faucet squeaks)
(door bangs shut)
(deep foreboding music)
(Eli babbling)
(Quad Lilim gurgling)
(Eli giggles)
(Eli babbles)
(Quad Lilim grunts)
(Eli giggles)
(glass shatters)
Shit.
(water splattering)
(soft haunting music)
(glass clinks)
(dramatic boom)
(tense music)
(Eli screams)
- What, you just...
you left him?
- What?
No, I just-I just put
him down for a second.
The-the bathroom...
Is he okay?
Vivian.
- They're here.
(eerie music)
Lilith's servants.
We cover mirrors after funerals
so our departed loved
ones don't stare at us
from the afterlife.
So it is with Lilith.
I thought that breaking
the mirrors would work,
but this is better.
This is right.
- Right.
- Isn't she supposed to
be in the psych ward?
- Maybe.
- [John] So you thought
it was a good idea
to bring your crazy sister here?
- [Rachel] Don't talk
about her like that.
- [John] Maybe this wasn't a
fire that needs gasoline, Rach.
- [Rachel] I just
thought after everything
we've been through and
experienced and, you know,
the book was hers.
She-she-she lost it.
- Exactly. She lost.
She lost her baby.
She lost her husband.
She lost her mind.
- I didn't lose my baby.
That thing we buried
was not my child.
Lilith took my little boy
and her Crone killed my husband.
- I thought a
mirror fell on him.
- You don't have the
luxury of skepticism, John.
Not anymore.
You sang her song,
and now she is coming for Eli.
- What's the plan here?
I mean, but how... How
do we protect our son?
- Don't take your eyes off him.
And if you see her Crone,
run.
(telephone rings)
Come with me.
Let's finish.
- Hello?
- [Man On Phone] I
understand you have a book.
- Who is this?
- [Man On Phone] Your rabbi
said you need help, John.
Get a pen.
- You're leaving?
- There's something
I have to do.
- Don't worry.
We'll keep Eli safe.
(Elevator arrival chime)
(engages lock)
I see congratulations
are in order.
- With everything going on, I...
I don't think I've
even told Johnny.
That came so easy.
(Eli fusses)
- What is it?
- No, this thought just
comes into my head sometimes.
I don't even wanna
say it out loud.
It's a horrible,
horrible thought.
What if this is the
universe's way of telling me
I'm not fit to be a mom?
No, Rachel, no.
Don't you dare question that.
This, this is exactly
what she does.
She gets inside your head,
makes you ask if you
deserve to be Eli's mother,
makes you lose faith.
You can't let her
take that bond away.
You are his mother and
you always will be.
I always loved this lamp.
I'm glad you kept it.
- Hey, where did the
lullaby book come from?
- Nowhere exciting.
Little antique shop in
West Nowheresville, Maine.
- Why didn't you throw it away?
- Because it's real.
Because it proves what happened.
(deep somber music)
(horn honks)
- It's Shabbes.
- Oh, right, yeah.
I'm sorry.
Uh, I'm looking...
Looking for this address.
- The Dybbuk Man.
(other man spits three times)
(deep somber music)
(siren blares in distance)
(crickets chirping)
(pounding on door)
(John sighs)
- Unbelievable.
(sighs)
(door clangs)
- Rabbi Cohen's waiting.
(door closes)
(woman sobbing deeply)
("We All Fall Down" by
Red Wine Hangover plays)
♪ Remember when ♪
♪ plaid was in ♪
♪ And our hair
was all a mess ♪
♪ Government scandalous ♪
♪ There's a stain
on her red dress ♪
♪ We got lost in the fame ♪
♪ And it all became a joke ♪
♪ Just so they know our name ♪
♪ Then that's all
they need to know ♪
- Jesus Christ.
- I thought you gave him up,
convert.
Come this way.
♪ Need to know ♪
(Rabbi Cohen hums along to song)
♪ Here comes the ground ♪
♪ We all fall down ♪
(door bangs shut)
(Rabbi Cohen sighs)
- You called me on the Sabbath.
- You brought the book?
(book thuds onto table)
Now...
- Kinda beautiful
in a creepy way.
- We live in kinda creepy,
kinda beautiful times, don't we?
(Rabbi Cohen mumbles)
- My wife's parents didn't
speak to her for months
when she got her tattoo.
- This is not classical Hebrew,
but neither is it modern,
probably from a middle period.
- Oh.
Well, see, it's-it's pressed.
Can't be older than late
15th century, I'd say.
- Mm-hm.
Good.
These tattoos are
not the only reason
I'm going to be unwelcome
in a Jewish cemetery.
And as for the phone call,
with what you're facing,
God will understand.
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
(creaking)
(ghostly grumblings)
You sang this song to
make your child sleep?
- My wife did, yeah.
- It's a clever trap,
tricking you into
taking that first step,
giving the key that first twist.
- First step?
- The first of
three... rituals.
Lilith is close,
she's watching you,
but the door's not
open for her yet.
The song is the first ritual,
which calls her
handmaid, the Crone,
and her servants, the Lilim.
- Lilim?
- Fucked up, mutant babies.
- Mutant?
(scoffs) Okay.
(eerie music)
(door creaks)
(Quad Lilim hissing)
(guttural sounds)
- The second ritual
is a blood sacrifice
of an unclean beast
to profane your home.
- Wait, right, uh,
what-what kind of rabbi
did you say you were?
- The kind that saves your son.
Have you had any animals
that have died lately?
Pets, that sort of thing?
- Yeah, I had a...
a cockatoo that died.
It was an accident.
- A parrot.
That's unclean.
- What's the third step?
- The third step is you have
to spill the baby's blood.
- Well, that's not gonna happen.
- Neither would
sacrificing your pet.
Don't you see?
The harbingers are subtle.
They manipulate.
They live to open
the door for Lilith.
If Eli spills one drop of blood,
Lilith will come and
she will take him,
and she will leave an imposter,
a golem, in his place.
(deep tense music)
(Wolf Lilim growls)
(Quad Lilim grunts)
(slow mysterious music)
(Eli cries)
- Hey, what's up? What's up?
What's up? What happened?
What happened? What
happened, baby?
What, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh.
Okay, okay, okay.
♪ Hush little baby,
don't say a word ♪
(door bangs)
(Eli's head thuds)
(Rachel gasps) (Eli screams)
Oh, my god, baby. (Eli crying)
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
(scary bang)
- Hey, are you okay?
(Eli crying)
- I hit his head.
I hit his head I think.
(Eli crying)
- Sh.
- Oh, he's okay.
- Shush, shush.
Oh, Vivian, I don't
know what to do.
- Here, here, let me take him.
Okay, okay.
Sh, sh, sh, sh, sh.
(Eli fusses)
Oh, yes, oh.
Sh, sh, sh.
Yeah, he's good.
Hi, there.
- I'm actually... I'm
gonna take a moment.
I'll be right back.
- Take your time.
Oh. Bye, Mama.
- You need to
recite these words.
Stevie, please.
Those candles must
burn until dawn.
Lilith cannot come
into holy light.
You must do these things
until the first
light on Shabbes.
Then, and only then,
will Lilith be driven
from your home.
- So, it's like
splashing some holy water
and saying the Our Father?
- Wake up, man.
This is about saving your son.
Tell me, John, why
did you convert?
- Love.
And my mother-in-law. (scoffs)
- Unfortunately, Lilith
isn't that easily fooled.
She can tell the
difference between apathy
and a true believer.
Take this.
It professes your faith, John.
Lilith is strong,
but she's not as
strong as faith.
And that's something you're
going to need to muster.
(paper rustling)
(John sighs)
(hand thuds) (eerie boom)
This stays here.
It is a thing of darkness
and does not belong
in this world.
(deep somber music)
Go with God.
(chair scrapes floor)
(slow somber music)
(glasses clatter to desk)
- Is everything okay?
- [Vivian] Yep. He's
getting ready to snooze.
(Rachel sighs)
(slow foreboding music)
- Nebech.
Poor motherfucker.
(slow foreboding music)
(cellphone buzzes)
(water splatters)
(Rachel sighs)
(car engine revs)
(slow haunting music)
(Eli babbling)
- Hi, honey.
Yeah, I got you.
(soft tense music)
(water splattering)
[Vivian] ♪ Into dreams ♪
♪ We'll follow her ♪
♪ Into dreams ♪
♪ Endless dreams ♪
♪ Take her hand ♪
♪ Come far away ♪
♪ To a distant world ♪
♪ So far away ♪
♪ Charming boy ♪
♪ Beloved boy ♪
♪ Find your peace ♪
♪ In her arms ♪
♪ Beloved boy ♪
♪ Go now to sleep ♪
♪ You she will guard ♪
♪ From every harm ♪
- You know the words?
(Eli babbles)
- I know everything about her.
- What are you doing?
- There wasn't any
other choice, Rachel.
This is the only way.
- I don't understand.
- When Lilith
comes for your son,
I'll get my Zachary back.
- You wanted this to happen?
- Not want.
I needed it to.
- You, you told Mom to
send me the lullaby book.
You wanted me to sing it.
- Yes.
No.
A bit of both, Rach.
Every night since Eli was born,
I sat there praying
that you'd sing
and praying that you wouldn't.
- Give him to me.
- She'll come.
We'll follow her into the dark,
and we'll bring them both home,
Eli and Zachary.
- If you hurt him...
- It's just a little pin prick.
(Eli coos)
(tires squeal)
(eerie music)
- Fuck this. (engine revs)
(Crone roars) (John grunts)
(John panting) (Crone hisses)
- Sing with me, Rachel.
We have to face this together,
as sisters.
♪ Take her hand ♪
♪ Come far away ♪
♪ To the distant land ♪
♪ So far away ♪
(hand slaps)
(Vivian cries out)
(Eli cries)
- You're insane.
Get outta here!
Go back to your psych ward.
(Rachel grunts)
(Rachel yells)
(both grunting)
(Vivian yells)
(Vivian screams)
- I'm not crazy, Rachel.
You have to trust me.
(Rachel yells)
- No!
(shelf crashes)
(Vivian panting)
(deep tense music)
(Eli coos)
♪ Just follow me ♪
- Vivian.
♪ Into dreams ♪
♪ Endless dreams ♪
(Rachel breathing heavily)
(Rachel gasping)
(Rachel screams)
(Rachel yells)
(eerie music)
- Rach?
Vivian?
Eli.
- Vivian.
Vivian?
(haunting music)
- Oh, no.
No, no.
She took my son.
(Rachel breathing heavily)
- Vivian?
- She took my son.
- (gasps) John.
John!
(fist thuds)
- Huh?
Huh? What?
Rachel?
(scary music)
- [Rachel] John.
(eerie music)
(Wolf Lilim snarls)
(Rachel cries out)
(dramatic bang)
(eerie chaotic music)
(Rachel gasping)
(Wolf Lilim growls)
(Rachel yells)
(Rachel breathing heavily)
(Wolf Lilim growls)
Stop it!
Stop it! (gasping)
Help! Help!
(Rachel yelling)
Help! Help! (echoing)
(Rachel yells in distance)
(Rachel screams)
(dramatic bang)
- I got you.
(breathing heavily)
Come on.
(Vivian and Rachel groan)
(Quad Lilim growling)
Get off her! Get off
her. (Rachel groaning)
(Quad Lilim screeching)
(both breathing heavily)
- Where the fuck
did you bring us?
- This is Lilith's home.
Tell me you wouldn't have
done the same thing for Eli.
We're not gonna
find them like this.
Hey, you're not gonna
find him like this.
- Get off me!
- You're not gonna find him
like this, you need
to call his name.
He needs to hear your voice.
Call your son.
(Rachel sighs)
- Eli.
Eli?
(baby crying)
Eli.
(ominous music)
- Rach.
- [Rachel] Eli.
John.
(baby crying)
- Wait, wait, wait.
(glass shatters)
- You have to cover them.
- What?
- You have to cover the mirrors.
- It's not safe.
- I can't hear you.
(mirror cracking)
(scary bang)
- You have to.
(soft bang)
(ghostly whispers)
(dramatic whoosh)
(John gasps)
(soft bang)
(haunting swooshing)
(John speaks Hebrew)
(loud steady banging)
(steady banging)
(flesh sizzles)
(John speaks Hebrew)
(dramatic rumbling)
(tense music)
- I said shalom, bitch.
(whoosh)
(tense music)
(John speaks Hebrew)
- What the hell?
Vivian?
(baby crying)
Eli, Eli, Eli.
(Rachel gasps) (eerie music)
(door rattles)
(glass scatters)
(Rachel cries out)
(Rachel grunts)
(glass scatters)
(haunting music)
Eli?
(baby crying)
Eli.
(John speaking Hebrew)
(baby crying)
Oh, Eli, Eli.
Eli, Eli.
- Zachary?
(baby crying)
- I can't tell which way.
I can't tell which way.
(babies crying)
(haunting music)
Eli, Eli.
(crying intensifies)
Eli, please...
(cacophony of crying babies)
Please, just... Please...
Please stop, stop, stop.
(babies stop crying)
Okay, all right.
(baby crying)
Eli.
(babies crying)
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, baby, you're right there.
You're right there.
(babies crying)
(Rachel laughs)
- Shhh.
(babies stop crying)
(haunting music)
- Lilith.
(tense haunting music)
No.
Go away. Leave us alone.
(Rachel grunts)
(Rachel gasping)
He's my baby. He's my baby.
(tense music)
(Eli fussing)
Give me back my son, you bitch.
(Rachel yells)
(Rachel grunts)
(Eli fussing)
(Rachel moaning)
No. No.
(Rachel shudders)
- Motherfucker!
(glass slices)
(Lilith roars)
Take Eli and run.
I'll make this right.
(Lilith roars)
(dramatic rumbling)
I love you.
- (gasps) Wait. No.
(Lilith roars)
- Go, Rachel!
(Vivian grunts)
(eerie music)
♪ Follow me ♪
(gagging)
♪ Into dreams ♪
♪ Pretty dreams ♪
- (moans) Stop.
♪ Endless dreams ♪
♪ Take my hand ♪
- Uh...
♪ Come away ♪
♪ Find peace ♪
♪ In my arms ♪
♪ Beloved girl ♪
♪ Go to sleep ♪
♪ I will guard you from ♪
♪ All harm ♪
♪ Follow me ♪
♪ Beside me ♪
(haunting music)
(Eli coos)
- John.
(John speaks Hebrew)
John, John.
John, where are you?
(John speaking Hebrew)
(Rachel gasps) (Eli fussing)
[Lilith] ♪ Follow me ♪
♪ Into dreams ♪
♪ Pretty dreams ♪
♪ Endless dreams ♪
♪ Take my hand ♪
♪ Come away ♪
(mirror crackling)
♪ To distant worlds ♪
♪ Far away ♪
(mirrors shattering)
- No.
No! No!
♪ Beloved girl ♪
(John speaking Hebrew)
♪ Far away ♪
- John.
(John speaking Hebrew)
(Rachel grunts)
(glass shattering)
(Rachel gasping)
(Eli fussing)
- Are you okay?
- Oh, my god.
- You got him. You did it.
Oh, my god.
- Oh, my god.
(dramatic bang) (Rachel yells)
(Crone screeches)
(John speaking Hebrew)
(John and Rachel speak Hebrew)
(Crone screaming)
Ha!
(electricity buzzing)
(both breathing heavily)
(sighs)
- She's gone.
She's gone, she's...
(Rachel whimpers)
(John breathes deeply)
Where's Vivian? What happened?
- She stayed. She got us out.
(sighs)
Oh, my god. What the...?
(Eli fussing)
Oh, my god, baby.
No.
She switched babies.
This is Zachary.
Oh, no, no.
(Zachary crying)
(ominous music)
(birds chirping)
(zipper scratching)
- Does Rabbi Cohen
know you took it?
- No.
I was careful, like you asked.
What do you want it for, anyway?
(children chattering)
- [Man] Oh, you're doing
it, honey. Good job.
Let's go this way.
- You got it?
(Rachel exhales sharply)
- Now what?
(gentle haunting lullaby music)
♪ Twinkle, twinkle
little star ♪
♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
♪ In the dark blue
sky you keep ♪
♪ And often through
my curtains peek ♪
♪ For you never
shut your eyes ♪
♪ 'Til the sun is in the sky ♪
(gentle haunting music)
(dramatic boom)
("The Only One" by
Tassia Zappia plays)
♪ Nowhere left to run ♪
♪ Lost behind the
line of battle ♪
♪ Hiding from the sun ♪
♪ Resting in the
arms of shadow ♪
♪ I can hear you call ♪
♪ You're calling my name ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♪ Now, I'm coming back
to take you home ♪
♪ You no longer
have to be alone ♪
♪ I'm coming back
to bring you out ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm telling
you without a doubt ♪
♪ I'm gonna save you
'fore the day is done ♪
♪ Even if you're
the only one ♪
♪ A broken, empty heart ♪
♪ Crying in the darkest cavern ♪
♪ A ghost of who you are ♪
♪ Locked inside an
ancient labyrinth ♪
♪ I can hear you call ♪
♪ You're calling my name ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm coming
back to take you home ♪
♪ You no longer
have to be alone ♪
♪ I'm coming back
to bring you out ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm telling
you without a doubt ♪
♪ Gonna save you 'fore
the day is done ♪
♪ Even if you're
the only one ♪
(gentle somber music)
♪ I can hear you call ♪
♪ You're calling my name ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm coming
back to take you home ♪
♪ You no longer
have to be alone ♪
♪ I'm coming back
to bring you out ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm telling
you without a doubt ♪
♪ Gonna save you 'fore
the day is done ♪
♪ Even if you're
the only one ♪
(slow haunting music)