[music playing]
CHARLIE: You know,
one of these days
you're going to
say, OK, Charlie,
let the truth be known.
[laughs]
You were right.
You will, Sambo, guarantee it.
SAM: No, never.
Hey, hand me some
of the duck sauce.
CHARLIE: OK, wise
ass, you listening?
I'm listening.
You're sure you're listening?
Charlie, I'm listening.
Is this the last
packet of duck sauce?
Mm.
That's it.
These people won
the damn war, Sam.
Sure, maybe we dropped
the bomb on them
and walked away with
a win, but now they
own half the goddamn country.
I'm not talking real estate.
Cars-- they make better cars.
Oh, bullshit.
SAM: They make
better cars, Charlie.
Give me some of that rice.
I'm not going out andbuying a Chrysler just to have
a break down after two months.
Fucking treason, Sam.
[sucking noise]
That's a shitty
habit, Charlie.
It's good for the gums.
And the cost factor.
They make better
cars that cost less.
You see what Detroit isputting out for that kind
of money-- garbage.
Your wife and kids are goingto wake up someday and find
a Jap standing in your house.
I'm telling you,
you got to get out.
Oh, you know you're nuts.
You'll see.
They're taking over
the car industry.
Laugh when the Japs areselling your soul to the devil,
Sam Levinson.
[laughs]
There he is.
I seen you.
You cops must think I'm a jerk.
We never said that.
Hey, we got to ask, why didyou kill your roommate, Brian?
I didn't kill anybody.
Somebody stabbed him,
18 times with a knife,
just like the one
you're holding.
James and I were marriedand he was cheating on me.
Should've tried a
marriage counselor.
Fuck you.
Get him, Sam.
[music playing]
[yelling]
Fuck.
Fuck, my ear.
He bit my fucking ear off.
Get the fucking cuffs on him.
Got him?
Bit my fucking ear off!
You have the right to remainsilence, so shut the fuck up.
So did she give you static?
Nah, she always knew
I wanted this job.
You call this a job?
Not this.
I mean detective.
You're just the tight asskind of a guy for detective.
[police radio chatter]
I got this one.
It's about time.
Well, you're very welcome.
Ancient Chinese holidays.
Cinco de Mayo.
[police radio chatter]
[music playing]
[gunshots]
Shooting in progress.
Officer down.
[sirens]
Freeze!
In pursuit, heading
east on Jackson Street,
towards the Chinese mall.
[yelling]
Stop.
Get down.
Put your hands behind your back.
You have the right
to remain silent.
If you chose to give upthe right to remain silent,
anything you say will be usedagainst you in a court of law.
Secure a weapon.
Got it.
OK.
You have the right
to have an attorney.
to speak with one
and have one present
before any questions.
[music playing]
BARTENDER: When you going toturn over that broken record,
Charlie?
They make a better product.
Ah, you just saying thatbecause half your clientele
are Japs.
SALLY: Charlie, you evergoing to admit you could be
wrong just once in your life?
Hmm?
You watch, you'll buyone of those pieces of shit
and two weeks
later, you're going
to be wondering what the fuck'swrong with his drive shaft.
What do you care?
You don't even drive.
Hi, Charlie.
Hi, Monica.
Me driving or not
has nothing to do
with giving good, hard-earnedmoney to some foreigner.
So how was your
night on the town, huh?
Family spat between aguy named Dice and his wife
named James.
Ugh.
What's the strongest
shit you got back there?
151 proof rum.
Give me a shot.
On top of all that scotch?
Are you nuts?
Just get it.
[gargling]
You are nuts.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Hey, listen, it's about 12:50.
He told me 1:00 AM.
No, finish your drink.
You know Winch, scared littleshit that he is-- sees us
both-- he'll freak.
Are you sure?
SAM: Yeah, I'll get whateverinformation he's got.
Hey relax.
Lick your wounds or something.
[music playing]
I got to get ready.
BARTENDER: What the hell's thematter with Sam these days?
I don't know.
Tired, I guess.
Yeah.
Ain't we all?
[music playing]
That much girl I know.
But it feels the same to me.
Cause you know you just don'tshow that you still might have
something deep inside for me.
Tell me what's wrong girl.
Please just set me free.
Nothing changing.
Tell me baby what is going on.
Some kind of something istaking you away from me.
Tell me baby, do I do you wrong.
Tell me, tell me, girl, oh,won't you tell me please?
What the fuck is keeping Sam?
You need a ride home, Charlie?
Nah.
[music playing]
Tell me baby do I do you wrong?
You girls finished out here?
Get back.
WINCH: Wait a minute--
Get back!
It's not what you think.
I can explain everything, OK?
Look it's not--
[groans]
Charlie?
Oh, jesus.
Charlie, what happened?
Oh, my god.
Oh.
You go around and get our car.
It's the blue one
across the street.
No-- no, I can't--
I can't do that, Charlie.
Get the fucking car!
OK.
[crying]
[music playing]
All right.
SALLY: Why not just leavehim back in the alley?
CHARLIE: Ah, jesus, Sally.
It's all about trust.
SALLY: You're not
talking sense, Charlie.
A cop doesn't
fucking kill somebody.
Not even a fucking scumbag.
Mother fucker.
Charlie.
Son of a bitch.
Charlie, god dammit.
Stop it.
Fucking ass.
Stop it, Charlie.
Charlie?
Stop it.
No.
Let go of me.
[crying]
CHARLIE: It's all
fucking [inaudible]
[music playing]
Charlie!
Mother fucker--
Charlie-- [crying]
Oh, Jesus.
Charlie!
CHARLIE: Just go.
What am I supposed to do?
Go home and keep
your mouth shut.
You've got blood on your face.
[music playing]
Fucking, fuck.
Fuck.
What the hell is going on?
Got a fucking cop!
Fuck, Sam.
You dumb son of a bitch.
[sniffs]
CAPTAIN: Charlie,
I'm sorry about Sam.
I know what you guys were.
But life goes on.
Now, here's how the
caseload stacks up.
Halloway and Orlanser aregoing to do the Levinson case.
No fucking way, Cap.
That's my case.
It happened in
their jurisdiction
and on their watch.
OK?
Fellas-- take it easy.
Yeah, I just told Charliethat you guys are going
to be handling the Levinsoncase and if you need extra help,
you have it.
Ah, I think we'd like togo it alone for a while.
Yeah.
Charlie, can you tellthese guys anything else that
may have happened last night?
It's all in the report.
Pretty damn
detailed too, Charlie.
Thanks for that.
CAPTAIN: Picked up a
floater this morning.
Preliminaries indicate thathe was dumped in the Bay
either late last night
or early this morning.
Nobody knows.
- Mm.
Just another fun-filled
day in the city.
Did they ID him?
Yeah, one of your
snitches, Leon Winch.
CAPTAIN: Guys, can
you get me Murrow?
- Sure.- Sorry about Sam, Charlie.
Yeah.
Thanks.
OK.
I know you want to keep
busy, and because you
knew this guy and
his world, I'm going
to give you the Winch case.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
It's a very good idea.
And don't get your noseout of joint on this one,
but here comes your new partner.
Michael?
Oh, shit.
Mike Murrow meet yournew partner, Charles Falon.
It's an honor to meet
you, Detective Falon.
Under normal
circumstances I would
give this to another team.
So let's be
normal on this one.
CAPTAIN: Yeah, no.
Uh-- look, he's going to fillyou in on this guy, Winch.
OK?
And everything, right?
You're going to do the
right thing, are you?
You're not going
to be an asshole.
And you've got to
understand that I
know what you're going through.
You capisce?
I'm old and deaf,
but I understand.
Be careful who
you go to bed with.
CHARLIE: Coming through.
Excuse us.
MURROW: Excuse me.
[interposing voices]
CHARLIE: There's one smallbit of information you
got to understand real fast.
There's the law,
and there's justice.
It's best if you
understand one has
nothing to do with the other.
Me, I side with justice.
The law can take care of itself.
That's, uh-- a little cynical.
Don't you think?
Cynic's just a
soured romantic, kid.
Say, Jerry?
- Charlie.
Ray.
What have you got?
Oh, a few tire prints.
Some shoe prints in
the mud over there.
Not much help.
No, not much.
[music playing]
Stick around here, maybeyou'll learn something.
I'll call you.
Jerry, this here is the
shooter from Chinatown.
Be good to him.
Might get lucky.
CHARLIE: Bless me father,for I have sinned.
I killed a slimy,
no-good, son of a bitch.
He took the life
of a good friend.
My partner was the only thingI had in this lousy world.
I just want you to know thatI know what I did was wrong.
But I'd do it
again, if I had to.
[crying]
Have you come to
give your confession?
Uh-- no, thanks, padre, I'vealready been taken care of.
Have a nice morning.
WOMAN: What is on your mind?
MURROW: It's just, it's myfirst homicide assignment
and my partners a wacko.
What?
You don't get
along with the man?
That's just it.
I don't know.
I mean, he's got decorationscoming out of his ears.
He's got commendations
as long as my leg and--
And--
He's very cynical.
Well, I guess his
partner's death
must have really hit home.
Hell, you live with a guy thatlong, working together and all,
something's got to
grow, somethings
got to develop between you.
I don't know.
Do you want to maybe
go away for a few days?
I'd really like to
get to know this guy.
We could spend an
entire weekend in bed.
Sure.
Come on.
What do you say?
We could make passionate love.
Mm.
I could learn a
lot from this guy.
You could learn a
hell of a lot from me.
[music playing]
[gunshots]
Jerry.
Clean and neat, Charlie.
Some unwanted guests showup during the transaction.
They want a piece of the pie.
Nobody wants to share.
Bang, bang, guests
take the whole pie.
Fuck the friends.
Was that why?
Does Steve Young
throw a football
like threading the needle?
Remember him, Charlie?
Jose Alvarez Santiago BentinoDiego, AKA Willy Wasserman.
Can you imagine that
bill, fucking Wasserman.
Certainly you
would know them all.
Why did you call us?
I found this on Wasserman.
It's got a name and address.
Jeez.
What happened to your hand?
Caught in a mousetrap.
Friend of Winch.
A low-life like
him doing staying
at the Sir Francis Drake?
Maybe he likes
the room service.
One other thing, Charlie.
It's nothing positive, but, um--
asshole over there,
looks like he
was killed with the same
type of weapon as Sam--
still wearing it.
Ah, forget it.
There's no connection.
Didn't say there was.
Yeah, but why
do you think that.
CHARLIE: These guys ran
in different circles.
This is a typical I
want what you got thing.
[police radio chatter]
No mysteries.
See you, Jerry.
Thanks.
All right, Charlie.
Hey, Charlie.
Marv.
And Mike, the shooter
Murrow, from Chinatown.
Right, right.
Yeah.
I didn't shoot anybody.
Yeah, yeah, so we hear.
[laughs]
How's it going, Charlie.
[non-english speech] And you?
Oh, we got a couple
of things lined up,
should only take
a couple of days.
We're onto a few things.
- Swell.
- Yeah.
Take care, huh?
See you later.
Hell of a party, huh?
Yeah.
[police radio chatter]
Where to?
Sir Francis Drake Hotel.
You don't like the type.
Fuck you.
Just drive.
Good afternoon.
Hello.
Thanks for the lift.
[interposing voices]
This character Winch wasone of our informants--
gave us a few tips.
He'd call Sam.
They'd set up a deal.
Nothing complicated.
This whole thing smellslike a drug deal gone south.
Thanks.
[music playing]
What floor is this?
Six.
CHARLIE: Probably got his assinto someone else's backyard.
Question-- motive?
Answer-- fucking wrong backyard.
Uh-- Falon, don't youthink we need probable cause?
You don't hear that ladyscreaming inside this room?
It's a nice room.
[music playing]
What have you got?
Just fucking dealers.
Collect their IDs.
I'll check it out.
I got it.
I'll do it.
Let's go.
I'll call you later.
This sucks.
[music playing]
[bagpipes]
Present.
[crying]
Thank you.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
It was lovely.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you.
Let's go home.
CHARLIE: Grace?
Charlie.
How you doing?
I've been better.
Naomi?
She's OK.
I guess time will tell.
If there's anything I can do--
anything at all.
Sure.
CHARLIE: Grace?
Yes, Charlie?
Have you seen Sam's notebook?
The one he carried all the time?
His thought book.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's
what he called it.
Yeah.
He was never without it.
Right.
Take care of yourself.
- Yeah.
You do the same.
Take care, baby.
Sorry I couldn't
make the funeral.
You weren't missed.
Yes, so I figured.
I've been waiting forthe lab reports on Winch.
Been staying after
school, have you?
Winch was beaten to
death-- no weapons.
What do you call bare hands?
I mean, besides bare hands.
His head was bashed in.
OK.
We pulled two distinct bloodtypes from the wood splinter
samples off the dock--
type A and type B. Winch
was type B. Also have somegood photos of what they think
were the killer's big feet.
A lot of people have big feet.
I'm only telling
you what I found out.
So you told me.
Anything else?
No, not really.
Charlie, the only hard
evidence we got on Winch
now are these foot
and tire prints.
We're just trying to
match up tire prints
to a car we ain't found yet.
Probably end up
in the bay, huh?
Probably.
Now, uh-- about Levinson.
From the look of Sam'sbody, there was no struggle.
I'd say he was caught off guard.
The scene behind
the bar suggests
a struggle of some kind.
That's what's so strange.
Sam's body was clean.
Well, there's probably adozen fights behind that joint
every month.
- Hey, bad luck, huh?
Excuse me?
Having to work
with Falon here--
drew the short straw.
Jesus, Falon, why nottry a decent meal for once?
Actually, he's workingon that new high-fat diet.
This piece of shit's ready.
Whatever that means.
Thanks, Bob.
So, where to?
Spencer, Texas.
OK.
I guess we're going to
drive around a bit, huh?
Listen, uh-- my wife wantedto know if you wanted to come
over for dinner tonight?
She a good cook?
Well, we eat out
a lot, but, uh--
sure.
Um-- don't you think youought to change that bandage?
What?
Are you a doctor now?
How did you do that?
[inaudible],, the
near wife-killer.
What?
Did he bite you
back or something?
Head over to Broadway.
What's over there?
I'm still looking
for somebody.
[music playing]
- Shit.
- Get after him.
Get after him.
Open the goddamn door!
Open the door.
Open the god damn door.
Open the god damn door now.
Come on, you punk.
Open the fucking door.
Stand back.
Aw, shit.
Oh, what the fuck?
What the ruck is
wrong with you, Falon?
What are you?
Are you out of your
fucking mind, too?
Leave me the fuck alone,
for christ's sake.
Come out here.
That's for making us run,you little, live turd.
No more next time,
you understand me?
Yeah, I do.
I do.
shit.
Now, down to business.
Wipe your face.
Falon?
Sorry, Police Detective
Murrow, the Mink.
His real name was
Harold Kinclowski.
Listen, you turd, you'rewhat's known in street parlance
as a small-time,
no-good mother fucking,
ass-licking scumbag of awart on humanity's backside.
Deals drugs and shit.
Why don't you correct me
if I'm wrong here, Mink.
OK
He uses more than he sells.
He's also one of
Winch's gophers.
What can tell Detective
Murrow here about Winch?
There's some big deal pending.
Winch was in on it.
I don't know how.
But the guy was
setting something up.
What about Mink?
I honestly don't know.
I swear to God.
But people on the street,told me to shy away from him.
There was something funnyabout Winch, you know?
I mean, he-- he wasn'twhat he was supposed to be.
You know?
I mean, he wasn't right.
You could sense it, man.
he had his own personal agenda.
Agenda-- jesus christ,
listen to these people.
Something else--
What?
Levinson-- what
have you heard?
Uh-uh, No.
Not me, Falon, no.
Boil me in fucking piss.
I don't know shit
about that. huh-uh.
No, no, nothing.
No fucking way.
Fuck.
Fuck you.
CAPTAIN: Number
five, step forward.
Turn around.
And around.
And step back, please.
What do you think?
I don't know what the hellI'm doing here, Captain.
I told these guys there
was nothing to see.
This is a waste of my time.
Mm-hm.
Ms. Niece?
I didn't say anything.
Thanks for coming in.
Thanks for trying to help us.
If you get any ideas,
even in your sleep,
will you contact me?
Get in touch with me?
Will you?
Sure.
Thanks a lot.
You know what we
got here, stugots!
Doesn't really matter.
We know the son
of a bitch did it.
We'll nail them in other ways.
Be nice to have a positive ID.
Maybe we ought to talk tosome of Jerome's friends.
Bet your ass.
I'll tell you something.
The same guys that iced
the warehouse group
also killed Levinson.
It's all one big family.
CAPTAIN: Mm-hm.
We're going to
play show and tell.
All right?
Just the facts ma'am,
just like Dragnet.
Capisce?
Yeah, sir.
Take care, Charlie.
Yeah.
What is this crap?
What crap?
That lineup.
Nobody saw jack shit.
I know that kid.
He's no killer.
Well, they think that
he was there that night.
They think he's
involved somehow.
They want to see if theycan get an ID at the bar.
Would you follow me please?
Shooter, you too.
Can you give me an
idea of when there's
an end to these taxi receipts?
Huh?
Look at this.
Look, if the lousy mayorcan take a fucking limo,
we can take cabs.
You know what you can take?
The vehicle that the San
Francisco PD gives you.
You are an adult. You
are middle-aged man.
Get a life, will you?
Drive a car.
Do you understand,
it is at an end.
This is not IBM.
It's over, finished.
I promised myself.
That's a pact I
made with myself.
No more singing the sametune, my friends-- no more.
I've got to get out of here.
I got to get--
spaces-- I got to get space.
Captain?
Don't pay any attention.
I go to go to the southwest.
If you like the southwest,that's where it is.
You see, that's where
there's a lot of space.
Only you need a pony,
just like Shane had.
Shane.
I love Shane.
God, My heart is beatingSee, it's medium to high.
That's no good.
That's terrible.
When's the Captain
due for retirement?
Any day now.
Hey?
[music playing]
Get off Falon,
I'll get you, Falon.
You bit off my ear, you
fucking son of a bitch.
Don't hurt her ear.
Fuck.
Oh, get in the car.
I'll get you Falon.
You son of a bitch.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
No style anymore.
Style?
What's style got to do with it?
Used to be, 90% of
police work was style.
No more.
I thought substance wasthe thing that mattered, no?
Take Muhammad Ali, there's aman who did things with style--
made him a champ.
We've lost our style.
Are you saying that the
ends justify the means?
I'm saying you got to bewilling to take a few punches
below the belt. I'm going home.
MURROW: Don't you
want that ride?
I'll walk.
MURROW: Don't forget--dinner, tonight, 7:00 sharp.
Can't wait.
[honk]
[music playing]
[buzzer]
Charlie?
I never took notice
of the view up here.
Been here a hundred times andI never really looked at it.
Pretty nice, Grace.
I was just making a sandwich.
Do you want one?
Yeah.
Extra mayo, as usual?
Shane was telling me that Naomius starting college next fall.
Yeah.
That's great.
Where is she going?
Stanford.
Really?
Big bucks.
How long have you
owned this place?
10 years.
Thanks, Grace.
Well, got to go.
Got to ask you, Grace, wheredid the extra money come from?
I don't know
where it came from.
It was cash, and
there was a lot of it.
He said, he was sending
Naomi to a good school.
Bye, Grace.
[music playing]
Hey Wally?
Hey, Wally?
Yeah?
Look, we want to
ask you a favor.
I don't do favors for cops.
Oh, come on,
don't be like that.
Come on, guys,
get out of my face.
Huh?
- Oh, really?
OK.
Come on.
[interposing voices]
Have a seat here.
Get in.
[knocking]
The Dr. Falon.
Just Falon.
Nectar of the gods.
Thank you.
Please come in.
Can I offer you a drink?
Scotch, neat.
Your husband is one
of the few cops I know
who hangs his hat on Nob Hill.
Most live in Oakland.
Where do you call
home, Detective Falon?
Just Falon.
North Beach.
Hey, Charlie.
Uh-- welcome to our home.
Yeah.
Thanks for coming by.
So, uh--
What do you do?
I'm a clothing designer.
Actually, she's justtrying a new line at, uh--
Macy's.
Swell.
- Um--
- Shall we eat?
Yeah.
You hungry?
MURROW: Here's to, uh-- my hero.
That's you, honey.
Are you married,
Detective Falon?
The only broad I
ever had was the job.
Broad-- I haven't heard
that term used in years.
[laughs]
Women only make
things more difficult.
You ever live in Berkeley?
Do they?
Berkeley's too expensive.
Sure as shit, they do.
Things have changed.
Take this food here.
Is there a problem
with the food?
No, it's fine,
for store bought.
No more home cooking these days.
Women would rather be
doing something else,
working out at the gym,
jogging, making money.
You don't like
the competition?
Honey, did we tell
you what happened today?
It has nothing to do
with the competition.
It's roles-- who does what.
And you probably
think the wife should be
at home, cooking and cleaning.
Bet your little tooshie.
OK.
It's her god-given
task in life.
Ah.
MURROW: Come on, guys,
yeah, um-- can we just
like change the subject here.
Just a second, Mikey.
Mikey?
It's Mike.
[laughs]
Nobody knows who
they are anymore.
How about another scotch?
How about one?
How about another
topic, honey, please?
Is this how you
relate to your job?
Used to be the good
guys were the good guys
and the bad guys
were the bad guys.
Now it's piss and
shit, who's who.
Can't be all-- uh--, thatkind of dry anymore, though.
No.
I mean--
Good cop tries like
hell, does his best.
What does he get for it--
can't send his kids to
a good college, can't
afford a decent place to live--
why?
I don't think that's true.
CHARLIE: Oh lady,
look around here.
Who plays the load
around this place?
Mikey, here?
No fucking way.
You do.
Your money.
I'll bet it eats at himevery stinking, fucking day.
Does it eat at you, Mikey?
Could we just talk
about something else?
He's not going to admit
it, at least not to you.
What man likes his balls handedover to him on a plastic dish?
No clear lines.
A good cop gets killed
by number one scumbag
of a fucking drug dealer.
Let's say he gets caught--
he's out of jail in three days.
And the cop?
They plant him,
play the bagpipes.
His wife and kids got to scrimpand save just to carry the nut
they had going--
bullshit.
I better go.
Oh, hey, uh--
Charlie, it's all right.
Before I say something
that might offend.
Before you say something?
Honey.
Thanks for the takeout.
Charlie, come on,
listen, you don't--
hey, Charlie, are
you always like this?
Like what?
A complete asshole, man.
Probably so.
I'll see you, shooter.
[music playing]
You do us this little favorand your made-- nice digs,
clean underwear, the works.
Fellas, it-- it
just ain't right.
Well right and wrong dependson what side of the fence
you're on, Wally.
But there are basic things.
We understand that, but
we're doing is right--
right in anybody's book.
This creep is a low lifemother fucking druggy who
we've busted too many times.[laughs]
He say's he's
trying to clean up.
ORLANSER: That's
pure bullshit, Wally.
You want another round?
Hey chief, bring my cousinanother round here, huh?
Look, Wally, we tried
to help this punk.
I don't know.
We're being nice.
Real nice, Wally.
Real nice isn't working here.
So let me put it
to you like this.
If you don't help us out--
[screams]
--we'll fucking kill you.
Now how's that?
Hey, buddy, it's OK.
Hey, hey, take it easy.
Huh?
It's all right, buddy.
[phone ringing]
Yeah?
SALLY [ON PHONE]: Charlie,it's-- it's Sally.
Can I talk to you?
I'm listening.
SALLY [ON PHONE]:
No, face to face.
I'll stop by the
bar tomorrow night.
SALLY [ON PHONE]: Now, Charlie.
Now?
SALLY [ON PHONE]: Please?
Where?
SALLY [ON PHONE]: Um--
Kip's Coffee shop.
I'll be there.
SALLY [ON PHONE]: OK.
You look like shit.
Well, you look about the same.
Yeah, we're a match set, baby.
I need a little something tohelp me get through the night.
So what are you
calling me for?
We stopped sharing the same bed.
Remember?
Well, you see, Sam--
Sam used to be my supplier.
You're full of shit.
And he's dead now, soyou got to take his place.
Sam never gave you no dope.
What?
You've been blind?
No fucking way.
Any fucking way,
he used to give me.
He's gone.
You sure as hell know whatyour partner was doing?
You bitch.
I need it, Charlie, now.
Fucking hustle me, Sally.
You're an asshole.
Charlie?
Conveniently deaf,
dumb, and blind--
is that it?
Sam was giving me the stuff.
It was his way of being nice.
You leave Sam out of this.
They want me to fingersome Innocent slob, Charlie.
What are you talking about?
Hey.
Charlie, you owe
me and we haven't
had a good screw in months.
What do you say?
[inaudible] I should
baby, that's what I say.
I'll clean up.
I'll clean up, I
promise, Charlie.
Please?
[crying]
Never say that
about Sam again.
You understand me?
Do you understand me?
Yeah, Charlie.
[crying]
[opera singing]
I know.
I wasn't too crazy
about her either.
- You looking at Burnside.- Who?
The passport you found
in Winch's hotel room.
Look, I told you, these
fucking drug dealers
got a zillion fake IDs.
Can I see it?
I forgot where I put it.
Let me ask you something.
How long before
you found Levinson?
Hour.
That long?
You sure?
What the fuck is this?
Yeah, I'm sure.
[music playing]
I want to check this
guy out on computer.
What did Sally Niece
tell you on the night
Sam Levinson was murdered?
She say anything about that?
Since when are youinterested in Sally Niece?
What did she tell you?
Read the report, shooter.
And don't you have
enough to keep
you busy with the Winch case?
That's Jerome Johnson, right?
Right?
- What?
Yeah.
[music playing]
Fuck.
Listen, what we're
going to have to do--
What's going on
in here, Vincent?
Gentlemen, would
you excuse me.
I'll get back to you right away.
Falon, what is your problem?
Who are those guys?
What's it to you?
And who in the fuck
is Harry Burnside?
This whole fucking thingis going south, anyway.
Harry Burnside was a cop.
What do you mean a cop?
I thought it best
that you know nothing
about this whole fucking thing.
What fucking thing?
It was an IA sting.
Some dirty cops were skimmingdrugs off their collars
and selling it back to dealers.
Burnside was IA.
No.
What do you mean, no?
Yes.
He was supposed to installhimself as a drug dealer
so he could put
pressure on those guys
who were under investigation.
And Sam Levinson was one ofthe cops under investigation.
You fuck, you thought me andSam were into selling drugs?
You were cleared months ago.
How the hell do you think yougot the Winch investigation?
Those guys are IA.
You son of a bitch.
Hey, go fuck yourself!
Levinson was selling drugs.
The kind that you find inlittle kids arms, dead.
Only he got cold feetand he wanted to get out.
What in the fuck
are you telling me?
I am telling you
something simple.
This fucking Burnside--
poor bastard--
that night was going
to tell Levinson
what the whole fucking thingwas about and he got dead.
We thought we had this
whole thing set up.
Burnside was supposed to putpressure on the bed cops,
have them turn state's
evidence-- ah, shit,
the whole fucking thing is gone.
Bye, bye.
Have a nice fucking day.
Ah, shit!
Get out.
Relax, pal.
Get the fuck out!
Leave him alone.
Let's go.
I said, get the fuck out!
[crying]
[music playing]
Ah.
[laughs]
Oh, yeah.
You 're fine and dandy.
What can I get you, pal?
I'm Charlie
Falon's new partner.
My condolences.
Can I talk to
you for a minute?
About what?
The night Sam
Levinson was murdered.
What can you tell me?
Levinson leaves,
goes in the back alley.
A little while later,
Falon goes back.
How much later?
A half hour maybe?
Not longer-- say an hour?
No, no, no.
Couldn't have been that
long-- half hour tops.
Me and Sally locked up.
I asked if she
wanted a ride home.
She says, no.
She only lives a few
blocks from here.
I say good night to her.
I got in my car and I went home.
Anything else?
That's it.
Thanks.
Uh-- do me a favor, will you?
Sure.
Take care of Charlie.
I'm know he's a pain in the ass,but deep down, he's a good guy.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
I know what you mean.
I'll try.
Thanks.
Now, this has to be
done by the book, Wally.
You understand?
Huh?
Yeah, sure.
Right.
Good.
Now, you know the guy
from the Cherry Lounge?
You even spoke with him onoccasion, about drugs, right?
OK.
All right?
Yeah.
Good boy.
See what a good boy?
Now you led us to this addressbecause you saw the whole thing
the other night.
Yeah, whatever you guys say.
You saw everything.
OK?
When this is over,
all you gotta do
is sign a statement saying thatyou saw this guy kill Levinson.
All right?
HALLOWAY: You understand, Wally?
I said, you understand?
Yeah, sure.
You move while we're
gone, you're dead.
Very dead.
HALLOWAY: Let's go.
[music playing]
Here you go, darling.
Oh, thank you.
Will you go check on
your brother for me?
Mm.
OK.
No problem.
- Ah.
Oops, excuse me.
Hey!
Yo, what the hell
is going on, man?
Ah, ah, ah.
Hello, Jerome.
How's it been?
Still trying to keep thatnose of yours clean, Jerome.
How dare you!
You still on
probation, Jerome?
Man, no.
I finished with
that two weeks ago.
Now, what-- what--
- Still pushing drugs?
What do you men want?
You used to give
us some shit, Jerome.
Hey, man, I neverbothered you two, all right?
JEROME'S MOTHER: Well, you menhave no right to come in here
and talk this way to him.
You've always been a
big headache, Jerome.
You made me ruin a good
pair of floor shines
chasing your ass
through that garbage
pile over on Grant Street.
Well, you have no right
to treat us like this.
Now get out!
Get out?
But we have a warrant
for your arrest, Jerome.
ORLANSER: In connection withthe murder of Police Detective
Samuel Levinson.- What you talking about?
I didn't kill nobody.
Mom, I'm telling you--
I know you didn't.
Hey!
Everything will be clearedup once we get you downtown.
Yeah, well this isn't right.And I'm going to call somebody.
I ain't going downtown.
Now get your asses
out of my house!
Well, I'm sorry,
ma'am, but, uh--
Yeah we'll see about that.
We're just doing our job.
[gunshots]
Oh, Jesus.
[baby crying]
What the fuck is
wrong with you all?
Oh, my little baby!
Oh!
[crying]
JEROME'S MOTHER:
My baby's in there.
Now, you had
better pay attention.
Shh.
Calm down.
It's OK.
- My baby's in there.
- It's OK.
It's all right.
Now calm down.
All right.
Look, I don't know
what's going on, mom,
but I'm-- when I get
to where I'm going,
I'm going to call you.
- OK.
I'm going to go to you, OK?
You happy?
I'm going.
All right now, when
I get back, I'm going
to let you know something.I'm going to call you.
Just take care of
the baby, all right?
HALLOWAY: Jerome?
What?
You want to throw
some clothes in a bag?
You know, you all
you got a lot of nerve
coming to my mother's
house like this.
[gunshots]
[baby crying]
ORLANSER: Hey.
Hey , little guy.
Hey, hey, you're not goingto tell anybody, are you?
Huh?
Because, you know, if youdo, that wouldn't be so good.
You know what I mean?
Huh?
Hey, this kid can't even talk.
Jesus christ, will
you knock it off?
Do you want to play with this?
HALLOWAY: Hi, this is Halloway.
Yeah, I got a 187 at 1310 Allen.
Yeah, look, we're
also going to need
somebody from Child Welfare.
MURROW: Told me
you'd probably be
here around this time of day.
Computer couldn't
tell me jack shit.
Tell me something, Murrow,why did you want to be a cop?
I don't know.
I guess, maybe, because mydad always wanted to be one.
He could have been one.
That's what he always
kept telling us,
and ended up selling
life insurance instead.
Hated himself for that.
The good guys and the bad guys.
Nice and simple, huh?
Just the way you like it, no?
Fuck, that's the way
we'd all like it to be.
Bad guys got to pay the
piper, sooner or later.
Now, what's that mean?
You want the guy who
killed Winch, don't you?
Don't you?
You're going
about it all wrong.
Get your gut to lead
where you want to go.
Fuck this technical shit.
A cop should keep hisfeelings out of his work.
You do that and you're dead.
Let's get out of here.
Let's get some coffee.
Charlie?
You know, I used to
think a lot about God.
God?
I was an alter boy,right there in that church.
I thought I knew all there
was to know about God.
Not anymore.
[music playing]
That's beautiful.
Yeah.
Let's go light a candle.
First you got to
look at the motives.
Motives-- drugs, obviously.
Look at all the possibilities.
Motive, personality
are usually connected.
A dead person's personality--
live by the sword, et cetera--
those are possible motives.
Jealousy, revenge.
Your standard fare.
Let's run it down.
The position of the weltson Winch's face and neck
indicate he was caughtoff guard or by surprise.
He didn't expect it.
He wasn't gotten frombehind, which means if he
didn't anticipate the beating--
He knew the killer.
Maybe.
Maybe even trusted the killer.
Or at least thought thekiller wasn't a murderer.
In 90% of all homicides,the victim and the killer
know each other.
They usually have
something in common.
Yeah, something in common.
Remember, physical stuff-- moreimportant than any theories.
MURROW: You wanted
to see us, Captain?
Yeah, I wanted you andyour partner to hear this.
Go ahead.
HALLOWAY: Yeah, anyway, wesuspected this Jerome Johnson
from the onset.
He knew Sam from a few yearsback when he was a teenager.
What we needed and got
was an eyewitness--
Wally Pental.
ORLANSER: So we figuredthat the, uh-- same person
or persons hit the warehouse,
tied that, the dealers
there to Jerome Johnson.
Johnson was in the process ofbuilding up a small clientele--
big mistake.
He hit them.
Their friends got
pissed and hit him.
So now, they're even.
And good riddance
to bad rubbish.
Yeah.
Well, we knew that
Wally knew Johnson,
so after a little prodding,Wally gave us what we needed.
Shit, it turns out he sawthe whole thing himself.
Eye witness number one.
Jesus, and that two-year-oldkid seen all this?
Money and drugs all
over the apartment
from the warehouse deal.
Odd.
What's odd?
CHARLIE: Nothing.
Not our case.
Now, how fast did
you guys get there?
I don't know.
Couldn't have been too long.
Something wrong, shooter?
MURROW: I'm just asking.
Come on.
We got work to do.
You want to leave
them behind, shooter?
Sure.
Here you go, Captain.
There's something not right.
I'm listening.
It's just a feeling I have.
Some things don't fit.
Oh, you're listening toyour feelings today, are you?
Johnson had to know the badguys were gunning for him.
Yeah?
Why put his family
in the line of fire?
Why not empty his weapon
through the damn door?
We know he had a full clip.
Maybe the guy is
scared shitless?
Why, if he's so
scared shitless,
hang back and wait until
they bang down the door?
Protect his family.
Protect his family-- bullshit.
Falon, come on.
Does he even get a
clean shot off at them?
- Does he?
- No.
With 10 rounds left,
he just turns his back
and heads for the door?
Not a very brave
thing to do, was it?
You know, I don't like
coincidences, Falon.
You?
Depends.
Halloway and Orlanser
get there minutes after
it happened-- coincidence?
Life's full of them, kid.
Well, it's too neatly wrapped.
All right?
It's-- it's too tight.
Falon--
Yeah.
You dealt with Winch
as much as Levinson?
It was really Sam's contact.
But you knew him, right?
Yeah, I knew him.
Listen, I'll see you later.
I forgot something.
CHARLIE: Hey, Cap?
- Yeah?
Can I ask you a question?
Ask.
Who else in this precinctknew about this sting operation?
- Me.
- Just you?
Yeah, and now you.
Want a candy bar?
No, thanks.
CAPTAIN: Hypoglycemics, like me,have to keep our blood sugar up
or we get sick.
What's on your mind?
- Feelings.
Feelings?
Yeah.
Thanks, Cap.
Anytime.
How about Halloway
and Orlanser,
they know anything about it?
No.
Mm.
See how much better
I feel already.
It works, like clockwork.
Put it in, I'm good.
COP: Switch shifts
with me tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
That's my last day
of traffic court,
I tell you that right now.
That's for sure.
[music playing]
Something I can get you?
- How about your job?
- You got it.
Ha, fuck you.
Oh, fuck you, too.
You should really try this.
It's good for the blood sugar.
[music playing]
I told you.
Liz, right?
Hi, um-- could you
run a test on these--
blood types?
And if you get a minute, I--
I need to-- I need
to get the blood
types of Falon and Levinson.
Falon and Levinson-- what for?
It's a personal favor.
[music playing]
COP: Hey, shooter.
Can I get the evidencephotos on the Winch murder?
What do you need these for?
I'm borrowing them.
COP: Like hell you are.
Look, don't give me any shit.
This is my case and I'm takingthe fucking photographs.
[music playing]
No fucking way.
Nice shot.
I want to talk to you.
Stop shaking.
You're making me nervous.
Oh, I'm making
you nervous, huh?
Why are all these
people staying
away from this Winch kid?- I don't know.
Oh, you know.
No, I don't.
I'm going to ask you onetime, and one time only.
Why were they staying
away from Winch?
I don't fucking know.
Ah.
What the fuck you doing, man?That's my--
- Am I clear?
- Shit.
Get off me, man.
- You playing with me?
No, I don't want to play.
I don't know what thefuck you're talking about.
Is this what you like?
Is this what you need?
[yelling]
OK, man, OK.
Winch-- Winch was a cop, man.
[laughs]
What did you say?
I said he's a fucking cop.
Make me a believer.
He was undercover, man.
At least that's the word.
All right?
He was looking to, you
know, bust some bad cops
or some-- some shit like that.
Which bad cops?
I don't fucking know.
But you can guess.
Come on.
Yeah-- yeah, I
suppose I could guess.
So guess.
Levinson, man.
Levinson.
Now, you be real
fucking careful
about this next question.
What about Falon?
Here's what I'm saying, man,is that all cops are assholes.
And that's all-- oh, fuck.
Shit.
Jesus christ.
Falon's a fuck.
Man, you should
know that by now.
Shit.
He's a mean motherfucker--
Yeah?
But he was never
on the tape, man.
Never?
No.
You sure?
Real sure?
I'm sure.
OK.
I owe you one.
Now get out of here.
- All right.
Get the fuck out of here.
[music playing]
[knocking]
Hello, Sally.
How's it going?
Hey, let's party.
Hmm?
[music playing]
[knocking]
Hi.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Your husband here?
No, he's not.
You know where he is?
No, I don't.
Thanks.
Uh-- can I offer you a drink?
You do still drink, don't you?
No thanks.
Listen, I know you're
not too crazy about me.
No matter.
I think you two got somethingreal special between you.
I think you need to know thatI want Michael to be a cop.
That's nice.
I just don't want him
to be a cop like you.
Lady, he would
never let that happen.
[music playing]
Oh, shit.
More coffee, Charlie?
Thanks, Milt.
Well, hey.
A cop stealing police
property from the cops.
That's a good one, Charlie.
You guys are getting
sloppy in your old age.
Are we?
How many junkies
you know stick
their shit in their leftarm with their left hand?
Well, you know junkies.
They're all fucked up.
Sam should have kept
his thoughts to himself.
You two are dead meat.
Me and Stanz wanted to bringyou in from the beginning.
It was Sam who said no.
Why?
Why what, Charlie?
Why kill the guy?
Oh, couldn't have
a guy with cold feet.
We liked to Sam, but he wasgoing to turn state's evidence.
And Sally?
Jesus.
Charlie, we
couldn't take a chance
on her saying the wrong thing.
And an innocent family--
that was a real piece of work.
We like you Charlie,
so I should ask, you in?
Fuck you.
Sam said you wouldn't
be reasonable.
See you, Charlie.
Charlie.
Shooter.
Been working that oversizedbrain of yours, huh kid?
Yeah, not much.
So you're getting somelab reports worked up, huh?
Yeah, blood types.
And?
MURROW: I haven't
opened them yet.
Why is that?
I wanted to ask
you if I should.
Who's in the report?
Winch, Levinson, you.
I prayed tonight, Charlie.
Yeah, sat down in your
apartment and prayed.
Did you?
My apartment?
You loved Sam, right?
Yeah, I loved him.
It's good to love people, butthey can make you do things.
Sometimes.
Come on.
I need to talk to
you in private.
I had a good buddy once,shooter, a true blue partner.
Why did you wait an hourto go out in the back alley
and look after Sam?
The kind of guy whowould do anything for you.
More like half an
hour, huh, Charlie?
What's time anyway?
Enough with this shit.
You know, I figured it out.
It came to me in Delgoti'soffice, the motive.
You find the motive,
you find the killer.
You hated Winch because youthought he killed your partner.
You though he killed
your best friend.
Sam and I were
like the same person.
You thought you were
dishing out justice--
some fucking justice.
Sorry, kid.
I got to do this one alone.
Milt, hang on to
these for the kid.
Charlie, what the
fuck is going on?
These guys want me
to call the cops.
Seems like a good idea, Milt.
[music playing]
HALLOWAY: What do
you say, Charlie?
One last chance-- you
with us or against us?
ORLANSER: You know
we like you, Charlie.
What do say-- partners?
HALLOWAY: We trust you, Charlie.
ORLANSER: Like a
brother, Charlie.
HALLOWAY: We feel
real bad about Sam.
But you're a lot smarter
than Sam, Charlie.
ORLANSER: Right, Charlie?
[gunshots]
HALLOWAY: Unless he ain't.
Did we get him?
Stanz, you there?
Stanz?
Take your time, Charlie.
You ain't get much of it left.
MURROW: Halloway!
What do you think, Charlie?
Shooter got the balls?
I'd bet my life on it.
[gunshots]
[music playing]
I remember the day
I told my old man
I wanted to become a cop.
His face just lit up
like a Christmas tree.
That's all he ever
wanted to become,
you know-- a big city cop.
You know what he told me?
He said, kid, you operatefrom the heart always.
Hell, the head-- the headcan only get you in trouble.
You see?
He agreed with you.
[crying] You and
him are a lot alike.
[sirens]
[music playing]
[MUSIC PLAYING - DOLLY PARTON, "AMAZING GRACE"]
Amazing grace, how sweet thesound that saved a wretch
like me.
I once was lost,
but now I'm found,
was blind, but now I see.
Twas grace that taught
my heart to feel.
And grace my fears relieved.
How precious did
that grace appear,
the hour I first believed.
I once was lost
but now I'm found,
was blind, but now I see.