[melodic music]
[music continues]
[female #1]
Taxi, taxi.
[male narrator]
I cannot believe that life
can be more generous
than it was to me
when I was a young writer
living in New York City and in love with a girl named Janet.
[typewriter keys clacking]
Janet was from Iowa.
Now an editor
at a fashion magazine.
She was convinced that
when I was working
I'd forget to eat.
[doorbell rings]
- Is that you?
- It's me.
[knock on door]
I bought you corn beef
on rye with potato salad.
You said you'd rather have
potato salad than coleslaw.
- Thank you.
- I thought I'd never get a cab.
There's a slight mist
falling out there.
- You know how it gets.
- Mmm, yes, I know.
Oh, Aunt Flo invited us
to tea tomorrow.
Okay.
Why is it so dark
in here?
Janet.
Sit down.
John, I'm on a deadline tonight.
I gotta get back to the office.
Oh.
You really are an odd person
even for a writer.
[slow music]
Thank you for
the corn beef on rye.
Thank you for remembering
the potato salad.
And thank you for coming
into my life.
You're welcome.
I never thought
I'd get married.
I used to think my work was
so important and so demanding
that it could take the place
of a wife and a family.
That night you walked
into the Algonquin for dinner.
I turned to the people
I was with and I said..
...that's the woman
I'm gonna marry.
You're awfully sure of yourself,
aren't you, Mr. Walton?
Janet, you proposed to me
back on Walton's Mountain
but I never really
proposed to you.
I love you, Janet,
and I'm asking you to marry me.
I'd like that
very much, John-Boy.
Why don't you
call me John?
[birds chirping]
[keys clacking]
Corabeth, I think we're gonna
have to buy a new cash register.
Corabeth, I said I think
we're gonna have to
buy a new cash register.
And I think we're gonna
have to also buy a hearing aid
to stick in your ear
so I won't have to yell!
For God's sake, please.
I am in the throes
of creation.
Now, what on Earth
is it now?
I was trying to
get your attention.
How's the book coming?
Mr. Godsey,
I am inspired.
The news of
John-Boy's wedding
has positively
energized my muse.
[bell rings]
Oh, good morning,
Mr. Godsey.
'Well, good morning, ladies.'
Good morning, Ike.
And how are you, Corabeth?
Well, you'll have
to forgive, Corabeth.
She sent away for one of those
correspondence courses
that teaches you how
to write a romance novel.
Oh.
'So, what can I do
for you, ladies?'
Well, we need just
oodles of sugar.
Uh, how many,
Miss Emily?
How many, what?
How many oodles?
Oh, several.
- Wouldn't you say, sister?
- Oh, indeed, yes.
And we also need some yeast.
The kind we usually order.
Ah, something tells me
you ladies are mixing up
a batch of the recipe.
We're making a special run
for John-Boy's wedding.
We are personally transporting
the recipe to New York
and to John-Boy
and his friend.
Sister's already
started practicing
driving the automobile
and I'm going to navigate.
Well, it isn't all
that difficult.
One simply gets out
to Route 29 and heads north.
Sister, you remember the time
we drove to New York with papa?
Was that the time
we were stopped
by the law enforcement
officers, sister?
'Remember papa gave him
some of the recipe'
and he tore up
the speeding ticket?
I have no recollection
of that, sister.
Oh.
[Mamie]
'That will be all,
Mr. Godsey.'
Well, fine. I'll send that
all over this afternoon.
And how will you ladies
be taking care of the bill?
We had a notice from the bank
that we've run out of money
and so I'll have
to mail you a check.
Well, that'll be fine.
Isn't that right, Corabeth?
- Bye bye.
- Goodbye, Mr. Godsey.
"She knew not what
to say, save
Oh, my Pierre.
Dear Pierre."
'"They sailed for Europe
on an ocean liner.'
"On the deck,
as he embraced her
"his pectoral muscles
touched her
"sending multiple
electrical shock waves
through her ample bosoms."
[bell rings]
[instrumental music]
[dog barking]
- Morning, Drew.
- Good morning, John.
Thought you fellas
might want some coffee.
You've been out here
since the crack of dawn.
Well, we have another
big order to get out.
You and Drew have done
a good job running the mill.
Now that the election's over,
I'll be able to help out again.
It'll be good to have
you back, daddy.
Yeah, it sure will.
Especially with this big
contract we got coming up.
- You tell your dad yet?
- Madison Development.
They're planning to build
a big subdivision
here in Jefferson County.
I talked them into getting
all their lumber from us.
I wish you'd talked that over
with me first, Ben.
I'm not sure we can handle
a big order like that.
Don't know if we have
the tools or the manpower.
Manpower is
no problem, Johners.
Men all over the county
looking for work.
You know that new mill
that folded in Rockfish?
I got a great price
on their equipment.
I bought out
the whole place.
So how you figurin'
on paying for it?
We've made a down payment.
They're gonna take
a percentage of profits
from Madison until they're paid.
It's foolproof.
I don't know how
you figured that.
The county's gotta vote
on this development first.
It's good for the county,
it'll go through.
Besides, you're on
the board of supervisors.
I hope I'm hearing
you wrong, son.
If it's good for the county,
I'll probably vote for it.
But we can't stake our
business on how I vote.
No, you better
get on the phone
and cancel all
that fancy equipment.
I can't do that.
We're locked into it.
Look, it's a good deal, John.
I knew when I put you in charge
you were gonna take some risks.
I didn't think you'd
put us out like this.
- Daddy, it's a sure thing.
- Didn't I teach you anything?
This business is built
on common sense and hard work.
There's no such thing
as a sure thing.
Get the paperwork
on this deal, now.
Bring it inside.
Well, it seemed like
a good idea at the time.
John.
Hello.
Janet tells me
you're from Virginia.
That's right.
My family's been living
up in the Blue Ridge Mountain
since the early 1700s.
Well, one of my very best
husbands came from Virginia.
I just adore Virginians.
Well, I'll take that
as a recommendation.
Now, I probably will become
a pain in the neck
as time goes by.
Janet is the daughter
I never had.
She comes from a distinguished
family as, of course, you know.
Please sit.
And since her mother is not here
to arrange things for her
I have to do it.
Well, all we want, Aunt Flo,
is your moral support.
Oh, my dear.
Of course, you have that.
That's all, Dean.
Thank you.
It's just that until your mother
and father actually get here
I really feel I have
to stand in their place.
Uh, we thought we'd just arrange
the wedding ourselves.
Of course,
you can and will.
All I'm offering
are suggestions. Shortcuts.
After all, I have been married
a number of times.
[laughing]
[Aunt Flo]
'Introductions to
the right service people.
Caterers, engravers, florists.
I got a wonderful florist.
And some assurances
that good taste be observed.
Do we have a problem
with good taste?
Obviously not,
my dear young man.
I mean, look who
you've chosen to marry.
'No, it's-it's just that'
I feel an extra
responsibility since..
Darling...it looks
like your father
is going to have
some difficulty getting here.
- If he does get here at all.
- Oh, no.
Well, they're having
civil unrest down there
or whatever it is they're
calling revolution these days.
I finally did get
a telephone call
through to your poor
dear mother and she said
that under the circumstances,
perhaps it would be best for me
to stand in for her.
'Make any decisions
she might make.'
Um, I wonder if you saw
the wedding has been mentioned
in Walter Winchell's column.
Actually, Aunt Flo, we're
planning a small wedding
at the little church
around the corner
with just our family
and some friends.
And some neighbors
from Walton's Mountain.
Well, u-uh..
Darling.
What about your
father's associates
in the diplomatic corps?
What will they think
if I allow you to get married
in that dowdy
little church?
St. Bartholomew's would be
so much more appropriate.
You could play
the World Series in there.
[laughing]
Yes, you could.
Aunt Flo, we appreciate
your concern
but we really do wanna
keep it simple.
Children, I know it seems
like an awful lot to go through
but after all it is
these rituals
that separate us
from the savages.
Maybe we should
think about it, John.
We have thought about it.
We've talked about it for hours.
We've invited people.
We've reserved the church.
Oh, that.
Oh, darling.
Not to worry.
All that can be arranged.
Just leave everything to me.
Saturday Evening Post.
John, I want you to know
there's some good stuff in here
and there's some stuff
that's not so good.
I know. I'm not satisfied
with it either.
- What's the problem?
- I wish I knew.
My own grandmother.
I've known her all my life.
I can't get her down
on paper.
I like her relationship
with the grandfather.
Oh, they worship
each other.
And her determination
to keep going after the stroke.
[John]
Grandma's always been
a real fighter.
It has the makings
of exactly the kind of article
I'm looking for, John.
But it has no depth.
May be we should
get some background
on her family history.
Where does all
that grit come from?
Sybil, I'm gonna need more time
than you've given me for this.
I'd love to, John,
but my deadline's firm.
There's no way
to change it now.
Okay, okay, don't worry
about it. I'll get it done.
I wonder if this isn't
a case where we've taken
the boy out of the country
and the country out of
the boy at the same time.
It's possible.
It's hard not to get
a citified veneer
when you've been living
in New York for a while.
Maybe you might find this
article easier to write
if you went back to that
mountain of yours for a visit.
That could be.
I suspect, John. You need
to go back to the well.
'Spend some time
with your grandmother.'
Get in touch with your
original inspiration.
Well, I'm always looking
for an excuse to go back home.
You've got one.
Maybe.
[knocking]
[John]
'It's me.'
Hi. Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't make dinner.
I-I tried to reach you
but your line's been busy.
I took the phone
off the hook.
Your Aunt Flo
called to suggest
the Sherry Netherland
for the reception.
She gets that way when she's
in the middle of a project.
Call her off, Janet.
She's driving me crazy.
- I've got a deadline.
- She's only trying to help.
Mother would take care of these
things, but we can't reach her.
The phone lines are down.
She's not your mother, and she's
taking over our wedding.
Let's not fight.
We're both tired.
Maybe you should go back
to Walton's Mountain
to finish your article.
You're the second person
who's told me that.
Everybody wants me
out of the way.
I just don't want us
to be at each other's throats.
Not now.
Not before the wedding.
How can I go anywhere
when you look at me like that?
[Aunt Flo]
'Hello. Hello.
Somebody left the door open.
Oh, John. How lucky
to find you here too.
Aunt Flo, what are
you doing here?
I've just come from
a perfectly marvelous party
and you'll never guess
who's back in town.
David Drucker.
He was over in Monaco.
He was doing one of his charity
balls for the Grimaldis.
He built
the whole affair
on a Scottish
Highland theme.
He's mad,
he's just completely mad.
Anyway, when I told him
about you children
'he insisted on seeing you
and giving you some ideas.'
Oh, Aunt Flo. You know
we're both terribly busy.
Oh, I know. I said they couldn't
take more than a minute.
But you see once we have
the plan settled on
you can just leave
it to me to carry it out.
We need to talk
about this.
John, I couldn't possibly
wiggle out of this.
I mean, he's offering
his services as a favor to me.
And you're gonna
to love his ideas.
You know, for this Scottish
thing, he had a regiment.
I mean an entire regiment.
A regiment of bagpipers.
And he served
stuffed Scottish grouse.
You ever had stuffed
Scottish grouse?
Actually, I like them.
They nest in the woods
outside our house.
My dad used to go in the morning
and shoot 'em for breakfast.
In fact, they taste
absolutely delicious
if you fry them with a mess
of biscuits and brown gravy.
You know, you're right. I'll be
back home on Walton's Mountain.
[door opens and closes]
Oh, my dear.
I hope I didn't
offend him.
I mean, it doesn't have
to be grouse.
Pheasant would do perfectly.
[owl hooting]
[door closing]
'Evening, Liv.'
- Evening.
- Is that anyone I know?
"Feminine Mystique."
What's that?
Some kind of romantic novel
that Corabeth gave you?
Not exactly.
- Has ma gone to bed?
- An hour ago.
Kept your supper
warm for you.
Yeah.
The meeting ran overtime.
The sky is changing so fast,
it's hard to keep up.
If I'd known this supervisor's
job was gonna take so much time
I never would have
run for office.
When those voters find out
how smart you are..
...they're gonna want you
to run for governor.
How'd you like to be
First Lady of Virginia?
[Olivia chuckling]
I'd rather go back to school.
- Seriously.
- You unhappy, Liv?
Sometimes when I'm here
in the house by myself
with nothing to do
and nobody to look after
I start wondering
what I'm good for.
Is something in this book
bothering you?
I'll tell you something
if you promise you won't laugh.
The other morning,
I found myself looking at you
and wondering
who is that stranger?
Did you ever look
at me like that?
I can't say as I have.
Guess I just need to get
to know myself a little better.
Find out where I fit
in the world.
There is so much I wanna know
and so much I don't know.
If it's that
important to you, Liv
maybe you ought
to go back to school.
You might like living
with a co-ed.
I think you'd look nice
in saddle shoes
and a tight sweater.
I'll see about dessert.
The only dessert
I want is you.
Now, let's see, um...what'd
you say your name was?
This conversation
is not over.
And then the husband says
"Well, what do you expect
after 50 years of marriage."
[laughing]
Anybody for seconds?
- Oh, me. Me, me.
- Mmm, not you.
Why not?
Because you've put on
too much weight.
- Even for your ninth month.
- Yes, doctor.
But you can help me
to seconds.
Me too.
You've decided
on a name?
Yes. If it's a girl,
Patsy Cline Walton.
- And if it's a boy?
- Elvis.
Of course.
- Hi, mama.
- Hi.
Mother and baby
are doing fine.
Took all three of you
to figure that out?
We're here to help.
Elizabeth, I think you'd better
pay close attention
because I've seen a gleam
in Drew's eye lately.
No, I'm not gonna
have any children yet.
I'm going back to school.
There's no reason
you can't do both.
I just signed up for a class
at Boatwright College.
- 'American Studies.'
- Mama, that's great.
My mother the freshman.
I don't mind telling you
I'm scared to death.
This mean I'm gonna have
to find a new babysitter?
I'll always be there
for my grandchildren.
And that includes you.
You be sure and let me know
the minute it's on its way.
You got it.
Better call me first
if I'm gonna deliver it.
Toni, that baby
better hurry up
or you're not gonna
make John-Boy's wedding.
Actually, I plan to have it
during the ceremony.
[laughing]
[Toni]
I'm not missing the wedding.
Brides are getting more
beautiful every day.
I would suggest that we get
Halsman to photograph you.
Well, I've already arranged
a photographer from my magazine.
He's done shoots
for me before.
I'll phone his agent
later today.
Flo, now what have you
come up with so far?
St. Bartholomew's Cathedral.
- An evening ceremony, I think.
- Mm-hmm?
Well, actually, we were planning
on a morning ceremony.
Wonderful.
Morning coats, top hats.
I've always wanted to do
a wedding with the bridal party
arriving in a carriage.
I don't think John's family
will go for morning coats.
They're country people
from Virginia.
The Virginians I know
are the tweedy types.
Fox hunters.
Horses. Hounds.
Actually, they are
mountain people.
Ah, I don't do moonshine.
[laughing]
You don't have to.
Two old ladies from the mountain
are bringing enough for all.
We'd better come up
with another idea, David.
Alright.
Ah, I'm thinking
of white lace.
A sea of candles.
Aunt Flo, that's not
what we have in mind at all.
String quartet.
Not quite right, David.
A thousand Cymbidium orchids
which I'll have flown
in from Hawaii, of course.
[bell tolling]
[female #2]
Excuse me.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Could you tell me which way
to the Science Building?
I'm sorry, I'm lost too,
if I don't hurry up
and figure out where I'm going,
I'm gonna be late for class.
What do you teach?
I'm not a teacher here.
I'm a student.
Oh, I wish my mama would
come back to school.
She's not even
as o...old as you.
Is that what I look like?
An old mother.
Oh, well, you don't
look old or anything.
But you don't look
like a regular student.
I-I mean, look,
I'm sorry, ma'am.
[chuckling]
Little twit.
[male #1]
And it will include a unit
on contemporary
political movements.
'Are there any questions?'
Mmm. Surprise, surprise.
Class dismissed.
Uh, Mrs. Walton, I'd like
to see you for a moment.
You want to speak to me?
I-I was curious as to why
you signed up for this class.
I wanted to know more
about our country.
Mm-hmm.
What makes it work?
How it works?
Sometimes, how
it doesn't work?
I thought this would be
a good place to start.
To start what?
Back to school.
I'm hoping to take more
classes next semester.
Maybe get my degree eventually.
Female students your age
are generally isolated
from the student population.
They find studying difficult
and they miss assignments
when their children get sick
and very often
they end up
failing
or dropping out.
Well, I don't intend
to do either.
Well, all the same, I'm not sure
you belong in this class.
Have you considered
taking, uh..
...home economics?
Professor Trumbull, I could
teach home economics
with what I've learned
raising seven children
and being married
half my life.
I could also teach nursing,
bookkeeping, psychology
first aid, carpentry,
and gardening.
I can shovel snow,
I can deal with a leaky faucet
dead car battery
and a leaky roof.
What I cannot deal with
is human ignorance.
Well..
...this is certainly going
to be an interesting semester.
[birds chirping]
Carry your books?
Oh, John-Boy,
what a nice surprise.
I am so proud of you going to
college. I can't believe it.
If I'd known how hard
it was gonna be
I might've thought twice.
What are you doing here?
I came home to finish
writing an article.
[laughing]
The minute we heard you were
writing about grandma
we rushed to help.
No. Nothing's changed.
They still won't let me
get any work done.
Don't forget the time
that grandpa
got thrown out of the hospital
when grandma had her stroke.
That was something else.
Or the time she found the jar of
a recipe in grandpa's toolbox.
[Bob]
She didn't speak to him
for a whole month after that.
Keep that up, and grandma
won't let John-Boy
write an article
about her at all.
How do you like the idea
of being a celebrity, ma?
Come on.
Well, grandma. Maybe they'll
put you on the cover.
♪ Grandma was a cover girl
Grandma was a cover girl ♪
on a big-time magazine ♪
I love having
brothers and sisters
but I'm gonna need
a lock for my door.
♪ Grandma was a cover girl
Grandma was a cover girl ♪
♪ On a big-time ♪
♪ I said a big-time magazine ♪
[applause]
Woo.
[knocking on door]
Come in.
- Still up, son?
- 'Yeah.'
You know, I've been thinking.
That old cabin
over by Drucilla's Pond?
Yeah?
That'd be a quiet
place for you.
That is a great idea. I'll take
my stuff over in the morning.
What you got there,
the old family Bible?
Yeah, I've been studying it
looking at the births, deaths,
weddings, baptisms.
The whole family's here.
Except I can't find a single
entry for grandma's daddy.
You won't find him
in here either.
I won't? Why not?
Grandma has her reasons.
She might not like you
stirring things up either.
Don't work too late, son.
I won't.
- Goodnight.
[slow music]
[insects chirping]
[yawning]
Ah, I keep reading the same
sentence over and over again.
I think my brain's
stopped working.
Same here.
No matter how many times
I add up these bills
I just can't figure out
how we're gonna pay
for all that equipment.
I knew I should've kept
a closer eye on Ben.
You couldn't be
in two places at once.
Runnin' the mill
and the campaign, both.
For once, I thought
our money problems was over.
I could wring his neck.
Ben thought he was
doin' the right thing.
On top of everything else
is John-Boy's wedding.
There's new clothes, trip
to New York, hotel rooms.
There's that rehearsal dinner
we're supposed to put on.
I suppose that'll mean
a fancy restaurant.
This whole thing could cost us
over a thousand dollars.
Oh, oh.
If that subdivision goes
through, won't that help?
That's what puts me
in a bind, Liv.
If I vote
for the subdivision
it looks like I'm featherin'
my own nest.
If I vote against it,
we're gonna lose a lot of money.
[slow music]
[birds chirping]
Thank the Lord
some things don't change.
[John]
Sparrows still nest
in the eaves.
Fish still bite
in the pond.
There's that canoe
I used to paddle around in.
[John]
Yeah.
We bring it in each winter,
patch her up in the spring.
I give your mama a ride
when the weather warms.
Hope Janet and I are gonna be
happy as you and mama.
I don't wanna pry but everything
alright between you and Janet?
You showed up
kinda sudden.
She's got an aunt
that's takin' over the wedding
and I had to get
out of there.
Before marrying, you ever wonder
you were doing the right thing?
I don't know a man
who didn't get the jitters.
I've been single so long, I got
my own way of doin' things.
Closer it gets,
I start wondering
if I'm gonna be able
to change my ways.
She's probably wonderin'
the same thing.
What?
How would you feel
if she changed her mind?
That'll about kill me.
There's your answer.
You know, if you love
each other enough
all the doubt in the world won't
keep you from being together.
Daddy, it would mean a lot to me
if you'd be my best man.
Oh, son, you got
brothers for that.
Oh, I can't
play favorites.
Come to think of it, I probably
am the best man in your life.
[chuckles]
Are you saying yes?
John-Boy, I'd be honored.
You holler
if you need anything.
Thank you, daddy.
- Now, this one.
- Yes.
Perfect for the men.
Absolutely perfect.
[doorbell chimes]
- 'What about the ladies?'
- 'Well, no.'
'I can always depend
on your taste.
'You don't mean that.
I can tell you're lying.'
What is it?
What's wrong?
Oh, everything is fine, dear.
Why do you ask?
I was in a meeting and my
secretary brought in a message
that said that you
had to see me at once.
Darling, I'm sorry,
but we had to consult with you.
David has come up
with an idea
that will appeal to you
and your young man.
Ready?
A folk wedding.
We'll rent a ballroom
at the Waldorf
and decorate it
like a barn.
'Shocks of corn.
Bales of hay.'
'Pumpkins and
pomegranates, etc.'
We'll bring up a country
band from Nashville
and some dancers.
Now, I have already
spoken with Agnes.
And she is going to choreograph
some special folk dances.
And Rudi says
he'll be the caller.
Everybody will be
able to wear overalls
and plaid shirts--
I hate it.
- I beg your pardon.
- I hate it.
Oh..
We were so sure that this
time we'd gotten it right.
Aunt Flo, I don't want
a hillbilly wedding.
I don't want a ballroom
at the Warldorf
nor do I want my guests wearing
overalls and plaid shirts.
And I do not want Rudolph
Nureyuv calling the dances.
At this point, I'm thinking
of not getting married at all.
Maybe I'll just
live in sin.
No, darling.
I don't recommend it.
Now, not to worry.
David and I will come up
with an idea that's suitable
for the daughter
of an ambassador.
Aunt Flo..
...I love you.
David, I-I know
you mean well
but this is not another
of your charity balls.
This is my wedding.
This is mywedding.
And I'm taking it back.
[door opens and closes]
So, you need anything else,
John-Boy?
No, thanks, Ike.
That's about it.
John-Boy, you may have heard
that I too am pursuing
the literary muse.
Oh, well, I wish you luck,
Corabeth.
Perhaps you'd be willing to read
a chapter or two of my novel.
As a favor, you might say,
from one wordsmith to the other.
I'd love to, but now is not
a good time 'cause I'm working.
Oh, I understand
that perfectly.
- Tomorrow perhaps?
- We'll talk about it sometime.
It's good to see you, Corabeth.
Take care, Ike.
See ya, John-Boy.
[male #1]
And what of the other symbols
we have come to associate
with our country?
Can anybody tell me where
Plymouth Rock is located?
Does anyone know
when Jamestown was founded?
'Who can tell me the statement
of the Statue of Liberty'
its significance to us all?
Mrs. Walton..
'...you've had little at all
to say in this class thus far.'
Do you have any ideas?
Are you going
to remain silent all term?
A woman...named Emma Lazarus
wrote the poem
that's on the base
of the Statue of Liberty.
[softly]
Ah..
And would you be so kind
as to locate a copy of that poem
and bring it to class one day?
I know the poem
if you'd like to hear it.
[male #1]
By all means.
'It goes..'
..."Give me your tired,
your poor
"your huddled masses
yearning to breathe free.
"The wretched refuse
of your teeming shore.
"Send these, the homeless,
tempest-tossed to me.
I lift my lamp
beside the golden door."
Very well said.
But it doesn't tell us
how you perceive the ideas
'it is trying to convey,
Mrs. Walton.'
I was about to do that,
Professor Trumbull.
The Statue of Liberty
is a symbol of hope
for people coming
from other countries.
To me, she's like a mother
offering them shelter and love
and a place to dream.
And since all our forefathers
came from somewhere else
I guess that applies
to all of us.
I think that's the message
the poem is trying to convey.
What do we have here,
a petition?
That's right. It is.
There are 65 names on there.
And they are all
concerned citizens
who don't think that
the development will be good
'for Jefferson County.'
Well, I'm a little surprised.
Wouldn't this bring new
customers into your store, Ike?
Well, not if they build
a new supermarket up there.
And the taxes will go up.
And suppose they decide
to pave all the roads?
It could mean a lot of new jobs.
That would be good
for the whole community.
We know all that. What really
is at stake is the way we live.
'Simple and neighborly and our
doors are always unlocked'
and the welcome mat
is always out.
We don't want Walton's Mountain
to be turned into
'some kind of suburb.'
I understand.
Well, I can't promise you
how I'll vote.
But I'll give this
serious consideration.
We knew you would.
That's why we voted for you.
Madison's tied up all this land
at the base of Pinetop Mountain.
They want to build 25 duplexes
and 50 single family homes.
That's a lot of lumber.
We could get rich on it.
And there'll be plenty of jobs.
- What do you think of it, ma?
- I don't know.
I don't even know
where I stand yet either.
'I can see both sides.'
[door opening]
Oh, I'm glad
somebody's still up.
How's the writin' going?
I've been over to the courthouse
going through records.
I went to the
county library.
Not a word. As if
the man never existed.
Why's it so important now?
It's one thing
to avoid something
because it's uncomfortable.
But to erase a man
from history.
You're making a mountain
out of a molehill.
No. If there's a skeleton hiding
in the family closet, grandma
I'd like to know
what it is.
I want my story to be honest.
How can it be honest
if a big piece
of your history
is missing?
- Go easy on her, son.
- She wouldn't want me to.
- She's the toughest person.
- John-Boy, you're over-tired.
You can say that again.
[knocking on door]
Janet, sweetheart,
what are you doing here?
I just threw myself together,
and I got out of New York.
What happened?
- Hi.
- Hey.
I've taken a leave of absence
from my job.
If it's alright with everybody,
I'd-I'd like for us
to get married here
at Walton's Mountain.
I think that would be great.
What about Aunt Flo?
I fired her.
Olivia, I'm not even sure
my folks are gonna make it.
I'm on my own
and I need you.
Well, bring your things in
and get settled.
We'll talk about
making plans later.
Come on.
I can't say
I'm unhappy about this
but how are we gonna
manage a wedding
on top of
everything else?
I haven't
the slightest idea.
[knock on door]
Who is it?
Oh, Corabeth.
It's so nice to see you
but I'm-I'm really busy.
Oh, good! I deduced that
you might be scribbling away.
Corabeth, I don't scribble.
I write.
There's a big difference.
I did not mean to make light
of our profession.
And I didn't mean to be rude.
I got so much on my mind.
I'm behind schedule and I can't
express what I need to say.
Well, perhaps if you hear
just a bit of my novel
that will clear
the cobwebs away.
I find there's nothing
so inspiring
as the company
of a fellow writer.
Go right ahead.
'Of course, this is
just a rough draft.'
"Romance on the High Sea..
"...by Corabeth Godsey.
"The young novelist,
Pierre Boudin
"stood on the deck, his shirt
unbuttoned to the waist
"revealing a wind-burned chest
rippling with masculine
muscularity."
Corabeth, young novelists
rarely strip to the waist--
"Below, the beautiful
young model lay trembling
"as she awaited his footsteps.
"She knew he would come,
and her bosoms heaved
"at the thought
of his fiery hands
on her firm young flesh."
I hope this is not too strong
for you, John-Boy.
I'm...speechless.
Oh, thank you.
You have no idea how much
your praise means to me.
"The helpless young woman knew
that to resist him was futile
and the desperate
pounding of her heart--"
Corabeth, stop it. Please.
Please stop. Stop.
Really? Really,
there's much more.
Corabeth...I don't know
how to tell you this.
It's not good. It's..
It's not good.
But...I'm following
the instructions
that came with that
correspondence course.
And I was inspired
by the romance
'between you and Janet.'
I don't like
hurting your feelings.
But you're my friend.
So I have to be truthful
about your...work.
You probably
can be a writer.
But instead of this nonsense,
you gotta start writing
about something
that you're familiar with.
Something you've
experienced and observed.
Something that you care about
with feeling and passion.
I'm afraid I've experienced
very little in my lifetime.
You might think
that's true
but if you look,
I'll bet you'll find
that there's plenty of love
and romance in your own life.
But you gotta
look for it.
I'm sorry, Corabeth,
but I had to be honest.
Oh, and I appreciate it.
I do.
And Corabeth,
there's one more thing.
Your hero's name,
Boudin?
It means...pudding.
[door opens and closes]
Oh, how about this one?
Isn't it wonderful?
It's not really you.
I don't think
it's really anyone.
I like this one.
Oh, that's too sexy
for a bridesmaid's dress.
Let's go somewhere else where
they carry the latest styles.
You know,
the best shop in town?
[both]
This is the best shop in town.
Oh!
'Janet, it's time to learn
about high fashion'
'on Walton's Mountain.'
Oh, I'd love to help,
but I can't sew.
Janet.
You can cut.
I can cut.
Right here.
It's a good place to start.
Just cutting right
along the line.
All the way around.
Oh, there you are,
Corabeth.
I'm sorry, I didn't wanna
wake you so early.
Oh, very considerate of you
but I wanted to get this
in the mail quickly.
- Your correspondence course.
- I'm returning it.
It's filled
with erroneous advice.
I expect to get my money back as
promised in the advertisement.
I never got to read
your first novel.
I have abandoned it.
I'm starting
a new work
entitled
"The Storekeeper's Wife."
Doesn't sound
very romantic.
Au contraire,John-Boy assuresme that there is a great deal
of romance and love
in being a storekeeper's wife.
Do you really believe
that, Corabeth?
Mr. Godsey, please.
Not in broad daylight.
Where's your
high-powered crew?
They're out making a delivery.
- Selling more lumber, I hope.
- I'll give you a hand.
There're some gloves
over there.
I need a chance
to let off some steam.
Yeah, same with me.
There's some rumors
going around I don't like.
Bad rumors?
Well, something about me
being a crook.
You got too good a reputation.
Nobody's gonna believe that.
Don't count on it.
This is politics.
Right over here.
-This alright?
-Yep.
How's that
article coming?
I'm not getting
anywhere with it.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd take a look at it.
- I don't know about writing.
- But you do know grandma.
That's for sure.
- Alright, I'll give it a try.
- Thanks.
[bell tolls]
Ah, Mrs. Walton,
what a pleasure.
Come walk with me
to my next class.
Don't we have
an appointment today?
Yes, I have
to clear my topic
for that oral report
you assigned us.
Have you gotten an idea yet?
Yes.
I'd like to do something on
the status of women in America.
Well, you'll have
to be more specific.
I'm reading this book
by Betty Friedan.
It's called
The Feminine Mystique.
What makes you think that would
be appropriate for my class?
She explains
how difficult it is
for women to achieve
in our society.
Some people try to make it
difficult for us to have careers
or...to get an education.
It seems to me our
country would be stronger
if we made it possible
for everybody to take part.
Alright, Mrs. Walton,
you can go ahead with it.
But I am warning you,
this is not the kind of
subject matter that will
assure you a passing grade.
You don't get it.
It's not the grade
that's important to me.
It's the future of women
in this country I worry about.
Half the population
in this country is female
and three of those women
are my daughters.
I don't know
your three daughters.
But I'm beginning
to know you.
And I think I would be
quite foolish indeed
to antagonize the Walton women
to say nothing of half
the population of this country.
Huh, good luck with it.
We're delighted your nuptials
are gonna take place
on Walton's Mountain, John-Boy.
So am I, Miss Emily.
You'll be married
in the very church
that Ashley Longworth and I
were to march down the aisle.
Yes, ma'am.
Here you are, John-Boy.
Papa's old portmanteau.
It has all his letters.
And I hope, you find
what you're looking for.
- Thank you, Miss Mamie.
- You take it.
I'll take care of it and bring
it back as soon as possible.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye, Miss Emily.
- Bye.
Oh, what a fine, young man.
I wonder whatever became
of Ashley Longworth.
He kissed me, you know.
'It was in October'
and all the leaves
were the color of gold.
It's a long way
from St. Bartholomew's.
It's-it's intimate.
I still can't believe it.
In a few days, dad and I
will be walking down this aisle.
Yup.
Well, I'm not quite
as distinguished
as Ambassador Gilchrist
but would you care to practice?
Dad can be intimidating
but when you get
to know my parents
you'll find
they're good people.
I'm looking forward
to meeting 'em.
Do you ever sleep
with the windows open?
- Year round. How about you?
- I love fresh air.
- Do you like to read in bed?
- I like to read everywhere.
How do you feel
about big families?
I don't know how I feel
about any-size family.
Big, medium, or little.
Probably guess that's something
we're gonna have to talk about.
I've never been around babies.
They scare me.
Too bad, you had to fall
in love with a Walton.
Maybe you shouldn't be
marrying an only child.
Does it make a difference..
...when we have each other?
I guess not.
[door opening]
'Lot of homework, huh?'
Mostly I've been working
on those bridesmaid's dresses.
How's John-Boy's article?
Tell you the truth,
I don't think it's very good.
He can't concentrate.
He's got a lot of things
on his mind.
I know. That's why
I can't tell him that.
You have to.
He asked you to be honest.
It seems like we got
an awful lot of things
to worry about
around here lately.
Do you think John-Boy and Janet
are right for each other?
I think Janet can hold her own
with our son, Liv.
I don't think writers
are easy to live with.
She is a thoroughbred.
That's what worries me.
They come from such
different backgrounds.
That's what people said about
us when we got married.
I guess differences
don't always matter.
Some of them do.
Why, John Walton.
[honking]
What the heck?
[dog barking]
[country music]
What's goin' on out there?
[music continues]
Just hold your horses!
Hello.
I know it's a little late
to come calling
but I've been searching all over
this countryside for a hotel
and I've come to the conclusion
that there isn't one.
You're right.
This isn't one either.
Aunt Flo?
Wha-what are you doing here?
Janet, darling, I was thinking
about your honeymoon.
I was in the bath and..
Oh, how do you do?
And, um, I had
the most wonderful idea.
You've got to let me
do this for you, sweetheart.
[Janet]
'Fine, fine. Come on in.'
So that's Aunt Flo.
[grunts]
Oh! Gee!
[birds chirping]
- Good morning, daddy.
- 'Mornin'.'
Whatever that is,
I hope it's edible.
Your mama was teaching Janet
to make baking powder biscuits.
They wanted you
to have some.
I like the room service
at this hotel.
Thank you.
Mmm.
Janet wanted me to tell you
her Aunt Flo got in last night.
Isn't she gonna give up.
Where is she?
She's staying with us.
I'll avoid the house
as much as possible.
That was my plan.
- I read your article, son.
- What do you think?
I don't know.
Seems to me that,
maybe you're looking
at your grandma through
rose-colored glasses.
I know.
I left the vinegar out.
You turned her
into some kind of saint.
You know if grandma
hadn't been tough
and stubborn as a mule
she never would've
overcome her stroke
or gone on living
without grandpa.
I intended toughening her up,
it's just that..
I think what's throwing
this whole thing off
is the missing ancestry story.
This gap in her family history.
'I just can't get past that.'
Well, I gave you
my two cents worth.
I'll let you get on
with your work.
Thanks, daddy.
[breathing heavily]
- Hi, kids.
- Hi, mama.
Grandma.
I went to see the
Baldwin ladies the other day.
And they gave me some
of your papa's old papers
and I found this letter
about your daddy.
I thought we agreed
to forget about that.
You know what I found out
from this letter?
Grandpa Morgan fought with
the Union in the Civil War.
- Damnit! Damnit! Damnit!
- Alright. Alright.
The war of Northern Aggression.
John-Boy.
'I also found out
he was anti-slavery'
'like a lot
of these hill people.'
And when he joined
the Union Army
everyone around here
called him a traitor.
[Olivia]
'Is that all, grandma?'
Is that what you didn't
want us to find out?
As far as I'm concerned,
my great-granddaddy is a hero.
I wanna tell
the world about him.
It's alright, ma.
I'll talk to him.
Daddy, this should
not be a secret.
It's wrong to bury
somebody's history.
That's enough, son.
I think...we should all sleep
on this, especially grandma.
It's not good for her
to get upset like this.
Grandma, I'm sorry about this.
I love you,
and I respect you
but I'm gonna write the truth.
'Oh-oh, something's up.'
Maybe I oughta go, huh?
You better not.
Morning, daddy.
I thought it was good
till I read this.
"Supervisor Walton in sweetheart
deal with developer.
"It's been discovered that John
Walton and Son Lumber Company
"has a lucrative contract
with Madison Developers
"to supply lumber
should their subdivision
receive county approval."
And that vote comes tonight.
Go on, read.
There's more.
"Supervisor Walton's integrity
is in question for his failure
to report this
conflict of interest."
Not only is our whole
business at stake
but so is my reputation.
For 200 years, our family
has lived in these parts
and this is the first time that
a shadow's been put on our name.
A stain like this
hangs around.
On me, on your brothers
and sisters, on everybody.
Daddy, I'm really sorry.
You got me in to this.
What are you gonna do about it?
I don't know.
I wouldn't blame you
if you threw me out.
I feel the same way, John.
You oughta fire
both of us right now.
I'm considerin' it.
[Ben sighs]
It's bad enough she tried
to take over the wedding.
She is not gonna
take over the honeymoon.
[Janet]
'Would you please
stop shouting?'
She's only suggesting that
we go to the Bahamas.
Suggesting? She already
bought the airline tickets.
'She hired a limousine
to go to the airport.'
- She's made reservations.
- She meant well.
She's only trying
to do something nice.
She'll be at our wedding night
to ensure we get that right.
You might've been appreciative.
You insulted her.
It was long overdue!
Maybe we should call
the whole thing off!
That's fine. Maybe I can get
some work done.
- Fine!
Fine.
[car starts]
John-Boy.
Janet.
[knock on door]
How you doin'?
I tried to call my mom,
but the lines are down.
I don't know what to do.
I know it's not the same
but she's there, and I'm here.
Is there anything
I can do?
I never knew
he had such a temper.
Oh, he has
a temper, alright.
Takes a lot for him
to lose it.
He yelled at me.
Well, you were doing some
pretty good yelling yourself.
I don't know what made me think
I wanted to marry him.
All of a sudden, he seems
like a total stranger.
I know what you mean.
Marriage changes everything,
doesn't it?
It sure does.
First, you lose your name.
You find strange clothes
in your closet.
You discover that wonderful man
you married snores in his sleep
and you consider the
consequences of murder.
All my life, I've never had
to share my room with anyone.
I've been able to do what I
wanna do when I wanna do it.
All that's gonna
be different.
Maybe that's what's
bothering you.
Instead of John-Boy
being upset over
what he has a right
to be upset over.
Hard being married, isn't it?
It's the hardest thing
you'll ever do.
- I'm scared.
- Marriage is scary.
But I think it's worth it.
No. I'm scared
he won't come back.
Oh!
[male #2]
'Alright.
Let's settle down.'
[hammering]
Let's settle down, please.
The first item on the agenda
is Madison's request
to build a one hundred unit
subdivision.
'In regard to this issue, there
may be a conflict of interest'
'on the Board of Supervisors.'
Mr. Walton, would you
care to address
the accusations against you?
Mr. Chairman, may I have
the floor?
- I'd like to say something.
- Go ahead, Ben.
Father asked me to take care
of the mill during his campaign.
I made the deal with
Madison Development Company.
Long before I knew
that my father was gonna
be coming here to vote today.
Daddy never had anything
to do with any of this.
I just wanted him
to be proud of me.
Instead, I've
made him look bad.
I'm sorry.
[group chattering]
'If there are no objections,
let's move on to the vote.'
Now, you all know
where I stand.
I feel that the subdivision
would benefit Jefferson County.
I vote, yes.
All supervisors in favor,
could I see a show of hands.
Two.
Opposed?
'Two oppose.'
Supervisor Walton,
looks like it's up to you.
It seems to me
we have a problem.
There's unemployment here.
Folks need jobs.
'At the same time,
we don't want to destroy'
'the air and the water
and the woods'
'that makes Jefferson County
such a fine place to live in.'
So...I'm gonna vote
no on this proposal.
'But if those folks bring
back a simpler proposal'
that provides jobs
but doesn't ruin the air we
breathe or the water we drink
then I'll vote for it.
'And if they do come back
with a new proposal'
I'll make damn sure
my company's not involved.
Mr. Anderson, it could've
turned out different.
- Handled that well, John.
- Thank you, Ike.
Goodnight, fellas.
I like the way you handled
yourself tonight, son.
I appreciate it.
Drew and I are willing
to take a cut in pay
till we get
outta this hole.
I just might have
to take you up on that.
Unless you get out there
and hustle up some business.
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah, you bet.
Just don't stand there,
let's see some hustle.
- Okay, daddy.
- Let's do it.
[crickets chirping]
John.
You're a tougher young man
than I thought.
You're pretty tough yourself.
You know, uh..
John, I see that I have caused
you and Janet some distress.
But I want you
to know that I..
...I acted
only out of love.
I never doubted that.
I never had any children
of my own.
I think I just forgot to.
And my brother
just had the one.
'And I was there
when Janet was born'
'and I looked forward to being
there when she married.'
But I really think now
that I should leave
before I break up this
wedding altogether.
Too late for that.
You can't leave now.
Why?
Because you're family.
Besides, I thought you were
gonna be my matron of honor.
Sweetie.
Only if you promise
to toss the wedding bouquet
in my general direction.
[Janet]
'I promise.'
I'm sorry.
I should not have yelled
at you like that.
I'm sorry too. I..
I didn't know how
to stand up to Flo.
Well..
...the Bahamas
are fine with me.
No. No, no.
We'll make our own plans.
We'll...go someplace
simple and quiet
where we can be by ourselves,
just the two of us.
Why don't you leave
our first night to me?
I know just the place.
It's a small inn on the
north side of Drucilla's Pond.
Quiet.
You can hear the leaves
rustle at night.
In the morning, you can hear
the birds call to each other.
That sounds good.
And the next day..
...we'll go to the Bahamas.
We will?
Too good a deal
to pass up.
[laughing]
It's a beautiful
quilt, Olivia.
How long have you
been working on it?
Oh, quite a while.
I had a feeling
the first time I met Janet.
Has quilting been a family
tradition for a long time?
It goes back a way.
A family is like the rings made
when a pebble drops in a pond.
'Like the rings on this quilt.'
I wonder, if I had, had
a quilt like this
perhaps, one of my marriages
might've lasted a little longer.
[laughing]
It takes more
than a quilt.
[Aunt Flo]
'You should know.'
What's your secret, Olivia?
I've no idea. Sometimes,
I think I know a thing or two.
Then a whole new set
of problems comes up.
I'd like to think
that each stitch is like
a special wish
for the bride and groom.
My stitches are
for the happiness
I wish them
in the years to come.
What is my wish for them?
The word is romance.
It's what makes
the world go round.
I wish them a happy,
carefree wedding
and forgiveness
for my excesses.
[laughing]
You were forgiven
a long time ago.
Where's grandma?
Isn't she going to join us?
Nope. She says she's not
even coming to the wedding.
Oh, mama!
What happened?
[phone rings]
Would you get that, Janet?
It's probably for John-Boy.
Walton residence.
Speaking.
Dad! How are you?
Where are you?
It's my folks. They're at
the airport in London.
'John and I will pick you
up at the airport'
'in Charlottesville
tomorrow night.'
Wonderful.
See you then.
Bravo!
I don't understand
what's keeping 'em.
They should've been
here an hour ago.
Will you stop worrying
and sit down?
I've never entertained
an ambassador before.
If they're anything like Janet,
they'll be real down to earth.
What's the name of that country
he's ambassador to?
I'll think of it.
Oh, this tie
is killing me.
I'll be glad when this
wedding stuff is over.
[phone rings]
Get back to normal livin'.
Hello?
Janet! You alright?
We'll be right there.
- What's up?
- They're all in jail.
'Jail?'
- Howdy, folks.
- We're here to see--
- Daddy!
- Oh, there he is.
- John-Boy, what's going on?
- Janet, what happened?
The plane was late,
I was trying
to make up some time
on the way home.
He was doing that alright.
75 per in a 60-mile zone.
- John-Boy.
- You lock people up for that?
We do. When they yell at the
officer and call him "Stupid."
Uh, John, Olivia,
these are my parents
Uh, Ralph and
Charlotte Gilchrist.
[both]
How do you do?
That one kept talking
about something, uh
diplomatic impunity,
whatever that is.
I-I am a United States
ambassador.
That entitles me
to certain privileges.
And I am a deputy sheriff
of Jefferson County, Virginia
and this is my jail.
Mr. Walton, my husband and I
left a small African country
over 48 hours ago.
In that time, we've not
had a change of clothes
a decent meal or used
a clean bathroom.
Could you please
get us out of here?
Yes, ma'am.
Now, you must be new
around here, deputy.
I'm John Walton,
County Supervisor.
And you're just gonna have
to learn something about this
diplomatic..
[both]
Immunity.
...immunity.
Supervisor Walton.
Yeah, I know about you.
We sure could use some
things fixed around here
when you get a chance.
And we need to get
these people outta here.
These two young people
are getting married tomorrow.
Well, why didn't
you say so?
I'm letting you off
with just a warning.
Well, that's decent of you.
Now, if you'll open this cell
door, we'll be on our way.
Can't.
It's broke.
You get me a bigger budget,
and I'll fix it.
- Ah!
- Oh!
Now, you must make sure
this thing can lock.
Any criminal
could walk out..
No, no, not you.
Oh, don't worry.
He'll-he'll get over it.
Sorry about this, daddy.
I'd say we haven't exactly
gotten off to a beautiful start
with the Gilchrists.
Janet, in my professional life
I have found myself
in some very strange places.
Still, I have trouble believing
that I am in the
backwoods of Virginia.
Miles from a streetlight,
with a clan of people
that seems to number
into the thousands.
And that my daughter is about
to marry into that clan of
folksy, fertile
poor but honest salt of
the Earth mountaineers.
Have-have-have you given
this sufficient thought?
I think so.
And you're totally comfortable
with what you're doing?
Even though it may mean
that you'll have to subsist on
chitlins and bootleg liquor
when the going gets tough?
I've never been happier
in my life, daddy.
Good.
Because I like your young man,
and I like where he comes from.
These are good people.
There's only one thing, daddy.
I doubt very much they've ever
had chitlins in their lives.
Well, bring 'em on out to Iowa,
and we'll give 'em a sample.
Tell her, Charlotte.
Well, your father
has decided
to retire from
the Diplomatic Corps.
We wanna be home again.
We want you to have
a home to come home to.
Not an embassy
in some troubled country.
We're going home to Iowa
to buy back the house
on East River Drive.
I've always loved
that house.
I know. Well, you've gotten
in touch with John's roots.
In Iowa, John can get
in touch with yours.
You know, I cannot
wait to bring him
and our children
to that house.
How many children
do you have in mind?
Well, let's put it this way.
He's a Walton.
[laughs]
Look at that moon.
How about when
all this is over
I take you
on a second honeymoon?
Good. Aunt Flo
can arrange it.
Maybe that little cottage
in the Bahamas is free.
Well, with all
this wedding stuff
and that moon.
How about going
to Bahamas?
If it's between semesters.
Liv, what is a Bahama,
and where is it?
It's probably
a little south of here.
[laughing]
I love you.
[owl hooting]
Do you think your parents
will ever forgive me?
For landing them in jail?
No, for taking you
away from 'em.
My dad said you were
folksy and fertile.
[laughing]
Okay.
But he and mother
both approve.
Do you realize...
this is the last time
that we will look up
at the moon as single people?
You scared?
I'm terrified.
Me too.
It's not too late
to back out, you know?
I'm saving it
for the altar.
Oh! Oh, my God,
are you alright?
[laughing]
[tapping]
[loud bang]
What's that racket?
[tapping continues]
There's a whole bunch
of strangers out there.
Looks like
Aunt Flo is in charge.
[groan]
Darling, don't
drop that table.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, young man,
I want the bandstand
and the dance floor to be
at an angle off the mill.
It'll fit, I've just paced it.
Oh, flowers? Yeah.
[whistles]
- Flowers?
- Yes, ma'am.
Yes. Come right
here with me.
Hello, darling.
What's she doing now?
I think she's trying to make up
for all the trouble she caused.
Charlotte,
what's going on?
This is Flo's gift
to the newlyweds.
A party with all the fixings.
Do they know about this?
Believe it or not, she spoke
to them, and they agreed.
She's giving them the kind
of party that they really want.
These tables end-to-end across
here in a line for the food.
[whistles]
I had a first sergeant once
not half as tough as she is.
[Aunt Flo]
'No, eight chairs around
each of the round tables'
and then scatter some
of the chairs randomly
beyond the tables
where the food is.
- Breakfast?
- Yes.
[Aunt Flo]
'Now, somebody
bring me a ladder..'
Breakfast, pa?
We got it.
Just keep breathing.
Janet, your friends
from New York have arrived.
Ah. Thanks, Elizabeth.
Mom, do I look okay?
Perfectly beautiful.
All of you are beautiful.
- Thank you.
I like having sisters
help me dress.
How are you feeling inside?
Like I might be ill.
[soft piano music]
Grandma.
You wouldn't really miss
my wedding, would you?
It's the most important
day of my life
'and I'd like you
to share it with me.'
I'm sorry that
I hurt you
but if this is your way
of punishing me, it's working.
Of course,
I can't blame you.
You're as stubborn
as your father was.
He did what he felt was right
no matter what people thought.
And I know somebody else
who would have admired him too.
My grandpa.
I wish he was gonna
be here today.
It's gonna be tough
not having any grandparents
at my own wedding.
I don't know.
[sighs]
My very best and most favorite
husband gave me this.
We were in Paris. We were
standing on the Pont Alexandre.
The most beautiful
bridge in the world.
And he said to me, "Flo
"I give you this bridge
and this little piece of lace
to remind you of it always."
Thank you, Aunt Flo.
Thank you for everything.
Well, you know
I like to help.
My darling, I do not have
a bridge to give you.
Just my love.
And one more thing.
My mother wore these
on her wedding day.
I wore them on mine.
I want you to give them
to your daughter
when the time comes.
Thank you, mom.
Look who's gonna be next.
[laughing]
- Not me.
- Oh...how about you?
- Mm-hmm, not again.
- Aww.
I don't know what's the matter
with me today.
I cannot tie my tie
for love nor money.
I'd say it's more love
than money.
Just like old times, huh?
You have to stand behind me
just like you were
tying your own tie.
- Here you go.
- Got it?
- Is that alright?
- Yeah, it looks pretty good.
Daddy, were you this nervous
when you got married?
Well, your mom and me eloped.
But, yeah, I was nervous.
Every time I looked at her,
she was so beautiful
I could hardly talk.
Oh, my.
See what I mean?
Mama, you are gonna be
the prettiest la..
Oh, my Lord.
The ring.
You just gave it
to me, remember?
Better get him
out of here.
I'll go tell ma
we're leaving.
Daddy never could
get his tie right.
Well, uh, I guess after today
everything's gonna be different.
I can't help thinking about you
when you were a boy.
So serious and dreamy.
Always asking questions.
Climbing the tree to dream
and look at the clouds.
John Junior, you
turned out real good.
I love you, mama.
Ready?
[soft music]
[sighs]
Ready?
I am now.
[female #3]
Come on now.
We're gonna be late.
[pipe organ music]
[music continues]
[audience whispering]
[bridal music]
[music continues]
You okay?
I'm okay.
Yeah, I'm okay.
[piano music
"Here Comes The Bride"]
[gasping]
[music continues]
♪ Oh, promise me that
someday you and I ♪
♪ Will take our love
together to the sky ♪
♪ Where we can be alone
and faith renew ♪
♪ And find the hollows
where those flowers grew ♪
♪ Those fresh sweet violets
of early spring ♪
This is it.
♪ Which come in whispers,
thrill us both ♪
♪ And sing of love ♪
♪ So beautiful
our life with thee ♪
♪ Oh, promise me ♪
[Mosely]
'Dearly beloved.'
Toni, are you alright?
Oh, Jason, go get
my medical bag out of the car.
Do we have time
to get her to the hospital?
With contractions
this close together, no.
This baby's in a hurry.
If any man
can show just cause
why they may not
be legally joined
let him speak now
or forever hold his peace.
- 'Push, Toni, push.'
- 'I am pushing.'
[Toni groaning]
[Mosely]
'Will you, John, have this woman
to be thy wedded wife?'
'To live together
after God's ordinance'
'in the holiest state
of matrimony.'
I will.
I can't stand it.
[Mosely]
Will you, Janet,
have this man
to be thy wedded husband?
'To live together
after God's ordinance'
'in the holiest state
of matrimony.'
I will.
[Toni groaning]
[Mosely]
'I now pronounce you
husband and wife.'
[baby crying]
[laughs]
[baby squealing]
[Mosely]
'If you wish, you may now,
seal your vows with a kiss.'
[baby continues crying]
Patsy Cline Walton.
[crying continues]
Ladies and gentlemen...
it's a girl.
[attendees cheering]
[cheering continues]
[gasps]
'Ladies and gentlemen,
it gives me great pleasure'
to present Mr. and Mrs.
John Walton, Jr.
[recessional hymn on piano]
[audience cheering]
[country music]
[music continues]
[male narrator]
The ceremony was over
but the celebration
was just beginning.
Aunt Flo had more
than redeemed herself.
And the reception
was just about
the grandest party ever held
on Walton's Mountain.
It was a real combination
of city and country
plain and fancy.
[no audio]
[country music]
[guests cheering]
- Bravo.
- Yeah.
I'd like to make a toast
to the bride and groom.
May they be as happy together
as my bride and I have been
all these years.
'Please join us.'
And to Charlotte and Ralph
who made all this possible.
Oh, and Aunt Flo,
who does the impossible.
I had a few doubts
about this place.
Minute we landed
they threw us in the pokey.
[laughing]
I want you to know that
we are proud and pleased
to join our family
with the Walton's family.
And thank you for
your very special blend
of Southern hospitality.
[crowd cheering]
[country music]
[music continues]
Hey Jason. Way to go, son.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
[slow violin music]
[music continues]
[crowd cheering]
[Janet]
'You ready?
Alright, here it comes.'
One, two, three.
Aww.
- Thank you.
- Mwah, mwah.
Well, I certainly
do hate to break this up.
But, uh, we got
to be going now.
Bye-bye, grandma.
And thank you.
Bye-bye, ladies.
- Happy days, John-Boy.
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
- 'Bye-bye.'
[guests singing Daisy Bell's
"Bicycle Built for Two"]
♪ I'm half crazy
all for the love of you ♪
♪ It won't be
a stylish marriage ♪
♪ We can't afford a carriage ♪
♪ But you'll look sweet
upon the seat ♪
♪ Of a bicycle
built for two.. ♪
[soft music]
- Oh, John!
- Look at this.
I love you.
- Let's go.
- In the boat?
Yup.
Alright fellows.
[music continues]
[male narrator]
And so it was,
that a folksy, fertile clan
from the Blue Ridge
Mountains of Virginia
was united with a distinguished family from Iowa.
Janet's father
would be happy to know that
in spite of some lean times'
Janet and John-Boy
never had to live
on chitlins
and moonshine whiskey.
It was a fine wedding
and the memory of that day
is still warm and wonderful
and will stay with us always.
Goodnight, Janet.
Goodnight, John-Boy.
Goodnight, everybody.
[all]
Goodnight.
[instrumental music]