[bells tolling]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[bells tolling continuous]
[thunder crashes]
[speaks Spanish]
Help me, Lord.
[car horn honks]
[shouts]
[yells]
[panting]
[grunts]
We can't wait any longer.
[truck doors slam]
[speaks Spanish]
Father!
Please...
[sobbing]
[door hinges creaking]
[faint wheezing]
[wheezing breaths]
[mumbling]
[woman gasping]
[woman speaks Spanish]
It's the Devil, the Devil!
- [roars]
- [screams]
[woman moaning]
[man]
Are you alright, mom?
[cackling]
[roars]
- [walls crackling]
- [dirt sifting]
[laughing]
Her heart,
it won't take it.
[breathing heavily]
Father Michael,
there's no time.
[Michael, on phone]
Do not insist!
I've already had
the authorization.
I'll be there in two days.
If I don't do anything now,
she dies.
There is a protocol.
A set of rules.
But especially a training
which you didn't finish.
You could die, Peter.
[demon]
Michael!
[demon laughs]
I have enough faith.
Are you free of sin?
Because if the devil
finds a single crack in you,
he will reach
the depth of your soul.
Of course I am.
Peter!
I forbid you
to perform this exor...
[slams receiver]
[breathing heavily]
[demon]
You are not ready, Father.
[footsteps thumping]
I must do this alone.
[door hinges creaking]
[footsteps]
[door closes and latches]
Help me, Father.
[sobbing softly]
Please.
[in demonic voice]
Come closer.
The three of us
fit in this bed.
[sighs]
So you like to watch.
- [chuckles]
- [recorder beeps]
[in normal voice]
Of course he does.
I've seen how he looks at me
during Mass.
[speaks in Latin] Our Father,
who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name...
[grunts]
[in demonic voice]
Come on.
I'm an easy girl.
There's no need
for foreplay.
Thy kingdom come,
Thy will be done,
[snarling]
on earth,
as it is in Heaven!
[roars]
Give us this day
our daily bread,
and forgive us
our trespasses,
[roaring and snarling]
as we forgive those,
who trespass against us!
[breathing heavily]
You've always
desired me, Father.
[sighs heavily]
[gulps]
[shuddering breaths]
[moaning]
God, who from hands welfare
established the most wonder...
[roars]
Ah!
[heavy breathing]
I will use in your mysteries
and endowed with your grace,
cast out demons
and banish disease
so by the sprinkling
of this water,
may she be protected
from every barrel.
[sighs]
Come eat my body.
It's way tastier
than the son of God's.
- All-powerful God...
- [demonic laughter]
...God of God,
God of all creation,
God, you bring power
to your apostles
to bring forth
and pass forth dangers.
[laughing]
You gave commands
to your apostles
with wondrous moments
to do great things,
and you said,
"Drive out, evil spirit!"
[panting]
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I command you
to leave this body!
[in demonic voice] I'll leave
this body when you come in it!
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I command you
to leave this body!
[moans seductively]
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I command you
to leave this body!
[moaning]
In the name of Jesus Christ,
I command you
to leave this body!
[moans]
[gasps]
[sighs]
No!
[breathing heavily]
[theme music plays]
[speaks in Spanish]
What the fuck?
[whistling]
- [man speaks Spanish] What are you doing?!
- [gasps]
You fuckin' moron,
let's go, they're not eating.
- [inhuman roar]
- [screams]
[screaming]
[birds tweeting]
Boo!
[children laughing]
[shouting playfully]
[speaks Spanish]
That's it!
- C'mon!
- Let's go, father!
Let's do this, guys.
[speaks Spanish]
Manuel!
That's holy water!
[all laugh]
[indistinct chattering]
God bless you, father!
We're out! No more!
- I'm sorry.
- Thanks, father.
[woman]
Father!
[crying softly]
[wheezing breaths]
This way, father.
[breathing heavily]
[speaks Spanish]
What's the little one's name?
Felipe.
[speaks Spanish]
The rumors are true,
you are a saint.
He's in God's hands now.
[gasps]
Felipe?
[ambulance siren wailing]
[woman crying]
We lost Blanca.
All my children.
Did you call
the capitol again?
I told you,
they never answered me.
There is no food,
no medicine.
No one who can lessen
this virus.
- [bombs explode]
- [gasps]
These are good people,
Father.
They don't deserve this.
[bells tolling]
[Peter, in Spanish] His resurrection
manifests forgiveness,
and above all,
the renewal of our faith.
We ask for the healing
of our children,
we beg Thee with all our faith
and free of all sin.
- Let us pray to the Lord.
- Lord, hear our prayer.
Peter.
I'm sorry.
[sighs]
We've lost four kids
this week.
Feels like a punishment
from the Lord.
[children shouting happily]
You were possessed.
It wasn't you.
I let it happen.
I was weak.
I haven't been
forgiven, Nelson.
God hasn't forgiven me
and I haven't forgiven myself.
I tried to confess,
but Father Tomás
gave me a penance
that I've never been able
to go through with.
He told me to confess
the facts to the bishop.
It's not the
best decision, Peter.
I haven't found peace.
These mountains,
Nelson.
The church.
The children.
The orphanage.
This is where
I found my true home.
And you'll lose it.
You'll be ex-communicated,
and you won't be able
to help our people anymore.
There's nothing I can do
to help them now.
[roars]
[Balducci]
Welcome, Father Peter.
It's not every day
you get a visit from a saint.
Monsignor Balducci,
I am not a saint.
A long time ago
I committed a sin, and...
I've never had the courage
to confess it to you.
Come on, Peter.
Please.
You have been helping
our people for 18 years.
People here love you.
And even in the Vatican,
there is talk about
the miracle you performed
18 years ago.
Are you serious, Monsignor?
But of course.
The Vatican has not
been blind to your work.
Maybe you are not
a saint for that, Peter,
but only someone
who carries God inside
could do something
like this.
And I also know
everything you've done
to ask for humanitarian aid.
But your prayers
have been heard.
This is a lot of money.
This Easter will bring
a miracle.
You are destined
to do great things, Peter.
And from Rome,
you will be able
to help children
all over the world.
- [man, speaks in Spanish] The medicine is here, family!
- And the medical equipment!
[applause]
[Peter screaming demonically
on TV]
[Peter panting on TV]
[Peter, on TV]
No!
[turns TV off]
[Peter]
I confess to Almighty God.
And to you,
my brothers and sisters.
I have greatly sinned
in my thoughts
and in my words,
in what I have done,
in what I have failed to do.
Through my fault.
Through my most grievous fault!
[sighs]
[man screaming distantly]
[door hinges creak]
[rushing footsteps]
[man sobbing distantly]
[man crying]
Sir?
You okay?
[crying continuous]
Sir?
[sobbing continuous]
- [shrieks]
- Ah!
[gasping and panting]
[necklace jiggle]
Blood of Christ,
protect me.
Blood of Christ.
- Blood of Christ.
- [door creaking open]
[breathing heavily]
[object clatters]
[snarls]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[phone rings]
- [speaks Spanish] Hello?
- [Uribe speaks Spanish] Father Peter...
- Who's calling?
- It's Uribe.
I'm the warden
at the Sagrado Corazón prison.
How can I help you?
- We have a case with an inmate...
- Is she sick?
I wouldn't call it that.
You want me to send
my doctor over?
She doesn't need a doctor.
She needs a priest.
She asked for you personally,
she's running out of time.
Good morning, father.
Morning.
[cell door closes and latches]
[radio beeps, static crackles]
Symptoms of epilepsy,
hysteria, schizophrenia.
She hasn't eaten
in over two weeks.
I don't know how
she's still alive.
[door buzzes open]
- What are the charges against...?
- Esperanza killed a man.
They found him bled to death,
hanging from a tree,
his head completely backwards.
I don't feel comfortable
with this,
trust me, we tried everything
before calling you.
Shall we?
Keep your distance, she's
extremely strong and aggressive.
[door creaks open]
[door closes]
[whispering]
You can speak from here.
[inaudible]
Hello, Esperanza.
[in demonic voice]
The Easter will bring a miracle.
How?
Resurrection.
We're five.
Who?
The children.
What's the matter
with the children?
[in normal voice] It feels like
a punishment from the Lord.
Who are you?
We already know each other,
Father.
Oh, yeah.
Very well.
[guard speaks Spanish]
Stay back!
I said stay back!
[wheezing]
[gasps softly]
I'm wet for you again.
- What...?
- [cackles]
[door opens]
[shrieking in demonic voice]
[keys jingle]
[ghostly voices overlapping]
[ghostly voices screaming]
[demon shrieking]
[voices stop]
[speaks Spanish] A long time ago
I performed my first exorcism.
I swore it would be the last.
Do it for the girl's mother.
She's desperate, poor thing.
Do it for me.
Do it for your daughter.
She asked for you
to come.
And she didn't even
know you existed.
I heard you spent the last
several years saving lives.
I couldn't live in this town
with those memories.
A few weeks later,
I realized what you did to me.
But who was going
to believe me?
Who would see
the downside?
It wasn't me, Magali.
I swear to God,
I was possessed.
Look at her.
This is her true face.
The demon has never left.
He's been possessing
my girl over and over.
Save her.
If you really want
to redeem yourself,
expel that demon
out of her body.
[gasps]
[gasping and whimpering]
[loud thump]
[door slams]
[footsteps thumping heavily]
[walls crackling]
[ghostly wheezing]
[groans]
- [demonic snarling]
- [mumbling prayer]
[snarling intensifies]
[praying inaudible]
...the demons and Satan.
God come into us...
- [whispering prayer]
- [snarling intensifies]
..and who he has redeemed,
at a great cost,
the tyranny of the devil!
Ah!
- [snarling stops]
- [panting]
[screams]
[roars]
[gasps]
- [child coughing]
- [monitors beeping]
[Nelson]
Five children, Peter.
We've made every kind of test.
There are no signs
of affected organs
or of a virus.
It doesn't make any sense.
[door closes]
[whispers in Spanish] God will welcome him
into His eternal light.
God doesn't exist.
Saints don't exist.
[Peter and children
reciting prayer in Spanish]
In the name of the Father, and of the
Son, and of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
- Good night, children.
- Good night, father.
Group hug!
[all laugh]
[singing "Ave Maria"
in Spanish]
- [speaks Spanish] Merry Christmas, children.
- Merry Christmas, Sister Magali.
Why does Baby Jesus forget
about orphan children?
You really think so, Camila?
Did you behave?
Well, I don't think
he's forgotten about you.
Yes, I saw him myself,
and guess what?
He left something for you
under your bed.
[all scream
and chatter excitedly]
Thank you.
[all laughing]
Sister Magali?
Camila.
[sighs]
[inhaling and exhaling deeply]
The inmates have suffered
the influence of the evil one.
[demonic snarling
over recording]
I'm afraid there
could be a tragedy
if Esperanza's transfer
to a juvenile facility...
I mean, thank God because
of the ineptitude and red tape,
they haven't
transferred her yet.
You have all my support,
Father Peter.
The Vatican
needs to approve...
Just do it.
We won't let
our own bureaucracy
do away with the life
of this innocent girl.
I've earned
the Vatican's trust,
and they'll approve
on your exorcism.
If you'll allow me,
I'd like someone
to join me this time.
You have someone in mind?
Father Michael.
You made it.
If I can make it to hell,
I can make it to Mexico.
Which, according
to the London Times,
is about the same.
[both laugh]
[drops luggage]
[both grunt]
[Peter]
Well, Magali could have died.
[Michael]
You too.
Why didn't you want to do
this exorcism alone?
You're the greatest
exorcist in the world.
[chuckles]
And you faced Balban
and defeated it.
So did you.
I...
I didn't defeat it,
Michael.
What are you talking about?
Balban left Magali,
but then he came into me.
And then?
He just left.
Impossible.
Balban wouldn't have left
without taking your soul.
The only explanation is,
you expelled it.
You carry God
inside you, my boy.
No!
[panting]
[demonic snarling]
[zipper rasping]
[snarls]
[bed thumping]
[monstrous grunting]
[demonic roar]
[gasping and panting]
[grunts]
God!
[muffled screaming]
[pounding on door]
[man]
Open the door!
Peter!
[doorknob jiggles]
Open the door!
[pounding on door continuous]
[zipper rasps]
Peter!
[pounding on door continuous]
My child!
Oh, God. She's fine.
Thank God that she's fine.
[speaks Spanish]
Thank you, father.
You are a saint.
God bless you.
Can't sleep?
[sighs]
- Nightmares?
- Hmm.
[chuckles]
Here.
Mescal.
The best holy water
I've tasted in a while.
[coughs]
Come on.
Tell me your nightmare.
Hmm.
Come on. Tell me.
I see Jesus...
possessed by the devil.
He comes for me
every night.
Strangles me, and...
I can't even move.
He wants you.
Balban is trying
to possess you.
[blows]
[whispering prayer]
[gasps softly]
[gasps]
[loud crash overhead]
Two thousand years ago,
he tried to possess Christ...
but he was defeated.
Balban is a demon
with a noble lineage
with legions of henchmen
under his command.
If he's calling you,
he's not doing it
without a purpose.
You are part of his plan.
[footsteps]
[screams]
[sobbing]
[hisses and snarls]
[panting]
[shrieks]
[woman singing "Ave Maria"
in Spanish]
[panting softly]
[pounding on door]
[woman]
Time to play, children!
Tomorrow, to free someone
who is totally possessed,
we have to be
totally clean.
[rapid pounding on door]
[loud banging on door]
[all scream]
[chuckles]
[demonic croaking]
[both yell]
[snarling]
Fuck the priest,
you fucking whore!
[coughing]
[demonic yelling]
I condemn you back to hell!
[shrieks]
I expel you in the name of God,
the Father...
- [screams]
- ...Christ the Savior,
and the Holy Spirit!
[growling]
[all scream]
I condemn you
back to hell!
[scream fading]
[children whimpering
and sobbing]
[speaks Spanish]
It's OK, don't worry.
Faith, Camila.
Faith.
[all breathing heavily]
What the fuck
is this, Peter?
It's a third-world prison.
I don't know whether I should
spray holy water or bleach.
[door hinges squealing]
[faint wheezing]
My friends.
They're sick.
[cries]
It's your fault, Father.
Your fault.
[in demonic voice]
I'll take them!
I'll burn your damn
children down here!
Not if I expel you first.
Silence.
Don't fall for her tricks.
So...
you're from "down there."
Prove it.
Come on, prove it.
[chuckles]
Well, gentlemen,
we have no demon.
No possession.
Let's go get a drink.
Someone must have a mescal
in this shitty prison.
- [guards speaks Spanish] Open up!
- [pounding on door] What's wrong?
[faint wheezing]
Simple telekinesis.
I've seen that in village...
[gurgles and gulps]
[Peter]
Father, are you okay?
Even if you were a demon...
you'd be the lowliest kind.
So simple,
so predictable,
that I would leave you to rot
with your cheap tricks.
[Michael gasps]
[chuckles]
We have a pact,
Father Michael.
[giggles]
In an hour, we will be
raping you down here.
[speaks Spanish] Save me, Michelangelo!
Please, save me!
If my nephew dies,
it will be your fault!
No!
- [distant shrieking]
- [speaks Spanish] The inmates...
[Peter] God, creator
and defender of humankind,
turn your eyes to this servant,
Esperanza Valasquez,
whom you have
redeemed...
A tree is known
by its fruit.
- [voices shrieking]
- [loud pounding and rumbling]
...to make her strong
for the fight,
and to defend her
with this powerful protection.
[roars]
[screams]
[demonic shrieking]
[inaudible over screaming]
...with his blood...
[Michael]
He kept in captivity...
the devil!
[snarls]
[screams]
Hallowed by thy name,
thy kingdom come,
they will be done...
[snarls and yells]
[roars]
- Hyah!
- [screams]
[gasps]
[Nelson]
Are you okay?
[Michael]
Killed it.
[speaks Spanish] Here you can do
whatever you want,
we don't use this place
anymore.
We need everyone
to leave.
The prison must be empty
except for Esperanza and us.
Your mother, just in case!
- How many inmates are here?
- Thirteen.
And four in maximum security,
plus the possessed one.
Mr Uribe,
we need to get them
out of here.
- Everyone must leave.
- No, sir, that's impossible.
You saw it yourself,
it's dangerous for them,
and for us.
I don't know how things work
in your country,
but it's different here,
and I don't want any trouble!
The inmates stay put,
and so does my guard.
I can put them
to sleep.
[keys jangle]
[Peter] Our prayers...
they didn't hurt it.
Balban is the demon
of deceit.
You cannot believe anything
that comes from it.
Not even what it
tells you about me.
It will always play
with our biggest fears.
And even as it agonizes,
it will make us believe
it is still strong.
It is the best weapon
to destroy our faith.
And, above all things,
never make a deal with it.
If you do, he will always win.
[mumbling prayer]
[steam hisses]
- [cell door slams]
- [lock clicks]
[Michael]
Demons reject holy water.
This will make it float
around the room.
making it impossible
for Balban to jump
from one body
to the next.
I bet it's new.
Doesn't have the Vatican
seal of approval.
Peter, the conventional ritual
will not work against Balban.
For centuries,
the Church has used
the same ritual
in exorcisms.
But the devil's
not a fool.
He's learned.
He won't fall twice
for the same trick.
That's human.
What has the Vatican done?
[chuckles]
Perfect the ritual?
Plan a strategy through time?
No.
They send us into battle,
but they leave us alone.
Sometimes, I think the devil's
in the Vatican's own ranks.
- Michael, that...
- Shh!
The consequence of this
is the auteur exorcism.
Each priest performs
the exorcism
as he wants.
The problem is,
many faithless priests hesitate.
And that makes
the demon stronger.
Michael, I...
use that ritual.
And only God and the devil
know why you're not dead.
But without a ritual...
how will I do it?
By not believing
God is with you...
but by believing
you are God.
[Magali]
She wants to be an astronaut.
Or a film director.
She didn't pick
easy ones.
[chuckles]
She's obsessive.
When she wants something,
she doesn't give up.
She... She goes on and on,
and you want to kill her.
[laughs]
But at the end,
she always gets what she wants.
I've never met her
and my heart is already hers.
Magali, I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
- I was hard on you.
- No.
I let it in, Magali.
I fell for its temptation.
I had you in my arms,
and kissed you, and...
Shh.
[sighs]
I thank God it happened.
If not, I wouldn't have her.
My gift.
My miracle.
My Esperanza (hope).
For many years...
I couldn't accept that...
very deep down...
I was falling in love with you
without realizing.
I'm sorry.
[speaks Spanish]
Every door is secured.
- We'll be here in the morning.
- Alright.
God bless you, father.
Father...
save her.
I swear to God.
[loud banging]
Shit, Peter, I hope you
spoke to God last night.
[cell door clangs]
Where is the guard?
[shouts]
[electricity crackles]
[Peter]
May God be with you.
[Michael]
And with your spirit.
- He wants to kill my children.
- Silence.
I told you, you can't believe
anything from it.
It's just trying
to scare you.
[clattering]
[gasps]
[sighs and exhales]
[slams and latches]
Peter!
[woman sobbing]
- [shrieks]
- [blade pierces]
[door creaks open]
Nelson!
[object dragging along ground]
- [object dragging continuous]
- [footsteps]
[whimpering and gasping]
[groans]
[shushing]
You're going to be okay.
You're going
to be all right.
[snuffles]
[mumbles weakly]
Run.
[snarls]
[speaks Latin]
Stay back, Satan!
[all scream]
Dear merciful God,
the prayer
of the Blessed Virgin Mary!
[all shrieking]
[metal clanks]
Dying on the cross.
Just the head
of ancient serpents.
I declare you anathema,
Satan.
Enemy of human salvation.
[cackles]
[Michael] And entrusted
to his mother.
Omen has a son!
[all roaring]
St. Michael.
Archangel.
Prince of heaven...
[sizzling]
Fair trial sentenced your pride
and your envy...
Go back to hell!
- Go back to hell!
- [growls]
No! No!
Michael!
Come on!
[panting]
- [demonic snarling]
- Ah!
[yells]
[screams]
- You all right?
- Yes!
Yes! Run!
[demonic shrieking]
- [panting]
- [demonic shrieking]
- [latch clicks]
- [pounding on door]
[panting]
You okay?
What...?
You lied to me!
What are you talking about?
Your prayer,
it didn't work.
What sin are you
carrying with you?
Speak!
[panting]
Esperanza.
Eighteen years ago...
She's your daughter.
God, Peter,
what have you done?
It wasn't me. I was possessed.
It was Balban.
- Your sin let him in!
- It wasn't me!
I told you,
you weren't ready.
- What did you want me to do?
- What about confessing?
God would have
forgiven you!
I did. I confessed.
But I couldn't fulfill
my penance.
Now you'll never be able
to defeat Balban
or save the children
or your daughter!
You can do it.
You can exorcise them.
You defeated Balban once.
[laughs]
Peter, Balban didn't lie.
In order to save
the possessed child,
I had to make a deal with him.
I sold my soul to him
and lost all power over him.
[loud crashing]
They're waiting for me,
Peter.
When I die...
I'm going to burn in...
- [loud crashing continuous]
- [objects clattering]
- Stand up.
- No, no, no.
Stand.
I'm sorry.
Stand up! Stand up!
[loud crashing
and banging continuous]
Peter...
Balban will tempt you
by using your biggest weakness.
But you already know
the only rule.
Don't make a deal with him.
[whimpers]
There is no place for God
and the devil
in the same body.
Always remember that.
Let me go.
No, no, no, no.
[loud crash]
[demonic shrieking]
- [loud pounding continuous]
- [panting]
[pounding and crashing stops]
[muffled snarling]
[object dragging along ground]
[sobbing softly]
I'm Father Peter.
Peter Williams.
Eighteen years ago,
while I performed an exorcism...
on Magali Valasquez, I...
was tempted by Balban.
And I was...
dominated by own feelings,
and...
my forbidden desires for her.
So...
I broke my vows with God...
and Balban
took advantage of this
to possess me
and sexually abuse her.
The fruit of this sin
is that her...
daughter, Esperanza...
my daughter.
I destroyed the videotape
that proves my crime,
but this confession
will help justice
to be served on Earth,
as in heaven.
[children laughing]
[all laugh]
[all laughing]
[applause]
[woman speaks Spanish]
God doesn't exist.
Saints don't exist.
Save her.
[phone beeps]
[cell door opens]
[demonic voices moaning
and snarling]
Stay back, Satan!
[all scream]
Under the Almighty's authority,
I command you to leave
these daughters of God.
- God is inside.
- [all shriek]
Jesus is inside
and the Holy Spirit
is inside.
[object dragging along ground]
[snarling]
[roars]
[shrieks]
Kneel before God!
It is God who commands you.
The Holy Spirit commands you.
The church, the virgin,
the saints, and the archangels...
[roars]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
[deep, animalistic breathing]
[demonic chuckle]
The Easter will bring
a miracle.
Resurrection of
the possessed messiah.
- [sizzles]
- [screams]
Our Father walks in hell.
Hallowed by thy name.
Thy kingdom come.
Thy will be done
on Earth,
as it is in hell!
[screaming]
Lead us into temptation
and deliver us
towards evil.
Amen.
God is within me.
And that's why
I'm going to take him
out of you.
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[monitors beeping]
[ghostly breathing echoes]
Satan lo made the
eternal torment of sin
sprout from the darkness
in order to destroy mankind.
Listen to our prayers
with all thy wickedness,
and infuse all thy power
in this blood!
[screams]
By serving thy purpose,
the sanctity of
the angels is averted.
Bringing upon doubt,
the seed of all sin.
[all]
God, leave this body!
No!
- [monitors beep fast in unison]
- [gasps]
[heavy breathing]
[rapid beeping continuous]
[door rattling]
[throaty demonic gasp]
In the name of Satan,
I command you to leave
this man's body!
[screams]
- [croaks]
- Ah!
[shrieks]
[yelling]
Father, Son, the Holy Spirit,
do not forsake me...
[screams]
...and the divine justice,
for evil...
[demonic roaring]
[yelling]
The nine circles of hell
command you!
Darkness commands you!
Leave the soul
of this innocent girl.
The power of Christ
compels you!
[screams]
- The Holy Spirit commands you!
- Sin commands you!
The flames of purgatory
command you!
- Father in heaven commands you!
- Sin commands you!
[demonic voices shrieking]
[roars]
[shrieking]
[breathing heavily]
Free my daughter now.
Lucifer's slave.
Our daughter.
Let me in!
[breathing heavily]
[snarling]
God Almighty,
origin of our soul
and of our life,
bestow your blessing
on this woman!
Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with me.
[demonic shriek]
[howling]
[Peter]
In the name of God,
the Father, the Son,
the Holy Spirit,
I command you
to leave my daughter, Esperanza.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll do it.
But you just need to consider
something before...
[screams]
[heart monitor flatlines]
No.
[demonic laughter]
If you expel me,
they all come with me
to hell.
No!
Time to make a choice,
Father Peter.
[slurps]
You daughter...
or all those innocent
children of God.
No, damn you,
you son of a bitch!
- [gasping and choking]
- [snarling]
Your daughter or the children.
Decide now.
No.
No, no.
What do you want?
I want you to let God
exit your body.
If you do it,
all your children
will be saved.
[cries]
[Esperanza chuckles]
And you'll save
my daughter too?
I will free Esperanza
and all the children.
Deal.
[cackling]
- [screams]
- [shrieks]
Let the will of the Lord
be done.
[heart monitors beeping]
[breathing heavily]
[sobs softly]
[whimpering]
[both cry]
[Magali]
Thank you, Father.
You're a true saint.
[bells tolling]
[Peter, speaks in Spanish]
Do not be deceived,
neither the sexually immoral,
nor idolaters,
nor adulterers or perverts,
nor sodomites or homosexuals,
nor thieves, drunks,
swindlers, or slanderers,
none of them will inherit
the kingdom of God.
[applause]
[reporter speaking Spanish] The whole world is talking
about Peter Williams,
the gringo priest who cured
112 sick children,
by just placing his hands
on top of them.
Are we in the presence
of a living saint?
[indistinct chattering]
May God be with you,
God bless you.
May God be with you.
The video?
I deleted it.
Our confession is bound
by the sacred seal.
Your actions
reached important ears.
There's a job
as a special counselor
waiting for you
at the Vatican.
This way.
Bless me, father.
May God be with you.
[Peter speaks Spanish]
And with your spirit.
Thank you.
[giggles]
Glory be thy honor,
Prince Balban...
for defeating the man
who would have become
a living saint.
The priest sacrificed God
to save his daughter
and the children.
The way I see it,
he is a living saint.
Heaven's played
its cards too.
[indistinct chatter]
How did I not
see that coming?
[inaudible]
We'll take care of God's
new chosen one later on.
[laughing]
[bells tolling]
[bird wings beating]
[Peter]
No, the evil ones
will not inherit
the kingdom of God.
They will inherit the earth.
[bells tolling continuous]
[theme music plays]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[distant muffled voice]
[ghostly voices echo distantly]
[man singing
in Spanish language]
[muffled ghostly screams]