[instrumental music]
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
[music continues]
Oh.
[eerie music]
[rustling]
[music continues]
[intense music]
[muffled screaming]
What was that?
Stay here.
Mom?
[music continues]
[ominous music]
This is nancy gardner again.
Yes, eva jones' mother-in-law.
It's been well over
12 hours now. No.
[nancy] we haven't heard
a thing.
Yes, I suppose this is
out of character for eva.
The police are out looking.
I know this seems impossible,
But try not to imagine
the worst-case scenario.
-First dad, now this.
-Yes.
Does make one wonder.
What do you mean?
From the moment eva called
to tell me he was gone,
I knew something was off.
A healthy 34-year-old man
Doesn't drop dead for no reason.
-He had a heart attack.
-And now your mother disappears.
Right as I'm pushing
for a second autopsy.
I'm gonna pretend you didn't
just say that out loud.
[instrumental music]
Mom, please come home.
-[intense music]
-[car engine starts]
[music continues]
Mom?
Mom!
Mom! Mom! Mom, wake up! Help!
Mom, mom, mom, wake up! Mom!
Help! Help!
Mom, mom, wake up, please. Help!
-Hey, dane.
-Oh.
Ah.
Oh! Well, thank you kindly,
grace.
-Hey, dane.
-Hey.
Not too cold
to be working outside?
-No way, it's refreshing.
-Ah.
Hey, girls, why don't you go
inside and start your homework?
-I'll be right there.
-What about you?
You, uh, adjusting to sami
having her license?
Well, actually, it's kinda nice.
I'm all caught up on emails.
Hey, uh, any word yet
from 9 moon?
I have refreshed my emails,
like, 20 times the last hour.
-Still nothing.
-You're gonna get it, I know it.
Thank you.
I, uh, I thought you'd given up
on this one.
No, I, I just figured I owed it
to ryan to get it running again.
If it bothers you,
I can put it in the garage.
No, no, it's...
I know how much ryan enjoyed
rebuilding it with you.
It's a nice memory to have.
-[cell phone vibrating]
-oh. Hang on, sorry.
-Oh.
-Everything okay over there?
Yeah, it's just this guy clint.
Just can't take a hint.
Uh, first guy I go out
on a date with,
And it turns out this guy
is a, uh, total creep.
Yeah, wasn't that date,
like, weeks ago?
-He's still calling you?
-Yeah.
And the worst part
is that I left
My favorite earring
in the back of his car.
Well, you know, if you want,
I could, uh, make sure
He leaves you alone.
You know, well...
Oh, yeah,
I can be very intimidating.
-Oh, wow, tough guy. Okay.
-Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Wow, I got this. Actually,
I'm gonna just block his number.
-So... Thank you.
- Yeah. Smart.
After the year you had,
you can't be too careful.
Yeah. Anyways, what about you?
Now that your divorce
is finalized,
Are you gonna finally ask
my friend ashley out or what?
-Oh, come on. Get out of here.
-Come on!
What would she want
with a guy like me?
You gotta give yourself a little
more credit.
-[chuckles] come on, I'm a mess.
-Okay.
Well, listen, I'm gonna
go inside and make dinner.
I'm gonna tell ashley
to expect your call.
You got a little somethin'
right here.
Thanks.
[instrumental music]
[knocking on door]
Hey, hon.
-Just checking in.
-Right on schedule.
Ah, very funny.
What you working on?
-Jacket.
-Huh? Can I see?
-It's a mess.
-Oh.
I like it.
I like what you've done.
Do you want a suggestion?
Try mirroring this structure
in the front.
That'll make
some interesting lines.
What do you think?
-I'll never be as good as you.
-Of course, you will.
But all designers
need their beauty sleep.
-Few more minutes?
-Yes, of course.
-Hey.
-Mm-hmm.
-You're okay. You're okay.
-Okay. Okay.
All right, ten more minutes.
-Love you.
-I love you.
Sleep tight.
[door shuts]
[eerie music]
[dramatic music]
[laptop beeps]
Got it.
[engine revving]
[ominous music]
[exhales sharply]
[engine revving]
Ah.
Dane!
Dane! Dane!
-Dane, there's a car.
-What? What's going on?
Car. Uh, there's a car.
It's following me.
[panting]
There was.
Someone was following me.
What kind of car?
Did you see who was driving?
I don't know.
Well, what about
a license-plate number?
-[mumbles]
-uh, here, here, sit.
But I didn't...
I didn't get one.
[breathing heavily]
I don't know,
maybe it was nothing.
What are you doing
joggin' in the snow anyways?
[sighs] I don't know.
Just clears my head, I guess.
I don't know,
maybe I just panicked.
Maybe it's nothing.
Clearly, I'm just
easily rattled these days.
Eva, you were kidnapped out of
your own driveway and they never
Caught the guy, if you think
someone is following you,
You should go to the police.
I think we both know what a
Waste of time that would be.
I mean, if they didn't
believe me then,
Why would they believe me now?
[sighs] I just wish
I got my life back.
You don't have
to go through this alone.
Seriously, if you need anything.
Yeah, no, thank you.
I really appreciate you
Looking out for me.
-Yeah.
-[car door shuts]
-[dane] oh.
-Wow.
This day couldn't get
any better.
-Nancy for dinner again, huh?
-Yup.
That woman can't go one week
without telling me
How terrible of a parent I am.
-Helpful.
-Very helpful.
So, uh, beers tonight,
after I get rid of her?
Yeah, yeah, no,
I-I'm just about to
Head out, but I should be back
around 8:00 or 9:00.
Great. Is that a new shirt?
Oh. Uh, no, it's just...
[chuckling]
-Where are you headed?
-Nowhere.
Okay, so did you finally give
my friend ashley a call?
-Wouldn't you like to know?
-I would like to know.
Text me when you're done.
I want all the hot goss.
Yeah, I-I think nancy needs you.
I could use some help with
these, if you're not too busy.
[dane chuckles]
Yeah. I may have
some news myself.
I'll be right there, nancy.
[eva] oh, wow, you went all out!
Thank you so much, nancy,
this is delicious.
My pleasure. Grace, well, have
a few more vegetables there.
-Please. There's plenty.
-Grace, just a few.
Mom, what's the big news?
So, 9 moon offered me the job
As the creative director
for their head office.
Wait! 9 moon fashion house?
-Yes.
-Mom, that's amazing!
Well, I mean, we're still
working out the details,
But, um, it comes with great
perks and full health benefits.
And the best part is
they're gonna let me work
On my own designs.
-It's kind of a win-win.
-Wait.
Isn't their head office
in new york?
-Mm-hmm.
-So, we'd be moving?
What about school
and our friends?
Well, you'll make new friends
and you'll go to a new school.
I mean, that's exciting, right?
Plus, this isn't just
an opportunity for me,
It's for you girls as well.
Sami, you could go
To the design school after you
graduate.
-Think about the opportunities.
-Yeah, but we have a life here.
-Well, I know, but--
-if you needed money...
I wish you would've asked.
I-I don't, nancy,
but thank you.
Regardless,
you can't sell this house.
This was yours and ryan's
first home.
It'll be a fabulous first home
for another couple.
Right? New york's a fresh start
for all of us.
Moving across country isn't
going to bury your past, eva.
What's that supposed to mean,
nancy?
There are too many unanswered
Questions
regarding ryan's death!
Moving away
while his case is unsolved
Is simply irresponsible.
Don't you want to know
what happened to him?
Girls, do you mind...
Just go to your room for
Just a second.
No, stay.
-The matter of their father's--
-nancy, stop!
He had a heart attack.
Why can't you understand that?
Why can't you accept that?
The facts of his death
remain as murky
As your apparent kidnapping.
So easy for you to believe
that ryan was killed,
But it's-it's very difficult
for you to understand
That I was, I was taken.
Oh, yes, by someone who happened
To drop you back
in your own front yard?
I was in a diabetic coma, nancy.
You think I did that to myself?
Then who did it, eva?
Who kidnapped you?
Oh, that's right, you can't
remember. How convenient.
Get out of my house.
[nancy] excuse me?
You heard me. Get out.
[intense music]
Congratulations on your job,
mom. Really.
Girls, wait.
Grace.
[scoffs]
[music continues]
[intense music]
[gabe] so I got, uh, a
for question 46.
What about you?
Sami? Everything okay?
Yeah, sorry. My mom dropped
this bombshell on us tonight.
I don't know, I'm still trying
to process everything.
-[gabe] what did she say?
-Wow, it's later than I thought.
I should go talk to her.
I'll see you tomorrow?
Yeah. Night.
[instrumental music]
[knocking on door]
Mom, can we talk?
Mom, I'm sorry.
Mom?
See you at breakfast.
I love you. Goodnight.
-[clattering]
-mom?
Mom?
Okay, so when was the last time
you both saw her?
Uh, around 4:00, I think,
right around when nancy arrived.
And she didn't seem off
in any way?
She did say she thought
Someone was following her
earlier that day.
-What? Who?
-Sami, go to your room.
-Let the adults handle this.
-She didn't get a good look.
But said they drove a dark car.
-And you?
-Um...
I-I left the house around 6:00.
Is that it?
-They had an argument.
-About?
[chuckles]
family matters.
That's enough from you.
Okay, well,
I've got your statements.
So I will reach out
when we've got something.
Wait, you're leaving? You've
been here, what, 20 minutes?
Well, there's not a lot
we can do right now.
What are you even saying? You
should be out looking for her.
-We all should.
-I understand you're concerned.
But we don't wanna jump the gun.
Nobody's jumping the gun.
My mom's
obviously been taken again
Because you couldn't find
her kidnapper the first time.
Sami, show the officer
some respect.
An open window
and one knocked-over vase
Aren't necessarily
signs of a struggle.
I mean, you told me you were
in your bedroom all night.
She could've just as easily
walked out the front door.
[sami] without her phone
or her purse?
Well, you'd be surprised
how common that is
For people having breakdowns.
A breakdown?
So she just left and we all
just have to accept it?
Give it 48 hours, and if your
mom isn't back by then, call me.
-[grace] sami, what's going on?
-Wonderful.
You've woken up your sister.
Sami, sami!
[sami] detective campbell!
[dane] sami!
Hey, it's gonna be okay.
How do you know?
You're right, I don't.
Dane, look.
-[dane] careful. Sami!
-Hey! [clicks camera]
Sami, stop! Hey.
Chasing after random cars isn't
gonna bring your mom back.
What am I supposed to do?
Did you get a picture
of the license plate?
Send it to campbell. Come on.
[sobbing]
[instrumental music]
[cell phone vibrating]
[dramatic music]
[knocking on door]
Do you remember,
after your father died,
How I came to stay
with you girls for a week
Because eva went on vacation?
She wasn't on vacation, sami.
Your mother fell apart.
I was grieving my son,
And I had to put that on hold
to pick up her pieces.
I didn't want you or your sister
seeing that.
But your mother, she...
She deals with stressful
situations in her own way.
She, um, you know, has trouble
facing things head-on.
Last year
was just a practice run.
This is the real thing.
No. She would never leave us.
I wish I could believe that.
That's mine.
You leave this mess to me.
I've cleaned it up once before.
Pretty sure I was there
last year, too.
And after everything
that's happened, you're still
Treating me like a child.
Get some rest, you girls
Will be staying with me
starting tomorrow.
[instrumental music]
Where are you, mom?
[dramatic music]
[exhales sharply]
[music continues]
Oh.
What?
[music continues]
Ah.
Ah! Ah...
Oh.
[intense music]
[grunting]
Ow!
Hello? Hello?
Let me out of here! Please!
Let me out! Help!
Please let me out!
What do you want?
Let me out of here.
[captor on speaker]
you're not ready.
Sami?
-I hate it here.
-Tell me about it.
It's like living
in a haunted art gallery.
We should be at home. We're old
enough to stay by ourselves.
It's only for a little bit,
until mom comes back.
How do you know
she's coming back?
Because she'd never leave us.
You know that, right?
[nancy] sami, grace, lunchtime!
Let's go.
[ominous music]
[door creaking]
[intense music]
My bedroom's off-limits.
You're not to go in there.
Do you understand?
[cutlery clanking]
-Is this fizzy?
-Mm-hmm.
We haven't had it in forever,
mom won't buy it
Anymore since dad...
Yes, well, I know
how much you two enjoy it.
Your father did as well.
[cell phone vibrating]
Has detective campbell
called you yet?
-What are the police doing?
-Rest assured.
They're doing
everything they can.
Like what? Are they organizing
a search party?
Are they doing
a press conference to alert
People that she's missing?
Sami, leave this all--
To you?
Yeah. You said that already.
I will call detective campbell
after lunch and get an update.
But you have to promise
to let this be.
Now, let's finish our lunch.
Afterwards you girls may watch
some television if you like.
[sighs] so, how you doing?
I'm great, thanks for asking.
Sorry, I know this is tough.
No, I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm in this
never-ending nightmare
And I can't shake myself awake.
Do you think your grandma
would let you have visitors?
I can stop by
and give you some company and...
-I don't know, we could.
-[sighs]
-What?
-My pencil crayons.
I must've left them
at the house.
Well, couldn't you use
something different?
It's not the same.
I better go get them.
Sami, are you sure
that's a good idea?
Gabe, I need to get out of here.
I can't stay cooped up
for another second.
Let me come pick you up.
No, that old junker will just
alert my dungeon master.
It's a quick bus ride.
It's cool.
Okay, well, just, uh,
Shoot me a text when you get
there, so I know you're okay.
-I will. Bye.
-Bye.
[instrumental music]
[intense music]
Oh. Hello.
-You must be sami.
-How do you know my name?
Eva told me
all about you and grace.
Whoa! Hold on.
-Wait.
-Get away from her.
-Get out! Get out of here.
-I don't want any--
Get out of here!
-Are you okay? Who was that?
-I-I don't...
I don't know, um...
Wasn't that the car we saw
yesterday?
Yeah, I think so. Come on.
[sami] and once again,
detective, if you can call back
As soon as you get this message,
I'd really appreciate it.
As soon as possible, please.
Hey, I'm gonna head home, but
thanks for keeping an eye out.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Sami, I'm sorry.
I should've been there
that night.
I should've been drinking beers
with your mom,
Not on some lame date. I...
I could've done something.
-I could've stopped--
-no, hey, it's okay.
It's not your fault. I know
you would've if you could.
Yeah, all right. Here.
Let me give you a ride
to your grandmother's.
No, it's okay, bus stop is,
like, half a block away.
-All right, come on.
-And...
-Mom got me this.
-Are you sure?
Yeah. Thank you.
Well, I'll keep an eye out till
you get on the bus at least.
Okay. Thanks.
-And, dane.
-Yeah.
Thank you, for everything.
Feels like we're the only ones
that actually believe
She was taken.
We're gonna find her, sami.
[instrumental music]
[shivering]
[dramatic music]
Oh, my god.
[shivering]
[camera whirring]
Hello.
Thank you for the food.
This place is the best.
Thank you for the clothes.
You got my size and everything.
Do you think that I could...
Thank you in person?
It'd be nice to see you...
Face-to-face.
-Maybe we could eat together.
-[captor] I would like that.
Hm. This is a nice place
you have here.
Where are we exactly?
[captor] that's not something
You need to worry about, eva.
Oh. Um...
Sorry.
[rustling on speaker]
Hello?
A-are you still there?
Just like I showed you,
twist it over
And then loop it on the top
like that.
All right, you give it a try.
No, twist it. Just twi-twist it,
make a loop and...
Oh, for heaven sakes,
we're casting on.
-Not casting for fish.
-That's what I'm doing.
Can we go outside or something?
I think some air
will do us all good.
Later, sami.
Let's enjoy this nice,
Quiet morning while we can. Yes?
[cell phone vibrating]
Excuse me a moment.
[line ringing]
[cell phone ringing]
-Campbell.
-Hi, this is sami again.
-Eva jones' daughter.
-Sami. How can I help you?
I wanted to make sure
you got my messages
About that man standing
outside our house last night.
Uh, you shouldn't be
at the house, sami.
-It's an active crime scene.
-Funny.
-You don't seem very active.
-[sighs]
This guy, did you get
a good look at him?
Height, build, anything
that makes him stand out?
Not very tall, but not short.
Regular build.
Look, I can sketch him out and
send it to you if that'll help.
Any idea
why he'd be at your house?
I don't know.
But he seemed to know my mom.
-And was super creepy.
-Okay.
Send me the sketch
and I'll look into it.
-Wait? Is that it?
-Is there something else?
No, but this is taking
too long.
What if she's...
What if whoever has her
wants to hurt her?
[sighs] we're doing everything
in our power to find your mom.
In the meantime, you can't be
running around at all hours.
-I found you a suspect.
-Sami!
I need you to stay
at your grandmother's house,
Where it's safe.
I will call you back
if I hear anything more.
[intense music]
[sighs]
[knocking on glass]
[man grunts]
[ominous music]
-[gasps]
-hey.
Oh. Oh.
Trying to give me a heart attack
or what? Oh...
Were you able to get out of the
house without getting caught?
Yeah. My dad's in tour mode.
Leaves tomorrow.
So right now his focus
is on packing his fenders.
-Any news?
-Nothing.
My grandmother's
keeping me in the dark
And the detective
working the case
Brushes me off
every time I call.
It's like
no one wants to find her.
-Except for us.
-Yeah.
Look, you know your mom
better than anybody.
If you say somebody took her,
then somebody took her.
-Ready?
-Let's go.
-[grunting]
-[chain rattling]
[dramatic music]
Hey.
Hello?
[knocking]
No.
[knocking on metal]
No. Ah! No!
[man on speaker] eva!
Please.
I miss my family.
I miss my home.
[man] you are home.
This isn't a home.
It's a prison.
[keys jingling]
[lock clicks]
[intense music]
[chain rattles]
Thank you for coming to see me.
Really means a lot.
I wish I could see your face,
though.
Do you wanna come inside?
Cooper's.
I love their coffee.
They make great danishes, too.
[music continues]
-That shirt...
-Ah. Ah, ah.
-Here, let me help.
-[grunts]
[door locks]
What are we lookin' for?
Anything weird.
[exhales sharply]
Gabe, my mom's laptop.
[gabe]
"eva, the girls deserve more.
It is not healthy
the way you are raising them.
You are not well?"
No. That's not true,
none of it is.
Why would your grandmother
say that?
What's fish in the sea?
A dating site.
"can't wait to see you again.
Did you wanna come over?
Tried calling.
You didn't answer.
You're a tease, you led me on."
gross!
[gabe] they're all
from the same person. Cb-56.
[sami] "I know you're home,
your bedroom light is on."
Gabe, this was sent
the night she was taken.
Wait, that's the guy I saw
outside my house.
Let's keep looking.
Yeah.
[instrumental music]
So your mom keeps her insulin
in the fridge, right?
Yeah. Why?
It's not there.
Her toothbrush, pills,
they're all gone, too.
Well, that's weird, but--
But what?
Why would her toothbrush
be gone?
The kidnapper must've come back.
-[doorknob rattling]
-[intense music]
-Did you lock the door?
-I don't remember.
[keys jingling]
[music continues]
[door unlocking]
-Ah!