♪ Tell your good friends ♪
♪ You're gonna leave them ♪
♪ All bloodshot eyes wide ♪
♪ More proof the box lied ♪
♪ No need to think when ♪
♪ This crowd gets movin'... ♪
♪ If I wanted to say to you ♪
♪ That I wanted to see
your face again ♪
♪ That I want
to hear you laughing... ♪
Yeah?
I'm making tea.
You want some?
♪ If I wanted
to hear you talkin' ♪
No, honey, I'm fine. Thanks.
♪ Or to hear your sense
of things ♪
♪ Or to call you up
on a Sunday morning ♪
♪ In spite of all the damage
I've done... ♪
"The wretched pin with all
its victims was approaching."
Jesus, they couldn't feel
as rotten as he felt.
He made his way slowly.
A man hunched
at the wheel of a boat
glared at him from the sea.
The men took each other's
measure.
Turner was hunched over, too.
One needed a shave
as much as the other.
Their chins bristled with
a matching fury of whiskers.
Turner had another sack
in his hand,
"this one fatter than the last."
I read that.
Great book.
Full of adjectives.
Always the right one.
Florid, one reviewer said.
Well, there's an adjective.
You, on the other hand,
"remarkable," "fascinating,"
"awe-inspiring."
I never read my reviews.
Sign it.
Please.
Thank you.
Your door was closed.
I didn't want to disturb you.
Get lots done?
Lots and lots.
Hmm.
Lots of adjectives.
Good.
Hello, lovebirds.
Leonard, can I have you up front
signing books?
You know, I'd forgotten
you'd written a book.
It's nice visiting them,
isn't it?
Like saying hello
to old friends.
She's hard on the next one.
Yeah, how's that coming?
It's coming splendidly.
Good.
You should take Sally to lunch.
I would love to.
Call me. Leonard?
Yeah.
Not a bad book
at all.
Hi, honey.
Don't let me forget
that my stuff's in the dryer.
How was the reading, Leonard?
Adequate.
It was marvellous.
Honey, what is this?
It's my stuff, Mom. Leave it.
You are not taking your clothes
to university in garbage bags.
You would.
You only have one chance
to make a first impression.
Well, there's a trunk
in the basement,
but it smells like mould.
Nice.
That's Mom.
Pack it away and forget it.
Good, excellent.
Look, perfect. There it is.
Ha, the old trunk from Hawaii.
We'll just dump it out
and dust it off,
it'll be great.
Inky! Oh!
It's my Inky that Dad won
at Punahou Carnival!
How is it that you remember
things about Hawaii so clearly?
I mean, seriously,
I remember a palm tree
every here and there.
I remember this.
You used to carry
this everywhere.
"It was King Kamehameha
who first... "
What?
It's... late.
Argh. Good grief,
what have you got in here?
Okay.
You sure you don't want us
to drive with you?
I'm sure.
Look after my mom.
Have fun.
I will.
- I love you.
If you need anything,
you call me.
Mom.
You need anything, you call me.
Go.
Drive safe.
I will.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
"There's a statue outside the
courthouse of King Kamehameha,
who made the first laws
against murder in Hawaii.
He was the first here
to use witnesses
to pass judgment on the accused.
The law says you're presumed
innocent...
"...but the newspapers
say you're evil."
Have a seat.
All rise.
Be seated.
Good morning, Your Honour.
Morning.
Good morning, ladies
and gentlemen of the jury.
What we are beginning today
must end in justice being done.
The State will prove
that on the night of June 19
of last year,
Theresa Nichol met Bobby Gordon
at a nightclub in Waikiki,
where she lured him
into her car.
She forced him to drive
her out to Hanauma Bay,
intending to rob him.
You see, she had robbed men
this way before.
But on that night,
on an empty stretch of beach,
she shot him.
And she killed him.
The State charges Theresa Nichol
with first-degree murder.
Juror number 11,
there are no notebooks
allowed in the jury box.
Go ahead, Ms. Maguire.
Aimee?
Danny?
Honey?
What are you doing under there?
Shh, hide-and-seek.
How long have you been
under there?
Never mind. I'm sure
Daddy's just about to find you.
We want everything
coming up roses.
Cool. Well,
when can we meet him?
Danny.
Yeah?
Oh, I will have the permits
by then, not a problem.
Yeah, we'll be taking a bath
in yen
before you know it, pal.
Alright, see ya.
What did
Mrs. Miller want?
Hmm. Is she gone?
I paid the rent last week.
Good.
Danny, Aimee's hiding
under the bed.
She thinks you're playing
hide-and-seek with her.
Will you please go look for her?
Ready or not, here I come.
I was picked for a jury.
How do they know who to pick?
Well, there's something
called a jury pool
and they ask people
all sorts of questions.
But if they don't like
your answers,
then they don't pick you.
They don't want
smart people, sweetie.
They want stupid people.
People that'll just...
kind of roll over
and do what you tell them,
think what you want
'em to think.
Actually, they didn't
want to pick me,
but the prosecutor ran out
of challenges, so they had to.
The whole system's
corrupt anyways.
I'm telling you,
you should've seen me
today down at City Hall
applying for those permits.
Everybody's got their hand out.
What permits?
What permits, Danny?
Hey, you know what's funny?
This Theresa, it says
in the paper
she liked to get down
after they roll the guys.
What's "get down"?
You have to ask
your mommy that, sweetie.
Actually, what am I saying?
She's the last person to ask.
Gotta go meet a guy.
Why did you come to Hawaii?
Why'd I come...
Uh, bill collectors.
Back in Arizona, bill collectors
knocking on the door.
And what did you
bring with you besides
your clothes and things?
Uh...
.38 calibre Smith and Wesson.
.38 revolv...
What else?
- Sorry?
- What else?
A knife. A Buck knife.
What did you call the knife?
Justice.
Why Justice?
Well, uh, well,
Theresa called it that.
You'd have to ask her.
After you moved to Honolulu,
what were you doing
to make a living?
I couldn't get a job.
Flat-out couldn't get a job.
I felt bad about it.
Did Theresa feel bad about that?
Objection!
Overruled.
Mr. Nichol,
did Theresa reproach you
for being unemployed?
You know, I just wanted
to support her.
I just... You know,
take care of her.
She deserved better.
So you started robbing people?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am, but only people
who wanted to buy narcotics.
I mean, Theresa even said,
What are the cops gonna...
What are they gonna say?
I wanted to buy some dope
and he ripped me off?
You know, she made it
easy to live with.
When you say
"easy to live with,"
what do you mean?
Well, it's, it's...
It's... it's hard
to initiate violence.
You know, and it had
to be right, and, uh...
Well, she convinced me
that it could be right.
How did she convince you?
I loved her.
He loved you...
but listening to him now,
it's hard to believe.
He looks at you
like you're a stranger.
I guess it's hard to remember
love when it's gone.
How there was a time when
you'd do anything for him.
Tell her she'll have
her money next week.
But there's money
in the account.
No, there isn't.
What?
There isn't money.
Come here.
- What? What?
- Come here, come here.
What?
Tell her you're sick.
No, no, no, tell her, uh...
Tell her
Aimee's sick, Aimee's sick,
we spent the money on a doctor.
I-I can't lie to her.
Why are you
looking at me like that?
Where is the money? Like I'm
letting you down, or something?
It's tied up, okay?
In the property
with those business guys.
It'll be a couple weeks
and we'll have it.
Would you calm down?
How're we gonna pay the bills?
I don't know.
Call your mother.
I can't call my mother.
Yes, you can...
I cannot call my mother, Danny.
Okay, could you answer
the door, then? Please? Please?
I warned you about this.
I'm really sorry.
It's just...
Aimee's been really
sick this week,
it's just been rough.
But... next week, I promise.
Alright, next week.
How was Theresa
acting towards Bobby Gordon
in the bar?
Well, like he had a play coming.
What do you mean by that?
Well, I mean, you know,
not to be... not to be, uh...
gross, but... like, romantic.
And what did you think
Theresa had in mind for him?
Objection!
Overruled.
Your Honour! You'll get
your turn, Mr. Kahane.
Did Theresa tell you her plan?
I thought we were
gonna rob the guy.
You know, that's what I
thought we were gonna do,
and he turned around,
and not to jump her,
nothing like that,
and she shot him. She just...
she just shot him.
And what were you doing?
I was yelling,
I was freaked out.
I couldn't believe it,
I was, you know,
"What'd you do that for?!"
I...
What happened then?
I-I got in the car
and I took off,
I had to get out of there.
I just...
I drove.
How did Theresa appear to you?
- Objection!
- Overruled.
How did Theresa appear to you?
Like, uh...
Like, I do this
every day. Just...
Just calm.
I do this every day.
Looking at me, like, you know,
"What's your problem?"
I should be a man,
like I let her down
or something.
I'm gonna get fired
if we don't wrap it up.
Her lawyer's taking forever.
My father used to say
he spent his whole life
studying the law so that
12 people could think about it
for the first time.
I'll be happy to think
about the law
once we lock that woman up.
But we don't even know
if she did it.
Are you kidding?
If she didn't do it, who did?
Her guy?
And if he did it,
they'd have him on trial.
Look, we're not even supposed
to be talking about this.
You're not supposed to be
writing in that notebook.
Mr. Nichol.
Isn't it true
that prior to your marriage,
Theresa was a close follower
of the Mormon Church?
No, that's not true.
Wasn't it your idea
to start robbing tourists?
No, she came up with that
all on her own, come on.
Is it true
you stole your knife, Justice,
from a neighbour?
You see, right...
That's what I told
the detectives, right, but...
no, that's not true.
Oh, so you lied.
Definitely I lied.
I lied outrageously,
but that's when I was fighting
the-the-the robberies
and the murders, you know?
You were fighting them by lying?
Yeah, that's what
criminals do, you know?
Move it along, Mr. Kahane.
Mr. Nichol,
did you study law
while you were in prison
in California?
Yes, sir. Yes, I did.
Have you testified
in other court cases?
- Objection.
- Sustained.
The jury will disregard
the question.
Your Honour!
Mr. Nichol, were you
offered a deal
for your testimony at this trial?
No!
Watch yourself, Mr. Kahane.
Your Honour,
I am trying to establish
the witness's motivation.
Your Honour, I already pulled
life without parole in California.
Mr. Nichol...
Let him finish.
You know,
I got nothing to gain here.
I just want to see justice for
that kid she killed. That's it.
Your Honour, can I
continue with my cross now?
Counsel, approach the bench.
Two days before
Bobby Gordon was killed,
Theresa and Vincent Nichols
robbed you.
Where do you want me to go?
They jumped my truck,
said, "Drive to the beach."
I think he thought
I was trying to get us lost.
Who did?
She said he was her brother.
- Vincent Nichol?
- Yes.
Let the record
reflect that the witness
is referring to Ms. Nichol's
husband, Vincent Nichol.
My cam...
My camera's in the car.
Look at me, don't look at her.
The guy, Vincent,
went to tie me up.
And what was Theresa doing?
She was holding the gun.
She looked...
I don't know, blank.
He had the knife.
He called it "Justice."
Did he say why he called...
What kind of people
name a knife?
My parents used to tell me:
"Don't get in trouble, because
we won't bail you out."
And I'd think:
Well, I'd never ask you.
I'd think: I can take care
of myself.
And then for a while,
I thought Danny would.
Sally?
To what do I owe the pleasure?
You could've called me, Mom.
Well, I did leave
a message several months back
with, um... uh, Danny.
Don't pretend you can't
remember his name.
Has he found a job yet?
Yeah, he's working
on a real estate deal.
Oh, dear.
So, do you need money?
No. No, actually, I just
called to see how you were.
Are you taking care of yourself?
No cigarettes? Promise me.
You sound just like your father.
I miss him, Mom.
Yes.
Well, so do I.
Raise your right hand.
Where is your family, Theresa?
There's no one here
in the court for you.
I am.
Who do you belong to now?
Theresa, why did
you come to Hawaii?
It was going to be
our honeymoon.
I didn't know
we weren't going back.
Who named the knife Justice?
Vincent did.
And who decided
that you would start
robbing people?
Vincent made all the decisions.
Before you met Vincent Nichol,
were you religious?
I was raised Mormon.
I was a Sunday School teacher.
Your parents must have been
very worried about you.
They didn't want me
to marry Vincent, so...
when I did, that was kind of it.
During your time in Hawaii,
did Vincent ever threaten you
with bodily harm?
- Objection.
- Sustained.
Did you and Vincent argue?
- Yes.
- You fought.
Did he ever point
the gun at you?
- Yes.
- Did it ever go off?
Yes, once.
The bullet went
right by my face.
Objection, Your Honour.
This line of questioning
is completely irrelevant...
Your Honour,
I'm trying to establish...
She's right, Mr. Kahane. Please
stick to the case at hand.
Theresa...
did you shoot Bobby Gordon?
I did not.
It started just like
the other times.
Vincent asked Bobby
did he have a car.
Said he knew another
party we could go to.
But you didn't go to a party.
- No.
- No, instead,
you made him drive you out
to Hanauma Bay.
Yes.
Why?
There was never anyone around.
Vincent said it was
his lucky spot.
What happened
when you got there?
Vincent was mad,
because we didn't have any rope.
Alright.
And he robbed him?
Took all the money he had,
but it was only about $40,
I think.
Hands behind your back.
Come on!
Did you even see Bobby get shot?
No.
Why not?
I had to put my boots on.
I went back to the car.
Maybe Bobby said something
to Vincent, I don't know.
Sometimes Vincent got jealous
if he thought I was
acting too friendly.
You were at the car
when you heard shots?
Yes.
And what did you do then?
I couldn't even
hardly believe it.
I can't hardly believe it now.
Okay, sweetie,
you're all tucked in.
Sleep tight, don't let
the bedbugs bite.
I want Daddy.
Well, you got me.
I love you, sweetie.
"You're so young."
A nice Mormon girl.
Vincent must have taken
your breath away.
Did you know he was dangerous?
"Is that why you fell
in love with him?"
Where have you been?
"Hawaii, the edge of the world.
You're Adam and Eve."
"Bonnie and Clyde.
No one for you but him."
Did you not see anymore
"that you could still get away?"
Wow.
That's so deep, Sally.
Let me guess.
You don't think
she did it, right?
It was his word against hers.
I knew it!
Only you, Sally,
could turn it all around,
twist it around,
and make it seem
like it's all the guy's fault.
Pfft. Is there anything to eat?
You missed dinner.
Oh, really?
Where have you been?
City Hall.
They won't grant the permits...
Can't tear the building down,
can't sell the property...
I don't understand.
Oh, you don't understand?
Well, let me make it
simple for you.
I got screwed, okay?
So now you can go ahead
and tell me that you told me so.
But... if-if we can't pay the
rent, Danny, we can't live here.
So go. Go, please. Leave.
Where am I gonna go?
I gave up everything for you.
I-I left everything behind.
Poor Sally! Oh, poor Sally!
Poor little Sally!
Left her mommy and daddy behind,
did ya?
Huh?
Poor Danny has to live
with this!
Sally...
Hey, shh...
Be quiet, we don't
want to wake up Aimee.
I'm sorry, okay?
Sally, I'm so sorry.
I don't know why I do that.
I'm an idiot.
I'm trying. I'm really trying,
I am. You know that, right?
I love you.
You know I love you,
right, Sally?
I don't know why I do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna go.
I'll pack up my stuff,
I'll just go.
I'll leave you two alone.
You'll be better off without me.
I'm just gonna go.
No.
Please don't go.
I'm sorry.
I'm never gonna do that again.
We could have another baby.
Another baby.
You want to do that?
After Bobby Gordon's murder,
did you leave Hawaii
with Vincent?
Yes, we did.
You went with him to California.
Yes.
You didn't leave him.
Even though you claim
that he had killed someone.
No.
Even though you claim
that you were afraid of him.
No. I mean, no,
I didn't leave.
Can you tell me why not?
We were married.
Did you write
this letter to Vincent?
Ms. Nichol?
I don't recall.
You don't recall?
You wrote this letter while
you were in California waiting...
Objection!
Withdrawn.
Could you read it out loud,
please?
"Honey, please don't
blame yourself"
for what happened.
You tried to keep me from it,
but I didn't
"want to leave."
You wrote this
letter from prison
when Vincent had no way
of reaching you.
No way of hurting you, correct?
Yes.
Nothing further, Your Honour.
If Vincent shot the guy,
why would she pack up
and go to California with him?
She was afraid.
Why would she be afraid?
Afraid to leave him.
Afraid of life without him.
She's not big on fear.
She's the one
that killed someone.
I don't think she did it.
Jeez...
Bye, sweetie.
Okay, bye.
See ya.
Wait, where are you going?
I'm going to meet some guys
about taking that property
off my hands.
But are you taking Aimee
with you?
Um, no, I'm not.
I have to go to court.
Yeah, well, okay...
figure it out, alright?
I gotta go.
Give me the keys.
No, Danny, you stay here
with Aimee. I have got
to go to final arguments,
it's the last day of the trial.
I'm not messing around,
give me the keys.
No, call and cancel
or stay here with Aimee,
I am leaving now.
Do not go out that door.
Sally.
Yeah, good.
I'm not gonna do this anymore.
Do what? Don't walk away
from me.
I won't do this anymore!
What's the matter with you?!
I'm done!
Mama?
That's good, that's great.
Come, baby. Come, come.
It's okay, sweetie.
Okay, let's go.
Hey, Sally.
Don't.
Come on, we gotta go.
We gotta go now.
Come on.
- I don't wanna go!
- Aimee.
Do me a favour, come here,
get in your car seat, okay.
Hop on in, hop on in,
quick, quick, quick.
We're late.
I don't wanna go.
Okay, there you go. Okay.
Come on, Aimee, sit still,
please!
I wanna stay with Daddy!
- Well, you can't.
- Not today, we gotta go.
All rise.
Be seated.
Mommy, stop pulling me.
I'm sorry, but we gotta...
We're late.
Why don't you sit
right here, sweetie, okay?
Sit here and colour.
Would you watch her
until first recess?
Juror number 11, you're late.
You are excused.
Juror number 11 will be replaced
with the first alternate.
Your Honour,
the prosecution requests
an evidential clarification
of the State's
evidence exhibit 13 A.
Mr. Gordon's shirt...
Mr. Gordon's sandals,
Mr. Gordon's pants...
Mommy, what now?
The jury had to be unanimous. It
took them less than two hours.
Guilty?
30 years!
The average felony sentence
in Hawaii
is four or five years.
Even mob killers
get less than 20.
Well, she must be out by now.
Parole, something.
She's still in prison
in California.
After all these years.
After all these years,
and you never brought it up?
I buried it.
Five minutes I was late.
I guess I felt...
Guilty?
Maybe I could stop
and visit Theresa
on my way to my mom's.
California is not
on the way to Kansas.
You think it's stupid.
No, I like it
when you get like this.
Like what?
Maybe this is your book.
Your next book.
Dear Theresa,
I was on your jury in Oahu
many years ago.
I know it's been a long time,
but lately I've been
thinking about that,
and wondering how you're doing.
I had no idea
what happened to you,
but I made some calls,
and there you are in California.
I hope you don't find this odd.
Dear Sally... ...but I'm
wondering if I might visit you.
I received your letter,
and to say I was overwhelmed
is the understatement
of the year.
I want to thank you
so much for writing.
I don't get a lot of mail.
Or a lot of visitors,
for that matter.
I'm trying to picture you.
I wonder what you remember
about the trial.
There's so many things
I want to ask you.
I'm enclosing the forms
you'll need
if you want to visit the
next time you come through.
And don't worry, there
aren't any hard feelings.
I'm looking forward
to meeting you very soon.
I remember you.
Thank you for sending
your book. It was...
interesting.
Well, I wrote it
a long time ago.
Uh, what can I get you?
Coffee would be great.
You look different
from what I expected.
Oh, well, the book,
the picture...
it was taken like 11 years ago.
Makeup, hair, doesn't even
look like me at all.
I didn't see your picture.
It was on the back jacket
of the book.
We're not allowed
hardcover books.
They rip the cover off
before we get them.
You look different
from what I remember.
That's what I meant.
Fancier.
Here, you try.
I'm not allowed
to touch the money.
I'm sorry.
I wonder why you came here now.
I found this old notebook
that I used to keep
during the trial.
I remember.
The judge took it away.
I remember you took notes
the whole way through.
It's the only way
I could see to get through it.
To write.
Yes.
Then you became a real writer.
And here I am.
When I started
to read the notebook,
it was like someone else
had written it.
I had forgotten all of it.
And I guess when I left,
I wanted to put it all
behind me.
Hawaii, all of it.
You should know...
I wasn't there at the end
for your deliberations.
I know. The last day,
you were late.
I couldn't leave my daughter.
I-I started to, but I couldn't.
It was complicated.
Don't worry.
I would've done exactly
the same thing in your place.
That's what mothers are for.
Yeah, but I think
I might've made a difference.
That's not why you came.
We were almost the same age.
I ran away to Hawaii
with my husband.
I went from my father's house
to my husband's house.
Just like you.
What about you?
You met Vincent...
He kept bugging me
about getting married, so...
one day I said okay.
I wanted to make him happy.
I wanted to make
everybody happy.
Next thing I know, it was done.
My parents didn't like Vincent,
so when I married him,
that was kind of it.
My parents were furious
when I married Danny.
I fought with my father.
He said if I left,
I shouldn't bother coming back.
He never forgave me.
He died the summer
before your trial.
My dad died in July.
He never forgave me either.
"All of these
coincidences are amazing."
Her first job was at JC Penney's,
mine was at JC Penney's.
I don't know why you want
to go on stirring up the past.
It was nice of you to come see your mom.
It's been a long time.
She's not really visiting me,
she went to see a murderer.
Oh, a real murderer?
Who'd he kill?
It's a woman, actually.
The prison's in California.
I'm just the stopover.
She says she didn't do it.
They all say that.
It's very In Cold Blood.
Right, but except
those murderers were guilty.
She's innocent?
Fantastic for the book.
Well, not totally innocent.
Sally, help me out here.
What do you think?
Well, she's not that
different from the trial.
The same things that sunk her -
the calm, the blankness -
now it almost seems reasonable,
as if it's the only
way to bear it.
So you think that's why they
convicted her, because she was calm?
I don't know. I wasn't there.
And do you really believe
that if you had been there
it would've made a difference?
It had to be unanimous.
So, what's the book?
We're connected.
My life to hers.
I can't figure it out,
but I want to know.
Hi, I'm here to see an inmate.
Theresa Nichol?
I wanted to bring
my notebook in with me.
They said I needed special
permission at the gate.
You're the one
that's been calling here.
The writer.
I'd like to be able
to make some notes.
Theresa Nichol?
Give me a break.
I mean, my husband's no
walk in the park,
but at least I go home
every night.
Wanna write a book about that?
Theresa never
gets in trouble. Perfect record.
Now you come along,
they're all over her.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Theresa says you're gonna
help get her out of here.
Good thing.
I mean, it's ridiculous.
I deserve to do the time.
I took a life.
Well, he was a mean
son-of-a-bitch.
My roommate.
- What did she...?
- Shot her husband.
Most of the lifers here
are in for something like that.
She's been here 28 years.
Had a mastectomy this summer,
chemo,
radiation...
They won't let her out.
I don't want to die in here.
You know, those dogs can
turn the lights on for you,
lock the door?
Inmates train them
to help disabled people.
How come you're not
in the dog program?
I just don't want it, you know?
Even to pet them,
because then you're stuck.
You can't be happy again
without each other.
When I first moved out,
I had this little beagle puppy.
Man, I loved that little guy.
Vincent made me get rid
of him when we went to Hawaii.
Where is Vincent now?
From the time he was 14,
he's only been out of jail
a few months.
I honestly believe
if he'd been free longer,
he would've had a following
and more people would've died.
A following like a cult?
He told me he could
read my mind.
My face was like an open book.
It's weird that I believed him.
Well, you were in love with him.
You know,
in most states, the husband
can't testify against the wife.
But they can in Hawaii.
Because they changed the law
that summer, just for me.
They were gonna get me
no matter what.
Vincent failed a polygraph,
you know.
Well, they didn't
say that at the trial.
You being a few minutes late
was very convenient for them.
That judge wanted you
off the jury.
I think there's a reason
you came back into my life now.
When you wrote me
how your father was a lawyer.
Yeah, but I'm not a lawyer.
You're a writer.
I'm sorry.
I think I misunderstood.
You're gonna stay up all night
again looking at porn?
No, I'm coming in soon.
Look, she was right.
Hawaii changed the law
about spousal testimony
right before her trial.
You out of your mind?
You can't start buying
all her conspiracy theories.
Look, Leonard, I know
her theories are crazy, but I...
But?
I have to find Vincent Nichol.
He's in prison.
He's been in prison
all but 18 months
of his entire adult life.
- Why?
- I don't know.
No, I mean why find him?
Because he's the only one
who knows what really
- happened that night.
- What about Theresa?
Sally...
have you even asked her?
How you doing?
Good.
Good, good, good, good.
I took a writing class
once in here.
The teacher wasn't half
as good-looking as you are.
"Write what you know,"
that's what they told us.
Same as therapy.
It's all about what you know.
What about what you want
to know, writer lady?
Like what I said in my letter,
I was on the jury
at Theresa Nichol's trial.
Right, right, poor old Theresa.
Why do you say poor Theresa?
Can't please all people
all the time, right?
Is she still good-looking?
Yeah, well, that's her thing.
Pretty girl.
It's like a charm.
Everybody wants to do
for a pretty girl.
I'm just interested
in the truth.
You know what
they told us in therapy?
About how, uh...
criminals want to blame
everybody else.
Like Theresa?
We're talking about me here!
You want to blame
everybody else.
No, no, no, that was before.
I don't make victims
out of people anymore.
So, Theresa was a victim.
Come on...
She loved it.
You know all about that,
don't you?
Maybe I do know.
Maybe that's why I don't think
you told the truth about
what happened that night.
Look at you.
Yeah.
You look at me.
You look at me, and you look
at that little girl.
What do you think happened?
She's serving a life sentence
for a murder
based solely on your testimony.
Well, that's, uh...
You see, to me, that's funny,
because the cops made
a real big stink
about how they didn't
believe a word I said.
And at the trial, everybody!
Everybody ate it up.
Why did you testify?
Hoping for a break,
shot at parole.
Surprise, surprise.
They, uh, screwed me.
Does Theresa deserve to be free?
It's a joke that
that girl's incarcerated.
Now, that's what you
should write in your book.
Because...?
What do you think?
I think you shot Bobby Gordon.
Well, there you go.
Guess this therapy works
pretty good after all.
Happy birthday, Grandma!
Happy birthday!
Yeah!
Well done.
Get the cake knife, please.
Are you alright?
I'm fine. Cake knife, please.
In the silver drawer.
Okay.
Uh, excuse me.
Grace sent me here
for more liquor.
Oh, right. That was supposed
to be my job.
Help yourself.
Uh, well, actually, um...
the-the really good stuff
is here.
You must've worked
with my father.
And you must be Sally.
I'm John Emory.
Oh, my God. John Emory, yes.
Yes.
Right.
Yeah.
Y-y-you... you're not, uh,
having cake?
Uh, no, I'm, I'm...
just a bit preoccupied, I guess.
Oh, with the murder.
Right. Your mother tells me
you're obsessed.
Oh, well, my mom is mystified.
But this woman went to prison
for a crime she did not commit.
My prisoner, Theresa Nichol.
Her husband was the only one
who testified against her.
And now he's saying that he's
the one who pulled the trigger.
Well, that, that...
that might help you
at a parole hearing.
But to get the judge
to reopen the case,
that's next to impossible.
You'd have to... you'd have to
prove a miscarriage of justice.
You'd have to prove the trial
was rigged against her.
- Well, it was.
- Well, you know that?
Yes, I was there.
Well, I'll tell you what.
You send over the files,
and I'll have a look at them.
Great, thank you.
He's an old friend
of my father's.
Friend, enemy, defence lawyer.
Well, you pretty much
missed the party, Mom.
I'm sorry, honey.
It's just that this John Emory
could really help me out.
He's everything a lawyer
should be. Open-minded,
forgiving; he was nothing
like my father.
An open mind
is a relative thing.
It always seemed to me
that it was you who could
not forgive your father,
not the other way around.
Dear Sally,
I've been thinking about
where you live
and how you live.
Trying to picture you
up there in Canada.
I've been thinking
about you working,
writing away.
And I think someday maybe I
could have a place like that.
To write and be alone.
Dear Theresa,
thank you for sending
the transcripts of the trial.
I haven't written a lot because
there's so much to read.
Did I actually listen to all
these millions of words?
I think about that,
looking for a place to live,
something I've never done.
And what about the rest?
Getting a job, making friends.
There are so many things
I don't know how to do.
Sometimes, that scares me.
I probably need your help.
I hope that's okay.
When I first came
to Canada with Aimee,
that's what I wanted too:
a new life.
Everything new
so that I would be new.
I like to close
my eyes and think about
that room to write in,
how I would decorate it.
How I would spend my time there.
How it would be entirely my own.
Sally, I'm so grateful
I met you.
It frightens me,
but I can't wait
to get out of here.
It's funny,
you write to me
about the future,
and I'm just now
getting started on the past.
And what was Theresa doing?
She was holding the gun.
She looked...
I don't know, blank.
Did he tell you why
he called it Justice?
What kind of people
name a knife?
Mr. Sneed?
Yes?
My name is Sally Linden.
I...
Thanks, I'm not interested.
I was on the jury for the
Theresa Nichol murder trial.
You testified.
I'm writing a book.
All I got is instant coffee.
The bachelor way.
Half of the time, I make it
with hot water from the tap.
You know Theresa Nichol
is still in prison?
Good. I hope she dies there.
But at the trial you testified
that she looked blank.
Did you think she was scared?
I said she looked blank?
Yeah.
Let me show you something.
It's so long ago. Still...
there's some lessons
you don't need to learn twice.
How's that?
That's the last time
I let a pretty girl
get one over on me.
They took my camera, you know.
Police found a pawn shop
ticket on...
What was his name?
Vincent.
They held it for evidence
in the trial, but...
when I finally got it back...
Does she look blank?
Does she look scared?
They're having the time
of their lives.
You said you're guilty about
the five minutes you were late.
Well, what about her?
What about the...
five minutes she held the gun
on that poor
son-of-a-bitch they killed?
That's five minutes she didn't
run out in the road
and yell for help.
That's five minutes she didn't
turn the gun on her husband.
Hi, Mr. Emory.
Yeah, I filed the writ.
I think we've got a case here.
Great.
Did you know that
Vincent Nichol failed
a lie detector test?
And they still let him testify.
Yeah, they let him testify.
The State allowed him
to perjure himself,
they encouraged it.
But why?
Vincent offered them
a murder, a story.
He said Theresa wouldn't talk.
Why would he do that?
Offer it up?
He cut a deal, he cut a deal.
He got immunity in Hawaii,
which left only one person
to swing for it, so...
They needed to convict someone.
Yes, and he was hoping
it would help his case
in California where he was awaiting
trial for the other murder.
What? I'm sorry,
the other murder?
Yeah, for the Ernesto Navarro
murder.
The other one, the second one
in California.
Oh, so you lied.
Definitely I lied.
I lied outrageously,
but that's when I was fighting
the-the-the robberies
and the murders. You know?
Sally?
After the first killing,
Theresa left Hawaii
with Vincent,
fled to California.
Two weeks later,
Vincent shot and killed
this guy named Ernesto Navarro
while Theresa looked on.
You didn't know this?
I... cannot believe
she would do this to me!
Really, Sally,
she didn't do it to you.
Don't do that.
Do what?!
Be smug! Superior!
What are you gonna do?
If you're gonna go down there,
you have to visit your mother.
Why? So she can say
"I told you so"?
You do whatever you want.
You're a grown-up.
But your mother's sick,
and it's on the way.
California is not
on the way to Kansas.
Right, right.
Why did you only ship me
evidence from the Hawaii trial?
I've served sentence
for my involvement
in the California crime.
Involvement? Theresa!
California law doesn't care
who pulled the trigger.
I was convicted of felony murder
just for being there.
That's not the law in Hawaii.
Then Vincent told them
I shot Bobby Gordon.
Vincent. It's always Vincent.
Theresa, you knew what he was.
You left Hawaii with him,
you went to California with him,
but you didn't leave him.
He said he would kill me.
Did you even try?
I did try.
I tried in California.
Thought maybe he could
drive me away.
Drive, drive, go!
But Vincent wouldn't let me go.
He couldn't.
He always said he could
tell what I was thinking.
So I thought it was my fault.
I tried to get away,
and that man died.
There was nothing I could do.
Nowhere I could go.
After that,
I didn't ask for help.
Until I came along.
I never asked you for anything.
You came here, you wanted
to write your book.
The book.
That's right, I wanted
to write my book.
Goodbye.
Mom?
I'm here.
Sally.
Mom, I'm calling an ambulance.
No, no, no, no.
Just stay with me, sweetie.
Mom. I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have...
I've been so wrapped up,
I haven't...
No, no, it's alright.
It's alright.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm tired of being sick.
Just stay with me.
I've thought over and over,
trying to figure out
maybe there was something
different I could've done.
I'm still thinking about that.
I've been thinking I wish
there had been something to do
or I'd been thinking
more clearly at the time.
I wish I'd not been
so powerless.
I've thought about it a lot
since my last hearing,
and in the last many years.
I've thought about
the whole thing a lot,
and I didn't
enjoy being involved
in the crimes.
And I didn't enjoy
the intimidation and the fear
that I felt with him.
Dear Sally,
my parole hearing was today,
and I was shaking so bad
I could barely
get the words out.
It didn't really matter
in the end.
I haven't had a letter from you.
I guess I might not
have one again.
But I wanted to say thanks
for everything,
and for visiting me.
I'll miss you.
I shouldn't have read it.
I don't need it.
I've given up on the book.
"Hawaii, edge of the world."
You're Adam and Eve,
Bonnie and Clyde.
No one for you but him.
Did you not see anymore that...
"you can still get away?"
Florid?
No.
I didn't know...
any of this.
That's because
I didn't tell you.
That's what we do in my family.
Pack it up and forget it.
I've been thinking
about these...
little moments that
determine our lives.
The minutes when things
can go either way.
I walked out
of that courthouse...
and I had Aimee by the hand.
She was looking up at me.
"What now, Mommy?"
All I could think of to do...
I went back into the courthouse,
I called my mom.
She said...
she would wire me money
for plane tickets
that afternoon.
She told me to come home.
Yeah, open number three.
I didn't think you'd come back.
I didn't know that I would.
I'm so sorry about your mother.
I heard you were denied parole.
Yes.
I talked
to John Emory last night.
The lawyer?
Yeah, a judge in Hawaii has
granted the writ of habeas corpus.
He's going to reopen your case.
And Vincent's gonna get
on the stand and tell them
what he told me.
I can't believe it.
Theresa, I need to know
what happened that night
at Hanauma Bay.
I testified very truthfully
at my trial.
You believe that at least?
I believe you told us the facts,
but the truth is something else.
I went back...
to start the car,
and then Vincent just...
shoots him.
Shoots him, and I can't...
believe it, I'm...
I'm standing there
and I can't move.
And it's awful.
But...
It's all mixed up
with love and...
everything I should do,
but...
What I think is...
how it's only Vincent and me.
We've only got each other.
How could I... have loved him?
How could that have been me?
How did I get in the car
and leave that boy
lying in the sand?
And then we were driving,
and I...
I knew it was wrong,
but it was...
Too late.
Hey.
Theresa...
I sat at your trial.
I watched.
I thought I understood...
that it was wrong.
That you should've left
Vincent, done anything
to get away from him, but...
I knew why you didn't.
How?
Because we were alike.
We weren't so much alike
then, were we?
I mean, you left.
Did you know that Vincent Nichol
failed a polygraph?
I don't recall.
Did you know...
why he agreed to testify
against his wife?
It's a long time ago.
I don't recall.
There were only three
witnesses to the murder,
and one was dead.
But it wasn't enough for me
to show that Vincent was lying,
I needed the jury
to understand why.
Vincent Nichol made a deal.
Immunity in Hawaii.
In California, he was hoping
for a chance at parole.
He had everything to gain.
So the prosecution
knew about this deal?
They did, sir.
Did they tell you
about the deal?
No, they told me
the opposite was true.
Vincent said under oath
he had nothing to gain,
and they let it stand.
Even if this is true,
Mr. Emory,
it's probably not enough
to throw out a murder.
With all due respect,
Your Honour, I'd have argued it
completely differently
if I had known.
It would've made my case.
- Okay, talk to you later.
- What?
Vincent Nichol
is not gonna testify.
Why not?
I'm sorry.
He's gone, he's gone.
Gone? He's in prison.
Well, he ratted out
another cellmate
in a capital case,
and they put him
in witness protection.
Where?
Uh, I don't know.
They're not gonna tell me,
and he's not gonna testify.
- Do we even have a chance?
- Come on.
Your Honour, this is
a habeas corpus hearing.
We're not here to determine
whether or not
the prisoner is innocent.
We're asking if the prosecution
so tainted this trial
as to make the conviction
a denial of due process.
That's Donnelly versus
DeChristoforo, 1974.
John, I know why we're here.
Now, they used the testimony
of a witness who sold themselves
to the prosecution.
Your Honour... Now, the
State had the obligation...
the obligation
to tell the defence,
and they didn't.
- You haven't proved that.
- Not enough.
Not enough because
I have to convince you
that's correct, that...
tainted testimony
swayed the jury
and determined the verdict.
That's true, and I'm gonna
call a witness.
Sally Linden was on
the original jury,
but she was removed... Your Honour,
it's impermissible for a juror...
on the last day of the trial.
To testify as to how
a verdict was reached.
She was removed from the jury
on the last day of the trial.
She was not involved
in the verdict.
Theresa, did you
shoot Bobby Gordon?
I did not.
This was a long time ago.
You seem to remember it
so clearly.
I took copious notes.
They wanted us to think
that Vincent
had absolutely nothing to gain
by testifying, and we did.
- Your Honour.
- This is a big deal, Lynn.
Don't interrupt again.
So you're saying
the State's case
rested solely on the testimony
of Vincent Nichol?
Absolutely.
It was his word against hers.
We were led to believe him.
You're asking
this court for remedy.
I have to be certain.
Your Honour, we're asking that
the conviction be overturned.
Wait, wait.
Please, I just have to say this.
Theresa Nichol was young.
She was frightened.
She did the wrong thing.
We can sit here
and talk about why,
we can talk about
what she should've done...
we can wonder
if there was one moment
where she could've
changed everything.
But in the end,
there's no undoing it.
No one knows that
more than Theresa.
She has paid the price for it.
But... Theresa didn't
shoot anyone.
Justice wasn't served.
We have a chance now,
here today, to make that right.
We have a chance
to do what's just.
Sally.
Hi, Danny.
Uh...
Do... do you want
to come inside?
Come on in.
I'd, uh... offer you something
to drink,
but I gave it up, so...
Oh, that's okay.
I can't stay for long.
Right.
Um, well, here, have a seat.
So, uh, tell me, what...
what brings you around here?
Uh, well, they reopened
Theresa Nichol's case.
The jury I was on.
Oh, right, right, yeah,
the, um...
the murder trial.
Yeah.
I just thought I'd stop by,
see how you were.
Yeah. Good, good.
Terrific, actually.
Got a bunch of deals
going out of Hong Kong now.
Um, just got money to burn,
those guys, I'm telling you.
You talk to Aimee?
Uh, yeah. She calls
once in a while, yeah.
She's doing great at school,
I guess.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Wow, you...
You look great, Sally.
You really do.
Thank you.
I... I just drove out
to Hanauma Bay, actually.
To see where
the murder happened.
You know, there's a legend
about that place.
It's these...
these two guys are fighting
over this girl.
This beautiful girl.
And, uh, she wants them to stop.
So she turns herself
into a crater.
You know, sacrificing her life.
And her father,
he puts his arms around her
to protect her,
and those are the arms
of Hanauma Bay.
Sure was great to see you.
You too.
Listen, Sally, I just feel
like I should, uh...
Don't, Danny.
It was a long time ago.
Goodbye.
See ya.
♪ You're tired of being poor ♪
♪ You say you've got
to change ♪
♪ If you're going
to live here ♪
♪ You're wired and
you're sore ♪
♪ You say it makes
you strange ♪
♪ But I know it's
a good tear ♪
♪ In your eye ♪
Thank you.
♪ I know it's a good smile
that makes you cry... ♪
You open a trunk and it comes
rushing out at you.
Open a notebook,
and out comes the past.
All the mistakes I made.
Everything I couldn't see.
Hello?
I changed countries,
changed lives.
And somehow, I'd left
the past unfinished.
But it doesn't leave you
alone, the past.
It doesn't.
What?
The judge in Hawaii
ruled on Theresa's case.
And?
The verdict of murder
is overturned.
Congratulations.
♪ You're wired and
you're sore ♪
♪ You say it makes
you strange ♪
♪ But I know it's a
good tear ♪
♪ In your eye ♪
♪ I know it's a good smile
that makes you cry... ♪
Congratulations.
I'm in love.
This time, he's worth it.
Dexter, Golden Retriever.
You joined the dog program?
So far, he's not so hot
with the light switches,
but we'll get there.
But your verdict was overturned.
They'll appeal.
They could decide to retry me.
It could take years.
They have to let you out.
Eventually, but I can't
keep living in the meantime.
I have to live my life
the way it really is.
You too.
You should finish your book.
But there's no ending.
Well...
This is as good an end as any.
Will you keep visiting me?
Yes.
After all, we've known
each other for years.
♪ Just one good thing
to hang onto ♪
♪ This one good thing
will let you ♪
♪ Give it all away... ♪
Okay.
Good boy. Sit.
There you go!
♪ Give it all away ♪