[Woman] NO! NO! NO!
♪ [Asie Payton
singing I Love You]
[Woman moaning]
OH!
YES.
♪ OOH, BABY ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU ♪
[Woman moaning]
♪ I'VE BEEN WAITING
ON YOU, GIRL ♪
♪ HOPE YOU'LL BE BY MY SIDE ♪
♪ LOVING, LOVING EYES ♪
♪ OOH, BABY ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU ♪
[Boy] HEY, YOU GUYS!
♪ OOH ♪
WAIT UP!
♪ BABY ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN SITIN' ROUND
HERE ALL DAY LONG ♪
[Woman moaning]
♪ WAITIN' ON YOU TILL DAWN ♪
♪ I DIDN'T LEAVE UNTIL
YOU CALLED ME, BABY ♪
[Woman] OH, GOD, YES.
OH, GOD.
MMM.
[Woman] NO, NO, NO.
[Honking]
[Woman moaning]
OH, RIGHT THERE.
[Woman] NO, NO, NO!
[Woman] YES, YES...
[Moaning]
OH!
WAIT.
[Woman laughing]
[Woman] WAIT.
[Knock at door]
HEY, BOBBY-BOY!
AAAH.
[Grunting]
HEY, BOBBY!
BOBBY-BOY.
[Leon] SOME DREAMS
RUIN BEING AWAKE,
IF YOU KNOW THE DIFFERENCE.
BEST NOT TO KNOW.
[Coughing]
BOBBY!
BOBBY-BOY.
YEAH?
HEY.
ARE YOU ALONE?
YEAH.
ARE YOU AWAKE?
NO, I'M AWAKE NOW.
I GOT SOME BEER.
YEAH?
I'LL JUST GET IT.
ALL RIGHT.
"DEAR MR. BARLOW,
"THE SMALL SIZE OF OUR STAFF
"PRECLUDES INDIVIDUAL
COMMENTS ON SUBMISSIONS.
"NEITHER THIS, NOR THE
RETURN OF YOUR MANUSCRIPT
"REFLECTS ON THE
QUALITY OF YOUR WORK.
"THANK YOU FOR THE SUBMISSIONS
AND KEEP UP THE GOOD WORK."
THANK YOU FOR YOUR SUBMISSION.
[Coughs]
YOU GOT SOME MAIL.
HE SAID.
POLITE OF HIM NOT TO CALL
IT BATHROOM WALLPAPER.
HEY, HOW THE HELL THEY
PULL THAT OFF, ANYWAY?
THESE REFUGEES.
THERE'S HUNDREDS
OF THOUSANDS OF THEM.
TAKE 'EM FROM HERE,
MOVE THEM OVER THERE.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW HOW HARD
IT IS JUST TO GET 2 PEOPLE
TO AGREE TO DO THE SAME THING,
SHOW UP AT THE SAME PLACE.
HAVE THE SAME OBJECTIVE.
WELL, YEAH, OF COURSE YOU DO.
NO AMENDS MADE LAST NIGHT, HUH?
WOMEN.
YEAH.
JESUS CHRIST.
HIM, TOO.
YEAH.
YOU WANT A JOB?
I COULD USE A JOB.
I NEED SOME MONEY.
GOT A BIG HOUSE NEEDS PAINTING.
THANKS, MONROE.
VELMA SAID SOME OLD BOY
FLASHED HER AND MARILYN
OVER AT THE FOOD
WRANGLER THE OTHER DAY.
PULLED IT OUT WHERE
THEY WERE PARKED,
BY THE CHARITY CLOTHES DROP.
[Leon] CHARITY TROUSER DROP.
WHERE'S THE HARM?
JUST WHIPPED IT RIGHT ON OUT.
HOW BIG WAS IT?
[Chuckles]
YEAH, I ASKED THE SAME QUESTION.
VELMA SAID SHE DIDN'T
LOOK. BUT MARILYN...
COULD PICK IT OUT OF A LINEUP.
SAID IT WASN'T NO
BIGGER THAN AN ACORN.
WELL, YOU'RE THE BEST HOUSE
PAINTER I EVER SAW, BOBBY.
BUT YOU DON'T
REALLY LIKE IT, DO YOU?
SEE, I LOVE PAINTING.
I LOVE EVERYTHING ABOUT IT.
BUT I GOT NO TECHNIQUE.
OF COURSE, FRANCIS BACON SAID,
"IN PAINTING,
"YOU HAVE TO KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING, NOT HOW."
OF COURSE, HE COMMITTED SUICIDE.
[Leon] EITHER ONE OF THOSE
DAMES GET A LOOK AT THE ACCUSED?
VELMA. MAKE, MODEL,
YEAR, COLOR, PLATE.
SHE'D HAVE GOTTEN HIS SHOE SIZE IF
HE HADN'T OF BOOKED OUT OF THERE.
CREAM-COLORED '78 CHEVY PICKUP.
HUH.
WITH A WHITE TAILGATE,
KIND OF LIKE A BUNNY.
SHIT. WE GOT HIM, NOW.
VELMA.
HELL, YEAH. SHE'S
THOROUGH AS A BY-GOD.
DON'T GET UP.
YOU SAY YOU GOT NO TECHNIQUE.
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
THAT YOU DON'T THINK YOU'RE
ANY GOOD AT PAINTING, OR WHAT?
[Monroe] NO, NO, NO.
NOT THAT, SO MUCH.
I... I MEAN, I GOT NO TECHNIQUE
FOR GETTING UP IN THE
MORNING, EITHER, BUT HERE I AM.
YEAH, WHY IS THAT?
I MEAN, YOU'RE
SITTING ON FORT KNOX.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT
HERE, BREAKING YOUR BACK?
[Monroe] AH, FORT KNOX.
EVERYBODY'S GOTTEN A JIG
THEY GOTTA DANCE ABOUT WORK.
FORT KNOX, HARD
KNOCKS, PLAID SOCKS,
CHINESE FUCKING PUZZLE
BOX, IT DON'T MATTER.
[Monroe] IN THE ABSENCE OF
THE BENEVOLENT
ARISTOCRACY, THOUGH,
THE OLD COLOSSUS
STILL GOT ONE FOOT
PLANTED IN ART, AND
THE OTHER IN COMMERCE.
HE'S PISSING ON YOUR HEAD,
WHILE HE'S WEARING
YOUR WRISTWATCH.
NOT TO KICK A METAPHOR
IN THE WHAT-DO-YOU-CALL.
WORK IS JUST WORK,
BROTHER, AND I THANK YOU.
[Man] HOW Y'ALL DOING?
MR. AARON.
YES, SIR.
HEY. HEY.
WHAT YOU GOT TO
SAY FOR YOURSELVES?
I CAN'T THINK OF A THING.
[Aaron] NOW, LOOK HERE, NOW.
YOU EVER HEAR OF THIS PLACE?
I CAN'T EVEN SAY IT.
WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
WELL, LOOKS LIKE A WAR
OF SOME KIND OR ANOTHER.
NOW, WHAT THE HELL DO THESE
PEOPLE GOT TO BE FIGHTING ABOUT?
DON'T HARDLY NEED
MUCH OF A REASON.
YOUR DADDY AND I HAD A REASON.
YOU AND MONROE DID, TOO.
"DID, TOO," WHAT?
TALKING ABOUT RE-ENLISTING.
SHOOTIN' SOME OF THEM
BOYS OVER THE SUB-SAHARA.
OH, RIGHT IN THE
SUB-SAHARA, HUH?
HOW'S YOUR LEG?
OH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
MIGHT HAVE TO CUT THE DAMN
THING OFF AND GET RID OF IT.
DID YOU GET THEM WAY
BACK WHERE IT'S COOL?
YOU BOYS LOOK LIKE
YOU NEED SOME COOLIN'.
HEY, I PUT THIS ONE TO
WORK TODAY, MR. AARON.
MMM.
AND WHAT ELSE CAN I DO YOU FOR?
I'LL JUST GET SOME ICE.
ALL RIGHTY.
HERE YOU GO.
YES, SIR.
[Honks horn]
THANKS FOR THE ADVANCE.
LET'S BEAT THE SUN UP TOMORROW.
♪ [Blues music playing]
[Man] "DEAR CONTRIBUTOR,
WE'RE SORRY THAT WE CANNOT
"USE THE ENCLOSED
MATERIAL AT THIS TIME."
[Woman] "DEAR WRITER,
"YOUR MANUSCRIPT DOES NOT
MEET OUR NEEDS AT THIS TIME."
[Man] "...WE'RE SORRY
THAT WE CANNOT ACCEPT
[Woman] "...YOUR SUBMISSION
FOR PUBLICATION AT THIS TIME."
[Man] "...IN NO WAY A
REFLECTION ON THE
"LITERARY VALUE
OF THE WORK ITSELF."
[Woman speaks Spanish]
[Dogs bark]
[Radio DJ] THIS ONE GOES
OUT TO LEON BARLOW.
IT'S A REJECTION
LETTER, OF COURSE,
BY A NEW YORK AGENT
IN WHOSE HANDS
LEON PLACED HIS TRUST
AND A 330-PAGE NOVEL.
♪ DEAR MR. BARLOW ♪
♪ WE ARE RETURNING
THE MANUSCRIPT ♪
♪ BECAUSE THE MARKET AT
THIS TIME IS NOT AMENABLE ♪
♪ TO NOVELS ABOUT DRUNK
PULPWOOD HAULERS ♪
♪ AND REDNECKS IN
HUNTING ACCIDENTS ♪
♪ READERS HERE AT THE AGENCY ♪
♪ FOUND YOUR WORK
HILARIOUS AND TOUCHING ♪
♪ WITH TERRIFIC CHARACTERS,
GREAT DIALOGUE ♪
♪ AND NO TYPOS ♪
♪ BUT WE DON'T FEEL
THIS COMPELLING NOVEL ♪
♪ CAN BE PLACED
WITH A PUBLISHER ♪
♪ PLEASE CONTACT US IF WE CAN
BE OF ANY FURTHER ASSISTANCE ♪
♪ WHOO OOOO ♪
"DEAR MOTHERFUCKER,
"YOU, SIR, ARE AN IGNORANT
AND SPINELESS CRETIN.
"HOW THE HELL DO YOU KNOW
THAT MY BOOK WON'T SELL
"UNLESS YOU GET OFF YOUR
FAT CAN AND TRY TO SELL IT?"
"YOU THINK I CAN JUST SHIT
ANOTHER ONE OF THESE OUT?
"I WORKED A SOLID YEAR
ON THIS COCKSUCKER.
"YOU KEPT MY MANUSCRIPT
3 GODDAMN MONTHS
"AND DIDN'T EVEN SEND IT AROUND.
"I'D LIKE TO STOMP A MUDHOLE
IN YOUR ASS AND WALK IT DRY."
♪ WHOO-HOO ♪
COCKSUCKER!
"SINCERELY..."
[Radio DJ] LEON BARLOW,
WHOSE GRITTY FICTION
HAS ENTERTAINED
SO FEW, FOR SO LONG,
ISSUED A STATEMENT TO
HIS WASTEBASKET TODAY,
WHILE IGNORING A BILL
FROM HIS EX-WIFE'S LAWYER.
REACHED FOR COMMENT
AT HIS SHITBOX HOME,
THE DEADBEAT GAVE
NO EXPLANATION.
IN OTHER NEWS TODAY,
A FLASHER TERRORIZED
THE POPULACE NEAR
A PIGGLY-WIGGLY.
♪ TAKE THIS HAMMER ♪
♪ GIVE IT TO THE CAPTAIN ♪
♪ TELL HIM I'M GONE ♪
"HIS NAME WAS...
"HIS NAME..."
GODDAMN.
[Rattling noise]
[Crashing]
"HIS NAME WAS MBEMBE,
WHICH MEANS 'SMOOTH TALKER'.
"HE COULD GET ANYONE
TO DO ANYTHING HE WANTED.
"BUT HE DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT HE WANTED.
"THE EVIL SPIRIT THAT HAD
POSSESSED ONE SIDE OF HIS BODY
"HAD BEEN EXORCISED,
AND HAD FLED TO MEXICO.
"BUT WHEN THE SPIRIT LEFT,
"IT HAD TAKEN MBEMBE'S
WILL ALONG WITH IT.
"HIS YOUNG BRIDE,
HOMESICK FOR THE NORTH..."
[Woman] "YOUR MANUSCRIPT
DOES NOT MEET OUR NEEDS..."
[Cow mooing]
BARLOW, BARLOW, I'M TRAPPED.
I'M TRAPPED IN A BOTTLE
BEHIND THE BAR AT CINDY'S.
HELP ME, I BEG YOU.
A CRY FOR HELP.
I MUST NOT TARRY.
♪ MAN, WOULD YOU
LET MY BABE RIDE ♪
♪ LOVE, YOU'RE THE DEVIL,
WELL, YOU WON'T GET ME ♪
♪ MAN, WOULD YOU
LET MY BABE RIDE ♪
♪ LOVE, YOU'RE THE DEVIL,
WELL YOU WON'T GET ME ♪
♪ MAN, WOULD YOU
LET MY BABE RIDE ♪
ASSHOLE!
♪ LOVE, YOU'RE THE DEVIL,
WELL, YOU WON'T GET ME ♪
♪ GONNA LET MY BABE RIDE ♪
♪ LOVE, YOU'RE THE DEVIL,
WELL, YOU WON'T GET ME ♪
[Moaning]
AHH.
[Mrs. Barlow] LEON?
GET AWAY.
GET!
[Sighs]
[Mrs. Barlow] WILL YOU GET AWAY
FROM THIS HOUSE, YOU MONGREL?
LEON?
ARE YOU GOING TO GET THIS
BEAST AWAY FROM ME OR NOT?
LEON?
DAMN IT. LEON?
GET AWAY.
[Mrs. Barlow] GET.
LEON!
ARE YOU GONNA GET THIS
BEAST AWAY FROM ME OR NOT?
I'M NOT COMING IN UNTIL YOU DO.
[Leon] "HIS MOTHER
YELLED, ALMOST MEANING IT."
[Leon] YELLOW DOG!
YOU DON'T WANNA
TANGLE WITH HER. GET!
CAN'T A DECENT HUMAN
BEING GET OUT OF A CAR
WITHOUT BEING ATTACKED
BY WILD ANIMALS?
[Mrs. Barlow] THIS
LITTLE TEA SET.
WHERE'S THE CREAMER?
IT WAS BROKEN.
I DON'T WONDER.
YOU BROKE IT.
LONG AGO...
I?
BEFORE IT EVER CAME
INTO MY CUSTODY.
I?
OH, YES.
A RARE FIT OF SMALL PIQUE.
SO SMALL, SO RARE, INDEED.
LEON,
WHAT DO YOU INTEND TO DO, LOVE?
I TEND TO DO WHAT I DO.
AFTER ALL IT'S COST YOU?
WELL, IT WOULDN'T MAKE A WHOLE
LOT OF SENSE TO QUIT NOW, WOULD IT?
IT IS OF NO SIGNIFICANCE TO YOU
WHAT OCCURS WHEN A DADDY
RUNS OUT ON HIS FAMILY?
I CUT MY TEETH...
HOW WILL YOU LIVE?
ON ITS SIGNIFICANCE.
YOU HAVE NO VOCATION.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
IT'S MY GRANDCHILDREN
I WORRY ABOUT.
HOW WILL YOU MEET
YOUR SUPPORT OBLIGATION?
WHEN WILL YOU SEE THEM?
HAVE YOU SEEN THEM?
I'LL GIVE THEM ALL THE
MAMAW THEY CAN STAND,
BUT IF THEY HAVE NO DADDY...
MOTHER.
I SAT FOR MARILYN, FRIDAY LAST.
HOW WERE THEY?
WHAT DID THEY SAY?
THEY WANTED TO KNOW
WHEN YOU WERE COMING HOME.
[Woman] "DEAR MR. BARLOW,
"'THIS STORY CAME SO CLOSE.
"WE HAD A 2-WEEK
BATTLE OVER IT HERE,
"BUT YOU AND I LOST.
"SO DID OUR READERS,
FEW THOUGH THEY BE.
"I DID WANT TO ASK
ABOUT THE TITLE.
"NO ONE HERE WAS SURE WHAT
"WHITE GIRLS WITH BLACK
ASSES ACTUALLY MEANT.
"THE STORY REALLY
PUT SOME PEOPLE OFF.
"IT'S THE STRONGEST
THING I'VE SEEN IN YEARS.
"I'D NEVER TELL YOU
HOW TO WRITE, BUT
"IF YOU CHANGE THE TITLE
"ANOTHER MAGAZINE MIGHT BITE.
"I'D LOVE TO SEE ANYTHING
ELSE YOU WANNA SEND.
"PLEASE KEEP WRITING, AND DON'T
LET THIS BE DISAPPOINTING TO YOU.
"YOU HAVE GREAT TALENT.
"AND WITH MATERIAL LIKE THIS,
"YOU WILL NEED GREAT STAMINA.
"ALL WARMEST WISHES,
"BETTI DELOREO."
[Knocking at door]
HI, DADDY.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
YOURS FOR THE REST
OF THE WEEKEND.
WHAT?
YOU PAYS YOUR MONEY,
YOU GETS YOUR KIDS.
PAYS MY MONEY?
GOD. NOT A CLUE WHEN YOU FUCK
UP, NOT A CLUE WHEN YOU DON'T.
BILLS PAID.
COURT ORDERS COMPLIED
WITH, LAWYERS PAID IN FULL.
CHILD SUPPORT, 3 MONTHS' WORTH.
100-DOLLAR BILLS IN A MANILA
ENVELOPE, UNDER THE DOOR.
IS ANY OF THIS RINGING
A BELL, LEON? HELLO?
DRUNKEN-DEBT-PAYERS-R-US.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
[Bells ringing]
[Leon whispers] MONROE.
OH, I GOT EXTRA
CLOTHES FOR BOTH OF 'EM
AND I GOT EXTRA UNDERWEAR
AND ALISHA'S MEDICINE.
SHE'S ON A NEW STEROID, SO
SHE NEEDS A LOT OF WATER.
JUST REMEMBER TO
KEEP HER DRINKING.
ALAN, YOU'RE GONNA
HELP WITH ALISHA, TOO.
I LOVE YOU. BYE.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
LEON, DO YOU REMEMBER
HOW TO DO THIS?
IT'S ALL COMING BACK TO ME, NOW.
[Marilyn] THAT'S GOOD.
I PICKED UP 2 EXTRA
SHIFTS AT THE HOSPITAL,
NOT KNOWING OF MY
IMMINENT WINDFALL.
C'MON, HONEY.
WE'RE AT DADDY'S.
C'MON.
I'LL BE THERE IF YOU
NEED ME, ALL RIGHT?
YOU CALL ANYTIME, OR...
GREAT, MY OWN LOST WEEKEND.
OH, ALL THE MISSED
OPPORTUNITIES.
[Leon] ARE YOU SEEING SOMEBODY?
WHAT?
ARE YOU SEEING SOMEBODY?
HUH?
Y'ALL CAN SLEEP IN
YOUR OWN ROOM TONIGHT,
OR YOU CAN SLEEP
IN HERE WITH ME.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
SO ONE DAY, A TRAIN
COME THROUGH THE WOODS.
WILD BOY HISSED
TO ALL THE SNAKES.
TOLD THEM TO LINE
UP ON THE RAILS.
AND THE TRAIN COME
OFF ON NEW SNAKE TRACK.
WHY, THE SNAKES
TOOK THEM ALL THE WAY
THROUGH THE WOODS
TO THE CAVE.
WELL, WILD BOY CALLED OUT
TO HIS NUMBER ONE, MAGIC DOG.
[Barks like a dog]
AND OLD MAGIC DOG
COME RUNNING UP.
WILD BOY SAID, "I'M GOING
TO TELL YOU THE PLAN."
THEY WERE GOING TO TAKE ALL
THE COAL FROM THE COAL CAR,
AND THE BEAR WOULD SQUEEZE
EVERY LUMP WITH A BIG STRONG PAW
UNTIL THEY ALL
TURNED INTO DIAMONDS.
HEY, DAD, ME AND MAGIC DOG
CAN RUN FASTER THAN A TRAIN!
[Leon] STAY BACK
FROM THAT A LITTLE BIT.
COME ON OVER THIS WAY.
♪ [Robert Belfour
singing My Baby's Gone]
♪ MY BABY'S GONE ♪
♪ MY BABY DONE LEFT ME ♪
♪ MY WOMAN IS GONE ♪
♪ I WONDER WHERE SHE'S BEEN ♪
♪ SHE GONE AND LEFT ME ♪
♪ SHE DONE GONE AND LEFT ME ♪
♪ I WONDER WHERE SHE'S BEEN ♪
"STILL LIFE WITH BOXCAR," HUH?
HEY!
HEY.
I DIDN'T HEAR YOU COME UP.
I'VE JUST BEEN WATCHING.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE, LEON.
[Alan] LOOK WHAT I GOT!
HI, HONEY. WHAT DO YOU GOT?
OH, MY GOD, LOOK AT THOSE.
THOSE ARE AS FLAT AS MAMAW'S
PANCAKES. YOU KNOW THEY ARE.
LISTEN, WOULD YOU GET ALISHA'S
BACKPACK AND HER NEBULIZER
AND YOUR BACKPACK
AND PUT THEM IN THE CAR?
GO DO THAT FOR MAMA, ALL RIGHT?
DOES THAT DOG
HAVE ITS SHOTS, LEON?
WAIT A MINUTE.
IT'S A MANGY-LOOKING THING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT'S SUNDAY, P.M.
I'M PICKING UP THE KIDS,
JUST LIKE THE PAPERS SAY.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO
GET A WHOLE WEEKEND.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO GET
A WHOLE WEEK-END, LEON!
IT JUST DIDN'T TURN OUT THAT
WAY. WE GOT A LATE START.
I GOT A BARBECUE
GOING. SHE'S TAKING A NAP.
SHE'S TAKING A NAP.
I GAVE YOU A COUPLE
EXTRA HOURS, ALL RIGHT?
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
LET 'EM STAY? THEY GOT TO EAT.
WELL, I'LL FEED THEM. I WANNA
GET BACK HOME NOW. I'M TIRED.
THEY GOT TO EAT.
LET ME FEED 'EM.
IT'S GONNA RAIN. I
WANNA GET HOME.
PLEASE, DON'T...
WHAT? W-WHY?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "WHY?"
WELL, YOU... IS
SOMEBODY COMING OVER?
WHAT?
[Thunder claps]
ARE YOU SEEING SOMEBODY?
OH, DON'T YOU DO
THIS. DON'T DO...
YES. YES. I AM, I'M
SEEING SOMEBODY.
[Whispers] I'M SEEING
A LOT OF HIM, TOO.
ESPECIALLY OVER AT THE
DRUGSTORE DUMPSTER.
COME ON, ALISHA.
OH, BIG GIRL.
THAT FLASHER.
OH, IS HE A FRIEND OF YOURS?
THAT MAKES SENSE.
DID YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME?
BYE-BYE, BABY.
SO, HOW BIG WAS IT?
WHAT?
HOW BIG WAS THIS FLASHER?
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS?
GO. MOVE AWAY.
COME ON, HONEY, ALAN. ALL
RIGHT, PUT ON YOUR SEAT BELT.
OH.
WOW!
WHOO! WHOO-HOO-HOO!
♪ [Robert Belfour
singing My Baby's Gone]
♪ I WONDER WHERE COULD SHE BE ♪
[Leon] "EVERYTHING HAD UNWOUND,
"AND NOW WOUND BACK AGAIN,
"AS IF THE YEARS
HAD STUMBLED BACK
"IN HORROR FROM
THEIR OWN REFLECTION.
"AS IF ALL THE WORDS
WERE, ONE BY ONE,
"UNSAID, UNTHOUGHT,
THE LOVE UNMADE.
"NO DECAY, THEN NO
ATTACK, THEN SILENCE.
"SO THAT IF IT WERE
POSSIBLE TO DREAM,
"THE DREAM MIGHT BE ALL
THAT WAS POSSIBLE AGAIN,
"THE SCATTERED PIECES
REASSEMBLED INTO ONE.
"EFFECT STRIPPED BACK TO CAUSE
"AND CAUSE STILL UNCONCEIVED.
"DIM STIRRINGS OF
ELECTRONS IN THEIR ORBITS.
"THE GLEAM NOW
DRAINING FROM HIS EYE,
"RESTORED TO
INNOCENCE OR EMPTINESS.
"BLIND HOPE...
"WITH NO TAINT OF THE
FAILURE YET TO COME,
"NO HINT OF THE HIDEOUS
STRANGER WHO LAY INSIDE HIM
"WAITING TO BE BORN."
"DEAR MS. DELOREO,
"THANKS FOR TAKING SO MUCH TIME
"TO EXPLAIN THE
REJECTION OF MY STORY.
"MOST EDITORS DON'T.
"I APPRECIATE YOUR
ADVICE AND QUESTIONS.
"INSTEAD OF ANSWERING THEM,
"I'M GOING TO REORGANIZE MY LIFE
"AND WRITE SOMETHING
BETTER FOR YOU.
"SOMETHING THAT'LL
MAKE YOU STAND UP
"AND PUT ON THE GLOVES.
"BEST WISHES, LEON BARLOW.
"P.S. I KNOW THE ENCLOSED STORY
"IS NOT YOUR
MAGAZINE'S CUP OF TEA,
"BUT IT MIGHT TICKLE YOU."
RUB-A-DUB-DUB.
[Cow mooing]
♪ GONNA FIND ME
SOME WEDDING BELLS ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DIDN'T HAVE TIME ♪
♪ TELL ME BABY
WHERE YOU'VE GONE ♪
♪ HEY! ♪
[Siren blaring]
♪ HEY! HEY! ♪
[Policeman] TAKE
HER IN THE HOUSE.
♪ HEY! ♪
[Door closes]
[Steppenwolf on radio] ♪ ...ALL AROUND,
A LOUSY CANDLE WAS ALL I FOUND ♪
♪ WELL, .YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT ♪
♪ WE CAN FIND ♪
♪ WHY DON'T YOU COME
WITH ME, LITTLE GIRL ♪
♪ ON A MAGIC CARPET RIDE ♪
♪ WELL, YOU DON'T
KNOW WHAT WE... ♪
GOING IN.
♪ [Steppenwolf singing
Magic Carpet Ride]
♪ I LIKE TO DREAM ♪
CORPSMAN. CORPSMAN.
CORPSMAN.
♪ ON A CLOUD OF SOUND
I DRIFT IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ GOES FAR, FLIES NEAR ♪
CORPSMAN.
[Shortwave radio sounds]
DID YOU SEE HIM?
CORPSMAN.
[Screaming]
♪ CLOSE YOUR EYES, GIRL ♪
♪ LOOK INSIDE, GIRL ♪
♪ LET THE SOUND TAKE YOU AWAY ♪
[Ringing]
[Crickets chirping]
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I JUST... CAN I COME IN?
YOU'RE... NO.
HELL, NO.
HELL, NO, AND A
RESTRAINING ORDER, NO.
JUST FOR A MINUTE. I JUST
WANT TO LOOK IN ON THE KIDS.
100 YARDS AWAY,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE...
JUST LET ME COME
IN FOR A MINUTE.
I JUST WANT TO LOOK IN ON THEM.
WELL, NEXT TIME
THEY'RE AT YOUR PLACE,
YOU CAN LOOK IN ON
THEM ALL YOU WANT.
HEY, HEY, HEY! BUDDY!
ALAN, THIS DOESN'T CONCERN
YOU. THERE, YOU SAW HIM.
LET ME JUST COME IN.
WHAT THE HELL?
JUST LET ME GIVE HIM
THIS. IT'S A MAGIC DOG DOLL.
YOU SMELL WEIRD.
I TOOK A BATH. JUST LET ME
GIVE HIM THIS. TELL ALISHA I GAVE...
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS
SHOW UP LIKE THIS?
IT'S SHIT LIKE THIS. ALAN!
IT'S FORCED ENTRY.
I'M GOING TO HAVE YOU
AND THIS DOG ARRESTED.
WILL YOU JUST... JUST
GIVE HIM THE DOG.
♪ [Piano tinkling]
GOOD NIGHT, HONEY.
"HIS NAME WAS HONED, OR
'HORSEFLY WITH ONE WING, '
"BUT THEY CALLED
HIM SMOOTH TALKER.
"HE COULD GET ANYONE
TO DO ANYTHING HE WANTED.
"BUT HE DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT HE WANTED.
"FROM THE RED
CREEKS AT ANTIETAM,
"TO THE GLAZED GREEN CATHEDRALS
"OF THE RUONG RUONG VALLEY,
"THE MEN IN HIS FAMILY
HAD SOLDIERED UP
"AND COME HOME BROKEN,
"TRAILING HOMESICK
YANKEE BRIDES IN THEIR WAKE.
"ONE SHELL-SHOCKED UNCLE
"HAD IMPORTED KUDZU TO THE SOUTH
"AS A PROMISE TO
END SOIL EROSION
"AND MAYBE A FEED CROP TO BOOT.
"BUT IT SWALLOWED THE LAND
"AND THE LIVESTOCK
WOULDN'T TOUCH IT.
"NOW HIS HOUSE HAD
BEEN ENGULFED BY IT,
"HIS FAMILY LOST, ALL OF THEM,
SEARCHING FOR EACH OTHER,
"BLIND AMONG THE VINES.
"'IF I EVER ESCAPE,
' HE THOUGHT,
"'I THINK I'LL GO TO MEXICO
AND JOIN THE CIRCUS.'"
YOU DON'T CALL. YOU DON'T WRITE.
MR. AARON.
YOU BOYS LOOK LIKE
EXTRA-STRONG VAMPIRES.
THAT SUN DON'T QUITE
KILL YOU, BUT IT SURE
MAKES YOU LOOK
LIKE HOMEMADE SHIT.
OH, WELL, HOW YOU
DOING, MR. AARON?
TAKE THE HIGHWAY, SON.
WHEN A LADY CAN'T
GO TO A BEAUTY SHOP
WITHOUT SOME SICK BASTARD
JUMPING OUT FROM BEHIND A DUMPSTER.
HOW BIG A PECKER
WE TALKING ABOUT?
FEW INCHES SHY OF
MEMORABLE, I THINK.
HAVING A LITTLE DICK IS LIKE
HAVING A MEXICAN-MADE VOLKSWAGEN.
YOU CAN DRIVE IT
AROUND THE HOUSE,
BUT YOU DON'T WANT
TO TAKE IT ON THE ROAD.
[Laughing]
OUGHT TO FIND THAT FELLOW
AND SLAP SOME MANNERS INTO HIM.
WELL, THAT'LL HAVE TO WAIT.
ME AND BOBBY GOT
A DATE WITH VELMA.
GOD, LOOK AT HER. SHE'S AMAZING.
[Leon] SHE'S A HELL
OF A GARDENER.
YOU SEE WHAT I'M SEEING HERE?
WELL, YEAH, OF COURSE YOU DO.
SO, UH, ABOUT HER
COMING OUT WITH US, SEE...
THAT'S FINE. THAT'S FINE.
WELL...
I BEEN LOOKING AT HER
A LONG TIME, YOU KNOW?
BUT INSTEAD OF IT WEARING OUT,
IT SEEMS LIKE LATELY
IT'S GETTING STRONGER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M SEEING
HERE. I'M TOO OLD TO BE INFATUATED.
LOOK AT HER.
[Chuckling]
JUST, YOU KNOW, LIKE
OBSERVE US. OK?
JUST TELL ME WHAT YOU SEE
WHEN YOU SEE ME AND HER.
OK?
OK.
HI.
MISS VELMA, HERE'S
LOOKING AT YOU.
AND WHAT A PLEASURE
THAT IS THIS EVENING.
♪ [Marching band plays]
[Velma] CINDY, HONEY,
TAKE ONE OF THEM POLAROIDS.
TAKE ONE OF THEM POLAROIDS WITH... WITH
ME AND MY BABY BABY BROTHER BROTHERS.
THANK YOU.
JIMMY.
[Monroe] THE LIMMAT RIVER RUNS
ALL THE WAY THROUGH TOWN
ALL THE WAY OUT TO LAKE ZURICH.
SEE? AND THERE'S
ALL THESE RIVERBANKS
AND A LOT OF BANKS, TOO.
A LITTLE WORDPLAY FOR YOU THERE.
YOU WANT A RIVER? YOU
TRY THE AENEID, BOOKS 7, 8.
GOD OF THE TIBER
SHOWS UP IN A DREAM...
WE'RE A FEW CLICKS NORTH
OF THE TIBER HERE, BOBBY.
HE SAYS, "AENEAS, YOU
GO DOWN TO THE RIVER,
"YOU'RE GOING TO
SEE A BIG WHITE SOW."
THE WHOLE DREAM TURNS
OUT TO BE A PROPHECY
ABOUT WHITE SWINE ON THE TIBER.
NO, NO. THE LIMMAT. AND
THERE'S THESE 2 CATHEDRALS,
UH, GROSSMUNSTER
AND FRAUMUNSTER.
FUCK IT. YOU KNOW, VIRGIL STOLE
ALL THAT FROM HOMER ANYWAY.
START WITH THE ILIAD.
NOW THERE IS A BOOK YOU CAN
WEAR LIKE BY-GOD HIP WADERS.
THERE'S THESE WINDOWS
PAINTED BY CHAGALL.
I MEAN, YOU CAN'T
EVEN BELIEVE IT.
♪ [Playing jazz music]
[Woman giggling]
[Man laughs]
WHOO...
LOOK, SHE'S GOT...
SHE'S A HELL OF A PROM QUEEN.
LOOK AT HER.
OHHH... I LOVE HER.
[Velma] SAYONARA.
SHE'S A HELL OF A DANCER.
[Leon] JUMP OUTSIDE.
DOWN THE WORMHOLE
PILGRIMAGE OF TIME
AS TIME BENT BACK
AND TURNED ON ITSELF.
COMET GAS FIERY
TRAIL OF EXHAUST.
IT'S WAKE OF DARK ROWS
AND YOUR SEA RIVERS.
ARE YOU LISTENING TO
ME? EARTH OF AMERICANS.
DARK MOTHER!
CROSSED YOUR WIDE SEA
OF AMERICA TO BE BORN.
[Leon] YOU KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE A KID
DRIVING AT NIGHT
WITH YOUR FOLKS?
YOU'RE LYING IN THE
BACK. YOU FEEL SO SAFE.
THIS IS NOT LIKE THAT.
THIS IS NOT LIKE THAT AT ALL.
[Monroe] THEY GOT
MY LADDER, BOBBY.
WHERE'S VELMA?
[Man laughing]
[Monroe] OHH!
[Monroe] SATURDAY!
♪ [Radio music playing]
[Leon] I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
WELL,
WE HAVE HAD A NICE LONG CHAT
ON THE PORCH HERE, HAVEN'T WE?
WE TALKED ABOUT THE
GARDEN CLUB MEETING
I HAD TO CANCEL,
ABOUT THE PHONE CALLS I
HAD TO MAKE TO CANCEL IT.
HOW MANY CALLS DID WE
MAKE ON THIS PHONE, ALAN?
12, MAMAW.
12.
AND AS THE SUN
WENT FROM A FRIENDLY-
MORNING SMILEY FACE OVER THERE
TO A HOT, ANGRY BLAZE UP THERE,
WE DISCUSSED THE SUMMER WEATHER
AND BEING HERE IN IT
WITH NEITHER A HOUSE
KEY NOR A DADDY IN SIGHT.
[Mrs. Barlow] WHAT
ELSE DID WE DISCUSS?
BIKES, MAMAW.
BIKES.
WE SAW A BICYCLE
RACE, RIGHT OUT HERE.
AND WE COUNTED
THEM AS THEY WENT BY.
ONE OF THE GROUPS OF CYCLISTS
WAS SO LARGE, WE LOST COUNT.
AND WE WONDERED, WHAT DO
YOU CALL A GROUP OF CYCLISTS?
A... A CLUSTER?
A HERD?
A GAGGLE.
PELOTON.
A PELOTON OF CYCLISTS.
YOU KNOW A WORD LIKE THAT,
AND YOU DON'T KNOW
THE MEANING OF "MORNING."
I'VE BEEN PRETTY BUSY.
AND I HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING TO DO, GETTING THEM FED,
MAKING AN EMERGENCY
RUN TO THE DRUGSTORE.
EMERGENCY RUN?
NEVER MIND.
HOT, BLAZING SUN HALF THE DAY.
I SAID I WAS SORRY.
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
NOT A WHIFF OF IT.
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
[Marilyn] THE POINT
IS THAT YOUR MOTHER
BROUGHT THE KIDS TO YOUR HOUSE
AND SHE HAD TO
CANCEL HER ENTIRE DAY
WHILE YOU WERE, I DON'T KNOW,
CRAWLING OUT OF SOME
DITCH SOMEWHERE, NO DOUBT?
SO WHY ARE YOU CALLING ME? HMM?
DO YOU KNOW THAT
THIS IS THE FIRST NIGHT
THAT I'VE HAD TO
MYSELF IN 2 WEEKS?
HERE YOU ARE, CHATTING ME UP.
YOU IN THE BATHTUB?
NO.
THAT'S JUST THE SOUND
OF YOU PISSING UP A ROPE.
[Giggles]
WHY DON'T YOU COME OVER?
MARILYN?
[Sobbing]
MONROE.
♪ [Jazz music playing]
THAT'S ME AND MONROE.
I'VE GOT TO MEET MONROE.
MONROE.
[Men laughing]
[Car approaches]
[Car door opens]
[Monroe] WHAT DO YOU THINK?
CAN'T THINK AT ALL WITH YOUR
JACKET TURNED UP SO LOUD.
[Monroe chuckling]
LITTLE PARTY OUT AT
THE RANCH TONIGHT.
UH, WELL, UH, IT'S
NOT REALLY A PARTY.
IT'S MORE LIKE A RECEPTION.
WE WENT OUT TO VEGAS TO
MAKE IT LEGAL ON THE CHEAP.
WELL, SHE DIDN'T WANT
HER OLD MAN PULLING
SOME CRAZY SHIT
DURING THE VOWS, AND
I WAS GOING TO ASK YOU
TO STAND UP WITH ME, BUT...
WHEN YOU'RE IN THE FUNERAL GAME,
LIKE VELMA'S FAMILY, IT'S HARD
FOR HER TO SEE A WEDDING
AS ANYTHING BUT BUSINESS.
BUT NOW THIS PARTY...
[Leon] SORRY,
I CAN'T TAKE ANYTHING
YOU SAY SERIOUSLY
WITH THAT HAT ON.
[Sighs]
SAID VOWS, HUH?
YEAH, YEAH. I DID. NOW LOOK...
NOPE, NOPE, CAN'T LOOK.
I CAN'T EVEN SEE YOU.
YOUR FACE IS SO SUNNY.
SO EBULLIENT.
HEY, I PUT THE "BULL" IN
"EBULLIENT," BROTHER. COME ON.
LITTLE DRINKING, LITTLE DANCING,
LITTLE MARIACHI BAND.
YOU CAN SLEEP IN
THE BARN LIKE YOU LIKE.
I'M BUSY.
LITTLE TECHNOLOGICAL
FIX TO A SPIRITUAL PROBLEM.
WELL, THAT SOUNDS
REAL PROMISING.
WELL, NOTHING TO
IT, JUST A LITTLE...
TINKERING, A LITTLE SOLITUDE,
NAVEL-GAZING.
"MEN MET EACH OTHER
WITH ERECTED LOOK
"THE STEPS WERE
HIGHER THAT THEY TOOK
"FRIENDS TO CONGRATULATE
THEIR FRIENDS
"MADE HASTE"
THAT SHIT NEVER HAPPENED!
BUT THOSE WERE THE DAYS!
INCOMING, BROTHER.
♪ [Music playing on radio]
♪ BROKEN LINES, BROKEN STRINGS ♪
♪ BROKEN THREADS,
BROKEN SPRINGS ♪
♪ BROKEN IDOLS, BROKEN HEADS ♪
♪ PEOPLE SLEEPING
IN BROKEN BEDS ♪
[Leon] NOW, YOUR CHEST FREEZER
CAN GO DOWN IN YOUR BASEMENT.
NOT IN YOUR GARAGE.
IT'S SUB-SUBTERRANEAN.
BUT YOUR... YOUR UPRIGHT
FREEZER GOES IN YOUR KITCHEN
OR TUCKED IN BEHIND YOUR DOOR
IN YOUR DEN OR SOMETHING.
WHY IS THAT?
[Panting]
[Coughs]
OH.
THANK GOD.
IT FELL OUT.
DIDN'T EVEN KNOW.
TRUCK'S ON UP THE ROAD.
WENT TO TURN AROUND.
RAN OUT OF GAS. FUCKING
STUPID! RUN BACK HERE.
MUST HAVE BEEN HALF A MILE.
YOU GONNA WATCH IT FOR ME?
UH... NO.
GIVE ME YOUR KEYS.
I'LL BORROW YOUR CAR.
I'LL GO GET SOME GAS.
THEN I'LL COME BACK HERE.
YOU GOING TO HELP
ME LOAD IT, RIGHT?
NO.
HERE. YOU GO GET SOME GAS.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL GO GET SOME GAS.
YOU WEREN'T GOING TO TAKE
IT, WERE YOU? DON'T TAKE IT.
DON'T TAKE IT, ALL RIGHT?
[Leon] CHEST FREEZERS
SEEM LIKE IT'S SEPULCHRAL.
IT'S SEPULCHRAL.
"SOME SAY
"AND SOME FEW MAY
STILL BELIEVE IS LOST...
"SOME SAY.
"IS LOST A PLUMMETING OF SUNS."
"SHADOWS PAST..."
SO LOVELY AREN'T THEY?
DON'T THEY DRIVE YOU MAD?
THEIR SELF-CONTAINED,
IMPLACABLE GREEN CALM.
YOU WANT TO PICK
ONE. UPROOT WORLDS.
YOU'VE HAD YOUR HAND
OUT NOW FOR 8 YEARS...
[Woman] ...TOWARD
DARKENED POOLS OF EVENING.
YET IF THE BLOOD TIDE RISES,
THE MOON DRAWS BACK
THE SILVER MYSTERIES.
IF HANDS REACH UPWARDS
TOWARDS THE BREAST
OF LIFE DESIRES PAROBALA.
DESIRES PAROBALA.
PARABOLA. PARABOLA.
[Woman] HOPES. EARTHWARD.
PLUNGE, DESCEND...
COMES THE FALL OF NIGHT.
[Man] COMES THE FALL OF NIGHT.
[Man] HEY, MOTHERFUCKER,
GET OUT OF THE ROAD!
[Incoherent reciting]
[Leon] MEN'S TONGUES DROWN
IN THE HONEY OF YOUR NAMES.
CORPSMAN!
[Heartbeat pounds]
[Creaking]
[Car engine starts]
[Trickling]
[Groans]
[Birds singing]
THERE'S POEMS,
AND THERE'S POEMS.
I NEVER READ ANYTHING LIKE IT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I WISH YOU BOTH THE BEST.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S LOOKING AT YOU...
[Both] ASKANCE!
OH!
I REMEMBER THIS LITTLE
EXPERIMENTAL PIECE OF CRAP.
I BET THEY DO, TOO. THEY JUST
DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO HANDLE IT.
WITH RUBBER GLOVES.
"DEEP IN THE DREAM OF ANDROMEDA,
"THE QUEEN OF THE
VOID MOUNTS HER HORSE
"OF FIRE AND DUST, HER
NEBULOUS MAYFLOWER STEED
"FULL CARGO OF LONG-AGO LIGHT."
"FULL CARGO."
"FULL CARGO OF LONG AGO LIGHT!"
YEAH.
"DRINK DEEP, DREAMER, AND
TAKE THE BURNING ONE INSIDE YOU.
"HOLD HIM UNDER, HOLD HIM,
MAKE HIM SHOUT, 'I SURRENDER!'"
[Siren blares]
♪ [Music playing]
YOU BOYS GO ON HOME NOW.
AND MONROE,
DON'T LET BARLOW
GET BEHIND THAT WHEEL.
[Monroe] "THE
ANNUNCIATION OF VIRGINS,
"OF MAIDEN VOYAGES.
"MAPS THAT CURL AT
THEIR EDGES LIKE SPACE"
[Monroe] THE WHOLE
BASEMENT'S A STUDIO.
I TOOK ALL THE FURNITURE
OUT AND IT'S ALL SET UP.
I GOT SOUNDPROOFING
OUT THE ASS DOWN THERE.
IF I HAD YOUR ASS, I'D
SOUNDPROOF IT, TOO.
THE BOARD'S A MONSTER,
TOO. IT'S ALL DIGITAL.
I CAN RECORD MAJOR ARTISTS,
ONCE I FIGURE OUT WHAT I'M DOING.
ANYWAY, I'LL GET A
CD PLAYER IN HERE,
I WON'T HAVE TO FUCK WITH
THESE TAPES. LOOK AT THIS.
HEY. SHIT.
HEY LOOK... LOOK HERE.
IS THAT... THAT'S THAT GUY.
WHAT GUY?
THAT GUY, THE FLASHER.
MR. POINT-AND-SHOOT.
YEAH?
TURN AROUND.
LET'S JUST HAVE A
RUN AT THAT FELLOW.
TURN AROUND. TURN AROUND.
YEAH. OK, PENIS-BOY.
LEGION OF DECENCY
IS ON YOUR ASS.
SICK BASTARD.
YOU KNOW, HE JUST CAN'T GET ANY.
CLEAN HIM UP, A NEW PAIR
OF LEVI'S, A LITTLE EDUCATION,
WHO'S TO SAY HE COULDN'T
QUALIFY FOR A BLOWJOB IN ATLANTA?
JUST NEEDS A WARM
PLACE TO PUT IT.
GIVE ME A BEER, WON'T YOU?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW,
I KIND OF FEEL SORRY FOR HIM.
KIND OF, BUT NOT THAT MUCH.
THAT'S RIGHT. LET'S KNOCK
HIS DICK RIGHT IN THE DIRT.
LITTLE DICK,
LIKE A MEXICAN-MADE VOLKSWAGEN.
[Laughs]
NO, NO, NO. IT'S LIKE AN
INDOCHINESE CUSTOMS AGENT.
YOU WAVE ENOUGH MONEY AROUND,
HE'LL JUST LOAD THE DUFFLE BAG HIMSELF.
LIKE A CLARKSDALE BLUES JOINT.
IT'S TOO DARK TO SEE THE
MUSIC, YOU GOT TO HEAR IT TWICE.
HUH?
LET'S LIGHT HIM UP. THERE WE GO.
PULL AROUND, BOBBY. PULL
AROUND. LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT HIM.
LET'S TAKE A GOOD LOOK AT HIM.
HEY, YOU LITTLE SHIT!
PULL UP! PULL UP!
[Tires squeal]
DID YOU SEE HIS FACE?
DID YOU SEE WHO IT WAS?
NO. I CAN'T TELL.
TURN AROUND. NO, BACK UP.
HE GO DOWN ROBERT FORD
ROAD? DID YOU SEE HIM?
NO, HE'S GONE.
HE'S GONE, BOBBY, YOU LOST HIM.
NO, I DIDN'T LOSE
HIM. WE GOT HIM NOW.
THERE WE GO. ALL RIGHT.
A LITTLE DICK...
A LITTLE DICK'S LIKE A... A FOREIGN
EXCHANGE STUDENT ON CRACK.
IT DON'T MAKE FOR MUCH OF A SLIDE
SHOW WHEN YOU GET BACK HOME.
THERE HE IS NOW!
RIGHT. BACK UP.
BACK UP. BACK UP.
I'M GONNA KNOCK HIS ASS OUT.
THERE HE GOES.
OOH, YOU CAN GET
HIM. YOU CAN GET HIM.
OOH, TURN AROUND.
WE GOT HIM NOW.
HE'S GOING. SEE HIM?
ALL RIGHT.
GOT HIM NOW.
STEP ON IT!
NO, NO, STEP ON IT!
[Car stalls]
WHAT THE HELL?
[Laughs]
WE OUT OF GAS?
WELL, SHIT THE BED.
[Laughs]
I'M GOING TO TAKE ME A TRAVELER.
I'M GONNA GET SOMETHING TO READ,
I'M GONNA WALK OUT
OF HERE, GET SOME GAS.
NO, YOU GOT TO HELP ME.
WE GOT TO PUSH IT
OUT OF THE STREET.
[Monroe] IT WON'T
OPEN LIKE THAT.
YOU CAN'T REACH
OUTSIDE. OPEN THE...
[Laughs]
ALL RIGHT, I'LL JUST GO OUT.
[Monroe] WHERE YOU GOING?
[Truck approaches]
[Tires squeal]
[Shortwave radio] DR. CLAYBURN'S
GONNA HAVE TO REFUEL,
SO HE'LL BE BREAKING
STATION SHORTLY.
I JUST WANT YOU TO CHECK
FOR PROBLEMS, SEE IF HE CAN, UH,
PUT AN ADJUSTMENT ON THIS OR
TELL HIM THAT WE GOT PROGRAM...
[Man, distorted] ♪ CRAZY ♪
♪ I'M CRAZY FOR FEELING ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ I'M CRAZY ♪
♪ CRAZY FOR FEELING ♪
♪ SO BLUE ♪
♪ [Song speeds up]
[Woman] ♪ I KNEW ♪
♪ YOU'D LOVE ME AS
LONG AS YOU WANT ME ♪
I'M PISSING.
♪ AND THEN SOMEDAY ♪
♪ YOU'D LEAVE ME... ♪
WHEN IT GETS TO $28, SELL IT.
♪ WORRY ♪
♪ WHY DO I LET MYSELF WORRY? ♪
♪ WONDERING ♪
♪ WHAT IN THE WORLD DID I DO? ♪
GET UP, FUCKER!
GET UP!
♪ CRAZY ♪
STAY RIGHT HERE.
♪ COULD HOLD YOU ♪
GO OVER THERE.
♪ I'M CRAZY FOR TRYIN' ♪
♪ AND CRAZY FOR CRYIN' ♪
♪ AND I'M CRAZY FOR LOVING YOU ♪
MONROE?
I NEED SOME HELP, HERE.
MONROE!
♪ AND CRAZY FOR CRYIN' ♪
♪ [Song resumes normal speed]
♪ AND I'M CRAZY ♪
♪ FOR LOVIN' ♪
♪ YOU ♪
MY HAT.
YOUR HAT?
I LOST MY HAT.
[Woman] LEON BARLOW?
MY HAT.
IT'S MISS MURPHY.
MISS MURPHY, FROM THE 3RD GRADE?
LEON, LEON! SHH! WE NEED
TO GET YOU HOME. ALL RIGHT?
M-I, A CROOKED LETTER?
CROOKED LETTER?
I... CROOKED LETTER.
CROOKED LETTER. I...
HUMPBACK. HUMPBACK. I...
LOOK, LISTEN TO
ME. MONROE'S ALIVE.
ALL RIGHT? HE'S BREATHING ON HIS
OWN. HE COULD WAKE UP ANY TIME.
MONROE?
LET'S KEEP HIM
BREATHING, BREATHING.
LET'S GO! HURRY UP, DAMN IT!
GET SOME REST. THAT'S
THE BEST YOU CAN DO.
I'M DOING IT!
YOUR EX-MOTHER-IN-LAW'S
ON THE PHONE.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL GET
BACK TO HER. STOP IT.
WH-WHAT? GOD, LEON!
[Woman giggling]
LEON?
SHE'S GOT CF. SHE'S ASTHMATIC.
SHE'S GOT A PORT ON HER RIGHT SIDE.
LEON, MOVE!
SHE DIDN'T EVEN CR... SHE DIDN'T
EVEN CRY WHEN SHE WENT TO SLEEP.
[Marilyn] ALMA, I NEED
YOU! LEON, GET ALAN.
GO GET ALAN!
[Mrs. Barlow] SHE WAS FINE.
[Marilyn] WAS SHE BREATHING
WHEN YOU FOUND HER?
DID SHE DO HER TREATMENT?
[Woman on radio] ONE-BETA-12?
DID YOU GET THE BARLOW GIRL?
ONE-BETA-12, DO YOU COPY?
[Marilyn] WHERE ARE HER SHOES?
[Priest] "SEE THEY RISE
"AND BECOME THE FIRST
FRUITS OF THEM THAT SLEPT.
"FOR WE ARE BORN OF WOMAN
AND LIVE BUT A SHORT TIME.
"WE COME UP LIKE A
FLOWER. WE FLEE AS SHADOW.
"SO GRANT TO THE CHILDREN
A TABERNACLE IN THE SUN.
"AND THE DISCIPLES
CAME UNTO JESUS
"AND SAID, 'WHO
SHALL BE GREATEST?'
"HE SET A CHILD IN THEIR MIDST
"AND SAID 'EXCEPT YE
BECOME AS LITTLE CHILDREN,
"'YE SHALL NOT ENTER
THE KINGDOM OF HEAVEN.
"'SO SUFFER THE LITTLE CHILDREN TO
COME UNTO ME AND FORBID THEM NOT.'
"FOR OF SUCH... FOR
OF SUCH IS THE KINGDOM.
"FOR WE ARE BORN OF WOMAN
"AND LIVE BUT A SHORT TIME.
"WE COME UP LIKE A FLOWER.
"WE FLEE AS SHADOW.
SEE THEY RISE.
"AND ARE BECOME THE FIRST
FRUITS OF THEM THAT SLEPT.
"BLAH, BLAH, SHE SHALL
SUFFER NO MORE. BLAH, BLAH.
"PLATITUDE ABOUT THE MYSTERIOUS
WAYS IN WHICH GOD WORKS.
"PLATITUDE ABOUT FAITH.
"PLATITUDE ABOUT GRIEF.
"CLICHE ABOUT GOD
CALLING HIS CHILDREN HOME.
"CLICHE ABOUT
ANGELS. BLAH, BLAH.
"SHE SHALL SUFFER
NO MORE, BLAH, BLAH.
"IN THE TWINKLING
OF AN EYE, BLAH.
"FOR THE TRUMPET
SHALL SOUND, BLAH, BLAH.
"AND THE DEAD SHALL BE RAISED
INCORRUPTIBLE, BLAH, BLAH.
"BLAH.
"AND WE SHALL BE CHANGED."
[Television playing]
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
MUCH OBLIGED.
GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT.
[Mrs. Barlow] I JUST LOVE THE
SMELL OF FRESH-CUT LEMONS.
I REMEMBER I WAS ON A TRIP
IN A BEAUTIFUL HOTEL
IN PORTUGAL AND...
AND THIS YOUNG MAN
BROUGHT IN MY BREAKFAST.
AND RIGHT THERE,
HE CUT THE LEMON FOR MY TEA,
AND I SHALL NEVER...
[Sighs]
EXCUSE ME.
AUNT SALLY,
MISS HARRISON, MISS GRACE,
AUNT BETSY, I...
Y'ALL OUGHT TO COME OUTSIDE.
PRETTY NICE OUTSIDE.
[Church bell chiming]
[Alan] BIG BLACK CAR
ON A GRAVEL ROAD.
BIG BLACK CAR ON A GRAVEL ROAD.
[Coughs]
OH, HEY.
IT'S NOT RAINING, IS IT?
NO.
WERE YOU SAYING SOMETHING?
NO. HUH?
WHAT WERE YOU SAYING?
STORY.
WHAT? STORY.
WHAT STORY?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT WAS YOUR STORY?
YOU DON'T WANT TO TALK TO ME?
NO.
TELL ME YOUR STORY.
WHAT?
THIS IS BROKE. WHAT?
ALAN.
ALAN!
[Thunder claps]
ALAN.
[Voices whispering]
[Children giggling]
HEY.
[Woman sobbing]
MAMA?
MOTHER?
VELMA AND HER FRIEND ARE HERE.
[Car approaches]
FIRST WOMAN IN SPACE, MY
ASS. I BEEN THERE ALL MY LIFE.
SO SORRY WE DIDN'T
MAKE IT TO THE CEMETERY.
I'M SO, SO SORRY WE'RE LATE.
MONROE?
HE WON'T GET OUT NOW.
MADE ME HAUL HIM ALL OVER,
ALL UPSET ABOUT ALISHA.
HALFWAY HERE, HE CAN'T
REMEMBER WHY HE'S IN THE CAR.
THEN WE PULL UP AND HE
SAID THE PLACE IS HAUNTED.
NOW HE'S ON ABOUT, "GOING TO
GET BACK IN THE DOPE BUSINESS.
"GOING TO SELL THAI STICK
TO RUSSIAN COSMONAUTS."
BE NICE IF WE COULD BE A
LITTLE SUPPORTIVE, YOU KNOW.
DID I TELL YOU HOW SORRY I AM?
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO?
OH!
BLEEDING WOUNDS OF THE MARTYRS.
AW, SWEETIE.
HEY, VEL. THANKS FOR COMING.
HOW'S THE BIG GUY DOING?
WELL, YOU KNOW, HIS BRAINS
ARE ALL MIX-MASTERED ALL TO HELL.
YOU GOT TO HELP HIM, BARLOW!
HE'S GOT NO... WHAT
DO YOU CALL IT?
EQUILIBRIUM.
COME ON NOW.
COME ON.
LET GO.
OH, CHRIST.
STOP IT! JACOB BITES
GABRIEL. STOP IT!
SHOULD WE STOP IT?
NO, NO, NO. WHY?
YEAH.
SEE, THIS IS IT.
THIS IS IT, EXACTLY.
SEE, YOU ALWAYS, ALWAYS THINK THAT
SOMETHING ELSE IS MEANT TO HAPPEN.
TINY LITTLE COFFIN,
TINY LITTLE GRAVE.
GET ALL DRESSED UP.
YOU'D THINK THAT THE TWO OF
THEM COULD JUST SIT TOGETHER AND,
I DON'T KNOW, MURMUR?
BUT INSTEAD, THIS.
WE'VE LIVED FOR 4 YEARS
KNOWING SHE'LL DIE.
BUT WHEN THE DAY COMES,
YOU JUST DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
YOU'D THINK, ON
A DAY LIKE TODAY,
HE COULD JUST STOP
AND TAKE A BREATH.
BUT INSTEAD, THIS.
STOP TELLING US THIS STORY.
STOP...
STOP TELLING US THIS.
STOP
TELLING US THIS!
SORRY.
OK.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL FRUIT SALAD.
COME ON, LET'S GO INSIDE.
WE'LL HELP ALMA RUN THE SHOW.
WE'LL SIT WITH THE
MATRIARCHY AND WHISPER.
WE'LL WHISPER OURSELVES INSANE.
[Aaron] WHAT DO YOU BET,
WHEN IT'S THE END OF THE WORLD,
SOME DAMN FOOL'S GOING TO SAY,
"WELL, IT AIN'T THE END OF THE WORLD."
PEOPLE USED TO KNOW WHAT
TO DO TO GET YOU THROUGH IT.
LITTLE CEREMONIES, YOU KNOW?
LIGHT A CANDLE FOR THE DEAD.
PIN A MEDAL ON YOU FOR BRAVERY.
DUNK YOU IN THE RIVER
TO SAVE YOUR SOUL.
[Leon] I JUST GO THROUGH
THE GODDAMN MOTIONS.
YOU GOT A GOOD HEAD
ON YOUR SHOULDERS.
YOU GOT TO START USING IT.
GOT TO THINK BEFORE
YOU TALK TO YOUR BOY.
YOU GOT TO THINK
BEFORE WE FIND SOME
CROW PICKING WHAT'S LEFT
OF YOU OFF THE PAVEMENT.
OR SHOVELING YOU OFF SOME
COUNTY 2-LANE LIKE YOUR...
LOST, DRUNK DADDY.
FAMILY'S NOT YOUR ENEMY, BOY.
YOUR FAMILY'S NOT THE ENEMY.
[Man] SHE HAD GERANIUMS.
GERANIUMS.
[Horn honks]
GERANIUMS. LITTLE BLACK
NOTEBOOKS CRAMMED FULL OF THEM.
DON'T KNOW HOW MANY. STARTED
COUNTING ONE DAY AT 11:45 P.M.
I GOT UP TO 372, DOORBELL RANG.
I GO TO THE DOOR,
I'M THINKING 372.
372.
BORN WRONG.
DROWNING FROM DAY ONE.
FELLOW FROM CLARK'S, LITTLE
BLACK MUSTACHE, LITTLE SLEAZY EYES...
CRACKED LITTLE HEART.
HE'S LOOKING ALL
AROUND BEHIND ME,
TRYING TO SEE IN THE HOUSE.
[Leon] BORN WRONG.
I STABBED HIM WITH MY PENCIL.
CHILD OF GOD.
[Man] A BAKER'S DOZEN CHRYSANTHEMUMS
FOR MRS. ROSE DALE BOURDEAUX.
WAFTING...
INTO SPACE.
[Man] GERANIUMS.
I STABBED HIM WITH MY PENCIL.
[Man #2] 9 SHOTS
OUGHT TO BE ENOUGH.
KEEP IT IN SINGLE DIGITS.
I'M NO STRANGER TO
UNDERACHIEVEMENT, DADDY.
WHAT'S-HIS-NAME SAYS
YOU'RE A PRETTY GOOD WRITER.
THAT FRIEND OF YOURS. MONROE.
HE HAD A BRAIN INJURY.
NO, BEFORE.
HE SAID THAT WAY BEFORE
YOU DID THAT NUMBER ON HIM.
I'D LIKE TO READ SOME
OF YOUR STUFF SOMETIME.
NOBODY READS MY STUFF.
EXCEPT MONROE.
TAKE THE HIGHWAY, SON.
I'M SORRY.
[Car approaches]
[Siren blares]
BARLOW.
BARLOW? BARLOW? YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU DONE
COME BACK FROM THE DEAD ONCE.
YOU OUGHT NOT PUSH YOUR LUCK.
[Man] I'M SORRY ABOUT
YOUR LITTLE GIRL.
I WAS FISHING UP NORTH.
DIDN'T GET A SINGLE BITE.
HOW'S YOUR MAMA?
SHE'S STEADY.
YES, SHE IS.
WELL, SON, YOU'RE
LOOKING AT 30 DAYS.
IF I WERE YOU, I'D TAKE THE
COMMUNITY SERVICE OPTION.
CUT YOUR TIME IN HALF.
GET OUT OF JAIL DAYTIME.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
WORST PART FOR YOU IS
BEING RIGHT UP THE ROAD
FROM THAT DEVIL'S DEN, AIN'T IT?
IT DOES SEEM BOTH
CRUEL AND UNUSUAL.
WAKE UP, MAURICE!
DON'T YOU SMOKE IN MY KITCHEN.
WELL, LORD HAVE MERCY.
CLEANEST POTS I'VE SEEN IN 135
YEARS OF GOVERNMENT COOKING.
COULD I...
COULD I TROUBLE YOU
TO USE YOUR PHONE?
NO.
I LOST SOMEBODY ONCE, TOO.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE.
ALL THOSE SURPRISE
VISITS IN YOUR MIND.
OOPS, LOOKY THERE.
ME TURNING MY BACK,
NOT KNOWING IF YOU STEP
OUT FOR ONE COLD BEER
AND ONLY ONE ON SUCH A HOT DAY.
WORKING SINCE DAWN. MM!
MM, MM, MM.
♪ [Humming]
[Woman] HEY, THERE! WHERE
YOU BEEN SO LONG, STRANGER?
[Leon] JAIL.
SO WHAT'D YOU DO?
JUMP THE FENCE JUST SO
YOU COULD COME SEE ME?
COMMUNITY SERVICE, UP THE ROAD.
BY THE WAY, YOUR CAR
KEYS WERE TURNED IN HERE.
SOME GUY FOUND THEM
IN THE PARKING LOT.
AND I HAD THEM HERE, BUT, UH,
THIS GIRL SAID SHE
WOULD KEEP THEM FOR YOU.
UH, WHAT'S HER NAME? UM,
YOU KNOW, THE ONE
WITH THE TWIN BROTHERS?
WHAT'S HER NAME? UH...
VELMA! VELMA HAS YOUR KEYS.
HEY!
GODDAMN IT, YOU TWO! CUT IT OUT!
YOUR CAR IS STILL
IN THE PARKING LOT.
CUT IT OUT! QUIT
FIGHTING IN HERE!
YOU KNOW I DON'T
ALLOW FIGHTING IN HERE!
QUIT IT! STOP IT! I MEAN NOW!
♪ I REMEMBER ♪
♪ HOLDING ON TO YOU ♪
♪ ALL THEM LONG AND ♪
♪ LONELY NIGHTS I'VE ♪
♪ PUT YOU THROUGH ♪
♪ SOMEWHERE IN THERE ♪
♪ I'M SURE I MADE ♪
♪ YOU CRY ♪
♪ WELL, I ♪
♪ CAN'T REMEMBER ♪
♪ IF WE SAID GOODBYE ♪
♪ WELL, I RECALL ♪
♪ ALL OF THEM NIGHTS ♪
♪ DOWN IN MEXICO ♪
[Sobbing]
♪ ONE PLACE I MAY NEVER GO ♪
♪ IN MY LIFE AGAIN ♪
[Sobbing]
♪ WAS I ♪
♪ JUST OFF SOMEWHERE ♪
♪ OR JUST TOO HIGH ♪
♪ BUT I ♪
♪ CAN'T REMEMBER ♪
♪ IF WE SAID GOODBYE ♪
[Barlow sobbing]
[Barlow] OH, GOD.
[Sobbing]
[Sniffles]
♪ I ONLY MISS YOU ♪
♪ EVERY NOW AND THEN ♪
♪ LIKE THE SOFT BREEZE ♪
♪ BLOWIN' UP FROM
THE CARIBBEAN ♪
♪ MOST NOVEMBERS ♪
I HEARD YOU WAS
GETTING OUT TODAY.
I NEVER HAD A
CHANCE TO TELL YOU,
I'M SORRY ABOUT
YOUR LITTLE GIRL.
I KNOW WHAT THAT'S LIKE.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
♪ IF WE SAID GOODBYE ♪
♪ BUT I RECALL ♪
♪ ALL OF THEM NIGHTS ♪
♪ DOWN IN MEXICO ♪
♪ THAT'S ONE PLACE
I'LL NEVER GO ♪
♪ IN MY LIFE AGAIN ♪
♪ OH, WAS I ♪
♪ OFF SOMEWHERE ♪
♪ OR MAYBE JUST TOO HIGH ♪
♪ BUT I ♪
♪ CAN'T REMEMBER ♪
♪ IF WE SAID GOODBYE ♪
♪ BUT I ♪
♪ CAN'T REMEMBER ♪
♪ IF WE SAID GOODBYE ♪
♪ GOODBYE ♪
[Birds sing]
[DeLoreo] "BRAVO, LEON BARLOW.
"BACKWARDS WEDDING
KNOCKED US ALL OUT.
"HOW'S IT FEEL NOT
GETTING THE STORY BACK?
"WINTER ISSUE, FRONT AND CENTER.
"NEED A BIO TO PRINT, SOCIAL
SECURITY NUMBER TO PAY.
"SEND THOSE A.S.A.P. BUT YOU
NOW HAVE BIGGER FISH TO FRY.
"THAT NEW YORK FRIEND OF MINE
"WANTS TO SEE THE
REST OF THE BOOK.
"IF IT'S ALL GENUINE BARLOW,
"YOU'RE OUT OF THE SLUSH
PILE. ARE YOU READY?"
AM I READY?
"CHEERS. BETTI D."
♪ [Tom Waits singing
Long Way Home]
♪ WELL, I STUMBLED
IN THE DARKNESS ♪
♪ LOST AND ALONE ♪
♪ THOUGH I SEEN HER GO BEFORE ♪
♪ SHOW THE WAY BACK HOME ♪
♪ IS THERE A LIGHT UP AHEAD? ♪
♪ CAN'T HOLD ON VERY LONG ♪
♪ FORGIVE ME, PRETTY BABY ♪
♪ BUT I ALWAYS TAKE
THE LONG WAY HOME ♪
IT'S SOMETHING, AIN'T IT?
GET IN, I'LL TELL
YOU ALL ABOUT IT.
HE'S REALLY OUT OF IT.
YOU KNOW HOW HARD IT IS TO REPLACE
SOMETHING SO OLD AND BEAT-UP?
YOU WOULD NOT BELIEVE.
A FEW DETAILS ARE OFF, BUT,
IT'S CLOSE ENOUGH TO THE
ORIGINAL TO BE A MINOR MIRACLE.
ISN'T IT, HONEY BOY?
HE WAS SO HYPER
ABOUT GOING FOR A DRIVE.
I HAD TO GIVE HIM AN EXTRA DOSE.
I MIGHT'VE OVERDONE IT.
OH, HEY, MY CAR'S BACK THAT WAY.
SLIDE OVER.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
ME WHERE I TELL YOU?
[Velma] TRY GETTING
US THERE IN ONE PIECE.
[Velma chuckling]
[Pig squeals]
I THOUGHT WE'D TAKE A DRIVE OUT TO
THE BOULEVARD OF BROKEN HUMAN HEADS.
YOU REMEMBER THE FIRST
TIME WE COME OUT HERE?
NO.
I SWEAR, NOTHING'S REAL TO
YOU, EXCEPT WHAT'S IN YOUR HEAD.
YOU GET RAPED IN JAIL?
MET A COUPLE OF NICE GUYS,
IT NEVER WENT ANYWHERE.
[Laughs]
GUESS IT'S NOT
EXACTLY STATE PEN.
BUT YOU KNOW,
YOU EVER NOTICE HOW,
YOU KNOW, THERE HE IS?
YOU EVER HAVE A JOB HE DIDN'T GET
FOR YOU OR WORK RIGHT ALONGSIDE YOU?
EVEN PULPWOOD AND LUMBERJACKING.
BET YOU NEVER KNEW
HOW MUCH HE HATED THAT.
IF YOU'D HAVE JUST LET
HIM GIVE YOU A MILLION OR 2,
NEITHER ONE OF YOU WOULD
HAVE HAD TO WORK SO HARD.
COURSE NOW, HE MIGHT NOT
EVEN REMEMBER HE'S RICH.
YOU KNOW, HE'S MISSING
WHOLE CHUNKS OF HIS LIFE.
I KNOW HE REMEMBERS
THE WAR, 'CAUSE I QUIZ HIM.
BUT, YOU KNOW, HE MIGHT NOT
REMEMBER OWING HIS LIFE TO YOU.
NO. NO.
HE SAVED MY LIFE.
HALF OF ONE, 6 A
DOZEN THE OTHER.
I DON'T THINK HE'S
EVER COMING BACK.
I MEAN...
HE'LL PROBABLY BE
BETTER THAN HE IS NOW,
BUT IF HE WAS COMING
ALL THE WAY BACK,
HE'D BE WAY FARTHER
ALONG BY NOW.
IT'S ONLY PEOPLE WHO KNEW HIM
BEFORE WILL REMEMBER THAT HE...
WASN'T ALWAYS LIKE THIS.
THEN AFTER A WHILE,
WE WON'T REMEMBER EITHER.
IF...
OK, OK, HERE'S THE THING.
I... I CAN'T ASK NOBODY ELSE.
IT'S GOT TO BE YOU.
WHAT I REALLY WANT
IS FOR THE KIND OF MAN
HE WAS TO BE KNOWN.
WILL YOU TELL THE
STORIES? WRITE SOME THINGS,
SO THAT WE DON'T EVER FORGET.
[Crying]
[Leon] FRIENDLY PERSUASION.
WE SAW HALF THE SHOW.
[Velma] IT EVENTUALLY ALL
COMES BACK TO YOU, DOESN'T IT?
♪ WATER'S JUST SOAKING THROUGH ♪
♪ OFF THE BACK OF A TRAIN ♪
♪ THOUGHT WE'RE
HEADED FOR LIGHTENING ♪
♪ HAT FULL OF RAIN ♪
♪ AND I KNOW THAT I SAID ♪
♪ I'D NEVER DO IT AGAIN ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU, PRETTY BABY, BUT I
ALWAYS TAKE THE LONG WAY HOME ♪
[Marilyn] YOU'D BETTER GET
UP HERE BEFORE YOU SINK.
GOD, THIS IS HOW BEAT I AM.
I WENT OUT TO TAKE
THE LAUNDRY IN.
JUST LAID DOWN HERE.
I BEEN WATCHING THE STORM.
DO YOU THINK IT'S OVER?
YOU KNOW, YOUR BOY, HE WOULDN'T
SETTLE FOR A BOOK TONIGHT.
NO, HE WANTED A REAL STORY.
I TOLD HIM, "ALAN, YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO TELL ME ONE. I'M JUST OUT.
"MY BRAIN'S..."
SO HE STARTS RIGHT
IN, "ONCE UPON A TIME..."
AND THE NEXT THING I
KNOW, HE'S SHAKING ME.
HE SAYS, "YOU CAN'T FALL
ASLEEP YET. IT'S NOT OVER."
I OPEN MY EYES.
THAT COWBOY LAMP.
THE SHADE'S RIPPED. I'M
STARING RIGHT AT THE LIGHT BULB.
AND IT BLEW.
USUALLY IT'S WHEN YOU
FLIP THE SWITCH, BUT...
I'D NEVER SEEN ONE
JUST GIVE OUT LIKE THAT.
JUST A TINY LITTLE POP.
I COULD FEEL IT RIGHT
DOWN MY SPINE, LEON.
INTO MY BONES.
IT'S LIKE THAT CARTOON
LIGHT BULB, YOU KNOW?
ABOVE YOUR HEAD,
ONLY THIS ONE WENT OFF.
NO IDEA.
NO IDEA I COULD BE THIS TIRED.
NO IDEA ABOUT ANYTHING.
I JUST SAT THERE, AND HE TOLD
THE REST OF THE STORY IN THE DARK.
SOMETHING ABOUT...
OH, GOD, HE WORKED
IT IN JUST THE WAY YOU...
THE ARMY SHOT OUT
THE SUN WITH A BAZOOKA
OR SOME DAMN THING LIKE THAT.
JUST GOT UP AND CAME OUT HERE.
IT MUST BE LATE.
[Thunder claps]
I'LL LET YOU GO TO BED.
[Marilyn] WHY...
WHY'D YOU COME HERE?
[Sighs]
SOME...
SOMETHING HAPPENED
TO ME, BUT, UH...
I FORGOT WHAT IT WAS.
[Thunder claps]
GOOD NIGHT.
[Tom Waits] ♪ I'LL PUT
FOOD ON THE TABLE ♪
♪ AND A ROOF OVERHEAD ♪
♪ BUT I'D TRADE IT
ALL TOMORROW ♪
♪ FOR THE HIGHWAY INSTEAD ♪
♪ WATCH YOU BACK,
THE ASH IS MADE ♪
♪ AND LOVE'S THE ONLY
THING I'VE EVER KNOWN ♪
♪ ONE THING'S FOR
SURE, PRETTY BABY ♪
♪ I ALWAYS TAKE
THE LONG WAY HOME ♪
[Marilyn] HIS NAME
WAS LEON, OR BARLOW,
OR ANY EPITHET THAT MIGHT APPLY.
LIKE A LOT OF WORDS, THE
NAME DIDN'T MEAN MUCH.
HE COULDN'T GET ANYONE
TO DO ANYTHING HE WANTED.
BUT AT LEAST HE
KNEW WHAT HE WANTED.
HE REMEMBERED WIND,
THE MUSIC IT MADE.
HE THOUGHT IT MUST SOUND
THE SAME IN HIS OWN LUNGS
RUSHING THROUGH THE
DARK CORRIDORS OF THE BODY.
HIS CURSE WAS REMEMBERING.
IT WAS ALSO A BLESSING.
THAT WAS EASY TO FORGET.
HE WAS SURE THAT
WHATEVER IT WAS,
BACK THERE IN THE DISTANCE,
IT COULD CHASE
ANYONE DOWN IN TIME.
NO ONE WOULD BE SPARED
AND FEW SPARED THE GRIEF
OF LOSING THOSE
WHO WOULD GO BEFORE.
THERE WAS NO BLAME, THEN,
TO LAY AT THE
FEET OF THE LIVING.
POINT TO YOURSELF, YOU
GOT TO POINT TO YOURSELF,
SO HE KNOWS WHO
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
MONROE, WHY DO
YOU CALL HIM BOBBY?
WHY DOES HE CALL YOU BOBBY?
I DON'T KNOW, SON.
[Marilyn] THERE WAS
ONLY THE OLD STRUGGLE
TO HOLD ON OR TO LET GO.
THERE WAS ONLY THE
STORY OF THE LOST FAMILY
RUNNING ALONG IN
THE NIGHT STREETS,
RUNNING FOR HOME.
WHATEVER THEY WERE RUNNING FROM,
HE KNEW HE HAD TO
SAVE THEM FROM IT
AND THAT HE WAS THE
ONLY ONE WHO COULD.
[Train chugging]
THEY WERE RUNNING.
RUNNING.
THE WIND WAS BLOWING
AND HE COULD FEEL
THE COLD NIGHT AIR.
HE COULD SEE THE ROAD.
TO FIND OUT WHERE IT LED,
HE HAD ONLY TO GO THERE.
AND HE RAN AS FAST AS HE COULD,
NOT KNOWING HOW IT WOULD END,
KNOWING HE HAD TO KNOW.
♪ [Tom Waits singing
Long Way Home]
♪ MMM ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU, BABY ♪
♪ MORE THAN THE
WHOLE WIDE WORLD ♪
♪ YOU'RE MY WOMAN ♪
♪ YOU KNOW YOU WERE MY PEARL ♪
♪ LET'S GO OUT PAST
THE PARTY LIGHTS ♪
♪ WHERE WE CAN
FINALLY BE ALONE ♪
♪ COME WITH ME ♪
♪ AND WE CAN TAKE
THE LONG WAY HOME ♪
♪ MMM ♪
♪ COME WITH ME, TOGETHER ♪
♪ WE CAN TAKE THE
LONG WAY HOME ♪
♪ MMM ♪
♪ COME WITH ME, TOGETHER ♪
♪ WE CAN TAKE THE
LONG WAY HOME ♪
♪ THE SKY HOLDS ALL OUR WISHES ♪
♪ THE DISH RAN AWAY
WITH THE SPOON ♪
♪ CHIMNEY SMOKE TIES
THE ROOFS TO THE SKY ♪
♪ THERE'S A HOLE OVERHEAD ♪
♪ BUT IT'S ONLY THE MOON ♪
♪ WILL THERE EVER BE ♪
♪ A TREE ♪
♪ GROWN FROM THE SEEDS ♪
♪ OF SONG ♪
♪ LIFE IS A PATH ♪
♪ LIT ONLY BY ♪
♪ THE LIGHT OF THOSE ♪
♪ I'VE LOVED ♪
♪ LIFE'S A PATH ♪
♪ LIT ONLY BY ♪
♪ THE LIGHT OF THOSE ♪
♪ I'VE LOVED ♪