Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[intense music]
[growling]
[shrieking]
[screaming]
[glass shattering]
[intense music]
[ship rumbling]
[suspenseful music]
[creature growling]
[creature shrieking]
[suspenseful music]
Oh, God.
Uh.
What is that?
Oh, God.
[object clattering]
[transmitter beeps]
Otis, Otis?
Do you read? It's Click.
Come in.
Hey, hey, hey, Click. Right here.
What's going on?
Otis, I think this is it.
I think we found what we're looking for.
That's fantastic.
Just keep me updated.
I think it's some sort
of video archive system.
I'm going to try and
get it up and running.
You sound anxious.
Did you run into any trouble down there?
Ooh, now we're talking.
[system beeps and clatters]
[system whirring]
[system clattering]
What is this?
Oh.
[system beeping]
[system clattering]
[alarm blaring]
[static buzzing]
[crickets chirping]
[suspenseful music]
[lighter clicks]
[object whooshing]
Hmm.
[object banging]
[devices beeping]
Yeah, possible hostile
contact in sector 3. Standby.
[suspenseful music]
[device beeps]
[cartridge clacks]
[suspenseful music continues]
Charles, contact confirmed.
[intense music]
[man screaming]
[static buzzing]
Shit.
[suspenseful music]
[door opens]
[gun parts clacking]
[crickets chirping]
[wind whistling]
Hey.
[beeping]
[indistinct chattering]
[Man] Really?
Yeah, we got the bodies out.
[suspenseful music]
[whirring]
[electronic buzzing]
[woman gasps]
[object whacks]
[intense music]
[man breathes heavily]
[bushes rustling]
[creature chirruping]
[transmitter beeps]
[static buzzing]
[suspenseful music]
[creature chirruping]
[gun firing]
[creature groans]
[suspenseful music]
[creature pattering]
[creature shrieks]
[man gasps]
[suspenseful music]
[man groaning]
[creature hissing]
[gun firing]
[man breathes heavily]
[man groaning]
[dramatic orchestral music]
[man groans and coughs]
[creature hisses]
[man gasps]
[flesh squelching]
[body thuds]
[whirring]
[distorted rumbling]
Otis, come in.
I got it up and running.
You're not gonna believe what I found.
[sighs] This is the
discovery of the year.
[suspenseful music]
[electronic buzzing]
[distorted buzzing and whirring]
[electronic pulsing]
[beeping and whirring]
Madam Chell's Red-Light
District Cathouse.
[upbeat hip hop music]
♪ Hey ♪
[dramatic theme music]
It's spring across the Southern Sector,
which means two things:
[electronic whirring]
Transfer students
are boarding drop ships
for the lunar colony education cycle,
and it's time to watch
out for those egg sacs
because the Trioxin 245
spiders are hatching.
Let's send it out to
Aurora Hakiki who has more.
[electronic whirring]
They look like regular
- mark 5 arachnids,
- Mm.
but Trioxin 245 enhanced
spiders are not garden pests.
They're rad, they're
deadly, and they are growing
in record numbers this cycle.
Old Town and Red District
are taking the highest hit,
travel advisories are in effect.
Kay, back to you.
[dramatic theme music]
[dinging]
[whirring]
[suspenseful music]
[pod whirring]
[upbeat hip hop music]
[barrels clattering]
♪ Hey ♪
[laughing]
[pod whirring]
Fucking trash!
[pods whirring]
[thunderous boom]
[suspenseful music]
[system whirring]
389 credits.
[mellow music]
Hi.
If you're with the National
Protection Services,
you have to tell me or it's entrapment.
[chuckles]
[whirring and pulsing]
[beeping]
[mellow music]
[party horn blaring]
Great! Then you need to fuck a hooker!
Yay!
Wow. That's direct.
Then come on down
to Madam Chell's Red-Light
District Cathouse.
So go ahead and set up
an appointment today.
[buzzing and pulsing]
[buzzing]
Madam Chell's Red-light
District Cathouse.
Hi.
I would like to set up polite
intercourse with a girl.
That'll be 500 credits for one hour.
Ooh! What can I get for 389 credits?
We just happen to have
a super saver package discount today
for our less discerning customers.
Ooh, what do I get for that?
Agnosexual encounter, a half and half.
And a pat on the head.
Great.
Come on down to the
Raspy Beef Hotel, room 89.
Don't knock. One hour.
[static buzzing]
[ominous music]
[suspenseful music]
[toilet flushing]
[Woman] Put your thumb on the scanner.
[scanner beeping]
[Computer Voice] Not enough credits.
[door sliding]
I cost 389.
I had 389,
but I had to take the
people mover to get here,
and I bought us both hot dogs.
[ominous music]
[sighs] You agreed to 389.
Well I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Did you want your hotdog?
[hot dog thuds]
How much do you have?
- 250.
- All right.
Give me that.
What do I get for 250?
[dramatic drum roll]
Um, sex.
[intense music]
Oh, yeah. Big daddy.
You feel so good.
[bed squeaking]
You wanna get on top?
Pew, pew, pew, pew!
- [hand whacks]
- Fuck me!
[intense music]
[man breathes heavily]
[woman moaning]
[woman screaming]
[man groaning]
[spider hissing]
[man whimpering]
[flesh squelching]
[woman screaming]
[Flesh squishing]
[woman gasping]
[man groaning]
[flesh squishing]
[spider hissing]
[spider belching]
[intense music]
[Computer Voice] Music off.
[spider chirruping]
[spider cracking and squishing]
Eh.
[sniffs] Ooh, it's hot in there.
Was that okay?
You're doing great.
[chuckling]
Thank you for feeding
all 23,000 of my babies.
[suspenseful music]
Can I go home now?
I haven't seen my family in six months.
So help me, please.
[chuckles] Maybe tomorrow.
I have four more
appointments for me today.
Hey, you're doing a great job.
Who's my little black widow?
I am.
That's right.
[intense music]
Hey, hey, hey.
It's not like you're gonna die today.
Huh?
[chuckles]
[door opens]
Hey, sexy.
I've got some cocaine.
Both edible and old school powder.
Huh, yeah. Some amyl nitrate.
And 500 credits with
your name all over it.
See the ladies, they call me Chad,
but you can call me Rad.
Oh, yeah. Feel me now.
[intense music]
[static buzzing]
I can't tell if these are historical
or fictional narratives.
[sighs] It's hard to say.
Things were a lot different back then.
[suspenseful music]
[static buzzing]
Do you think it's safe?
To forage here, I mean?
It could be territory.
No, the riders never come up here.
They're way too superstitious.
But keep your eyes open.
Do you think it's true?
What they say about the Northlands?
[chuckles] What that
people never return?
Think you can chock that
up more to feral tribes
than any kind of war ghost.
[wind rustling]
[suspenseful music]
It's a graveyard up here.
I can see why Sliv and the
others didn't wanna come.
You came.
I won't forget that.
I couldn't let you go by yourself.
Besides, if there is any
water stored up here,
I couldn't let you get
all the praise for it.
[both chuckling]
[wind whistling]
[objects scraping and clattering]
[soft music]
Tig!
Come see this.
A sea glass.
Can't do much with those.
It took the ancients long enough
to figure that out on their own.
I haven't seen one since I was little.
Hmm.
Don't stare into it too long.
We've got work to do.
See if you can find something useful.
Dried food, water, supplies.
Yeah.
I know the drill.
[wind whistling]
[suspenseful music]
[growling]
[blade clicks]
[shrieking]
[suspenseful music]
[bellowing]
Tig?
[suspenseful music]
Tig!
Tig?
Stop messing around.
[suspenseful music]
[distorted voice]
[distorted whispering]
[creepy breathing]
[shrieking]
[slurping]
[intense music]
[snarling]
[hissing]
[creepy breathing]
[woman yelping]
[intense music]
[clanking]
[poles clattering]
[snarling]
[distorted whispering]
[pole clanks]
What are you?
[woman gasps]
What happened?
What...
What's wrong?
What was that?
What was what?
Who are you?
It's me, Tig.
I don't understand why you're upset.
- Everything's okay.
- What is... [sobbing]
It's okay. It's okay.
Shh, calm down. Calm down.
Calm down. It's okay.
[woman sobbing]
It's okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Everything will be just fine.
[snarls]
[glass cracking]
[intense music]
[woman screaming]
[static buzzing]
I have no idea what
I'm watching right now.
It's really bizarre.
Back then people used
to subject themselves
to horror for entertainment.
Insane.
[suspenseful music]
[static buzzing]
[wind whistling]
[engine starting]
[gasping] Help me!
[coughing]
[gun fires]
[engine rumbling]
[suspenseful music]
[beeping]
[door buzzes and clanks]
[gentle music]
[snoring]
[door opens]
[machinery beeping and whirring]
[Woman] Not all are up yet, I see.
[Max] What do you think?
Let's get started.
[machinery beeping and whirring]
[suspenseful music]
[monitor beeping]
[Nile sighing]
- [static buzzing]
- Nile!
Get up and get in here!
[monitor beeping]
[indistinct chattering]
[Nile] Robin?
Robin!
[Robin] It's not quite the same.
- Is it?
- No.
[Nile] Robin!
[papers fluttering]
[pen clatters]
Where are you going? We need to talk.
[suspenseful music]
We need to commence human trials.
What? Are you serious?
- No.
- We have to.
How? How do you
suppose we do that, Nile?
What? Are you insane?
It's the only way we
can ever know for certain.
No, I won't allow it.
You think I don't know
what's been bothering you.
You've been watching the same
damn video for weeks now.
If you want to know
what's happened to Ben-
- Do not talk about my son. Ever!
If you ever wanna see him
again, we have to do this.
I could never risk it, Nile.
You know that.
[gentle music]
[Nile sighs]
[suspenseful music]
[elevator dings]
[doors clank]
[door creaks]
[waves crashing]
[inhales and exhales deeply]
[gasping]
[coughing and choking]
[breathes heavily]
[suspenseful music]
[Nile wheezing]
[slide clinks]
[Max] Nile?
Can I have the next sample please?
Nile?
[suspenseful music]
- He's infected.
- What?
He's infected! Move!
[intense music]
[powering down]
[clicking]
[hissing]
[wheezing] It's over.
There was a message [wheezing]
from ATCORE. [wheezing]
[suspenseful music]
[static buzzing]
[Woman On Message]
Extinction is eminent.
We are running out of time.
Infection levels have reached far greater
than we could ever have prepared for.
The human race will not last.
Your efforts are now
solely for the continuation
of the few populations
zones left standing.
We regret to inform you
that your loved ones
have not been accounted
for in the remaining zones.
We hope this does not deter your resolve.
Find the solution.
Save us.
The fate of our world and we as a species
is in your hands.
Extinction is eminent.
We are running out of time.
[message clicks]
Ben.
[dramatic music]
[Max Voiceover] We can't give up.
There must be something we can do.
Nile, maybe he was working on something.
Maybe, maybe he found something.
Human trials.
[Max] Look, this infection
will only get stronger.
[Robin] I'm not asking
you to come in with me.
Robin.
The sampling lab.
[machinery whirring and beeping]
[Max] Nile?
[suspenseful music]
[Niles snoring]
[needle stabbing]
[Max screams]
Max!
[intense music]
[Nile wheezing]
[Robin gasps]
[Robin panting]
[Robin breathes heavily]
[suspenseful music]
[beeping]
[Woman On Message] Facility
lockdown override, activating.
[alarm blaring]
[beeping]
[intense music]
[needle stabbing]
[Nile gasping]
[flesh squelching]
[Nile gasps]
[body thuds]
Facility lockdown override in 10 seconds.
Oxygen infection levels
will reach critical
in five,
four,
three,
[Robin gasps]
two,
one.
[clanking]
[whirring]
Air support compromised.
Evacuate the facility.
It wasn't the infection.
It was...
The vaccine.
[waves crashing]
[door creaking]
[soft music]
[foot steps tapping]
[footsteps pattering]
[static buzzing]
I don't know whether
that's cool or disgusting.
We could go through that for years
and never figure it out.
The past is riddled with lies.
[suspenseful music]
[static buzzing]
[birds chirping]
[Clint panting]
There he is!
Let's go in there and get him!
No!
[intense percussive music]
What?
Nothing but death in those woods.
But, no!
We go back to the car.
[Clint breathes heavily]
Looks okay.
It's okay.
[intense music]
Sorry. You startled with me there.
My name is Clint.
You are not supposed to be here.
I'm sorry. I was just passing through.
[intense percussive music]
[suspenseful music]
Excuse me?
I think I saw your,
your brother back there.
Is your mom or dad
here?
You are not supposed to be here.
[pick whacks]
Oh shit!
[intense percussive music]
You are not supposed to be here.
[ax whacks]
[Clint panting]
I've had enough of you sons of bitches.
Two can play at this game.
Help!
[Clint breathes heavily]
Have you seen the children?
[tapping]
What?
I'm so proud of them.
[bottle shatters]
I made them myself.
[electricity zapping]
[liquid bubbling]
There now, look at you.
I have to protect your eyes.
They're still sensitive.
Yeah, that's right. Mama.
Mama, Mama.
Ma..
- Mama.
You know...
You really are not supposed to be here.
[intense percussive music]
No!
[Clint gasping]
They're so precious.
[body thuds]
Such good kids.
[Children] You're not
supposed to be here.
I should really make
you a father sometime.
[Children] You're not
supposed to be here.
[static buzzing]
This isn't...
[sighs] This has to be fiction.
The old ones were crazy.
They blurred the line between reality
and fantasy constantly.
[suspenseful music]
[static buzzing]
[Woman On Computer] System reboot.
[ominous music]
Wait.
[dinging]
[whirring]
Online.
Mainline power will be
restored momentarily.
Welcome to the Semrams Advertising Company
founded in 1888 by William King Greedman.
Semrams has seen itself at the forefront
of ad agencies for generations.
We have remolded the
face of three centuries,
providing the best in
commercial photography,
videography and graphic design.
Semrams brings the top creative minds,
modeling and acting
talents to the battlefront
of the contemporary advertisement wars.
There's a storm coming and you
must fight to stay relevant.
We are glad to back you up.
[ominous music]
[beeping]
Incoming call.
[Mother] Where did you go?
[Aria] Mom, don't
worry about me so much.
You never tell me when you're going out.
Breakfast is getting cold.
What a waste of perfectly good food.
Then stop making it for me every day.
You said the animal
shelter starts at nine?
I haven't started that job yet.
[Mother] But you go it, right?
[Aria] Yes, but I'm
still exploring my options.
Oh, don't explore that much
or you'll end up with
taxpayers expense like me.
They are not interested in
young women with no jobs.
[sighs] I gotta go.
Stop worrying. Okay?
You're all I have to worry about.
Goodbye, Mom.
[static buzzing]
[Woman On Computer] Call ended.
[suspenseful music]
[clicking]
[man clears throat]
[suspenseful music]
System experiencing
technical difficulties.
Due to severe weather conditions,
our main system is currently down.
Backup System Operational.
We apologize for the inconvenience
and guarantee full
system recovery shortly.
Is someone out there?
[static buzzing]
Yes.
Sorry if I'm intruding.
What are you doing? [clears throat]
Um, well, I had a modeling
audition here today,
so, I do this a lot.
I've learned it's best to get out early,
and get ready after.
Especially on days like today
with the weather being bad.
There's a storm coming.
[lightning striking]
It's already hit. Can't you hear it?
[Woman On Computer] System experiencing
technical difficulties.
Due to severe weather conditions,
our main system is currently down.
Backup system, operational.
We apologize for the inconvenience
and guarantee full
system recovery shortly.
[suspenseful music]
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[man clears throat]
[Man] Do you like what you do?
I love my job.
It becomes me.
[Man] You like for
people to stare at you?
I like being admired.
I mean, that is the job right?
Catching people's attention.
My goal is to actually make
it on a billboard someday.
Sounds kind of selfish, I know,
but it excites me to
think that I can inspire,
that people wanna be like me.
Or not.
That's interesting too.
Having haters.
[sighs] At least you know
you're still a somebody.
[Man] What sort of message do you wanna
get across to these people?
You mean when I wanna advertise?
Well anything really.
What to wear or to eat.
Who to date.
When to make love. How to pray.
Done it all, sort of.
I like being positive about
every job that comes my way.
It's just fun to be able to
invoke some sort of emotion.
Even if there's no message, really.
[lightning striking]
Everything's an experience, right?
I don't turn down experiences.
I'm always learning and evolving.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
I'm just waiting for my big break.
And when it comes, it
has to be my best work.
[Man] What if you're not at your best?
What if you don't like what you see?
The audition started already.
So long as they like
it, the people that is.
But you're right, I have
to learn to love myself
before I can let others love me.
And I'm learning to do that
more and more every day.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
That's a good sign.
I've been having my picture taken
and put on display in some way or another.
since I was a baby.
My mom was a photographer.
I've been modeling since birth.
It's my passion, my journey in life.
[lightning striking]
I just want every moment documented.
And if you die?
If that image people have of you
isn't those moments after your death?
Have you seen pictures of dead people?
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
I have to get going.
[footsteps tapping]
[Woman On Computer] System experiencing
technical difficulties.
[water running]
Due to sever weather conditions,
our main system is currently down.
Backup system, operational.
We apologize for the inconvenience
and guarantee full
system recovery shortly.
[man breathing heavily]
[eerie music]
[Man] Beautiful death.
A beautiful death.
[thunder rumbling]
[dramatic vocalizing]
[eerie music]
[Man] The unseen and its
promise of the unknown,
has forever fathered the impulse
to seek for new things in new guises.
This world demands a world of beauty.
These internal things wrought by God
are lovely and unchanging.
A new world is constantly
opening before us.
An ever-accelerating greater progress.
A greater growth, a better world,
a world which always been pulled forward.
Made possible by constant striving
toward new and better horizons.
[eerie music]
[suitcase clattering]
And then we'll come to an ample eye.
Seeing everything and
recording everything.
[indistinct]
[suitcase clattering]
To provide everything human...
[indistinct]
[rain pattering]
Have either of you
heard anything strange?
Strange? How do you mean?
Voices that come from nowhere?
[lightning striking]
You're a funny little girl.
What is your name?
Aria.
Hello, Aria. I'm Selena.
Yes. I feel like I've
known you for so long.
I see you everywhere.
I've worked here hundreds of times.
Since I was 17.
- I've heard somebody-
- And I haven't seen
anything that would lead me to believe
that this place is haunted, Aria.
I didn't say haunted.
I don't believe in that.
Who does?
Nevermind.
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
You know what they used to do here?
Postmortem portraits.
Posed photographs of the dead.
Back then, photography
wasn't widely available.
So people had their loved ones
photo taken when they died.
Probably because they didn't have
any done while they were still alive.
Scary, huh?
But that's how the studio started.
It sends shivers down my spine, Aria.
[rain pattering]
[suitcase rolling]
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[lighting striking]
[distorted voice]
[Man] Photographs bring
news reports to life.
They strengthen the appeal of advertising.
They provide entertainment for millions.
[voice distorted]
[thunder rumbling]
[Selena] We are done, if
you want use the mirror, Aria.
[heels tapping]
I hope you get this job.
I'd like to see you around.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
We'll see. If not, I'll keep trying.
I don't quit.
[Selena] Maybe you
did encounter a ghost.
[heels tapping]
Maybe it's envious of you, Aria.
You are still alive.
[door creaks and closes]
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[suspenseful music]
[distorted voice]
[intense music]
[Man] A beautiful death.
[door clanks]
[dramatic vocalization]
[intense music]
[beeping]
[Selena] Relax, Aria.
[dramatic vocalization]
[Man] 'Cause they don't remember us.
[whirring]
[Mother] Where'd you go?
[Announcer] Young model found dead
in popular commercial building restroom.
The body of one Aria Christiansen
had been found discovered Sunday evening.
Post in fashion model forum.
[static buzzing]
We have no frame of reference
to be able to tell what this is.
Ancient peoples had strange customs.
[suspenseful music]
[static buzzing]
[water running]
No, he's not, he's not the problem.
There just isn't a lot of, you know,
acting jobs going around at the moment.
Uh, no, I, okay. Listen.
I'm not, I'm not gonna
ask my engineer brother
for acting advice, okay?
Oh, oh you, oh, no.
God, listen. It's getting really late.
So I'm just gonna go to bed.
Yeah, I love you too.
Hmm.
[phone beeps]
[suspenseful music]
[Lillian gasping]
[intense music]
[kettle whistling]
[suspenseful music]
[Lillian coughing]
[Lillian gasping]
[intense music]
Help! Somebody!
Help! Hello!
Please help me! Get me out of here!
Hello!
[Lillian screaming]
[footsteps tapping]
[opening scrapes]
No! No, wait, come...
Come back.
[Lillian sobbing]
[Lillian groaning]
Ow!
[suspenseful music]
[camera whirring]
Who's there?
[camera whirring and beeping]
What the fuck do you want?
Huh?
[Lillian sobbing]
[camera whirring]
[shutter clicking]
You're a sick fuck.
[intense music]
[lock clacks]
No.
Stop!
Get off me. Get off!
What do you want from...
Get off!
[Lillian groaning]
Get away from me!
[fist whacks]
[Lillian groaning]
Please! No!
No, no, no, no!
Let go of me! No, no!
No, let me go!
Let me go!
No, no, no, no!
[Lillian spits]
[intense music]
[Lillian sobbing]
No, no, no, no, no!
No!
[opening scraping]
[trash clattering]
[Lillian screaming]
[suspenseful music]
Why?
What do you want from me?
I can hear the camera, you know.
I know you can hear me.
I know you can see me.
So what do you want from me, huh?
What the fuck do you
want, you fucking perv?
[urine splashes]
Huh?
[bucket bangs]
You cannot keep me here forever!
[suspenseful music]
You keep me here forever!
[bucket bangs]
[plastic cracking]
I can do it myself.
[suspenseful music]
[Lillian grunts]
[pounding on door]
[Lillian yelping]
[Lillian sobbing]
[baton whacks]
[machinery beeping]
[ambient music]
[Lillian groaning]
One, two, three.
What do I do? Four.
What do I do? Five.
What do you want from me? Six.
What do you want from me? Seven.
What do you want from me?
[voices distorted]
Nine, 10.
What happened? 12.
13, 14. [sobbing]
Get out of here. 15.
Get me the fuck out of here!
18. [sobbing]
19.
[sobbing] I can't get out! 20.
21, 22, 23, 24, 25.
[doors clanking]
[audience cheering]
It is over!
Lillian Rouge has endured three months
in the viewing room.
[audience cheering]
How do you feel, Lillian?
[suspenseful music]
You have made it through.
You are only minutes away
from finding out whether
you've won $200,000!
[audience cheering]
How does that make you feel?
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, well.
It looks like Lillian's a bit
caught up for words right now.
[audience cheering]
Let's take a look back
at how this all started.
This week on "Snare",
aspiring actress and Bakehouse
Employee, Lillian Rouge,
is thrown in the viewing room
for her shot at $200,000.
I nominated Lillian for "Snare"
because she has a great personality.
And now the world will
get to know her as I do.
Plus that extra $200,000 couldn't hurt.
Lillian won our hearts
from the very beginning
with #bitethatfinger trending worldwide.
[dramatic music]
She made us laugh,
and she made us cry.
[audience cheering]
Voting is closed.
I have the results here
on this piece of paper.
You have voted.
Is Lillian worth it?
Does she win $200,000?
[audience cheering]
The answer is...
Ladies and gentlemen, yes!
Lillian wins!
With an approval rating of 87%,
Lillian has won all our hearts.
She has now been given
a check for $200,000!
Congratulations, Lillian.
May all your dreams come true.
Thank you once again
for watching, "Snared."
[static buzzing]
Okay, Otis. I think I've seen enough.
I'm gonna gather everything I can
and head back to the rendezvous point.
There's no way the university
is gonna believe this.
Copy.
Be sure and wait for me
at the rendezvous point.
[suspenseful music]
[beeping]
Executor Corvid, this
is Agent 23 reporting.
[static buzzing]
Agent 23, deliver your report.
Click has evaded the century
and has activated the Sacred Archive.
Than the original
plan must be activated.
Leave the planet immediately
and return to the cabal.
Additional guardians will be activated.
Are you sure we can't exfiltrate Click?
That seems like a tremendous
waste of resources.
Consider this a test of faith, 23.
You have your orders.
Courted out.
Orders confirmed.
Agent 23, out.
[suspenseful music]
[intense music]
[Man] You know nothing.
Hell is only a word.
Reality is much, much worse.
[intense music]
Where we're going, you
won't need eyes to see.
[intense music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull