FIXES-SYNC
by VaVooM
Action.
Okay, great.
Now maybe above your head?
Yeah, perfect.
Great.
Okay, all right.
Are we done yet?
Can I get back to work now?
Just a couple more.
Maybe one
where you don't look so...
Constipated?
Nauseated?
Try smiling with your eyes.
Yeah, Zach,
smile with your eyes.
Make 'em twinkle.
Okay, that's enough.
I think I'm done.
Come on, Zach, it's Christmas,
it's for charity.
You love helping kids.
All the other guys did it.
You're going to be on the cover.
I don't want to be on the cover.
Let Rey be on the cover.
Really?
How many calendars you think
Rey's going to sell?
That's a good point.
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go!
Come on, move it!
If you want to
go over the pictures,
or grab a coffee sometime
or anything, call me.
Great, thanks.
Seriously?
What's with you and the women?
It's the uniform.
I'm wearing the same one.
Yeah, but you're married.
Come on, man.
They don't know that.
That's true.
Feline dilated cardiomyopathy
and hypertrophic cardiomyopathy
are both common in many species.
Your pussycat patient
may present with...
Miss White?
Can you tell us
some of the symptoms
a cat with cardiomyopathy
might present with?
Miss White?
Feline heart disease.
Can you tell us
some of the symptoms...
a low-pitched cough,
breathing difficulties,
noticeable weight loss or gain,
reduced mobility,
swelling in the abdomen.
Thank you, I...
Heart disease typically causes
the heart to enlarge,
and this enlargement causes
the loss of efficiency...
Very good, miss White.
You may go back to sleep.
You need some balance
in your life.
I mean, you're
clearly exhausted.
All you do is work and study.
You need to relax,
have some fun.
It's Christmas.
Go get a Mani/Pedi,
watch television, go to a movie.
I haven't been
to a movie in years.
Exactly my point.
I just joined this dating site
called "Just Dessert".
You should sign up.
I don't have time to date.
After I graduate,
I'll figure out...
you fill out a questionnaire,
they put a group of potential
soulmates together,
and you meet
at a catered party for dessert.
I mean, even if you don't
make a love connection,
at least you get cake.
Have you met anyone yet?
No, and I've gained,
like, six pounds.
I'm 79 years old,
and I'm going to die fat,
old and alone.
Please, you are not fat,
and you need to stop
counting your age in dog years.
I'll see you Monday.
Yeah.
Bye.
Alright...
Okay.
Increased thirst,
frequent urination, vomiting.
Poor coat appearance,
depression, shock, trauma.
That's it.
That's exactly
how I feel today.
You are going to be
a very good doctor.
Lucy, I'm sorry,
but you may have
feline kidney failure.
Or too many
margaritas last night?
First holiday party of the year.
She's back.
Marilee, could you please
work some of your magic
on Mrs. Smith?
Sure, I'll take care of her.
Mrs. Smith!
Oh, Marilee.
Hello, Bootsey.
Bootsey has been
a little anxious lately.
He wakes up in the night
worried about our visit
to my daughter's house.
My daughter has a very
judgmental cocker spaniel.
Well, the holidays
can be hard on all of us.
You've come to the right place.
Huh, Bootsey?
Maybe a new outfit
would help Bootsey
feel more comfortable, huh?
We are having
a Christmas Special
on canine leisure wear.
Hey!
Hey, come on,
leave the cat alone.
Hey...
Leave the cat alone!
Come on!
Hi.
Come here.
Okay...
You're okay.
You're safer now, all right?
Just run home
before it comes back.
There you go.
Hi.
How did you get in here?
Ambrose?
What kind of name is "Ambrose"?
I work 24-hour shifts,
then I come home and crash.
I don't do commitment.
All right.
There's the door.
I'm serious.
I'm serious, you have to go.
What are you doing?
I live alone.
I don't even own a plant
because they require
too much care.
I said, you have to go.
Really?
One night, but that is it.
I'll feed you, but that's it.
I've had a long day,
so stay in here
and don't bug me.
Fine, you can come in here,
but stay off my chair.
It's the one place
I absolutely insist...
All right, move over.
One night, that's it,
then you're gone.
Mrs. Winnamucker.
Hello, miss White.
You scared me.
Vilma Tuttle thought
she heard a cat this morning.
Have you heard anything?
No.
No, but we're surrounded
by other apartments,
so maybe one of them have...
she distinctly heard it
as though it was coming
from this building.
Well, I'll keep my eyes open.
But I can't imagine anybody
would want to break
the Angel Arms' sacred
no pet policy.
It would mean
immediate eviction.
Of course it would.
Yes.
Hi, Queenie!
How are you?
How was your day?
Wow, that good, huh?
Well,
my day was pretty ordinary.
I fell asleep in school,
I almost got hit
by a fire truck,
and then I went to work and
got slobbered on by a bulldog.
Well...
All in all, a pretty good
start to the holiday.
I'm going to get going.
I left them right here.
I'll check your equipment.
Have you seen my keys?
No, sorry.
Hi, yeah, this is Zachary Stone
calling again.
I left you a message last night.
I found your cat, Ambrose.
And this number
was on his collar.
Nothing in here.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah, thank you.
Hey, what's up?
Well, I found
this cat yesterday,
and he followed me
into my house.
Turns out his owner's
this elderly woman
who died last week,
and she doesn't have any family.
Do you know anyone
who wants a cat?
Not me, I'm a dog guy.
I don't understand cats.
That's probably because
you've never had one.
Hey, check this out,
there was this dog on you tube.
He got separated from his owner
and walked
over a thousand miles,
using only scent to find him.
A thousand miles?
How bad did the guy smell?
All right, maybe I got
the actual distance wrong,
but that's not the point.
The point is, dogs are loyal,
I get that.
Cats,
they're mysterious.
Not once you get to know them.
Actually, cats are
very intuitive.
They feel earthquakes
before they happen,
they smell smoke
long before the fire alarm.
They save lives.
Great.
You want to take him?
Harriet's allergic.
Hey, how does the gorgeous
dental hygienist feel
about cats?
Melinda?
I'm not seeing her anymore.
Yeah, he's dating Blair now.
She's a model.
Of course she is.
You know, it's like
this magical revolving door
of beautiful women.
And seriously, I don't know
what they see in you.
Women like the challenge.
He tells them he's not
interested in a commitment,
and they think they're the one
that's going to change him.
Zach, she's a model.
Come on, would it really be
that hard
waking up next to her
every morning?
She does not want to
get married,
and neither do I.
One of these days,
you're gonna
meet the right girl,
settle down, get married.
It'll never happen.
You don't believe in
happily ever after?
I believe in happy right now.
Ever after never works.
Keep the model,
don't keep the model,
but the cat stays.
No.
Off the bed.
I'm serious.
Sorry, man, I've got to
draw the line somewhere.
No? No good?
Not-not good.
I'm new at this.
What kind of cat do you have?
Well, he's sort of orange-ish
with stripes.
That's a very rare breed.
You should take
extra special care of him.
He's not mine.
It's a temporary thing.
I rescued him from this dog,
and he sort of
attached himself to me, and...
His name is Ambrose.
Cats have very good
intuition about people.
You should take it
as a compliment
he wants to live with you.
Well, he doesn't really have
much of a choice.
His owner died,
so he's stuck with me
until I find him a new home.
I volunteer at the shelter,
and cats rarely make it
out of there, so...
You're a hero.
I mean, obviously,
you're a hero,
with the...
You're a double hero.
The cheap dry food
can be hard on their kidneys,
and if you have a male cat,
they have a tendency
towards prostate problems.
I'd go with this dry food,
and alternate it
with the canned.
Well, I gave him milk,
and he wouldn't drink it.
Yeah, no, milk's
not good for them.
They can't process
the sugars in it.
It gives them horrible diarrhea.
Are you a vet or something?
Almost.
I have another year
of school left.
Right now, I work at
Bosley's pet supply.
I know the family who owns it.
Eggshell, right?
You're painting?
I only ask
because I just finished
my living room.
I painted it pearl.
I couldn't decide
between eggshell, ecru,
or butter cream.
It's stupid, sorry.
No, no, not at all.
I have six shades of white
on my wall,
and I can't decide
which one to use.
Is your house
more traditional or modern?
Definitely more traditional.
I'd go with more...
Creamier, yellowish tones,
those whites, they're warmer.
Like your eyes...
For...
...instance.
Y-You having a party?
No.
Why?
Just...
Right.
That... is going to last me
a really long time.
Good luck with the cat.
Pathetic.
Hey.
You're the guy!
You're the guy
who saved my life!
I'm gonna have to
come around here
and give you a bear hug.
That's...
Yeah, that's not necessary.
This guy,
this guy climbed
through my kitchen window
and saved my life
when my oven exploded.
Just doing my job, ma'am.
Well, I'm glad you're safe.
That's what counts.
Forget it.
I don't have time to date,
and even if I did,
guys like Mr. Brown Eyes
don't date girls
that talk about cat diarrhea.
What was I thinking?
Thank you.
No problem.
Yeah.
Well, I just...
Merry Christmas.
See?
I'm watching T.V.
I do have balance in my life.
...She has a mate,
a companion...
Hey...
You're missing the best part.
These are your
ancestors, Queenie.
Are you looking for a new house?
Christmas is
a great time to buy.
Hey, Jaclyn!
I'm watching you
on T.V.
Take my hand
and I'll walk you through it...
Jackie, just a sec.
I thought you were my landlord.
Hi.
You forgot about
your birthday dinner.
I didn't forget,
you're early, right?
I'm always early.
I have to show a house
on the way to dinner,
and Kyle is double parked,
so let's go.
Wait.
You stay here
and watch the house,
I'll be right back.
I'll grab my jacket.
I wish I could
take you home with me,
but my four dogs
would eat you alive.
Four?
I thought you and Kyle
had three dogs.
We took in another one.
You sound like mom.
I know.
Let's go.
Which ones seem creamier
or yellowish to you?
Yeah, I agree.
None of them are right.
Don't get too comfortable.
I'm still looking for
a new home for you.
Blair,
that's some kind of dress.
I'm glad you like it.
It's Gucci.
I wore it for an editorial
in vogue,
and they let me keep it...
At least they didn't
say anything when I took it.
What was the ad for?
Toothpaste...
I think.
Well, you look amazing in it.
Well, amazing is what
I was going for,
so mission accomplished.
It doesn't look like
you've made much progress.
Well, I haven't had
a lot of time to work on it.
Here, help me pick a color.
They're white.
No, that's the eggshell,
that's ecru,
that one's butter cream...
they're all white.
What's that?
You got a cat?
You didn't tell me
you got a cat.
Well, he kind of got me.
I rescued him from a dog,
and now he's
stuck to me like glue.
I've been looking for
a family to adopt him.
Good.
Just put it on craigslist
or pet finder.
Get rid of it.
I'm kind of surprised
you don't like cats.
I thought you'd be
more of an animal lover
since your father owns
a pet supply store.
A cat's a nuisance.
You have to clean up
after it, feed it.
What if you wanted to
go to Italy for Christmas
on a whim?
You're going to
have to find somebody
to look after it.
It's like having a kid,
only worse,
because it never
grows up and moves away.
He's only here
until I find him
a new home anyway.
That's why I like you so much.
Good times, no strings.
Now, please go get dressed.
I made us reservations
at Mangiamo.
Oh, fancy.
I want you to meet my friends.
I just know you'll love them.
Buonasera!
And happy holidays.
I saw you on the TV
again last night.
Hello, Ellio.
Happy holidays to you, too.
Hi, Ellio.
May I take your...
Puffy coat?
Oh, yeah.
Right this way, please.
For you, we have reserved
a beautiful table.
So, for your birthday gift,
I'm taking you on Sunday
for a day of pampering.
Oh, Sunday?
I can't.
Monday's my anatomy final.
It's the last final
of the semester.
It's worth 60% of my grade.
So I gotta...
so bring your books.
You never do anything
for yourself.
We're going,
end of story.
Now catch us up.
Everything's really good.
Yes, school's great.
Work's great.
I can't believe
I'm going to be
calling you "Dr. White" soon.
Mom and dad would be so proud.
Are you getting out at all?
Have you met someone?
No, I really,
I don't really have time.
After I graduate and...
Marilee still has
this silly rule.
No love life till she graduates
and starts her practice.
It's not a silly rule.
I just want to finish
what I started.
I can't afford
any distractions right now.
No.
Kyle has this friend, Brad.
He's a dentist.
He's really handsome.
You don't have to marry him,
but just go on one date
and see what happens.
Do you remember what happened
the last time you set me up
on a date
with one of Kyle's friends?
That was not our fault.
How were we supposed
to know he was married?
He wasn't wearing a ring.
You ask.
Well, Brad is not married.
He's never even had
a serious girlfriend.
Why?
What's wrong with him?
Nothing.
We could double date.
We just want you to be
as happy as we are.
I'm calling Brad
tomorrow morning.
Actually,
I'm seeing someone.
What?
He's a-he's a firefighter.
Yeah, he saved the life
of this woman
who works in my market.
Her...
Her oven exploded.
It was...
it was just...
Why didn't you tell us?
Because of this.
You guys get so excited.
I didn't...
We just started dating, okay?
I don't even know
if it's going to work out.
It's great news.
We have to meet him.
No!
Yeah.
Not yet. Not yet.
When?
Soon.
He's just, he's...
he's really busy, you know,
with fires and stuff.
Tell us everything,
leave nothing out,
speak slowly.
Ellio, we need more champagne!
Craig's in the stock market
and he made a bundle last year.
I manage a private hedge fund.
Blair tells us you're a fireman.
Must be a lot of fun.
Yeah, it's a blast.
I admire you.
I want you to know that.
Thank you.
Zachary buys
and restores homes, too.
He's in real estate.
How exciting.
A man of hidden talents.
Yeah, I'm not at all
what I seem.
You know what,
Kyle and I are invited to
this big Christmas party
on December 23rd
at the mayor's house.
Yeah, it's a fundraiser
for the children's hospital,
and...
We just happen to have
four tickets.
You two will come with us.
That's more than two weeks away.
I don't even know if we're still
going to be dating.
I mean, it's so early in our...
what's his name?
His name?
Is...
I call him...
"Brown Eyes".
Just a silly little nickname
that we have for each other,
and...
He calls me...
"Marilee".
Hi.
The...
From the grocery store.
Yeah.
How's Ambrose?
You remembered his name?
Of course.
Have you found him a home yet?
No. No, not yet.
Who are you hiding from?
I'm not hiding.
I'm just getting
some fresh air.
Now, what does it say
about the people we're with
if we have to escape them
to catch our breath?
You love them too much?
Or too little.
I'm here with my little sister
and her husband.
I love them a lot, but she's
a little overprotective.
I'm here with a date
and her friends.
You have a girlfriend?
Well, "girlfriend" implies
a possible future.
She's someone I'm dating.
I don't really believe in
the whole happily-ever-after,
fairy-tale ending thing.
Well, I believe in true love.
Are you married?
No. No, I'm focused on
my education right now.
I'll think about dating
after I graduate and get a job.
Well, what if you meet him
before then?
You can't find
what you're not looking for.
That's true.
You know what I just learned?
Mountain lions actually take
a leap of faith in love.
They do?
Yeah.
When a male finds a female
that he's attracted to,
he jumps in front of her,
stopping her in her tracks,
and then he climbs
to the highest peak he can find,
and starts howling,
and professing his love for her.
Yeah. If she joins him
at the top of the mountain,
they'll be together for life.
It's... very romantic.
How do they know who to choose?
Instinct.
What if I don't trust instinct?
What if I need a guarantee?
I don't think love has
any guarantees.
I think you just
have to have faith,
and believe it'll last.
Well, I should probably
get back to my date
and her pretentious friends.
Yeah.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
Bye, Brown Eyes.
I just said that out loud,
didn't I?
You kind of did.
Could I be any more embarrassed?
I saw Brown Eyes today.
Yeah.
We talked for a long time.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not even interested.
Even if I was,
he has a girlfriend,
or rather somebody
that he's dating.
He doesn't believe in love.
No.
It's just you and me.
And that's all I need
for Christmas.
Yeah.
Hey, Blair.
Good morning.
Did I wake you?
No, I slept in.
My shift doesn't start
till this afternoon.
Is that the cat I hear?
You're not letting it
sleep in your bed, are you?
Absolutely not.
Sometimes.
Yes.
Zachary, that is just too much.
You know what, tomorrow,
we're going to take it
to my father's pet supply store
to find someone to adopt it.
It's either that,
or it goes to the shelter.
He's pretty easy
to take care of.
I pretty much just feed him.
What if we want to go
to mount Everest on a whim?
Or go skydiving, or parasailing?
Who are we going to find
to watch it?
You want to do those things?
No.
I don't have a death wish.
I'm just saying,
do we really want to be tied down?
I told my sister
and brother-in-law
that I would bring him
to a holiday Christmas party
on the 23rd
so they could meet him.
That's not a problem.
We have two weeks
to find you a date
who has Brown Eyes.
I'll make you a profile
on "Just Dessert".
No, I could never do that.
Do you want to get
your sister off your back?
Then sign up,
go to a "Just Dessert" gathering,
find a date for your sister's party,
then shut down the profile.
I don't know.
Do you want to die
old, alone, in a housecoat,
surrounded by cats, and dogs,
and shattered dreams?
I'm sorry,
it's what my mother says to me.
Anyway.
Name, Marilee White.
Age...
26.
I'm 29.
Same thing.
Work?
Student and pet supply store employee.
Veterinarian,
loves animals, red wine,
and long walks on the beach.
I like white wine.
What are you looking for
in a man?
A nice guy who likes animals,
and understands
that I just want a date
to a party.
Looking for a professional man
who loves animals,
is handsome,
athletic,
sexy...
And has Brown Eyes.
Don't write that.
What did you just do?
You'll thank me
when you're happily married
to a sexy lawyer,
and you have three children,
and a house full of animals.
What?
You already have
three happy cupcakes.
That means that there are
three guys that want to meet you.
You have to go
to the next party.
It's a holiday mixer this Friday
at a member's house.
I'll text you the address.
Promise me you'll go.
Promise!
Fine.
Morning.
Hey.
Hey, I'm glad to see
you're still around.
Yeah, not for much longer.
I'm taking him to get
adopted tomorrow.
That's a shame.
It is, actually.
I really kind of
like the little guy.
Why don't you
just keep him, then?
Well, Blair
isn't too fond of him.
Blair, huh?
Well, you do
what you want, but me?
I don't trust a woman
who doesn't like cats.
Just put him in
the back of the truck.
No, I would never do that.
He can ride
in the front with us.
But you have to
hold him, please.
Hold him?
Me?
Yeah, make sure he's safe.
He's not really used to
the cat carrier.
I'm beginning to think
you don't want to
get rid of that cat.
He deserves
a better owner than me.
Someone who's around more
and can hang out with him.
My father will find him
a new home.
I'm really glad
we're doing this.
Look what the cat dragged in
for you on your birthday.
The Blair Witch Project.
Oh, man, what is she doing here?
She never comes here.
Maybe she needs to be declawed.
You work here, right?
Yes, Blair,
I've worked here
for three years.
You think my name is Lynn.
I remember.
You have to help me
get rid of this cat.
Find him a home.
What a sweet cat. Hi.
Ambrose?
You know its name?
It says it right here
on his collar.
It belongs to my boyfriend.
We have to
get rid of it right away.
You take it.
Actually, if you do,
I'll have my father give you
all the cat food
and kitty litter
you'll ever need.
- Hi, daddy!
- Hi, sweetie.
Sorry, are you following me?
Actually...
I work here, so...
Technically,
you're following me.
So, how's school?
It... it's finals now, so...
Just really busy studying.
It's all settled.
Lynn is going to take the cat.
I'm sorry, I can't.
My apartment building
doesn't take cats.
Fine, we'll give it
to a shelter.
No!
Did you see that?
It has to go.
It's dangerous.
He was just playing.
He wasn't trying
to hurt you, Blair.
You call that vicious swipe
it took at me "playful"?
It wasn't a vicious swipe,
it was a playful gesture.
Excuse me?
What do you think you are,
a cat whisperer?
Cats are like people.
They can sense
when they're not wanted.
We're leaving.
Daddy!
Well, I guess we're leaving.
Sorry, I didn't
realize she was so...
Psychotic?
Sensitive.
She'll be all right.
Let's go!
Right, well.
Yeah.
Thank you.
By the way, my name is Zachary
in case you continue
to stalk me.
Well, Marilee,
in case you continue
to stalk me.
Come on, bud, let's go.
That woman is such a...
Marilee?
Can you come to the office?
Called into the boss' office?
You think he knows
it's your birthday?
Well, I got a raise last year
on my birthday, so...
Feliz cumpleanos!
What's wrong?
I just...
I just got fired.
What?
Why?
Blair told her father
that I was rude to her.
But she's obnoxious.
Everyone's rude to her.
Well, I think
he's scared of her.
What does Zachary see in her?
Hey, leave a message.
Hi, Sarah.
Sorry, I'm not going to
be able to make it
to the mixer tonight.
I'll see you in class.
I read that petting a cat
lowers your cholesterol.
You know, it's crazy,
but I actually think
that I sleep better
when he's in the house.
No adoption?
No, not yet,
but Blair's still determined
to get rid of him.
You know, you're going
to have to choose
between her and that cat.
Well, I say,
keep the cat
and give Blair my number.
So we are going to
take him on calls with us?
We can't be seen with a cat.
I like having a firehouse cat.
Every firehouse has a dog.
Ambrose makes us unique.
Yeah.
All right, you're the chief.
So...
What are you going to do?
Hi.
I was in here the other day,
and I'm looking for the woman
who was working
with you that day.
Marilee.
Yeah, Marilee, is she here?
No, she no longer works here.
She was fired.
What? Why?
Your girlfriend, Blair,
made a complaint to her father.
I'm sure he didn't
want to fire Marilee,
because she's our best employee,
but his daughter is
a very beautiful,
but horrible, superficial,
nightmare of a human being.
Yeah, I get it.
She's putting herself
through school.
She needed this job.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
Do you have her phone number
or home address?
Why?
You want to burn down her house?
What? No.
I would like to apologize.
Look, I had no idea
that Blair got her fired.
If I had,
I promise you,
I would have stopped her.
Please, I feel awful about this.
White.
Her last name is White,
and that is all
I'm going to tell you.
Any progress?
No.
She's not on Facebook,
or LinkedIn, or anything.
And I can't believe
Blair had her fired.
That is cold.
You know, maybe I don't want her
to have my number after all.
You barely told us
anything about this woman.
What's she like?
Well...
She's wicked smart.
Probably gets straight "a" s.
Yeah, but more importantly...
What does she look like?
What?
What, I'm curious.
She's really pretty.
But she doesn't know it.
That's the best kind of pretty.
Is she nice?
Unbelievably.
She's got a really big heart,
she's sweet,
she loves cats.
Wicked smart, beautiful
but not full of herself,
heart of gold, and sweet.
What are you saying?
Sounds like a special person.
She is...
Guys, could you finish
that equipment inventory?
Right after I beat Mark
for a record
fifth straight game.
How about now?
Now would be good.
Don't be looking
at my cards either.
So, Marilee?
She doesn't want to date
until she finishes school
and starts her career.
Besides,
she's not the kind of girl
I usually go out with anyway.
She believes in
true love and marriage.
You know,
just because your parents
couldn't make it work out,
doesn't mean you can't.
No, thank you.
And yet,
you're here searching
for this very smart, pretty,
nice girl.
Yeah, just to apologize.
Right.
Don't you want to have
a family someday?
Someone you can share
the holidays with?
You and the guys are my family.
Hey, you can't snuggle up
with me and the guys
on a cold night
after a long day's work.
So that's a firm no?
Okay, so here's the thing,
looks like we're going to
be stuck with each other
for a little while.
You can stay here
until I sell the house,
but then you're on your own.
New rules,
we come and go as we please.
You're not responsible for me,
I'm not responsible for you.
We're just a couple of bachelors
living together.
Good talk.
Let's go watch the game.
Hey... what are
you doing here?
I thought you had
a commercial shoot?
It got postponed.
Surprise!
I made dinner.
Where's Ambrose?
I don't know.
I thought he was with you.
No,
and he always greets me
when I come home.
I'm sure
he's around here somewhere.
Ambrose, where are you?
Just forget about the cat.
Go get in the shower,
I'm going to
put dinner on the table.
Ambrose? Ambrose!
I wonder if he got out somehow.
I'm going to go find him.
Why?
No, he'll be fine.
You really don't get it, do you?
What?
Did you really have that woman
who works at your father's store
fired?
Yes, she was horrible.
She talked back to me.
She was a total...
so you had her fired?
You can't do that, Blair.
You can't just have
somebody fired
because you don't like them.
Look...
Everything's okay.
She doesn't matter
and the cat is gone.
Everything's back to normal.
This isn't working.
What?
You and me.
You're kidding me, right?
No.
You're breaking up with me?
That's the way it looks.
I'm a professional model,
and you're breaking up with me?
I wasted my entire night
cooking for you.
I got my hair done.
These are expensive highlights.
I know you didn't cook, Blair.
You left the packages
from Mario's,
they're still in the trash,
right where I can see them.
I also know you didn't cook,
because I just bought
that stove,
and it's not connected yet.
Trust me,
I'm the best thing
that's ever happened to you,
and you're going to regret this.
You're going to call,
and you're going to beg
for me to come back.
Guess what?
I won't.
Ambrose? Ambrose!
Ambrose, where are you, buddy?
Ambrose!
I can't remember the last time
I got a Mani/Pedi.
That's just the beginning.
You need to take time
to pamper yourself.
All you do is volunteer
and work and study.
I should be studying right now.
No, you need to go
with your little sister
to get your hair and makeup done
and then go shopping
for a new dress.
That was our deal.
I don't know,
I've already been gone...
Marilee... stop.
Breathe. Okay?
Enjoy the holiday season.
Better?
Better.
Good.
You deserve this.
Come on.
I deserve this.
Are you almost done in there?
Just about.
This dress is beautiful.
No, you're beautiful,
and Brown Eyes is going to faint
when he sees you.
No, no, I can't afford this.
Not a problem.
I sold three houses this month,
and I want to take
care of you for once.
It's too much.
Marilee, when mom and dad died,
you came home
and put your life on hold
to take care of me.
You have done
so much for me,
and the dress is nothing.
You look like mom.
I do?
Yeah, you really do.
Pinky swear?
I love you.
Why are we stopping here?
You don't think I'm taking
you home looking like this.
You're going to go in there
and make Brown Eyes faint.
No, I...
I'll go in with you.
I want to meet this guy anyway.
No! I have to study
for my anatomy final tomorrow.
I have to go home now.
If you don't go in there
and show him how you look,
I'm going to drag you in.
Wait!
I'll go in. I'll go in.
Good.
He's going to be so surprised.
You have no idea.
I want to...
I need to go in there by myself.
Because...
He's going to want to...
Grab me
and kiss me all over,
and it would be awkward
if you were standing there.
You'll meet him
at the Christmas party.
Okay, fine.
Go. I'll wait
for you here.
No, you just...
You go home.
Yeah.
He-he'll give me a ride.
He's...
Getting off shift right now.
Are you sure?
Yes. Yup.
Have fun.
Thank you for today.
You're welcome.
Bye.
Here I go.
See ya.
Okay...
Ambrose?
Ambrose...
What are you doing out here?
Are you lost?
Oh, babe...
Okay.
Hi...
I'm looking for
the owner of this cat?
He's mine!
Actually,
I think he belongs to
a guy named Zachary.
Zach!
Someone is here to see you.
Okay.
Hey, it's you.
And Ambrose.
I found him wandering outside.
I thought he might be lost.
Hey, buddy...
Yeah.
I've been looking for you guys,
and here you are together.
You were looking for me?
Why?
Yeah.
I wanted to apologize.
I'm so sorry about your job.
It's my fault
that you got fired.
You don't have to...
It's not you,
it was your girlfriend.
She's...
She's not my girlfriend anymore.
That's great.
I mean, in a...
In a sad way.
Well,
you've got Ambrose
back now, so...
Yeah.
You know, actually,
I'm getting off work soon.
Can I give you a ride,
or buy you dinner?
You don't have to do that.
I'm fine. I can...
I can walk home.
Let me buy you dinner.
It's the least I can do.
It's the least he can do.
Well, that's nice of you,
but only if I can take you
to my favorite place.
Yeah.
Should I go home and change?
I know the owner pretty well.
I think I can get you in
dressed like that.
What about Ambrose?
He's used to being here.
He's the firehouse cat.
He's our mascot.
We're determined to be unique.
We like having him around.
Okay.
Okay, we've got two beef tacos,
one burrito,
and one chicken taco.
So, this is your favorite place?
Yes,
it's like a surprise party
in your mouth,
and he's open all night.
If I'm studying late,
I usually end up here.
I'm game.
You're right, that was amazing.
I know, right?
Are you cold?
No, no, I'm fine.
I'll be right back.
When I was in college,
my parents died
in a car accident,
so I went back home
to take care of my little sister
until she graduated
from high school.
When she went off to college,
I went back to get my degree
and started veterinary school.
Why a vet?
My parents were
huge animal lovers.
I guess it rubbed off
on me and my sister.
My mom would take in
every stray she could find.
When I was seven,
I was walking home from school,
and there was this baby bird
in the middle of the road.
He had fallen out of his nest.
So I picked him up,
I took him home,
I nursed him back to health,
I was there
for his first flight.
God, I totally
forgot about that,
but you're right.
That was when I knew
I wanted to be a vet.
How about you?
What made you want to be
a firefighter?
What was your defining moment?
Well, when I was about 14,
our house caught on fire,
and I was trapped
in the bedroom,
terrified,
until this amazing firefighter
crashed through
my bedroom window
and saved my life.
That was the moment you decided
you wanted to be a firefighter?
Well, it was
the moment I decided
I didn't want
to be angry anymore.
My parents fought all the time...
they're divorced now...
and it made me
a pretty angry kid.
That was the moment I decided
I wanted to do something
that would make a difference,
so I started focusing on
helping people,
the way I was helped.
That's powerful.
What were your parents like?
My parents...
Loved each other so much.
When my mom
walked into the room,
my dad would just...
Light up.
They met each other
in high school,
and that was it.
He stopped her in her tracks
and she joined him
on the mountain.
Exactly.
This has been really nice,
but I...
I have an anatomy final
in the morning.
I should probably go.
Yeah.
No problem.
I'll take you home.
Thank you for dinner.
Thank you for
accepting my apology.
Well, good night.
Good night,
and good luck on the final.
Thank you.
That test was so hard.
I'm sure you did fine.
At least it was the last one.
Hi.
How did the test go?
I think I did pretty well.
Great.
Can I take you out to coffee
to celebrate?
That's Brown Eyes?
Okay...
- Hi.
You know what, dinner-
dinner was enough...
you went to dinner with him?
Let him take you for coffee.
Yeah.
Besides, you still have my coat,
and, you know,
I kind of need that back.
Right.
Go.
Have fun.
I love that coffee shop.
I've never been there before.
Yeah, well,
firemen and policemen
always know where
the best coffee is.
Oh, no...
What is it?
She found Queenie.
I knew you were
hiding something.
The plumber came in
to check on the sink,
and guess what he found?
Where is she?
I put her in the back.
Queenie? Sweetie?
Hey, sweetie.
Are you okay?
Were you scared?
This is a clear violation
of Angel Arms' bylaws.
It's a class-two infraction,
which is clearly spelled out...
I assume you gave this tenant
48-hours' notice
before a service person
entered the residence.
Well, I'm not sure if...
what about fire codes?
Are you up to date
on the 456 city fire codes
pertaining to
apartment buildings,
and the mandatory bylaws
stipulated in the state statutes?
I...
I'll be back next week
to make sure
you're in compliance
with each and every
state and city fire code.
I hope I won't have to write you
a 777,
or shut down
your apartment building.
Thank you so much.
I can't thank you enough.
It's not a problem.
Thank you.
Sorry that I couldn't
keep her from evicting you.
But I'll make her life
as miserable as I can
for a while.
Well, I guess I could
stay at my sister's house.
I don't know how Queenie will
survive her dogs, though.
I have an idea.
Oh, yeah?
This house is amazing.
Yeah, it will be
once I get it painted.
Come on.
The house is great.
I love the crown molding
and the hardwood floors.
The staircase is beautiful.
Thank you.
I built it.
Really?
Yeah.
Come on, I'll give you
the two-cent tour.
There's an apartment upstairs
with a separate entrance.
It's not much,
but you're welcome to it
until you find a place.
Thank you.
But I couldn't do that.
I couldn't impose.
No, please, I insist,
I'm the reason you got fired.
Do you allow cats?
Allow them?
We require them.
You can't stay here unless
you have at least one cat.
I'm going to pay rent.
That's not necessary.
But you could, you know,
help out around the house
if you want.
Maybe take care of Ambrose
when I don't take him into work.
I think he likes her.
Yeah, Queenie is usually so shy,
but I think she likes him, too.
I guess it could work,
us living together.
Well, not living together,
but sleeping together...
not sleeping together...
but, you know, under...
Under the-the same roof.
You know what I mean.
Yeah, I do.
I'm going to
stay out of your way.
You won't even know
that I'm here.
I should have a new job
and somewhere to live
by the end of the week.
No hurry.
We should
get your stuff, though.
I have to go to work soon.
You just make yourself at home.
It's perfect.
It's a layer of eggshell
over ecru.
It's really
the only way to get pearl.
It's the exact shade of white
that I wanted
but couldn't find.
How did you do all this?
School's on Christmas break,
and I don't have a job.
It's the least I could do
for you rescuing Queenie and me.
Thank you.
It looks really great.
I'm used to having
so much to do.
I'm not very good at
doing nothing.
Well, I appreciate it.
Look at those two.
They haven't left
each other's side
since they met.
I'm glad
they're getting along so well.
There's chicken
and potatoes on the stove
if you're hungry.
It smells great.
Where did you get it from?
I cooked.
I hope you don't mind,
I connected the stove.
You...
Really?
Yeah.
That's...
Well, I'll see you later.
It was pretty quiet
at the station,
so I'm not tired...
If you wanted to stay
and eat with me.
Us.
Thanks, I already ate, but...
Okay.
Bye.
Don't look at me like that.
It's not my fault they left.
I asked them both to stay.
Oh, sure, blame me.
Of course, we shouldn't have
stayed for dinner.
He was only offering to be nice.
He probably has a girl
coming over later.
Yeah.
What are you up to there?
Curbside value.
When you're trying
to sell a house,
Christmas spirit
can go a long way.
Well, thank you.
Yeah.
My sister's in real estate.
She says the more homey
you can make a house feel,
the better.
Have a good day.
You too.
Yeah.
I actually have an appointment
to look at some tile.
You wouldn't want to go,
would you?
Yeah. Yeah,
I guess I could.
All right.
There's this other thing
I have to do first.
It's sort of important.
What's that?
I have to give a speech
to a group of
fascinating people.
You might like it.
Should I dress up?
I think I can get you in
dressed like that.
Did you guys know
that the leading cause
of Christmas tree fires
is from dry trees?
So remember,
get your parents
to give your tree a drink
every night
to keep it from drying out.
All right?
You guys got that?
Got it!
Alright.
Who in their right mind
barbecues a turkey
in the fireplace?
The holidays make
people do crazy things.
Yeah, I was saying
the same thing to Marilee
after my talk at the school.
Wait, what,
you took her with you?
She's living with him now.
He's falling in love.
That's not true.
Sorry.
He's falling in love,
but doesn't know it yet.
Tell me that's not true, Zach.
You're my idol.
Playing the field,
no commitment,
no responsibility.
Don't worry, nothing's changed.
I'm not in love
and I'm still
never getting married.
Really?
Can you say no
to these three things?
You live with her?
Yes.
You spend all your
free time with her? Yes.
You think about her
when you're not with her?
No! No.
I don't live with her.
She's only staying with me
till she finds her a new place,
and I only spend time with her
because she's there.
You are five minutes
from marrying this girl.
Okay, so wait, wait, wait,
so, what are you saying,
he's human after all.
Come on, Zach,
say it ain't so.
This girl is a temporary
roommate, nothing else.
Right.
Hey, why don't we
hit the stores tomorrow,
and we don't stop
until we've found
all our Christmas presents?
Sure.
It'll be way more fun
if we do it together,
and then we can get
a Christmas tree.
Do you believe in
love at first sight?
What?
Look at those two.
They make it look easy.
My mother used to say
falling in love
with the right person
is easy.
I've never felt that.
Yeah, me neither,
but it doesn't mean
it's not true.
I haven't had
a Christmas tree in a while.
Really, why?
Well, I buy houses,
I fix them up and I sell them.
I never usually
stay in one long enough
to care about the holidays.
I can't imagine
Christmas without one.
It's my favorite part about it.
So how do you choose which one?
Well, that is pretty scientific.
Okay.
First, you've got to check
to make sure it's fresh.
Then you've got to inhale deeply
to see if the scent
is Christmassy.
That's not a word.
Yes, it is.
"Christmassy"
is definitely a word.
It's an adjective.
It means to be filled
with Christmas spirit.
Okay, I see.
Then you're going to
give it the lean test.
You're going to look
straight on at your tree
to make sure that it's even,
then you've got to
lean to the right...
Then you've got to
lean to the left...
And then back straight,
and if it's all good,
you've found your one.
That is very scientific.
Yes.
There it is.
There's the one.
The one?
There's only one?
How do you know?
And what if you're wrong?
What if you commit to it
and realize it's not the one,
then you...
Yeah, that's a good tree.
When I was a little girl,
there was always
one Christmas present
under the tree
that was unaccounted for.
My parents said
they didn't buy it,
so that's how
my sister and I knew
it was from Santa.
It was always
my favorite present.
What are your favorite
Christmas traditions?
I usually end up
working Christmas Eve
and Christmas Day.
The guys with families
really want the time off,
so I end up being the guy
who holds down the fort.
That must be hard.
It's no big deal.
What do you do for Christmas?
This year, on Christmas,
I'm volunteering
at a big pet-rescue adoption
the shelter is putting on
in the park.
Then I'll go
to my sister's for dinner.
You know, I really
want to thank you again
for all the work you did
around the house.
I may be able to sell it
sooner than I thought.
That's great.
You didn't just fix up
another house this time.
You built a real home
for a real family.
Nothing's happening.
We're just roommates.
But you're both single
and you like each other.
It's not like that.
He's not even looking
for a serious relationship.
He dates models,
and I am...
I don't have time to date
because I'm busy.
But you live together
and you spend all
of your free time together.
It's not like that.
That's crazy.
I mean, you're perfect together.
You enjoy each other's company,
you get along great,
and your cats are best friends.
I mean, how many more clues
do you need?
I'm not going down that road.
Okay, I'm not going to
fall for somebody
who's clearly not interested
in a serious relationship.
You can't decide
not to fall in love
with someone.
It just happens.
Do you want to know
how he feels about you?
You know, test the waters?
Use this.
What is that?
Mistletoe.
That's not mistletoe.
It's a metaphor.
Go get some mistletoe,
put it in the house.
If he stands underneath it,
gives you a kiss on the cheek,
then he just
wants to be friends.
But if he kisses you
on the lips,
then he really likes you.
That...
That is the most ridiculous
thing I have ever heard.
I would never do that,
not in a million years.
It's nothing.
I'm just decorating.
Don't judge me.
Hey!
Welcome home.
- Hey.
How was your day?
Good. Great. Great...
How-how was yours?
Great.
Good.
Well...
I'll see you later.
You're leaving?
Yeah.
Why?
I just...
I just thought
maybe you could help me...
Grout the kitchen sink.
Sure.
Yeah, I could do that.
Get it down, get it down.
Sorry.
I didn't have a choice.
What?
Mistletoe.
Yeah.
No...
This cannot be happening.
This is...
This is not happening,
not to me.
Calm down.
It's not such a bad thing.
Answer me this.
There's a fourth step
before you fall off the cliff.
I thought you said
there were only three.
It varies.
Has she asked you
to meet her family yet?
No. Not yet.
Well, there's that, then.
Yeah,
but have you kissed her?
No.
Yes.
But it was only
because of mistletoe, okay?
I didn't have a choice.
He's toast.
You didn't come home
till really late last night.
Was everything okay at work?
Yeah, I do that sometimes,
just kind of go with the flow,
blow wherever the wind takes me.
So I guess things
are permanent now.
You have a family.
What?
Wait a minute, what do you mean?
You and Ambrose.
You're not looking for
a home for him anymore.
He's your family.
Yeah.
I guess so.
Are you okay?
Is something wrong?
No.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm good.
There's this thing
I have to do tonight.
Yeah? What's that?
It's nothing, really.
It's just a party my sister
and her husband invited me to.
I can bring someone if I want.
You want me to meet your family?
I just thought it would be
something fun thing to do.
You'd really like my sister
and brother-in-law.
They're great.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
Yeah, I mean, of course.
I mean, it's...
It's totally last minute
and everything.
No, it's just that
I have this work thing
that I have to do.
I would like to,
but I just can't.
I thought you were off tonight.
I was, but it got changed.
So...
Man, it's later than I thought.
I actually have to get to work.
I'll see you when I get back,
if you're here,
otherwise I'll see you
when I see you.
Okay.
Are you sure everything's okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Bye.
Hi!
Hi.
You made it.
Hi. How are you?
You look great.
Yeah, thanks.
So, where is he?
I'm sorry, he couldn't make it.
He had a work thing.
That's too bad.
I'm sorry.
They're clients.
Will you excuse us one second?
Yeah, yeah.
You sure?
Okay.
I'll just...
I'm sorry.
- Hey.
I was just writing you a note.
I thought I'd be gone
before you got home.
Gone?
How was work?
It was fine.
Where are you going?
I finally got a job
and found a place
that takes cats.
Thank you so much for letting
Queenie and me stay here.
It was really kind of you.
Yeah. Y-You don't have to go.
You can stay.
I really appreciate everything.
I hope you have
a wonderful Christmas.
But what about Ambrose?
He's going to miss you guys.
He is?
Yeah.
Yeah, he has a...
He has a real connection
with Queenie.
Well, maybe I can
bring her by sometime.
That would be great.
You should definitely do that.
I'll call you,
set something up
in the new year.
In the new year?
Hey, buddy.
Hey...
Why are you so sad?
This is what we wanted, right?
Yeah, maybe not.
She just moved out,
found a new place to live.
It's probably for the best.
I don't want to lead her on.
No, you wouldn't
want to do that.
I mean, it's not like
I was in love with her
I liked her.
I mean, who wouldn't?
She's wonderful.
Zachary, what are you
so afraid of?
Nothing.
Harriet and I have been
married for 26 years,
and I don't regret
one day of it.
She and the kids
give my life meaning.
I know,
and that's a great life for you.
It's just not for me.
Because you're different?
Exactly.
What about Ambrose?
Do you care about him,
or have you just gotten used to
him being around?
That's different.
He's a great cat,
and he needs me.
But you don't need anyone?
No.
Remember when you were a kid,
and I crashed through
your bedroom window that night
and saved you from the fire?
Yes.
You decided that day
to become a firefighter,
right?
That was years ago,
you still know it was
the right decision.
That was a defining moment.
This, right here, right now,
this is another defining moment.
If you care about that girl,
you need to go find her
and tell her how you feel.
That's great, but I just...
I don't know
where to find her, Sam.
Ambrose...
Where... is Marilee?
He's not Lassie.
He's not going to
lead you to her.
It's Christmas Eve, though,
a time for miracles.
Maybe...
Maybe she'll walk right through
that door right now
and tell you she loves you.
It was worth a shot.
Thanks for coming down
and hanging out with me.
Hey, no problem.
Merry Christmas, Zachary.
Merry Christmas, Sam.
He told me he didn't want
a serious relationship.
Yes, he did.
And I told him
I didn't want to date
until after I graduate.
Yes, you did.
And then he told me
he was going to work,
but he wasn't going to work,
he was-he was on a date
with a...
With a beautiful woman.
He lied.
Yes, he did.
But he didn't really lie.
I'm not even dating him.
He doesn't owe me anything.
I...
But we've been over all that.
He told me...
What's with the kiss?
See, that was my fault.
The mistletoe-kiss test?
Clearly flawed.
Yeah.
Yeah...
Will you please answer it
this time?
No. No.
No.
He's clearly interested
in someone else.
I'll call him in a few weeks,
you know, when I'm...
Over him.
You're going to get over him?
Yeah... yeah.
Okay.
Hi, Marilee,
it's Zachary calling again.
I just wanted to say
Merry Christmas,
and, I hope you're having
a great Christmas Eve.
Just wanted to call
and say that Ambrose and I
miss you and Queenie,
and...
Give us a call.
Merry Christmas.
Santa!
Merry Christmas!
Well, we blew it, Ambrose.
We let them get away.
Okay, I blew it.
This is
the worst Christmas ever.
What do you want me to do?
If I knew where she was,
I would go get her.
You're a genius, Ambrose.
And this little guy
is very good with kids.
What are you doing here?
Ambrose.
He reminded me that you
volunteer here for Christmas.
He did?
I don't understand
why you're here.
I thought you'd be
with your new girlfriend?
What new girlfriend?
The one I saw you with
at the mayor's Christmas party.
What, you were at that party?
Yeah, that's the party
I invited you to,
but you had to work.
And then you were there
with the woman in the red dress.
I was there to promote
the firefighters' calendar.
It's something we do
every Christmas
to raise money
for the children's hospital,
and that woman
was the mayor's wife.
Marilee White,
you are the smartest
and most beautiful woman
I've ever met,
and I love that you know
the right shade of white,
I love that you know
how to install a stove
and cook dinner,
that you love animals,
and I love that you know
how to buy a Christmas tree,
and I love
that you believe in love
and made me believe.
I know you want to finish school
and start your practice
before you find love,
but sometimes, it finds you
when you weren't even looking.
I want to jump in front of you
and stop you in your tracks.
Mountain lions.
I'm climbing
to the highest peak I can find,
and if you join me,
I know we will be
together forever.
I love you.
FIXES-SYNC
by VaVooM