(eerie music)
(hiss)
(melodious, haunting music)
- How's the second floor?
- Everyone's asleep.
Just another quiet night.
(distant shriek)
(rasping)
What the hell?
- I'll check outside.
- I'll check the second floor.
(water drips)
(bestial moan)
(low groan)
(low rumble)
(discordant music)
- Who is that?
(low rumble)
(dramatic music)
(choking)
(growling and snorting)
(squishing and tearing)
(cackle)
(bestial moan)
(shriek)
(ripping and growling)
- What the hell is that?
(roar)
(growl)
(scream)
(crunch)
(high-pitched keening)
(distant screams and growls)
(ominous music)
- [Gruff Voice] From hell
it came, born from darkness
by the Old Ones,
before the time of man.
It is a traveler
between the realms
of this world and the next,
used to protect the secrets
of the Five that are One,
the Lords of Darkness and Evil.
The creature was first
summoned by alchemists
searching for these
arcane secrets.
They were unaware of the toll
that they would have to pay.
Those who call the beast
must make an offering to it,
five lives to
appease its masters.
Only then will it return
to the shadowy world
from which it came.
The abomination can be
controlled by the one
who summoned it,
only if he can bestow
the mark of the beast
to the five chosen.
(primal shriek)
For them, there is no salvation,
for he who hears the
creature's bloodcurdling shriek
is doomed.
(primal shriek)
- [Zak] So, do you have a major?
I mean, I know you can't
pick one officially yet,
but do you have one?
- [Clark] Yeah.
- [Zak] It's not something
pointless like media studies
or education, is it?
- [Clark] No it's, it's math.
- [Zak] You're a math major?
- Yeah, and I've never even
owned a pocket protector.
- I don't believe all those
cliches about math majors.
- Yes you do. (laughs)
- Okay, I do, but I'm
working really hard not to.
- Oh.
- No glasses, huh?
- No, better than 20/20 vision.
Look...
- Zak.
- Zak, I appreciate you trying
to be roommates or whatever--
- Oh, it's my pleasure.
I was in the same bind
when I was a freshman.
- What I really
need to know though
is what it's gonna cost,
because money-wise--
- It's free.
- It's free?
- And then again, it isn't.
It's great housing for free,
but you can never
tell anybody about it,
you can never give
anyone your address,
you can never bring
anybody by there,
all your mail goes
to a P.O. box,
no calls except
through a cell phone.
Now those are the absolute
rules of the house.
- Okay, I get it.
You're squatting.
- Some might call it that.
- Well, what is it, and
old house or a building?
What?
It's a hospital?
- It's been empty for
something like 50 years.
The county owns it.
It beats sleeping in the park.
We took off their key and
padlock and put on our own.
You have to keep it
locked at all times.
We don't want anyone coming
back and finding the gate open.
Here, I made you a copy today.
Your key to the merry kingdom.
(Clark laughs)
Come on.
Hey look, everybody's here.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Okay, Clark, this is David.
He started it all.
He was here first.
- David.
- Clark, huh?
- Yeah, it was my
mother's family name.
It's a Protestant thing.
(Elaine chuckles)
- David's in pre-law.
Mike over here is in
mechanical engineering,
so whatever water and power
we have, he's the man.
- I'm not gay.
- I'm sorry?
- Just 'cause I have short
hair and a great body,
I don't want you
to think I'm gay.
- Okay.
- I mean, I've slept
with 17 different women,
and not one of 'em was a man.
- Fine.
- I've got a girlfriend,
two girlfriends.
I'm obsessive compulsive,
but I'm not gay.
- This is Tanya.
- Comrade.
- I beg your pardon?
- Tanya's not her real name.
What is it, Tammy or something?
She's into this whole
anachronistic Red Army thing.
- What David doesn't realize
is when the revolution comes,
the lawyers are gonna be
first up against the wall.
- I'm telling you,
you need a beret.
It'll make the whole
image complete.
- Keep laughing.
Are you taking any
poli sci courses?
- No, not really.
- Um, this is Elaine.
- Hi.
- [Zak] She's a bit quiet.
She's in pre-med.
- So, what's the procedure?
- Turn around.
Any vetoes?
You're in.
Let's go.
We've all staked out
rooms on the second floor.
- Why the second?
- Well as you can see, the
first floor's full of junk.
There's some furniture
in the basement
if you want to look
around down there.
Do you have a thing about rats?
- Um, yeah.
- Then you might not want
to go down to the basement.
- Don't worry.
Every Thursday's
big garbage day.
That's when people throw
out their furniture.
- A few rules.
We got the windows
on two blacked out.
You can't have any light
anywhere in the building
where it could be
seen from the outside.
There's no smoking, no visitors.
An open secret is no secret.
You want to sleep with a
guy, you go to his place.
- So we're the only
ones in the hospital?
- Just us six.
Nobody else lives here.
Nobody else even
knows we're here,
and that's the way we want it.
They had a kitchen back
in the nurse's station.
Electric range.
You want to use it,
you clean it up.
These are all the old
semi-private rooms up here.
Zak's there, Tanya,
Elaine, Mike.
That side's ward B over there,
and that's where I live.
- You have a whole ward?
- I've got a lot of stuff.
I was also here first.
You want a ward?
There are four of
them in the hospital,
as well as three
buildings in the compound.
You clean one out, you can
have one to yourself too.
You can live anywhere you want.
It's up to you.
Lock your space up, don't,
that's also up to you.
Tanya here likes to
keep her space locked.
- So do you.
- Yeah, but I believe
in private property.
- Then you shouldn't be living
in someone else's building.
These guys don't
want to admit it,
but this, this is
communal living.
- Yeah.
Oh yeah.
- This is urban pioneering,
and we're staking out
unwanted territory
that's going to waste.
- Actually, I think this is
just a bunch of college kids
who need a cheap place to live.
(Clark laughs)
Pick a room.
- I'll take it.
- [Zak] Clark, you
realize you picked
the best room in the house.
(water dripping)
I really hope that you like it.
Seriously, it's so much
better than living in a dorm.
(distance obscures Zak's voice)
(rattling)
(eerie music)
(shrieking)
(bestial moan)
(shriek)
(exerted breathing)
- God, are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Do you want some
water or something?
- Yeah.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Oof!
- Look, um, Zak I really
appreciate the help
you've been giving me.
- That's okay, but this
is the last of it, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay. (laughs)
Oof.
- What do you think?
- It's awesome.
- Yeah.
- Hey uh, do you
want to go celebrate?
You know, get a
cocktail or something?
- Oh--
- I mean, I have to
catch my breath first.
- Yeah.
Well actually um,
well I have some work
I should do around
here, and I actually,
I should study, so--
- Oh hey, no problem.
I'll um, I'll see you around.
- But, but...
Well Zak, I just
meant not tonight.
I mean, maybe later--
- Hi there.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- Did you see Zak?
- Yeah, I think he just
headed down the hall.
Anyway, look.
No pressure or anything.
- What?
- But these are some
pamphlets, all right?
Students For a Better World.
- Oh.
- And The Truth About Socialism.
Now you don't have to
read them, but if you do,
and you want to talk.
- Thanks.
- We have meetings every
Tuesdays and Thursdays,
and if you'd like to come--
- Communism is dead!
- Go tell that to
Two Bang Red Chinese!
Fuck off.
So, if you want to just
come hang out some night,
we'd really like
you to be there.
It's not like a high pressure
kind of thing, all right?
- I'll look at them if
I get a chance, okay?
- Oh that's great!
- Yeah.
- That's great, all right!
- Okay.
- Okay, so, no hard sell
or anything like that.
- No, okay.
- All right, okay,
I'll talk to you later!
- All right, great.
(eerie music)
(water dripping)
(rasping)
(distant groan)
What the...
(hiss)
(soft rattle)
(distant shriek)
Where's it coming from?
(water drips)
(distant scraping)
(water spraying)
(groaning)
(water dripping)
(distant scraping)
(soft rattle)
(gasp)
Who are you?
(clapping)
- Clapper.
- What?
- I got the lights
rigged to a Clapper.
Clap twice, they go on.
Clap twice, and they go off.
- What are you doing here?
- I live here.
You must be Clark.
- How, how do you know my name?
- The elevator shaft.
You listen close, and you can
hear what people are saying
in some of the
hallways and the rooms.
- You're not supposed to
be here without permission.
- Whose permission?
- Our permission, the permission
of the people who live here.
- Who gave them permission?
Who gave you permission?
- I was here before any of you.
- And you've been down
here this whole time
and nobody ever found you?
- I'm a quiet person.
People don't come
down here very often.
And when they do, I hide.
- Why didn't you hide just now?
- My motives are varied
and often obscure.
So why are you here?
- How do you mean?
I'm in the basement
because I smelled smoke.
Somebody's been messing
around up there.
There were these
marks on the ground
and the center part was burning.
I don't suppose you
know anything about it.
- That means you do suppose
I know something about it.
- Do you?
- I didn't do it, if
that's what you're asking.
- Well, I'm in this building
because I can't afford
any place else to live.
I'm at the university
because I want to study math.
As to why I'm here on
earth, to learn maybe.
- So you're here on
earth to learn, huh?
- I suppose.
Good a reason as any.
- You know what my
father used to say?
He said that fear is the
place you go to learn.
- I don't believe that.
- I didn't for a long time
either, but I'm starting to.
I think what he meant
to say is that fear
is the place where you go
to learn about yourself.
- [Clark] What's this?
- Actually, I'm not 100% sure.
Somebody did this
when I was out.
And I do go out you know.
I think it's some
sort of an experiment,
not a completely successful one.
- What kind of experiment?
These are just like
the ones in the alley
and the center part was burning.
- Just like it?
- No.
These are smaller.
What kind of experiment?
- You see these marks?
They're apostolic symbols,
an old ancient script from
around the first century.
- So this is some sort
of an occult thing?
- Nobody's ever been able
to translate them before.
They say that that's
because these symbols
aren't a language at all, but
they're actually equations.
- That's an interesting
coincidence.
Somebody just happens to
put these things down here
and you just happen to
know everything about them,
but you didn't do it.
- I'm a collector of facts.
Facts are overrated, of course,
just raw material until you
organize them into theories.
These aren't the first
ones that I've found here.
There's a few other
on the far wall there.
But this is the first
one that resulted in a
ignition.
- But what's it for?
- It may be some kind
of lightning rod,
or somebody wants it to be.
- What kind of lightning?
What are these?
- Texts of apostolic symbols.
Also some notes that I wrote.
I've been trying to decode them,
but I haven't had much luck.
Did anyone ever tell
you about the Shrieker?
Someone has been messing
around with some arcane stuff,
which normally wouldn't matter
because 99% of the
occult is bullshit,
and none of the
people studying it
are smart enough to recognize,
never mind figure out
the 1% that isn't.
Somebody in this place
has stumbled onto something.
They're experimenting,
and they're getting close.
- To drawing lightning?
- Find out about the Shrieker.
- [Clark] What's the Shrieker?
- What you need to know you
can find out in the library.
- Under what, occult
studies, mythology, folklore?
- Local history.
- Local, you mean the
town, the university?
- I'm talking about
this building.
- I won't tell anybody you're
here if you don't want me to.
- I don't.
Thanks.
Hey.
You should do something
about that cut.
On your back.
- Oh.
Thanks.
So, um, what's the average
yearly rainfall in Athens?
(soft chuckle)
- 15.8 inches a year.
- What about Lima?
- 1.6.
(laughing)
- [Zak] Jesus Christ.
You could have been
killed down there.
- Hm?
Okay.
- Is it serious?
- No.
- What are you looking up?
- Average yearly rainfall.
Athens, 15.8.
Lima, 1.6.
Damn.
- Is this a problem?
- Hm?
- Well, the burn in the
alley's definitely cold.
- Yeah, I'm gonna install
some smoke detectors
down there just to
be on the safe side.
You guys'll buy 'em,
and I'll install 'em.
- All right, listen up.
I've chained up the door
down to the basement.
Whichever one of you was
fucking around in there
with that voodoo
bullshit in the alley,
there better not be a repeat,
or somebody's gonna get
their ass kicked out of here.
- David, maybe it
wasn't one of us.
Maybe it was someone else,
someone from the outside.
- There isn't any other
way into the compound
without the keys, unless
somebody around here
gave copies to somebody.
So it's one of us.
I'm not gonna make some
kind of issue out of it.
Far be it from me to
point the finger of guilt.
This time.
- Feel better.
- Thanks.
(Mike sighs)
- Last booster shot?
- Uh...
Six months ago.
- Okay.
Done.
- Thanks.
- Do you want any painkillers?
- No, I'm all right.
- [Elaine] Bye.
- Bye.
(staticky grunge music)
He thinks I did it.
- Hm?
- David.
He thinks I did that
thing in the alley.
- Well, he's got no reason.
You can just--
- No, it makes perfect sense.
I mean, I'm new here and
none of you really know me,
and I was there.
But I didn't do it.
- I believe you.
Well, I better go too.
- No, no, you don't,
you don't have to go.
Do you, um, do you
believe that fear
is the place that
you go to learn?
I mean, when you
confront your fear,
do you think that you
can turn it into wisdom?
- I'd love to be able to
respond appropriately,
but I've got to be honest.
I'm clueless.
Appropriate response. (laughs)
(dial-up beeping)
(beep)
(screech)
(ominous music)
- The Shrieker.
(haunting choral music)
(keystrokes)
No, you're all wrong.
(crickets chirp)
(distant groans)
(roar)
(dramatic music)
(hiss)
- I think the
building's on fire.
- [Tanya] Can we
turn on the lights?
(clank)
(coughing)
- [Clark] Who the hell did this?
- [Zak] All right, let's
search the compound.
(suspenseful music)
(Elaine gasps)
- Chain's still
on the front gate.
(exerted breathing)
Gate's still locked.
- Big surprise.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- I don't know what kind
of Halloween bullshit
you're pulling here, but
I want you out of here.
- Hey, who the hell
put you in charge?
- I was here first.
I found this place.
I staked it out.
I'm trying to preserve it.
You know Zak, you ought to
try to think with your head
instead of your dick.
- Hey, fuck you.
- You think I don't
know what this is about?
This is like some kinda
fucked up Scooby-Doo episode.
You're trying to scare us out.
Maybe you and Zak worked
the whole thing together.
What's the matter, you want
the whole fucking hospital
for yourselves?
- Fine, I'll leave.
I'll find someplace
else to stay.
- No, no, you don't
have to go anywhere.
David is not the
landlord around here.
He is just a squatter
like the rest of us.
You don't give anybody orders!
- Yeah, well you can get
out too, Miss Daily Worker.
You know something,
comrade Tanya?
You want to go help the
workers, go fuck one.
- All right, come
on, come on, come on.
- What's the title
on your party anyway?
Fag hag?
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
What's that supposed to mean?
- When was the last
time you fucked someone
without the express
intention of trying
to change his political views?
- Fine, I'll leave!
Anybody who does
not wish to remain
in the company of this
oppressive fuckhead
can come with me.
- Didn't something like
this happen in Reds?
- All right guys, look.
If we let this turn
into open warfare,
everything we've got
going here's just
gonna go up in smoke.
- How ironically apt an analogy.
I'm telling you guys,
somebody isn't what they seem,
and unless we rid ourselves
of that person, or persons,
there isn't going to be
any peace around here.
- What about the scream?
What made the scream?
I mean it wasn't human.
Doesn't this bother anybody?
- You said you're gonna go when?
- No, I changed my mind.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm gonna find out
what's going on here.
Unless you plan
on kicking me out.
- No, he isn't.
- Oh really?
Why not?
- Because if you do I'll
rat this whole thing out,
and then we'll all
be on the street.
- That's great.
Fucking great.
Fucking surprise.
- Hey, is Zak around?
- No, it's just us.
- Do you need help with that?
- No thanks.
You know Clark, if we
would work together,
we could really change some
things around this place.
- Look, Tanya, I think some
really dangerous things
are going on around here.
- Tell me about it.
You think I don't recognize
the tactics of oppression?
You need to wake up, Clark.
The only safety is in sisterhood
united under the
banner of communism.
Think about it.
(Clark sighs)
(crickets chirp)
(ominous music)
(guttural rasping)
(snorting)
(metallic thud)
(clanging)
- Hello?
(snorting)
Hey.
(groan)
(electric buzz)
(shrieking)
(hiss)
(growl)
(clink)
(shriek)
(shrieking)
(screaming)
(distant shrieking)
- What is it?
- [Clark] I don't know.
(distant shrieking)
(moan)
- Where is it?
Where is it coming from?
- [Clark] I don't know.
I can't tell.
Come on.
- No, no.
- Wait, Tanya, just
stay here and be quiet
and I'll go check outside.
- No no, stay here!
I mean, what are you gonna
go do if you find it?
What?
Just, you stay here
and just be quiet.
- I think it's gone.
- Back from Siberia?
(knocking)
- Heard any weird
sounds tonight?
- No, why?
- (scoffs) Yeah right.
(knocking)
(Tanya sighs)
Have you seen Mike around?
He told me he'd turn the
power on in my building.
- I haven't seen him.
Make sure you black
out all the windows
before you turn on any lights.
- Don't think I don't
know what you're doing.
(door shuts)
(knock)
- Hold on.
Come in.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Oh, hey.
- Just wondering if
you want some company.
- Um, sure.
Come in.
- So, what are you working on?
- This, oh.
Well actually it's
multidimensional topography.
You see, it can describe a
fourth dimensional object by--
- Please stop, oh.
I'm sorry.
It's just
not my area.
- Okay.
- Look, I just want you to know
that whatever's
going on around here,
I think David is
way out of line.
- Thanks.
(phone rings)
Hello?
- It's Robert.
- [Clark] Oh, hi.
- [Robert] I've been hearing
some weird noises lately.
Last night and
again this evening.
Was I dreaming?
- No, you weren't.
- Well I guess the
latest experiments
were more successful
than the previous ones.
Have you had a chance to
look at the notes I gave you?
- Yeah, I was just...
Hold on.
Zak, actually this
is a private call.
Do you mind?
- Oh no, no.
Do you need these?
- Oh yeah.
Thanks.
- See you later.
- Okay, I've been
looking over your notes
and you're completely wrong.
- Well that's progress at least.
Why am I wrong?
- You've been
treating these symbols
as if they were mathematical
terms, but they're not.
- Then what are they?
- They're cross sections.
Look, can I come
down and see you?
I have some things
I want to show you.
- I'm here.
Come around the back.
It's unlocked.
- Right, right.
(beep)
- Hey.
- Sorry, I gotta go.
- At 11:30 at night?
- School thing.
See, the even symbols are
two-dimensional cross sections
of a three-dimensional shape.
The odd symbols define the
angle of a cross section.
Watch.
- This is what I think.
There are higher dimensions,
and things live in them.
Sometimes there's weak spots
between the higher ones
and our own where they
can break through,
and I think sometimes
these breakthroughs
must happen spontaneously.
Not often but,
there have been other cases.
- Like lightning.
- That's right.
And if you wanted to draw
lightning on purpose,
where would you go?
Someplace you knew lightning
had already struck on its own.
- Maybe.
But you wouldn't just
go on a mountainside
holding a lightning
rod, would you?
Whoever's doing this
knows about the Shrieker.
They know what it did.
They wouldn't just conjure it up
unless they had a death wish.
- Not unless you had some
means of controlling it,
directing it.
- You know, just listening
to it, I'm scared to death.
- Did you learn anything?
- No, I was too
petrified to think.
- The problem was that
you didn't go to it.
You didn't face it.
That's why you didn't
learn anything.
- Okay, I have to
be honest with you.
That sounds like a monumentally
bad piece of advice.
- Sometimes lies are more
agreeable than the truth.
Which do you prefer?
- The truth.
- What do you make of those?
- Nothing yet.
They're different
than the others.
- The mark of sending.
You use this symbol to kill.
Draw it on a piece of paper
and hand it to a
prospective victim.
Once they've received it,
they can only get rid of it
by giving it to somebody else.
Tearing it up and throwing
it away won't work.
The mark of binding.
Once you have derived
or invoked the demon,
this symbol, this shape,
makes it your slave in theory,
but that symbol only works
after you've given it to
five victims.
- You knew what these
symbols meant all along?
Those notes you gave
me, they were bullshit.
You knew what these meant.
- Do you believe in it?
- What?
- Say it.
Tell me that you
believe that it's real.
- I believe that it's real.
- I think Mike is dead.
He was the first victim and
four other are gonna die too
if this thing isn't stopped.
And to be honest with you,
I don't think this
thing can be stopped.
You've got a decision
to make here.
That door over there,
it leads to the outside.
You can go and you
don't have to come back.
- What about the others?
- They won't believe you.
And they're certainly
not gonna believe me.
- God Zak, I've
got to talk to you.
- We wanted to
talk to you, Clark.
- We?
- Come on.
- Have a seat, Clark.
- To what do I owe the pleasure?
That was in my room.
- Well now it's in here.
- You had no right.
- We all have the right
to self-protection.
- Look, I was gonna tell
you about this, okay?
I didn't do those drawings.
I got them from Robert.
- Who's Robert?
- Robert lives in the basement.
He's been down there--
- Bullshit.
There isn't anybody
in the basement.
I've been down there 20 times.
- Oh really?
And what were you doing
down there all those times?
- No no.
Don't you try to
turn this around.
There's no bogeyman
in the basement.
There's just you.
- No, I didn't.
Zak?
- You were hiding this
stuff in your room.
What do you want me to think?
- I wasn't hiding.
- Yes you were.
I saw the way you
closed that notebook
when I came in the room.
Don't tell me that.
- Look Zak, you've
gotta trust me.
- No.
You don't have the right
to use me and lie to me
and then ask me to trust you.
- Okay, I'm sorry I didn't
tell you about the drawings,
but I never used you.
- How can I believe you?
- I don't know how, but
you've gotta try, okay?
Look, I think we're all
in real danger here.
Honest to God, I
think Mike is dead.
- Why?
Because he hasn't come home?
You know, he wasn't
lying you know.
He really does have
two girlfriends
and this whole gender
thing he's always gotta
constantly prove, him not
being here isn't so unusual.
- 50 years ago
something happened here.
Seven people were
killed by something.
- Yeah, probably by
poor medical care.
- Christ, don't you think I
know how ridiculous this sounds?
- Good, then we're in
agreement on something.
- Don't you see I'm
trying to warn you?
I'm trying to save your lives.
- Go on, Clark.
You want to tell us something,
go ahead and tell us.
- It isn't a joke.
The newspapers reported it.
They called it the Shrieker,
and I believe that it came
through here last night,
right through that door.
- Then why didn't
anybody see it?
- I don't know.
It may be able to
make itself invisible
or move through solid matter.
- Well that would explain it.
(water dripping)
- And this Robert, he
told you about these, uh--
- Apostolic symbols.
- And you believed him.
- Yes.
- Did you ever think he's
the one who's doing this?
- There's no way.
With the first floor
door locked off,
the only way out of the basement
is through a door
to the outside,
and the only way back
in and up the stairs
is through a side entrance
that's been chained shut.
- This is ridiculous.
Who even says there is a Robert?
- Well hell, that's
easy enough to test.
Either he's there or he isn't.
Why don't we go check?
Prove that much of
the story anyway.
- That's fine by me.
Let's go.
(bestial roar)
Okay, fuck this.
(click)
- Hey man--
- Hey yourself.
What are you do when
you're a squatter
and someone breaks
in, call the police?
Home defense, man.
We're urban pioneers.
- So I guess it's not Clark.
- Maybe it's Clark.
I'll take it further, maybe
it's Clark and Robert.
(roar)
(clang)
Okay, let's go.
(hiss)
(bestial roar)
(dialing)
(phone rings)
(gasping)
Hello?
- Look David, you
fascist fuckhead.
I know what you're doing.
- What am I doing, Tanya?
- Knock of the noise.
- Guess again, Tanya.
We found the incriminating
evidence in Clark's room.
- Bullshit.
- Hey, hurrah for solidarity.
We're kinda busy here.
(beep)
All right, you say
there's a Robert.
Let's go find him.
- Well maybe we should split up.
- Is that supposed to be funny?
Let's go, everybody!
(suspenseful music)
(roar)
(electrical buzz)
(screeching)
(distant shriek)
(distant growl)
(screech)
(crashing)
(bestial roar)
(dramatic music)
(exerted breathing)
Shit!
- Is that the right key?
- Let's see.
It has a piece of tape on
it that says facility two.
Shit shit.
- What?
- It's not the same lock.
Somebody replaced it.
Man, this is really fucked up.
- What, it doesn't work?
- Well duh, yes Zak.
It's not the same lock.
It's brand new.
And don't tell me some
thing from another world
went to the Sandals
Hardware Store.
- It needs four more victims.
There's five of us.
- There's six.
- Mike's dead.
- I'm talking about Robert.
(phone rings)
- What!
- Knock it off.
- Knock what off?
- Whoever is out in the hall,
you better tell them
to get the fuck out.
- I hate to break this to you
Tanya, but we're all out here.
- Look David, this is
not funny, all right?
- You're doing this, aren't you?
- What?
- You've got tape recorders.
You're orchestrating
the whole goddamn thing.
What's the plan, a little
purge of the compound?
(roaring)
(screech)
- Something is in the room.
- Maybe it's the ghost of Lenin.
- God, give me that!
Tanya, can you hear me?
Did you find a square of paper?
(shrieking)
- What?
What do you mean?
- Did you find a piece of
paper with some markings on it?
- (stammers) I don't understand.
(roaring shriek)
What the fuck?
(shriek)
- What, what's happening?
- I don't know.
(thud)
(snorting)
(shriek)
(Tanya screams)
Oh Jesus!
(Elaine shouts)
You've got to get it to work!
Tanya!
(snort)
Something's in there.
- No no.
Hey, you want to
pull that pistol out,
now would be a pretty good time.
- Okay, okay.
- Come on.
(water drips)
(haunting ambient music)
(hiss)
(eerie echoes)
(low growl in distance)
(dramatic music)
(hissing and screeching)
(shouting)
(roaring and shrieking)
(bestial moan)
(roar)
- Hold up.
- Where is it coming from?
- Okay, let's go.
(shrieking)
How did it get in front of us?
- The three-dimensional
cross section.
- So?
- So it can move instantly
from one place to the next,
even move through walls.
- That's fucking great.
- It has to be solid to kill us.
- Yes.
- Okay then, when
it's solid we kill it.
- Where's my fuckin' phone.
- Who are you calling?
- Who do you think,
National Enquirer?
911.
- Well, tell them it's a maniac.
Don't tell them it's a monster.
They'll never believe you.
- Thanks for the hint.
Hello? Hello?
(shrieking over phone)
Shit!
It's in the fucking phone!
(gunshot)
(soft gasp)
(dramatic music)
- [Clark] Robert!
- What the fuck?
- Clark!
- [Clark] Oh...
- [Elaine] Don't bother.
- Oh my God.
- Can't you give him
CPR or something?
- He's been shot
through the heart.
He's dead.
- Way to go, David.
One guy in the whole
world who knows
what's going on around here,
and you just killed him.
- Aren't you gonna cover
him up or something?
- Why?
(click)
- I don't suppose you have
any more bullets for this gun?
- No, I don't.
- Well shit.
When that thing comes
walkin' through a wall,
maybe we can throw it at it.
- Why isn't it coming after us?
Why doesn't it
just come after us?
- Somebody here knows why.
It's killed twice.
It'll kill three more times.
Three of us have
been given the mark,
a square piece of paper with
a symbol inscribed on it.
That's what draws it.
Once you've been given
the mark, the only way
to get rid of it is to
give it to somebody else.
It kills whoever's
been given the mark.
That's the price for binding it.
Mike, Tanya, and three
of us, five lives.
That leaves one
person left standing,
the one person who's
been doing all of this,
and I know it isn't me.
That means it's one of you.
As far as I'm concerned,
it could be any one of you.
- (scoffs) Well I
know it's not me.
- I'm not so sure.
You were here first.
You waited until five
other people were here.
In the other building, when
you had to shoot that thing,
your aim wasn't so good
but you didn't have any
problem hitting Robert.
Why is that?
- Screw you, all right.
You're the one who
brought her in.
Maybe you needed to
finish the collection.
History major, how about that.
Who better set up to learn
about all this arcane shit?
- Christ, knock it off!
- The marks, we should
look for the marks.
- What?
- If you've been given one
of those piece of paper,
then you're not the one, right?
- Right.
- But it might not be on you.
It could have been passed
along in a book, anything.
It doesn't have to be on you.
- Jesus.
What is this?
Is this it?
This is it.
Who did this?
Who put this in my wallet?
Great.
- It's not on me.
I'm gonna go search my room.
- Clark, (stammers)
how do we know if...
Fine, fine.
You want to hear.
You think I'm gonna
come over there
and force you to take it?
Fine, keep your distance.
Stay away from me.
Go to your room.
All of you can
stay away from me.
I found mine.
You find yours!
(bestial shrieking)
(growl)
(moan)
(snorting breaths)
(high-pitched shriek)
(water drips)
(shriek)
(electric buzz)
(echoing moan)
(hiss)
(snarl)
No!
(shrieking)
(screaming)
(roar)
(David screams)
- Oh my God, David.
(thwack)
- Zak, no!
Zak!
- Use your head.
If it's not you and it's
not me, it's gotta be her.
Haven't you noticed
everyone else is dead?
We'll make her tell us how
to get rid of that thing.
If worse comes to worst,
we'll make her tell us
where those damn marks are.
We'll force her
to take them back.
We'll shove them down
her throat if we have to!
Whoa, hey.
What?
You think it's me?
Is that it?
Oh Christ, that's great.
That's just great.
You think I'm doing this.
Why don't you use that?
- I'm not sure.
- You better get sure.
Stay here, watch her.
I'm gonna go find that mark
while we still have some time.
Watch her!
- Clark.
Where's Zak?
- He went to his room.
- You heard the Shrieker, right?
It went around the
stairs with Tanya.
You heard him.
- Yeah.
- That's when it
was killing Mike.
- I guess.
- Who else?
Who else was in the
damn building Clark,
that's still alive?
(dramatic music)
- What is this?
(distant growl)
- Stop!
- Shit.
- Well in case you're wondering,
these are symbols of
power, protection.
As long as you have these on,
the Shrieker will leave you
alone and can't hurt you.
It's sort of like a vaccination.
Oh, you don't have any.
- Christ, why are
you doing this?
- Why am I doing this?
You wouldn't understand.
It's almost time.
These things happen
on a schedule.
- Which one?
Which one of us?
- I'm not quite sure.
(shriek)
(electric buzz)
It's here.
It should be reacting by now.
- It was you all this time?
All this time?
- It's hard to explain, Clark.
See, it's horrifying
but thrilling, really.
You should surrender to it.
Just let it happen.
Just...
(crackling)
ow.
What the...
Oh God.
(loud crackling)
Ow!
Oh my God.
(gasp)
(shriek)
(crunch)
(gasp)
- Come on!
(high-pitched shrieking)
What happens now?
- What?
- Well Elaine obviously
didn't plan that,
and she also didn't draw
that mark on her own back.
I'd say it came as a big
surprise, so who set her up?
- I don't--
- Well let's narrow
the field a bit.
I know it wasn't me.
Who does that leave?
- I don't know.
- I'm doing my best, Clark.
God knows I'm doing my best
with this whole
good guy routine.
I want to trust you.
I'm trying to, but you keep
giving me reasons not to.
- Let me go.
- No!
I'm not gonna let you go.
I'm gonna hold on
to you so tight
that whatever happens to
me, happens to you too.
(thwack)
(Zak gasps)
(Zak groans)
Jesus Clark.
- Of course.
Of course.
- [Zak] Of course what?
(whistling)
- Come out, come out.
All sorts of complications,
but it's almost over.
- You fucker.
- Back a pace.
Just who the hell do
you think you are?
Norman?
Is that you, Norman?
In case you're wondering,
there are real bullets
in this one, not like the
one that Elaine loaded
into David's gun.
- Robert...
- Clark, in a couple of minutes
the Shrieker's
gonna be coming out.
Now it can take one of you,
him, or the both of you.
- What are you talking about?
- Well, I hadn't originally
planned on killing Elaine,
but it became clear to me that
her motives were conflicted.
She wasn't serious.
If she had been, she
would have realized
that the symbols of protection
that I drew on her were phony.
Not like these.
These are real.
Remember Clark, I
gave you a choice.
Don't ever say I didn't.
I said you could leave,
but you decided to stay.
- I wanted to help the others.
- Well now, that
obviously didn't work,
and I don't believe it.
I think you stayed because
you wanted to learn.
You wanted to test your
soul in the furnace.
There's wisdom to be
found here, dark wisdom.
I'll teach you.
I'll show you.
(roar)
(high-pitched shrieking)
Well now, that must
be the Shrieker.
Clark, you might
want to stand back.
It won't hurt you, not yet, but
it could get a little messy.
Clark, you are rapidly
approaching a moment of truth.
You can't save him, but
you can save yourself!
I think it's a good idea, Clark.
Zak, give me the mark.
- [Zak] What?
- Give me the mark.
- No!
- Trust me.
- What are you doing?
(snorting breaths)
I am very disappointed
in you, Clark.
I think we have a lot in common.
What the hell are you doing?
- Fear is the place that
you go to learn, right?
Right?
(low growl)
I'll show you what it taught me.
- Wait!
(roaring)
(buzzing)
What are you doing?
(shrieking)
(gunshot)
(shriek)
(roar)
(electric buzz)
(snarl)
(buzz)
- Is that it?
- I think so.
- Why do I have the
feeling either we should
still be trying
to kill something,
or something should still
be trying to kill us?
I guess not.
(soft laughter)
- Come on.
I'll get you to the hospital.
- Thanks.
Oh, wait.
We'll need this to
shoot the lock off.
Somebody's gotta
think of these things.
(crickets chirp)
You know I've been thinking.
- About what?
- Sleeping in the park.
It's not that bad when
you think about it.
What'd you ever see
in that guy anyway?
(melodious haunting music)
(dramatic symphonic music)