You want the legend of the Blair Witch.
The legend of the Blair Witch is long and involved,
and in my opinion it's mostly
just stories to scare children.
Startedback in the 1700,
the stories began circulating supposedly as
i understand about a witch in the area.
Chris Carrazzo
film archivist
Some old woman that was cursing
people that was doing things.
I don't know all that but she
became the witch of the area,
as I understand she might even have
been put to death over it.
Years progressed from there every bad
thing that happened to the town
it was the Blair Witch, causing people
just have to find something to tag,
someone to label as the cause of things
the Blair Witch became that,
for this area for Birkedsville.
Quite some time again after
that a child drowned in a river,
and people attributed that to the Blair Witch,
which there's absolutely nothing to substantiate that.
So I understand it, was a shallow part of the river,
but there were laims supposedly that
the child was seen being pulled down
by a hand in the river. The fact is
there's a for sure drowning in shallow water.
I mean, i know people have
drowned in soup bowls,
so you can't tell me that eight
inches of water is not too shallow
for someone to drown in.
A child did go missing,
after the child drowned and a young boy i believe,
search party went out looking for the young boy,
young boy was recovered, the
search party never came back.
So they sent out a search party for the search party,
and they came across the
bodies found on Coffin Rock,
right by the river and every member of
the search party was dead.
They were not just dead.
They were mutilated, they were hacked to pieces.
I'm not denying that that ever
happened that's a fact that happened,
but it got attributed to the Blair Witch,
and i don't see how that happened.
There was the Ruston Parri incident which
became attributed to the Blair Witch,
in some way or another,
because Ruston Parr
claimed that he did what he did
because an old woman told him.
To the old witch it's been said in different ways.
The most recent incident that we've had happen,
is these three college kids,
went out into the woods in the Burkinsville area.
They were going to make themselves a
documentary concerning the Blair Witch,
and they went missing and they were assumed dead,
and then some time later their equipment was found.
They pieced together the material found, there are a
lot of videotapes and film reels and stuff.
And they managed to pieces together,
and what they think implies
that the Blair Witch attacked them and killed them.
This is just, really this is absolutely
more of the urban legend,
being built up these kids aren't missing.
They aren't dead, this is just a sick joke.
It's the kind of stuff that sad sick people
perform on these kind of events.
That's the blair Witch legend.
The Burkittsville 7
How long have you been in here?
He was a boogeyman for the area.
We were always told, don't do that.
Rustin Par is going to get you.
Go to sleep and be quiet or
Rustin Parr is going to get you.
Well, this is my collection of cameras,
predominantly super 816 millimeter here.
This is the camera that I got from my parents, though.
Used to have a viewfinder on it.
I kind of was just attracted to the odd angles in here.
I think they had a gun. And part of the
roof is just a nice flat roof.
And you come into another area
where the bedroom is,
and it's a peaked roof, basically,
i've been working in film all my life,
a projector that I've used for years.
Not in Hollywood, not making it as a filmmaker.
yeah, I have some stuff that
probably has not seen too many eyes.
Let's see.
Okay, we got it.
We got it right here.
This is...
my Rustin Parr treasure box.
Well, initially, it wasn't just Rustin parr,
I just kind of always had
a fascination with serial killers.
Convicted Murderer Ruston Parr
executed for Burkett'sville killings,
Transcripts from the trial.
Here's Rustin giving his testimony.
That was just one of the few times
i had someone like that,
a serial killer of that repute that
was like in my own backyard,
that i could possibly find something out myself.
Why did you do it, mister Parr?
I heard voices in my head.
I'm Bill Barnes, executive director of
Burkittsville Historical Society,
and the Historian of Burkketsville.
It's my responsibility there to teach
the children the history of our area,
because we're at close to three larger towns:
Rockville, Baltimore, and Washington, DC.
Which are all fairly historical,
but I don't want to lose touch with the fact that
we have a pretty good historical town too.
Let's go back, say, to the fall of 1940.
The birth of a small town,
Everybody knew everybody, usually
most of them by their first name.
Emily Hollands
abducted 13 november 1940
But we've had some kids disappearing in town.
They were mostly between the age of six and eight.
Kyle Brody
abducted 5 december 1940
It went long after that Mr.
Parr came into town,
Terra Shelly
abducted january 8 1941
and walked to Mr. Smith or Mr.
Striker's store, I don't know which one.
Steven Thompson
abducted february 20 1941
One of the general stores who titled, who
was telling the story as to where he went.
Michael Guldry
abducted march 5 1941
But he come in and he said, the words that become
famous in Burkettville is that "I finally finished."
Eric Norris
abducted march 13 1941
Julie Forsyth
abducted april 2 1941
Well, they didn't know what he
meant, and they asked him.
Margaret Lowell
abducted may 20 1941
He said, I've killed those children.
He was charged and convicted with
the abduction of eight children,
and the murder of seven children in that area.
Ruston was basically, up until that point,
he was a pretty harmless guy.
He was friendly.
He was nice.
All of a sudden, he became this monster,
the demon of burkittsville,
as they referred to him at times.
I don't think anybody ever thoroughly
looked at the story.
People just assumed things about Rustin Parr.
They decided that certain things were this way,
and they never did a thorough investigation.
Rustin's mother and father, they died around the 30s.
At That time already Rustin was...
Leonard Torrington
Rustin Parr Relative
Rustin was living out in the back woods.
He was very uncomfortable in society,
society was very uncomfortable with him.
Dominic Cazale
Former Priest
When he was arrested for killing
seven children in Burkettville,
I was serving that prison, I heard his confession,
which I have kept as a private valve
for what, 50 years now?
Just like all the other sort of tales to
scare children, that kind of thing.
Ruston had this reputation, just like the
old scary house in the neighborhood,
where people say, you know:
who everlives there, if you go near the house,
they'll put a curse on you, or something like that.
That's what the voices told me.
I'm finally finished.
Those were the words that are attributed to him.
I have asked around to anyone who
might have been a survivor of that time.
I can't find anybody who's willing to say they
know that Ruston Parr said those words.
I'm finally finished.
He said, I'm finally finished.
And that was his acceptance of death.
I think it had nothing to do with the crime,
Everybody said, oh,
but I don't think it had
anything to do with the crime.
So they got the sheriff come down
and he arrested him.
And he went up to the cabin and sure
enough he found seven bodies.
Not eight. That's was seven.
And the 8th one that they didn't find, was Kyle Brody.
While they were looking for the bodies in
the home and uncovering those bodies,
kyle Brody comes walking back
into the town of Burkettville,
and he starts telling people about Rustin Parr,
and what Ruston Parr has been doing for the last year.
How Rustin Parr held him captive there in his home,
how Ruston Parr was committing these horrible,
unspeakable acts to these children.
But he came back in town.
He testified against him at the trial.
You know, I do I do not know
why they took me to that trial.
I mean, what were they thinking
taking a child my age
Janine Brody
Kyle Brody Sister
to hear someone testify about killings and murders?
And there were all these people.
They were all around.
I just remember there were so many people
all around and they were staring at Kyle.
I remember angry voices.
I remember a tall man with glasses shouting and pointing
at someone who I think was Rustin Parr.
And I remember, I guess it was the judge banging.
And I remember Kyle sitting in this big box just staring
straight ahead, not looking at anyone.
And those eyes are just looking straight ahead
and answering these questions.
He begins telling everyone what
happened to him overthis time,
that he's been locked into Rustin Parr's home,
into one of the rooms in the upstairs.
And periodically he would be
brought out by Rustin Parr.
And then, according to Kyle Brody,
Rustin Parr would face him into a corner,
while Rustin Parr then performed
these atrocities on these children.
I just remember Kyle's face all white and
pale and his eyes all blue gray,
and almost as though he didn't want
to see what he had seen.
He didn't want to say what he was about to say.
He didn't want to know what he had come to know.
He had details about Emily Holland's abduction.
Emily Holland was abducted an entire two weeks
before the Kyle Brody went missing.
And yet he knows events about the abduction,
about where Parr found her in the woods,
and abducted her and brought
her back to his place.
And justice being real swift, they took him
down in Rockville behind the jail,
where the galas was and hung him.
He seemed to get some pleasure from telling
them the stories they wanted to hear.
They would have hung him anyway.
I think that the decision was made
that Rustin Parr was guilty,
before anybody had a chance to even look at the facts.
It was all decided as they were marching
up the hills to Rustin Parr's home.
And then with the boy coming in at
the same time and laying out his story.
By the time they came back with what they
were looking at as conclusive evidence,
it was done.
Here's one on a young Parr's
victim put in institution living.
Parr's victim leading difficult life.
Poor Kyle's suffering.
There's Kyle Brody.
One of his many trips before the law.
We had a boy there in town named Kyle Brody.
A weird sort of kid.
And being like he was, some of the
things he'd like to do is,
he'd like to catch cats and
stuff them in a mailbox.
Kyle Brody when we first saw him,
I determined almost immediately that
he belonged away from society.
He belonged in the mental institution.
He was obviously mentally ill.
Dr. Alvin Frasier
Psichologyst
I remember I used to see him outside
playing by the stream all the time.
The classic tearing wings off a flies.
That's nothing.
But he would also take the frogs out of the river.
He'd capture them, and he would
chop the legs off of the frogs.
He wouldn't kill the frogs first.
And so apparently Kyle came home that
day and filled one of his buckets with frogs.
And he began cutting off the
legs of one of these frogs.
So eventually all four legs were chopped
off and there was just this horrible,
painful creature writhing on the ground.
My mother said, what are you doing?
And he said, I'm trying to see
if frogs have feelings.
Children who've been abused.
They sometimes take things out
on small animals or insects.
He said that's the first sign of
a psychological disturbance in a child.
He believed that he was severely physically
beaten as a child by his father.
My feeling is that this was probably not so.
All I can tell you is he believed it.
my father wanted Kyle to be a man.
And he disciplined him very harshly at times.
With schizophrenic personality,
there is no way to substantiate
what they're saying is true or not.
Unless, of course, you have another
family member who will corroborate it.
In this case, we did not.
There's history of the boy being a problem child,
a very difficult child to deal with.
When he disappeared, the parents
thought he had run away,
so they were rather surprised when he came
back with his story of being abducted.
Rustin Parr abducted eight children.
One of them was my brother.
Seven of those children were butchered by that man.
My brother was forced to stand facing a wall
while other children were killed behind him.
He could hear the sounds,
he could hear them screaming,
not knowing what was going to happen next.
What is the reasoning behind having a child face
a corner for all this, just is just illogical.
And this man butchered these seven children.
How Kyle ever got away, I have no idea.
I think, in my opinion, from some
of the facts that I've gathered,
from some of the experiences
i've had in my life as well,
that what might have happened actually,
was that Kyle Brody had actually
planned this from the beginning.
Kyle was a beautiful child, though
perhaps this man fancied him.
Perhaps he thought he could
get sexual favors from Kyle.
Perhaps Kyle may even have provided
those to save his own life.
I don't know.
And then to turn around and say that
my brother killed those children.
Those children were his friends.
The seven children that died,
none of these children knew each one of
the other children that were missing.
The only person out of the entire group,
that did know all eight of the children
abducted was Kyle Brodie.
But he liked to fight. He'd always
fight with the other kids,
and he didn't care how big he was.
He'd dump on and fight with them.
He had past histories with them,
some of them troubled pastors.
Some records, not records,
but knowledge from the people I've talked to
of there being disturbances between
Kyle and some of the other kids.
One day he tried to pick a fight with me,
but I never thought nothing about fighting.
Kyle Brody was involved with
the abduction of Emily Hollins.
Hence he knows all these facts and details about it.
Rustin Parr never threatened anyone in any way.
He was a peaceful person, and I just don't believe
that he had it in him to perform these acts,
these atrocious acts that were done to these children.
This kid had it in him to develop these ideas,
these schemes, these plans.
And I think that he is the one who led
Rustin Parr through every one of these things.
I don't think he stood there with his
face facing a corner during all this.
I think he was there taking Rustin Parr's hand,
putting the knife in it and having him do this,
because he wouldn't need someone with the
strength of an adult to do some of these acts.
But he was the one that was making the decisions,
and he was the one guiding Rustin parr through this.
I met Cal Brody in the late 60s,
I was assigned to the psychiatric ward of the
Maryland State Institute for the Criminally Insane.
I heard about him before I got there
because he was quite infamous,
and his case made quite a number of newspapers.
The state of the mental institutions
when Kyle Brody was first incarcerated,
of course, is nowhere near as
humane as they are now.
He was a legendary dark figure in the hospital.
It was this last incarcerated link to this heinous
multiple murder that had taken place in 1940.
Kyle Brody's pharmacological
chart was all over the place.
When I first met him.
They tried everything,
probably known to man,
and nothing was working.
Dr. David Hull    Dr. Harlan Miles
Co-case worker Kyle Brody
And I read that and I said, this has got to stop.
He had apparently been taking the medication
that had reduced him to Catatonia.
And on the first day,
They thought that the medication
itself had created the catatonia,
or had created the climate for catatomic.
I mean, just like rigid like that.
I narrowed it down to two or three medications
that I felt we could zero in on.
What would be the outcome
that we wouldn't looking for?
I discussed it
with Dr.Miles, and we decided to narrow it
down even more, which we did.
I mean, these medications are so potent,
the side effects are unspeakable.
And I remember him laying in his bed, rigid,
and i remember looking down at
him and he couldn't speak.
The medication I had originally
suggested, he finally agreed.
Yes, we both agreed.
Let's try that. We did it.
And there were some noticeable changes.
Then I noticed he had changed.
He was back again.
And I found out later that Dr.Hall had switched
the medication without consulting them.
And I remember looking down at the sheets,
and I remember seeing that the sheets were wet,
and they were sweat.
And I was so upset, I called the orderly
and I said, you've got to change him.
And the orderly I get this.
The orderly said, we want to teach
him to go to the bathroom on his own.
We're dealing with human beings, not just patients.
I would imagine that those that work there,
particularly in subsidiary positions such
as guards andinterns and orderlies,
can probably get carried away and
perhaps get into abuse of the patients.
I told mom and dad and I said we had
to get him out of there, but they couldn't.
I couldn't afford to.
Kyle Brody's sister, I guess you could say,
was one of the many thorns in the side of
a system that was already full of thorns.
She was convinced the Kyle that
her brother was not insane,
and did everything to the best of her ability
to keep him out of mental institution.
Kyle Brody I'm not going to say that he had an
easy existence after the Rustin Parr trial,
but certainly I think it's better than being hung,
But he became a rather aggressive panhandler,
where it wasn't really an option for people
to walk away and not give him something.
He also had incidents of shoplifting.
He has robberies, not armed robberies,
but very violent, aggressive.
So he tended to spend most of his time in
a couple of different institutions,
and that's actually where he died as well.
I'm not seeing anything.
I have nothing to base my opinions
of the adult Kyle Brody on,
until I hear about this film called "White Enamel".
I don't call them documentaries.
I don't like the term documentary very much.
It conjures up something stale
and boring to most people,
so I call them nonfiction films.
David Hooper
White Enamel Filmmaker
White Enamel was a documentary,
a black and white documentary
shot back in the 60s in
various, in insane asylums in Maryland.
They tend to center on one in particular which,
wonder of wonders is the very same institution
that Kyle Brody spent a great deal of time at.
I think I expected a certain thing when
i went in into the hospital there,
andit was completely different than I thought.
And I took a deep breath
and I jumped off the cliff.
I let it happen as it was happening.
Nixon, I should give you not.
I could be a general.
I mean, yeah, I could, but no.
Nixon and Kissinger, they don't want
to share no war at all.
My father was in World War II.
He was a gunners made on the USS Idaho.
And I'm here because of Richard Milhous Nixon.
And Mr. Kissinger.
I am here.
They're hearing right now what I'm saying.
They don't fool me.
They're hearing what I'm saying.
The mere man was bugging. Yeah.
Just not looking at a meal.
He's bugging this whole place.
David Hooper, I think when he made
the film, he was almost an innocent,
and i think he was also heroic in a way.
It's a heroic act to take on this kind of inhumanity.
I doubt very highly that most people
know they're doing anheroic act,
when they're in the middle of doing it.
It's just
something propels you into this.
And you either have the balls
to follow it through or you don't.
And he did.
How long have you been in here?
I've been here a long time.
Why are you in here?
I don't know why, they should they told me.
I asked David Hooper about that, how
he made the decision to do that.
I knew he thought it was powerful.
He had no idea how powerful it was going to be,
but he knew he had to say
something about how humankind
in general can treat the unwanted,
and how this culture is a beautiful culture,
and doesn't tolerate what's ugly.
So that as this
frame after frame after frame starts to stack up,
at first you think, man, I just don't want to watch this.
It's too tedious to be on words of this.
And then all of a sudden you go,
this would be very hard to live with.
This would be a very difficult job to have.
Who gets this job?
Who wants this job?
What are the families of the people
who treat these people this way?
Whose dad shoves a tube down some guy's nose
and pours lunch into their stomach?
And what's the kid like that lives in that family?
How far out do the ripples of this go?
And all of a sudden questions are being asked
without you even knowing them.
Because there is no linear context to this film,
because it doesn't have a
beginning, middle, and an end.
It has a beginning, middle, and end at all times.
So it is a life force that's coming at you.
Not a tidy picture.
White enamel is well, it is
a very exciting point for me.
I get to look at this thing, and it's mind blowing.
I mean, the film itself is an interesting film as
far as the information you can glean from it as,
to how inmates are treated in insane
asylum, that's interesting, but
I'm not really that interested in that.
There is actually about five minutes worth of footage,
approximately, of Kyle Brody as an adult.
There is a scene of Kyle Brody in his cell,
and he's chanting something.
What he's chanting is the phrase, a two word phrase.
Never given.
He's chanting that and what this means.
The importance to this is there's actually
reported fact from the guards
that watched over Rustin Parr on a suicide
watch while he was waiting to be killed.
They have reports of Rustin Parr
screaming the words never given.
The same two words "never given".
To say Kyle Brody creeped me out.
I'd be putting it mildly. Kyle Brody,
was every nightmare you've
ever had as a kid.
That guy played with my head.
Everything I asked him to do,
he would do the opposite.
I don't know what the phrase means, "never given".
But here is another connection.
Rustin Parr is chanting never given
or screaming, yelling never given.
Kyle Brody is chanting it in his cell.
So I didn't stop there.
I know enough about filmmaking to know that if you
have less than five minutes of Kyle Brody in your film,
there could probably be another, maybe an hour's worth of
footage of Kyle Brody that was never put into the film.
Filmmakers overshoot.
So I began to look for David Hooper.
He was very forthcoming with information.
He did remember Kyle Brody.
Kyle Brody made it quite an impression on him in the film.
He's a very intense figure.
And then he told me that he
had other footage of Kyle Brody.
Chris is a maniac. And I recognize
myself at the same age.
It takes brass balls to do some
of the stuff that he's doing.
I begged, I pleaded, I joeled,
I bribed everything I could.
And he was willing to send me
the extra footage that he had.
This stuff was a mess.
I did everything I could to restore this
before Ieven began to look at it,
built it up into the best shape
i could watch this stuff.
And there i found another very interesting key.
There was a shot in the rec room of this insane asylum.
And Kyle Brody is there with this large art notepad,
and he's writing on the notepad.
And what is being written on that notepad
being written from right to left.
The way it is supposed to
be written is transitus fluviate.
The language, the witchcraft language.
This is not a common language.
It's not known all around the world.
Very few people know this.
And here is Kyle Brody.
To the best of my knowledge that that is
what he's writing in his transit is fluviate.
I took this footage and I took whatever
stills I could grab from it,
and try to find people who could substantiate this.
Chris Carrasco found me through my website,
and he sent me an email and it said,
Sarah Didonna
photo analyst
I have this piece of footage from the late 60's,
and I needyou to analyze it and take a look at it.
He wanted me to figure out and analyze
what this particular gentleman was drawn.
And he was convinced that I could do it.
And I was equally convinced that there was no
way that you could conclusively say
what this individual was drawn.
She got some improvements, but she could
not verify for sure from what she found
that it was what I was hoping, the .
I found another woman at Kendra Fineman,
who actually is relatively fluent in this.
456transit of Fluvia
Chris brought that to me and asked if
i could tell him what that was.
So after examining that footage, we determined that this
gentleman actually was writing in transit of Fluvia.
Kendra Fineman
Philosophy professor
You can see very clearly the little
circle embellishments at the end,
the little loops at the end of the letters.
And she looked at this, and she fairly quickly was able
to decide that this was transit as Fluviae.
That language was mostly really used in secret
societies and cults and different sects,
and with witches that lived and practiced in Europe.
This is what Kyle Brody is writing from right to left,
the way transit from Fluviae is written, as if,
as in the Hebrew language.
They're saying that there are occult in alphabet,
or they can tell what they're writing
because that's what they want to believe.
That's their theory. And so that's
what they're bearing out.
I saw him writing.
I saw how he was writing.
And I, based on my own knowledge on the language,
could decipher those characters.
Cannot start the theory and then
look for it in the photograph,
have to take the photograph or the
piece of film as aseparate entity,
analyze it on its merits alone.
Then if there's some correspondence
with the theorem, then great.
But if there isn't, you need to let it go.
Now, this is the exact same language that we find
on the walls of the upstairs of Rustin Parr's home.
Transit is Fluvi, written by this kid who has a high IQ,
and might have somehow picked this
up at some stage in his life,
as compared to the possibility of Rustin Parr,
a man who was illiterate, could not
read or write at all in English.
The idea of him writing transit, his Fluvia language
all over the walls of his home, it's absurd.
This is a very important key piece of evidence that I've
found that I think links Kyle Brody to these murders.
And it's not really being considered that seriously.
As I was pouring over the ideas of the Rustin Parr case,
and thinking about Rustin, who is
a rather simple fellow. Actually.
A simpleton. And this child,
This magnetic, charming child of Kyle Brody.
Who I think has manipulated Rustin Parr.
Made him do his bidding.
If not actually holding his hand and leading him to it.
Directing him still through every action
through the abduction of Emily Hollins.
Which Kyle Brody should not have
known anything about. But he did.
To all the actions of each of the deaths
within the basement of that house.
I think it was Kyle Brody leading him through this.
Now, this story of what happened in Rustin Parr's
cabin is being told by an unreliable witness,
who is insane, who is also
the person, in my opinion,
responsible for every one of the murderers.
These are things that once you
start putting them together,
once you start thinking of all the facts,
it'll shape your beliefs and
everything that you know so far.
One short time ago, there was a guy from Ohio,
started researching the death of those seven children.
And he came up with a theory that
nobody else had ever come up with.
That Mr.Parr did not kill those children.
That Kyle Brody was actually a murderer.
Rustin Parr was tired of living
in the way he was living.
But I guess I've told you something
of what he told me in confession.
But he told me that he had killed no one.
Not just me. He told his God
that he had killed no one.
And I asked him, I said, let me
go to the judge for this story,
let me tell the people.
And he said, no, this is my confession.
You have no right to take it anywhere.
Kyle Brody is caught up in a situation that no
twelve year old should ever have to live through.
And I think that's what triggered some deep seated
illnesses that manifested itself later in life.
I think he lived in a world of his own.
who can say what goes on inside a person's head?
But perhaps that world got to be too much for him.
Kyle Brody he wasn't much older
than the kid that kept killed.
He was a kid himself.
He was mean. That's true.
I don't think he'd ever had
to stomach to kill those kids.
Searching for the truth is not an easy thing.
It's not something that most people want to face.
I have generally found that once people
set their mindson what has happened,
if you start offering them any sort of alternate idea,
especially if it's something that really goes against
this happy world that they've set up forthemselves,
you become hated for it.
Chris Carasco is a blooming fucking idiot.
He's just some bozo who is trying to
drum up publicity for himself,
with his preposterous hypothesis about
a very inflammatory subject, anyway.
I've talked to people that i
could that might have known Kyle.
People that would talk to me.
His sister won't have anything to do with
me after she found out my ankle.
Janine Brody has just closed herself up,
but i think she hasn't information
that would be very handy.
I would love to talk to her in an open, free way.
I guess I would like to see
Chris Carrasco and just deck him.
You can make what you want of it.
I don't tell you that,
This is absolutely what happened that.
This is the only way it could happen,
that this is God's honest truth.
I'm not saying that. All I'm offering
you is my viewpoint on it.
Do I think Kyle Brody is a killer?
Could be.
Kyle is simply was simply incapable
of doing violence to someone.
I mean, finally he did violence for himself.
I've looked at everything with an open mind.
I did not set myself on anything,
and I've gotten every fact I could.
And then i put them together into a hypothesis.
Now, you tell me anyone else that does it,
you introduce them to me,
you show me their material material,
and then I'll be happy to change my opinion.
Nobody else has done the work I've done.
You're welcome to go off and
think whatever you want.
I'm not telling you what to think,
but this is what I've come to
and this is a conclusion that i found.
That's it.
I do take them out and i do,
as I said, experimental pieces.
I'm not so much into storytelling
now as capturing imagery.
Some of it may be a little on the disturbing side.
Here's Rustin being hung on the gallows.
Nice close up.
Basically, I go out and I will capture images,
and occasionally annoy the hell out of people.
These are my babies.
This is an actual copy of the newsreel footage
announcing Rustin Parr's execution,
and going overthe testimony,
the court case as well.
This was extremely difficult to come across.
I have never felt that I've gone overboard on this.
And once you start looking into this and
getting a glimmer of what's going on here,
I findit really hard to turn myself away.
And it amazes me that these other people
don't want to find out more about this.
He's creating pain for these parents,
he's taking my brother's name
and fame, to put it mildly.
I can be touched by someone walking down the street,
to know one of those fabulous geeky guys
with penholders in their pockets,
and too many wallets and lumpy
pockets, and then you go,
oh, my God, they have the cards just to be who they are.
And then I think of that guy standing
in the corner, and it isn't voluntary.
He is that naked guy standing in the corner.
It's a human tendency to let sleeping
dogs lie, but his instincts are right.
It takes one to no one.
And this guy has a reason and a
need for finding this stuff out.
And if I can help him, I'm happy to do it.
I have gone to Burkittsville trying to
open up information on this,
trying to get newideas, trying to
interview some people.
They're not interested.
It took quite some time to get
some people to open up at all.
Some people never will.
Basically, you're trying to burst everyone's illusions,
and people don't take kindly to that.
But if you care about what you're doing,
if you believe in what you're
doing if you think you have
a shred of the truth in your hands,
you want to fill the hand up.
You just want to get more,
you need more information,
you need to find more and you hope to get
the truth out in the light of day.