[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[READING FOREIGN LANGUAGE TEXT]
- MAN: What the hell are you wearing?
- [CONTINUES READING]
MAN: You're not going
to the prom
MAN: dressed like a tramp!
GIRL: What?
You want me to wear my
communion dress?
I'm 18. You don't own me!
- I hate you!
- WOMAN: Watch your mouth, young lady!
Just shut up!
MAN: Well, if you're not
changing, you're not going!
-To Satan, giver of youth and
-GIRL: I'm not going to the prom
- happiness.
- GIRL: dressed like an old spinster!
- WOMAN: No, no, no!
- Come, almighty Eternal Devil.
WOMAN: No, no, no!
[SCREAMING]
[WATCH BEEPING]
RJ: [OVER RADIO]
NYC's top pop radio!
Hello New York!
What a beautiful day.
This one goes out to Jessie
from David who says,
"Let's make some
memories this weekend!"
[POP MUSIC PLAYING]
- [JESSIE LAUGHING]
- [DAVID GRUNTING]
Oh David, look!
An antique store!
- It looks cute! Come on, let's go, please?
- No, no.
What about the reservations?
We're running late already.
- The weather's getting bad.
- Are you serious?
- Come on.
- [SIGHS] Okay.
You're right.
Let's go antiquing.
- Yay! I love you!
- [CHUCKLES]
[DOORBELL CHIMING]
You know what?
This place is awesome.
I knew it would be worth it.
Oh wow.
This place is unbelievable.
I've never seen
anything like this.
[PHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
Oh, hello.
You know where I'll be.
Okay.
- Have fun.
- [PHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
I need to take some shots
for my blog anyways.
- I'm behind.
- Sure.
- [PHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
- I'll be here when you're done.
[METAL SCRAPES]
[FLOORBOARD CREAKING]
[1940'S MUSIC CROONS OVER]
[METAL SCRAPES]
[FLOORBOARD CREAKING]
[PHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
- Oh God!
- Hey... Hey Jessie.
It is you, isn't it?
I'm sorry, who are you?
Oh, I'm...
just one of your fans.
[JESSIE CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Wow.
Your...
Your skin is so beautiful.
You're even prettier in person.
- You're... [GASPS]
- Oh, please.
- Don't touch me.
- It's cool, it's cool. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I just... wanted to get a
picture with you?
For my blog?
- Oh, um...
- [SIGHS]
[FLOORBOARD CREAKING]
Please?
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, sure.
Cool, cool,
cool, cool. Come here.
- [PHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
- [CHUCKLES]
[FLOORBOARD CREAKING]
Hey. How's it going?
Good, good. There's some
cool stuff in here.
- Glad we stopped.
- [CHUCKLES]
Look at this.
It's sort of cute.
[CHUCKLES] -[TOY GRUNTS]
What is it?
I don't know.
Some 1920's creature.
Can you believe someone thought
this was like a great gift for a baby?
[CHUCKLES] Well, it sure explains
why my parents are so dysfunctional.
- Hmm.
- Oh!
I think I'll take a pic with this
and send it out to all my crazy fans.
[PHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
- [PHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
- You know what?
I hate it when you do that.
I don't like having my face
plastered all over the internet.
Especially not with that thing.
It's a toy, David.
I mean, I'm posting it as a
part of my vacation for my fans.
Come on, after all,
you are the love of my life.
Yeah, well,
I love you too, baby.
But that thing is horrible!
- Let's hit the road, huh?
- Okay.
[DAVID SIGHS]
You okay?
I'm sorry.
Hm? I didn't mean to
explode at you. I just...
I just...
I detest the whole
social media thing.
And I hate selfies.
That's not it.
It's something else.
Well, what?
There was this guy
at the antique mall.
He came up behind me
and scared me.
What the fuck?
Said he recognized me,
was a fan.
Just wanted a photo with me,
but he... touched me.
God, you know I hate when
strangers touch me.
So, go on.
Well, he took the photo
and just vanished.
I mean, he just disappeared.
Really creeped me out.
You see, Jessie?
That's what I'm talking about.
If you post your
entire life on social media,
I mean, [CHUCKLES] you have
to expect that you're gonna get
some creepy guys following you.
Literally, doing God
know what with your photo.
Oh, Jessie! Oh, my God!
- God, you're such a jerk!
- Ow!
I'm sorry.
[CHUCKLES]
You'll be okay.
[RADIO SPUTTERING]
Where's the entrance to this highway?
It's gotta be around here somewhere.
I can see, it's right there!
- Goddamn it! This is not the highway!
- [HORNS HONKING]
What? We're going
to be late for our reservation.
You know how funny
these B&B people can get.
And you know what? I don't wanna
get stuck in some cramped room.
Can you call them?
God! You know,
you need to chill.
- Yeah.
- So what if we're late?
- They charged my credit card in advance anyways.
- Yeah.
- You're right.
- I know! David, my favorite!
["OUTLAW" BY SHANE PATRICK
PLAYS OVER RADIO]
Yeah, uh-huh.
♪ Your hands on the wheel
♪ Driving like it's stolen And
ya don't know Where you're going
♪ But you know that you feel
♪ Like an outlaw ♪
- DAVID: It's a good song.
- JESSIE: Oh, hell yeah!
Oh! Got it! It's the tractor
on the yellow road sign!
How are you so good at this?
Okay, my turn. Hmm...
- I'm gonna make this tough.
- Great.
Okay. I spy something red.
Well, it better not be a cop pulling us
over. I'm driving way over the speed limit.
- Oh, it's that barn over there?
- Oh, you are so cold.
Um... Is it your car?
No, but you're getting warmer.
- Here, I'll give you a hint.
- Okay.
Take a peek.
Oh, my God.
- [PHONE CAMERA CLICKING]
- Babe, stop doing that.
Don't be such a grouch.
[CHUCKLES]
- [WINDOW OPENING]
- Jessie.
- What are you doing? Would you stop doing that?
- What?
[PHONE CAMERA CLICKING]
Oh, fuck! Shit!
JESSIE: My phone!
- Uh, we're gonna have to pull over.
- Great.
I don't fucking believe this.
How the hell did this get here?
Jessie! What are you doing?
My phone! It's ruined!
God, now what?
[WHISPERS]
Thank God.
Wait, what is that?
- Is that the thing from the antique mall?
- Yeah.
- Well, get it out of my tire!
- I don't want to touch it!
I'll just leave it stuck in
there. I'll put on the spare.
Oh, David? I got a flat a while
back and I used the spare.
- I guess I forgot about getting a new one.
- Okay.
Do you have roadside coverage?
You can use my phone?
No. But if you get
this thing out of my tire,
we can drive
to a service station.
Well, I don't know how far
we can get with a flat tire.
It's fine. Just get it out of my
tire, all right? I hate this area.
Oh, I'm taking it.
What? I want to
know how it got there!
[DAVID SIGHS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
JESSIE:
This place is a ghost town.
DAVID: Jess, I'm afraid
the axle is gonna break.
Let's just park and find
a place to stay.
[DAVID CHUCKLES]
Look at this building.
It could be right out of France.
JESSIE:
You mean hotel.
DAVID: Huh?
This building that you're
drooling over instead of me?
- Yeah?
- Yeah, it's a hotel.
There's a sign. See?
Well, let's get our overnights.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
It says use the back entrance.
I guess this place
is called Monroe Manor.
Oh! Pretty and smart.
Well, someone has to be the
brains behind this outfit.
Well then, Einstein,
let's follow the arrows.
I know you're pissed off but
this could be fun, right?
A little adventure,
spontaneous, excitement.
I'd rather be in Saratoga.
[TRAP DOOR CLOSES]
- Norman!
- [DOOR CREAKING]
- Norman are you home?
- Okay, that's not funny.
[DAVID LAUGHS]
DAVID: Huh.
- [BELL DINGS]
- Jeez! Don't do that.
God, this place gives
me the creeps.
Yeah, but I like
the architecture in here.
I'll have to ask about it and take some
photos before the partners meeting next week.
Yes, yes!
This building is a gem.
It was constructed
in 1898 as the City Hall.
But then the owner's family
purchased it in 1982 and did renovations.
But then...
Plans changed.
Things happened.
But no worries!
I am Salim.
Welcome to Monroe Manor.
Well, hi, Salim. I'm David
Bradley, and this is Jessie.
Now we're broken down
out the front with a flat tire,
no spare, so we need
a place to stay.
Flat and no spare.
Hmm.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Well, bad storm's blowing in
tonight. Town is shutting up early.
You're gonna have to deal
with that tomorrow morning.
Lucky for you, I do have a
vacancy in one of our best suites.
And our chef is serving
dinner until 9 P.M.
Place seems pretty dead.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
[CHUCKLES]
There are other
guests here, Jessie.
It's just there have been so many
cancellations due to the bad weather.
And as you can see,
we are short-staffed.
But don't worry about
any of that, all right?
Tonight, you and David will
have me at your service.
So, all I need from you is,
if you could just...
...sign the guest register.
Don't you just
swipe a card or something?
Oh, no.
We do things
the old fashioned way here.
I just need your name,
an address and a phone number,
and just a hundred dollars,
cash only.
- Just to cover the meal and drinks.
- [DAVID SIGHS]
Jeez, I don't even know if I have
200 cash. Baby, do you have any?
- I know you were gonna do some shopping.
- I guess so.
No, I'm so sorry. I mean a
hundred dollars for both of you.
DAVID: Oh!
Okay.
DAVID: Ah.
DAVID: Here you go.
That seals the deal.
Follow me.
Let me show you to your room.
Now, you best stick close to me because
Monroe Manor has many twists and turns.
It's easy to get lost
around here.
It does seem
a little odd in here,
but hey,
I love the architecture!
It's his job.
He just made partner.
Oh, congratulations!
That's great news.
And how about you, Miss Jessie?
Let me guess.
You're a model?
Yeah.
Hey, so that's a relic.
Is it original?
I see all the kids
are wearing them these days?
Oh yes, this was a present
from Mr. Monroe himself.
It keeps excellent time.
- [ELEVATOR DINGS]
- [ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS]
Well...
Our chariot awaits.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Here we are.
I believe that you'll find
your stay here most rewarding.
- Oh really?
- Mm-hmm.
Aha! Here it is.
Room 409.
Our most romantic suite.
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
Wow.
Oh yes. It has the most lovely
view of the courthouse.
Oh!
Babe, look at this building.
Jessie, it's a classic.
SALIM: Oh, yes, yes, yes,
everything here is vintage.
Oh come on, babe.
Look at the bright side.
You love antiques.
[CHUCKLES]
I hope this place
doesn't have black mold.
Mm-hmm.
JESSIE: Oh,
let me have your phone.
I better call Saratoga and let them know
we'll be there by, what? 11 tomorrow?
Yeah, good idea.
[LINE RINGING]
AUTOMATED VOICE: We're
sorry, all circuits are busy now.
All circuits are busy? What?
I don't know,
maybe the weather's bad?
Looks like there's
a storm brewing.
Do feel free to stop by the
lobby before you go to dinner.
The restaurant can be
rather difficult to find.
Okay.
Thanks, Salim.
- [DAVID GRUNTS]
- [BED CREAKING]
JESSIE: Babe?
Can you bring me my shampoo?
I forgot it on the table.
Found it!
Um...
It's locked.
No, I left the door unlocked.
What's going on?
- Well, I don't know what to tell you, it's locked.
- What's going on?
David, what's going on?
Seriously. Open the door!
Babe, just hold on for a second.
It might be jammed.
David, open the fucking door!
Ow!
This better not be
one of your tricks,
- David Bradley.
- No no! It wasn't me!
You know I hate
being locked in anywhere.
The door was jammed, I told you.
I got your shampoo.
DAVID: Hmm?
Oh.
[DAVID CHUCKLES]
DAVID: Oh.
Hey, I've got an idea.
How about I shampoo your hair?
[SIGHS]
- JESSIE: David?
- Hm?
- Could you zip me up?
- Oh.
With pleasure.
- Come on. It's a mistake.
- [DAVID MOANING]
You smell so good.
Hmm, you look stunning tonight.
Just wait till tonight.
[KNIFE CLATTERS]
[FAUCET SQUEAKS]
- Oh! Cheeky thing.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
- Oh. He's cute.
This guy? Leroy Barnes?
[CAMERA PHONE CLICKING]
- DAVID: He's a lucky guy.
- [CAMERA PHONE CLICKING]
One with me.
- [DAVID EXCLAIMS]
[DAVID LAUGHS]
- You don't even have service.
- Your camera works.
I'll post it later.
- I bet you will.
- [ELEVATOR DINGS]
[ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS]
[MAN SIGHS, WINCES]
Gotta get this chapter done.
[GROANS EXHAUSTEDLY]
Oh, I need coffee.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[SIGHS IN EXASPERATION]
[GROANS]
Fresh coffee.
[WINCES]
Oh, I gotta get this
chapter done tonight.
[DAVID CHUCKLES]
- Oh!
- [JESSIE GASPS]
[SALIM CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I've been expecting you.
Come. We should get going.
Chef Linda closes the kitchen
promptly at 9 O'clock.
Yeah. You mentioned that.
I imagine this was once
quite a uh, a grand City Hall,
and I guess the Monroe family
was very fortunate to obtain it.
Oh, yes, yes.
They're a very wealthy family.
They did their
best renovations here.
Interesting. Oh, actually,
that reminds me,
today we had a bit
of an incident in the bathroom.
See, the door got jammed,
and uh, well, Jessie got locked in.
Oh. Oh, I'm...
I'm sorry. I'm...
I'm so sorry.
I will tell Mr. Monroe.
Well, thank you.
Yeah, Jessie normally never locks
the door, so it was a little upsetting.
If you know what I mean.
No worries.
Old doorways and locks,
they tend to act out
when it gets damp.
Oh, it's okay, Salim.
We worked it out.
- DAVID: Hey Salim, wait up.
- BOY: One.
- DAVID: I have a question.
- Two.
Three, four, five, six.
[CHUCKLES]
[SALIM'S WATCH BEEPS]
Hot date, Salim?
No. Not exactly.
I just have to tend to
another visitor. But please.
Take a seat.
- JESSIE: Thank you.
- [CHAIR SQUEAKS]
Well...
Chef Linda will be
down in just a moment.
Thank you.
- I think he...
- [BOTH LAUGH]
What's with the plastic watch?
It's so annoying!
I know. He's an odd one.
Did I mention how beautiful
you look tonight?
[TYPEWRITER CLACKING]
MAN: Good time.
[CHAIR BEING DRAGGED]
[CHAIR FALLS OVER]
[NECK CRACKING]
[BODY SWAYING]
[TYPEWRITER CLICKING]
So, this guy continues to tell
me for, like, an hour about how
Frank Lloyd Wright
is the greatest of all time.
I said, " How could you say that if you've
never been to Barcelona to see Galvany?"
Good evening, I'm Chef Linda.
Tonight's menu is prime rib and
baked potato,
and pineapple upside down cake
for dessert.
Oh, um. No, I'm a vegetarian.
David! She just ignored me.
I mean, I have barely eaten
anything today.
I mean, I'm sure she heard you.
It's okay. You won't starve.
Are you saying I'm fat?
You know I have to look good
for my blog.
No, I'm just saying that I'm sure she heard
you and that she'll bring you some food.
So relax,
and enjoy this lovely room.
[DISTANT THUNDER]
Mmm, baby.
It looks like you
have another admirer.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
God, David, don't be gross.
Well, that's what you get when
you put yourself on social media.
Well,
you have a better suggestions?
Yeah,
I could think of a few things.
Yeah, I'd share wine...
- Compliments of the house.
- Ahh! Thank you!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[WATCH BEEPING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Enjoy.
With my deepest apologies for
being understaffed this evening,
and for that mishap
with the bathroom door.
Eugene Monroe.
Welcome to Monroe Manor.
Yeah, thanks.
We love this place.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Well,
enjoy your stay.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Father Bet an court.
Thanks for taking care
of our little lady.
- [EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GUITAR PLAYING]
[MAN SINGING]
♪ Whispering in my ear ♪
[GUITAR PLAYING]
Not bad.
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Ow! Damn!
God, this place sucks.
It's just one night.
Hey,
I can share my steak with you.
- Oh, God. No, no, no.
- DAVID: Just a little steak-ie?
- David: No?
- JESS: Stop.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
GIRL: One, two, three.
[MAN TALKING IN BACKGROUND]
[BOY TALKING]
Three.
One, two, three.
Two, three, four, five.
- Hey, you cheated!
- No, you're a liar!
I saw you cheat! I hate you!
- [STABBING SOUNDS]
- [YOUNGER BOY SCREAMS]
[WATCH BEEPS]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
God damn it, Linda!
You forgot to serve dessert.
[WATCH BEEPS]
Wait.
Something's terribly off here.
All the loops are off.
Yummy time.
I am sorry for the delay.
Chef Linda, she always closes
the kitchen promptly at 9 p.m.
Oh, where is the chef?
I want to thank her
for my baked potato.
DAVID: Jess!
I'm sorry.
- It has been such great service.
- DAVID: I know, right?
You know what? Fuck it, I'm
not counting calories tonight.
Perhaps I can interest you
in some port.
Would you be interested
in some port?
We have some 1980s
vintage port from Portugal.
Oh! More vintage.
Thank... thank... thank you,
Salim. This is...
This is delicious.
Thank you.
Have a good night.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Cheers.
Jess, come on.
We'll have more fun tomorrow,
hmm?
How about we, uh,
take some photos, eh?
- Show you fans how much fun you're having?
- [PHONE CAMERA CLICKS]
The only good thing
about this place is the booze.
You know what?
This tastes pretty good.
Try some.
Come on.
- Hmm.
- Mmm.
Delicious.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh. Vintage lights too?
- JESS: How charming.
- Now what?
No power?
Oh, come one, David.
It's romantic.
Did you plan this all
for a reason?
Huh? No. No. This sucks.
He must not have stayed
for dessert.
What? Who?
The cowboy and his pony.
God, you're so disgusting.
Hey,
I'm sorry I dragged you here.
I mean...
you deserve better than this.
David, I know I'm being a bitch,
but I just...
you know what look, I'm sorry.
I know you're trying to make
the best of the situation.
That's my girl.
I am sorry to break the mood,
but we have the elevator running
right now.
But I don't know how long
the generator will last,
so I'll have to ask you
to follow me.
Now.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT TALKING]
- [CHILDREN SCREAMING]
- [STABBING SOUNDS]
Oh, my God. David!
Hurry.
- JESS: The kids! They're dead!
- Hey, hey. What?
DAVID: What's wrong?
SALIM: Miss. Jessie, please,
calm down. There's nobody here.
My children went to bed
when you were having dinner.
Yeah, Salim's right. There's
no one in there. It's okay.
JESS: Your kids are here?
Isn't it late?
Yes, well, we've lived here...
since my wife passed away.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm so sorry.
DAVID: Too much port, huh?
No, no. I saw them. I saw them.
DAVID: I think she just needs
some sleep.
Yes, we must hurry.
We must hurry. Come, come.
- DAVID: Grab her bag.
- SALIM: Yes, yes.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
Go to sleep.
[WOMAN HUMMING]
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYS]
[CONTINUES HUMMING]
[SPEAKING IN LATIN]
- GIRL: I'm not going to the prom dressed like a...
- [INDISTINCT VOICES]
- GIRL: I hate you!
- WOMAN: Watch you mouth, young lady.
[KNIFE SLASHING]
- WOMAN: No! No!
[SCREAMING]
[KNIFE FALLS]
Oh, um, I'm sorry to
disturb you, sir, but...
We have a problem.
- All the loops are off.
- That's your fault.
I told you just the girl.
But... I thought you said
you wanted both of them.
- Eugene, what about my children?
- It's too late.
You have empowered the demon.
Now, we've got to work fast
before all hell breaks loose.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WALKING DOWN THE STAIRS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
What have I done?
[SHOWER RUNNING]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN HUMMING]
Jessie?
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
Gotta get this done.
Gotta get this chapter done.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
I need coffee.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BETANCOURT SCREAMS]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll see you in hell.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
What the fuck? Ahhh, God!
What the fuck? What is this?
Get the fuck...
Jessie!
Jessie.
Fuck.
Jessie!
Oh, my God!
Fuck!
Oh!
Baby, we gotta get outta here.
I'm serious. We have to leave.
Now.
Jessie?
[STATIC OVER THE PHONE]
Jessie? I'm serious,
we have to go. Baby?
Fuck.
[ACTION MUSIC PLAYING]
Baby?
Wake up!
Jess!
All right,
I'll be back in a minute, okay?
- Oh, fuck!
- [DOOR LOCKS]
God! Jess!
Okay.
What the hell is going on?
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Salim?
Salim!
Salim, We got a problem here!
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey! Your showers are spitting
out black shit, man!
Salim?
What the fuck?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, God!
[HIGH TENSION MUSIC PLAYING]
You... you okay?
Fuck.
Salim!
Fuck!
- [THUNDER BOOMS]
- [GASPING]
[JESS VOMITS]
[JESS GASPING]
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Hey. Hey old man, um,
have you seen Salim around?
Because uh, uh, Linda,
Linda the Chef, um...
I was just in the kitchen and
she was lying on the ground, and...
she... she's dead!
You hear what I'm saying?
She's fucking dead!
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
All right, well...
I don't normally drink
this stuff, but I'm...
I'll be honest with you,
I'm having a bit of a bad night.
I mean, my fiance,
she's all pissed off at me.
There's this... this black goo that
keeps shooting out of the shower.
I mean what the fuck is the deal
with all the black goo around here?
Were you listening when I
told you that the chef is dead?
MAN: I'm listenin'.
Take care of your little lady.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Jesus.
No thanks for your help, buddy.
I guess you stay here long
enough, you become an alcoholic.
- [WOMAN HUMMING]
- Salim?
Salim, is that you?
Fuck you, Salim. Just fuck you!
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[STATIC OVER THE PHONE]
Damn!
Nothing in this place works!
[SOOTHING MUSIC PLAYING]
David! Salim!
Open the damn door!
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
Shit.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Soon as I saw it,
I knew she was something
special.
[DOOR OPENS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I didn't expect to see you here.
How can I help you?
Who was that?
He gave you money?
It was a... a tow truck driver that I...
I... I hired to get rid of the evidence.
- He called me earlier.
- Really? Why did you sell the car?
Well, I thought that if we were
using the owners
to help get my children's souls
back, then we could...
Give me the cash.
We've got bigger problems. Look.
SALIM: What?
How is this possible? Wait.
Wait. Let me rewind it.
EUGENE: I locked David and Jessie
in their room. We'll deal with them later.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
DAVID: Salim?
- He's out.
- DAVID: Salim, is that you?
That's impossible.
[WOMAN HUMMING]
Humming?
Find him.
I'm getting Jessie.
[WOMAN HUMMING]
DAVID: Salim?
Is that you?
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[WOMAN HUMMING]
DAVID: Who are you?
Are you okay?
[SOOTHING MUSIC PLAYING]
Come play with us, David.
[GASPING]
[INDISTINCT VOICE]
- Who's that?
- Just me, Rohan.
- Salim's dead son.
- DEV: And me.
Dev. Don't you wanna come
and play with us?
Emma likes to play too.
David.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Thank God you're here!
David's missing and there's
black shit all over the bathroom.
Now, now, Miss Jessie. This is an
old hotel, we don't get many guests.
That's just rust from old pipes.
Yeah, no,
rust is not black and gross!
Don't be worried, all right? Why
don't you and I look for David.
I have a flashlight. The
halls are dim from the storm.
- DAVID: Help!
- Wait, did you hear that?
That's David!
Come on we have to go!
DAVID: Help me.
Help me.
Help.
She killed us.
DAVID: Jessie!
Jess.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Help! Help! Help!
Help!
[CHILDREN GIGGLE]
Jessie!
[WOMAN LAUGHING]
DAVID: Jessie!
Jessie, I really need you!
Help me.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[TYPEWRITER CLICKING]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Shit.
I don't have the time for this.
[PHONE DIALING]
Come on, Salim.
Answer the God damn phone!
[PHONE DIALING]
Where the fuck are you?
Uh...
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on.
No. No, no! No, Thomas,
don't do that!
[BODY SWAYING]
[TYPEWRITER CLICKING]
I need coffee.
What is going on?
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
JESS: Hmm.
- JESS: Hmm.
- EUGENE: All right, take it easy.
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[EUGENE GRUNTS]
EUGENE: Ah, okay.
Okay.
All right.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[ELEVATOR DOOR CLOSES]
[JESS WHIMPERS]
[JESS CRYING]
[SPEAKING IN LATIN]
- [SPEAKING IN LATIN]
- [JESS CRYING]
[GRUNTS]
You must smell it.
It's magical. It's pachouli.
It's magical.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Oh, hey Salim!
What the fuck is going on here,
man?
You see me covered in this black
goo from your lousy showers? Huh?
Or what about Chef Linda?
She's dead! Up in the kitchen!
Did you know that?
Or what about Thomas?
Thomas, the guy that likes
to hang himself in front of me!
- Hands up, chap.
- Whoa.
I owe you no explanation.
- Okay.
- You signed the guest register.
What the fuck?
Here ya go.
That seals the deal.
No.
You're crazy.
Aren't we all a little insane?
[SALIM'S WATCH BEEPS]
[GRUNTS OF PAIN]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I wanna fix your hair.
Don't touch me!
Where's David?
David! Help!
Help me! Help me!
David?
Oh, he's not here!
You won't be seeing
David anymore.
[WATCH BEEPS]
What now? Salim!
[GROANS]
Jessie?
[DOOR CREAKS AND SHUTS]
[SNORES]
Baby. Baby, we...
We gotta get outta here.
Baby. Wake up!
We have to get out of here.
You hear me?
Hey. I love you.
And I know this trip
hasn't gone to plan.
But I promise I'll make it up
to you, okay?
Baby?
Jessie?
What the fuck?
Jessie, weren't you just...
Jess! Fuck!
[PANTING]
[WATCH BEEPS]
I'm sorry, Thomas.
You're on your own now.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CUTLERY CLANKING]
What the hell are you wearing?
What?
You're not going to the prom
dressed like a tramp?
What? Do you want me
to wear my communion dress?
I'm 18. You don't own me!
I hate you!
Watch your mouth, young lady!
That's not the dress I bought for you!
Take a chill pill, Mom!
Everyone will laugh at me
if I wear that thing!
Well, if you're not changing,
you're not going!
No! No! No! No!
I'm not going to the prom
dressed like an old spinster!
[DEMONIC LAUGHTER]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
No! Emma! No!
[SCREAMS]
[WATCH BEEPS]
What the fuck is going on here,
Eugene?
Where's Jessie?
And who is this crazy girl
following me?
It's my twin sister, Emma.
Bring him to the Lobby. Please.
Eugene?
I have him here. Eugene?
Where are you?
Eugene?
- [GUN CLICKS]
- Eugene? Eugene?
What the fuck did you do with
Jessie?
[GUN FIRES]
I hope that idiot
didn't kill him.
[SCREAMS OF PAIN]
Fuck! You fucking shot me!
What the fuck? [GROANS]
God damn!
Fuck! What the fuck
is your problem?
Eugene?
Good. He's not dead yet.
David, if you ever want to see
Jessie again,
I suggest you drag yourself
over here.
What is this?
What's going on?
This is my private space.
You think Bet an court could keep
Emma controlled with just drugs?
He had help...
From me.
Where's Jessie?
I need to see her.
Keep the gun on him, Salim.
He's a strong one.
- Jessie...
- Shut up! This will be over soon enough.
[GRUNTING]
Move! Move!
All right!
[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
What are you doing down here?
- It smells like death.
- None of your business.
Now, tie him up.
[MUFFLED] No! No!
He's bleeding!
Will you shut up?
Don't you understand you're
making things worse for yourself?
That the demon inside of Emma
gets stronger with anger.
It will kill you in a heartbeat
and suck out your soul.
[COUGHING]
Ah, fuck!
Hey. Jessie!
Fuck man. It's gonna be okay.
I... I got it under control.
Ow! Okay.
[SNIFFS]
Oh poor Bet an court.
I'm gonna miss
these excellent powders.
What is your problem, princess?
Don't you want eternal life?
It's simple.
See, I give you to the beast.
And he gives me back
my precious sister.
Now we get out of this hotel
and you get to stay... Forever!
[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
[LAUGHS]
It's not that bad!
It's really not.
It's really not that bad!
[DISTANT HUMMING]
What about my children?
What about Rohan and Dev?
I only brought these two
down here
so you could sacrifice them
for my children.
Your children are dead, Salim.
You're a fool, Salim.
This has always been about Emma.
You promised me!
I stayed here
and managed these dead souls!
Relived their lives
over and over again!
I've had to watch my own
children die, day after day!
And now you're telling me there is
no demon, there's just your sister?
You owe me!
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[GROANING]
[HUMMING]
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[GUN COCKS] -Stop,
Eugene! You can't do this!
[JESSIE WHIMPERS]
Come, Daddy!
We're happy here!
Come play with us forever!
[GUN FIRES]
No! You've wasted 30 years!
[GAGGING]
[DEMONIC LAUGHTER]
Emma!
Sweet little Emma.
Forever a child.
Please forgive me.
I love you!
[SCREAMS]
[GROANS]
Die!
[GROANING]
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Jessie. Jessie!
You gotta get outta here, baby!
I'm gonna find help, okay?
It's going to be okay.
Baby...
I don't think
I'm gonna make it outta here.
No, it's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
[SOBBING] I love you.
I love you too!
Look, I love you too.
Take my phone, so maybe...
- maybe it will work and you can get help.
- I'm gonna get some help.
You's gonna be okay, right?
I'm gonna get help, okay?
I'll be back as soon as I can.
You're gonna be okay, yeah?
Goodbye, baby.
[WHIMPERS]
FEMALE VOICE: The number you've
reached- -Oh, you're freakin' useless!
Help!
Where's my car? Shit!
It's going to be okay?
I'll be back soon, okay?
I gotta find help.
[CAR HONKS]
Wait! Stop! Please help! Stop!
Thank you. I need your help.
Do you have a phone?
I need to call the police.
I hope you're not one of those drunk college
students that throws up in my back seat.
You puke, it's a $100 cash fee.
No, no, no! I'm not drunk.
I need the police!
My boyfriend has just been shot!
Well, I don't have my phone
with me,
but I can take you
to the police station.
You okay?
You look like
someone tried to hurt you.
Please, just take me
to the police station. Go!
Jeez. Just trying to be polite.
Wait. wait.
Do you have to go down there?
Yes.
Where did you get that?
That was in my car!
Hey!
Your car?
- What the hell is going on?
- [DRIVER LAUGHS] Why?
Wanna take a selfie, Jessie?
Oh, my...
Oh, my God!
Oh! So now you wanna play hard
to get?
This is gonna be fun.
[YELLS]
Look at that girl run!
Good thing I got
my runnin' boots on!
I'm coming for you, Jessie!
[DOOR OPENS]
[PANTING]
Asshole!
JESSIE: David?
[SHOUTS] David! Where are you?
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
Where you going, Jessie?
Wanna play hide and seek,
do you?
JESSIE: David, where are you?
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Damn it, Jessie!
Why are you such a bitch?
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Go to hell, you son of a bitch.
David!
David?
[SCREAMS]
What are you doing here?
Wait.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
- David? David!
- DAVID: I'm up here at the bar!
Oh, my God.
David. I can't believe
I found you!
I love you.
Okay come on, we have to go.
You don't look so good.
Come on, let's sit down.
Let's make a toast, hmm?
To our victory.
[DRINK POURING]
Cheers.
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to drink up?
Come on.
Up, up, up, drink, drink!
No! No! I'm not
in the mood for whiskey!
I mean you have no idea what
I've been through since I left for help!
That stalker guy from the
antique store stole my car
and took that creepy furry thing
with him.
I mean, he picked me up in a fake
taxi and is in here trying to hurt me.
Didn't you hear him?
He's crazy!
No, I'm sorry. I can't say
that I heard anything.
I've been a little busy myself,
dealing with dead kids tormenting me,
and that dead guy Thomas,
he hangs himself in front of me,
and then I crawl to the elevator
and back to our room.
I'm sorry but I...
oh no no no...
[SOBBING]
There you are.
[GRUNTS]
And who's this?
I thought you said that your
boyfriend was shot and dying?
Did you lie to me, Jessie?
Or is he one of the dead bodies
in the basement?
Now, now. Be nice.
I was shot,
but I'm feeling much better now.
I think Jessie just over-reacted
when she saw so much blood.
Jessie, Jessie, how many times
do I have to tell you
the dangers of
too much online exposure?
David!
[LAUGHS]
No more exposure
when I'm through with you.
Apologize to her!
[DEMONIC] Now.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm really sorry.
I love Jessie.
I think she's so pretty.
And smart and funny.
And she was nice to me
when I was a total creep.
I'm really sorry,
it was a huge misunderstanding.
- I won't do it again.
- Shh. It's okay.
I'm sorry, Jessie.
[NECK CRACKS]
[KNOCKING]
What's wrong, Jessie?
I thought that you loved me.
I was gonna propose to you.
But when I got back to our room,
the ring was gone.
Any idea where it went?
No, David. I have no clue.
What's wrong with you?
[MOCKING]
"What's wrong with you?"
Stop, David!
[DAVID CHUCKLES]
Come here, Jessie.
[DEMONIC] Come here, Jessie.
Stay with me.
And we can live.
Here!
Forever.
Hmm?
[SCREAMS]
[GUN FIRES]
David. I'm so sorry.
David.
[CRYING]
David. I'm so sorry...
[CRYING CEASES]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[POP MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE ROARS]