FEMALE NARRATOR: There is
a charming tradition
observed by the Adelie penguins.
Once a year, during the mating season,
all the male birds gather
on the Antarctic beaches,
and there,
each selects an extraordinary pebble.
With pebble in hand,
each male presents his precious gift
to the lady he most desires.
If she accepts it, they mate for life.
(NOW AND FOREVER PLAYING)
(NOW AND FOREVER
CONTINUES PLAYING)
Hey. How about you, Hubie?
You got a pebble for your girl?
Well, you know, it's...
Not really.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, this is all just so exciting.
- It's so romantic.
- Knock it off.
Romance has nothing to do with it.
Listen.
You know, I don't think a pebble
should be that important.
Marina, if you don't care about
the pebble, how will you choose?
How will you know if it's Mr. Right?
(MARINA SINGING)
WOW!
FEMALE NARRATOR: Of all the penguins
in all the world,
the most romantic was Hubie.
He had a secret love in his life,
Marina, the most beautiful
girl penguin in the rookery.
- Hi, Hubie. Tell us a story.
- Yes. A love story.
Oh, that's mushy stuff.
Oh, Beany!
Well, once there was a penguin
who fell in love
with the most beautiful girl penguin
in the whole rookery.
- Did she love him back?
- They never even met.
You see, he was painfully shy.
Well, one day,
he just swam up to her and said,
"Hello, Marina.
I'm Hubie, and I think you're fabulous."
(ALL LAUGHING)
(SIGHING)
Who am I kidding?
(STUTTERING) I mean,
I never even talked to the girl.
(SCREAMING)
(STUTTERING) Goodness glaciers!
Marina!
(CHUCKLING)
So, it wasn't an avalanche.
That was some landing, Hubie.
(HUBIE GROANS)
(HUBIE STUTTERING) I'm sorry, Marina.
I'm just so clumsy.
MARINA: Oh, don't be silly, Hubie.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
FEMALE NARRATOR: But someone else
had his eye on the fair Marina.
Drake, an evil penguin
who always got his way.
That little wimp.
I'll knock the stutter right out of him.
Marina doesn't know it yet,
but she's going to be my wife.
Our children will be the strongest,
the smartest, the bravest,
not to mention the best looking.
Why, they'll be just like me.
(LAUGHING)
(GROWLING)
I'm telling you, boys,
Marina is as good as mine.
MARINA: This is quite a spot, Hubie.
What do you do up here?
Well...
(STUTTERING) ...I wonder about stuff.
Stuff? What kind of stuff?
I just... No. You'd think it was silly.
I bet it's not silly at all. Try me.
(SINGING SOMETIMES I WONDER)
(GASPING)
I'm sorry.
Go on.
- Oh, where was I?
- "Choosing brides."
(STUTTERING)
You must be bored to tears
with all this wacky nonsense.
Oh, no. I don't think it's nonsense
at all, even if you are a bit wacky.
NARRATOR: The full moon mating
ceremony was fast approaching.
The rookery buzzed with excitement.
All the bachelors took to the beaches
to find their engagement pebbles.
And none was more determined
than Hubie.
He dove, scrambled, scrapped
and raced against the best of them.
But try as he might,
- Hubie couldn't hold on...
- It's mine.
...to a single pebble.
(PANTING)
I've nothing.
NARRATOR: Poor Hubie.
With the day almost done,
and the beach picked clean
of the best engagement stones,
how could he ever hope
to find the perfect pebble
for his perfect love, Marina?
"Star light, star bright
First star I see tonight
Wish I may, wish I might
Have the wish I wish tonight."
(HUMMING)
(GASPS)
Wow.
Oh, my-
It's perfect.
Marina! Has anyone seen Marina?
I got to find her.
I just got to find her.
Wait till she sees this. It's perfect.
Perfect!
MALE PENGUIN:
Hey, what's the holdup?
Somebody saw a leopard seal.
Oh, not today. I'm starving.
So, nerd.
I hear you want to be a big ladies' man.
Marina is mine.
You big bully!
Wake up and smell the seaweed,
you little fool.
Nobody's going to
marry a loser like you.
- Now give me that stupid pebble.
- No, it's for Marina.
(LAUGHS)
Hope you can swim
better than you can talk.
Bye, Hubie. Sleep with the fishes.
(SCREAMING)
(DRAKE LAUGHING)
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, look. The water's safe.
- Let's eat.
- Oh, boy.
Hubie!
(SCREAMS)
(PANTS)
MARINA: Hubie!
HUBIE: Marina!
FEMALE NARRATOR: Huddled against
the wind and buffeted by the storm,
Hubie was swept far away
to warmer waters
where there lived an enemy
even greater than the leopard seal.
Man.
FEMALE PENGUIN: So sweet.
MALE PENGUIN: Oh, look.
I think he's coming around.
Welcome back, lad.
Where am I?
You're aboard the good ship Misery.
You've been sleeping
for nearly three days now.
Three days?
I've been asleep for three days?
I'm sure Marina
thinks I'm lost forever.
Marina?
My girl back home.
(CHUCKLING)
Why, you're our first Adélie.
- What's your name?
- Yes. Yes. What's your name?
I'm Hubie.
Welcome aboard, Hubie.
Although, "welcome"
probably isn't the appropriate word.
- Outrage! That's the appropriate word.
- Yes.
Abomination.
- The indignity.
The horror.
(SINGING THE GOOD SHIP MISERY)
Just thought I'd ask.
MAN: Get a hold of them feet.
Here come the boots.
- The boots!
(ALL CLAMORING)
MAN: Be quiet down there.
Blast it all, mate.
Let's get him down below.
Open the door, man. Open the door.
Hold still, lad,
or I'll give you a fist in the beak.
Now get in there and stay there.
Come back here,
you yellow-bellied landlubbers.
Take a breather, laddie.
That door will be there later.
I can promise you that.
Save it, old-timer.
Nobody locks up Rocko the Rockhopper.
Those humans just did.
(LAUGHING)
Hey. When I get out of here,
you're seal bait.
What are you staring at, birdbrain?
That's Hubie, and he's heartbroken.
Yes. He was snatched away
from the lady he loves.
Poor, poor pebblehead.
If he had any guts, he never
would've let them take him alive.
So, where is this floating scrapheap
headed, anyway?
Our destination would be
difficult to determine at this juncture.
- That means he doesn't know.
Well, we be in warm waters.
We be in Bora Bora, Pops.
I know where we are. Where do we dock?
That's what I'm asking.
Where do we dock?
We can't say for sure, lad,
but I've heard stories
of sailors selling penguins to zoos.
- Zoos?
- Zoos? I'm not going to no zoo.
No, no. I'm going to the helmsman.
I'll go to the first mate.
I'll go all the way to the captain
of this oversized dinghy.
I'll make him turn this tug around
if I have to.
But I can't go to a zoo.
I've got to get back to Antarctica.
Who's with me?
Who's for busting out of here?
Come on, you jellyfish.
How about you, seal bait? You?
Sorry, Mr. Rockhopper, but free food
at the zoo sounds awful good to me.
ROCKO: Bunch of birdbrains and
seal bait. Get me out of here!
Get me somebody!
WOMAN 1: Marina, Hubie is gone.
Face it. Forget him.
WOMAN 2: Why don't you
just marry Drake?
MARINA: No, Priscilla.
I believe Hubie
is still out there somewhere,
and he'll come home to me in time
for the full moon mating ceremony.
- You're saying you want to marry him?
- I do.
How could you possibly choose a wimp
like Hubie over a hunk like Drake?
Hubie's a sweetheart.
He's generous and kind,
and he's always thoughtful
of others, and...
Good morning, ladies.
(ALL SIGHING)
DRAKE: Marina, my pet.
I want you to be my mate.
Drake. Drake. I love Hubie.
Hubie?
I deeply sympathize, Marina,
but since he is nowhere to be found,
I offer my own hand.
- My answer is still no.
- Think about it.
Give me your answer later.
But remember. You must choose a mate
before the full moon mating ceremony
or be banished.
Gosh. That's the law.
I got just 10 days to get back home
before the full moon ceremony.
Sir! Sir! Take me with you.
- ROCKO: You talking to me?
- Yes, sir, I am.
- Don't call me "sir." Call me Rocko.
- Rocko. Right. Yes.
- Well, Rocko, it's about my girl.
- Wait, wait, wait.
You want me to spring you
out of this joint
so you can go home
to Miss Wonderful, right?
Yes. Yes. You're right. You see,
there's another guy who's after my girl.
- Forget it.
- But a moment ago,
you asked
"Who's for busting out of here?"
- Well, I am.
- You're too dumb.
- Take me, please.
- Why should I?
Well, because if the humans see me
tripping all over myself,
that'll divert their attention to me,
giving you more time to escape.
Like I really need a diversion.
I could squawk and yell
and make horrible noises.
(SQUEALING)
(LAUGHING)
Well, you made me laugh.
Give me a chance, please.
I'll bring the house down.
- What's your name?
- Hubie.
Well, Hubie. All right. You're on.
Yeah, go for it, Hubie.
But, hey, once we're on deck,
it's every man for himself.
Yes, sir!
Okay, Hubie. Here's how
you're gonna break out of that cage.
Now, I want you to pay attention.
Watch my beak.
(BELL RINGING)
- Have you got everything?
- This is all I need.
(MAN SINGING)
Here come the boots.
- Okay, kid. This is it. Get ready.
- Ahoy, mateys.
Get your gullets ready
for the sloppiest slop
that ever graced a galley's garbage.
You don't know how lucky you are, matey.
(LAUGHS)
(HUMMING)
Now, I don't want no trouble
from you today.
Well, now. That's more like it.
(LAUGHING)
- Come back here, you... Come back.
- What's going on down there...
ROCKO: Come on, Hubie. Let's go!
There's two of them out now.
- HUBIE: Let me go!
- ROCKO: Come on. Take your best shot.
I'm out of here.
- ROCKO: Come on, Hubie. Come on.
- HUBIE: My pebble!
Forget the blasted pebble!
(WHOOPING)
(ALL CHEERING)
MAN 1: Charlie!
MAN 2: He's heading for the side.
ROCKO: Come on! Let's go!
So long, Hubie. I'm out of here.
- HUBIE: Please don't leave me.
- MAN: Wait till I get my hands on you.
(BOTH GROANING)
ROCKO: You can stop following me now.
You're on your own now. Come on.
(TROPICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANING)
Hey. Where are we?
Let's see. Judging by the heat,
I'd say I'd died and went to Phoenix.
Rocko, look. People.
ROCKO: Looks like some private beach.
We must be in Moorea or Tahiti.
- How do they live like this?
- They pay for it.
I wonder how far it is to Antarctica.
Three thousand miles in that direction,
but you'll never make it.
I will so. I'm fit.
Hey, trust me on this one. You've got
"Eat me" written all over you.
I'm a good swimmer.
You don't know these waters
like I do, birdbrain.
You're right. I'm lost.
Yep. You're lost.
And I'm looking at a dead penguin.
Yeah, I give it two days, tops,
and you'll be in the belly of anything
from a killer whale to a sardine.
Getting back to Marina
is all that matters to me.
I mean, Rocko, look.
I dream about her night and day.
I see her face when I close my eyes.
And this. Just look at this.
Wow.
Is that an engagement pebble, or what?
Do you have to gush like that?
You're probably asking yourself
where I got it, right?
- Yes.
- Picture this.
Pebble beach, moonlit sky,
gentle breeze.
Come on. Come on. Get to it.
Suddenly, I look up and there it is...
...the first evening star.
- ROCKO: Summarize. Summarize.
What do I do? I make a wish.
And, like magic, it jets across the sky
in a blaze of glory
and comes to rest at my feet.
- ROCKO: Really?
- I pick it up, and there,
shining deep inside, is...
There is the face
of my own true love, Marina.
Oh, so special. So unique. So what!
Don't you see? It's my fate, Rocko.
I'm destined to marry Marina.
It's in the stars.
"I'm destined to marry Marina.
It's in the stars."
Why don't you get that thing fixed?
Oh, I'm sorry. I guess
nobody likes a blabbermouth, right?
No. You think?
There. I'm free of you at last.
Now go away. Shoo. Adios.
Boy. You're really one grumpy guy
in the morning, aren't you?
- No. I'm grumpy all day.
- What happened?
Did your girl run off
with another penguin?
No. She did not.
- Oh, then she's waiting for you, right?
- Look, will you stop following me?
You know what you need?
You need a dream.
- I got one.
- What is it?
- I'm sure not gonna tell you.
- Your secret's safe with me.
- I don't even know you.
- I won't laugh.
- Forget it!
- It doesn't matter how silly it sounds.
Get away!
I promise. Cross my heart.
I won't laugh.
- All right. All right. All right.
- What?
- I got something.
- What is it?
You're looking at it.
I'm looking at...
You want to fly, do you?
- Don't laugh.
- Rocko, everybody knows
penguins can't fly.
You're wrong! You are dead wrong.
Our ancestors flew.
They gave us wings, but we can't fly?
I mean... I mean, whose idea
of a cruel joke is this?
I mean...
I mean, you've got to just accept it.
No! No! I don't accept nothing!
But, Rocko, that's the way things are.
I want to fly. I'm gonna fly,
and no one's gonna stop me. I'm flying.
Flap them. Flap them. Flap them.
(SCREAMING)
(WHOOPING)
Don't laugh.
Nobody laughs at Rocko the Rockhopper.
That's funny.
You see, I expected you to tell me
something big, really stupendous.
You know, like hopping up the slopes
of Mt. Everest or something, you know.
But flying? Oh, for heaven's sakes.
That's so easy.
Says who?
- Waldo, that's who.
- Waldo?
- Yeah. He's...
- Who's Waldo?
Waldo is a short little penguin
back in my rookery.
- Yeah? Really?
- Yes, really. And listen,
he claims to have gotten
the hang of flying.
And his wings
are a lot stubbier than yours.
Hey, hey, hey. These aren't stubs.
Oh, but... There I go being
a big blabbermouth again.
Wait. Wait. Come back here.
Thank you for helping me escape, Rocko.
I've got to go, though.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
I must be back before the next
full moon. Marina needs me. Goodbye.
Wait, wait. You're lost.
That way's north.
Oh. I just...
I just remembered something.
I think Waldo said
the secret to flying was wind speed.
- Well, anyway.
- Wind speed.
- Off I go.
- You know, that's right.
That's exactly what I think.
That's what I've been working on.
That's my theory. Wind speed, see?
You know, that's amazing,
that there's...
Someone else knows about that.
Well, come here.
What else did Waldo say?
Can we swim as we talk?
Marina's waiting.
Yeah, sure. Why not?
I got a couple of days, anyway.
- Which way is south?
- That way.
- I want to meet this Waldo character.
- Waldo?
You get me and Waldo together,
and I'll get you to the Antarctic
by the next full moon.
Oh, I like the sound of that.
DRAKE: Well,
there's only eight days left
before the full moon mating ceremony,
and Marina still won't agree
to be my mate.
Although, my faithful servants,
we have seen
that Hubie is a leopard seal meal.
It's a pleasant thought
that that stupid little
penguin nerd will never return.
(LAUGHING)
Silence, you idiots!
Marina is mine.
(HORN BLOWING)
So, what happens
if you don't make it on time?
Oh, that's too horrible
to even think about.
Well, think about it.
Who would Marina marry?
- Drake!
- Drake?
- Why, is he any good with the ladies?
- Yeah.
Well, Captain, full speed ahead.
Here we go.
We only have five days left, Rocko.
We're running out of time.
Look. We can't swim in this storm,
unless you want to die.
Maybe Drake will leave Marina alone.
Yeah, well, maybe Drake
has already married Marina.
No. No. I know my girl. She'll wait.
And if she accepts this pebble,
we'll be married.
If she accepts the pebble?
You mean, you're not sure
if she's gonna accept the pebble?
(LAUGHING)
You mean, you're going
through all this trouble
- and you're not even sure?
- She'll accept it.
Oh, come on.
It's beautiful. It's...
- It's perfect.
- Yes, it is perfect, isn't it, Rocko?
- There, that ledge.
- Rocko?
We have discovered an authentic
ancient "aviarial" airstrip.
What?
This is beautiful. This is it.
You're not gonna try to fly again,
are you?
- Oh, you bet your tail feathers I am.
- Rocko, penguins can't fly!
- Feel that wind.
- Rocko!
Where's your sense of adventure?
- This is the chance of a lifetime.
- This is the end of a lifetime.
Wind speed, perfect. Altitude, perfect.
Tail feathers, perfect.
- Wing, span, wind, sky, airlift!
- Rocko, don't.
You're gonna kill yourself.
Hubie, watch. I'm flying! I'm flying!
Yes. Yes.
Oh, wind speed.
Wind speed, not enough wind speed.
(HOLLERING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
HUBIE: Goodness glaciers.
Rocko, are you all right? Rocko!
- Get away from me.
- But I just...
Don't touch me. Just get away.
I was just trying to...
I don't need any help.
Just get away from me now.
Fine. Suit yourself.
I will. Just keep going.
Go back to little green eyes
or whatever her name is.
Well, maybe I will.
Yeah, go.
See how long you last on your own.
Hubie. No!
No. I mean, no, wait.
So you decided to apologize, huh?
Well, then, I...
Don't be stupid.
I don't apologize to anybody.
- Look.
- (WHALE SCREECHING)
That, pebblebrain, is a killer whale.
The meanest killing machine
in these waters.
Goodness glaciers! You saved my life.
Oh, no. Come on.
Don't get all whiny about it.
Just go. Go, go play with your pebble.
It's no big deal. Just go.
Go. Leave me alone.
No, I'm serious.
I could've been killed.
I'm starting to wish you had.
Just go, will you?
Can't you even admit
that you like me just a little?
What? I don't like you. I hate you.
I just happen to hate killer whales
a little bit more than you, that's all.
Is that so?
- Yeah.
- Well, then, fine.
Fine is right.
When the whale leaves,
we'll just go our separate ways, then.
Yeah. Well, sounds good to me.
I don't need to be seen with...
(SCREAMING)
ROCKO: Fire in the sky!
Fire in the sky! Fire in the sky!
Hide, hide, hide, hide!
That's it.
Hey, what is that? Who's that?
What are you doing? Who...
Ah!
- Get your own shelter.
- I was here first.
So, I'm here second. So what? Move!
DRAKE: So, Marina. When should
I announce our engagement?
Today? Tomorrow? Wednesday?
Drake, I wouldn't marry you
if you were the last penguin on Earth.
Don't worry. I'll make it official
with the obligatory pebble and all that.
The answer is no.
No? No?
Oh, I get it. You're joking.
(LAUGHING)
What's so funny?
(SINGING DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH)
(DRAKE LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS)
(SNORING)
Hey, Rocko. Wake up.
Rocko, look.
What? What? Where?
Isn't it beautiful?
Yeah. I mean, it's...
Well, I mean, it certainly looks better
than a killer whale.
It's our first sight of home.
We're almost there.
Look. It's all right
if you wanna split up.
I understand. No hard feelings.
Well, it's probably for the best.
Hey, give my regards to Waldo.
Waldo? Waldo.
Oh, yeah. I sure will. I...
Rocko, there's something
you should know.
Waldo...
Waldo isn't real.
What?
I needed you to show me the way home.
I didn't think you'd do it
if I just asked, so I...
So I made up stories
about a make-believe guy named Waldo.
Well, say something.
You told me a lie?
You dumb penguin nerd.
Rocko, stop!
I could've been back in Tahiti
- with those people on the beach...
- I'm sorry.
...feeding me
because I was a cute little penguin.
I said I'm sorry.
- No, you! You decided to lie to me!
- Oh. Come on.
To drag me through 3,000 miles
of water and killer whales.
You're a dead penguin. You are a...
Clear! Clear that beak! Clear!
(CHOKING)
(LAUGHING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You're either the greatest
romantic hero of all time,
or you're the stupidest penguin
who ever lived.
HUBIE: I'm sorry I lied to you, Rocko.
Who likes a liar? Not me.
I really needed your help.
Look. If you're ever down
near the South Pole,
please look me up.
(CHUCKLING)
In four days, birdbrain,
I'll be in Antarctica.
Where will you be, huh?
- Rocko!
- Come on. Try to keep up.
HUBIE: Great.
ROCKO: Looks like
I got me a new student.
You know anything about fighting?
Well, how do you handle pain?
- What?
- Oh, just kidding! How about blood?
(SINGING SOMETIMES I WONDER)
(GROANS)
Rocko, I don't think I can walk.
Hey. How big is this Drake guy?
I could have a broken bone.
You're gonna have to fight him.
- I'm what?
- You have to put Drake in his place.
Well, I'm not a fighter.
- I'll teach you.
- I've never hit anyone.
Look, the first thing you need to know
about winning is how to bluff.
Rocko, I can't.
- Do you love the girl?
- Of course, I do. I...
Then shut up.
Put your fins up, your neck back.
Put your feet out.
Balance, balance, balance.
Okay. Now make a face.
Give me your meanest look.
Like this?
No! Like this.
Well, you know what? That's fantastic.
It's a bluff.
I'm tougher than any bird.
Why, I'm tougher than any polar bear.
Why, I'm hungry-
What do we have here?
Looks like a seal's fishing hole.
Do you think it's safe?
I'm too hungry to care if
it's safe or not. Let's go.
- How much farther to the Antarctic?
- I don't know.
It could be a few miles.
It could be a few days.
Who cares? Come on.
A few days.
I don't think I could wait that long.
So, you wanna go first?
What?
Well, if you're not brave enough...
Hey. Who says I'm not brave enough?
Then, I'll go.
I'm brave enough.
Come on. Let's go. One, two, three. Go.
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(COUGHING)
You idiot! You almost got me killed.
What's the matter with you?
You risk your life to get back to that
chick and give her that blasted pebble.
You're crazy! You're insane! You're...
(LAUGHING) You are amazing.
Amazing? Me?
What? No, no, I didn't say that.
Yes, you did. I heard you.
No, no, no. I didn't say that.
No, no, no, no. Get out of my face.
Get out of my face.
I didn't say nothing like that.
You do like me.
- I don't like anybody.
- Oh, yes, you do.
And I knew it all along.
Get away from me.
Hey, Rocko. I guess this means
we've put our differences on ice.
Get it? Put our differences on ice?
I'd like to put you on ice.
(SINGING
LOOKS LIKE I GOT ME A FRIEND)
Take it, Rocko.
Hey, Rocko. What do you
call a flower before it opens?
What?
What do you call a flower
before it opens?
A bud.
I love it when you call me bud.
Take it, Rocko.
Hey, Rocko. I caught you a herring.
Where should I put it?
- What?
- I caught you a herring.
Where should I put it?
Put it there.
Put it there?
- All right.
- Oh, stop it.
Goodbye, Rocko.
Oh, knock it off.
Hey. Hey, you're all blue.
Breathe, you birdbrain.
Hubie!
Say it!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- We really showed him.
- We showed him? We?
Come on. You're a terrible fighter.
FEAMLE NARRATOR: As they continued
their journey home,
Rocko was determined to teach Hubie
that it wasn't enough
simply being in love with Marina.
The time would come
when he would have to fight for her.
But with Drake as his opponent,
would he be up to the challenge?
(WHOOPING)
I won. I won. I won. I won.
I beat you by a mile.
You're blind as a bat.
I was winning, man.
I won the whole way.
I was way in front of you.
- Rocko!
- I left you in the cold. Come on.
(THUDDING)
Goodness glaciers! What was that?
Looked like a killer whale.
It was bigger than a leopard seal.
Twice as big, twice as fast
and twice as mean.
- Oh, good.
- But that's not the worst part.
Wonderful. What's the worst part?
Killer whales always travel in groups.
- What?
- Groups.
- Oh, no.
- Big groups. Lots. Oodles and oodles.
What do we do now?
We...We...
- You see that iceberg?
- What iceberg?
That one! Swim for it.
- Swim?
- Or we could fly.
- My pebble.
- Pebble? Your pebble.
- Forget about the blasted pebble.
I don't want to hear "pebble" from you.
All right. Swim for the berg.
I'll lead them away.
No. If you stay, I stay.
No. Go on. Go on.
I'll lead them away. Go on.
Now. Let's go.
Faster. Faster. Come on.
Swim for the berg.
Come on. Go. Go. Go. Go.
Move it. Move it. Move it.
(WHOOPING)
Rocko!
Oh, no. Oh, Rocko.
- Marina's gone.
- She ran away.
No. Drake kidnapped her. Hurry up!
- He can't force her to marry him.
- I know, but he'll try.
I wish Hubie was here.
(DRAKE LAUGHING)
DRAKE: As I said, my pretty,
I refuse to lose.
You're hurting me.
Then get smart. Yes, or be banished.
You'll never get me.
But, precious, you'll only starve.
Stop it.
Let me go.
Get your filthy flippers off my girl!
Hubie!
What the...
Hubie. We thought you were dead.
You heard me, Drake!
Now you're gonna wish that you were.
(LAUGHING)
That was easy enough. Marina.
Let me go!
Hubie! Oh, no! Come on.
Let's get him on his feet.
Help me, Timmy.
I can't. He's too heavy.
Wake up! Oh, hurry!
Hubie, you must save Marina.
Wake up, Hubie!
Come on, Hubie. You can do it.
(GRUNTING)
- Hubie, come on.
- Get up.
- Get up!
Now, open your eyes.
Go knock his block off!
I didn't come 3,000 miles
and lose my best buddy
to be stopped by the likes of you!
Drake!
Come on! Take your best shot!
(YELLING)
Come on!
Hubie!
Drake, let go.
(CRUNCHING)
I'll teach you to bite me.
(GROANS)
MARINA: Hubie!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
I'm sorry.
Oh, Marina.
Will you be my mate?
I thought you would never ask.
Oh, Hubie's wonderful.
Hubie.
Rocko?
Hey, Romeo!
Goodness glaciers. Rocko!
Oh, oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I can't believe you're alive!
(MARINA SCREAMING)
Say your prayers, you...
Help.
Somebody. Hey, Rocko. Hey, Rocko.
Hold on, good buddy. Hold on.
All right.
Give me some slack. Don't let go.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Hold on, Hubie. Hold on.
Hubie!
(WHOOPING)
Hold on, Hubie. Hold on.
I'm flying. I'm flying!
I'm flying!
He made it.
Hip, hip hooray! Hip, hip hooray!
(ALL CLAMORING)
Hubie.
Marina, I want you
to meet my best friend, Rocko.
Rocko, Marina.
The flying Rocko. Pleased, I'm sure.
Hey, hey, hey, Hubie.
You forgot your blasted pebble.
My pebble. My pebble.
Rocko, you found it!
Don't just stand there, Romeo.
Give the girl the pebble.
- Do you like it?
- I love it.
You'd better.
- Good.
- But don't you know?
It's not the pebble. It's the penguin.
I love you even more.
(ALL CHEERING)
FEMALE NARRATOR: So Hubie
and Marina proved
that neither distance nor danger
can stand in the way of true love.
You need only follow your heart.
And goodness glaciers,
they lived happily ever after.
(NOW AND FOREVER PLAYING)