(MultiCom Jingle)
(light piano music)
(telephone ringing)
- [Brian] Hi, this is Brian.
At the tone, please leave
me a message, thanks.
(patrons chattering)
- You mean all the way down here?
Wherever you want.
- Um, right there.
- Whoa, close, not good
for your eyes, okay.
Are you sure you wanna
see this movie again, huh.
You seen it what, 17 times?
- Seven.
- Oh, only seven.
Oh man, I'm hungry.
- [Murray] Sandra, do you realize
you are not wearing your shoes?
(audience laughing)
- [Albert] Uh, Miss Markowitz
and I have been asked
by the Social Service unit
from the Child Welfare Board
to investigate and examine.
- I didn't know what you wanted,
so I got a little bit of everything.
- Oh, thanks.
- Good for his teeth.
- [Murray] Won't you sit down.
I'll just get rid of these things.
(audience laughing)
- [Albert] I investigate and examine
certain pupils of the Revere School
- [Claudia] Rock.
- [Joshua] And Rover.
- [Claudia] Mike.
- [Tom] Yeah, that's good.
- Marty.
- Who's next?
- Uh, Monty.
- Um, Snookie.
- Uh, Woodrow, uh, Chevrolet.
- Bluemont, Rex.
- Lefty, The Phantom.
- And Chip and there's one more.
- There's one more, there's
one more, there's one more.
- Um, Raphael Sabatini!
- Hey, you're really a nut
for this picture too, huh?
- Yeah, I even beat Joshua.
This is my eighth time.
- Hey sport, what do you say,
why don't we invite Claudia here
to join us for your birthday dinner, huh?
- Oh no, no, don't be silly.
I don't wanna butt in, really.
Well, happy birthday though, are you 10?
- Yeah, how do you know?
Did he tell?
- I'm a good guesser and I
have 14 nieces and nephews.
- I guess you can come if you want.
- Oh no, really, thank you.
I don't wanna intrude, really I don't.
- No no no, no, come on, come on.
It's a tradition, you
get cake, then lobster.
- Oh, I think I'm too
conservative to eat cake first.
I don't know about that.
- Hey Jerry, the cake is great, thanks.
- [Jerry] Anytime.
- Happy birthday, sport.
- Oh, thanks Dad, this is great.
My favorite, chocolate.
- I know what you like.
Hey Diane, can I get a
knife and some plates?
- [Diane] Sure.
- No candles, no singing?
- Nah, we don't believe in
making wishes, do we Josh?
- Gee, I'm about 75% wishes and dreams.
- Well, don't you think
it's kind of embarrassing
for people to start singing?
(Tom laughs)
- [Diane] Here you go.
- All right, here we go.
Do the honors?
- Okay.
- [Claudia] How is it?
- Mm, it's great.
How should I cut it?
- Well uh, oh, right across there.
- [Joshua] Here?
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Joshua] Okay.
(diners chattering)
- Good morning, Stephanie.
Do you have anything for me?
Thanks.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Claudine.
- What's this?
- I just won $13.00 in the lottery,
and I thought I'd share the booty.
- [Claudia] Thanks.
- You're very welcome.
What's with the Blast account?
- Oh well, the photos aren't that good,
but I can't get too
upset about that today.
- Why, oh, what happened to you?
Did Brian finally propose?
- Ah, hardly.
No, he stood me up.
I called him for two hours.
He didn't answer the phone, he's history.
- Well, I know that look.
I've seen it too many times before.
You met someone, well?
- The most incredible guy.
- I knew it, where?
- At the movies.
- A Thousand Clowns again.
- (chuckles) It's his son's favorite.
- Oh great, that's swell.
Did the whole family go,
just the four of you?
- He's divorced, I guess.
- [Nick] And of course, you didn't ask.
- No.
- What about his dating record?
- Nick, don't be so skeptical.
- Well, it's just that
you're such a Gidget.
(knocking on door)
Tell me, is he the fabulous blond hunk?
Is he everything you always wanted?
- Claudia Casara?
- Oh, please.
- His name is Tom.
Yeah, he's an architect.
Uh, at the movies.
Well, he was with his.
(knocking on door)
Oh Mom, I gotta go, he's here.
Yeah, yes, I'll go slow, Mother.
Okay, I love you, bye.
- Hello.
- [Claudia] Hi.
- Hi, for you.
- Oh, they're beautiful, thank you.
- You are too.
- (giggles) Thanks, um, I'm
gonna go give them some water.
I'll be right back.
- Okay.
I would dream about houses,
and I made models with toothpicks and gum.
I had them hanging off
the sides of cliffs.
Is this, is it boring you?
- Oh, no no, not at all.
- At any other time in history,
I would've built churches, cathedrals,
but now, I built a better mall, you know.
Compatible with the landscape,
but I'm working on one house,
and it's, well, it's really
quite something, you know.
I would love you to see it.
- I'd like to.
- It's very daring.
- I worry about how things look too.
How images affect people,
especially children.
I guess that's why I wanna
illustrate children's books.
What?
- Nothing, I'm, I'm,
I'm just looking at you.
You're so lovely and bright, shiny,
and lit up from the inside.
Relax, I'm not gonna hurt you.
You are shy.
Are you afraid of me?
- You're a little fast for me.
- Oh oh, hey, all right.
Thank you, I had a wonderful evening.
- (giggles) Me too.
- I do have to leave town
very early in the morning.
Maybe we could get
together over the weekend.
- Mm hmm.
- Maybe you could come out to the beach.
- I'll call you from Denver.
- Um (clears throat).
- Goodnight.
- Come on buddy, come, come on.
Okay, good boy, sit, sit.
Good boy, now, stay.
Oh, you're my pal, you're
such a good doggie.
- Hey Joshua!
- I wonder if this one
will pretend to like us.
Yeah, come on, come on Chuckles.
Stay Chuckles, come here.
Hi, this is Chuckles, Chuck for short.
- Oh, Chip, Chip, Chipper
Monkey (chuckles).
- My dad's always late.
You wanna cup of coffee?
- Sure.
- Okay, come on Chuckles, come on.
Come on, come on boy.
- Leo, my acupressurist
says I'll make buku bucks.
Oh no, he's part healer, part Edgar Cayce.
Hi, I'm Sandy.
- Hi.
- All the negative energy
is just being cleared
right out of my life.
No, his uncle was Clark
Gable's ex-partner, okay.
Okay, ciao.
- Um, filberts, carob, and macadamia.
- Thank you, so, who's Sandy?
- Well, she's supposed
to be my babysitter,
but she's always talking this
weird stuff on the phone.
She's lasted three months so far.
- Well, who took care of you before that?
- Well, I pretty much take care of myself,
but before her was um, Emelda, Mrs. Cross,
Greta, Concepcion, and then there was um.
(telephone ringing)
Hello, oh hi, Dad.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
It's for you, it's my dad.
- Hi, no no, no, don't worry, it's okay.
Josh is taking good care of me.
Yeah, that sounds great.
Okay, Old Topanga Road, two lefts.
All right, I'll be there soon.
Me too, goodbye.
- Excuse me, just for a little bit, okay.
I'm sorry, clients always
screw up the schedule,
but they're getting ready to leave.
Oh, I missed you.
Boy, I forgot how cute you are.
- Well, I'm glad to see you too.
Oh, this is beautiful.
- Watch your step.
- Oh, it's incredible.
- I couldn't stop thinking
about you in Denver.
Am I still too fast for you?
- Oh, I don't exactly trust myself.
- You know, this is so crazy.
I think I love you.
(light piano music)
- [Claudia] Oh, what about Josh?
- [Tom] Would you stop
worrying about Josh.
Look, he's a self-reliant realist.
He's got both his feet on the ground.
- Doesn't he ever spend the
weekend with his mother?
- I don't even know where she lives.
She only came to visit him
once or twice last year.
- It must be hard for you
raising him all by yourself.
- Oh no, he practically raises himself.
He has been getting himself up
and dressed since he was five.
Makes his own breakfast.
Puts himself to bed.
Drives himself to school.
(both laughing)
- Since he was five?
- Yep, yeah yeah.
- I'm sorry, I shouldn't have
asked you so many questions.
- That's okay, don't apologize.
- [Claudia] Hi.
- Hi.
- Do you make coffee every morning?
- Sure, don't you?
- Yeah, I do.
Um, do you think it would be all right,
if I came out with you and your dad
on your little Sunday adventure?
- Well, you make it sound like a TV show.
Doesn't matter what I think.
Why don't you ask him?
- I did.
- What did he say?
- He said to ask you.
- He did?
- [Claudia] Mm hmm.
- Good morning, hey squirt.
- [Joshua] Hi, Dad.
So, where are the three of us going today?
- Uh, I don't know.
We were just talking about, you know.
- Well I, I don't know
what I was thinking.
I gotta go work on my book.
- [Tom] Well, Claudia.
- No really, thanks for
the invitation though, bye.
No, yeah, it's fine, it's fine, bye.
Nick wanted me to go to
Palm Springs with him.
Yeah, I know it sounds like fun,
but I gotta wait for Tom
to get back from San Diego.
I don't know, about an hour or so.
Yeah, weekends mostly.
Look Mom, I gotta go get ready.
Yes Mom, I know all about safe sex.
I'm the one who told you, remember?
I will, okay, I love you, bye Mom.
(telephone ringing)
Hello, hi, where are you?
Oh great, no, I understand.
It's just that I could've gone
to Palm Springs with my friend Nick.
My friend from work, Nick.
My best friend, you know, no, nevermind.
What, I'm working on my book.
Her car is broken, how will he get home?
No, no, it's okay.
No, it's okay, I will.
Yeah, Agora Elementary School.
Me too, okay, bye.
(horn blowing)
(light country music)
Hi, Josh.
- Hi, is Dad okay?
- Yeah, he's fine.
A main burst at the sight.
He couldn't leave.
I'm sorry you had to wait so long.
- It's okay, I'm used to it.
Just as long as he's all right.
Does my dad know you listen
to that redneck music?
- [Claudia] (chuckles) Get in here.
- [Joshua] Oh, missed that one, yeah.
- Hi, may I come in?
- [Joshua] Sure.
- Is this a picture of your mom?
- [Joshua] Her name's Kit.
- You have the same eyes.
When was the last time you saw her?
- [Joshua] Last summer, I guess.
- Do you ever see any other relatives?
- Well, I saw my dad's parents two times.
They live in this mansion
and they have a tennis court.
- Oh, that sounds neat.
- Dad doesn't like it there.
You know, you don't have to
hang out with me, Dad doesn't.
- Well, I just thought we
could play a game or something.
- I'm not as dumb as a
regular 10 year old, you know.
- I can tell.
I really do just wanna play a game.
- Is that because you have
14 nieces and nephews?
- I'm flattered you remember.
Nine.
- 10.
- [Claudia] Jack.
- Queen.
- [Claudia] Oh, um, um,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, King, Ace.
- Ace, I got one too.
Um um, three!
- [Claudia] Four, yes!
- Oh no, no, I lost it.
- One, two, three, spit.
- [Claudia] Spit, eight, seven!
- Good job, queen, oh, no no no.
Jack, Queen, King, nine,
um, three, um, Queen, King.
- Wait, wait, wait,
you're killing me here.
- Three, two, um, three, I got it!
I got it all alone with that one!
- Claudia.
- [Claudia] Hmm?
- Move in with me.
- I don't know,
everything's going so fast.
- Come on, we're great together.
It doesn't get any better than this.
- How would Josh feel?
- Josh, you are the first female
that he's liked since Mrs. Cross.
- He's just glad I
helped get rid of Sandy.
(both laughing)
- Yeah, that too,
and you are the first
woman that I really like.
- Oh yeah, since who?
- Mrs. Cross.
(both laughing)
Come on, come on, move in with us.
I wanna spend the rest
of my life with you.
(light piano music)
- [Claudia] Hey guys, lunch.
Lunch, come on.
- Touchdown!
- Oh no!
- [Claudia] Uh, did
anybody ever use that oven?
- Well, we mostly nuke food around here.
- Oh, you don't even have dried parsley.
I'm gonna have to grow my own.
- Wait a second.
Wait, there's no cheese, is there?
- Why, why no cheese, you eat pizza.
- Only pizza, I can't be around
any other kind of cheese.
It smells like throw up,
and I always have to leave the room.
- (laughing) come on, sit down.
- No, no, no, no.
- [Tom] Sit down, you huge liar.
- [Claudia] There is no cheese.
- Where'd you get these
biscuits, they're great.
- I baked these biscuits in the oven.
- [Tom] No way.
- Yes, I did.
- You're the greatest.
- No nukes, Josh.
- Salad, all right.
(crowd laughing and shouting)
Watch me now.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, look out!
(crowd laughing and shouting)
Okay, who wants the big one?
(whimsical music)
Be careful, you all right?
- That was great, that
was great, hey Chuckles.
- I need something green,
I'm making a salad.
- Ooh, we got a message.
- [Tom] You wanna grab it.
- [Kit] Hi guys, uh, this is, it's Kit.
I was just calling, I don't know.
How is everybody?
I'm, I'm working part-time
at a dancing school here.
I'm in Seattle.
It's okay, I mean, I'm okay.
I hate these machines.
Uh, I'll talk to you later Josh, bye.
- When was the last time
you saw your parents?
- Claudia, not everybody
has a great relationship
with their parents,
or calls their mother four times a week.
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean anything.
I just thought it would be nice
for Josh to have some family.
- Things are not so warm
at my old Chicago home.
- I'm sorry, I shouldn't
have brought it up.
- It's okay, you can ask me anything.
- What's Kit like?
- Now, don't get jealous about her, baby.
She left five years ago.
Besides, you are so much
cuter and down to earth.
- Hey, she left when Josh was five?
- Right before his birthday.
(speaking in foreign language)
- Josh!
- Well, how do I look?
- Not too scary.
Is this your costume?
- I think Halloween's dorky,
but I met this new friend, Rafe,
he just moved here from New York,
and he's taking me to some party.
- Well, that's great.
- Not to me, but I don't
have too many friends,
so I said okay.
- So, what're you supposed to be?
- [Joshua] A grownup.
- Oh.
(doorbell ringing)
- [Joshua] Oh, hi Rafe.
- [Rafe] Hi.
- Oh wow, you look
incredible, look at this.
- My mom's waiting in the car.
Is it okay if you don't come
home till 11 on a school night?
- I don't know.
- You better go ask your mom.
- Okay, I will.
- Look Josh, now, I'm just
gonna be a couple of minutes,
and I want you to wait
in the car, all right?
- [Joshua] Well, Chuckles
can stay in the car.
- No, Josh, don't argue with me.
I want you to wait in the car.
You didn't bring his leash,
you have to stay with him.
- He'll be okay.
Chuckles is an incredible dog.
- [Claudia] Stay in the car, Josh.
- No no, no, Chuckles, Chuckles!
- Chuckles!
- [Joshua] Chuckles!
(tires screeching)
No, oh no, Chuck, no.
(Chuckles whining)
- Josh, it'll be all right, let me see.
Easy Chuck, you're gonna be all right.
Could someone please help me
get the dog in my car, please?
Josh, leave him alone.
- [Woman] Good girl, good girl.
Oh, that's a girl.
- [Man] She's beautiful.
- [Woman] Oh, thank you, thank you.
- Um, how long is it gonna be for my dog?
- Josh, Chuckles is gonna be okay.
Now, he's pretty banged up,
and he's got a few broken bones,
but he's gonna be okay.
Now, there's gonna be someone
here with him all the time,
and you can call and check
on him anytime you want to.
- It's all my fault.
- No, this was an accident.
- I don't cry, I don't cry, I never cry.
- I know, and you don't believe in wishes,
and Halloween is dorky.
It's okay, it's all right to cry.
The dog was just lying there
and I thought he was dead,
and all I could do was yell at Josh
about how irresponsible he was.
- So, where is dear old dad all this time?
- He was working, Nick.
Can't you have any sympathy for Josh?
- Sympathy, honey, my
mother remarried five times.
I have sympathy, I even have empathy,
but that's not the point.
My allegiance is to you.
You know, three months ago you
didn't even wanna have kids.
You wanted a career instead.
- Well now, I don't know.
That was before Josh.
- Claudia, you're not the kids mom.
Even if Rafe thinks you are.
You know, you hardly ever mention Tom.
Which one of these boys
are you in love with?
- Both, isn't that okay?
- I don't know.
I'm starting to get a little nervous.
- Uh, starting?
- Yeah.
- Nick, you have been
suspicious from day one.
- Oh stop, I have not.
- No, I listened to you about
hanging on to my apartment,
now what more do you want from me?
- I don't know, more of your time.
You know, I never see you
outside the office anymore.
Do you know that your mother is calling me
to find out how you are.
Do you know that?
Come on.
- [Joshua] None for you Chuckles.
- Thank you, dude.
- Hi Mom, how are you?
Yeah, yeah, I know.
It's just that I've been
really busy lately, and I.
Well, I know the harvest
is your busiest time, and?
Yeah, I know you're really
disappointed, and I am too.
It's just that I wanna be here
to spend Christmas with Tom and Josh.
No, I haven't missed one in 28 years,
but just try and see this from my side.
I really hate not to be there.
Okay, I love you, Mom, bye.
Hey Josh, why don't you go
upstairs and go to sleep?
- No, he never goes to bed this early.
He likes to stay up and
watch the sports news.
- Tom, he's not watching anything.
He's falling asleep.
- No.
- Okay, I'm going to bed now.
Goodnight, Dad.
- Goodnight, dude.
- Goodnight, Claude.
- Goodnight.
- [Joshua] Goodnight Chuck.
(light piano music)
(Chuckles barking)
Watch it, Chuckles.
- Hey Chuck, watch out.
Put it over by the window.
Right in front of it.
Right there by the presents.
- Right there?
- Yeah, okay.
- Get outta here, Chuckles.
Chuckles, look out.
- [Claudia] Josh, whoa, whoa.
- [Joshua] I'll get the tinsel.
- No wait, wait wait,
wait wait, wait wait wait.
First lights, ornaments, then tinsel,
but first you gotta get me a knife,
so I can cut this cord, okay?
- [Joshua] Okay.
- Hey Josh, the cookies are ready.
- Okay.
- [Tom] Hello.
- [Joshua] Dad, hey.
- Hey, sport, hey.
- [Claudia] Hey.
- Oh, what in the hell is all this?
Kind of looks like Olvera Street.
- It's Christmas,
or hadn't you noticed
it was December 20th?
- Look, Dad.
- Are you into all this junk now too?
Josh doesn't believe in
Santa Claus, do you sport?
- Well, I don't know.
Maybe we could check
it out just this year.
- [Claudia] I'm sorry about
all this Christmas stuff, Tom.
I didn't realize you felt
so strongly about it.
- Well, Josh and I have always avoided
all this holiday madness,
and I'm very surprised
to see him so into it.
- And disappointed.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to upset you.
- I know you're crazy
about this Christmas stuff,
and you did this for Josh.
Just don't get him all
dressed up as a wise man,
and expect me to come to some pageant.
- [Claudia] Okay now, we're
gonna leave for the airport
to pick your dad up in a little while.
- [Joshua] Well, first I want to fix
that broken pine cone on the wreath.
- [Claudia] Okay (chuckles).
- [Tom] Hi guys, it's me.
I got some bad news.
It's been snowing here since dawn,
and they're forecasting a blizzard.
Saying no flights will leave here
till tomorrow night at the earliest.
Sport, I'm sorry about this,
but hey, Claudia knows
where your presents are.
So, Merry Christmas and I'll
talk to you both later on.
- He's coming back, isn't he?
- Josh, of course he's coming back.
It's just that the planes
couldn't take off, that's all.
Hey, you know what?
If we're in the car in 15 minutes,
we can be at the farm
in an hour and a half.
- You mean your parents will let me come?
- [Claudia] You bet, and Chuckles too.
- Okay.
- Okay, let go, come on.
(horn blowing)
(family laughing and shouting)
- [Man] Did you get caught in traffic?
- No, not at all.
It was completely clear.
- [Vera] Oh, I'm so glad you got here.
- Me too, Mom, this is Josh and Chuck.
Josh, Chuck, this is my mother, Vera.
- Hi Josh, how are you?
Hi Chuck, well, come on in.
We've been waiting for you.
- [Joshua] Are they all Casara's?
- Absolutely, come on, let's go.
- So, did you get any supper yet?
- [Claudia] No, and we're starved.
- Are you hungry, come on.
(family laughing and chattering)
It's lovely, darling.
I didn't know you still embroidered.
- [Claudia] Mm hmm.
- I'll hang it up with the others.
Does Joshua spend Christmas
with his own mother?
- Well, she moves around a lot.
He only gets to see her
about once or twice a year.
Now, I don't know the whole story,
but I guess she was just
too young and too flakey,
couldn't handle it, so she took off.
- Well, a 10 year old is
a lot of responsibility.
- (chuckles) Yeah, a
real pain in the butt.
He interferes with my work.
He interferes with my whole life.
- I'm getting a little worried about you.
You're becoming so attached
to him, aren't you?
- No, I just like having someone
besides myself to worry about.
- [Vera] And Tom?
- Oh, he's smart, he's
charming, he's a great dad,
and he's enormously
generous about everything.
- Except his time.
- He works very hard, Mom.
- Well, that's all very admirable, dear,
but if he's so great,
why didn't he rearrange his schedule?
- Claudia, you look wonderful.
- Oh, Mom, this is incredible.
- Isn't he gorgeous.
- That's just huge.
You want me to take this?
- Please, if you'll take that in, okay.
Yeah, you can take that.
Can you take these sweet
potatoes and the gravy too.
(family laughing and chattering)
(speaking in foreign language)
(family cheering and applauding)
- [Luigi] Hey Bruno, how
about some cranberry sauce.
(speaking in foreign language)
(family chattering)
- [Tom] Hey, happy day after Christmas.
- [Joshua] Hey, Dad.
- Hey, oh, I'm sorry I
screwed up the holidays,
but I think I got a present here for you.
- [Joshua] Okay.
- Where is it, oh, it's the big one.
Whoa and it's heavy too, here you go.
- [Joshua] All right.
- There you go.
Hey, baby.
- [Claudia] Hi.
(light piano music)
- Oh, it's beautiful, thank you.
- [Joshua] Oh wow, oh my gosh.
- [Tom] You love it?
- Oh my gosh, look at this.
- [Tom] You can make your own
Thousand Clowns now, right?
- [Joshua] Oh my gosh, I can't believe it.
- I set it up for you.
Come here, come here.
Look at the Chinese food I got.
You guys hungry?
That's cool.
(light piano music)
Are you tired?
- Mm hmm.
- What else, you didn't like your present?
- No, no, I love it, it's beautiful.
Are we really headed anywhere?
- That's what's bugging you.
I thought you were still
burned up about Christmas.
- No, no, I was disappointed.
That still doesn't answer my question.
- I'm crazy about you and
about the three of us together.
We're headed wherever you want.
You wanna get married?
- Hi Claude, where's Dad?
- [Claudia] I don't know.
He said he'd be back by three, you hungry.
- No, I thought your book was done?
- No, the publisher sent it back.
They didn't want it.
- Probably got too many books.
What's so great about this gardening?
- Oh, I don't know.
I guess growing up on a farm
it just kind of relaxes me,
and it's fun to watch
things grow, like you.
Josh, cut it, cut it, give me the camera.
- [Joshua] No no, no.
- Give me the camera.
- [Joshua] No!
- Come on, come on, come on.
Come dance with me.
Come here, come here, okay, ready?
Put your arm in here.
Okay, now the other way, the other way.
- [Joshua] This way?
- [Claudia] Okay, this way.
- [Joshua] Maybe I can help.
- [Claudia] Think so?
- Does he move to the city,
because his parents are splitting up?
- No.
Okay, you ready.
- [Joshua] Yep.
- Okay, okay, whatever you do,
don't make a funny face,
don't make a funny (laughing).
Okay, fish face, fish face.
(Claudia laughing)
- Hi, Josh.
- Hi, Kit.
- Are you ready to go
or uh, should I come in?
- You can come in.
I'm gonna go get my stuff.
- Josh, sorry it's so late,
but uh, it's for your birthday.
He moves, look.
(light piano music)
Are you hungry?
- No.
- Josh, I've uh, been thinking
about maybe moving down here.
We could see more of each other.
- Sure.
- You've grown so much
I hardly recognize you.
The alligator was a stupid idea.
You're too big for it.
- No, I like it, Kit, I really do.
- So, what's new?
How was Christmas?
- Oh, it was great.
Went to Claudia's parents farm.
They grow more almonds
than just about anybody
else in California, yeah.
There were about 15 people
at the dinner table,
and they were all related.
- Is Claudia your friend from school?
- Oh no, she's Dad's friend, you know.
- I know, and you like her a lot?
- Yeah, but she's different.
I mean, she really likes me.
- From the people that
brought you the moon.
Don't you think it's just
a little pretentious?
- Well Wax and Wane Productions
deserves something pretentious.
- What's with you?
Is it the book?
What time's the meeting with
your publisher this afternoon?
- It's 3:30.
- Honey, you'll be fine.
- No, no, that's not it.
- I felt really funny when
Josh's mom came to visit.
Like a cheater.
- A cheater, honey, I
can't believe this guy.
He gets a live in lover.
He gets a housekeeper.
He gets an extra mom for his kid.
- This isn't about Tom.
- [Nick] What's it about?
- This is about.
(telephone ringing)
I asked her not to put any calls through.
Yes, Ava?
Yeah, oh, okay.
It's Josh's school, yes.
- Oh, Josh's school.
- Well, what's wrong with him?
He did, no no, I'm not his mother.
No, I'm not his step-mother.
I'm not related to him.
Look, did you call his father?
Listen, I have a very important
meeting this afternoon
that I can't miss.
Don't you have a nurse or
an infirmary or something?
Well, not even until 4:30.
All right, all right, okay, yeah.
Don't say anything.
- Not a word.
- Okay Chuckles, get down.
How do you feel?
- Okay, sorry you missed your
meeting on account of me.
- Look, don't you worry about it.
You just worry about getting well.
Josh, what is it?
- Where did he go?
He's been coming home pretty
late for the last three weeks.
Maybe he's got a new girlfriend.
- What makes you think that?
- Well, three months is his usual limit.
You've lasted almost eight.
- [Tom] Okay, you know what,
then let him sit there.
Let him sit at school and not pick him up.
- [Claudia] Where were you?
- [Tom] It was your choice.
I was at the sight.
- [Claudia] Why couldn't you pick him up?
- [Tom] Because I couldn't
get away from the sight.
Look, I can't remember.
(dramatic music)
- You lied to me.
Why did you say you wanted to marry me?
- Because I did,
but you've got some magazine
concept of marriage.
I don't wanna be in the P.T.A.,
and Josh doesn't need Little League.
You're view is just, it's
way too middle class.
- Are you seeing someone else?
- Yes.
- What about Josh?
Your decisions affect his life, Tom.
He needs a family.
- Will you cut it out.
I mean, I know you love my son,
but don't make me a defective father.
- Well, you're the one
who left us alone so much.
What do you expect.
Are you jealous?
- Claudia look, you are very good for him,
but not so good for me.
This isn't working out, now maybe.
- I'm moving out.
(light piano music)
- I knew she'd leave us.
- Everything is gonna be
the same between us, Josh.
I'm just not gonna live here, that's all.
Okay, I'm gonna call you.
We're gonna do lots of stuff together.
I still need your help on my book.
You can call me anytime you want to.
I left both of my numbers in your room.
I love you, Joshua.
- Claude, wait!
(Chuckles barking)
If I hadn't said anything
you wouldn't have to go.
- Oh no, no no, Josh, it's not your fault.
Now, I do have to go, but it
has nothing to do with you.
You're the reason that
I'm so sad to leave.
- Please don't, Claude.
I never really thought you were weird.
- I know, but I have to go.
- I'm never getting
married and having kids.
- Don't you say that.
Loving is good.
Now, sometimes it hurts,
but it's all that matters.
You wait and see, Josh.
You're gonna be the very best dad.
(light piano music)
- How you doing, sport?
- Okay.
(telephone ringing)
- Hello, hi, great great, how are you?
Ah sure, he's right here, hang on.
It's your mom, Kit.
- Hello.
- Hi, I'm coming down in June.
I got two weeks vacation.
Is that okay?
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna find a job and an apartment.
Say something, Josh.
- Like what?
- [Kit] I don't know,
like, like what you think.
- It's great.
- Okay good, is something wrong?
- No.
- [Kit] You sure?
- Yeah.
- Okay, then I'll see you then, okay?
- Bye.
- Did you tell her to call?
- No way.
- I don't believe you.
I'm going to bed now.
- Wait, you don't wanna stay up
and watch the end of the playoffs?
- In case you forgot, Dad, I'm only 10.
I need my sleep.
- Well that's cool.
Whatever you say,
but don't forget we gotta get up early
to get the paper and the coffeecake.
- [Joshua] I'm not going.
(light piano music)
(knocking on door)
- [Tom] Can I come in?
- Yeah.
- (sighs) Look Josh, I
wanna tell you something.
I know things seem real tough right now,
but when you get a little older,
you'll see that you can love
lots of people, not just one.
- You love too many.
(light piano music)
- Now, aren't you glad
I convinced you to hand
onto your apartment?
- Thrilled.
- Well, at least you found out
you really do wanna be a mother.
- But I wanna be Josh's mother.
- We all want stuff we can't have.
I'm tired of tearing about it.
- I'm sorry, I shouldn't have
asked you to come over today.
I'm not just fit for
human consumption yet.
- Stop, I just can't stand
how screwed up you are
over a 10 year old kid.
If it was the guy I could understand.
- Yeah, you know something?
I really don't miss Tom very much at all.
I'm just mad at myself
for being such a pushover,
and for staying too long at the fair.
(Tom and woman laughing and chattering)
- What do you suggest, Claudia?
(Nick clears throat)
- Sorry, well, personally
I prefer this one.
- Tell her it's okay, Claude.
Tell her to let go of me.
- Ah, it's all right, Ava.
I don't think he's dangerous.
Um gentlemen, it you'll excuse me.
- Right, let's say tell you what.
Let's go to my office and uh,
I'll uh, I'll order lunch.
Please, as soon as you can.
- Tell me why I can't
come and live with you.
- Did you come all the way
here on your skateboard?
Do you realize you could've gotten hurt?
That was really dumb, Joshua.
I'm sorry, hey come on, sit down.
Do you want anything?
You know, I miss you too.
- Why can't I come and live with you?
- Because you don't belong to me.
- I don't belong to anyone.
- [Claudia] Josh, Josh,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
That was a stupid think for me to say.
- Don't you think we had
a lot of fun together?
- Yeah, the most, come here.
Now, I know that you're unhappy,
but your father loves you.
- Not as much as you.
- But we're not related.
They have laws about these things.
- The laws are dumb.
- Well, we'll see what we can do, okay?
But in the meantime,
we've gotta get you home.
Now, come on.
- Hi Josh, how you doing?
- Hi.
- Make sure and water the plants, okay.
Especially now that it's getting hot.
- Thanks for bringing me home, Claude.
See ya.
- You bet.
- So, did they tell you
it wasn't your fault?
- Yeah.
- Divorce, it makes you
have to be more grown up,
but still it's better
to live with your dad,
because you don't have
to do all that man stuff.
You know, like take out the
garbage and carry the suitcases.
- Yeah, but I wish I had a
brother or a sister to talk to.
- Hey, me too,
but at least you got
Chuck and a video camera,
and you don't have to take piano lessons.
- Yeah, so did you know
anyone who was adopted?
- Uh, I knew this kid Ethan.
He had a pretty good deal.
They act a lot more scared
of you when your adopted.
- Hello, I wanna talk to
somebody about getting adopted.
- Now look, Mrs. Kent,
I just wanna find out
what is going on here.
- As I tried to explain on the phone
it's my job to investigate
whenever there's probable cause.
- Of what?
- Joshua told us that you're never home.
That you leave him alone a lot.
- He is a kid, he was exaggerating.
Now, do I look like the kind of a man
who would leave a 10 year
old child at home alone?
- Abuse and neglect exists
in all sorts of homes,
all kinds of families.
- You get the hell outta my house.
Nobody comes in here and
accuses me of child abuse.
Now get out!
- I came here simply to
interview you and Joshua.
If you insist on my leaving
I'll be forced to get a court order.
- Okay, okay, you just do your thing.
I'll uh find him, he said
he'd be right around here.
Josh, Josh!
He's right down there on the beach.
- Well then, I think I'll go
down there and talk with him.
- Be my guest.
- They didn't fight or anything.
My friend Rafe said that his parents
were screaming and hit one another.
My dad took me on this camping trip,
and there was this other
woman there named Susan.
I just couldn't understand
why my mom wasn't along.
My dad wasn't too good
at explaining things.
You know, he still isn't.
We had a big, white porch,
and one day when I came
home from my camping trip
my mom was in the rocking chair crying.
She told me she was leaving.
- Do you remember how you felt?
- I asked her if she could
stay for my birthday.
She said no.
- Do you and your dad do
lots of things together?
- Well, he's pretty busy.
You know, he travels a lot,
but he takes me great places
for trips and on the weekends and stuff.
- Like where?
- Fishing in Alaska.
He took me snorkeling in Hawaii
and there was all these eels and fish.
Pretty neat because you
could almost pet the fish,
but they swam away just
before you could get to them.
So, how do you decide who gets adopted?
- Tell me about your friend Claudia.
- Well, she taught me
about plants and stuff.
I know when people are
pretending to like me,
but she really likes being with me.
We don't do anything
special except drive around,
go to the grocery shop.
She never looks at her
watch when she's with me.
She always asked me what I'm
thinking about and how I feel.
She really wants to know.
- You must miss her.
- Feels bad all the time in here.
- Some peoples hearts
are all dried up, Joshua.
You can hear them rattling around inside.
It won't hurt forever,
and it's good to know you've got one.
- You are not going to
allow a 10 year old child
to decided what is best
for himself now, are you?
- The departments evaluation
will be based on my interviews
with all the parties concerned.
Joshua is a thoughtful, sensitive boy,
and I'm sure you're to be
congratulated for that.
I know that it is not easy
to raise a child alone.
Especially when you have
a busy work schedule
and you travel a lot.
- You know, I'm not so sure
that I'm concerned about
the counties evaluation
of my parenting skills.
Now, do you mind telling me
what are your credentials?
What qualifies you to judge me?
- I'm a licensed psychiatric social worker
with 20 years experience
in child placement.
- I may not be the most uh,
sensitive man in the world,
but his own mother walked out on him,
and I love that boy and
I won't give him up.
(light piano music)
- Hi Claude, it's me.
I'm okay, Chuck's fine.
Mrs. Kent acted like maybe I
can come and live with you.
Well, she didn't say no.
And every Christmas we can go to the farm,
and I can make a video.
Yeah okay, I got a new idea
for a story we could work on.
It's about a screwed up family,
but the cool part about
it, it's a family of sheep.
- You want another uh, milkshake?
- No.
- More fries?
- You already asked me
that three times, Dad.
What is it, why are you acting so weird.
- I wanna ask you something.
Was it your idea to call up the county
and ask to be adopted?
- Yeah.
- You sure nobody suggested it to you?
- No, Dad, like who?
- Like, I don't know.
Why did you do it, sport?
- 'Cause I wanna live with Claude.
- Well, you just can't do that.
- [Joshua] Why not?
- Because, hey look, I may
not be some TV show dad,
but I'm the only one you got,
and we were doing okay,
and I know you want a
mom and a regular family,
and I'm sorry that it
didn't work out with Claude.
- It didn't work out with any of them.
You don't want it to work out.
Even Mom, you didn't like so much.
I like having someone to
talk to besides Chuck.
- You can talk to me, sport.
- You're never around.
When you are you're not really there.
- I was there when you were born.
I've always been there for you,
and, and when you go to
college, when you get married,
I will still be there for you.
- You could have all your Sunday's free.
- I don't want all my Sunday's free, Josh.
I mean, it's just now,
you got these bureaucratic dogs,
they're on my back,
and I gotta prove I'm
not some kind of creep.
- I never told them you were a creep, Dad.
I just said I wanna live with Claude.
- I can't believe Tom would neglect Josh.
I mean, he'd be more likely to spoil him.
Buy him too much stuff.
- But you haven't lived
with either one of them
for over five years.
- I've been planning to move
down here since last winter.
I was only 18 when I had Josh.
I couldn't take care of
myself, let alone him.
Well, I tried to five years,
but I wasn't a whole person.
I was just Tom's shadow.
He was so much older, I was
sure he'd be the better parent.
He's done a great job,
even though he's shuffled a lot of women
in and out of Josh's life.
I made a lot of mistakes,
but I want a shot at being his mother.
Don't you think I deserve a second chance?
- Did Joshua's relationship with Claudia
have anything to do with your decision?
- No, I decided to try and do this
before I ever knew about her, I swear.
- I have a really good
job, and I could move.
I could afford a small
house with a backyard,
if that's a problem,
because I know he would
wanna bring the dog in.
- Please, calm down, Miss Casara.
- I'm sorry, it's just that um,
I've been a little nervous lately.
I just miss Joshua so much.
Tom won't let me see him at all anymore.
You know, he actually accused me
of trying to get back at him
by making Josh call you
people about being adopted.
- Why do you think you and
Josh connected so much?
- Well, I think because I'm the first
motherly type girlfriend
that Tom ever had.
He's dated tons of women,
but not one of them could've
cared less about Josh.
- You think Josh was unhappy at home?
- No, not entirely,
but I do think that he's a lot needier
than Tom thinks he is.
I think that he denies the fact
that Josh might have emotional problems.
I mean, he just sort
of says thing like um,
oh, he's a tough little guy,
or he's resilient, he'll surprise you.
- Did you ever see Tom
hurt Joshua in any way?
Hit him or verbally abuse him?
- No, absolutely not.
- Did he ever leave him alone in the house
for long periods of time?
- No, not even for short periods of time.
There was always some sort of housekeeper
or babysitter there.
Look um, I would love to be with Joshua
more than anything in the world,
and I think that I would
be a good mother for him,
but I can't tell you that Tom
is some kind of a monster.
I mean, he's not the most
sensitive guy in the world,
but he's no worse than
most of the men I've known.
He's busy, distracted,
enormously self-centered,
but I don't think that he would ever
hurt Joshua intentionally.
- Well, I appreciate your honesty.
Joshua has told me that you've
shown tremendous respect
for his thoughts and feelings
in a way that no one else has before.
He feels very loved by you,
but these are very confusing
times, Miss Casara.
Family relationships are
a lot more complicated
than they used to be,
especially for a little boy of 10.
Children need categories.
That's how they understand the world,
and Joshua can not fit
you into any category.
He can't call you mother,
or step-mother, or aunt.
Miss Casara.
- Well, Josh doesn't
call Kit mother either.
- I know, but he used to,
and in time he may again.
- But Josh and I need each other.
- I feel for what you're going
through now, I really do,
and uh, strictly off the record,
you could seek legal council.
You might be able to make
a case for visitation,
but do think about it.
I know you care a great deal about Joshua,
and you want what's best for him.
- Now, I gotta go to camp.
Don't worry, boy, you
know I always come back.
Come on, Chuckles, come on buddy.
- It's only gonna be
three weeks, you know,
and at the end of it
you probably won't even wanna come home.
Come on, come on, Chuckles.
- [Joshua] Come on, Chuckles.
(light piano music)
- [Josh Voiceover] Dear Claude.
They made me draw this dumb self-portrait
in arts and crafts.
I really hate this camp, it's so dorky.
I bet Dad forgot to water the garden.
Do they let dogs live in your building?
I miss Chuck and Rafe.
Whenever I miss you,
I just have to look in my
heart and there you are.
Love, Josh.
(light piano music)
- This is a wonderful story,
darling, and very touching.
I'll keep my fingers crossed.
I think any publisher
would be lucky to get it.
- [Claudia] Thanks, Mom.
- And some man will be lucky to get you.
- Mm, I don't want one.
- You will, and maybe next time
you'll be more careful
about who you choose.
- I'll never pick another Tom.
- Should I tell you about
the man I almost married?
His name was Jack and he was charming.
Mama and Poppy didn't approve.
He wasn't Catholic and he wasn't Italian,
which is probably why
I was wild about him.
He was a dreamer and he could
play the piano beautifully,
and then I met your father,
and from that first day
he charged ahead with a
plan for our lives together.
He was hard to resist,
and I made the right decision.
Choose the one who will
sit up with you at 3 a.m.
when your baby has a fever.
- Where did you get all
your certainty from?
- I never had to worry about
making a way for myself,
or having a career or
living in a city alone.
Do you know I have never
even called a lawyer?
- Hmm, I talked to mine again
after I got the letter
from the department.
He thinks it's a longshot to
try and appeal the decision,
but I don't know, I really.
- Want what's best for Joshua.
- Oh Mom, I wish you'd
gotten to know him better.
- I could see he was a lovely boy.
- There's so much of him in my book.
I mean, you have no idea
how extraordinary he is.
He showed me the kind of
person that I need to be with.
I found out what it's
like to be with someone
who really cares about you,
who cares about what you're thinking.
- Claudia, listen to yourself.
He's a 10 year old boy.
- I know, I know it sounds crazy.
I just miss him so much.
I finally found someone who
really needed me, a need in me,
and I just don't think
that I can give that up.
- You have to, you have no other choice.
Kit deserves a chance.
She's his mother.
It'll be all right, darling.
You'll have children of your own.
(knocking on door)
- Hi, Claudia, I'm Kit.
- Hi.
- Thanks for coming.
I really appreciate it.
Come on in.
Did you have any trouble finding it?
I'm not too good with directions.
- No, I know Venice pretty well.
I lived nearby when I first moved here.
- The neighborhood's pretty weird,
but at least I can afford it.
I won't be making too much at my new job.
- What're you gonna be doing?
- Uh, I'll be working at the um,
music center in the box office.
I start next week.
That's as close to the
ballet as I could get.
You wanna see Josh's room?
He hasn't stayed here yet,
but pretty soon he'll be
coming every other weekend.
I uh, tried to fix it
up in a way he'd like.
- I'm sure it's fine,
but maybe we should just.
- You know what he likes.
- All right, I'd be happy to see it.
- I know Josh loves you.
He hates me, there's just--
- Please, don't, he doesn't hate you.
He just doesn't know you very well,
and he's probably a lot
different than you remember too.
You know, he's almost a teenager now.
- I bet the smell of cheese
still makes him sick.
- He'll come around.
You just have to give him some time.
- Will you give us time?
- What do you mean?
- I don't stand a chance
with Josh if you're around.
I've been a failure at
everything I've tried to do.
I couldn't make it as a dancer.
I couldn't make it as a wife.
Let me try and be a good mother.
(both laughing)
- You're fabulous.
- Oh, thank you.
- Hey dude, hit me.
You know, you got a birthday coming up.
Maybe we oughta figure
out what you wanna do.
- I wanna go out to dinner,
same as always, but with Claude.
- Maybe you oughta think about
spending the day with Kit.
- Mrs. Kent said I'm allowed
to see Claude one more time,
and I want it to be on my birthday.
- What about the bathing beauty layout?
- I don't know.
- Okay, what's the problem?
Is the new girlfriend going to be there?
- Oh God, I hope not.
No, it's just that I have so many things
that I wanna say to Josh.
About how much he means to me,
and how much I learned
about myself from him,
and it's just so hard.
I can't believe this is how
we have to spend our last time together.
- I just you would've told him
it was too upsetting for you to come.
- No, it's too important to him.
He picked this event.
- I know, but your torturing
yourself, it's torture.
As much as you miss Josh,
it's being in that
instant fake family again,
that's killing you.
With the dad and the kid
and the you playing the mom.
It's like, it's like a slap in the face,
and honey, you have got to let go.
- I really thought I had.
You know, when I went and saw Kit,
and she was trying to fix
up that little apartment,
I realized that motherhood
is more than just attachment.
- What do you say, sport, lobster?
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- I didn't think you'd come.
- I wouldn't miss your
birthday for the world.
I love the card that
you sent me from camp.
I'm gonna keep that forever.
- And there's this real dorky kid.
I mean, he was swimming and
he really couldn't swim.
I had to hold onto his hair
until the counselor came.
- Well, good for you.
- So, how's your book doing, Claude?
- Well, I sent it to a couple
of publishers in Boston,
and hopefully they're gonna
let me know something soon.
Oh, and I changed Andy's name to Joshua.
- Really, you did?
(light piano music)
- All right (laughs).
Did you make a wish?
- Yeah Dad, I did.
- Well, we thought maybe we'd
check it out, just this year.
(light piano music)
Josh, maybe you oughta give Kit a break.
It's only every other weekend.
So, don't make her work so hard, okay,
and try to deal with all
that emotional stuff.
You don't wanna end up like your old man.
- I'll try, Dad.
- Okay, sport.
- Come on Chuck, come on, good boy.
(Chuckles barks)
Ooh Chuckles, your favorite.
Just like the ones on the beach, yeah.
- All right, look what I've got.
- Oh great.
- Yeah, they almost done?
- Yep, I cooked the
first one for Chuckles.
- For Chuckles?
- Yeah.
- [Kit] All right, well,
I'll get you a bun.
- [Joshua] Okay.
- Okay, all right, there you go.
- Mm Chuckles, your favorite, yeah.
- He does like it.
- Yep.
- Surprise.
- Ooh.
- I can't believe it.
- How about changes?
- Nope, all they want me to do
is work on the title and the cover.
(Nick exhales deeply)
(upbeat jazz music)
- Congratulations, hon.
- [Claudia] Thank you.
(Claudia gasps)
(both laughing)
- Kit.
- Are you okay?
- I can't sleep, it's too hot.
- Me neither, what should we do?
- I don't know.
Well, my school's having a
Halloween Ball this year,
and I only know how to do-si-do.
Do you think you could
teach me how to slow dance?
- Sure.
Okay, you ready?
Put your hand here, right here.
Ready, we're gonna make a box.
One, two, three.
Good, one, two, three.
That's good, good.
Look up, look up.
- Come on, oh no.
- [Kit] Go faster.
- [Joshua] Oh no.
- (laughs) No, try again, come on.
All right, one, two, three.
One, two, three.
Good, good, gotta look up.
Don't you wanna see who
you're dancing with?
Wanna go faster?
- [Joshua] Okay.
- A little faster.
Ready, now make a square.
(Kit laughing)
- Tell me a joke, you
don't know any jokes?
- Nah.
- Nah, don't you hear them in school?
- [Joshua] No.
- [Kit] Hey look, Josh.
- [Joshua] Oh neat.
- We could hang these.
Who does that remind you of?
- [Joshua] You.
- [Kit] Yeah (laughs).
Some of these are great.
- Yeah.
(light piano music)
Can I go in, Mom?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- There you go.
(light piano music)
Here you go.
Hi, how are you?
- Hi, how are you?
(Claudia giggles)
- You first.
- I'm doing pretty good, Claude.
- Good, me too, how's Chuck?
- Oh, he's great, he just
got his teeth cleaned.
- Good, and how's Rafe?
- Well, his parents are
trying to get back together,
so he's moving back to New York,
but I get to spend
Thanksgiving vacation with him.
- [Claudia] Oh, that sounds like fun.
- Yeah.
- You know, I almost called
you to tell you about the book.
I even thought about trying
to see you one last time.
- It's okay, Claude,
I'm just glad we were
walking by and I saw you.
- Me too.
- Now your book came out.
- Mm mm, it's our book.
This is for you.
(light piano music)
(MultiCom Jingle)