(I got the feeling playing)
♪♪ out of my way
♪♪ I got something to see
♪♪ wasting my time
♪♪ I never felt this way before
♪♪ is this
something I can't see?
♪♪ tell me what's it mean to me
♪♪ never felt this way before
♪♪ I can't take it anymore
♪♪ I got the feeling this time
♪♪ I got the feeling
♪♪ that I'm gonna
score real big this time
♪♪ I got the feeling this time
♪♪ and I wanna say,
do, do, do, do, do, do
♪♪ do, do, do, do, do, do, do
♪♪ I'm losing track of time
♪♪ so please refresh my mind
♪♪ is it just a dream or
should I up ends with the scene?
♪♪ I don't wanna feel intense
♪♪ got this pounding in my chest
♪♪ never felt this way before
♪♪ I can't take it anymore
♪♪ I got the feeling this time
♪♪ I got the feeling that
I'm gonna score a win this time
♪♪ I got the feeling this time
♪♪ and I wanna say,
do, do, do, do, do, do
♪♪ do, do, do, do, do, do, do
how you doing?
Fine.
I'm here to change a 20.
I like a man with money.
Yeah?
Woman: Next, please.
Freeze, everybody! (All gasping)
This here is a bank robbery.
(Grunting)
Sam: See what happens
when you try to get cute?
Stick around,
kid. Watch the fun.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
this is a real bank
robbery. Trust me.
Now, everybody but the
tellers, down on the floor.
All fine.
Here, son, you're
gonna help me collect.
Open that bag wide.
You can start by putting
your own money in there.
My 20? Absolutely,
set a good example.
Are you gonna contribute
to our little venture? Huh?
It's a worthy cause.
Uh-uh-uh-uh! Where's big bills?
I haven't any larger bills.
Oh, no large bills.
Now, do you believe her?
Nelson: Please, lady.
Sam: Come on. Come on.
Atta girl. Atta girl.
What's your name, boy?
Ron, sir.
Lilly: Ronsir, you hear that?
You wouldn't want Ronsir here
to die a virgin now, would you?
Sam: Faster. Faster, honey.
Quicker, quicker, quicker!
That's it, girl, move fast.
Thank you very much.
Bunsy, oh, what
a beautiful name.
You ever get tired of the
same old dull routine, bunsy?
'Cause I'm gonna need some
help spending this here money.
Keep your mind on the business.
All right. Now, I want
everybody to sing
on top of old smokey, okay?
It's one of my favorites.
Now, sing it loud
and sing it clear.
And don't anybody stop
until you're all the way through.
And don't think about getting
up till you're done. Go ahead.
All: ♪♪ on top of old smokey
no, on key, for Christ's sake.
♪♪ all covered with snow... ♪
let me hear that
familiar refrain.
What took you so long, huh?
Come on! Come on! Why
did you ask them to sing again?
I'm driving. Push over.
Lilly: Come on, Sam. Let's go!
Tony: Go. Go.
The cops!
(Sirens wailing)
Can you make the cops sing, too?
Where are you going?
(Tires screeching)
(Tony yelps)
(Horn honking)
Yeah!
They're closing in on us.
(Car horn blaring)
Look out, they're
sandwiching us!
(Lilly yells)
(Police cars crashing)
Sam: Yeah, so much
for them. Let's go.
Tony: Come on! Come on! Go!
You're not losing them.
What kind of driver are you?
Every cop in the
county's after us.
Come on! Move it. Move it!
You want me to
take over? Come on.
Come on. Come on. Go!
Don't you have a plan?
(Truck horn blaring)
(All screaming)
Lilly: Ha-ha! This is great.
(Laughing)
Nice move, pop. Real nice move.
(Horn honking)
Tony: Ahhh!
Sam: I gotta find
another line of work.
Ohh...
Hey, Lilly, what's this crap
about me dying a virgin?
Well, you are. Yeah,
but it's embarrassing.
Hey, hey, hey, knock it off.
I was only playing with
him, for Christ's sake.
You slammed the hell out
of him. You call that playing?
I mean, Lilly, you gotta
knock off this ninja stuff
before you end up
killing somebody.
Well, hey, I gotta practice.
We're in it for the money, honey, not
so you show off your damn black belt.
(Sirens wailing)
Ah-ha. Here they are, pops.
Plan a?
Definitely plan a.
Look, dad, 385 east
intersects one mile up the road,
and just beyond that are
the dirt roads we need, okay?
I got you. Buckle up, team.
Oh, pop, uh, they're gaining.
Oh, yeah? I hadn't noticed.
Tony: What are you laughing
about? They're right on our tail.
Okay, dad, here it is, here.
Right past this junction.
It's that road we want.
Beautiful. Just beautiful.
A thing of beauty.
(Whooping)
(Fast-paced music plays)
This is how fast
you're gonna go, huh?
Excuse me for
interrupting, Tony, pop,
but they're like gaining
and they're after us again.
(Lilly whoops)
Tony: We're trapped! (Laughing)
Hey, dad. Dad, dad,
dad. Now hit the junkyard.
Got it.
You see, me and Nelson,
we scouted this place.
Tony, learn the value
of preparation, my man.
The value of preparation.
Dad, the manure. Go
to the manure, pop.
(Whooping)
All right, hang on.
Hang on.
(Screams)
Lilly: (Whoops) Yeah!
(Whoops)
Dad, remember, stay to
the right. Stay to the right.
You gonna hit the shit?
Sam: No, he is, butthead.
Lilly: Yes. Yes!
(All whooping and laughing)
Okay. Good.
Dad, we're surrounded.
Oh, my god.
All right, pop. Plan b.
Now, stay to the right
of the ladder, okay?
Lilly: Look out!
(Lilly laughing)
(Whooping)
All right, pop. Plan c.
Pass the dogs,
through the fence.
Sam: Piece of cake.
(Whoops)
(Dogs barking)
Nelson: All right,
dad. Dad, stay left.
Stay left to the ramp, pop.
Tony: Oh no, not again!
Lilly: Yes. Yes!
Sam: Airborne. (Whoops)
Yeah!
Touchdown!
(Laughs) Look at that, pop.
I need a picture of this.
Tony: That's
brilliant. Just brilliant.
Ha-ha. Suckers!
Lilly: Suckers!
Tony: Suckers!
Hey, I could have done
the same if I had the chance.
Butthead.
Nelson: Butthead.
Yeah. I just don't
get the chance.
I sure hate to ditch this
baby. It did all right by us.
Yeah.
Oh, go get your baby shoe.
That's embarrassing, okay?
Brings us good luck. Go get it.
Hi.
Hey.
Wow.
You wanna give us a minute here?
Can you swear
you're gonna make it?
Lilly: No, you know
how I get after a job.
I know. You know
I'm good for it, right?
I just got a couple
of things I gotta do.
Okay?
Later, right?
Yeah. A little later.
You know, and how
could anybody get it on
with the goddamned
kid around all the time?
I know he's your kid,
Sam, but enough's enough.
He's really starting
to get on my nerves.
Well, you better get used to it,
because he's part of the package.
Well, maybe it's time we
exchanged that package.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means, I thought maybe
just you and me alone.
He's my son.
You know, I think
you're goin' soft
in all the wrong places.
(Punches) (Groans)
(Grunts)
Hey!
Hey, pop.
So, what's next?
(Sighs) Webster.
Webster? Webster. Yeah.
You know, the bank I've
been telling you about.
It's in Webster.
Nah. No, that's one
bank we don't need to see.
I don't wanna see it,
dad, I wanna Rob it.
Forget Webster.
Nelson, look...
Lilly, all she's been saying...
Ignore her.
See, she's got certain
physical attributes...
Hooters, Hooters,
call 'em Hooters.
Yeah...
You got it.
But she got nothing upstairs.
So you're calling Lilly a moron?
Not to her face, I'm not.
(Both chuckling)
Not me. Uh-uh.
So, how much we rake in?
Uh, let's see...
Just over $12,000.
Okay, so that
makes four for you.
Four for me.
And four for Sam.
Ho.
Since when?
We always split it four ways.
Since now.
I'm not giving no snot-nosed
kid an equal share.
Pop?
Split it four ways.
Make me.
This isn't about the
money now, is it?
No.
It's not about the money.
(Grunts) (Groans)
Tony, it's mine.
It's mine, Tony, hands
off. Leave it alone.
I'm such a short
fuse. I'm sorry, Sam.
You're just short, period.
Hey, I was just kidding.
Come on, get over here.
(Grunting)
(Ripping)
Ohhh!
Tony: Kick him in the head, lil!
Lilly...
Tony: Money,
money. Money, money.
Sam: Losing my Patience, Lilly.
Tony: More. More, I need more.
Got enough.
Ho, good shot.
(Tony laughing)
Go. Go stand on top of him.
(Gunshot)
Tony: Oh, shit.
Hey, Lilly.
Hey, pop.
You wanna get the
hell off him, please?
Yeah, right.
(Cocks gun)
Get off, Lilly.
Phew.
Hey, pop, how are you?
I've been better, boy.
Okay, you two, this
partnership is now dissolved.
Get the hell out of here, okay?
Let's go.
How you doing?
Women, boy, women.
You got your ass
kicked is what happened.
(Car engine rumbling)
Lilly: Watch out for your dad.
Looks like he's having
a tough time of it.
(Toots horn)
I guess that's what's
called a property settlement.
(Laughing)
With Lilly's brains and
Tony's sense of direction,
they deserve each other.
(Chuckling)
She kicked my ass.
Oh, pop, you get your ass
kicked all the time, it's unbelievable.
Nelson: Hey, dad, dad.
Someone's pulling in right here.
Sam: Nah, Japanese.
Japanese.
What about this gray one?
But it's another Japanese job.
So, what? What is it with
you and these Japanese cars?
I'm not getting behind the
wheel of a Japanese car.
Why not?
Because if you
steal a Japanese car,
the owner goes to the
insurance company,
he gets the money, he goes
out, he buys another Japanese car.
So?
If you steal American, the owner
goes out and he buys American,
and if you steal American,
you help the economy.
Ah-ha.
Yeah. Here.
That's the one. Nuh-uh.
Let's go. Aw, come on, dad.
So I heard about this
new store they just opened.
They have these great
shirts on sale, 50% off.
(Both whistling)
(Engine starting)
(Laughs) Whoo!
(Music playing on radio)
Slide over.
I wanna drive.
Nelson, I've been thinking.
You're 16 years old, you
can't Rob banks forever.
Come on, dad.
Look... Look at you.
No, I mean it.
Soon as we get the money, it's
gonna be high school, college,
and you're gonna get your MBA.
My MBA?
Where do you think the best
criminals make their killing?
The backwoods of Colorado? No!
It's wall street.
Wall street?
That's where the best and
the brightest criminals are.
(Chuckles) Where
did you read this?
You may laugh now,
but someday when you're sitting
on park Avenue, sipping your Martini,
you're gonna thank your
old man for that. Okay.
Yeah, I'll call you from
my jacuzzi, pop. (Laughs)
We're gonna get the money, you're
out of the business. That's fine with me.
It really is, you know?
And then you can stop dating
women who beat the shit out of you.
(Both chuckling)
Nelson: Uh-oh.
Sam: Now, stay cool.
Ooh, look at that.
Ticket?
I must have lost my ticket.
Oh, you lost your ticket,
you gotta pay for a full day.
Oh, what would that
set me back, little lady?
6 bucks.
6 bucks? Yeah.
You got any money on you?
(Unzipping)
Here you go, sweetness.
Keep the change.
100 bucks?
That was thoughtful.
Didn't you have
anything smaller?
Ah, look, come on, dad, did
you see how cute she was?
Look, this way she'll
never forget me.
Besides all that, that's $100
Harvard will never see, okay?
Is that right?
That's right, pop.
How about one of
these? Oh, pop, no.
What are you doing?
You know, I like it better this
way, pop. Just the two of us.
Me too, Nelson. Me too.
Dad, can I ask you a question?
Yeah, sure.
You know, if
mom was still alive,
do you think she'd be
robbing banks with us?
I don't know. Uh...
I think she'd want
us to be happy.
Yeah? Yeah.
Yeah.
Does Lilly remind you of mom?
No way. No?
Your mom...
She was...
And Lilly is, uh...
Am I on the hot
seat here, Nelson?
Oh, no. Nothing like that, pop.
It's just, you know, Lilly has these
guzans things, you know, on her chest,
and I know you weren't
after her mind, you know?
Come on, pop.
You date a woman like Lilly when
you don't know what you're looking for.
All right. But
you treat her like a lady with
respect and you don't use her.
Dad, if you don't use
'em how do you get laid?
That's exactly why you're
gonna go to law school.
To learn the answers to
important questions like that one.
Dad, first of all, I'm
not going to law school.
Second of all, no one gets
laid at law school, okay?
They all end up yuppies.
You got a one-track mind, boy.
Thank you. I'm like you, pop.
Like father, like son.
(Both laughing)
Amen.
All right, pop.
(Country music playing)
All right. Here we go.
(Rap music playing)
Now, pop, don't
you like my music?
I love it, Nelson, I love it.
Look at that horse
taking a dump out there.
Where, pop?
(Country music playing)
Now, what is this?
It's some guy wearing
a cowboy hat, pop.
That's music, boy.
I don't listen to country.
I'm changing this.
(Rap music playing)
Now, pop, get into the
groove with this for a minute.
Well, let me see it.
Let me see the groove.
What's the groove?
The groove, pop.
Just the mellow...
Just doing like this,
here. Yeah, yeah.
The groove, pop. Like this here.
Yeah.
I'm getting seasick.
What are you doing?
Leave this.
What is wrong with you, pop?
There you go.
See, see how nice that is?
Just relax.
(Pop music playing)
How you doing, pop? Good.
Yeah? Yeah? Good.
Good. Good. Good.
Yeah, it's getting
out, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
(Both laughing)
That's it. Take this.
Okay.
Look, pop, Conesville's
100 miles out of the way.
I still say we hit Webster.
(Thunder cracking)
Nelson...
We can circle back
in, what do you say?
Dad, look, Webster,
okay? It's a piece of cake.
The timing is right for Conesville,
go ahead, read that clip.
All right, pop.
"All funds from the week's
lottery will be deposited
"in the Conesville post
office, where the winners may
"appear to cash
in their tickets."
Music to my ears!
It's Conesville, I
got that feeling.
Nelson, I got the feeling.
♪♪ boy I got that feeling
♪♪ I got that feeling ♪
work of art, pop, work of art.
(Whistles)
Sam: Aw, miss Lucy!
All right, check it out, pop.
Attempting to do what
women do while they drive.
What's this? What?
Five o'clock shadow.
Did you shave?
I told you not to shave,
it makes it grow faster.
So what, pop?
Here. Here.
Use it.
So, you tell me not to
shave, but I'm shaving.
Use it.
(Razor buzzing)
I'll smear my
lipstick to this, pop.
Uh, uh, uh!
Here. Here. Here.
That's it. "That's it."
Looks like a baby's ass.
Yeah.
Hey, you know what, dad?
I'm so cute I might even enter
the local beauty pageant out here.
(Both laugh)
Pretty as you are, you may win.
Hi.
Can I help you, miss?
Yes, you can.
Can I have some change for
the stamp machine, please?
(Door buzzes open)
How you doin', Joe?
Fine, as soon as I
hand over this stuff.
Big winnings for someone, huh?
Here you are, babe.
(Softly) Thank you.
Nice day, ain't it?
Hey, maybe we can go out
and have a cherry coke later.
Up! Up! Up! Put 'em up!
God, I love to say that.
All right, where's the
money? What money?
The lottery money, man!
I got no lottery money, mister,
this is the post office here.
Where you goin', sweetness?
Won't you come join us? Yeah.
Don't mess with me, porky.
'Cause the next line
out of your mouth
and sweetness here, she's
gonna buy the farm. Got it?
Hmm?
Oh, hey, be subtle.
Little twitch, huh? You nervous?
Join us.
Don't shoot! Don't
shoot! He's got a hostage!
Hands in the air!
Hands up. Hands up!
Reach for your guns slowly
and put them on the floor.
Thumb and index finger
on the butt. Come on!
Ah. All right. All right.
Now, my little girl scout here,
she's generously volunteered
to help me, haven't you, honey?
Please co-operate for her sake.
Okay, this is like our old
private drawing here, isn't it?
You ever see a real
lottery winner, baby?
Okay, now, I want you to sing
the national anthem, all right?
Sing it loud and clear, don't
move till you're done. Now start.
Come on, start!
All: (Weakly) ♪♪
o say can you see...
Sing it with meaning!
This is a federal post
office, for Christ's sake!
(Forcefully) ♪♪ by
the dawn's early light
♪♪ what so proudly we hailed
♪♪ at the twilight's
last gleaming... ♪♪
(alarm ringing)
Jesus, it's getting so you
can't trust nobody these days.
Come on.
(Laughing)
(Tires screech)
Nice going, pop.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
We're all clear.
(Sirens wailing)
Whoops.
Excuse me. My mistake.
Yeah, you spoke too fast, son.
Well, lose 'em.
Would you put your
damn foot on the floor?
In an event like this,
we would take plan b.
B it is. Okay.
Ready, pop? Yeah.
All right, let's see
what he's got, okay?
Hold tight!
Stay with me, baby.
(Both whooping)
Here we go.
Oh, yeah.
Now, step on it.
(Yelling)
Come on!
Whoo-hoo! Here,
watch it. Watch it.
It's like the derby again, boy.
Parking structure, there it is.
I got it.
That way. That way.
Brace yourself, pop.
We're goin' for a ride.
Sam: Hold on to your wig!
Whoa!
Whoo!
That's my pops!
Whoo-hoo!
Well, I tell you, boy, plan a definitely
would have been easier on my kidneys.
You and me, dad,
you and me. The team!
Like always, kid, like always.
Piece of cake, pop.
Whoo! We got a bundle. Ha-ha!
Oh, shit.
Oh, dad.
How did they get a
roadblock so quick?
Stay cool. All right.
Yeah, we can beat this rap.
Cop: Stop your vehicle.
Get out of your vehicle and...
Yeah, all right, dad,
you're doing good.
Ain't no big thing,
kid. All right, dad.
Damn it. What?
We have you
surrounded. Shit, dad.
Hey, dad, that thing
right there, the winch.
What? Come on,
just get out, get out.
Trust me.
Dad.
Cop: Put down your gun.
Dad, the gun. Put it on me.
Release the hostage.
Give me the binoculars.
Hey, what's going on?
Dad, put the gun on me.
Dad, the gun. Yeah, good.
Let the girl go.
All right. Good. Put
your weapon down
and let the girl go.
All right. Dad, dad, below
you there's a belt, a harness.
Tell me to go down and get it.
Tell me to go down... Yeah, that's
good. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That's good.
All right. Put this around you.
We have you surrounded.
All right, dad. Please
release the hostage.
Over here. Over here, dad.
There's one. Tell me to go get this.
Here.
Thanks a lot. You've
been a really big help here.
Real convincing, pop.
All right, step back here.
Let's go. Move back.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, dad, don't look down.
Sorry. Don't look down.
So, we're going over, okay?
Oh! You don't have to look down.
Oh! I told you. Are you ready?
I can't.
You got no choice.
Okay, we can do this.
Remember, hold your fire.
He's got someone with him.
Please release the hostage
now. Come on, let's go.
I repeat...
Put your weapon
down and let the girl go.
We have you surrounded.
Now, come on. Breathe.
Yeah. Yeah.
Come on. Come on.
Please, put down your weapon.
Oh, shit. Oh, pop,
that was our weapon.
Holy moley.
You ready? No.
Good.
Here we go. Hold on.
All right. That's it. That's it.
All right. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I'm getting queasy.
Don't puke on me!
Puke over there,
there's plenty of room.
Cop: Move in,
men. Move in. Unit 7.
Move in. Move in.
Come on. Let's go.
Unit 8.
Come on, dad. Yeah.
Hurry. You're doing good.
You all right? Yeah.
All right.
Piece of cake. Piece of cake.
(Wind whistling)
You all right? Yeah.
(Tires screeching)
(Both screaming)
Oh, dad! Oh, shit!
(Screaming continues)
Dad!
Are we dead?
I don't think so, man.
Oh, good. I don't want
to die a virgin, pop!
Oh, god!
Sam: You all right? Yeah.
That was beautiful.
Yeah. What a ride.
Hey!
(Both cheering)
This thing works!
(Whooping and laughing)
(Laughing)
All right, boys.
Let's reel 'em in.
Whoo!
Oh, dad... Oh, it's
all over, Nelson.
No, dad, dad, it's
never over, okay?
Unhook us. What?
Come on, dad, unhook us.
Unhook us. The higher we
get, the longer the drop, pop.
Do I have a choice?
Both: No.
(Laughing) Got 'em.
(Screaming) Oh, dad! Dad!
Oh, no.
(Both screaming)
(Gasping)
They're getting away.
Nelson!
Where are you, boy?
Dad! Dad!
Dad, I got the money!
(Yells indistinctly)
Come here, boy. Come on.
We made it!
Come here. Come here!
Come on. We did it, boy.
Dad, we did it! And we're alive.
Come on.
We did it!
And we're fine!
Are you all right? I'm okay.
Are you okay? You okay? Yeah.
We made it, dad.
Dad, we were flying!
Me and you, we're gonna
revolutionize the way people Rob banks!
You and me!
Dad, where's our next bust, huh?
Ain't gonna be one,
Nelson. We're out of stealing.
No, no, no, no, dad! Webster!
Yeah, Webster. No, dad,
the vault's gonna be loaded!
It's over!
Oh, dad...
Where to?
Respectability, boy.
Mmm. Mmm.
Mmm. Hurry up
and eat that thing.
I'm hungry.
Come on, Lilly, we just did
it two hours ago! I'm pooped.
What's the matter?
You didn't like it?
No, of course I did.
It's just... I don't
think I'll be able...
(Exclaims)
(Panting)
So, how long do we
have to stay here?
I told you. Till Sam and
his little shit son show up.
And so, why do
we need them, huh?
I'm smart. We can
do the bank ourselves.
(Tony moans)
What's our room number, Tony?
Uh...
So, how do you know
they're gonna be here?
Because the kid said Webster.
And when they show...
I'll grab the little snot.
(Exclaims)
(Moaning) Then
he'll make us rich.
Come here, my stallion.
(Imitating neighing)
Lilly: Hyah!
I don't believe this.
I'll show you how
serious I am, Nelson.
Come on, boy.
Can I help you, sir?
Uh, how much for this one?
The Pontiac?
Your lucky day.
This one's on special.
A steal. $3,600, it's yours.
How much for cash?
Cash, I can give it to you, and
I'm practically giving it away,
for $3,300.
$3,200.
A deal. Deal.
Pay the man, son.
(Scoffs)
You wanna drive?
Yeah, I wanna drive.
Wanna have some fun?
Yeah, I wanna have
some fun. Pop, I'm bored.
You go high, I go low.
I take high.
All right, ready?
All right, I'm gonna
let go. Grab the wheel.
I got the wheel, pop. Whoo-hoo!
(Chuckling) Whoo-hoo!
Let's get 'em,
pop. I got the gas.
Yeah. You gotta cut down
on the hamburger meat, pop.
(Laughing) Keep
your foot on the gas.
(Whooping)
All right, let me get
the gas. Let me get...
You got it. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
(Laughing)
All right. You know, pop, I still
say we should've stolen this vehicle.
Aw, get used to it, Nelson.
Dad, what's so big about
saddle river, anyway?
I'll tell you when we get there.
Could I have some change or
something? May I get a soda up ahead?
Boy, there is no rest
for the weary, is there?
Look, pop, I only
have hundreds, okay?
Take it all.
(Laughing) You're giving
me like $8 in change.
Where did you get this stuff?
I'm sorry. Go to sleep, pop.
Slow down, Nelson.
Slow down.
(You make me feel playing)
♪♪ I wanna feel
free like a bird, yeah
♪♪ I wanna roam
worlds not my own
♪♪ I wanna see the
light in the morning time
♪♪ I wanna feel beautiful
♪♪ not trying to smuggle you
with false infatuation, baby, no
♪♪ not trying to tell that
♪♪ I love you and I
can't live without your love
♪♪ you make me
feel like I wanna feel
♪♪ and I mean,
you make me feel like
♪♪ I wanna feel
when I'm with you
♪♪ you make me feel like
♪♪ I wanna feel... ♪
food. We're here.
You've been snoring.
Right.
(Groans)
Good ol' saddle river.
(Grunts)
Come on, pop.
Five stars.
Waitress: Coffee?
Yeah.
Okay.
Exactly where are we, Nelson?
Uh... we're at a diner.
A diner, where?
Uh...
We're at a diner in Utah.
You drove us to Webster.
We are in Webster,
boy, and that's dirty pool.
Yeah, yeah, dad, it's
dirty pool, it's dirty as hell.
I figure that'd mean we're even.
What?
All right, dad, you know how a couple
of miles back we stopped for soda pop?
There was a clerk hanging out, you know,
so, I go up and I start talking to him,
and I find out one very
ugly fact about saddle river.
An all-boys prep school?
(Scoffs) Nice
try, pop. Nice try.
Dad, what do you have
against Webster anyway?
Why are you frowning?
I mean, look
outside that window.
Look outside this window.
Look at that, dad.
That's one hell of a bank!
Dad, look. Look, dad,
it's like taking out sheep.
You know, it just keeps coming.
Look at this. Right
on schedule, pop.
It's a piece of cake.
No.
Yeah.
All right, deposit everything in
the bag, and nobody gets hurt.
Not even this scrawny
little kid here! (Laughs)
I tell you, you got
beautiful decor in this bank.
(Electric toothbrush buzzing)
I'd like to report a
robbery in progress.
(Electric toothbrush buzzing)
All right, time to move
back down on the line.
Hello, Mrs. Gates, how
are you this morning?
All right, little
faster, please.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
Let's move right down the
way here. Move right down.
Right on down.
Hi, young lady, how are you?
Okay, everybody. We're
moving right along here.
Do you want to wake up,
son, or do I have to shoot you?
Is that it? Come
on, a little faster.
Thank you.
That's it. Let's go.
All right, kid.
All right, now...
One more little favor.
I want everybody to
sing deck the halls.
Don't stick your nose out the
door or junior here is going to get it!
Start singing!
♪♪ deck the halls with...
Louder!
♪♪ with boughs of Holly... ♪
(laughs) I can see
the snowflakes now.
Okay, come on.
Ready? Yeah, yeah.
Let's go.
Cops: Freeze!
Cop 1: Hold it right there.
Cop 2: Drop the
gun. Cop 1: Drop it.
Cop 3: Move in, move in!
Cop 4: Grab the hostage now.
Get him out of there.
(Indistinct chatter)
Get him out of here.
Cop: Get him down.
Somebody get
that kid out of here.
Come on. All right.
Let's go. Let's go.
Tony: So, what's our move now?
We wait.
And then I go in and claim him
as his sister and legal guardian.
By that time, he'll
be glad to see me.
You'll see.
You don't look
like nobody's sister.
(Gasps)
When I want it, I'll take it.
Yeah.
But right now,
we have business to attend to.
Business.
(Groans)
(Woman humming)
(Television blaring)
♪♪ well, good
night, baby, so long
♪♪ and don't you cry for me
♪♪ when I'm gone
♪♪ hush-a-bye
♪♪ sail along
♪♪ close your eyes
♪♪ soon I'll be home
♪♪ and when the sky... ♪
newsreader: The entire town
of Webster was in shock today
by the daring daylight robbery
at the Webster national bank.
The alleged bank robber has
been identified as one Sam Potter,
formerly of Denver, Colorado.
The young boy who
refuses to identify himself,
and who the police
believe to be a runaway...
Jesus!
Cop: Come on, son, at least you
could tell us where you're from.
Does it matter?
There might be a
reward coming to you.
But your folks would have
to show up to sign for it.
Cop 2: Excuse me
for a moment, sheriff.
(Whispering indistinctly)
Hi, Nelson.
Who the hell is that
with him? Who knows?
Let's go. Come on.
So who are you?
I'm an old friend of your dad's.
Where do you know my dad from?
We were in the
demolition derby together.
Oh, shit!
What? What?
I left my iron on.
Oh. That's not good, is it?
It certainly isn't.
Uh-uh. Sorry!
(Tires screeching)
Come on. Keep up. Yeah, yeah.
Come on, get off
the road! (Screams)
Man: Learn to
drive you... Shmuck!
Road hog!
(Car horn honking) (Screaming)
Jerk!
(Crashing)
She got a faster car.
You drive just like my dad.
Who do you think taught me?
My dad taught you how to drive?
I told you, we were
in the derby together.
What's your name?
Lorraine.
Lorraine, huh? Yeah.
(Mouthing)
No, sorry, I haven't
heard of any Lorraine.
You know, me and my dad, we're
like this. He tells me about everybody.
Oh, yeah? Uh-huh.
How many everybodys
have there been?
About 2,000.
Look, Lorraine, relax. Okay?
It's not like there's a fire.
I don't see any smoke.
Hi, Lorraine. I
got to get my iron.
I've already got it.
Oh, thanks.
Who's this?
Nelson. Nelson's going to
be staying with me for a while.
Hi, Nelson.
Hi.
Woman: Honey?
That's my mom, I got to go.
Bye, Lorraine. Bye-bye.
Bye, Nelson. Bye.
Lorraine: Nelson?
Who is that?
That was my
neighbor's kid, honey.
I'm teaching her
how to drive a stick.
Honey? Yeah, honey.
I could teach her, I
could drive anything.
What's this?
Oh, that was... when I played
at the salt lake amphitheater.
I'm a singer.
You played there? Yeah.
How many does that seat?
Oh, about 8,000.
8,000? Uh-huh.
Oh, 8,000, $15 a ticket...
That's pretty major,
Lorraine. Ooh.
Don't you think that maybe it's
just a little out of your league?
Yeah, well, Lorraine, look, I
wanna thank you very much, okay?
Thank you. But me and
my dad, we have a pact...
One of us gets captured,
the other gets him out.
What if you can't get him out?
Have you even thought of that?
You know, you can't go on
robbing banks for the rest of your life.
One day everyone gets caught.
Lorraine, now you're starting
to sound like my pop, all right?
Look, let me explain
something to you, all right?
Me and my dad, we need the open
roads. We need to roam, you know?
Whenever, wherever
we want to. It's...
Look, Lorraine, all I'm trying to say is
Webster town jail ain't gonna stop us,
no how, no way. All right?
All right.
(Door clattering)
I'm back.
Lorraine: Okay. Here we
go. Nelson: Okay, okay, okay.
Uh-uh. Uh-uh. Uh-uh.
Okay, okay. No, no, no.
What you wanna do, you wanna
easily let your foot off the clutch.
Honey: Okay. Nelson: No, no,
no. No, don't touch the brake.
Don't touch the brake. Oh, god.
Take your right foot
and put it on the gas.
No, don't hit the brake anymore.
All right. See? See?
I'm good at this. Yeah,
I'm good at this. All right.
See. Never drive
like that. Ever. Okay.
It's kind of like this. It's
in and out and then...
It's up, over, up. Up?
Nelson: Just do that.
Take your left foot off.
Good. Smooth, smooth. Good.
There you go. Whoo! (Laughing)
Nicely done, honey.
All right! (Laughs)
All right! You're ready
for the big time, honey.
Yeah, you're ready for the big
time. You're a fabulous teacher.
I love it. Yeah!
Oh, this is great.
(Brakes squealing)
Just stop right here. Stop
right here. Stop right here.
Right here, okay? Stop.
I'll be right back, okay?
Okay.
Wait for me?
No, I'm going to leave.
Yo.
(Chuckles) You're back.
I'm back. Did you
miss me? Of course.
Do you love me?
Get in. Let's go.
What's that?
Oh, these are maps and things of the city. I
like to know where everything is, you know?
Hi! (Laughing)
Hi.
Did you miss me?
You're driving me crazy.
The salt lake city amphitheater?
It's nothing. It's a future consideration
school project thingamagjiger.
Yeah... Pull over here
again. Yeah. Stop right here.
Stop right here. I'll be right
back. Okay? My last stop.
I promise. I swear.
Okay, the first
right you see, pull in.
You're looking at everything
else but my driving!
Oh, you're doing fine, honey.
Pull up here. Pull up here.
Yeah, that's good.
Nelson. Yeah, yeah.
I've never met anybody
so into maps before.
Thank you very much.
Yeah? Yeah, thank you.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Uh, honey...
Uh, we should go.
You wanna go?
Yeah, we should go.
Okay. Well...
Wait.
Let me make sure that I
have everything right first.
Oh, that's great. Now, go
ahead. Go ahead first gear,
second, third, and reverse.
This is first...
And this is second...
(Exhales shakily)
And... this is third.
Wait, you know, I've always
wanted to know, what's fourth?
What's fourth?
Yeah. What's fourth?
This. (Chuckles)
Are you kidding me? There
could be people watching this.
No one's watching. (Laughs)
Oh, god!
Thanks for the lessons.
No, thank you for the lesson.
I got to tell you, third gear...
Oh, third gear.
Third gear was major.
Great. Good. Yeah.
Am I gonna see you again?
Maybe. Okay. Go home.
Oh, I got the feeling!
(Whistles)
Lorraine! Hello.
(Whistling tune)
(Ain't nobody like you playing)
♪♪ well, there
ain't nobody like you
♪♪ no, there
♪♪ and you're
the damnedest thing
♪♪ I ever did see
♪♪ and there
ain't nobody like you
♪♪ and nobody
loves me like you do
♪♪ no, nobody loves
me like you do... ♪♪
(knocking at door)
Yeah?
Planning your next heist?
(Sighs) Yeah, maybe.
Before you wear yourself out, why
don't you come help me with dinner?
Okay. I'll be right there.
Mmm. Not bad for a woman.
Yeah? Wait'll you taste it.
Do you like to cook?
Yeah, when there's someone
to cook for, I like to cook.
It's fun. Yeah.
I'm a good cook.
I cook spaghettios, cold cereal.
Lorraine, can I
ask you a question?
Sure.
In these pictures,
is this your boy?
Lorraine?
Hmm? Your boy.
Is that him?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, that's my son.
Yeah, I figured, but
where... I mean...
I haven't seen him or anything.
(Clears throat)
Why don't we just say I
lost him a long time ago.
I'm sorry. It's okay.
I know what it's like to lose
someone, I lost my dad for
eight hours now.
No, really.
Anyway, I checked the place
out today, it's no problem.
I'm gonna get dad
out, bust in, bust out,
piece of cake, just
like that. No problem.
Who know? Maybe you can.
Yeah, there's just two things.
Now, Lorraine, just
hear me out, okay?
Before you freak
out, just listen to me.
Okay, all right? Please? Okay.
Okay, look, I need a getaway
car and I need a getaway driver.
All right? Look, you can
drive really well, Lorraine.
My dad taught you in
the derby, you know?
And you have a car.
We're gonna eat dinner
together, I'll be all fueled up,
I'll be energized,
it'll be great.
Me and you, we can
do this. I need your help.
Please?
Sit down and eat.
That's not a no.
Sit. That's not a no.
Sit. That wasn't a no.
(Both chuckle)
I can't believe this.
(Engine starting)
(Exhales)
(Crashing)
Oh, Jesus!
(Alarm ringing)
Pop!
You crazy boy. Come on.
Go, go! (Sam whooping)
You all right? Yeah!
I'll pull you right
up, pop. Real easy.
Okay. Nelson, I love you, boy!
I love you, pop.
(Laughs joyfully)
Sam: Wait for your old man.
Come on, pop, let's go, come on.
You outdid yourself this time.
Yeah, yeah, thanks.
Come on, dad.
This way, this way.
(Grunts)
Come on, pop.
Let's go. Let's go!
(Grunts) You all right?
You all right? Come on. Come on.
Up and over, dad.
(Grunting)
Come on, dad.
This way, this way.
Pop, come on, hurry up!
(Sighs)
(Grunts)
Pop, come on, hurry up!
(Yells)
(Screams)
Hey, pop, can you handle this?
Hey, after the bridge...
It ain't shit.
(Both yelling)
Nelson: Dad! Dad!
(Grunting)
You all right?
Come on, dad. Come on.
Let's go, pop. Let's go. Whoa!
Let's go. Come on.
Jesus!
Don't look down, pop.
Yeah, come on.
Lorraine: Come on!
Get in and get down.
(Tires screeching)
Hey. Thanks for
helping out, Lorraine.
Still got that same old
Japanese bomb, huh?
Good cars. Damn good cars.
What?
I better stay out of sight.
(Sighs)
Yeah.
Hey, pop, how come you
never told me about her?
Oh, didn't I?
Huh. It must have
slipped my mind.
Come on.
Come on, pop.
Ooh.
Whoo. So, this is home, huh?
You shouldn't use four-letters
words in front of your son.
(Chuckles)
Well, I like it.
Don't like it too much, you
won't be staying very long.
Nelson. Yeah.
You think your dad and I
could have a minute alone?
Sure. Oh, no, no.
Why doesn't he stick around?
No, no, pop, listen, I
got a new game plan.
We'll talk about it later.
You guys talk, okay?
Nelson. Nelson. What?
Look, I just got
back from jail, man!
I want to see all the
friendly faces I can.
Tell me, Sam,
is this what you've been
up to for the last 12 years?
Robbing banks?
Of course not.
I mean, not the whole time.
Yeah.
I guess the rest of the
time you spent in jail.
Before this, we
never got caught.
Ever. Oh, Jesus.
Mmm, you still
look good, Lorraine.
I knew this town was
going to bring us bad luck.
Luck? This has
nothing to do with luck!
You left me, Sam.
Did you ever think that
maybe I did this for you?
Oh, please.
I mean, you were good.
You had a shot
at a singing career.
How're you gonna get that running
from town to town with a four-year-old son?
I want you to listen to me, Sam.
The only reason that I
helped get you out of jail
is because I know that you are
the only one that boy will listen to.
You have had 12 years with him,
and it's my turn.
I'm keeping him.
(Sighs)
Now I know that you probably
did the best that you could.
But any kid
who hasn't been taught anything
but how to heat up a can of spaghettios
and Rob a bank is not gonna
end up anything but a bum.
Or a dead bum.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Neither am I, Lorraine.
Hyah!
(Karate yells)
(Thuds) (Groans)
Oh, it's you.
Sorry.
You have a funny
way of showin' it.
I was just practicing.
(Karate yells)
(Mumbles in fear)
So?
Did you find her?
I found her.
Yeah, and?
She's singing at the
canyon bar and grill.
Perfect.
You know, since
we got some time,
maybe we could play...
(Karate yell)
I'm gonna go floss.
(Knocking)
Nelson: Password?
"No buttheads allowed."
Perfect. Come on in, pop.
Hey.
Dad, dad. Come here,
come here. Come here.
She beats the hell out
of bazooka-tits, you know.
All right, pop, I
gotta talk to you.
There's been a major
change in my life. Major.
I look different, too. My eyes
look a little glazy or something?
No, no. Why? Ah, come on, pop.
(Sighs) Hmm?
I got laid!
(Chuckling) That's right,
baby. I got the power.
I did it, dad. I broke the
cherry. I leaped the canyon!
And it was good. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Whoo!
You got the feeling, right?
Oh! Did I get the
feeling, pop. (Laughing)
I'm proud of you. Thanks, pop.
Hey, I got some news for you.
What's wrong?
I was just talking
to Lorraine...
Yeah?
And, um... she wants you
to stay with her for a while.
And I thought
about it, and I agree.
Pop, why did you agree?
I thought it was
the right thing.
That's a shitty thing to
do, dad. Watch your mouth.
No, I'm serous, pop.
Now, you watch my mouth.
What's wrong with you, pop?
Man, I break
your ass out of jail,
you turn your back on me all of
a sudden, man, what's going on?
And this chick, Lorraine.
Who is Lorraine?
Pop, she's not
like us, you know?
She is like us.
No, she's not, dad.
She's your mother.
What?
Nelson...
I just wanted you to be with me.
Are you telling me
Lorraine's my mom?
My real mom? I have a mom?
And you lied to me.
You lied to me...
How do I trust you now, pop?
I can't trust you now.
Do you mind getting
out of my room?
A stutter, pop?
What?
You know where
the money is buried.
(Scoffs)
Great.
Thanks.
(Door closes)
(Country music
playing in distance)
Tony: There she is.
I told you she
gets off at 10:00.
Lilly: Lead us
to that little shit.
(Chuckling)
Nelson? Hi.
What are you lookin' at?
Oh, I'm just
looking at pictures.
(Chuckling)
(Door rattling)
Dad's back?
Sam?
(Grunting)
Come on, buddy, let's
go. Come on, move it!
Out!
Nelson! (Cries out)
(Groans)
Don't hang up, don't hang up. I'm just
calling to find out how Nelson's doing.
Nelson is gone, Sam.
What do you mean, he's gone?
Two people came
in here with guns,
she kicked me in the
stomach and they took him.
I couldn't stop them!
(Breathing heavily) I couldn't very
well call the police now, could I?
How long would it take
to get to salt lake city?
I don't know, two hours.
Good. Then do it. I want you to bring
Nelson's notes, maps, atlas, everything.
You know that little cafe
on main and south temple?
Yeah. You meet me there.
And Lorraine? What?
Drive like I taught you.
Right down...
That's got to be it.
No, Nelson would never do that.
Maybe 10...
10...
No, bridge.
We don't do Bridges.
Thank you. You're welcome.
Are you sure this is what
he was working on yesterday?
This is the stuff
that was on top.
I'd assume that's what
he was working on.
Well, it doesn't make any
sense, 'cause it's not his style.
His style?
Look, Nelson is very careful.
He always planned
everything we got into.
But I don't know these places.
Are you trying to tell me that you
let Nelson plan your robberies?
Yeah, sort of.
I can't believe
you're for real, Sam.
Lorraine, these two
people, Lilly and Tony...
Yeah. They're dumb.
So that makes them dangerous.
We gotta find where Nelson's
gonna be and get there.
He's got val verda,
woods cross, Taylorsville,
and a thing for the
salt lake amphitheater.
What?
(Chuckles)
Here it is.
Salt lake amphitheater.
Concert today. Huh?
The salt lake city amphitheater
seats 8,000 people.
At $15 a head,
that's quite a haul.
We don't do concerts,
we're bank robbers.
(Sighs)
(Rock music playing)
You know, plaque is a leading
cause of gum disease in adults today.
Me and Lilly are doing it.
Where is my kid?
Oh! Well, he's
working for us now.
But with just one
small difference.
Money in the bag, boys.
Or I'll blow us all up.
Tony: Here comes your
walking firebomb now.
How you doin', pop?
Lilly: Get in.
Get in.
Now, back up.
The kid's loaded.
You know I'll do it.
Back up!
Use it if Sam
tries to be a hero.
I don't want this.
Now, move it!
(Car engine starting)
(Sirens wailing)
It's my fault, Lorraine.
I know it's your fault, Sam.
And they're going to kill him.
No, they can't set
off that dynamite.
They'll blow themselves up.
Yeah, then they'll toss him.
He's their protection
from the police.
When did you get so logical?
Nelson taught me good.
Move it!
What?
You still got the
kid's road atlas?
Yeah, I got it right down here.
Good. We're gonna try to
figure out his escape route.
His escape route?
Yeah, it's a bunch of lines
marked with a red marker.
Okay. Oh. Here's the salt lake
amphitheater. He circled that,
north on 107,
and then south on old sole...
I got it. Old sole
road. Right, right.
Lorraine: You think you can
get around them and cut 'em off?
Piece of cake.
(Gunshot)
Where in the hell are they?
(Gunshots)
Man: Jesus Christ!
(Both cheering)
Sam!
Sam: Right on time.
Shit.
Move it!
I'm going!
She's crazy!
Come here, you brat!
Sam!
Dad!
(Yells)
Shit! Dad!
I'll give you your dad,
kid. I'll blow you both up!
Look, Lilly...
I'm gonna pull up.
Oh!
Sam: Hold on, Nelson!
Nelson: Oh, god! No, dad!
Hold on, boy!
Come on!
Nelson: Whoa!
Oh, my...
(Screaming)
Hold on, Nelson!
Watch out!
(Gunshot)
All right, I'm gonna
make the move now.
Yeah, dad!
You're with me like
the old days, right?
(Gunshot)
All right now, take it.
(Gunshots)
(Gunshot)
(Grunting)
Nelson: Yeah!
(Groaning)
(Horn blaring)
(Screaming)
(Grunting)
Come on, Sam.
(Screaming)
Whoa!
Ah, no!
Yes!
Yeah!
(Groaning)
Lilly!
(Tires screeching)
Lilly: Tony!
Nelson!
Dad! Hold on!
Dad!
Give me the dynamite, boy.
Hold on!
Hang on, baby!
(Yelling) No!
God...
Sam: Lorraine!
Come on.
Leave me alone!
Come on, Sam.
(Yelling)
(Yells indistinctly)
(Nelson yelling)
Lorraine!
(Screaming)
Sam: Don't let go, boy!
The dynamite, Nelson!
The dynamite.
Dad, I got it!
Sam: Move!
Nelson: Get him, dad!
Oh, Lorraine.
Are you alive?
I don't know. Am I moving?
Only when you bleed.
Where's Nelson?
Oh, Jesus.
Baby, are you all right?
Come here, boy.
She broke my rib, pop.
Take it easy, take it easy.
You got him? Yeah.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
(Nelson groaning)
You'll be okay.
You're all right now.
Tony: Wait,
guys, I'm still here!
I'm down here, don't leave!
Help!
Oh, come on!
It was Lilly's idea.
She's the bad one.
(Sirens wailing)
Oh, no... I'm going,
I’m... The cops!
We're family!
(Screaming)
Come on... fire!
Help!
Please!
Oh, no!
Nelson: You know, I always
wanted to see Canada, pop.
Sam: You know, Nelson,
they don't have cops here.
They got mounties.
What's a Mountie?
(Country music playing on radio)
How am I suppose to...
(Rock music playing)
That's right. It
has a little beat...
(Country music playing)
What are you doing?
Dad, your stuff has no
rhythm, it has nothing.
It has no meaning.
Ask your mom what
she wants to hear.
Mom, you don't wanna
hear this, right? I'm out of this.
(Rock music playing)
This right here, see?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
(Sighs)
Got a problem with this, pop?
I love it, I love it.
You should love it, you know?
Right. Mmm-hmm.
Gives me constipation.
(Laughing)
Then pull up and buy something.
What do you want me to do?
(Stations changing)
(Country music playing)
No, no, boy!
Don't do it!
(Laughing)
(Rock music playing)
Yeah.
Nelson. Yeah.
Nelson, did you bring those,
uh, did you bring any maps,
or atlases for Canada?
Uh, you guys.
From now on, I'm calling
the shots around here, okay?
You guys are going straight
while you can still breathe.
You're absolutely right,
Lorraine. I know I am.
We outgrew the business
anyway, right, Nelson?
Oh, yeah, right, pop.
You see, robberies, they're just
not as easy as they used to be.
Did you see that helicopter,
how quick it was there?
Damn computers. Computers.
Computers. Computers.
Crooks don't stand a fair
chance in a modern world.
But in a less
sophisticated society,
that'll be a... Hey!
Piece of cake.
(All laughing)
(That's the way playing)
♪♪ that's the way
♪♪ it goes
♪♪ that's the way it goes
♪♪ I want to see
what I want to see
♪♪ I want to know
what's in front of me
♪♪ that's the way
♪♪ that's the way it goes
♪♪ I want to be who I want to be
♪♪ I want to say
what I want to say
♪♪ I want to do
what I want to do
♪♪ and I wanna do it
♪♪ and I wanna feel you now
♪♪ that's the way
♪♪ it goes
♪♪ and I say that's the way
♪♪ that's the way it goes
♪♪ that's the way
♪♪ it goes
♪♪ and I say that's the way
♪♪ that's the way it goes
♪♪ I want to see
what I want to see
♪♪ I want to know
what's in front of me
♪♪ yeah, that's the way it goes
♪♪ I want to be
what I want to be
♪♪ I want to see
what I want to see
♪♪ I want to do
what I want to do
♪♪ and I wanna do it
♪♪ and I wanna feel you now
♪♪ that's the way
♪♪ that's the way it goes
♪♪ that's the way it goes ♪