(low talking)
- What's up?
- Pull down your pants.
- Wait, wait.
(moaning)
(car honk)
- Oops.
- Don't forget your glasses, Sam.
- Oh, I've got 'em.
- Hello, anybody home?
- Can I have some salt?
- I'm sorry Dad, do you want it?
- Yeah, after you.
- One second.
Thank you.
- Which of these dressings do I use?
- Well I think you have a choice, Mom.
- Well this one here's
vinaigrette with olive oil,
it's really good.
- I'll put this one on the side.
Which one are you having, Sam?
- I don't know.
- Well here Sam, have at it.
- Good idea.
- Ken.
- Hm?
- Now listen, before you say anything.
I know this deal.
There's this corner downtown.
One corner there's laundry,
the other corner Stop 'N Go,
both going out of business.
Now there's this third place.
We could pick it up for a song.
- Why would you wanna get
involved in something like that?
- Well for the investment, Mom.
- So it's on some hands on kind of thing.
- No, not for us.
- I'm not interested in anything.
- No, we go down there.
- Forget it, Gary.
- Well it s an opportunity
is what I'm saying.
- [Mom] Forget it.
- [Sam] Give him a break, Susan.
- Well, have you the
heard the latest thing
about our esteemed Congressman?
- Mom!
- Why should I shush?
I can't talk about a black
man because Bernice is here?
- [Bernice] Just pretend
that I'm not here.
- Really Gary, if anybody's
being a racist, you are.
He's suing the airlines because he says
he choked on mashed potatoes
on his flight back from
Washington. (laughing)
- I thought he was the
kind to fly private.
- Says they cut his throat.
the airlines offered him, oh I don't know,
free flights for the rest of his life.
But he's holding out for the big bucks.
- Is that a light beer, Ken?
I thought you gave up on that stuff.
- No, no, I've lost a few pounds.
- [Mom] Lincoln.
- Yes ma'am.
- [Mom] Would you go get
my pills out of my purse?
It's in your father's room.
In the beige Capezio.
- I know which one it is.
- May I be excused?
- No you need to wait for desert.
- I don't want desert.
(heavy breathing)
(pop punk music)
- Man I can't believe
I'm eating this shit.
You think there's something wrong with me?
- You eat too much.
- Fuck it dude, everyone
in my family eats too much.
What can I do about it?
- You could eat less.
- Here, you want one?
- No.
- Come on, eat it.
- Stop!
- You want it.
- You're gonna make me wreck.
- Monica.
- What kind is it?
- Well, chocolate,
jelly and honey-glazed.
- Okay, I want a honey-glazed.
Thank you.
(car honking)
- What are you doing?
- I'm honking.
- I'll get out of the car, dickweed.
Think my mother raised
criminals or something?
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
- You mad at me?
- No, should I be?
- No, I certainly don't want you to be.
- Good.
- Hey Danny, can you run us by Taco Bell?
We haven't had nothing to eat yet.
- I don't know, what's in it for me?
- Bean burrito?
- You got a deal.
- Who took the money
off the kitchen table?
- I don't know.
- Jackie!
- I didn't touch your
purse Mom, I promise.
- So who did?
- I don't know.
- Hey look, you're the one with no job,
and you're the one with no money.
- I've got money, Tina.
- Oh yeah, I'm sure you do!
- Just ask me next time, okay?
- All right.
But you're really pissing me off, Mom.
- Nice to see you, Danny!
- See you, Mrs. Clifton.
- Come see me again some time.
- All right.
- Mom!
I wanna talk about this
when I get home, all right?
Because I'm not the person
that took the 20 dollars
out of your wallet.
- Then how'd you know
how much money it was, bitch!
- Fuck you, Tina!
- Come on, let's go, together.
- I'm not riding with her.
- Can you drive?
- Yes, I can drive.
- Yeah, she's a real big girl.
She just got her learner's permits.
- Whatever, Tina.
- What am I supposed to do?
- Just come with me, please.
- All right you guys.
What's your fucking problem?
- What's your fucking problem?
- I don't know, you don't
have to fucking bitch
at every person.
Come on, let's just try to have some fun.
♫ Slip away, yeah yeah
♫ Going too fast around that turn
♫ We'll pull if off baby
and we're gonna burn
♫ Oh yeah
(people talking)
- I need two forms.
- I don't have anything else,
and this has always been fine before.
- Well I need two valid
Ids, one with a picture.
Everybody's gotta have it.
- I can't get in.
- Why not?
- I don't fucking know,
he's just not letting me in.
So stupid.
- It doesn't matter, don't worry about it.
- Fucking asshole!
- Take the seeds out, Tina.
- Man, this stuff will get you so stoned,
I've been stoned all...
- What are y'all doing here?
- What does it look like we're doing?
- Can I have some?
- No!
- How old are you?
- Get your own, man!
- Hey, Tina!
Hey!
- What?
What?
- Hey I don't think this phone is working.
- Did you leave the number?
- Yeah I left the number.
What if he calls back
and it's not working?
- Use that one!
- What other one?
- The other phone, dumbass!
The one over on Jefferson.
- Here's a quarter.
- You think I should?
- Yeah, if you wanna go to Ted's house.
Hurry up!
- Is there a party?
- It's what we're trying to find out.
- Can't you fucking pop a
wheelie or something? (laughs)
- Is it a rave?
- Are you a raver?
What's your name?
- Michael.
- I'm Lincoln.
- Here you go Michael.
- Tina, what are you doing?
- He asked, okay.
- I don't care,
that's fucked up.
- Oh yeah, like you
weren't smoking pot at 12.
- Hey man, let's go.
- What'd he say?
- Oh man, he said we could
come over and hang out
and see what's going on but he sounds like
he's been up for like four days
and you know, we should get going now.
- Alright, let's go.
- Oh man, that is the worst
pot you've ever made me smoke
in my fuckin' life.
Hey what are you doing with our car?
Give me those keys, man.
Hey give me those keys.
- Leave him alone, Danny.
- God.
- Hey let's get out of here.
Where the fuck is (mumbling)?
- Let's go.
(low talking)
(upbeat music)
- What you want one?
- Yeah, I change my mind.
(talking drowned out by music)
- It didn't matter if
they were black or white,
if they backed into the car,
you see what I'm saying?
Like, it was gonna happen.
I mean it is, they did shot (mumbling)
but it'd be different if
they were walking down
the street and they just jumped on him.
Do you see what I'm saying?
That they're, I don't know, I don't think
it's blown that far out of proportion but.
- It's blown out of proportion.
- Yeah.
I don't know.
- But they've been saying that
a large group of black
people at our school
are pissed off.
- There was like, on the
news, did you see the news?
There's like thousands
on them on the campus.
(upbeat music)
- That was good.
(soul music)
(talking drowned out by music)
(laughing)
- No, it's obviously only for a playing.
It's all thick or thin,
it's got little fingers
on it and stuff.
And then it's all thin,
like only the very tip
of it glows.
- Who would want a fluorescent dildo?
(laughing)
We read the directions, followed them,
and it didn't glow.
- You have a very
illuminating dick. (laughs)
What's that, Mr. Happy?
- Watch out.
Hi.
- Hey.
- I didn't know where you were.
- Bullshit.
- I thought you were with Jackie and Tina.
- Sometimes you're so full of shit.
- I know.
- So why do you do it?
- I don't know, cause it's fun.
Come on, let's go.
- Hey, hey could please
get your country ass
off of my plants.
You gotta watch what you're doing there,
you're crushing them,
you're smashing them.
- You think I'm fat.
- Yes man, I think you are a big, fat pig.
- Don't get so defensive.
Good night.
Tina?
- Don't bring me into this dude.
- Adios.
- Later, dude.
- Man what do I gotta do?
Where you guys gonna go?
- I don't know.
- Where you guys going?
You don't wanna go out?
- Yeah, I don't.
- She want me?
- Not like that.
- How do you want me?
- Just come get in the car.
- Are you just gonna leave me here?
- You can stay here if
you want to, I don't mind.
I got plenty of clean towels.
- Don't give me that look.
- I'm not giving you a look.
- Yes you were.
- I wasn't trying to.
- What are you doing?
- Tell me you love me.
- You're hurting me.
- I'm not hurting you, tell
me you can't live without me.
- No stop it, Lincoln.
What's wrong with you?
- Sorry, I was just playing.
I didn't mean it.
- Then what did you mean?
- I don't know.
I was just fooling around.
- I want you to go.
- What can I say?
- You can't say anything.
I'm gonna go to sleep, okay?
- Don't be a bitch.
- How you doing guy?
- Alright.
- You have fun tonight?
- Nice night, huh?
- Yeah.
- Been here long?
- Yeah, too long.
- What you got planned for the night?
- Nothing.
- Would you like to come back to my hotel?
- Alright.
- Okay, tell you what?
Why don't you hop down, get in your car,
I'll wait for you and you can follow me.
- Okay.
- Stand up.
- What do you mean?
- I just wanna look at you.
Go over there.
Stand over there next to the mirror.
Hold your arms up like this.
Make some muscles.
- I don't have any muscles.
- Yes you do.
Look at that.
Keep 'em up.
Good.
Turn around.
All the way.
Hey, how you doing?
- Alright.
- Do you like that?
You like being daddy's boy?
- Yeah, I guess.
- You guess?
- Yeah.
- But you're not sure?
What else do you like to do?
You like that?
- What do you like to do?
- I want you to hit me.
Hit me.
You like that boy?
I thought you liked being daddy's boy.
- No.
- What are you doing?
- Putting my clothes on.
- So that's it?
It's over?
You're just gonna leave?
- Yeah.
- Do you just want a
blow job or something?
- No.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to go.
Look, I'll tell you what,
I'll be back in Memphis
in about two weeks.
This is the room I always stay in.
Why don't I give you the number
and if you want, you can call me,
we can get together and do something.
- Sure.
- I mean, we can get together
and do whatever you want.
We don't have to--
- I think I should go.
Thanks.
- I'd like that.
You liked it for awhile.
Take care of yourself, you're a nice kid.
- Yeah, you too.
- Hey, are you gonna give
me a kiss before you go?
It won't hurt.
There.
That's better.
Thanks.
- Thanks.
(moaning)
- Hey boy, how you doing?
- Fine.
- You don't remember me, do you?
- I remember you.
- Why you don't stop and talk to me?
- I'm just gonna watch some movies.
- Where you go?
You're so cute.
- I'm cute?
- I like those, very cool.
- These things?
Dimples.
- Dimble.
- No, dimples.
- Dimple.
- Yeah.
- You sexy.
- Sexy?
- Yeah, you know that.
Do you gay?
- Why do you care?
- For me?
I don't care.
I like straight guys.
You have girlfriend?
- I don't know.
Are you gay?
- Yeah, I am.
- So you like these places?
Come here a lot?
- Yeah, sometime.
Three time a week.
- Three times a week?
- Yeah.
How about you?
- It don't matter.
- I know you be here tonight.
- How do you know that?
- You know why I come here?
I wait for you.
I know you come here tonight.
- How do you know that?
- I come here and wait for you.
I really like you but I
wanna take time with you.
- Whatever.
- You wanna party tonight?
- With you?
- Who you think?
- What?
Why you not wanna look at me, huh?
I've been here long time. (mumbling)
For you, huh, I don't think so.
Let's go to your house.
- I don't think so.
- Why not?
- 'Cause I said so.
- We talk, we go somewhere,
this plan is good.
- Where do you wanna go?
- I don't care.
I can't stay here no more.
You're so wet.
You hot?
- My father's got a boat.
Do you like water?
- Sure.
- We could go there.
- We buy some beer.
- And what after that, huh?
- I don't know.
It don't matter.
- We could do that.
- You so cute.
Why you go so fast, huh? (mumbling)
This is nice boat.
What up here?
- Just a deck.
- This is really nice, really really nice.
You want another one?
- Sure.
- Boy, I like you boy, you know that?
How I miss you boy.
- What do you mean?
- How we missed again.
I don't think that's happened,
when I miss you last time.
I wanted to, but I don't think so.
- Why didn't you talk to me after then?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
It's always like that.
It's always like that after.
Like why I not want to
have sex with people.
I have sex with guy
and they don't want me.
But if I talk with guy first,
they like me, they love me.
That's what it's like all the time.
You want to love me?
- Huh?
- You want to love me?
- Do I wanna love you?
- Uh huh.
Did you know I love?
- Don't say that shit to me.
- But I do.
- You don't love me.
You don't even know me.
- But I do.
I do love you.
I tell you the first time I saw you.
And I go home and think
about you all night.
Okay, forget it.
Forget it.
- Why are you in such a hurry?
- Forget it, anything.
Let's go somewhere.
We take this boat out somewhere.
- What do you mean?
- On the boat, we go out somewhere,
we talk, drink some more
beers, say something,
we come home.
- We can't do that.
- Why not?
- I just don't think I can.
- You don't think so?
But maybe you can.
No reason, right?
So lets go, we have fun.
- Okay.
- Really?
Boy, I like you boy.
- I should go home and get some things.
- No, let's go.
Now is better.
If you go home, you change you mind.
- Maybe that'd be a good idea.
- Bad idea.
That'd be bad.
- You think so?
- I know so.
You good flirt.
- I'm a good flirt?
- I like it.
Me too.
(radio talking)
Hey boy, where you been?
- I was waiting for you to get up.
- What time is it?
- I don't know.
Late, I think.
I've been up for awhile.
- You want me to get up, you missed me?
You could have woke me up, boy.
I don't mind.
Whatever you want.
- You looked really tired.
- I don't know, I wake a dream.
A dream I rode to (mumbles)
and I win one million
and take you to Vietnam with me.
Then the lady in the
neighborhood, she want to have sex
with me.
This woman wanted me to have sex with her.
That wake me up.
She asked me to come inside her house
and she asked me to take
off all her clothes.
But before I do it, I wake up.
You come in the water,
make you feel better.
Feels very good.
- It was cold this morning.
- It's very warm, perfect.
If I have a lot of
money, I buy house here,
and I go Vietnam and I
buy house for my mom.
(mumbling)
- You dream a lot.
- But I never will.
- I'm worried about my dad.
- No, don't.
Don't think about us or talk about us.
I do everything for you.
Can you give me hug?
Come on, give me hug.
- You happy now?
- Okay.
- Ow, why did you bite me?
- If I hurt you, you remember.
I want you to remember.
Look at it, this is me.
- Do you know how old I am?
- How old are you?
- Take a guess.
- I don't care to know about that.
- How old are you?
- What do you think?
- I don't know.
23, two?
- Oh, I think I'm older
than you maybe 10 year.
- Thanks grandpa.
- Oh sorry.
Don't get mad to me boy.
- How long have you been in America?
- Three year.
- Do you miss Vietnam?
- Sometime.
Not much.
I have wife there.
- A wife?
- The last time when I go home,
we get married.
She love me very much.
I don't really want to marry her
but she tell me she die
if I don't marry her.
And my mother want me to.
She know she a good woman.
So I do.
- What happened to your dad?
- My dad's not married to her.
He black guy, he live
with my mom for three year
and then he left.
I never see him.
First, make me very
angry, I want to kill him.
But now, he gone, I don't want to bother.
My family strange.
They don't like me.
Maybe they know I gay, I don't know.
- I don't know if you'd
call my family strange.
My dad just tried to
get laid all the time.
So my mom left him for some freak she met
at a clinic in California.
- You think that bad?
- I don't know.
- Doesn't sound so bad.
But you got a lot of things,
nice house, boat, family.
Only way I know a place like this,
be here, not family, is to be gay.
- What's that got to do with anything?
- You think if I'm not gay, you know me?
I be here?
Who take me here?
You that's bad?
- No, I don't.
- I have park in Vietnam.
I go out with some kids there.
They don't like it.
They say I'm black, they
say I'm ugly and something.
And their mom say, no no
no, don't go out with him,
he's black.
- I should get back soon.
(water splashing)
- You're already gone.
You need some beer.
(talking low)
(upbeat music)
- Can I have two beer please?
- You old enough to buy?
- Yes.
- That'll be 2.50.
One, two.
- Keep the change.
Got ourself a big spender.
- Excuse me, do you have firework?
- What?
- Do you have firework?
- Yeah, in the back.
- You have any big one? (mumbling)
- I don't know what you call it,
you'll have to look for yourself.
Joe, show him the fireworks.
- What do you know about fireworks?
- A lot.
(talking drowned out by music)
- Enjoy your chocolate Amber.
- Okay.
- Alright baby.
- That's all we have.
Most of it's gone by now.
- Some very good.
- How can you tell?
- See what you want?
- Yeah, something.
Hold this.
You got a box?
- Sure.
- How much money do you have?
- 20 bucks but I don't wanna
spend it all on this shit.
- Give it to me.
- So where you from?
- Memphis.
- No, I mean, where you really from?
You from China or something?
- Yeah, I'm from China.
- That's interesting.
How'd you end up here?
(mumbling)
- Take a few things from this?
- Yeah, that's okay.
(crickets singing)
Get out of here.
Shit, kick it.
- What do you mean?
- Kick it out of here.
- What was wrong with it?
- You make me crazy.
- Stop it.
- Careful, okay?
- You be careful.
(firework screams)
- Woah.
Shit.
How many is it supposed to have?
- Two.
Three.
That one cleared.
- You boys can't do those here.
You outta take 'em back
to wherever you came from.
- Why not?
- It's illegal here.
You're gonna get me in trouble.
- Can you take me go back there?
- You understand you can't
do them in the whole county.
- I understand everything you said.
- Hey come on, we'll go,
we won't set off any more.
- I'm just trying to tell you the law.
- You a lawyer?
I don't see you no lawyer.
Nobody else cares so why
not live by the law, okay?
We're not doing anything.
- Oh well, we might as well stay here now.
(police sirens ringing)
No sense in going anywhere now.
- What's going on here?
Who are these kids?
- I don't know who they are.
- You set off those fireworks?
- No sir.
(laughs)
- I like that.
If you didn't, then who did?
Man, ya'll know we ain't had
no rain in the whole state
of Mississippi for over a month.
Those fields out there are dry as paper.
Where'd these fireworks come from?
- It ain't mine, Ron.
- They sure as hell come from your store.
Okay, I'm gonna have to ask
you fellas to come with me.
Hey, hey!
Come back here.
(heavy breathing)
(groaning)
- Crazy motherfucker.
Damn it.
- Motherfucker.
- Why'd you do that?
Why'd you do it to me?
(mumbling)
You crazy.
You leave me here, motherfucker?
(knocking)
- What happened to you?
- I spent the night out in the woods.
- Have you talked to your dad?
- No.
- He's called a lot.
Don't you think you should?
- I will.
- He kept calling here.
- What'd you say to him?
- Nothing, I didn't know what to say.
I didn't know where you were.
Where were you?
- I went everywhere.
Driving around.
Just couldn't go home.
- You've been driving around since Friday?
That's a pretty long time.
Did you take more drugs?
- No.
- I don't want my parents to see you.
- Can I lay down?
- I don't care.
- Come here with me.
Come on, I want you to.
Will you come to my house with me?
- I don't want your dad to be mad at me.
- He wouldn't.
- But he'll think I was lying.
- You don't have to lie, you
don't have to say anything.
- Oh sure, just be mute.
- That's not what I mean.
I love you.
You know I do.
I'll do anything you want.
I don't care.
- What?
- I'm just happy to be with you.
Do you have any clothes I can borrow?
- Yeah.
- When I was outside last
night, I had a dream about you.
You wanna hear it?
Huh?
- Okay.
- It was in my room at home,
except it was your room.
You were living there instead of me.
You wanted me to come in and
take off all your clothes.
I went in and then you were gone.
I couldn't see you anymore.
Do you wanna come in here with me?
- Do you want me to?
- I do, don't be a flirt.
- What if my mother hears us?
- Don't worry about her.
- Just get in the goddamn house.
(upbeat music)
(chattering)
- What you doing?
You make me scared.
- I'm sorry, that's
not what I meant to do.
Do I look so bad?
- No you don't look so bad
but it's the way you look
at me, I don't know.
- Well, I was just trying
to get up the courage
to come and say hello.
- I'm not sober.
- You finished with that?
- Yeah.
- Can I get you another?
- Sure.
- Excuse me, can I get two beers please?
So what's your name?
- John.
- I'm Ricky.
- Nice to meet you.
- Same.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- So how you been doing tonight?
- I'm okay right now.
I'm here talking with you.
Everything I want, I got it.
No problem.
- I'm glad.
- You're a nice guy.
- Huh?
- I thought I seemed scary.
- I don't know.
I like the people that come talk to me.
(mumbling) I can tell.
I don't like it, one
guy come, he talk to me,
he tell me he got a big dick.
I said, what the hell you
talking to me about that?
So what?
I don't care you big, you small.
Why you telling me about that?
I don't feel good for that.
Leave me alone, okay?
- He just came up to you and
said, hi, I got a big dick?
- Yeah and I said, what do you think I am?
I find some big dick?
No.
I need lover, I don't
wanna fuck around, shit.
You make me crazy, you know that?
Hey, let's get out of here.
I know a place we can
go, buy a beer and talk.
Get out of here.
- Sure.
- Yeah, I'd like that.
I don't like this place.
You got a car?
- Yeah.
- Okay, you ready?
(upbeat music and chattering)
It's so quiet out here.
- It's late.
- It's not that late.
- Where am I going?
- I tell you, keep going straight.
(singing in foreign language)
How long I know you?
One hour, two hour?
You think I like you a lot, right?
- I don't know.
- But you think maybe, you're not sure?
- No I'm not sure.
- I just playing.
- You mean you lie.
You don't like me.
- No, I don't lie.
But I play with people all my life.
I want to play game with people.
I call, I hug a lot, everybody like you,
they want me, they hug from me.
That's the way I am.
But I know someday I really hurt.
If you play game, you hurt form play game.
I know that.
But now, I just play game.
- What are you trying to say?
- I not do something for you.
I do something for me.
Before I young, I hurt from love,
but right now, I learn, I learn a lot.
I hurt a lot.
But now I know better.
I do everything I want.
I don't care.
- I don't believe you.
- You don't know me.
- I don't know you
basically but I don't think
you're the way you think you are.
- I talk, I say nice thing but inside,
nothing, nothing.
You don't know when I say
it but I have nothing here.
You think that I ask weird.
You think that I go home
and think about you.
But I'm not, I go home and
sleep, I never think about
you again.
- I get the feeling you
don't wanna have sex with me.
- Boy, I sorry.
You think I talk too much.
- No that's not what I mean.
- Yes you did.
You just wanna have sex with me, right?
- No, but it wouldn't be so bad though.
- That what you want, I know.
That okay.
Take off your shirt.
Come here.
You big guy.
- You mind that?
- No, that's alright.
(soft music)
(groaning)
(upbeat music)