(singing in foreign language)
(choir singing)
(speaking Latin)
(choir continues)
Partition.
Now that the British are leaving
India, the subcontinent will be
divided into two countries--
India, where the Hindus are
majority, and East and West
Pakistan, where Muslims will be
the rulers.
Yes, Sunita?
Is this something the British
want, or do we Indians want it?
Oh...
Opinions are divided on all
sides.
Mahatma Gandhi is against
partition, but many people who
follow him are all for it.
They believe that Hindus and
Muslims cannot live together
in free country.
Alice?
What do you think,
Sister Teresa?
There was a reason God asked
me to join his church.
He knows I have no head
for politics.
(laughter, bell rings)
Oh, 4:00, girls.
That's all for today.
We'll be late for Vespers.
What do you mean there is
no food?
Headmistress, we haven't had
any deliveries for two weeks.
Hadi, there is nothing
to cook, at all?
No.
But we have 200 girls
to feed.
There are riots in the
street, ma'am.
No one can go out.
This is not a safe area for us
to live in.
It's right in between the Hindus
and the Muslims.
Sister Gabriella...
if the mountain don't come
to Mohammed...
Mr. Pradesh's warehouse
should be down here.
This is it.
Hello? Hello?
Mr. Pradesh!
Hello?
(crowd shouting)
Oh!
(gasps)
(child cries)
What brings two nuns out of
cloisters at a time like this?
An emergency.
We are from Loreto Convent,
with 200 hungry girls to feed
and no food.
Well, there's only meat for
vultures out here.
No, I can't let those girls
go hungry.
Oh, come on, then. Douglas!
I'm sure they won't miss a bag
or two.
(crowd continues shouting)
On board, ladies, on board.
Ah!
This should keep your little
lot fed till this mess is over.
Are we stealing this?
Requisition is the word.
I'm sure your credit's good,
Sister.
Come on, lad.
Come on!
When you see what we had these
last few days, you'll say to
yourself, "We've given them
everything we can,
so let 'em have their blasted
independence."
(car horn honking)
Get off!
Back off, make way!
(crowd continues shouting)
Get back!
Get off!
Get out of the way!
Please, Sahib, help us!
Please help, Sahib!
Rice for me and for my child!
Pay no attention, Sister.
The war has caused these people
to be put through the worst
famine in Indian history.
They've been starving ever
since.
Get off!
Ride, man, ride!
(crowd continues shouting)
Go, go, go!
You're gonna get yourselves
killed!
Come on, Douglas, open the gate.
Now, move it! Go!
What's going on?
Mother, we have food.
We have food!
Oh, glory be to God!
Cook! Food!
(crowd shouting)
(girls screaming)
(gasps)
Ashad!
To infirmary.
Yes, yes, Sister.
He's bleeding-- I don't know
how to help.
Oh, Lord.
Right.
Put pressure on his wounds.
He's lost a lot of blood.
No, no.
You must keep up the pressure.
We've got to stop the bleeding.
Can you do it?
Sister, I am geography
teacher.
(sighs)
Sister Teresa,
I thought I'd find you here.
May I speak with you?
Sister Gabriella told me how
distressing it was to go
outside.
I'm so ashamed.
Ashamed?
But you went out for a good
reason.
I saw the starving children
of God out there, Father.
I did nothing to help.
You were bringing food for
our girls.
There were girls out there
too, Father.
Hungrier than ours.
But our first duty is to our
school and our convent, Sister,
surely.
How can that be?
How can God wish me to be
concerned only about the girls
in here?
Surely, he cares as much about
the people living outside
these walls?
We're all under strain
right now, Sister.
I spoke with Mother Superior.
We both feel you should go on
retreat sooner than planned.
You need time to think things
through--
to rediscover the joy
in your work.
Father Verru was right.
But I could not forget what I
had seen outside.
And I knew I had to do something
to make life better for the
poor.
Mary can't sleep, Sister.
She says she's having
nightmares.
Mary, Mary.
Hey.
When I was nine years old,
my father died.
In my own country, Albania,
where I was born, there was a
lot of political strife.
For many years, I couldn't
understand what happened,
why my father didn't come home.
And I used to recite a poem to
myself over and over.
"His red heart beat with love
for child, wife, and country,
and then burst into bloom,
like crimson rose dropped
on crumpled shirt."
This poem is about believing in
love, Mary, even when everything
you see around you is hatred
and destruction.
To bed.
Mary?
Tomorrow, I think you have a
poem to write,
just like I did when I was
nine years old and when
my father died.
Goodnight, girls, God bless you.
(girls) Goodnight, Sister.
Sister?
I-- some of the older girls,
they say we shouldn't take care
of the injured Muslims.
They say they are to blame for
the violence.
We take in whoever needs
our help, Maria.
Hindus, Muslims-- makes no
difference to God.
(train whistle blowing)
Darjeeling!
Darjeeling train, all aboard!
All aboard, Darjeeling train!
All aboard!
I'm thirsty, I'm thirsty,
I'm thirsty.
I'm thirsty, I'm thirsty.
I'm thirsty, I'm thirsty, ma'am.
I'm thirsty, I'm thirsty,
I'm thirsty, ma'am.
I'm thirsty, I'm thirsty--
Sister Teresa, come on,
we're leaving.
Thirsty, I'm thirsty.
I'm thirsty.
(groans)
I'm thirsty, ma'am, I'm thirsty.
Please, Sister.
I'm thirsty.
I'm thirsty, I'm thirsty.
(train whistle blowing)
So, what can I bring you
today, sir?
(sighs)
Look at it.
Breathtaking, isn't it?
I so look forward to these
retreats.
I can almost taste the mountain
spring water right now.
It's so fresh-- and the fruit!
It always tastes much better
up there.
(flute playing)
(train whistle blowing)
(overlapping chatter)
The more time I spent
outside, the more I became aware
of the privileges that were
being granted to me
but denied to others.
Why?
Why should I be treated any
differently?
We are all children of God.
Sister?
Come-- your friend, come.
What-- what is it?
She's gone into third class.
(gasps) Sister Teresa!
What on Earth are you doing?
It's another world, isn't it?
It's completely unacceptable
behavior.
I mean, what will people think?
I wish I had time to find
out.
I'm thirsty, I'm thirsty.
I'm thirsty, I'm thirsty,
thirsty, I'm thirsty...
Welcome back.
I understand you were very quiet
on retreat, very withdrawn.
I'm sorry, Father.
Oh, it's not to apologize
for.
I understand you were deep in
your thoughts.
And you do seem more rested.
Yes, Father.
I am resolved.
In fact, God himself told me
what I must do.
God lets us know him by our
own feelings.
He spoke to me.
He spoke to me through the voice
of a sick beggar.
Sister--
I heard him clearly.
Sister, you realize
what you're--
He said, "I am thirsty,"
Father.
You think you heard the voice
of God?
Same way I heard him when he
called me to his church, even
though I was too young, only 13.
Now, he has called me again.
He wants me to follow him
into the slums, to help the
poorest of the poor.
But you're a cloistered nun,
you can't go outside.
Father, it is a call.
It's a call within the call.
Do you remember what Mahatma
Gandhi told the Christians in
India?
He said, "If you want to help,
go to the people as one of them.
Work among them."
How can we do that from behind
these gated walls?
You no longer want to be
a nun?
Heaven forbid, Father,
the church is my life.
No, I only want permission
to work outside.
I've heard of nuns suffering
delusions as a result of heat
stroke, but this takes the cake.
We've all been affected by
the troubles.
And it could be that Sister
Teresa is struggling to reaffirm
her faith.
But she believes God has called
her to follow him into the slum.
Well?
I believe that Sister Teresa
is sincere.
She just hasn't considered
the implications.
Which are?
It'll upset the entire
convent if a nun of Sister
Teresa's experience gives up
everything and leaves.
She wants to apply for
exclaustration, Mother Superior.
This would allow her to remain
in the Loreto Order and live
by her vows.
All she's asking for is
permission to work outside
the walls.
That's the other problem.
The Loreto Order has always
been cloistered.
And now a nun comes along and
says she heard the voice of God,
in a tunnel!
But she makes a compelling
argument.
She says that in the face of
every suffering man, woman
and child in India, we can find
the face of Jesus Christ.
She calls it God's distressing
disguise.
Heaven forbid one of the
children hears that the
headmistress is hearing voices
and seeing visions.
I think it's clear this
matter should remain strictly
confidential.
Of course, but what are we
to tell Sister Teresa?
Tell her nothing.
But Your Grace--
This isn't the first time
a nun has asked for permission
to leave the cloister.
Last time, I advised the
applicant to wait a year.
12 months later, she sat in that
chair and thanked me for not
taking her request seriously.
Sister Teresa, Your Grace,
she's never not serious.
Tell her to write a letter to
me in a year's time.
Until then,
this matter is closed.
♪♪
I'm thirsty, I'm thirsty,
I'm thirsty...
(choir singing)
Commissioner?
Harry Harper.
We met the other night at the
reception at Governor House.
Ah, yes, yes.
The American journalist
hungry for a face-to-face
with Mr. Gandhi.
Yes, well, I'd like to report
on India's transition to
independence fairly.
People need to hear about
official ceremonies like this,
but they also need to hear about
Gandhi's presence in Calcutta
to protest the violence.
(people applauding)
Do you really care about the
Muslims and Hindus, Mr. Harper?
Absolutely.
(chuckles)
(trumpet calling)
(band playing)
(applause)
Now, the year is finished.
The Archbishop has agreed to
forward your letter to Rome,
but only under one condition--
that you apply for a decree of
secularization.
But that means I would have
to leave the order.
It's the only way he will
consider your request.
If you leave, you leave as a
laywoman, not as a nun.
But... I've lived as a nun
for 17 years, I can't live
any other way.
Then you must give up the
idea.
I can't leave Loreto.
Hello, there, Sister.
This is my family.
It's too much of a risk.
If your plan doesn't work out,
you won't be able to come back
here.
It's God's plan, Father,
not mine.
I will rewrite the letter.
A sad day, isn't it?
No, not really.
It was good while it lasted.
So...
you going back to England soon?
No, not me, sir.
I lost my wife and kids
in the Blitz.
Oh, well, I'm sorry.
Well, I've got my pension.
I might get around to opening up
a little hotel, gentlemen's
club, that sort of thing.
Uh-huh.
Your first time in India?
No, I was, um, born here
actually.
My parents moved to the States
and settled there when I was
a kid.
Oh, you work for the
International Chronicle?
Yep.
And I have a feeling things
aren't gonna stay quiet around
here for very long.
You let me know if anything
interesting happens in Calcutta?
Right you are, sir.
(laughing)
(overlapping chatter)
Sister? Sister?
You see that street?
The families we visit during
our Sodality outings live there.
Would it be all right if we
looked in on them?
Oh, please?
Then they can meet you.
Well, if we all stick
together, I suppose it'll be
all right.
You must not take more than
half an hour.
They will be worried at Loreto.
All right, girls.
Stick together.
(overlapping chatter)
(gasps)
This woman must be taken
to hospital.
What's wrong with you?
She's dying.
She needs care.
(flies buzzing)
(speaking foreign language)
It's all right.
We will help you.
Our hospitals are so crowded,
we just don't have any space.
It would be a waste to use
valuable resources on a hopeless
case.
But she's a person.
We can't do a thing for her.
Like anyone else, she's one
of God's children.
I understand your feeling,
Sister, but we just can't
take her.
What are we to do with her?
Try another hospital,
I don't know!
I want my cart back.
But they won't take her.
That's not my problem!
(thunder cracking)
Sister, take the girls
back to Loreto.
But what will you do?
I don't know.
Come on, girls, single file.
You come with me.
I take care of you.
Come on.
(woman groaning)
You have to leave.
You're blocking the entryway.
Don't worry now.
All right, Ma?
(rain falling)
Sister, the doctors have
agreed to take her in.
Bless you.
Ma...
You are doing a beautiful thing
for God.
(thunder roaring)
My mother always said if you do
something good, do it without
big fuss.
Suddenly, I realized I was lost.
Lost in the back streets of
Calcutta.
Give me money.
Money, rupees for food.
I don't have anything.
No money.
Why you in such a hurry?
No.
What are you hiding from us?
No, no.
Give me money. Money!
Money!
Can somebody help me?
Please, can...
(gasps)
Hari!
Are you all right, Sister?
Oh, yes.
I didn't realize the outside
world could be so confusing.
You are very lucky, Sister,
in this neighborhood.
No, Hari.
They're just very poor.
I must get used to that.
(organ playing)
I have the reply to your
letter.
(gasps)
If you like, I'll tear it up
unread.
If they've granted your request,
this may be your last mass
as a nun.
Let me pray first, Father.
Whatever God has decided for me.
Oh.
Oh!
It is manifestly God's will.
You've been granted the decree
of exclaustration for a trial
period of one year.
You can leave Loreto as a nun
and remain in our order.
How did this happen?
I changed your request to
secularization.
It's as if...
God knows what he wants.
Yes!
He knows.
My friend Mr. Pillay has
about the best saris.
This is pure silk,
worthy of a princess.
The thread is real gold.
Cotton, Hari.
I asked for a cheap cotton sari.
I told him, but he said it's
not fit for a European.
Ah, how 'bout this, Sister?
The cloth flows like wine.
And probably costs the same
too.
Ah... what about this one?
That one?
That one he gave me very
reluctantly.
It cost just a few rupees.
This is the one.
May the Father, Son, and Holy
Ghost bless this habit and
enable you to be faithful to
your commitment for the rest of
your life.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Ghost,
Amen.
His Grace, the Archbishop,
would like you to keep a record
of your activities.
With all you hope to do for the
poor in Calcutta, you'll need
help of all kinds.
Are you planning to meet
with the governor?
Oh, no, I won't do that.
Then where will you begin?
All I know is I must leave
Loreto.
After that, God will direct me.
(bells tolling)
After dreaming of this day for
two years, leaving Loreto
Convent was the most difficult
thing I had ever done--
much more difficult than leaving
my family.
It was only my firm belief in
God's plan that gave me the
courage to give up everything
once again.
He would not let me down.
(overlapping chatter)
(bell ringing)
Mommy?
You should go around
the back.
I will ask my cook to give you
something to eat.
I-- I'm looking for Mr. Goma.
Father Verru wrote to him
about me.
I am Sister Teresa from
Loreto Convent.
(sighs)
I'm so pleased!
Forgive me, I was expecting
a nun.
Please come, Sister.
My husband is waiting.
Oh, thank you for your
generosity.
And the church wants you to
work in a place like Moti Jihl?
That's a huge risk, isn't it?
Something I do willingly,
Mr. Goma.
Father thought, as a member of
his parish, perhaps you could
suggest a place for me to stay
not too far from Moti Jihl.
As you can see, my own home
is a humble place,
and I have a large family.
I'll have to think if, uh--
Daddy, the two rooms upstairs
are empty, and the attic.
(clears throat)
I suppose they are.
But I doubt Sister will find
them comfortable or--
The simplest of rooms would
be perfect.
I won't be in the way.
I will be gone all day, only
need a place to sleep at night.
We have plenty of spare
furniture.
If you need anything, you can
just ask, Sister.
Thank you, you're very kind.
♪♪
Mr. Goma.
Oh, we have more chairs and
tables you can borrow, Sister.
The fewer possessions I have,
the better.
Nothing should distract me...
from my work for the poor.
(overlapping chatter)
Sister, Sister, money!
Hello.
Sister, money.
Money! Money! Money!
Sister!
Sister, money!
(kids continue begging)
I have no money.
No, I have-- I have no money!
My lunch!
(kids chattering)
My name is Sister Teresa.
I'm a daughter of the Christian
Church.
I have come to Moti Jihl
to work with you.
To try to improve your lives.
But I need your help.
I can't give you clothes,
or food or money.
I am as poor as you.
But I can teach your children
how to read.
(woman screaming)
(flies buzzing)
(screaming continues)
(gasps) What are you doing?
Leave her alone!
(baby crying)
(man singing in distance)
When I was a little girl in
Skopia, Mother used to take me
to visit the poor.
She taught us that it is our
responsibility to help the less
fortunate.
Sometimes we would come to the
dinner table and find total
strangers sitting down to share
our meals.
"Who are these people?"
we would ask.
She would say, "Distant
kinsmen."
But they were beggars and
destitutes that my dear mama
had brought in.
But never did I see such poverty
and suffering there
as I see here.
(overlapping chatter)
Come!
You want to eat my lunch again?
Oh!
Do you like to hear stories?
I have a wonderful story
I will tell you.
Sit down.
Once, a long time ago--
I'm going to tell a story.
A long, long time ago,
there lived a handsome prince
called Rama, and his beautiful
wife called Sita.
They lived in a big, beautiful
palace in a beautiful country,
but that was ruled by a very
nasty king...
And the king was slain by the
brave prince, who rescued his
princess, and they lived
happily ever after.
Another one!
Tell us another one!
You like stories?
Yes!
(children) Yes!
You know, you can tell
stories like that to each other.
We don't know any.
But you can read them.
From books, you can read any
story you want.
We can't read.
Ohh.
Let me test you.
Let's all together say the word
"king."
(children) King.
Now, I show you how
to write it.
Kh-- everyone, "kh."
(children repeat)
Then, "ih."
Then, "nnn."
(children repeat)
Then, "guh."
And all together, that is...
"Kh-ih-nnn-guh."
(children) King!
You see!
You have just learned to read
your first word!
(gasps)
Yay, we did it!
(all clapping)
"A."
"N."
"E." "N."
(children repeating)
"N," "N," "N."
"I."
(children repeat)
"N." E."
Charu?
"U." "N."
Give this to the Sister.
Go on.
"Un."
(children repeat)
Oh!
Beautiful.
...lay them straight.
Nine, ten...
11, 12...
13, 14...
15, 16...
17, 18...
"L."
(children repeat)
"M."
(children repeating)
Why is she here?
European woman, what does she
want from us?
She is teaching them about
the Christian God.
She wants to convert them
to her faith.
No, she's teaching them
to read.
She's giving them a chance
in life.
She's a troublemaker.
You are a troublemaker,
Manik!
(scoffs) Women.
(children) "X,"
"Y,"
"Z."
Very good!
You all get a prize.
(groans)
Soap!
♪♪
Over here.
They arrived a week ago from
the country.
He came to get a job,
but he got sick.
Now, the whole family is sick.
No one can help them, because
they are afraid of getting
the disease too.
We'll take the worst case
to hospital.
(sighs)
(flies buzzing)
(people coughing)
(gasping)
Feeling better?
What happened?
You fainted.
You haven't been eating enough.
Your blood sugar was too low.
Don't you know that, when you
work in conditions like you're
in every day, you're supposed to
eat three meals and get plenty
of rest.
Oh.
No.
I'm Sister Stephanie.
Father sent for me.
Oh.
The sick family...
I have to help them.
I have to go.
You're not going anywhere.
The people in the slums...
I failed them, failed.
You neglected your own care
while worrying about others.
That is no way to bring charity
to the poor, Sister Teresa.
That is the way to-- to rob
yourself of your usefulness.
I've been through this all
myself.
You have?
In Patna.
I run a hospital in one of the
poorest areas for the Medical
Mission Sisters.
Believe me, to do this work,
you have to have strict rules
and rigorous discipline.
Will you be in Calcutta
for a while?
Will you teach me?
That's as clean as we can
get it.
Now, it's time to dress
the wound.
Now, remember, it's essential
that you take an hour of rest
every day, and one day off
a week.
To keep working in these
conditions, balance is
essential.
(indistinct conversation)
To guard against the spread of
disease, all clothing must be
washed every day.
And now, Sister, it's time for
you to administer this injection
yourself.
You delivered that little one
almost on your own, Sister.
You'll make a fine midwife.
(baby crying)
If the nuns at Loreto could
see me now!
(laughing)
♪♪
"I leave for Patna tomorrow.
I think you will find these more
comfortable in the heat of
Calcutta."
Ohh!
"Remember,
St. Teresa of Avila
wore hers without stockings."
Beautiful.
"Good luck with your mission
of charity, Sister.
God bless you."
Mission of charity.
(overlapping chatter)
Sister!
Thank you. Thank you, Sister.
Thank you.
(overlapping chatter)
(bells tolling)
Today I learned an important
lesson.
I was going and going, and my
legs and my arms were so sore.
And then the comfort of Loreto
came to tempt me.
I had not heard those bells for
several months, and I could not
resist a glimpse into my past.
Had I made the right decision
by leaving?
It did not take God long to give
me an answer.
(man begging)
Oh!
(overlapping chatter)
(baby crying)
Oh, baby.
Baby!
Oh, dear, oh, baby.
Come, baby, come, come.
(crying continues)
Oh, baby, baby--
What are you trying to do
with my child?!
He's my child!
Give me my child!
He was alone and crying,
I thought he was abandoned.
But he's my child.
I didn't abandon him.
He's mine!
Your baby is sick, so hot.
I would like to help you
take care of him.
No, no, I don't need your
help.
What do you want from us?
No, nothing--
What are you trying to do
to us?
I was only trying to help.
I know about you.
You are trying to steal
our children.
Please, I don't want to
cause any trouble.
Then why are you here?
You want to turn our children
into Christians.
No!
You are stealing their souls!
No, if I could just explain.
We don't need your
explanations.
They're all lies anyway.
We'd be fools to trust a
white person.
We learned that long ago.
She was trying to steal
my baby from me!
No! No! I wasn't trying to--
Ahh!
(screaming in foreign language)
Thank you.
No!
I should thank you.
Don't you recognize me,
Sister?
I am Jyoti.
You helped me at the convent.
Kali decided to spare me.
Manik, you of all people should
welcome Sister into Moti Jihl.
She can teach that layabout son
of yours a thing or two!
I don't need help from a
white woman.
How can I thank you?
You saved my life.
You've taken a huge debt
from my shoulders, Sister.
Good.
(kids chattering)
(birds cawing)
This will be a beautiful place--
a place where people can die
with dignity.
But people here don't
understand.
Why would a European woman leave
those beautiful, clean big
buildings up there,
where there's plenty of food,
fresh air and safety, and come
down here to live in the slum?
I don't know how to explain
it to you, Jyoti.
But Sister, everyone around
here would do anything to get
out of Moto Jihl, including me.
I choose this out of my own
free will to do the work of God.
(overlapping chatter)
We should be removing the
garbage from Moto Jihl,
not adding to it.
The people wouldn't like
that.
It's so unhealthy, look.
(scoffs)
If we all got together and
cleared all this up, Moti Jihl
would be a better place to live.
Never! It's our livelihood.
We survive by picking through
the garbage of Calcutta.
If this goes away...
(overlapping chatter)
I'll do it.
You finish the beds.
Your influence has even made
a big impression on this pigsty.
(chuckling)
And I thought I was making
a real sacrifice
letting you use the place.
You're a good and generous
Christian, Mr. Goma.
Your hospital pretends
to know nothing about you.
But my little Mabel refused
to leave until they gave her
some bandages.
Thank you.
Every spot of life has
infinite value.
And every person counts
no matter how sick,
no matter how disfigured.
Charu Ma.
Have you seen Jyoti?
He's out there, Sister.
Jyoti, I need the water
inside.
I can't go in there, Sister.
Why not?
I'm Hindu,
I can't be near death.
It's impure.
Only the harijan can deal
with the dead.
The untouchables.
But he's not dead yet.
We're trying to relieve
his suffering.
He has great suffering.
The body's not important,
the spirit is.
If that man is suffering,
it's his Karma, his destiny.
You are interfering.
I respect your beliefs,
Jyoti.
But I need you to respect mine.
Shouldn't you say
the last rites, Sister?
Receiving the water from
the River Ganges is the holiest
of rites for Hindus.
He's in the hands of God now.
Give me courage now
this very moment
as you did when I was 18
and I had to leave behind
mother and sister and brother,
knowing I might never see them
again.
Nanalokay,
sister Agay,
brother Lassar.
So many years have intervened.
So many words.
Today, what tortures
of loneliness.
From the Calcutta Corporation,
they will give us land
and build a small school house
when we have 100 pupils.
It won't be long now.
Meanwhile, I think we should
open a school for only
Muslim girls.
(truck horn honks)
(shouting)
Sounds like trouble, Sister.
(horn honks)
(crowd shouting)
It's for your own good!
Don't you understand?!
The authorities don't want you
to live in filth anymore!
Is this your doing, Sister?
No!
Then you have to stop them.
Will they listen to me?
It might make things worse.
Please.
(shouting)
Hey, you!
You're obstructing
municipal workers!
Get down!
Get down, or I'll arrest you!
Who are you?
Sister Teresa
from the Loreto Order.
I work here in Moti Jihl.
In this slum?
With these hooligans?
These people are
my sisters and my brothers.
We share the slum
with the rats.
She's not one of us!
Take her away with you!
We don't want a white woman!
Did you hear that?
Get out of the way
before you get hurt.
Their only fault
is that they're poor.
Poverty is an accident,
it tells you nothing about
a person.
I don't have the time
to be preached.
This man there,
Manik Sulamin,
the man you want to arrest.
He has four sons and a wife.
He keeps them alive by salvaging
garbage from this dump.
What will happen to his family
if you arrest him?
City officials have ordered
this operation.
It's my job to make--
Have the city officials asked
these people what they want?
No! No!
If they're so eager to help,
why don't they try
and find a way to bring
clean water to Moti Jihl?
What about those toilets
that are supposed to be cleaned
once a week?
The sanitation workers
never come.
No one can go near those places,
they're smelling so badly.
Some people use the gutters.
It's not my responsibility.
Then make it
your responsibility.
Please, Mr. Commissioner.
I ask you on behalf
of the people of Moti Jihl,
go to your city authorities
and ask them to cancel
these orders.
Yeah! Yeah!
Yes! Yes!
(crowd shouting)
(camera shutter clicks)
For the safety of the men,
this operation is discontinued
for now.
Thank you, Commissioner.
(cheering)
You haven't heard
the last of this.
(cheering)
Sister.
I was wrong about you, Sister.
No time for apologies.
We have much work to do.
(cheering)
(scoffs)
Well, I'll be.
If it isn't that pushy
little headmistress again.
Now, she's working in the slums.
Harry Harper,
this may interest you.
Now that you've
finished school,
will you go to Europe
with your mother, Sunita?
Perhaps. I first want to
visit Sister Teresa.
Ah, well, tell her
we miss her.
Good luck.
God bless you.
Thank you, Sister.
Tell Sister Teresa that
we want her to come back.
Tell her that.
They won't let her back.
They say she's walking around
Calcutta like a beggar woman.
They say she's cracked.
Oh, shut up.
Is it true?
That's not true.
I want to see for myself.
If I could, I'd run away
and go and work with her.
(laughing)
You better finish school first,
Maria.
Just one year to go. Bye.
Bye.
Five more deaths,
we are caring for 16 men,
13 women, and six children.
More come every day.
(knocking)
Who is it?
Sunita.
Sunita!
How did you find me?
What are you doing here?
Father gave me your address.
I've come to work with you.
Oh!
(gasping)
This is the first time
in my life I've seen you
at a loss for words.
The Sister of Calcutta
to help her poor.
Ah, morning, Mr. Goma.
Good morning, good morning.
The Bengalis have a custom
of setting aside a cup of rice
for a beggar.
Sister Teresa has inspired
our congregation to practice it
liberally.
Maria, what are you
doing here?
I have come to help.
But what about school?
What will your parents say?
They want me to get married.
But I want to be a nun.
Please, Sister Teresa.
Let me stay with you.
We can't, Sister.
She hasn't completed high school
yet.
But I want to help the poor.
Come to Moti Jihl.
Come and see.
Come and see if this the life
you really want.
(chanting)
(coughing)
(people groaning)
Come.
Let me show you what to do,
come.
There are four of them now.
It's outrageous.
Sit, both of you.
Do you realize
what it looks like?
A group of young Indian girls
from the best families
running around Calcutta
unsupervised.
But they are hardly
Sister Teresa is their
headmistress.
She knows how to handle--
I agree with the Archbishop.
It's putting our whole order
into a bad light.
I'm putting a stop to this
right now, Father.
It's clear this experiment
is grossly out of control.
With all due respect,
Your Grace, I think it's out
of our control.
Sister Teresa is inspiring
young women to give selflessly
to those who need service
the most.
Why would these young girls,
who have their whole life
ahead of them,
give up everything to work for--
To work for what?
I believe they think
they are working for our Lord,
Jesus Christ.
For her own safety,
and for the welfare
of those girls,
I think we ought to insist
that Sister Teresa
return to Loreto.
I beg you, Your Grace,
let her complete her year.
At least let her do that.
Good morning.
Good morning, Mabel.
Hope you slept well.
Good morning, Maria.
A letter arrived for you.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I wrote to my parents
to try to explain.
They didn't even open it.
We are your family now.
There are plenty of people
in Loreto who will welcome you
back at the end of the year.
The only problem is,
you've got these young girls
involved.
Why should there be
a problem?
They live by strict rules,
and as religious women,
even though they're not
nuns yet.
Yes, they're well into
their training as postulants.
And when you disband,
they'll be able to become
novitiates of the Loreto Order.
Disbanding?
What about the work?
We can't just abandon
these people we are helping.
But what are you going to do?
Father, I'm going to apply
for recognition
as a congregation.
(scoffs) The Vatican hasn't
authorized a new congregation
since 1850.
They'll say your work can be
taken over by lay people.
No.
There's a lot involved
in getting recognized.
You need to present a proposal,
document your work,
explain why a new order
is required,
write the constitutions.
A proposal, documentation,
constitutions.
Father, come.
Missionaries of Charity.
You're brilliant.
And this one?
"Angel of the Slums."
The local newspapers can't get
enough of her.
She even has the city council
on her side because of the work
she's doing.
If her group is recognized
as a congregation, Your Grace,
four of our girls will qualify
as novitiates.
She's paid close attention
to their religious--
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I see she proposes a fourth vow
in addition to poverty,
chastity, and obedience.
That's what makes her order
unique.
It's not her order yet.
"To give wholehearted and free
service to the poorest
of the poor.
There are over 200 rules
explaining the responsibilities
and training for membership
in her order.
I did read these documents,
Father.
I leave for Rome next month.
If, in the interim, I hear no
negative reports of Sister
Teresa's work...
I'll take this application
with me.
But Your Grace, I...
Oh, you mean you--
I mean, I--
Thank you, Your Grace.
Thank you.
(bells tolling)
We are careful not to breathe
in the scent of the flowers,
Sister.
It belongs to the goddess Kali.
You see that man?
He's a Brahmin, a holy man
in charge of the temple.
Where I grew up, there were
many different religions--
Orthodox, Muslim, Catholic.
We all worshipped
in different ways.
But as a child I always
believed we were praying
to same God.
What's that building?
It was the pilgrims'
rest house.
(gasps) This is the place
for my hospital!
It's perfect.
The Brahmins will not stand
for it, Sister.
This is the holiest of places
for us Hindus.
Then it's already sacred
ground for God's work.
Look, we can have beds here
and here.
(door opening)
Ah, Sister.
The city council has no idea as
to what kind of troublemaker
you are.
They give you permission to run
amok in Calcutta,
and I am the one who has
to clean up the disaster.
Just like in Moti Jihl.
I thought that you and I had
succeeded in stopping the
disaster, Mr. Commissioner--
Sister, please.
Don't try to whitewash
your actions.
What you did was incitement,
encouraging the poor
to resist authority.
(scoffs)
You can't hide your political
agitations behind
religious vows.
Is teaching the uneducated
and feeding the hungry now
considered political agitation?
All we are doing is providing
a little of God's love,
to make people's last days
on Earth less painful.
By making the slum a better
place to live?
No, a better place to die,
Mr. Commissioner.
So, you intend helping each
and every one of the millions of
sick and dying in Calcutta.
How do you count
to a million?
That's my point, Sister,
it takes forever.
But where do you begin?
One.
That's where I am beginning.
One, then two, then three.
Already we have reached
more than a hundred.
And now you are seeking
permission to move into
the pilgrims' hostel.
It has two sleeping rooms.
It has electricity.
It has connections for cooking.
I am not interested in its
pleasant features.
The hostel is right next to one
of the most enchanted, most
revered shrines in Calcutta.
How do you think Hindus will
respond to your presence?
Oh, I don't bring politics
into charity, Mr. Commissioner.
Sister! You are not the only
kind-hearted person in Calcutta.
You think no one else cares?
This is my city, and every day
I am brokenhearted to see our
people dying in the streets.
But for me, they're victims--
victims of colonialism
and 300 years of Christian rule,
which has blighted our country
and our culture.
Why don't we let God decide
whether we should do our work
here or not?
All you have to do
is open the way.
♪♪
The permission is
provisional.
And... if your presence
causes trouble...
the council will reconsider.
Thank you, Mr. Commissioner.
(people singing)
What's wrong, Sister?
(sighs)
The Albanian government have
refused permission for my mother
and my sister to leave
the country.
I'm so sorry.
We must count our blessings,
Sunita.
(singing continues)
Mabel said she'd go straight
to Sister to give her your
message.
Oh, I'm only concerned about
taking up your valuable time,
Mrs. Goma.
I'm used to waiting for
Sister Teresa.
Ah, here she is,
back from the war front.
I know you don't accept
hospitality from anyone,
as a rule.
Please, Sister, can I make a cup
of tea for you?
Thank you, Mrs. Goma,
I'm not thirsty.
Is that true?
The poor and the rich alike
invite us to drink tea with them
and to share their food.
We would never take anything
from people who have less
than us.
And to accept invitation only
from the wealthy would offend
the poor, so better say no
to everyone.
I'm sure that must frustrate
a lot of people, Mother Teresa.
Oh, I don't worry.
Mother Teresa?
(laughs)
Desperate, the lost,
the outcast.
Taking care of them,
rendering help to them,
visiting them assiduously,
living Christ's love for them,
and awakening their response
to His great love.
Amen.
God has triumphed through
you, Reverend Mother Teresa.
Welcome to the Calcutta diocese.
Just Mother Teresa,
Your Grace.
I'm too small to carry
so many names.
(singing in foreign language)
(girls) ...to quench the
infinite thirst of Jesus Christ
by wholehearted and free service
to the poorest of the poor.
Nursing the sick and dying
destitutes, gathering and
teaching street children.
Visiting and caring for beggars
and their children.
Sheltering the abandoned,
caring for the unwanted,
unloved and lonely,
living Christ's love in our
spiritual work of mercy.
(overlapping chatter)
Sister Gertrude.
We have been looking
everywhere for you.
I-- I was just thinking...
My dear daughter!
Mommy?
Papa!
How I wished I could have
seen my family again.
But God had other plans for me.
You have no right to be here!
You are desecrating
this holy place!
We are bringing the love
of God to the dying.
Not our God!
Your God!
Go back! Go back!
(baby crying)
Jyoti, take the baby
to Sister Angela.
Yes, Sister.
Quickly.
(protesters shouting)
Mother! Mother, look!
Don't let it distract you
from your work.
No, Mother.
Ahh.
Back up, back up.
Calcutta's a pretty peculiar
place for a holiday,
if you ask me.
Well...
I can think of a lot worse.
Actually, I'm here on a bit of
a busman's holiday.
I'm checking out the state of
post-partition India-- oh.
Well, while you're here,
you should pay a visit to that
nun I wrote to you about.
You know, she's really not
my kind of material, Stout.
(clears throat) I'm a war
correspondent, you know?
Well, if ever there was a war
to fight, she's found it, Harry.
(horn honking, people shouting)
Nirmal Hriday.
What's that mean?
That's "pure heart,"
"immaculate heart."
It's Bengali.
This woman has some guts.
(shouting continues)
(baby crying)
She was dying in the gutter,
Sister.
She wouldn't even speak to me.
And see, Sister?
She was clutching the baby.
Take her on inside, Manik.
Move toes.
Ahh!
(overlapping chatter)
What are they saying?
They called Gandhi
"Gandhiji," they're calling her
"Sisterji."
There she is.
I'll see you a little later on.
Um, excuse me?
Uh, my name is Harry Harper of
the International Chronicle.
I'd like to talk with you.
Oh, I have little time for
talking, Mr. Harper.
Excuse me, um, I would like
to write about your work.
The conflict between your
Catholic Order and Hindu
worshippers illustrates the
contradictions here in India.
All that matters is we are
serving the poor.
Yes, I know.
But wouldn't you like the world
to hear about your work?
God's work, not my work.
Mr. Harper, don't waste your
time writing about me.
I'm only an instrument.
Write about the poor.
All you have to do is open
your eyes, your ears,
your heart.
(people coughing, groaning)
Mother Teresa!
Oh!
Oh, the wound is infected with
maggots.
You must cut out
all dead tissue.
Yes, Mother.
Ooh.
(man retching)
Ugh!
(coughing)
He'll infect me!
Don't be afraid of them.
First day, it's a shock.
But you can get used to it.
Never, not that.
I thought I'd seen suffering
in the war, but...
Soon you'll be washing them
and feeding them.
You'll see.
How is that mother they
brought in a while ago?
I don't think she'll make it.
There's no life in her eyes.
But the little one is
fighting to survive.
Beautiful baby.
Now, what happens to her
if the mother dies?
I mean, who would take a sick
baby like that?
I've been thinking
about that, too.
Here, we have home
for destitute dying.
Now, what we need is home
for destitute living.
A home for children who have
nowhere to go.
How do you plan it all?
We have no plan.
We start our work where the
suffering of the people
calls us.
We start right from the ground.
(typewriter clicking)
> Let's see here.
"Dateline Calcutta.
Today, near a temple to a fierce
Indian goddess, I saw the face
of human compassion."
(groans)
"Among the teaming masses of
some of the poorest people on
Earth, a bright light shines.
Perhaps I saw the face of a
saint today, as she bent over
to change the bandages
of a dying..."
(sighs) Oh, Harry.
(man groaning, coughing)
Mother?
Not to worry,
we'll take care of you.
Sister Agnes?
He's a Brahmin.
Yes, he's dying of TB.
But the Brahmin want us
evicted.
They rejected him from every
hospital in Calcutta.
Don't worry, Jyoti.
You are welcome here.
(coughing)
I won't die in
this devilish house.
I want to leave!
Are you always
in a hurry, Mother?
There is a saying among
missionaries.
"If you want to preach
successfully, you move
your feet."
They call us
the running Sisters.
Well, I don't think
I'm fit enough to be
a part of your order.
But I-- I would like to help.
If you'd let me have
an interview...
Do you know what we really
need?
A mobile clinic.
Now, where would I find
something like that?
I don't know.
"I'd like to tell the whole
world, so all I want
is an interview."
Instead, she's sending me off
on a mission.
She's got under your skin,
old boy.
It's absurd.
I mean, where am I gonna
find a van?
How much is something like that?
Well, 100 pounds or so.
Exactly.
I'm not made out of money.
I think I've got maybe
ten pounds I can afford.
I can't afford 100.
Well... here.
Change that little one up,
you'll be up to 20.
(laughs)
(protestors shouting)
How can you care for me
when I despise you?
Because I love you.
I love you as God loves you.
Hindus believe we suffer to
pay for something we have done.
(coughs)
This is my time to understand
God through my physical pain.
Christ teaches us that
even the good can suffer.
Even the innocent.
(coughing)
Your God,
when we see him on the cross,
we ask, "What terrible thing
did he do in his life
to earn such a painful death?"
Christ died on the cross
to prove his greater love
in action.
He died for you.
(people gasp, scream)
I must go out there.
I must talk to them.
No, you can't!
We have to get help.
If they kill me...
I will go to my God sooner.
Attention!
You are ordered to vacate the
premises until your occupancy
of Kalighat can be reviewed.
If you don't do so voluntarily,
you'll be removed by force!
(cheering)
Attention!
What are we going to do?
(protestors shouting)
I warned you. And now...
either you leave peacefully,
or I will have
all of you arrested.
We have a lot of sick people
in here who can't walk.
If your plan is to remove us,
perhaps you would like to see
how many of us there are.
But how can we?
There is death in there.
No, Mr. Commissioner.
There is so much life.
Come and see.
All right.
(protesters continue shouting)
You realize that you'll all be
arrested if you disobey the
orders to vacate these premises?
Yes.
Arrangements have been made
to move these patients to other
facilities around Calcutta.
We Indians are quite capable
of taking care of our own.
(flies buzzing)
(people coughing, groaning)
These patients will be removed
to the city's facility for
indigents, where...
You-- you are taking care
of him, too?
Yes.
Remember the words
of Mahatma Gandhi.
That you must think of the
poorest and most helpless man
we have ever seen.
(coughing)
We must ask ourselves if the
step we contemplate is going to
be of any use to him, what will
the poor man gain from it?
(coughing)
Go out and tell your followers
she is not welcome here.
(coughing)
♪♪
(protestors shouting)
I promised you that
I will evict this woman.
And I will.
(cheering)
I will evict the nuns as soon as
I see you, your mothers,
sisters, and wives
come in here day in and day out
to take over the work
that they do here.
(murmuring)
(engine starts)
(car horn honking)
Pain?
Hey!
No pain here?
Here?
Not too tight, not too tight.
Here, good man.
Friend.
Mother?
Oh!
I came to offer my
congratulations.
I won't be able to make
the ceremony.
Oh, I am only accepting for
the poor, Mr. Harper.
I'm only the instrument.
Yes, yes.
An international instrument
working in over 30 countries.
Ah, we are looking for new
recruits, if you are interested.
We have brothers working as
missionaries too, you know.
Oh, no, I'm too old
and too wise, Mother.
After what I've witnessed,
the depth of wretchedness,
extent of suffering,
it's everywhere.
But then I come here--
Mother, what happened to the
legacy of Gandhi?
I passed a statue on the way
here, it's surrounded by
soldiers and barbed wire.
They need guns to protect
a monument to a pacifist?
I mean, if a man like Gandhi
can't transform people--
Mr. Harper, come.
I want to show you something.
Come and see.
This is Dr. Rama.
He was a child
in a leper colony.
He got treatment because
we were able to reach him.
The money you raised for the
mobile clinic has changed the
lives of many more people
like him.
(sighs)
What is it?
Mother Teresa, what is it
that you expect to achieve
in your lifetime?
More.
More, more, always more.
But don't you see?
Your beloved poor, these--
these people that you call the
blessed ones, are the result of
a criminal failure of society.
Isn't it better to correct
the causes instead of treat
the symptoms?
Someone must comfort
the poor.
But that's the problem.
With all due respect,
Mother Teresa,
Nobel Peace Prizes do little
more than appease the conscience
of the world. We can all shed
a tear because someone like you
is taking care of the needy.
And then, when the speeches have
been made, we go right on
living our numb, ignorant lives.
Maybe our work will inspire
others who are better able
to change conditions.
Not if you continue to make
the poor into some kind of a
holy icon, Christ's body on
Earth-- they're not Christ!
What good is it to pretend
that they're saints?
We owe them everything.
You have Western mentality.
You expect too much
from poor humanity.
No, Mother, I--
I think you do.
You expect infinite forgiveness.
How can you forgive the
violence, the corruption?
Why don't you get angry?
I get angry, Mr. Harper,
I get angry often.
When I find an abandoned child,
I get angry.
I got angry when I first saw
Rama living in inhuman
conditions.
I get angry when I see young
girls brutalized and raped
during the wars.
I am angry.
But I have to forgive.
Otherwise, how can I do
the work?
I forgive, but I don't accept.
Well, I--
I don't understand, Mother.
I don't think I ever will.
Will you do one last thing
for me, Mr. Harper,
before you go?
(man speaking foreign language)
Come on, come on, come on,
come on.
(man continues speaking)
Excuse me, excuse me?
What-- what, uh--
what is he saying?
(speaks foreign language)
He's giving you his blessings.
He was blessing me?
Yes.
I could buy him a million
times over with the change
in my pocket.
Yes, but you couldn't
buy his blessing.
I never thought that I would,
uh...
when you cross that line.
If I had not picked up that
first person dying on the
streets, I never would have
picked up the thousands after.
(patting leg)
(applause)
Welcome, Mother Teresa.
On behalf of the Nobel
Peace Prize Committee
and the citizens of Oslo.
His Majesty, the King,
greets you and looks forward
to meeting you personally
at the ceremonial banquet.
Banquet?
Tomorrow night in your honor.
Oh, please,
have this banquet cancelled.
Cancelled?
Put aside the funds to feed
the hungry and the poor
in Calcutta.
There, it can provide hundreds
of meals for one whole year.
All right?
All right.
Hello, beautiful child.
God bless you.
Mother Teresa? Mother Teresa?
(overlapping chatter)
Bless you.
(applause)
I accept this award for the
glory of God,
and in the name
of the hungry,
of the naked,
of the homeless,
of the crippled,
the lepers,
and the blind.
In the name of all those
who feel unwanted,
unloved,
uncared for,
humiliated.
In their name, I accept
this award, because it will
bring an understanding love
between the rich and the poor.
Because all of us here,
we are proclaiming to the poor
that we love them,
that they too have been created,
by the loving hand of God,
to love and to be loved.
If we turn our back on the poor,
we are turning our back on God.
And at the hour of our death,
we shall be judged by what we
have done for and to the poor.
God bless you all.
(applause)
♪♪