( tower bells tolling )
( rings doorbell )
( all chattering )
( cheering )
Philippe Leclerc!
Philippe's voice:
In 1955 when I was 18
I was afforded,
in the words of my
favorite teacher,
an interlude
of inestimable value--
a scholarship to
Asheland-Stuart University
in Virginia.
( train whistle blows )
- I'll take that from you.
- Pardon?
I'll carry that
for you.
No, thank you.
Fine.
The college is that way.
( train whistle blows )
♪ Life could be a dream ♪
♪ Life could be
a dream ♪
♪ Too-doo too too
sh-boom ♪
♪ Life could be dream,
♪ If I could take you up
in paradise up above,
sh-boom ♪
♪ And you would tell me
I'm the only one
that you love ♪
♪ Life could be a dream,
sweetheart ♪
♪ Hello hello again,
sh-boom, and hoping
we'll meet again ♪
♪ Hey nonny ding dong,
alang alang alang ♪
♪ Oh oh oh bip,
a-be-ba-do ba-dip ♪
♪ Oh, life could be
a dream, sh-boom ♪
♪ If only all
my precious plans
would come true, sh-boom ♪
♪ If you would let me
spend my whole life
loving you ♪
♪ Life could be a dream,
sweetheart ♪
♪ Too-doo too too,
sh-boom ♪
♪ Every time
I look at you ♪
♪ Something is
on my mind ♪
♪ If you do
what I want you to ♪
♪ Baby, we'd be
so fine ♪
♪ Oh, life could be
a dream, sh-boom ♪
♪ If I could take you up
in paradise up above,
sh-boom ♪
♪ Now tell me, darling,
I'm the only one
that you love ♪
♪ Life could be a dream,
sweetheart ♪
♪ Hello hello again,
sh-boom, and hope we'll
meet again ♪
- Girl: How are you doing?
- Philippe: Fine.
♪ Alang alang alang ♪
♪ Oh oh bip,
a-be-ba-do ba-dip ♪
♪ Oh, life could be
a dream ♪
♪ Life could be a dream,
sweetheart. ♪
Aren't you
Lucky Pierre?
No, Philippe Leclerc
is my name.
Yeah, right.
Okay, Lucky Pierre...
Philippe's voice:
That is what Frenchmen
were called in those days--
an allusion
to our mythical ways
with the ladies.
My advice, Phil,
for what it's worth--
go whole hog.
Whole hog?
Yeah, jump in
with both feet,
really involve yourself,
join the band,
the debating society,
that sort of thing.
But I don't play
an instrument.
I see.
Well, that is a pity.
Any sports?
Yes, football.
For real?
Yes.
I scored nine goals
last spring.
No shit.
We call them
touchdowns over here.
- Wide receiver, right?
- Of course.
Boy, you guys
have guts.
( boys chattering )
All right, girls,
practice practice.
- Hey, it's Cal.
- Cal, how are you doing?
Hey, buddy.
- Right on, Cal.
- Hey, Cal.
Hi, coach.
Philippe's voice:
That was Cal Parnell Cate,
our quarterback.
They just didn't make them
that way in France.
They still don't.
So is this the Frenchy
I'm supposed to try out?
He scored nine TDs
in Paris.
Oh, really?
Paris, Texas?
No, Paris, France.
Okay, kid, let's go.
It's your funeral.
Paris, eh?
( exhaling rhythmically )
Coach:
Keep it up, keep it up.
That's not good enough.
Come on now.
Come on,
keep it up.
All right, Frenchy,
now you tell the chief--
and no forked tongue--
you ever play this game?
No.
Just what you call
soccer.
Now I got to be square
with you, pilgrim,
this here game--
it ain't for everyone,
you know?
I mean, you got to like
getting hit.
( yelling )
Hey, you like
getting hit?
I don't know.
All right, forget it.
Forget it.
Just go out for a pass.
All right,
you see this line?
Yes, I do.
Okay, tenderfoot,
this here is a 30-yard line
we're standing on now,
all right?
When I say "hut hut"
you are gonna
run like hell
down to the 20-yard line,
turn around and
catch this here sucker.
I want you to concentrate
on the point of
the football.
And don't think.
Hut hut!
All right, Frenchy,
you're quick.
Hey, next time
you catch that ball
with your hands,
all right, never ever
with the chest.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's do it again.
Hut hut!
( thunder rumbling )
Lay low.
Chief Shitting Bull
just arrived.
Mr. Cate,
Mr. Cal Cate,
you think you're gonna
be able to quarterback
this football team
with a beer gut, huh?
Who's your little
playmate?
Phil Leclerc
from Paris, France.
Just messing around.
Nobody messes around
on my field, mister.
We play full-out
or not at all.
Go out for a pass, boy.
Hut hut!
What kind of
silly shit is that?
You lost your arm too?
Throw him a bullet.
You don't want
to jam his fingers
first day out, do you?
Put some zip on it.
All right, kid, listen.
I'm gonna throw it hard--
real hard, okay?
So listen, whatever you do,
catch it with
your palms this time,
not your fingers,
or you'll never
play piano again.
I don't play piano, Cal.
Hut hut!
Oh, nice hands.
Let's see if he can
take a hit.
Come on, coach,
that's bullshit.
Why don't you give
the guy a break?
Football's
a man's game, Mr. Cate.
Men get hit.
The sooner we find out
if he can take it, the better
it is for all of us.
Lewis, cover the kid.
Coach.
( growling )
But I'm much faster
without all this armor.
Better tighten
that strap, son.
All right, listen,
you see that guy, okay?
( growling )
When you catch the ball
he is gonna hit you
like you ain't never
been hit before.
I know him.
He's a sadistic
son of a bitch.
There's only one thing
you can do, Phil--
just stay as loose
as a goose, okay?
And then jump up.
Even if you think
you're in Bangkok
don't give him
the satisfaction,
all right?
Oui, mon colonel.
Shit.
On three.
Hut hut hut!
( grunts )
( moaning )
That's great, coach.
That's a great idea.
How are you feeling,
Hoss?
( boys chattering )
I don't know.
Strange.
Hey, I really tried
but I could not
get up.
Don't worry about it.
Listen, Lewis--
that bastard laid
a big-time hit on you.
Listen, I'll catch you
later, all right?
I'll come by and
take you for a ride.
A ride?
♪ Oh, yes ♪
♪ I'm the great
pretender ♪
♪ Pretending ♪
♪ That I'm doing well ♪
♪ My need is such ♪
♪ I pretend too much ♪
♪ I'm lonely ♪
♪ But no one
can tell. ♪
( screaming )
Philippe's voice:
True to his word,
Cal collected me
a few nights later
with two girls in tow.
My date was called
Sue Ann.
Quit staring,
will you?
I'm very sorry,
but you are
so very beautiful
it is difficult
not to.
Are you really
from Paris?
Yes, really.
Bet you had
a lot of girls already.
Well, not lots,
but some, yes.
It's normal, no?
Not in Wallatoona,
it isn't.
Wallatoona?
Where is that?
South Carolina, silly.
South Carolina City?
You're weird.
Sue Ann:
No.
Hey hey hey,
easy, tenderfoot.
Come on now,
these here girls
don't know from Frenchin'.
I said no.
No.
( distant dogs barking )
Hey hey.
Cheers.
Sue Ann said she wanted
to see me again.
No, that's
a big mistake, Hoss,
a big mistake.
You'd better
just save yourself
for the one and only.
Who is
the one and only?
She's the love
of your life, man.
She's out there somewhere
just waiting for you.
Don't blow it
by going steady
with some dame from SC.
Hell, Phil,
I reckon I must have
dated at least...
a hundred girls
since I've been here.
And how many
did you do it with?
Rule number one,
amigo--
good girls
don't do it.
And rule number two--
it don't count
if you don't do it
with a good girl.
You see, dog and pigs
don't count.
But what if you
want her too much?
What if you just can't
stand it anymore?
Well, then I guess you do
like everybody else--
make out
with your right hand
in the shower.
Yeah.
I believe Southern Bouquet
is probably about the best
soap for that.
See, it's nice and white
and it smells good.
And, hell, you can
pick it up anywhere.
What about whores?
Oh.
Danger, disease,
disgrace,
thrown out of frat,
heap big danger.
Come on, Phil,
me a Southern gentleman.
See, white whores
don't exist
and black whores
are off-limits.
Besides...
Besides what, Cal?
Well, there just ain't
no whores
in the Shenandoah Valley.
Philippe's voice:
One of my teachers,
Rex Jennings,
lived there
with his wife Doris.
He introduced me
to writers
like Raymond Chandler
and Salinger
whose books
I devoured.
( thud )
( creaking )
Doris?
Hi.
Hello.
I am terribly sorry.
I thought it was Doris.
You're foreign,
aren't you?
You're not
an ordinary student.
Is my accent that bad?
No.
I can tell by the fact
that you can look me
in the eyes.
American boys
can't seem to look
Negro girls in the eyes.
Do you want
some coffee?
Yes, please.
What's your name?
Philippe.
Philippe's voice:
Suddenly I realized
that I hadn't heard
my own name
in months.
I hadn't been Philippe
since I left Paris.
Careful.
It's hot.
You like this book?
I don't know.
I am only
on page two.
Have you read it?
Read it and taught it.
I don't just clean houses.
I'm a teacher.
- At college?
- No.
I teach elementary school
on the other side of town.
But now I have to go.
No, please,
five more minutes.
Non, Philippe,
ce n'est pas possible.
Vous parlez Francais?
Well, through the mail.
I took this
correspondence course.
But now I have to go.
No, stay
for just a moment.
Say my name again.
Please.
Why should I say
your name?
Because nobody calls me
by my real name.
And when you say it
it makes me feel
less lonely.
Are you lonely,
Philippe?
Sometimes.
Are you lonely now?
No.
What's your name?
April.
Hey, kid.
I'm glad
you're still here.
So how are you cottoning
to old JD there?
I am in love.
I know what you mean.
Wait till you get
to the part
where he dreams
of catching the boys.
No no, with a girl.
Oh, well,
that's great, kid.
Do I know her?
No, I don't think so.
I'm afraid
I have to go.
I have class at noon.
Well, take the book,
junior--
the least I can do.
Thank you.
You did a lot.
Careful now.
Don't let those
Southern belles
spin your head
around.
I won't.
( boys chattering )
- Hey, Frenchy.
- Hello.
Merci beaucoup.
( laughing )
( dance music playing )
Have you seen
Cal around?
Cal?
Cal who?
Please.
Cal Cate.
He's over there
watching TV.
Cal, can I borrow
your car?
Are you kidding me?
That's a big favor,
Greenhorn.
It needs a big trade.
You have a French exam
coming up, don't you?
- Can you
guarantee me an A?
- Of course.
- You got a license?
- I have everything--
a license, money,
insurance.
One scratch and I'll
pay you 1000 times.
Oh, Frenchy, Frenchy.
Boy, you are lying
when you're lying.
But if you want
I'll take you where
you need to go.
So, pard, is this
just a joy ride
or you actually want
to go someplace?
I want to go where
the black people live.
No shit!
Frenchy wants to go
to nigger town.
What did you do, boy,
go and get yourself
some whore?
She's not a whore.
Her name is April.
Look, just tell me
where it is and I'll walk.
Oh, okay, now he's gonna
walk in the nigger town.
Boy, they'll take
them straight razors
and cut your French ass
to ribbons.
No, me Southern
gentleman,
me keep his word.
But I don't have
to like it.
( people chattering )
( baby crying )
I don't suppose
we got an address
on this maid, huh?
April.
No.
She teaches school.
Not at this hour,
she don't.
I'll tell you what--
I know the Cates
rode with Lee.
If I had a couple of boys
like this on my team--
take conference
every year.
Why don't you
ask the coach?
Yeah, sure,
the day it rains beer.
Look, let's just get
the hell out of here,
all right?
No, please,
another five minutes.
All right,
you said she was
a school teacher, right?
Let's go to the church.
They'll know
where to find her.
( dogs barking )
Philippe's voice:
There are two hearts
that beat
in the body of America.
One is hidden
behind the other.
And once
I heard its cry,
nothing was ever
quite the same for me.
( people singing psalm )
All right, Hoss,
last chance.
Big Cal needs
his sleep.
♪ ...Just to know ♪
♪ Thus saith the Lord ♪
♪ 'Tis so sweet ♪
♪ To trust in Jesus ♪
♪ Just to take Him ♪
♪ At His word ♪
♪ Just to rest... ♪
Philippe,
what in God's name
are you doing here?
Looking for you.
Children, I know
God is love,
but you'd better
take this outside.
♪ ...Just to know ♪
♪ Thus saith the Lord... ♪
( door creaks )
How did you know
how to find me?
Inspiration.
Okay, Philippe,
what do you want?
I must see you again.
Otherwise I will die.
Well, we can't have
that now, can we?
No, my parents
will be very sad.
Give me one good reason
why I should see you.
Because...
I think sometimes
you must be lonely too.
And of course
I can give you
French lessons.
All right.
You be here
the day after tomorrow.
4:00.
Well, I got to say
one thing, Phil--
if you're gonna
risk your neck
for a colored girl,
it might as well
be her.
Isn't she beautiful?
Isn't she
the most beautiful girl
you've ever seen?
Sure she is, Hoss.
I mean, she's
really something.
And so are you,
so just be careful.
Why? Why is everybody
warning me?
Because we're
from the South.
What do you see
that's so bad?
Nothing.
I mean, hey, if she's
your one and only,
maybe God will
protect y'all.
But there's just
one thing, Phil,
and this is
real important--
hey, you don't
breathe a word
of this
affair of the heart
to anyone.
You understand?
Okay?
Or we're all dead.
Philippe's voice:
My favorite teacher
was a man
with the improbable name
of Zachariah Wilhelm Gilmore,
the Liberal Arts Dean
and the living legend.
During the war
he had worked
under Wild Bill Donovan,
the founder of the CIA,
and returned
to the Shenandoah Valley
with a chestful of medals
and his reputation made.
We called him Zach.
Now some poets,
ladies and gentlemen,
turn their lives
into their great poems.
Do any examples spring
to your eager minds?
The dreamy-eyed
Monsieur Leclerc?
Byron, sir?
Byron.
Byron!
He had to mention Byron,
the one man
who confounds us all.
But why don't we
mention Bulgakov,
who had to share
his mistress with Stalin
so he could write
the "Master and Margarita"
while locked
in a duel to the death
with morphine?
Or Harry Crosby
or Monsieur Rimbaud?
You mentioned
Harry Crosby, sir.
I'm not familiar
with that name.
Harry?
Crosby was a Brahmin,
a Boston Brahmin,
nephew of Pierpont Morgan
and a true decadent.
He lived
in your city, Philippe,
died in the arms
of his mistress,
the Fire Princess,
at the Hotel Des Artistes
in New York City,
a double suicide.
On the sole
of his left foot
they found a tattoo
of our Savior Jesus Christ
on the cross.
So if any of you feel
as if you are
a decadent,
as some of our young
Southern gentlemen
are wont to do,
feeling the weight
of their bloodlines,
you all have
a long way to go.
What are you still
doing here,
you dwarves,
you dreadful
onanistic
small-timers?
Can't you see
that I am walking
with the ghosts
of the great?
Philippe's voice:
French was the bridge
on which
April and I met.
In many ways she was
even more of an outsider
than me
because I could at least
go back to Paris,
but where was she
going to go
with her books,
her correspondence courses
and her dreams
except to a country
that hadn't yet been made
and is even today
far from finished?
Take aimer--
"to love."
Plus-que-parfait--
j'avais aimé.
I had loved?
Exactly.
And now for
the conditionnel passé.
J'aurais aimé.
I would have loved?
Oui.
J'aurais aimé Philippe,
but all we did
was study French.
What else
did you have in mind?
I don't know.
I'm very surprised
some Southern belle
hasn't thrown herself
into your arms.
They run from me.
You're meant to chase them.
I only want
to chase you.
So chase me.
( laughs )
What?
Why are you laughing?
How long
have you been driving?
Since this afternoon.
Cal is playing
Clemson.
He won't be back
until tomorrow.
Cal?
The golden boy
you showed up with
the other night.
Golden boy?
I want to be with you,
ma petit prince.
Mon prince.
"Ma" is feminine,
"mon" is masculine.
Okay, mon prince,
this will be far enough.
When will I
see you again?
Never.
( both laugh )
How about Monday
same time?
D'accord.
( car approaching )
( men chattering,
blues harmonica playing )
Who are those guys?
That's the blues
coming by.
April, sometimes
you lose me.
They're musicians.
They play the blues--
you know, devil music--
at the Jook.
What's the Jook?
The Jook is one place
a French boy should
never go.
You hear me?
You go home
and you keep yourself
safe for me till Monday.
Philippe's voice:
Devil music, Jook's,
the blues--
she might as well
have waved that red cape
in front of me.
I was at that
blissful age
where bad things
only happen to other people.
Mm, wow.
( rock music playing )
♪ Keep a-knocking
but you can't come in ♪
♪ You keep a-knocking but
you can't come in ♪
♪ Keep a-knocking
but you can't come in ♪
♪ Come back tomorrow night
and try it again ♪
♪ You said you love me
but you can't come in ♪
♪ You said you love me but
you can't come in, whoo ♪
♪ You said you love me
but you can't come in ♪
♪ Come back tomorrow night
and try it again, wow! ♪
( blues music playing )
Woman: Oh, I thought
we were gonna see
Howlin' Wolf.
Man:
Baby, I just want
to show you something.
Hello.
Whoa whoa whoa.
Are you looking
for something, white boy?
Yes, I would like
to see the show.
( chuckles )
Wait right there.
Just wait
right there.
- I have money.
- Just wait.
What the fuck
do you want?
I am terribly sorry,
but I thought it might
be possible
to listen
to the music.
You ain't
from here, are you?
No, but I can pay.
I wouldn't let you
in this place
if you paid me $100.
Hell, if something
happened to a white
boy like you,
I gots the sheriff's
all over my ass
and he shut me down.
You dig?
- Yes, I understand.
- White boy.
- Hey, boy.
- Uh-oh.
- Coming to
the coon show?
- Yes,
- Fucking college boy.
- I'm not a college boy.
I am French.
Hey, you ain't
going nowhere.
I'm not a redneck.
I am not
a Southern gentleman.
I am French.
Leave the goddamn
boy alone!
Are you French?
Yes, sir.
Paris.
Oh, yeah?
Paris, huh?
We've played Paris before.
The folks treated us
real nice.
I met this little
fine young thing
over there.
Her name was Edith,
you know.
Just a little
itty bitty thing,
but she could sing,
- couldn't she, Sonny?
- Yeah, man, yeah.
So tell me,
what does this thing
get up to?
Pardon?
How fast
does she go?
Oh, as fast
as you want to.
( both laugh )
This kid
is all right.
Yeah, you came
all the way from Paris
to see the show?
Yes, but they won't
let me in.
Oh, that's your
backwoods for you.
Yeah, see, now
if you was in Chicago
that wouldn't happen.
That's where we're from.
See, Chicago is
a wide open town
where everybody
digs the blues.
Man, these folks
have been down so long,
fear's their
daily bread.
But you-- you're
coming in with us.
Come on.
I thought I told you
to get!
This here kid--
with us.
Not in my joint,
he ain't.
Listen up,
motherfucker,
now it's one thing
I got to play in your
motherfucking joint
and look at your fat
fucking ugly face
all night long
while I know
that you are
ripping me off
at the gate,
but you see
this kid here?
This kid right here
is coming in with us.
And if anybody's got
a problem with that,
well, we can just
step on around
to the side--
you, me and my
little friend here--
and we can work this out
the Chicago way.
Come on, kid.
( blues music playing,
people cheering )
He's cute, ain't he,
the white boy?
- Girl, you look
so cute tonight.
- Thank you.
Ugh, a white boy.
Man:
Ladies and gentlemen,
the man y'all been
waiting for,
Mr. Howlin' Wolf!
Give it up for him!
( cheering )
( playing a blues song )
( people cheering )
♪ If you're long way
from home ♪
♪ Can't sleep
at night ♪
♪ Grab your telephone,
something just ain't right ♪
♪ That's evil ♪
♪ Evil's going
on and on ♪
♪ I'm warning you,
brother ♪
♪ You better watch
your happy home ♪
♪ Well, you're long way
from home ♪
♪ Can't sleep at all ♪
♪ You know another mule
is kicking in your stall ♪
♪ That's evil ♪
♪ Evil's going on ♪
♪ I'm warning you,
brother ♪
♪ You better watch
your happy home ♪
( playing harmonica )
Mr. Howlin' Wolf
sent this to you.
♪ Oh, something's wrong ♪
♪ In your home ♪
♪ Yeah, you better
check it out ♪
♪ Well, if you call her
on the phone ♪
♪ And she answers
awful slow ♪
♪ Grab the first thing smoking
if you have to hop on ♪
♪ That's evil ♪
♪ Evil's going
all wrong ♪
♪ I am warning you,
brother ♪
♪ You better watch
your happy home. ♪
( playing faster )
This next tune
is for our little friend.
He came all the way
from Paris to hear us play.
We have somebody special
gonna do it for you,
my main man
Sonny Boy Williamson!
( crows cheering )
♪ Come here, baby ♪
♪ Sit down
on daddy's knee ♪
♪ Come here, baby ♪
♪ Sit down
on daddy's knee ♪
♪ Got something
to tell you ♪
♪ Sure is worrying me ♪
♪ I cry cry cry ♪
♪ All night long ♪
♪ I'm crazy
about you, baby ♪
♪ But you know
you done me wrong. ♪
( muttering )
( distant train whistle
blowing )
Are you gonna be okay
to drive, boy?
Yeah, we'll drop you.
No no,
thank you.
I have to drive
this car back.
You be careful.
This time of night
everybody's a nigger
around here.
( laughing )
Thank you.
You showed me
magic tonight
I will never forget.
( man vocalizing )
( singing along )
♪ Love love me, darling,
come and go with me ♪
♪ Please don't send me
'way beyond the sea ♪
( siren wailing )
♪ I need you, darling ♪
♪ So come go with me... ♪
Merde.
( keys jingle )
Man:
What can I tell you, doc?
The boy was doing 73.
And unless
I'm mistaken,
he had more than
a few beers in him.
Now what I'd like
to know is,
where do you reckon
that boy
got them beers
at this hour
of the night?
Sheriff McLain, may I
take this opportunity
to make a small
contribution
to your reelection
campaign?
( chuckles )
One-- you're going
to do yard work for me
till you pay off
this debt.
I usually pay my boys
50 cents an hour.
Two-- you're grounded.
I've been watching you
for quite a while
and I have come
to the conclusion
that there is
something wrong.
I do not know
what it is
and I do not intend
to find out.
Come closer.
Closer closer.
At two inches
I begin to see.
I'm going to say
something very simple
and very fundamental,
and it is this--
don't spoil it.
Don't spoil
your semester.
This is an interlude
of inestimable value.
What you are
experiencing here
is priceless.
Don't be the Hamlet
of the freshman dorm.
( distant train whistle
blowing )
( panting )
I'm grounded.
Cal won't lend me
his car anymore.
Sorry I'm late.
But if you're grounded,
what are you doing here?
I had to see you.
You did that for me?
Of course.
I love you.
♪ You looked at me ♪
♪ With kindness
in your eyes ♪
♪ You took me
by surprise ♪
♪ You turned
my world around ♪
♪ I never knew ♪
♪ That there would come ♪
♪ A day ♪
♪ When love would feel
this way ♪
♪ And turn
my world around ♪
♪ Although I know
that we belong ♪
♪ In two different
worlds ♪
♪ I can't help believe ♪
♪ Our love will make us ♪
♪ Stronger every day ♪
♪ If tomorrow comes ♪
♪ And takes you away
from me ♪
♪ I'll take that chance ♪
♪ To be with you ♪
♪ When I'm with you ♪
♪ Time will be
on our side ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ As long
as we're together ♪
♪ You turn my world ♪
♪ Around. ♪
You're crying?
Why?
Why be sad
when this is
such a happy thing?
Because I'm gonna
lose you
to some belle,
some girl
with blonde hair.
Cherie,
I'm not interested
in those stupid girls.
And they are not
interested in me.
I only love you.
For you
I'll risk everything.
Can't you see that,
ma petite reine?
I'm your little queen?
Yes.
You're the queen
of my heart.
I'm going to take you
to Paris
where things
are different.
And we'll marry.
That's nonsense.
It's never gonna happen.
I like you.
You're different.
I like the way you talk
and you're gentle,
but it's all it is.
It's all it's ever
gonna be.
You and I come from
very different worlds.
No.
You and I-- we are
from the same world.
The wind blows
in our face the same way.
And the sun shines
in your face and in my face
the same way.
The rain
makes us both wet.
You are not from Mars
and I'm not from the moon.
Say my name in French.
Avril,
mon coeur.
Mr. Leclerc.
Mr. Leclerc,
I have decided
for the sake of my garden
and for my own mental health
to find another
assignment for you
more in keeping
with your talents,
meager though
they might be.
( all chattering,
crowd cheering )
( groans )
My leg, man.
I can't-- I can't--
All right, come on.
Coach:
Straighten out.
Straighten out there.
Hi, Cal.
Great game.
Yeah, sure.
What's the matter
with your kicker?
The asshole tried
to kick the ball
out of the stadium.
Now he's got
a groin pull.
What's a groin pull?
It's exactly what
it sounds like, Phil.
It means he's out
for the season.
All right, look,
next week we got
our biggest game,
Alabama Tech, okay?
I mean, their defense
is good--
really good.
You hear me talking?
It means I can't get 'em
in the end zone,
it's gonna come down
to a field goal again.
We're gonna be trying out
kickers all week.
It's gonna be
a nightmare.
Oh, I see that Faulkner
is lecturing
at Washington and Lee.
- Are you interested?
- Absolutely.
Good.
I think you and--
I think you and Sue Ann
should cover that.
Philippe's voice:
The last time
I saw Sue Ann
she was
a slightly dizzy belle
who I tried to kiss
in the back of a car.
Now she had reincarnated
herself into a journalist.
But then again,
at that age
we tried on
personalities
like other people
try on clothes.
What are you reading?
"Absalom, Absalom!"
Ah, the son of David.
Faulkner.
Look, this conversation
is pointless.
by a kind
of boredom
or embarrassed,
as if he was wondering
what in the world
he was doing
in front of
all these strangers.
He exuded the kind
of suave patience
He spoke
only for the front row
and I doubted
that most of them
even heard him.
But if Faulkner
wanted to whisper,
he'd earned that right
as far as I was concerned.
I'll never forget
that handsome face
his mouth moving
like a sinner
on his deathbed
confession.
I must admit
I'm getting
a little dizzy.
You'll forgive me.
He's--
he's so beautiful.
( laughing )
Sorry.
Look, the only reason
I gave my hand to that girl
is because she is sick.
She's in psychoanalysis.
On your couch?
April, I only love you.
I swear by all
that is sacred to me.
So you're telling me
my eyes are lying?
Your eyes are lying.
No, they're not.
I'll prove it to you.
Well, Hans, what do you think
about the quaint custom
of Thanksgiving?
Thank you, Joanne.
It's wonderful.
It's very nice.
Do you have anything
like it in Austria?
No no.
What is das?
Das is a yam.
How are your
parents, Cal?
They're fine, sir.
Philippe's voice:
You'd think that
of all people
Cal would have
a place to go,
but he didn't.
His parents
were alcoholics
which made him
kind of an orphan himself
and gave him
that edge of sadness
that made him
such a great guy.
Pardon?
Your parents.
You do have parents,
don't you, boy?
Philippe:
Yes, I do have parents.
And they are fine.
I just received a letter
from them
and also
from my brother.
He was a soldier
in the Indochine.
Indochina.
I was in Indochina.
It's a beautiful
country.
Very determined
people,
( door opens )
No, Dominic,
I don't have the magazine
and I don't know
where it is either.
Maybe you should use
your imagination tonight.
What for?
What's Dominic got to use
his imagination for?
Oh, April,
you are so cruel to me.
Here.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Oh, April.
Thank you, God.
You ever had
pumpkin pie before?
Did you make it?
No.
I'm devouring you.
It is you that I taste.
Your hands
have broken these eggs,
touched this flour
and puréed this--
this most interesting
vegetable.
And you came here
to see me.
Is it not incredibly
dangerous?
No.
It's Thanksgiving.
Forget it.
I'm still angry
with you.
Why?
Because of Sue Ann?
She is so stupid.
I always sleep
with her.
I mean,
when I'm with her
I go to sleep.
She is so boring.
Philippe, I have to
tell you something.
No no, please.
One kiss
for a poor orphan,
all alone
on Thanksgiving.
What's French
for "kiss"?
Bisou.
Un bisou.
That's French
for "kiss"?
Yes, un bisou
is a French kiss.
Well, maybe you'd better
give me one of those.
( Cal cheering )
Hey, Phil.
Phil, let's go for a ride,
little buddy.
Where is everybody?
Oh, I forgot.
With mommy and daddy
for turkey.
Well, fuck all y'all!
'Cause I'm
a Southern belle.
As long as what?
As long as he keeps
winning games.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
Cheers.
( shouting)
Yes, sir!
We're gonna beat
Alabama Tech, sir!
Hey, Phil...
where are you, buddy?
Where is everybody?
Hi, Philippe.
Did you have
a nice Thanksgiving?
Yes.
And you?
Did you go back
to Wallatoona?
Wallatoona?
Yes, where you live.
Oh, sure.
It was grand-- grand.
Did you finish
"Catcher in the Rye"?
Yes.
I'm-- I'm gonna see you
this afternoon.
Philippe.
Are you afraid of me?
Philippe's voice:
If only it hadn't rained
that afternoon.
If only I hadn't
sheltered Sue Ann
with my coat.
If only, if only...
Jennings:
"The silhouette
of a moving cat
wavered across
the moonlight,
and turning my head
to watch it,
I saw that
I was not alone--
fifty feet away
a figure had emerged
from the shadow
of my neighbor's mansion
and was standing
with his hands
in his pockets
regarding
the silver pepper
of the stars.
Something in his
leisurely movements
and the secure position
of his feet upon the lawn
suggested that it was
Mr. Gatsby himself,
come out to determine
what share was his
of our local heavens."
We don't seem to be
holding your attention,
Mr. Cate.
Well, it's just a bunch
of Yankee talk to me.
Oh, it's just
a bunch of Yankee talk?
What do you think,
Philippe?
Pardon?
You'll have to excuse
our French friend
today, sir.
See, it's my
considered opinion
that his mind is
on other things.
Oh, all right.
Let us move on
to matters
less controversial
then, shall we?
Something romantic?
Romantic?
Romantic.
Ah, here we go.
Lord Byron.
Ooh, mad, bad
and dangerous to know.
Yeah, you identify
with that, don't you, Cal?
It's my family's
motto, sir.
I'm sure it is.
Now...
- this here poem...
- ( door slams )
...is called
"When We Two Parted."
Excuse me.
You know
where it is by now.
Does anybody have
anything else
that they need to do
before we begin?
No?
Good.
This is a story
of a passionate
love affair...
- April.
- ...come to a painful
and premature end.
"When we two parted
In silence and tears,
Half broken-hearted
To sever for years,
Pale grew thy cheek
and cold,
Colder thy kiss;
Truly that hour foretold
Sorrow to this."
Go away.
"The dew of the morning
Sunk chill on my brow--
It felt like the warning
Of what I feel now.
Thy vows are all broken,
And light is thy fame:
I hear thy name spoken,
And share in its shame."
- Mrs. Jennings: April.
- Yes, ma'am.
Where is
that green bowl?
Jennings:
Honey, for crying out loud,
I'm trying to read here.
Mrs. Jennings:
I'm sorry.
"They name thee
before me,
A knell
to mine ear;
A shadow
comes o'er me--
Why wert thou
so dear?
They know not
I knew thee,
Who knew thee
too well:
Long, long
shall I rue thee,
Too deeply to tell.
Jennings and April:
In secret we met--
In silence
I grieve,
That thy heart
could forget,
Thy spirit deceive.
If I should
meet thee
After long years,
How should I
greet thee?
With silence
and tears."
You two
know each other?
No, we don't.
I need
that green bowl.
Jennings:
Now this poem
was published in 1816--
the same year
that Byron left England,
never to return.
He was, as I'm sure
you recall,
divorced
rather scandalously,
so this was probably
a goodbye
to some forbidden lover.
Well, Phil,
all I can say is
you missed
one hell of a poem.
Philippe's voice:
I looked for my April,
but she vanished
in December.
She left her job
at the Jenningses
and the Baptist minister
hadn't seen her either.
Hey, bubi,
want to play?
Good.
( muttering )
Argh!
Hans:
Good. Wunderbar.
( all grunting )
All right,
right here, Mr. Cate.
Here you go.
All right,
now go easy, Hoss.
It's consistency
we're looking for.
Capisci?
Great shot!
Do it again.
( growling )
Hey! Hey!
Hike.
( grunts )
Philippe.
Hey, Philippe.
Run, boy, run!
Put some heat
under it.
Let me ask you
a question--
you think you can do that
with 11 assholes
from Alabama Tech
looking to rip
your leg off?
I can do it with my
left foot too.
Okay, go get yourself
a number.
Pardon?
You just made
the team, Frenchy.
Go on.
( cheering )
Yeah, Frenchy,
you made the team!
Anyway, listen,
this alumni says to me,
he says, "Hey, Cal,
if you beat Alabama Tech
you got yourself
a brand new Caddy...
convertible."
Hi, Cal.
Hi, Philippe.
Hi, Sue Ann.
There's a girl
to see you.
She's downstairs.
April.
I came
to say goodbye.
John Patrick Baldridge,
Elizabeth's father.
I told them
you were a Marquis.
Elizabeth?
Oh, monsieur,
we're taking our daughter
back to Boston.
Much to our surprise,
we find
that she is
seriously ill.
Ill?
Oh, the unspeakable things
she's been reading.
He has
a black mistress.
Mr. Baldridge:
As you see,
Monsieur le Marquis,
she is really
very ill.
Yes, I can see that.
Mrs. Baldridge:
She is incapable
of meeting
the challenges
awaiting her--
challenges we have devoted
all of our love
and experience
to prepare her for.
Love?
Mommy,
did you say love?
( laughing )
Love?
Philippe's voice:
My God, her name was
Elizabeth, not Sue Ann--
just another square peg
trying to fit into
a round hole
till there was
nothing left of her
but splinters.
Philippe:
Excuse me.
I haven't seen her.
I know, I know,
but just the smallest
of messages...
I can't do that.
Now I can only guess
at your relationship.
Not only is it wrong
in the eyes of God,
but, son,
it's dangerous.
I know.
Yes, you're right,
I'm sure,
but if you could
just tell her
that I'm playing against
Alabama Tech tomorrow.
You?
Oh, dear Lord, help us.
I'm just a kicker.
But please please,
after this game
my semester is over
and I have to go
back to Paris.
Hey, son,
kick some 'Bama butt.
( cheering )
33 red on two.
One, two, ready?
What the hell?
He's calling
his own damn play!
He's calling his own
play out there!
( grunting )
Cover me, cover me,
cover me.
( crowd booing,
whistle blows )
( players cheering )
All right, you bunch
of candy asses,
get your butts
over here and listen up.
And I mean now.
Move it, move it.
Boys, what do you
think's gonna happen
if we don't win this
football game, huh?
Nothing.
Well, you'll be
disappointed,
but then you'll go home
for Christmas.
But for me
and my wife,
my boy Cody
and my little
Elizabeth--
we're not gonna have
any Christmas.
They're gonna fire
my ass.
Yes, sir.
So while you're
around your
Christmas tree,
opening your presents
with your family,
I'm gonna be trying
to explain to Cody
why he's not gonna
get that bicycle
he's counted on
all year
and why there's a sign
in our front yard
that says "For Sale"
instead of a snowman.
Jane and I will be
packing up
the last couple
of crates
and my little girl's gonna
come down the stairs
in her jammies
and she's gonna say to me,
"Daddy, why do we
have to leave?
Boys, I'm gonna
tell her the truth
like I always do.
I'm gonna say to her,
"Darling,
there was a group
of young men,
fine young men,
brave young men,
talented young men
who when the chips
were down--
they just threw in
the towel.
And the shame is,
they were good.
I mean, they were
real good.
They were this close
to being the very best,
but they threw in
the goddamn towel."
Let's kill
the bastards!
Philippe's voice:
Much later I learned
that Coach Mallard was
and always had been
a confirmed
bachelor.
( band playing,
crowd cheering )
Announcer:
And now they're coming back
for the second half.
So let's hear it
for the ASU Rebels!
Anybody lays a hand
on him,
and you're gonna be
the new altar boy.
You understand me?
Now you get out there
and you tear it up.
Go go go!
Announcer:
It's third down
and nine to go.
Can they do it?
Jack's open, coach.
It's third down.
We're running it.
Come on, coach.
It's wide open.
I can get it there.
Just trust me.
Okay, call your own
damn play.
Philippe.
Hey, Frenchy, come here.
How are you feeling,
Frenchy?
- Fine.
- That's good.
Down, set, hut!
( whistle blows )
Time out.
Kid, let's see
what you're made of.
Announcer:
And with only
seconds to go,
they're bringing on
their ace in the hole
Philippe Leclerc
to try for the field goal.
You got it.
Good luck.
Save my ass, buddy.
Time out.
( whistle blows,
players groaning )
Player:
Bring it in.
Another time out?
They want you
to think about it, Hoss.
What's there
to think about?
( players cheering )
Long enough
for my man here
to take a shot.
( rapid heartbeat )
( whistle blows )
Base.
Cal:
Hut hut!
Frenchy!
Throw the ball!
Frenchy, throw it,
throw it!
Frenchy, throw the ball!
Throw it, throw it!
( cheering )
( band playing )
April!
Put me down.
Philippe's voice:
This time she was
truly gone.
And at the end
of the day,
it wasn't
because of Sue Ann
or even the fact
that I was a student
and she a maid, no.
We'd been thrown together
for a brief moment
two foreigners
traveling side by side
through this great
and strange land
called America.
( dance music playing )
But all I had to do
to be accepted
was to win
a football game.
For April it wasn't
quite that easy.
Congratulations.
You were exhilarating
out there today.
I didn't know
you had it in you.
You have ice water
in your veins, son,
ice water.
Thank you.
( girls giggling )
Come on, Cal.
( Cal laughing )
Okay, hey, easy.
One at a time, girls.
Cal.
Hey, whoa, easy.
Philippe:
Now, almost
40 years later,
I've come to realize
that youth is a gift
wasted on the young.
I was too preoccupied
with my role
as the Hamlet
of the freshman dorm
to truly appreciate
the friends I made
in that semester
in the Shenandoah Valley.
Somehow I wasn't quite
up to the grandeur
of Cal Cate,
the poetry
of Zach,
the tragedy
of Sue Ann
and, most of all,
the passion
of April.
And now,
like so many men
who have taken more
than they have given,
I find myself standing
on a mountain of glass,
looking for the diamonds
I threw away.
( train whistle blowing,
crossing bells dinging )
( train chugging )
Need a hand?
Yes, please.
No no, thank you.
My daughter
made me promise
to give you this.
April's voice:
"Philippe, mon amour,
my love is yours always.
April."
♪ You looked at me ♪
Sir!
♪ With kindness
in your eyes ♪
Philippe:
Sir!
♪ You took me ♪
♪ By surprise ♪
♪ You turned
my world around ♪
♪ I never knew ♪
♪ That there would come
a day ♪
♪ When love would feel
this way ♪
♪ And turn my world
around ♪
( Cal cheering )
♪ Although I know
that we belong ♪
♪ In two different
worlds ♪
♪ I can't help believe ♪
♪ Our love will make us ♪
♪ Stronger every day ♪
♪ If tomorrow comes ♪
♪ And takes you away ♪
♪ From me ♪
♪ I'll take that chance ♪
♪ To be with you ♪
♪ You came to me ♪
♪ Girl ♪
♪ When I was all alone ♪
♪ Alone, yeah ♪
♪ So far away ♪
♪ From home ♪
♪ You turned
my world around ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ When I'm with you ♪
♪ When I'm
with you ♪
♪ Time will be
on our side ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ As long as we're
together ♪
♪ You'll turn my world ♪
♪ Around ♪
♪ When I'm with you ♪
♪ Girl ♪
♪ You turn my world ♪
♪ Around. ♪