[soft piano music]
[tense piano music]
[windshield wipers
scraping softly]
[soft piano music]
[tense piano music]
[rifle clicks]
[gunshot blasting]
[tires skidding]
[tires screeching]
[motor humming]
[grass crunching]
[shoe thudding]
[Nick groans softly]
[Nick gasps]
[radio clicks]
- This is 40 Victor-One.
Patch me through to
Crime Watch, over.
[radio buzzes]
- [Man] This is Crime Watch.
Go ahead, 40 Victor-One.
- I think I found your man.
- [Crime Watch] You sure?
- Yes, sir.
I got me a major
most wanted here.
Only he don't look much like
a dangerous killer, presently.
[door creaking]
[door thudding]
[stack thudding]
[envelope thudding]
- All right.
Would you mind putting
that crap back in the bag?
It's still evidence.
By the way, whose ring is that?
[pad thuds]
[Winslow sighs]
- You think we can get
through this today?
- You got a date?
Your name is Nicholas
Isidore Augustine,
AKA Nicholas August?
- Yeah.
- And you waived the right
to have an attorney present.
Is that correct?
- My attorney is present.
- Let's get to it.
I'm Special Agent
Winslow of the FBI,
Organized Crime Division.
I'm confused about one
thing, your residence.
Are you are living in Los
Angeles or Palm Springs?
- You seem to have all
the information today.
Why don't you tell me?
- You know something?
I'm sure that that wit got
you by in Baker and Colgate
and Virginia Law, but it just
doesn't cut it down here.
You know what I mean?
Let's not go down that path.
And if you're so goddamn smart,
what are you doing in here?
Look, before we get started,
you want like a soda?
Coffee?
Here, look, have a cigarette.
[pack thuds]
Relax.
[Nick sighs]
- Yeah, that's how I
used to do it, too.
- Excuse me?
- Look, let's just cut
the bullshit, okay?
You know who you're talking to.
See, the first
thing I used to do
is get the relationship going,
establish some contact.
Care for a cigarette?
[Agent Winslow sighs]
[lighter clicks]
[Nick laughs]
Oh, here we go, baby!
[men laughing]
[ball bouncing]
Hehe, got you there! [laughs]
Ho, coming in to me!
[ball bouncing]
[Anson grunting]
[Nick chuckles]
- Nice serve.
So, when were you
gonna tell me, pal?
- Tell you what?
- That you're getting
kicked upstairs.
- I'm not going anywhere.
Serve the ball, let's go.
- Deputy Attorney
General's office
ordered a job eval
on you, buddy.
I smell justice.
[ball bouncing]
[floor squeaking]
Yep.
Lousy back hand.
- I'm trying to concentrate
here, do you mind?
Thank you.
- There's rumblings going around
that Federal's putting together
a new team of hot shots
to work in organized crimes.
- Who told you that?
- Serve.
[ball bouncing]
I gotta tell ya,
I'm pretty jealous.
They must want you
pretty bad, too.
Your background check
alone was this thick.
- What's the score?
- Nine all.
[ball bouncing]
[Anson shouts]
My serve. [laughs]
[Anson sighs]
Organized crimes
has been monitoring
a new undercurrent of
hostility in the mob of late.
- I thought the families
went legit years ago.
- Well, they have
and they haven't.
I mean, one thing's for certain,
the mafia certainly has
assimilated into society.
Hell, you can't
buy a glass of beer
or a gallon of gas
without the mafia
getting a kickback
somewhere down the line.
- So, why are they still
warring with each other then?
- They're not.
Somebody from the outside
is coming at them.
- Who?
- Well, who do you think?
The guys that picked up
what the mob left behind.
The next generation
of immigrants?
The Chinese?
I mean, the Triads are
all fleeing Hong Kong.
I guess they figure it's
easier to come over here
and take on our
criminal justice system.
- Yeah, well, I don't see it.
- Yeah, but these
are smart guys.
I mean, they kept chipping
away, chipping away
until they found somebody that
could open up the back door.
Somebody who will let 'em
in, make some introductions.
They settled on this
mid-level hood from Jersey
who just got relocated out West.
Guy got a little too
ambitious for his own good.
You know, the Triads are wining
and dining the hell out of him.
He's gonna be their entree
into the power base,
setting him up with his
own little organization.
Organized Crimes calls
him the Toy Godfather.
He's got like his own
little empire already.
I don't know, maybe
you've heard of this guy.
Carlo Augustine.
[soft piano music]
Nick, you okay?
You all right, man?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
- Anyway, this guy came
up through the ranks.
He has some lineage.
His father was
Armando Augustine.
I mean, to the mafia families,
this guy was il
capo di tutti capi.
The godfather.
He was a tough old bastard too.
I think it was back in the '60s
when one of his
paisans took him out.
The hit wiped out the whole
family except for the two kids.
Two sons.
Carlo was the oldest.
Now the Triads are setting
him up out here, out West,
down out of Palm Springs.
- What happened
to the other boy?
- Oh yeah, well, he was just
a little kid at the time.
Nobody really knows
what happened to him.
[soft piano music]
[gunshot blasting]
[rifle clicking]
[gunshots blasting]
[body thudding]
[soft piano music]
[phone ringing]
- [Nick Recording]
Hi, leave a message
and have yourself a good day.
[answering machine beeps]
- [Anson] Nick, it's Anson.
Come on, bud, I
know you're there.
Pick up or I'm
sending a squad car.
All right, I'm giving
you a three-count.
One, two.
- Hi, Mom.
- [Anson] You okay, bub?
- I'm fine.
I guess I just must
be a little burnt out.
- [Anson] Can't handle
the pressure, huh?
I always knew you were soft.
My top boy goes AWOL, I'm
going berserk around here.
Seriously though, I was
getting a little worried.
- Hey, I'm sorry about
that, Ans, I really am.
- [Anson] Look, you want
some R & R, you got it, bub.
God knows you put in more
time than any five of my DAs.
You got enough sick
time and vacation leave
coming to cruise for a while.
- Great, that
sounds good, thanks.
- [Anson] Anyway.
It's good to know
you're all right, buddy.
- Okay, you take care now.
Something was
stirring inside me,
it was like pulling me back.
I felt like I was going crazy.
- You saying that
your strange behavior
was caused by some kind
of schizophrenia episode?
- You've got to
understand something.
I'm going along,
see, living the life.
Doing the job,
thinking I'm this guy.
And one day I found
out I'm not me.
I'm somebody else.
Somebody born out
of a nightmare.
- So, your conversation
with Waverley
at the racquetball court,
that's what prompted you
to go to Palm Springs?
- Something was
eating at me inside.
If Carlo was out there,
then I had to find him.
A buddy of mine at the
Palm Springs DA office
gave me the name
of the restaurant
the local wise guys hung out.
I wasn't the only one
staking out the joint.
[camera clicks]
- What were you
expecting to find?
[soft piano music]
[camera clicks]
[car motor hums]
[soft piano music]
[birds chirping]
[gun clicks]
[gate hums]
[car motor hums]
[birds chirping]
[alarm beeping softly]
[men grunting]
[legs thudding]
[Nick groaning]
- Nicholas.
Is this the ganef you
say was following us?
Oh God, get, get.
Nicholas, come, come,
come, shh, shh, shh.
Come, sit down.
Why are you here?
- That's what I'd
like to know, Manny.
You tell me.
And what's an East
Coast attorney
doing with the syndicate
in Palm Springs?
- Oh, they're clients.
You lie down with dogs,
you get up with fleas.
I count you with your--
- No, no.
This is not legal.
- Legal?
What's the difference?
We're lawyers.
We deal in the business
of interpretations.
That's not why you're
here, is it, my son?
- No.
- [sighs] I have always dreaded
that this day would come.
And now you shall
have that you seek.
Nicholas, this is
your brother, Carlo.
- Hiya, little brother.
[soft piano music]
[hand patting]
Yeah.
[Carlo chuckling]
[hand patting]
Little Nicky here comes
running across the yard,
dropping his diapers.
He runs buck naked up to Papa.
Papa picks him up.
You remember how burly Papa was?
- [Manny] Yeah.
- So, he picks Nicky up, holds
him up like this, you know?
All of a sudden, Nicky lets go.
Squirts the old man
right in the face!
[men laughing]
Pissed right in his eye.
He always called you
squirt after that. [laughs]
- Carlo.
What was Papa like?
- You don't remember?
- No, I mean, I was just a kid.
- He had a big laugh.
You could hear him bellow
anywhere in the house.
But he had a temper.
Like a good Italian son,
I guarded myself
whenever I walked by him.
I never knew if he was
gonna hug me or cuff me.
He liked to hit.
Yeah, but you, you got off easy.
He mellowed a lot with you.
For the first six months
after you were born,
I don't think he
put you down once.
He was always walking
around with you in his arms.
[coughs] Course that changed
some after you peed on him.
[men laughing]
Gabrielle, sweetheart.
You're up.
Hey, come on over here, I
want you to meet somebody.
Gabrielle, Kiki, this is
my kid brother, Nicky.
- It's very nice to meet you.
- Carlo, I thought we
were gonna go out tonight.
- Hey, not tonight, babe.
Come on, it ain't every
day you hook back up
with your kid brother.
- Carlo, I'm bored, and you
said we were gonna go out.
And you said it'd be tonight.
- We ain't gonna.
So cool your jets.
- Well, Kiki and I can go out,
and you can just ask Silvio
to bring the car around.
- Yeah, who do you think
you are, her father?
- Will you tell her to shut up?
You ain't going nowhere.
- We're going out.
- No, I said, now sit down.
- Come on, Carlo.
Don't be such a hard ass.
- What's your problem?
I bring you out here, you can
do whatever you broads want.
Lay out by the pool, tan your
tits, go shopping, whatever.
All I ask is you look good
when you're hanging on my arm,
be a good screw and
show a little respect!
I said sit, you sit.
Sit!
You fuckin' want some of this,
I'll fuckin' give
you some of this!
- Carlo, take it easy, okay.
You don't have to get
so rough with her.
- Hey, hey, college boy.
You may be the big dick
in LA, but in this house,
I'm pezzonovante.
I call the shots.
- Hey, tough guy.
This is family?
- Hey, I don't want
no grief from you!
I'll tell you when I
want to hear from you.
Otherwise you stay shut!
- Well, some gangster,
terrorize an old man.
[suspenseful music]
[belt smacking]
- Yeah.
Hey, you're lucky,
you know that?
You don't have to live
with Papa's temper
when you're like me, you know?
It comes quick, like
lightning. [grunts]
Hey, come on.
I'm just letting off
a little steam here,
you know what I mean?
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, how come you're
so different than me?
I look at you, I
see Mama's face.
But your different.
- Nicholas is a
good boy, this kid.
- Hey, you hungry, baby?
- You know, Manny
promised we'd go to Vegas.
And there's a volcano
in the swimming pool.
And I just love getting it on
with clowns in circus circles.
- [laughs] You got
to just love her.
[wine splashing]
- You know, this reminds
me of the time I was
working with Jimmy the
Fin, you remember him?
What am I saying, you
was just a little dink.
So Jimmy, he had
these jealous streaks.
He, especially when he
came to his old lady, boom.
He was convinced she was
doing half the neighborhood.
So, one day he follows her.
He finds her in bed
with another guy--
- [Nick Voiceover] I
realized that Carlo was
like every bad guy I
had ever prosecuted.
And deep inside, I had
a problem with that.
Over the next few days,
he gave me an insider's
look at the criminal world,
and it was mesmerizing.
- Well, you see a lot of
guys who make their bones
probably already hit
a couple three guys
before they get made.
It's kind of like them fighter
pilots making ace, see.
They gotta be confirmed
hits or it don't count.
- How many guys you gotta
kill to make your bones?
- Well, only one, but
you don't get made
till somebody says you did it.
It was kinda like me.
I whacked maybe three,
four guys coming up.
The man who says I'd
made turns out to be,
you ready for this?
Sammy G.
- Sammy G.
- You ever heard of him?
- Wasn't he some big
time hood out of Jersey?
- No, he was more than that.
Sammy G was the son of a
bitch that whacked Papa.
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
Of course, I'm sure.
Beautiful, ain't it?
I ended up going to work
for the prick, 10 years.
- You worked for the
guy who killed Papa?
- Hey look, pal.
Sooner or later, everybody
works with everybody.
Hey Manny, Manny,
Manny. [chuckles]
So kid, tell me what was it like
having your little pink butt
pampered by this old man?
- Old?
[chuckles] I'll
dance on your grave.
- [laughs] I couldn't wait
to get out of college, right?
Then after law school, all I
wanted to do was go back in.
- Yeah.
Hey, tell me.
You stick it to a
lot of college pussy
in the back of a convertible?
- I didn't let him
have a convertible.
It's too dangerous.
And you can't get
warm in winter.
Who needs the headache?
No, for Nicholas, a sedan.
- A sedan?
Manny gave you a sedan?
- A Buick.
- Nicholas is a good boy.
He got good grades,
he earned it.
- So, he gets a car,
goes to college,
and I grow up living
on the streets.
And why is that?
I'll tell you.
See, you were a
cute little baby.
Everybody loves cute little
babies, you know what I mean?
They're like puppies.
Me, I had no where to go.
Manny wouldn't take
me in like he did you.
- You were a punk.
- Yeah, punk.
I was too old for ya.
My family gets wiped out.
Because I'm too old, you
wouldn't give me shit.
And now you're working for
me, how do you like that?
[chuckles] Yeah,
that's right, pal.
You know something?
For me, the best.
The best food, best broads,
best lawyers and Manny here.
[lips smacking]
He's the best.
Hey, kid, you play
it, right, who knows?
Maybe you come work for me too.
Never hurts to have a DA
in your pocket. [laughs]
Yeah? [laughs]
- [Nick Voiceover] But then
I would get a reality check.
Carlo had a way of doing that.
- I'm sick and tired of
being stuck in this house.
Day in, day out.
[suspenseful music]
Christ, Carlo, you don't
fucking pay attention to me.
All you do is talk to
your stupid brother.
You want everybody to
think you're such a big man
and you're nothing.
You are fucking nothing,
and you know that I know it.
- [Carlo] You're asking for it.
Now you want it?
You want some Goddamn
attention, bitch!
Well, you got it!
- No!
[belt slaps]
- Okay?
- No!
[belt slaps]
- You had enough, have ya?
You had enough?
- No!
- Carlo, what the
hell you doing?
- Stay out of it!
- Get the fuck outta here!
[shoe smacks]
[suspenseful music]
[belt thuds]
- Carlo Augustine,
what a sweetheart.
This guy's in juvenile
hall until he's 18,
and he walks with
a clean record.
28 arrests, including
numbers, drugs, racketeering,
prostitution,
assault, laundering.
You name it, this guy's done it.
Murder, and implicated on five
others with no convictions.
Why?
Because he's got a good lawyer.
Like you.
Manny Kohen.
[crickets chirping]
- So, pal, tell me.
What are you thinking
about doing in LA?
You gonna be like
a judge or what?
- I don't know.
I was thinking about going
up to the federal level.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Maybe even the Attorney
General's office.
- I bet you got a lot
of good stuff you could
use against me, huh?
- It's privileged.
I couldn't testify against
you even if I wanted to.
But I do know the federal
boys are interested in you.
- What are you talking about?
- Yeah, they're putting
together an organized
crime task force.
You made the A list.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- What do you know about it?
- Well, not too much, just
that they got a name for you.
Toy godfather.
- Toy godfather, that's cute.
- Yeah, I like that.
That's funny, you know.
It sounds like something
they put on for Christmas.
Toy godfather.
[suspenseful music]
I'm a made mafioso.
Not some cannoli movie actor.
I killed men.
I ran neighborhoods in Queens,
in Brooklyn, the Bronx!
Now, I'm building a
West Coast franchise.
And you come into my house
and call me toy godfather?
- Nicholas doesn't think
this, the government does.
- Shut up!
You, what do you know?
You work for any
carbone that comes along
with a couple of
shekels in his pocket.
- And you don't?
- Yeah, but with
me it's different.
Now you take Sammy G, the most
respected Don of his time.
And I whacked him!
- Sammy G, Sammy
G, always Sammy G!
Enough already!
- Sammy G taught me very
many valuable lessons
with his mockery.
Every day he'd laugh
at me, every day!
Coming into our house.
Our house!
Cutting down our family,
killing them all with
his filthy bullets.
Killing them all except you!
- Hey, lighten up, okay, Carlo?
Take it easy.
- Who the fuck are you?
- What are you talking
about, who am I?
Manny.
- Who are you?
Who sent you?
- Nobody sent me.
- Carlo, this is your
brother, Nicholas.
- He's my brother
'cause you say he is.
How do I know which side of
the bread you're buttering?
You, what do you know,
you work for anyone!
You wired?
- [Nick] Wired?
- You're wired!
[shirt tearing]
- You fucking happy
now, Carlo, you happy?
Am I wired, am I wired?
- You know what destiny is, huh?
We were meant to be together.
We were made to be brothers.
The DA and the player.
We shouldn't be here.
We should've been killed
like Papa and Mama.
Nobody was to survive that.
But don't you see?
We can't die.
I mean, look it up,
Book of Genesis.
And thou shalt go to
thy fathers in peace.
Thou shalt be buried
in a good old age.
[Carlo laughs]
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
- Let's go to bed, huh?
[crickets chirping]
[jukebox whirring]
[soft rock music]
[upbeat pop music]
♪ It's not the way you
conceal your smile ♪
put my love on trial ♪
♪ I spent a long time
thinking it's over ♪
♪ It's time we started
something new ♪
♪ I'm tired of all
the things you do ♪
♪ I never loved you,
I never want you ♪
♪ So why is this
getting complicated,
getting complicated ♪
♪ I always want you,
no one can give me ♪
♪ All the satisfaction
that my body needs ♪
♪ You got it, you got
one thing, one thing ♪
♪ I really need, oh yeah
♪ You got it, you got
one thing, one thing ♪
♪ I really need,
oh yeah, ah, mm ♪
♪ I see you standing
there, you look so good. ♪
- [Nick Voiceover] The
next morning I walked
into the middle of something.
- Hey, hiya, little brother!
- Hey, Carlo, what's up?
- We're gonna go for a ride.
- What kind of ride?
- Out to the desert,
unless you got other plans.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
You got something
else going or not?
- No, I got no other plans.
- Good, so go get dressed.
Hey Silvio, get him
something to wear.
We're going for a ride.
- What's wrong with
what I'm wearing?
- It's business.
[suspenseful music]
[crane humming]
[dirt thudding]
[suspenseful music]
- [Nick Voiceover]
Something was up.
Although Carlo had seemed to
rebound back to his old self,
he was in a mood.
- [Carlo] Okay, so what do
you think of the ride, Nicky?
Beautiful, ain't it?
- [Nick] Nice, Carlo.
- Nice?
It's a '65 Lincoln.
It's mint condition nearly.
There ain't many of 'em
around, I picked it up cheap.
It cost the owner an
arm and a leg. [laughs]
See, I got people working
on putting a new highway
through here, we're
ahead of the game.
I got 16,000 acres cheap.
I'm telling you, Nicky,
this is gonna be the
next Vegas or Reno.
I mean, they got
Indian bingo here.
They've legalized horse racing.
They got off track
betting, casino gambling.
Hell, even the California
State Government's
in the numbers
business with lotto.
My oldest real
estate speculation.
Palm Springs is gonna
be the next boom town.
This is the foundation
of our new business, kid.
Yours and mine.
- Carlo, I don't know anything
about the construction business.
- Hey, the construction
business is like sex.
You gotta have the right tools,
and you gotta know
how to use 'em.
And you always gotta
be the one on top.
[motor humming]
'Cause there's always somebody
who wants to fuck with ya!
Wing, Xiao, my friends!
You wanted to meet, Xiao?
What can I do for you?
- You have not delivered on
the promises you have made.
- Hey, we could have
done this over the phone.
I told you what it would take.
If you want to meet some heavy
hitters on the West Coast,
you're gonna have to put up.
But you're not
interested in judges.
You want congressional
class juice.
That's extra.
- Funding is never
a source of concern.
Results, however, are
a different matter.
- Yeah?
Show me.
- [Man] As I have indicated,
timeliness is of
great significance.
- See, this is the
construction business for you.
I need money to build my new
city, and they want my Rolodex.
And they're willing to
pay dear, you know why?
'Cause they don't see a toy
godfather standing here.
They see Carlo
Augustine, power broker.
And for that they
pay me respect.
Now, I gotta give him
an answer, what do I do?
You got any answers?
- Who's this?
- I'm sorry, this is
my brother, Nicky.
He's like what you call a toy
district attorney. [laughs]
Hey Nick, this is
a Wing, Xiao, Tien.
Now, you figure out who's who.
Hey, Nicky's a college boy.
Very smart.
He and me are gonna go into
the construction business
together, right?
- Carlo, I can't be a part
of this, you know that?
- Oh, sure you can, kid.
All you gotta learn
is how to say no.
[gunshots blasting]
[gunshot blasting]
[car door slamming]
[tires screeching]
[suspenseful music]
Hey, Nick, you okay, huh?
[Carlo laughs]
Come on, let's get outta here.
[suspenseful music]
[car doors slamming]
Okay, you'll be all
right out here, kid.
There's an LA bus coming
by in a couple of hours.
You'll be there before dark.
- Carlo, do you even
realize what you just did?
You committed murder.
- What, are you talking
nuts, councilor?
I just sent a message
to the Chinks.
Now either they're gonna
get with the program
or they're gonna come gunning.
Either way, you
gotta get outta here.
[hand patting]
It was nice seeing you again.
- I'm gonna have to
take you in, Carlo.
[fist smashing]
[Nick coughs]
- Now, don't you ever touch me?
I don't care who you are,
you don't ever touch me?
- [Gabrielle] Stop it, Jesus!
- Now, he's turning
gray. [laughs]
Hey, come on, take him to
the men's room over there.
Get him cleaned up, will ya?
Come on, make it snappy!
[hands clapping]
[Nick groans]
[suspenseful music]
- Walk!
- Can you believe
that, my own brother.
[tires screeching]
[thrilling music]
[car door thudding]
[gunshots blasting]
[cartridge clicking]
[thrilling music]
[tires skidding]
[tires screeching]
[thrilling music]
[tires rumbling]
[fist banging]
[insects chirping]
[footsteps pattering]
- Nick, I'm tired.
I don't want to go any
further, my feet hurt.
I'm just gonna sit
here and that's it!
- Give me your shoes.
- No.
I'm gonna take
the heels off 'em.
- Look, if you wanna stomp
around the desert all night,
that's fine with me,
but I'm staying here.
- Great.
All right, listen, it's
pitch black out here.
We'll probably stumble
in the cactus all night.
I don't want to do that.
Okay, we'll stay
here, that's fine.
Is that all right with you?
- That's fine with me.
- Great.
Let me just.
[rock banging]
[chain rattling]
Hey, Gab, I got, there's
some burlap bags in here.
Some boots.
Pick.
What do you think?
[object rattles]
All right, here, why
don't you put these on?
Here, put this one on,
it's freezing out here.
Here, put these on.
Give me your feet.
[fire crackling]
[hands rubbing]
- You don't like me
very much, do you?
- No, you're all right.
You know, it's just that--
- I'm just not
your type of girl.
- You don't have to put
words into my mouth.
I just don't understand
how a girl like you--
- Would be with somebody
like your brother, Carlo.
- Want to tell me about it?
- What?
- You and Carlo.
I mean, if you don't mind.
I mean, we'll be here a
while, so it's up to you.
- I don't mind.
It's like somehow your
brother just understood me.
Or at least he understood
where I was vulnerable,
and we connected in that way.
- Carlo, vulnerable?
- Yeah, he was hurt, and we
both knew that about each other.
[gentle music]
See, my father used
to beat on my mom
right till the day he died.
And that kind of
thing just, well,
it just affects you
in ways sometimes you
don't even understand.
It's like, I always pick
the one guy in the room
who's gonna make
my life miserable.
Maybe it's just that you
go with what you know.
Like my boyfriend
before, Jimmy Simpliotti.
- Jimmy Simpliotti?
- Jimmy Simple is
what they called him.
He was the collector for
the boys in Atlantic City,
which basically meant
that he dished out pain.
So, you'd pay your visit,
and depending on how
much money you owed
was about the amount
of grief that you got.
- Sounds like a real nice guy.
- Yeah.
I was an exotic dancer,
and I was working in this
club when I met Carlo.
The money was good
and you get good tips
if you sit on the
customer's laps,
you know, so they can feel you,
but I never hooked or
anything like that.
It was just, you
know, just tacky.
And Jimmy used to
hang out there.
And he took a real liking to me,
except that he was
really crazy and jealous.
And so when Carlo came in,
and he started treating
me really nice.
He started paying me
a lot of attention,
told me I was good,
and I was good.
And he told me that he
knew all these people
in show business.
And well, Jimmy got
all pissed off about it
and got in Carlo's face.
- Not a good idea, huh?
- No.
I was supposed to meet
Jimmy the next night,
and then Carlo shows up instead,
and he brought me this
heart-shaped candy box.
I never saw Jimmy again.
- That's when you started
seeing my brother?
- Yeah.
I mean, Carlo
decided that for me.
[gentle music]
Do you have a
girlfriend back in LA?
- I did.
She was a drinker, we...
We had to break up.
- So, what's it like
being a district attorney?
- It's a job, you know,
just like any other job.
I'm just attracted
to the bad guys too.
[gentle music]
- What are you looking at?
- You.
- Your brother
isn't even cold yet.
[gentle music]
[Nick sighs]
[birds warbling]
- [Nick Voiceover]
The next morning,
we followed an old service road,
hoping it would
lead to somewhere.
- Is that where Officer
Thorpe was killed?
- No, that came later.
[footsteps pattering]
[suspenseful music]
[motorcycle motor humming]
[tires screeching]
[suspenseful music]
[motor humming]
[tires skidding]
[suspenseful music]
[men chattering]
[gunshots blasting]
[suspenseful music]
Stay back.
- Let me see!
Well, what's happening?
- They want us to come out.
- So, what do you think?
What do you think?
- Considering everything,
it doesn't look good.
Come on.
[mud splashing]
[motor humming]
[suspenseful music]
[motorcycle crashing]
[rod squelching]
[motor humming]
[suspenseful music]
[tires skidding]
Gabrielle, this way!
[motor humming]
[suspenseful music]
[tires skidding]
[thrilling music]
[tires screeching]
[body thudding]
[suspenseful music]
[car door thudding]
[objects crashing]
[gunshots blasting]
[man groaning]
[thrilling music]
[motor humming]
[brake clicking]
[cement slapping]
[motor buzzing]
[machine buzzing]
[metal creaking]
[cement slapping]
[feet smashing]
[building crashing]
[suspenseful music]
Hey, you!
[man groans]
[body thuds]
[car door slams]
You okay?
- Yeah!
Oh, look out!
[body thuds]
[plank thuds]
- [Nick] Let's get
the hell out of here.
[engine revving]
[engine humming]
[tires skidding]
- I want to wrap up this
Officer Thorpe thing.
- There was something
definitely not right
about this officer's procedures.
I was just too tired
to give a damn.
[siren wailing]
[suspenseful music]
[motor humming]
[radio chattering]
Am I glad to see you.
- Let me see your
driver's license please.
- Yeah, sure.
Nick August with the
DA's office out of LA.
- Right, DA's office.
- Officer Thorpe, you're not
gonna believe this, okay?
There's two dead
bodies out there.
Yesterday somebody killed my
brother and his bodyguard.
There's a couple of Chinese guys
buried in a lot somewhere
in Palm Springs.
I'm telling you, we had a...
What the hell are you
doing, man? [groans]
- I'm just gonna see if
your story checks out.
You have the right to
remain silent, use it.
[radio chattering]
And you say that you and
the little woman here
killed a bunch of
armed ninja bandits?
- I didn't say they
were ninja bandits.
They were Triad assassins.
- Right, assassins.
And they're supposed to
be around here somewhere?
- I don't know exactly
they are, okay?
We had to get out of
there as fast as we could.
Now, what I'm thinking is
if we can get a chopper
coming from the east,
cover this ground,
we can catch up to
'em really fast.
- Right, chopper.
- Oh, for Christ sakes.
This is really starting
to piss me off.
- I'm gonna give
you a chance to run
because I don't want
it to look like you
were in custody, you
know what I mean?
[body thudding]
Somebody wants you to
disappear real bad.
Go on out there a ways.
- Officer, you're
making a big mistake.
[gunshot blasting]
[body thudding]
[gun thumps]
- So, it was Gabrielle
that shut Officer Thorpe?
- She saved my life.
- An officer was shot,
and you contacted nobody<
- I didn't have that option.
[romantic music]
- So, you went
back to Los Angeles
and went straight back
to your apartment.
- I had witnessed five murders.
I'm involved in the death of a
cop, all in a 24-hour period.
[gentle music]
I just had to think.
But whatever happened next,
I knew that I had
to take control.
[gentle music]
[cars humming]
[door creaking]
[lamp clicking]
[flashlight clicking]
- Hey, bub.
You find anything interesting?
- Yeah, you're filing
system is a mess.
- I'm very disappointed.
I thought we were buddies.
- That makes two of us.
- We're gonna have to
take you into custody
for the murder of a police
officer named Thorpe.
Nick, don't!
[suspenseful music]
[latch clicking]
[tennis ball thumping]
[tennis ball whacking]
[body thudding]
[footsteps pattering]
[garbage bin rattling]
[suspenseful music]
[racket whacking]
[body thudding]
[ball thumping]
Ah, Nick!
Not my new graphite matrix!
You're dead meat!
[ice cubs rattling]
- Hey, Manny!
- Hmm?
Nicolas, I was worried.
- We gotta get
outta here, Manny.
It was a setup.
There's a hit on
me and I'm wanted.
There's Chinese thugs
coming out of the woodwork.
I came back to
get you, let's go!
- Oh, Nicholas, Nicholas,
you're talking like your crazy.
- Crazy, man, you bet your ass!
They just killed Carlo, okay?
- Hey, kid, how ya
doin'? [chuckles]
So, tell me, you think I
could make it in Hollywood?
- Oh!
- Oh, baby, I'm
not going nowhere.
I'm immortal.
[lips smacking]
Don't you know that?
Hey, what's wrong?
Smart college boy
like you never heard
of a bulletproof vest?
- I don't get it.
- We had to do a little save
face for the Asian connections.
It's political,
don't worry about it.
Besides, I wanted to
see which side you were
buttering your bread.
- [Nick] Did you know?
- I knew, but I never approved.
- Hey, think of it as hell week
at the frat house,
college boy. [laughs]
- You son of a bitch!
[hand slaps]
You nearly got us killed!
- What, who?
- What do you mean
who, you had no idea?
- Hey, what are
you talking here?
I faked up a death
scene, that's all.
I didn't send no...
Hey, come on, give me a break.
- I just killed three
Triad assassins.
- Hey. [laughs]
My little brother
finally made his bones.
- Yeah, well Gabrielle
made her bones too.
She killed a cop.
- I can't tell you how
proud I am. [laughs]
You showed initiative.
- I'm not amused.
What about the
Chinese guys, huh?
- Eh, that was just a hit.
Just business.
Hey, Mr. Wing?
You know anything about
any Triad assassins?
Yeah.
I had to do some house
cleaning for Mr. Wing.
Now, we've got the
right people in place.
You're looking at the new
West Coast Chinese connection.
[Wing laughs]
And you're in it too, Nick.
Keep it in the family.
We're gonna do some
serious business together.
- Would you excuse us, please?
I want to talk to
Nicholas alone.
- More dirty little
secrets, Manny?
- Oh.
- Ciao, babe.
[lips smacking]
- The truth is I am an old
man with very few pleasures.
Now, that I look
back on my life,
I am not very proud
of my accomplishments,
although I am proud of you.
But this is not what
I wanted for you.
No, this is not at
all what I wanted.
For you, a judge,
maybe a senator.
Maybe even president
like Jack Kennedy, hmm?
But that is not to be.
You are involved with Carlo.
Fate is playing a cruel game.
- I've come to accept it, Manny.
Questa e mia familia.
- Nicholas, you are
not of this family!
- What do you mean?
- I raised you,
not these carbones!
You were not to be part of this!
- I saw his criminal
record, Manny.
How did he get to
become so powerful?
- Well, he's connected,
very high up.
Someone very powerful
is watching over him.
And now the Chinese
want his allegiance.
But it's you I'm worried about.
You're dug in, your
life is forever changed.
You are a gangster.
I was young once myself
and full of bright ideas.
Then I took a couple of
cases I shouldn't have.
Oh, the money was very good.
And soon, I was in.
Look, I can arrange to get
you out of the country,
but you have to act at once.
- I can take care of myself.
- Can you?
You really think so.
Then you are in, and
I can't help you.
- [Carlo] What do you want?
I guessed wrong.
No, it's family,
it's my problem.
I'll take care of it.
[footsteps pattering]
- [Nick] Carlo.
- Hey, there he is.
- What's going on?
- I gotta get outta here, today.
- What for?
- Killing that cop's
bringing too much heat on us.
Silvio's bringing
the car around.
Come on, Gabrielle, let's go.
Now!
[footsteps pattering]
- It's unseasonably chilly
today, you should dress warmly.
- I got a sweater.
- You'll need it.
Great.
[tires rumbling]
[car doors slamming]
- Yeah, this is all right.
Hey, Silvio, go get the picnic
basket out of the trunk.
I know you're packing,
Nicky, hand it over.
Come on, don't play games.
Come on.
- Carlo, he's your brother.
- Shut up.
I heard you pick up on
the phone last night.
- Let's do it.
- Start walking.
Come on, you, I want
you to see this.
- God, you're hurting me!
- Good, you cheat on me!
What, you think I didn't know?
- Let her go, Carlo.
- One shot, Nicky.
You won't even hear it.
That's how I took Sammy G out.
I shot him right
through the ears.
They had to bury him
in a closed casket,
and I laughed at his funeral.
10 years I waited to
get close to that prick!
Just like I am to you.
- Hey, Carlo, you gonna do it?
Then you go ahead and you do it.
- That a boy, Nicky.
Don't beg.
Sammy G begged and
cried like a baby.
And you know what he told me
before I blew his brains out?
He said, "Killing your
Papa was just a contract.
"You know, business."
- Is this business too, Carlo?
- No, this is self-preservation.
[suspenseful music]
[gunshot blasting]
[Gabrielle screaming]
[Gabrielle whimpering]
I could kill you,
don't you know that?
- What the hell
is going on here?
- I'm saving your
ass like I always do!
Silvio turned, cut his
own deal with Wing.
He would have
whacked you himself.
I had to get up close.
Hit men.
They could smell fear.
- You used me as a
diversion, didn't you?
- Family business, Nicky.
You're family, I
never forget it.
Now, I got one more
thing to do for Papa.
- Papa's been dead 20 years.
When are you gonna let it go?
- You want to know
the truth, Nicky?
I died in that room that day.
My whole life's been
spent avenging Papa.
I'm almost done.
But you got a life ahead of you.
Now get outta here and
take here with you.
- Carlo, you come back with me,
I'll put you in the
witness protection program.
I can help you.
- You're a good
kid, you know that?
Here, I want you to
have Papa's ring.
- I can help the both of you.
- I can't, it's destiny.
By the time you get back
to LA, it'll all be over.
- Carlo, you can't
leave me here like this.
- Hey, Gabrielle, you're the
eighth wonder of the world,
you know that, hm?
[lips smacking]
But you gotta go where your
bread's buttered right?
Now, your bread's
buttered with squirt.
- I don't want this.
- Like Manny always says,
you lie down with dogs,
you get up with fleas.
[suspenseful music]
- Carlo.
- I gotta go.
Family.
[suspenseful music]
[gun clicking]
[gunshots blasting]
[hood clanging]
[suspenseful music]
- Carlo!
[car crashing]
[door slamming]
[gunshot blasting]
[bullet squelching]
[gun clicking]
[gentle music]
[suspenseful music]
[gun clicking]
[Nick panting]
[gun thudding]
[suspenseful music]
[shoes thudding]
[Wing grunting]
[fists smashing]
[men grunting]
[knees smashing]
[suspenseful music]
[Nick grunting]
[pipe whacking]
[knife thudding]
[body thudding]
[suspenseful music]
[knife thudding]
[motor humming]
[tires screeching]
[suspenseful music]
[car crashing]
[explosion blasting]
[lighter clicking]
- You know, I gotta confide
something in you, Nick.
You're like a tar
baby of misery.
Anyone who touches you dies.
By the way.
Where's your fucking badge?
- I left it in my apartment.
You see, I didn't know who
the good guys were anymore.
- What about Wing, why
didn't you kill him?
He tried to kill you,
he killed your brother.
Why didn't you kill him?
- The apple doesn't
fall far from the tree.
I didn't have it in me then,
and I don't know
now, Mr. Winslow.
- [Winslow] You're free to go.
- Nicholas!
- Surprised to see me, Manny?
- Oh, Nicholas, you could give
an old man a heart attack.
- Yeah, if you had a heart.
- I since hostility.
- Hostility?
No.
I would say that I'm impressed,
but then I've always
been impressed with you,
haven't I, Manny?
- Impressed, that's good?
- That's good.
Just like you, Manny.
- Sit, sit, sit, we'll talk.
[chair creaking]
- It took me awhile
to piece it together.
It was a bunch of
little things, really.
Then I saw the report
the FBI had on you.
- The FBI?
- Yeah.
They've been watching you
now for over 20 years.
- [laughs] That's the
trouble with this business.
Someone is always watching you.
- You covered your
ass pretty well,
but there was one small
fact you overlooked.
- Fact, what fact?
- You were my
father's consigliere.
- Yeah, that's
true, you knew that.
- And then you went
to work for Sammy G.
- [laughs] Sammy G.
When he took over your
father's concerns,
he took me with him.
In this business,
you always go where
your bread is buttered.
- You were heavily connected.
You were watching over Carlo.
You weren't working for him.
He was working for you,
only he didn't know it.
- In my own way, I was
watching over both of you boys.
- No, and Carlo was on to you.
- On to me?
Why should Carlo be on to me?
For what?
- I remember that day,
that terrible day.
We were in the living
room when they came.
The noise was like thunder.
[gunshots blasting]
[thunder cracking]
[suspenseful music]
He brought me to you.
To you, Manny.
You were waiting
outside in the car.
You knew what was going on.
- Nicholas, you hurt me
with these accusations.
- Come on, Manny.
Carlo didn't fake his
death to see what I'd do.
He wanted to see
what you would do.
And what did you do?
You put a contract out on me.
- Oh, you, no.
I never sent the
assassins after you.
That was Silvio's doing, alone.
Later I learned that
Wing didn't trust you.
And I was outraged.
- I'm not talking
about the assassins.
It was the state trooper.
You don't buy the state police
unless you got a lotta juice.
And you got a
lotta juice, Manny.
And then when I came back,
you knew he had to
get rid of both of us.
- No.
Nicholas, I love you.
Don't be ridiculous.
- The day Carlo died, he
knew I was carrying a gun.
You told him.
You set it up so we'd
both shoot it out.
[fist slams]
[Manny sighs]
- So many years, the guilt.
I am not a perfect person.
This is the hard part.
Armand Augustine
is not your father.
[crickets chirping]
You are my son.
Nicolas, I love you.
Armand Augustine
was a brutal man.
And he had no vision.
I made him great!
But all he saw was a fixer,
someone to do legal work.
Then your mother
and I fell in love.
It was not supposed to happen
that way, but things happen.
She couldn't leave her husband.
He would have killed us both.
Then he found out about us.
And then you.
He gave Sammy G the hit on
me and I turned the tables.
Sammy was no Armand, but
I made him something.
Then Carlo killed him.
Carlo could have
been even greater,
but all he ever
wanted was revenge.
All that anger he
walked around with.
And now there's you.
- And now you have to get
rid of me, don't you, Manny?
- May God strike me dead.
- Yeah, well you should have
when you had the chance.
The Feds picked me
up the other day.
They told me that
the hit's out on you.
The Triads have you
marked for death.
You're caught in the middle.
- Goddamn!
Even in death, Carlo
has me by the balls!
His hotheaded plan
started all of this.
[crickets chirping]
Can you help me out of this?
- No.
- You reap what you sow.
Well, at least try
to save yourself, eh.
- Don't worry about me, Manny.
I'll be okay.
- You know, ironically,
I'm very proud of you.
Goodbye, my son.
- Goodbye, Manny.
[birds chirping]
[Manny sighs]
[glasses clink]
[suspenseful music]
[knife whooshing]
[knife squelching]
[glass shattering]
[liquor splashing]
[soft piano music]
[tires rumbling]
[door thudding]
- [Nick Voiceover] Why was I
under investigation, Anson?
- [Anson] What makes
you think that?
You know, they happened
to find your name
buried inside another
investigation?
You had us worried.
And were trying to find out...
- [Nick Voiceover] Which side
I was buttering my bread.
- [Anson] No, son
of the godfather.
I mean, this does not look good
on the resume of a
district attorney.
They found Kohen's
body on Tuesday.
He'd been dead about 30 hours.
Chinese didn't waste any time.
[ring thuds]
So, what are you gonna do, bub?
- [Nick Voiceover]
Get on with my life.
- [Anson] Where will you go?
- [Nick Voiceover] I was
thinking about working
for organized crimes.
- [Anson] Why
should they take ya?
- [Nick Voiceover]
Because I know something
about the criminal mind.
Now, when I look in the mirror,
I don't see myself
like I used to.
I see Carlo and
Manny and Gabrielle.
But at least now I
know where I came from
and where I'm going.
And who I am.
There's always gonna be
a part of me that will
ask the question, if Carlo
and I had changed places,
how would I have turned out?
[engine revving]
Cain and Abel,
they were brothers.
One became a killer.
It could have gone either way.
[soft piano music]
[tense piano music]