(film projector running)
(ominous music)
(sinister voice laughs)
(thunder rumbles)
(somber rock music)
♪ I got nothing ♪
♪ But pain ♪
♪ From my bones ♪
♪ To my brain ♪
♪ I look at the sky ♪
♪ Wondering why each break ♪
- Jonathan Jones?
- Yeah.
- Are you ready?
♪ But woe ♪
♪ From my head ♪
- Mm-hm, here we go, okay.
Jonathan Jones.
You haven't done much, but
Rachel thinks you're hot shit.
- (chuckles) Rachel thinks
every cute guy in a suit
is hot shit.
- That's true.
(chuckles)
So where you from originally?
- [Jonathan] Oh, I'm from Kentucky.
- Kentucky, nice.
So do you have any questions
about the role, Jonathan?
- No, no, I, no.
- Okay, it's been a long
morning, let's do this.
(thunder rumbles)
- Jonathan, can you give me a slate?
- Oh, sure.
Yeah. (clears throat)
Hi, I'm Jonathan Jones with
the Rachel Green Talent Agency,
and I'm reading for the role of Max.
Thank you.
(clears throat)
- And are you ready?
- Just let me just take
a second to just...
Uh, get out, me.
Oh, I got it.
Yeah.
- Action, when did you get out, Max?
- I...
(foreboding music)
I graduated last week.
- Mm-hm.
What took you so long to come and see me?
- Well, I...
I, I've been looking for Lucy.
- Looking for Lucy, I told you that skirt
was trouble from day one.
I hope she was worth
five years on the Rock.
- Well, uh...
Maybe I should ask you, Stan.
- Why me?
- Why you?
I'll tell you why you.
You, uh...
You set me up on that
payroll heist, payroll heist.
And you kept the score to yourselves.
- Who put that crazy idea in your head?
- [Jonathan] The Creeper.
He told me just before I deposited
three slugs in his chest.
- (clears throat) Now don't
go getting twisted, Max.
You got it all wrong, I had nothing to do
with you going over.
- Oh yeah?
Well that's not what Lucy told me.
Yeah, before I deposited her
body in San Francisco Bay.
- You won't shoot, Max.
The boys downstairs will burn you down.
- I don't care.
(mimics gun firing)
- Put your gun away.
So, Jonathan, what did you do
before you had the big
brainstorm to become an actor?
- I worked at Costco.
- (scoffs) Costco?
Wow, another one.
- Costco, shit.
Well, I got some free advice for you.
I want you to get on a bus
and hurry back to Tennessee, Johnny boy.
- I, I'm from Kentucky.
Look, just, just let me do it again, okay?
I can do a much better job.
- No, you already wasted enough of my day.
- I don't understand.
- Johnny--
- [Jonathan] I mean,
Rachel said I was great.
(chuckles)
- I bet she did.
- Johnny, here's the deal, buddy.
Max, this guy you was reading.
He is a man's man.
(grunts) Marlon Brando, man's man.
And Johnny boy, you just ain't.
(foreboding music)
You blew it the moment
you walked in the door.
You should've looked me in
the eye, struck fear into me.
But instead you looked to the floor,
you avoided eye contact.
You didn't even comment on Missy's ass.
She got a great ass.
Send in the next victim, Johnny boy.
- Okay.
- Hey.
I like your tie, keep the tie.
- Thank you.
Nice glasses and shoes.
- Close the door.
(sighs)
Who's next?
♪ Don't know what I'm ♪
doing, but I do it anyway ♪
♪ I want to feel alive ♪
- They want you.
♪ Don't know where I'm going ♪
til I'm going down the drain ♪
♪ Hope I don't burn ♪
out before I'm bright ♪
(thunder rumbles)
(gentle jazz music)
♪ Hope I don't burn ♪
out before I'm bright ♪
(patrons cheer)
This one goes out to J.J.
(sultry jazz music)
♪ Something coming out in the dark ♪
♪ I can't get too far ♪
♪ Trying to step into the light ♪
♪ I keep on falling apart ♪
♪ But if you told me how to walk ♪
♪ I wouldn't find my feet ♪
♪ If you told me how to talk ♪
♪ I wouldn't feel my teeth ♪
♪ Been a river tune ♪
down to run for a ways ♪
- [Missy] Costco?
Wow, another one.
- [Alex] Well I got some
free advice for you.
I want you to get on a bus
and hurry back to Tennessee, Johnny boy.
(grunts) Marlon Brando, man's man.
♪ There's something ♪
coming out in the dark ♪
♪ I can't get away ♪
- Hey kid, snap out of it.
J.J., don't be so hard on yourself.
Jonathan.
Don't let that bastard
play you for a sucker.
Do you really want the role?
(foreboding music)
Then you need to become Max.
Get it?
You need to be Max.
Be Max.
Now call your agent and get a callback.
Make them an offer they can't refuse.
- Yeah, an offer they can't refuse.
(chuckles)
- Hello?
- Hey, Rachel.
- [Rachel] Who's this?
- Yeah, it's me.
- J J?
- J J.
- [Rachel] You sound different.
- Hey look.
- What?
- Hey, I'm gonna need you to get me
a callback tonight, doll face.
- [Rachel] Mm, how about tomorrow morning?
- No, no, tonight.
- Tonight?
- You got it?
- [Rachel] Yeah, okay, I'll try my best.
- Good.
Yeah, that's real good.
(chuckles)
Oh, that's real good.
- That a boy, Max.
Make me proud.
♪ Standing by in shame for far too long ♪
♪ Hiding out in solitude, ♪
saying what's wrong ♪
♪ When I opened the ♪
door to let myself out ♪
♪ I'd stay back and fall to the floor ♪
(sultry jazz music)
♪ There's something ♪
coming out of the dark ♪
♪ I can't get too far ♪
♪ Something coming out of the dark ♪
(thunder rumbles)
(dramatic jazz music)
- Are you ready?
- Always.
(Missy moans)
- Missy, I need a favor.
Christ, I figured you'd be halfway back
to Chickenshit Falls,
Arkansas by now, Johnny boy.
- Oh no, no, no.
It's Kentucky.
- Whatever.
Sweet cheeks, do me a favor.
Take that fine behind of
yours down to the liquor store
and grab me another bottle.
- Sure thing.
- Go, go, go.
Mm, nice, nice.
All right, so Rachel tells me
she won't send me any more talent
til we have this callback, so
let's get started, all right?
Are you ready?
And action.
(tense jazz music)
When'd you get out, Max?
- I graduated last week, Stan.
- What took you so long to come see me?
- Well, I, I've been looking for Lucy.
- I told you that skirt
was trouble from day one.
Hope she was worth five
years in the joint.
- Maybe I should ask you, Stan.
- Why me?
- Cause it was you two that
set me up on the payroll heist,
and you kept the score to yourselves.
- Now how did you get that
crazy idea in your head?
- Creeper, yeah.
He told me just before I deposited
three slugs in his chest.
- Now don't get it all twisted,
Max, you got this all wrong!
I had nothing to do with you going over.
- That's not what Lucy told me
before I dumped her body
in the San Francisco Bay.
- You won't shoot, Max.
My boys downstairs will burn you down.
(chuckles)
- I don't care, Stan.
- That was great fucking acting!
(gun fires)
- Shit, you shot me!
You shot me.
- You know what, Stan?
(suspenseful music)
I don't like playing the sap.
- No, no.
No, are you crazy?
(gun fires)
Say goodnight.
Sweet dreams, Stan.
(thunder rumbles)
(ominous jazz music)
- Hey, Johnny boy.
How did the audition go?
- Great.
I killed it.
(door closes)
(Missy screams)
(bell tolls)
(sinister voice laughs)
- So how are things at Fillmore Casting?
- You mean Missy Fillmore Casting.
(sighs) With the insurance
money for my late hubby,
I am going to become the
biggest casting agency in town.
How do you think I feel?
(sighs) Like a million bucks.
- Wonderful.
So what about that guy
you wanna set me up with?
- Oh.
You are going to enjoy him, Priscilla.
- You think so?
- I know so.
- Are you speaking from
personal experience?
- No, but I know what you like.
- He's, he's intense.
But under the surface,
he's bursting with fear.
- I love fear.
Fear is oh so sweet.
- Priscilla.
With my offering, am I
gonna gain passage now?
- Praying Mantis requires much
more than your gift, Missy.
(ominous music)
- I am ready, mind, body and soul.
- Are you?
Because once you cross
over, there's no going back.
Praying Mantis, it changes you.
- I understand.
- We'll talk about it
after I've seen your gift.
- You promise?
- Yes, I promise.
(line beeps)
Oh, hold on, dear.
It's him.
Hello?
- Is this Priscilla?
- Hi, you must be J J.
- Yeah.
- Oh, wonderful.
I've heard a lot about you.
- Well, I wish I knew
who told you about me.
- It's a secret, do you like secrets?
- Sometimes.
Are we still on for tonight?
- Of course.
I was thinking of a
Carpaccio Surprise for dinner
after our session.
- Oh, sounds good.
What's the surprise?
- There's no surprise in the telling.
I'll text you my address.
8 P M and don't be late.
I punish men who are tardy.
- I need to be punished.
I've been a very bad boy.
- (chuckles) Wonderful, see you tonight.
Ciao.
Missy?
- Was it him?
- Yes, we're having dinner tonight.
(sighs)
- Oh.
I just wish I could be there.
- Patience is always rewarded, my dear.
- Priscilla.
Tell me about your first time again.
- [Priscilla] I'll tell
you all the juicy details
in the morning.
(sultry western music)
♪ That lonesome little highway ♪
♪ When I'm driving down the road ♪
♪ I see the devil with his long red hand ♪
♪ He's looking for something to hold ♪
♪ Sometimes when I'm feeling lonesome ♪
♪ I just open up the door ♪
♪ And grab the devil ♪
by his long red hand ♪
♪ Put the old pedal to the floor ♪
(thunder rumbles)
♪ Close your eyes now, ♪
when the morning rolls ♪
♪ I'll be traveling home ♪
♪ Lonesome road ♪
- It's open.
(thunder rumbles)
(foreboding music)
Are you hungry?
I am.
(door closes)
Let's get a drink first.
Allow me.
Tonight is your night.
(ominous music)
So J J, how did your audition go?
- Great, I killed it.
- My world is not so easily rocked, J J.
- Oh, I've never disappointed a lady yet.
- I'm no ordinary lady.
- Yeah.
Mm, I can see that.
- Cheers, my love.
(thunder rumbles)
- Mm, yeah, that's good.
Yeah.
(groans)
(ominous music)
Oh man.
Fuck.
- My desires may be a bit more unusual
than you're used to.
- [Jonathan] Fuck.
(grunts)
- Let's go in my bedroom.
I'm hungry.
(dramatic music)
(moans in pleasure)
Oh yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
(thunder rumbles)
You're going to taste so good.
(groans)
(suspenseful music)
(snarls)
(moans)
- Hey Priscilla.
How was your date with J J last night?
- Delicious, I ate him up.
(ominous music)
- Well, I have the perfect offering.
(sinister voice laughs)
(foreboding music)
(static buzzes)
(sinister voice whispers)
(grunting)
(woman yelps)
(ominous chanting)
- [Sinister Voice]
Bring their souls to me.
(woman screams)
- [Carlos] The lord is my shepherd.
I lack nothing.
He makes me lie down in green pastures.
He leads me beside quiet waters.
He refreshes my soul.
He guides me along the right
paths for his name's sake.
(sinister voice growls)
(unsettling music)
(grunts)
(eerie music)
- [Announcer] Tonight's
Halloween Thriller,
"Thursday the 12th in 3D".
- Hold still, Donald.
Why can't you get a better wig?
- It's not a wig.
- I like your whip.
I'm Priscilla.
- Yes you are.
- Another glass of red, Count?
- Certainly.
- Give me a call in a few hours
and we'll see what you
can do with that whip.
- Well let's get cracking.
- People say poor Melania.
I strong, Donald, I very strong.
- Wrong, yes, dear.
(moans)
- Leaving so soon, darling?
- This party sucks.
I'm leaving.
- Such a nasty woman.
- Mm-hm.
(ominous choral music)
(gasps)
(groans in distress)
(tense music)
- [Carlos] Even though I walk
through the darkest valley,
I will fear no evil.
For you are with me.
And I will dwell in the
house of the Lord forever.
(suspenseful music)
- The body of Priscilla
Mantis was discovered
in this alleyway in the
early hours this morning.
Ms. Mantis' death has
been strongly alleged
by detectives to not be
connected to the L A Strangler.
The L A Strangler, who has
been murdering and raping women
for the last 20 years every Halloween
in spite of the biggest manhunt in L A,
has not been caught.
Here with us today, Ms. Fillmore,
to talk a little bit about her friend.
What can you tell us about Ms. Mantis?
- Oh my god, um...
Who could do such a horrible thing?
I mean, Priscilla was the sweetest,
most wonderful woman I've ever known.
And she wouldn't hurt a fly.
What is the world coming to?
- [Jennifer] I'm very sorry for your loss.
This is Jennifer Fox reporting live.
Back to you, Bob.
- [Bob] Well, it's a wet one.
Looks like nothing but rain
in the forecast, Angelinos.
Sure enough to dry up soon.
(sinister voice laughs)
(bell tolls)
(somber organ music)
- Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
- [Priest] What is the
nature of your sin, my son?
- I would walk home from school
and find my mother in my bed.
Always a different man.
Sometimes they would beat me with belts.
It hurt at first.
But with time, feel good.
As I grow up, I discovered my power.
With my hands, I could control.
Mm-hm.
Cleanse the earth of the
vermin and the filth.
Si.
Si, Padre.
Finish the work of a great man.
Finish his work.
And together, we write our legacy.
If only this day would last forever.
(bell tolls)
(ominous organ music)
- [Priest] Patience, my son,
for we always have next Halloween.
(laughs)
- Si, Father.
(speaking foreign language)
(sinister voice laughs)
(foreboding music)
- [Newscaster] With
insufficient information
to confirm it is the same virus.
But after a month, only
a few dozen Americans
have tested positive for the ailment
that has caused great concern
at the CDC in Atlanta.
We now go to Carrie Weems
at Mercy General Hospital
with the latest news.
- [Carrie] Yes, this is
Carrie Weems reporting live.
In the last 48 hours another dozen people,
mostly vagrants from the downtown area,
have arrived by ambulance.
From what I can see, a number
of them have bloody wounds
that resemble bite wounds.
Whether these wounds were
inflicted by animals or humans
has not been confirmed by any
of the medical staff here.
I did manage to grab a nearby
E R doctor to get the latest.
- [Doctor] I've never encountered anything
quite like this in 20 years.
Within an hour anyone
bitten has become deranged
and almost uncontrollable.
(moans)
- [Brandy] Hey.
- Hey, momma, hey.
- Hey, pappy.
- I wanna get my party on.
- Ah, love to party.
- What you think?
- What you got?
What else you got,
that's not gonna cut it.
Give me more.
- Come on, Daddy's hurting.
- Come on, give me more.
Oh yeah, wanna help you.
I wanna help you, but give me more, okay?
Yo.
- Come here.
Give me some.
- Yeah, really, is that
how you wanna play?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Whoa, oh, oh, oh.
Come here, yeah?
(electricity crackles)
(tense music)
- Carlos Ochoa?
(Carlos shouts in pain)
(grunts)
(foreboding music)
(electricity crackles)
(grunts)
- What is this?
What are you doing to me?
Help!
(grunts) Help!
Help me!
- No need to yell.
- I don't understand this.
What is this shit?
Where am I?
- Save it.
No one can hear you.
You're the Carlos Ochoa
who killed that prostitute
three months ago.
- [Carlos] I had nothing to do with that.
- You really did a number
on that poor woman.
- I had nothing to do with that, Jack.
(device beeps)
- Yeah?
What happened to those two prostitutes
you killed in Sacramento a year ago?
- I had nothing to do with that.
(device beeps)
- No?
Police arrested you for the killings.
- But they let me go.
Lack of evidence, my friend.
- So you're telling me you
didn't kill them either.
- That's right, I did not kill them.
I never kill anyone.
(device beeps)
So now
you are going to untie me.
Huh, come on.
Come on!
- You know what this is?
It's a voice stress analyzer.
(hisses)
Kind of like a lie detector.
That beep means you just lied to me.
- But this, this is not admissible
in the court, senor.
- Oh, they are in my court.
- This is bullshit, man.
Bullshit!
Now you untie me, huh?
This is kidnapping.
- It's worse than that, Carlos.
Much worse.
- Okay.
Okay.
- I'm sorry it's come to this.
But you have to understand,
I have no choice.
I made a vow to her,
and I mean to keep it.
- A vow?
To who?
- My wife!
- I never meet your wife!
- You're about to.
(foreboding music)
(rattling)
- What is this noise?
- Ever been married before, Carlos?
When you get married, you
make your vows to each other.
These days most people
make light of those vows.
Beth and I meant ours.
We really meant them.
- Cut me loose, bastard.
Cut me loose, cut me loose.
- To have and to hold,
from this day forward.
For better, for worse.
For richer, for poorer.
In sickness and in health.
Until death do us part.
In sickness, Carlos.
(Beth groans)
She got the Omega Retrovirus
while we were in Asia
a couple months ago.
It should've been me, not her.
You do know what the Omega
Retrovirus is, don't you, Carlos?
It's been in the news.
Some people call it the Z-Virus.
The Zombie Virus.
- Shit, man.
Are you crazy?
Cut me loose.
I will scream.
(screams) Hey, hey, help me!
- This room is soundproof, Carlos.
Scream all you want.
Just like your victims did.
(Carlos yelps)
(Beth growls)
- Okay.
You want me, I killed them.
I killed them all, okay?
Please, please.
(growls)
- They say they're working on a cure.
I pray every night they come up with one.
(screams in pain)
God forgive me.
(sinister voice laughs)
(whimsical piano music)
Such a sweet old couple.
It's a shame they can't
keep their room rented.
Hm.
♪ Watch me walk away ♪
♪ Putting myself on display ♪
♪ One, two, three a day ♪
♪ I'm on my way, on my way ♪
- Hey Cat, it's me, Cindy.
I found a room for you to rent.
It's, it's cute.
(foreboding music)
Okay, I'll take a picture
and I'll text it to you.
See you tomorrow, bye.
- When's that gal coming
by to look at the room?
- Said she'd be here at nine o'clock.
- And you told her it's a shared home?
- I did.
Told her our son works
away most of the time
and is here maybe once a month.
- That's good, dear.
- She said that sounded perfect to her
and the rent was more than fair.
- I hope she likes it.
I'm gonna go clean up the room for her.
(sultry music)
♪ I know who you can love ♪
♪ With my calculations ♪
♪ Your true loves awaits in all ♪
♪ You are and what you do ♪
♪ All this world is built for you and me ♪
♪ What an amazing match we could be ♪
♪ I'll show you a side of your dreams ♪
♪ It's so real ♪
♪ You know you love it, ♪
living life on the screen ♪
(foreboding music)
- Sorry, I had some hard night.
- No need to explain, dear.
I use it myself for my lower back.
- Cool.
- I'm Irene Kohn.
- Very nice to meet you, Irene.
I'm Catharine.
My friends call me Cat.
(Irene chuckles)
And you must be Jacob.
- Right, we spoke on the phone.
- [Cat] Yes, we did.
- Well, would you like to
come inside and see the room?
It's getting a little chilly out here.
- Absolutely, let's do it.
- Do you want some hot tea or cocoa?
(Cat chuckles)
- She makes the best cocoa.
- Um...
- Jacob's been drinking
it for fifty years,
it ain't killed him yet.
(Cat giggles)
- That's good.
Well, yes, why not?
I caught a chill outside.
- I'll get something warm to drink.
- Have a seat, Cat.
- [Cat] Thank you.
- So where'd you see our ad for the room?
I forgot to ask.
- Actually, a friend of mine
saw the ad out in your yard
and texted me your number.
- Ah, see, I told you those
internet ads didn't do any good!
- Yes, dear.
(ominous music)
- [Cat] That's a lovely picture.
- Thank you.
Be careful, it's hot.
- Is that your son in the picture?
- [Irene] Our pride and joy.
- He's very handsome.
- Yeah.
I don't know where he got his
looks, sure wasn't from me.
(giggles)
- How old is the picture?
- Oh, a couple of years old.
Well, you ready to go look at the room?
- Oh, yes.
Sorry if I talked too much.
You guys just make me feel so at home.
- Right this way, Cat.
- How long have you been painting?
- Oh, neither of us can paint.
Our son's been working on a self portrait.
Been working on it for a while.
Not finished yet.
- (chuckles) That's cool.
I love to paint myself.
- Right this way.
(singer screams aggressively)
(heavy metal music)
- So what do you think?
Utilities are included
like I said on the phone.
Fully furnished.
Son's room's just down the hall,
but like I said on the
phone, he's seldom here.
- Very cozy.
- I cleaned and swept it for you earlier.
(phone rings)
Please excuse me.
Hello?
- [Matthew] Mother, I've come home.
I'm hungry.
- Oh dear.
(foreboding music)
(dog barks)
(Matthew snarls)
- Do you have an application
for me to fill out?
- Oh, not as such.
Just write down your last address.
Name of the person you last stayed with.
What, Irene?
- It's just--
- What?
- Our son just called.
He's around the corner.
- Uh, I see.
Catharine, I, we--
- [Cat] Oh, no problem.
It'll be nice to meet him, I'm sure.
(doorbell rings)
- [Irene] It's him, he's here.
- I'll answer it.
(foreboding music)
(Matthew growls)
(screams)
(suspenseful music)
- Matthew, stop!
(claws rip)
- [Jacob] Cut it out, son!
You do this to us every month!
- [Irene] Oh dear.
(Matthew howls)
(whimsical piano music)
(hammer taps)
- Oh, I thought they'd
have it rented by now.
- [Matthew] Ma, what's for breakfast?
I'm hungry again!
(bell tolls)
(sinister voice laughs)
(helicopter blades whir)
(paramedics chatter)
(emergency sirens wail)
- What's all this?
Somebody die?
- Mr. Torrecelli.
He was an artist who
lived on the third floor.
- Yeah, what happened?
- Well the manager says it was suicide.
Somebody else, they said
he might have been killed.
- Killed?
- Killed.
- Whoa.
Well, boys, let's go play some poker, huh?
- You still owe me from last time.
- Hey man, I'm good for it.
Hey Kenny, can you lend me 50 bucks?
- Jake, you owe me a hundred.
- I'm good for it, man.
- Hey man, can you just
lend 100 bucks for tonight?
(chuckles)
- Nah.
(phone rings)
- [Irene] You've reached Irene
and Jacob, leave a message.
- Ma, I'm sorry I killed her.
I promise it won't happen
again next month, okay?
(foreboding music)
(ominous music)
Old bastard wasn't half bad.
(melancholy music)
(cat meows)
Midnight?
Midnight.
Aw, Midnight.
(cat yowls)
It's okay.
Gonna be okay.
(shushes)
(knocking)
- What took you so long?
- [Matthew] Huh?
- I've been knocking on the
door for like three minutes,
what's going on?
- See for yourself, but you're
not going to believe it.
He's back.
- Midnight?
How?
- I don't know, I heard him
at the door a few minutes ago.
- Yeah, but you lost him in
Big Bear four months ago.
- I know, I thought a
mountain lion grabbed him.
- There is no way Midnight
made it all the way back here
all by himself.
- But he did, he's right there.
- Are you sure it's Midnight?
- Yeah.
He has the same collar.
It says Midnight.
(foreboding music)
- Hey buddy.
Crazy.
- Tell me about it.
It's weird because I was
camped out on the sofa
doing a sketch of him, and
then I heard him at the door.
- Where did this come from?
- It belonged to Mr. Torrecelli.
The manager cleaned out his apartment.
That's real leather.
- Damn, did you see this stuff?
That creep was creepier than I thought.
Oh.
By the way, found out
how Mr. Torrecelli died.
Neck was snapped like a toothpick.
- So?
- So this sketch
looks just like Mr. Torrecelli.
And then you draw your cat
in the same sketchbook,
and voila, Midnight
appears at your front door.
Here.
Draw this.
- What?
- Just draw it, a whole stack of them.
- Kenny, you can't be serious.
- Humor me, bro.
- Fine.
I'll humor you.
(tense music)
Now what?
- We wait for the money to roll in.
(chuckles)
- Oh my god,
you are the most
superstitious person I know.
There's nothing in that
one but old magazines.
- Yeah, well maybe there's
some Playboys in here.
- Playboys?
Did you just get defrosted with Dr. Evil?
- Some of us like big boobs, Matthew.
- What the hell?
- [Kenny] I thought you
said you checked the box.
- I thought I di.
- Well maybe you did.
- [Matthew] It's a coincidence.
- Look, what are the odds
that you in that sketchbook
draw your cat, and then your
cat mysteriously appears
after being missing for
four months in Big Bear?
And then I ask you to
draw a big stack of cash,
and hello, we get a big stack of cash.
You know what?
I blame myself.
I should've had you draw like
a big diamond or a pearl.
- [Matthew] Or a giant penis.
- No, I'm good there.
Well, what are you waiting for?
A nice, big, fat, juicy diamond.
- I have only one page left.
- So what?
Once we sell that diamond,
you'll be able to buy
a gazillion sketchbooks
just like that one.
Ha!
You said you thought it was a coincidence.
So what are you gonna
do with that last page?
- I don't know.
- All right.
Later, bro.
(door opens)
("Moonlight Sonata" by Beethoven)
- Hi.
Can I see?
- Um, sure.
Can you keep still, please?
Thanks.
- Matthew, let's get out of here tonight.
Go to a club.
Monica found a great one in Hollywood.
- You know I don't like clubs, Rosie.
Besides, I'm in a groove right now.
I don't want to stop.
- Well I do.
I need a break.
I need some fun.
- [Matthew] Could you stop moving?
- I'm going out.
- Hey.
Hey.
(solemn music)
Rosie.
- I'll have Monica get
the rest of my stuff.
- Rosie.
Please, wait.
Who the hell is Shane?
Please, I'll do whatever you want.
Just don't go.
- Let go!
(tense music)
- Rosie!
Rosie, Rosie!
(phone rings)
Hey.
- It's me.
I got a better idea for the last sketch.
A mountain of gold!
- Too late, Kenny.
- [Kenny] What?
What did you draw?
- You know, even after six months,
I can still draw her from memory.
(somber music)
- [Kenny] Shit.
Rosie?
You drew Rosie?
- [Matthew] Yeah.
- [Kenny] Why?
The woman stomped all
over your heart, man.
Rosie going off with that biker dude
was the best thing that
ever happened to you.
- I loved her, Kenny.
I still think about her every night.
- [Kenny] Oh no.
Wait--
- I mean, it's not as if I
expect her to show up my front--
(knocking)
(cat mews)
(ominous music)
Who the hell could be at my
door at one in the morning?
(cat meows)
- [Kenny] Don't open the
door, Matt, you hear me?
Don't open it!
- Why?
- [Kenny] Just don't, Matt.
I should've told you, but I didn't think
it would do you any good.
- What are you talking about?
- [Kenny] Rosie died, Matt.
She went off a cliff into the ocean
with that crazy biker
a couple of months ago!
They never found them.
- What?
(knocking)
- [Kenny] Don't open the door, Matt.
Hang tight, I'm on my way.
(ominous music)
(knocking)
(suspenseful music)
- Rosie?
- No!
Why'd you have to draw Rosie, Matt?
Why?
(ominous music)
(emergency siren wails)
- Want a drink?
- No, thanks, bro.
(bell tolls)
(sinister voice laughs)
(knocking)
(melancholy rock music)
- Coming in!
Come on, get the fuck up.
Rent time.
Got the money?
- Yeah, yeah.
How much do I owe you, man?
- Twenty-five hundred.
I ain't taking no fucking
checks from you, homie.
The last three fucking
checks bounced, ese!
Twenty-Five hundred cash.
Or you and your shit can get
the fuck out on the street.
You got me?
Don't fuck with me, Jake!
Do you get me?
- Yeah, I got you.
- You fucking better, homes.
Damn junkie.
Thanks.
You kids get the fuck off my truck.
(kids chatter)
♪ Pain, hurt and sorrow ♪
♪ It's all I got ♪
- [Announcer] And it's Fallen
Angel clinging to the lead
by a half a length.
(announcer chatters excitedly)
It's Crimson Satan by a
length, a length and a half.
J.J.'s Pistol in second place,
and Fallen Angel a beaten third.
(train wheels squeal)
(upbeat rock music)
- Well, well well.
If it isn't Jacob the deadbeat.
- Hey guys.
- Where's that money, Jakey boy?
- Listen, I'll get it
for you this weekend.
- You hear something, Tiny?
- Yeah.
A broken record.
(grunts)
(groans in pain)
- Next time, we're gonna
take a piece of flesh.
Five grand tomorrow, you got that?
- You pay, we win.
You don't pay, you lose.
Look at me.
You understand?
- Yeah.
- He asked you a question.
- Yeah, I understand.
- Good.
♪ It's me that's going further back ♪
♪ I'm standing in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ Day washes over all and passes me ♪
♪ I'm pushing hard against ♪
the tides of time ♪
♪ So I can see you as forever ♪
(Ruby moans in pleasure)
(upbeat pop music)
(giggles)
- [DJ] Now some smooth ride for you.
Next up, Chubby Swagger's
"Til the Popo Come".
("Til the Popo Come" by Chubby Swagger)
- Damn.
There's nothing better
than a great fuck on coke.
(chuckles)
- Well you're welcome.
- Yes, you do have other uses
besides pool cleaning, Jake.
(chuckles)
- I'm kind of in a jam.
Was wondering if I could get a loan.
- What happened to the five
K I loaned you two weeks ago?
Shit.
You degenerate ass.
You lost it at the track, didn't you?
- Someone gave me a sure thing.
- [Ruby] Uh-huh.
- Hey, listen.
Listen.
These guys are gonna rip me a new one
if I don't come up with their money.
- Not my problem, Jake.
- [DJ] The smash hit, "Run".
(upbeat rock music)
- (gasps) they're playing my song!
♪ Listen to me, baby, cause ♪
you're making me crazy ♪
♪ Got to find your feet, ♪
start moving to the beat ♪
♪ And run ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ Do it, do it, get up and run ♪
- It's just five K, Ruby.
- I wouldn't give you
five cents, lover boy.
♪ Oh my God, you're so damn fine ♪
♪ You got to get to me, so run ♪
♪ I want to feel your heat ♪
pouring down like rain ♪
♪ I want to feel your sweat ♪
♪ Faster, baby ♪
- Ruby.
♪ To the beat of the drum ♪
- Hey Ruby.
You think your husband would like to know
how you tip the hired help?
- What?
You try that and I will scream rape
so loud your parole officer will hear me.
Who do you think they're gonna believe?
Me or a two-time loser like you?
Take your shit and get out.
This is over.
♪ Shake it, shake it, move it, move it ♪
♪ Do it, do it, get up and run ♪
♪ Hit it, hit it, make us miss it ♪
♪ Give it, give it to me and run ♪
♪ Do, do, do, do be do ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Go, go, go, go ♪
♪ What you going to do ♪
♪ You going to get over here or what ♪
♪ Don't think about it, just run ♪
♪ Now listen to me, baby, ♪
cause you're making me crazy ♪
♪ Get up on your feet ♪
- You're still here?
(ominous music)
- Ruby.
I need that money.
Please.
- Well life's a bitch, sugar.
Now get out.
Now!
- Yeah, life's a bitch, sugar.
(hair dryer whirs)
(Ruby screams)
(electricity zaps)
(Ruby moans)
(tense music)
(gasps)
(thunder rumbles)
(singing in foreign language)
(serene classical music)
- Well give her a pull if you like.
I must warn you, though.
- Hey, you give loans on rings?
- It depends on the ring.
(thunder cracks)
Where did you acquire this?
(foreboding music)
- My father.
He was the equipment manager
and everybody loved him,
so they gave him a ring too.
I want five thousand.
- What happened to your father?
(electricity crackles)
(ruby moans)
- He died.
- Of what?
- Heart attack.
- [Demond] Do you wanna
sell it or pawn it?
- I told you, man, I want a loan.
- (chuckles) Well people
in Hell want ice water.
- Look, man, you gonna
give me a loan or not?
- You're a gambling man, Jake.
How about I offer you 100
thousand for one pull of the arm?
You get the gold token, you get the cash.
I'll even throw in the machine.
- What, a hundred thousand?
Okay, what if I lose?
- I get your soul.
(chuckles)
- What is this, a joke, huh?
- No, I never joke.
No, 100 thousand would solve
all your money problems, Jake.
- So are you like the devil?
- I go by many names,
many of which you could
not even pronounce.
Do we have a deal?
- Let me see the hundred thousand.
(snaps)
(sinister voices whisper)
Wait, how'd you do that?
- That's a hundred K,
Jake, all for the taking,
unless maybe you're not the
gambler I thought you were.
Maybe the stakes are a little too high
for a low-roller like you.
- No, wait, wait, just give me a second.
(tense music)
Okay.
I think today's my lucky day.
- Spoken like a true sportsman.
(register chimes)
Sign here.
You, you might want to
read the fine print.
- Nah, I trust you.
(suspenseful music)
All right, here goes nothing.
(gasps)
- [Demond] You lose.
(Jake screams)
(laughs)
Welcome to my world!
(gun fires)
(Demond laughs)
("Howling at the Moon" by D Fine Us)
♪ I came from the mud ♪
♪ There's dirt on my hands ♪
♪ Strong like a tree ♪
♪ There's roots where I stand ♪
♪ Oh, I've been running from the law ♪
♪ Hope they won't shoot me down soon ♪
♪ Pacing on a sleepless night ♪
♪ Try to catch me howling at the moon ♪
♪ When it rains it pours ♪
♪ Water's up to my chin ♪
♪ Won't stop fighting ♪
♪ To the very end ♪
♪ Many men try to reach it ♪
♪ Many men have failed ♪
♪ Well if you want to get to heaven ♪
♪ You got to raise a little hell ♪
♪ I've been running from the law ♪
♪ Hope they won't shoot me down soon ♪
♪ Pacing on a sleepless night ♪
♪ Howling at the moon ♪
♪ Will you find me ♪
♪ Hope you find me ♪
♪ I'll be back home soon ♪
♪ When the sun rise ♪
♪ Try to catch me howling at the moon ♪