(dramatic music)
(truck whistle blaring)
- [Man] Thank you for your patience.
A customs officer will
be with you shortly.
(speaking in foreign language)
(upbeat music)
♪ Stop being so tough to me ♪
♪ Like a leather jacket ♪
♪ I know you have no sisters ♪
♪ No baby you just wouldn't hack it ♪
♪ Gotta be a strong man ♪
♪ To carry the beautiful
burden of your love ♪
♪ No sissies get your love ♪
♪ No slackers get your love ♪
♪ No weaklings get your love ♪
♪ No suckers for your love ♪
♪ No actors for your love ♪
♪ No gangsters for your love ♪
♪ No sissies get your love ♪
- [Man] Welcome to Canada.
(speaking in foreign language)
For prompt service, please
present your declaration card
to the customs officer.
(speaking in foreign language)
(cars honking)
♪ You got to be a fast man ♪
♪ To transport the beautiful
pictures of your love ♪
- Come on! Come on, what are you doing?
Come on! Move it!
Can you believe these many people
are actually waiting to
get into this country?
The cars are lined up all the
way to the border, Jeremy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for ruining my night.
- This is so gay!
This is gay, isn't it?
- Totally bites, man.
- This is gay.
- Yeah, I know.
I thought we were gonna find some chicks
and give 'em a spray.
- Look guys, I'm sorry.
I thought dad was going driving me back.
- Your dad's too busy
banging every babe in town.
- Shut up. You understand that?
Shut the hell up.
- Look, I don't see why we
just don't let him out here.
I mean, what the hell are we
gonna do in Windsor anyway?
(car honks)
- Now listen Jeremy, do not tell dad
I didn't take you all the way, all right?
He'll just say I'm not being a
good enough brother and shit.
- Yeah, that's so gay.
- Hello!
I don't wanna be doing
this every weekend, Jeremy.
I'm not your chauffeur.
You're the one that wanted
to live with mom in Canada.
Do not tell dad!
- You want me to say hello to mom for ya?
- Yeah, whachacallit, sure.
Look, gotta run. Okay?
- Bye.
♪ No actors for your love ♪
♪ No gangsters for your love ♪
♪ No sissies get your love ♪
- I've seen him cross four times
in the last two weeks, cap.
Two different cars, bus, now bike.
You want me in on this one?
- I have asthma.
- Brand new professional track shoes.
You buy these in Detroit, son,
so you could sell 'em in Windsor?
- No.
They're for me, I'm a runner.
- Well, I know you like
to run back and forth
across the border.
Which school do you go to?
- Wilfred Laurier High.
- You're on the track team?
- Yeah.
Well, I'm trying out.
- Help me out here.
What else are you hiding?
- Nothing!
- I could strip search you.
I find something, I'll make you wish
you never set foot in God's country.
- Search me if you want.
- That won't be necessary. You can go.
So what is it, Mr. Jeremy
Walling, born in the USA?
- [Jeremy] What's what?
- [Cap] Well, most young
Americans are crossing the border
as much as you are, are running a scam.
What's yours?
- [Jeremy] I got parents on both sides.
- [Cap] That's original.
(gentle music)
(Debbie panting)
- Come on!
Come on!
Almost.
Oh come on!
(panting)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Ben, it's almost eight o'clock.
Where is he?
- Buddy took him home
a couple of hours ago.
They're probably stuck
in traffic, Sunday night.
- Is Buddy coming?
- Yeah, I wanted him to see you.
I thought that would make you happy.
- Oh, right.
I guess you're just too
busy seeing how many times
45 goes into 22 to drive him yourself.
- Was that dad?
I promised I'd call when I got back in.
Tell him I'm all right.
- You tell him.
Is Buddy here?
- No.
- Make it short.
- Hey, dad.
- Jeremy.
- Thanks for the weekend.
- Listen, you like the
running shoes and the bike?
- Yeah, yeah. They're great.
- 'cause we could take
'em back if you don't.
We can get something else.
- No, no, I like them. They're fine.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, I gotta go.
So, I'll talk to you soon.
- I'll see you Friday and
you stay strong, all right?
- Bye.
- Yeah, bye.
(gentle music)
- Dad got me a bike.
- Oh. Nice.
(Beth screams)
- Feel better?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, like a whole new person.
Glory be, everything seems beautiful
in its own way, Mr. Dickens.
Could I go back to study hall
or lunch early to reflect?
- Oh, no. You had a breakthrough, Beth.
I asked you to imagine your
father starring in your dream.
You screamed, that was good.
Now, tell the group
what you were thinking.
- Nothing.
I'm on a diet. I was
trying to burn calories.
- [Mr. Dickens] Oh, Beth.
- [Beth] No, it is not funny.
My dad split because my mom's
butt got bigger than his.
It is the biggest cause of divorce.
- [Mr. Dickens] I think it's usually
a little more complicated than that.
Horace.
- [Horace] Well, I was
supposed to go with my mom
down to Florida this weekend,
but my dad wants me to
spend some quality time
with Karen's daughters.
- Oh, excuse me, are you joining us?
- Yeah, I guess so.
I'm Jeremy Walling.
- Oh, of course. Wow!
Don't be shy.
Pull up a pew.
Now, Jeremy's just transferred to Laurier.
How long have you been here, Jeremy?
- Since Thanksgiving.
American Thanksgiving. End of November.
- Well, that's good.
Well, I'm Mr. Dickens,
and we'll just go round
and introduce ourselves.
- Co-host, Cathy Lee.
- Guylain?
- Guylain.
- Oh, I'm Quinn.
- Horace, with a C.
- Hey.
- Mikey.
- And this is our little sleeping beauty,
and her name is...
- What?
Oh, my name's Rachel with an R.
- And as I said, I'm Mr. Dickens,
and I have a master's
degree in family counseling.
And this is our chat group.
This is a place where you
can just let it all hang out.
All the students here
have the exact same problems as you do.
So Jeremy, are your
parents actually divorced?
- Almost.
Can I just sort of watch for awhile?
- Oh no, absolutely.
Right, group.
What's the first thing that we learn here?
- [All] We are not alone.
- [Mr. Dickens] Once more with gusto.
- And for the sake of my government grant.
- Well, let's hear someone else speak.
Guylain, did you see
your father this weekend?
(Guylain whimpers)
Oh.
Oh, not again.
Oh, that's right.
Let it all out.
He's a bad man.
Say it after me.
- He's a bad man.
- Yes.
He's a bad man.
- He's a bad man.
- Hey, Gap guy.
You're American?
- Yeah, that's right.
I spell color without
U and I get a B for it.
I never got a B in my life.
- Wow! Color me impressed.
- Look, sorry. I'm just pissed.
Mad or whatever.
- Hey, it's okay to say
pissed in Canada, hey.
After hockey, getting loaded
is like our national pastime.
My name is Beth. Rhymes with Beth.
- Sweet.
- You're Jeremy. I heard.
So, a lot of people think that Americans
are pushy, obnoxious cretins
who come to Canada to rape and pillage.
- Well, what do you think?
- I'm into rape and pillage.
(laughs)
Actually, I'm an ancient
history buff freak.
As you can tell from the happy hour,
some people think the glass is half empty.
some people think it's half full.
With me, there's no glass.
- What's the happy hour?
- Mr. Dickens' rap
session for damaged goods.
CoDs. Children of divorce.
- So, why do you go if
you hate it so much?
- It's only Mondays and Fridays.
You get credit, and sometimes the stories
from the other losers in the group
help so that I forget to eat lunch.
So why'd your parents split?
- What do you think?
- Unselfish mom, tired
of being Holly home maker
decides to let her true soul gush forth.
Take a younger, richer
lover, male or female.
Close?
- Not really.
It's more like your wide butt theory.
- Men can be pus.
Hey, your dad's probably
thrilled that you're not home
so he can screw his brains out in piece.
- No, actually.
He wants me to live with him in Detroit.
- Aren't you lucky?
(bell ringing)
(gentle music)
- Got any gun, man?
- What, a gun? Me?
- Not gun, gum.
Like a chewing.
- Oh! Well, these are
asthma time capsules.
Forget it.
- I understand, man.
I get hay fever too, don't you know?
I'm Kellog.
- Jeremy. Nice to meet you.
- Next! Name and event, please.
- Jeremy Walling, 400 meter.
That's W-A-L-
- L-L-I-N-G.
Born in the USA, has asthma. I remember.
- No way. You work at customs.
You can't be coach.
- Well, we're even then.
Because you have $150 track
shoes and can't run the 400.
- Why not?
- Because it's too damn difficult.
It's one continuous sprint.
You need muscles, power and
better lungs than you got, son.
- No, no, I can do it.
I have in the States.
- Try a cross country, all right.
- What about my sweatshirt?
When do I get one?
- Not till you make the team. Move on.
Next.
(both panting)
Oh, Jesus.
No, no. Don't stop it.
Let him get a visit from
uncle Charlie tonight.
That'll teach him.
- No, don't file that until
we see what Ben is up to.
I don't wanna rush the sale of the house
until I know I've got half of the business
and primary custody of Jeremy.
What? Florida for spring break?
No way, Kevin.
I don't need any of mom
and dad's negativity.
I just visited them in September
and I still had a husband then.
Kevin, be a good brother.
Just be my lawyer.
Thanks. Love you too.
Sweetie, I've got a surprise for you.
- I'm busy, mom.
- Oh, come on.
I got you ice cream.
The kind you like.
Double strawberry.
- Is it Ben & Jerry's?
'cause I love Ben & Jerry's.
- Can you please stop saying the name Ben?
Stop saying the name Ben.
Get the bowls.
(Jeremy groans)
Oh my God. What happened to you?
- It's all right.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
- What is it? Did you hurt yourself?
- It's just a Charlie horse.
I think I overdid it at practice.
It's all right.
- I do not need this stress in my life.
The solution is simple, no track.
- It's gonna be all right
in the morning, mom.
Don't worry about it.
- Excuse me.
If you don't get all As, it's my fault.
If you don't get into a good college
with a Canadian diploma,
he'll blame it on me.
He'll tell the court I'm
limiting your future.
- He will not.
- Oh, stop defending him.
He just wants you to go
live with him and Buddy,
like a bunch of guys in a damn beer ad.
And he'll tell you how
special his first wife was.
How the hell am I supposed
to follow that act?
She died in childbirth.
Gimme a break.
- Just have some faith, all right?
- See?
He's poisoned Buddy against me.
Buddy never visits, never
returns my phone calls,
doesn't care if I'm alive.
He may not be my natural son,
but I've raised him like one, goddammit!
Your father cheated me
out of everything I've built for 17 years.
But he's not gonna get you, baby.
- I'm staying with track, mom.
- Fine.
That's just what he wants.
- What about my Ben & Jerry's?
(gentle music)
My mom's just going through a hard time.
She thinks everyone's
against her, and I'm not,
but it just keeps getting harder.
- In what way?
- Well, I wish she just
would forgive my dad.
- What did he do?
- Stab in the dark here.
He cheated on her, huh?
He broke a sacred oath for a cheap hump
with a size two stranger.
- Let him speak, Beth.
This is very difficult for Jeremy.
- No, not really.
My dad explained it to me and
I've thought about it a lot.
They just grew apart.
The love just stopped.
- There's no such thing as love.
There is mutual self-interest.
And when he lost interest,
he cheated on her.
- Beth, shh.
- It's okay. She's right.
My mom caught him with one of her friends.
- Women can be pus.
- Beth, zip it.
- At least it wasn't a cousin.
- Perhaps she cheated on him.
- No, no, no.
She wouldn't do that.
She's loyal.
- Do you think that your parents'
relationship was working?
- Yeah. Yeah.
I mean up until a few months ago,
and then my brother just came
to me and said it was over.
- Did he beat you when he found out?
- No.
- Did he start doing drugs?
Specifically, meth?
- No. He doesn't even drink.
They're both great.
- But when your mother packed
up and took you to Windsor,
you wanted to stay with
your father, correct?
- Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
(bell rings)
- Well, that's all very interesting stuff.
Listen, I hope you all
have a fabulous weekend.
And remember, nothing cures
the blues like a good hug.
Are you waiting for me, Beth?
- Not likely.
(both laugh)
- Have a great weekend.
- Hey.
If your dad's so great,
why don't you go live with the hard-on?
- Well, dad's got Buddy.
Mom doesn't have anybody.
- Well, so in other words, you care.
- Yeah, of course I care.
She's my mother.
- Well, are you helping her?
What's the money situation like?
- It's bad.
She wants more than he's offering.
- That's new.
I got my mother another 200 bucks a month
by threatening to tell
daddy's bimbos he had crabs.
- That's pretty disgusting.
(both chuckle)
- No, it's not.
What's disgusting is he had
the money the whole time.
(gentle music)
♪ I will survey the situation ♪
♪ Till Martha comes home ♪
♪ All my teachers always dying ♪
♪ Off them kids that keep on crying ♪
♪ It's me who feels like dying ♪
♪ Till Martha comes home ♪
- Hey, don't get me wrong, and I mean,
I don't wanna be confrontational here.
I'm just saying, this a little bit odd.
I mean, you've only been here 20 minutes.
You've already called your mother once.
You gotta call her 10
wide. What happens next?
Does that coach turn into
a pumpkin at midnight?
Just tell your mother
that you're sleeping over
at your girlfriend's house tonight.
- Ben.
- No, it's ridiculous.
You're 23 years old. You
deserve your own life.
What are you doing here?
- Well...
- Did you meet Sandy?
Sandy, this is Jeremy. Jeremy, Sandy.
Jeremy's my other son.
Sandy, would you wait
outside for a minute?
Would you?
- What?
- Outside? Okay.
Just go down the hall, make a right.
It's in the garage.
She's great.
Didn't your mother tell you
to come over here tomorrow morning?
- I never went home.
I came right from practice.
I ran all the way from the bus terminal.
Hey, what do you think?
I made the team.
- Hey, that's great.
That's terrific. I'm proud of you.
Good.
- So, where are you going, dad?
- Printer's union ball.
I gotta make an appearance.
You know, management.
I'm already late.
I just, your mother...
I can't believe she
didn't tell you that...
She couldn't just call the school up.
Say, "Hello. My son..."
- Well, just forget it.
I mean, I can go back.
- No, of course not.
What are you talkin'...
Make yourself at...
Make yourself at home. This is your home.
It's still your home.
Here, take off your pack.
We got a pizza going in the oven.
You can watch the satellite.
I told Buddy that Rocco
and Hayes can stay here.
So three of you, or the four of you.
You hang out, you have
some fun and rock and roll.
Hey, rip up the joint. I don't care.
Take your coat off.
It looks good.
(car honks)
She's really great.
You'll see, when we're
the three of us all.
Four, you know?
I'm not gonna be late.
- See ya.
(upbeat music)
- You know
I am the man.
Who's your mob?
- Hey, guys.
- What are you doing here, doofus?
- I didn't know dad had a date.
- Yeah, what is she? In ninth grade?
- Shut up!
What's with that sorry sweatshirt?
Laurier track?
That is so ghetto, Jeremy.
- Yeah, so faggy.
- Not as faggy as three
guys working out together
in their underwear.
- Does that excite you? Huh?
You like that?
- Shut up.
- Well, there's only one
way to find out, guys.
Pants him.
- Hey, guys, chill, chill.
Forget him.
Cool down, doofus. They're
just horsing around.
- Jesus, what did you do that for?
- Buddy, I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to.
- Oh, you're dead.
You stupid bastard!
You're not even supposed to be here.
Stupid bastard.
- Get off of him, man. He's your brother.
- Half brother! Half brother!
(Jeremy wheezing)
- [Hayes] Oh my God.
He's having an attack.
Get his inhaler.
Get his inhaler!
- You stupid bastard!
- You okay, man?
(gentle music)
♪ If the sky was sort of red ♪
♪ It don't mean nothing ♪
♪ If you've fallen out of bed ♪
- Why the hell are we being pulled over?
Will somebody please talk to me?
Hey, hey, yo, yo, what's going on in here?
- The weather is braking.
Get a good night's sleep.
Tomorrow at 7:00 a.m., we
bring out the starting blocks.
Gentlemen, have a good evening.
- Who is that guy?
- He's my track coach.
- What's your math teacher? A Mountie?
- I'll see ya.
- Hey, come on. Let's talk a little.
- Dad, dad, dad. What are you doing?
- I wanna get a couple of Havanas.
Just, I'll be back in a second.
- Hurry up.
I don't want her seeing
me waiting out here.
- Well, then get back in the car.
(somber music)
Hi there, you got any Cubans?
- [Man] Yeah, very good, sir.
- What is that?
- Well, it's like Canadian M&Ms.
It's just as good.
- Put it down. Come here.
Look, Jeremy, I don't want
you getting too involved here.
Well, you may be moving back real soon.
I'm pushing for an earlier
court date. Maybe next month.
You could be back at John Glenn
before, I don't know, spring break.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Which is why I don't want
you getting too wrapped up
with this whole Canadian team.
I think it might be better
if you drop out now.
- Dad, I thought you'd be proud of me.
- I am.
I just don't want you making
any emotional commitments
when ultimately you're
gonna be moving back in
with Buddy and me.
- I know, I know.
God, you're being bounced back and forth
like a ping pong ball, I'm sorry.
But that's all the more
reason to stay focused.
I mean, look at this.
Look, what...
This is not M&Ms.
This is an Astro.
And what is this? Mr. Big?
It's like a knockoff of a Baby Ruth.
Even Canadian football, it's all so fake.
It's like a bunch of wannabes.
Jeremy, you are the real deal.
You are first rate.
All of this, it's second rate.
It's like a cheap imitation of
what we are, of what you are.
- Anyway, at least you
can buy Cubans here.
- Yeah, but have you taken a look
at the fruitcake who's selling them?
(both chuckle)
- You know, I don't know why
you hate Canada so much, dad.
- Jeremy, I was married here.
(gentle music)
- Where's Walling?
- No, thanks.
So I guess you're off your diet.
- Yeah, it's my mother's fault.
She found out there are
men who like fat women.
They're called chubby chasers. (laughs)
- Beth, you're not fat.
- Well, not yet.
And not that it matters.
Have you heard the sad statistics
on CoD success stories?
Three out of four of us
will be dysfunctional
throughout our adult lives,
at best, borderline normal.
- Great.
(Mr. Dickens whistling)
- Hello, everybody.
I had a pretty good
weekend. I hope you all did.
Who's gonna start today?
Guylain.
- My father, he was arrested.
(all applauding)
- But when the needles all came home,
that's when I bail.
Split, right there and there.
- That was really clever
of you to say no, Quinn.
Let's have a round of applause for Quinn.
(all applauding)
Jeremy, how was your weekend?
- Well, my father informed me
that I'll be transferring
back to my old school.
He's gonna get primary custody.
So I guess I'm not gonna
be here very much longer.
- Get your head out of your ass, Jeremy.
What judge is gonna give you over to a dad
who cheats with his mom's friend?
He'll be lucky to get weekend visitation.
Unless of course he can prove
that your mother is unfit.
Namely, is an alcoholic, a drug addict
or sleeps with total strangers.
And for that, he would have
to hire a private investigator
and produce evidence.
- I don't think he would do that.
- Yeah, that's what I thought
about my daddy dearest
until this hard ass PI
on the witness stand
started showing pictures of my mom
trolling singles bars in a miniskirt.
Luckily, my mother had
also hired a private eye
and got my dad in a hot tub
with an underage hooker.
He didn't even get every weekend.
(bell ringing)
- Well, that was very,
very positive today.
Yep.
I shall see you all on Friday.
- Listen hey, sorry that
I attacked you there.
Just, I don't wanna see you go, you know?
- Yeah, I know.
I better go.
I'll see you later, all right?
- Okay.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yeah. Come on, have a seat.
Guys, do you wanna give
us a moment here, please?
Thank you.
You missed practice without an excuse.
You wanna be a part of this team?
- I don't have a choice here, Cap.
You know, I might be
moving back to Detroit.
I'd have to quit midway.
- Yeah, but you're bailing
anyway, aren't you?
Yeah.
You know, when you told me
you were a 400 meters sprinter, I laughed.
But then I got watching you.
I saw that crazy look in your eyes.
And I said to myself,
here's this mixed up,
talented kid who understands obstacles,
been battling his whole life.
Maybe I can help him become a champion.
- I'm not in control here.
My parents are fighting over me.
What do you want me to do about it?
- I want you to be a winner.
Give them something to fight about.
(gentle music)
No, no, come on, back.
Stay down through your
first couple of strides.
Get your hands up quick.
It'll bring you up.
Good balance.
- Hands up quick?
- Yeah, have good grade.
Pick it up a little bit more.
And...
That's it. You got it.
Get off the track.
- You invite a man to come
over and eat promptly at six,
and he shows up almost an hour late.
It's insulting.
I wanted to meet him.
(doorbell dings)
- It's Jeremy.
Come on in.
Hi.
I'll take your coat.
Okay. That's it.
- Jeremy, I've heard all about you.
- Hi.
I hope I'm not late.
- No, no.
Unfortunately, my mother was just leaving.
- Yes. I have a law class at the college.
- My mother's taking a
computer course there.
- [Mom] Oh, good for her.
Sorry to hear your parents
are getting a divorce.
- Yeah. Well, you know?
- Listen, if she wants to call me,
tell her I man a divorce hotline,
I know all the tricks for the trial.
You can never be too prepared.
- Or too thin.
(mom chuckles)
- Bye.
Oh, I'm sorry. I screwed up.
I thought you wanted me here at 6:45.
- I did.
(gentle music)
- Never saw you as a gourmet cook.
- [Beth] Well, you know...
- Or is that a recipe of the Visigoths
or the ancient Romans or something?
- [Beth] Actually pasta was invented
by this barbarian chief named Boy-R-Dee.
He might've been a chef.
I hope you left room for dessert.
♪ Come catch me if you can ♪
♪ I'm from beyond ♪
♪ Come sit here and be still ♪
♪ And tell me what you want ♪
♪ I'm probably yours ♪
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Jeremy, you ruined it.
- I just wanted to give you a hand.
- I just bought it for you.
Am I turning you off?
- No.
No.
- I look chunky?
- Absolutely not.
- I thought...
Don't you like me?
- Yeah. Yeah, of course.
It's just, why are you doing this?
- It seemed like the natural progression.
I figured we'd bared our souls.
What's a breast or two?
Are you scared?
- No.
You're just moving a little fast for me.
You see, I've never...
I mean, I'm a...
- Virgin.
Could you maybe just hold
me for a little while?
- Yeah.
♪ I'm probably yours tonight ♪
♪ I'm probably yours ♪
- A private detective.
Can you believe that?
He's trying to frame me as a drug addict
because I use tranquilizers,
which are prescribed for
the stress he puts me under.
Well, you should've seen
the look on his face
when my new lawyer slapped
that continuance on him, boy!
What happened with the judge?
- Nothing.
- [Debbie] Did he ask if you had a choice,
which parent you'd choose?
- Yes.
- And what'd you say?
- I said I didn't know.
- Thanks a lot.
After I let you stay with track?
- Mom, you only agreed
because dad wanted me to quit.
- Nevermind.
What did Buddy say?
That ungrateful little bastard.
- All right.
So we're gonna have to
wait a little while.
She's just trying to
slow down the process,
but she knows it's inevitable.
- Don't worry. Be strong.
You're gonna be home soon.
- You didn't make it any
easier, did you, Jeremy?
When the judge asked him,
he said, "I don't know."
I mean, come on, duh.
- It's all right. It's all right.
It's all right, he still wants to believe
that she's done no wrong.
But Jeremy, son, she has.
Look, she moved out.
She put a border between us
and now she's trying to
blackmail me using your future.
- Dad, I don't know.
Look, what if you gave her more money?
- Well, yo, yo, yo.
Did she have you ask me that?
- No.
- He doesn't get it, dad,
You're such a dolt.
- Shut up! Shut up!
The last thing I need is for you two
to be going at each other.
Please.
Okay. All right.
Look, I gotta go to Chicago
next week for some business.
I got a bunch of comp tickets
for the big King Flavor
concert at the Arts Arena.
You wanna take some of your old pals?
- Yeah.
Maybe some new ones.
- Yeah. Yeah, sure.
- Great. Some clueless hosers.
- Come on, Buddy. He's just
trying to get a rise out of you.
He will get you the tickets.
In the meantime, just be strong
and hang in there, all right?
And enjoy yourself at the show, huh?
Be strong.
- Okay.
Thanks, dad.
- All right.
- I'll see you, Buddy.
- I'll meet you at 8:30. Don't be late.
- Okay. 8:30.
- Don't say a word.
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat music)
- [Beth] I don't know.
Maybe Detroit is in a different
time zone than Windsor.
- [Jeremy] Sorry. He'll
be here, I promise.
- It's just the opening
act, don't sweat it.
- Unless of course we miss
all of King Flavor too.
- Why are you so peppy
today? What's with you?
- Well, I'm overcompensating.
Whenever I'm in the US, I
feel insecure and intimidated.
- No, no, no. Just don't worry.
I'm Ben Walling's son.
- Jeremy, hi.
- Ellie. Ellie, hi.
- How's Canada?
- Great. Great, how are you?
- Good.
- Who is that, Ms. Team breast implants?
- Stop it!
She was the editor of my school newspaper.
We worked together.
- Good job, man.
You're doing a great job there.
- Oh yeah!
- Whoo!
- Wait, wait.
- What?
- We've been waiting
for you. Where you been?
- Nevermind. Who is this?
- This is Beth.
This is my friend Kellog. I run with him.
This is my brother, Buddy
and Rocco and Hayes.
- Hey. Hey.
- Hang on a second.
Why don't I see if I got backstage passes.
- Okay.
- So you're a big King Flavor fan?
- Actually, no, I hate their happy lyrics.
- So, what are you doing here?
- Music turns me on.
- You want a real turn on?
Vodka and grapefruit juice.
Gives you a little bit of nourishment
while getting hammered.
- Don't tease these guys
'cause they're jerks.
It'll be nothing but trouble.
- Don't tell me what to do
because we're not married.
- Jeremy.
- I'm gonna go over and say hello,
'cause I haven't seen her since forever.
- I think you mean, you
haven't seen them in forever.
- What's with you?
God!
- Hey, how's it going?
- What do you think of
braving the washrooms with me?
- Let's get inside first.
- Tell that to my bladder.
- Well, how do you piss with tights on?
- Freely. They're crotchless.
- Oh, their music is so great. Awesome.
- You're funny,
- I'm thirsty.
- Uh-oh.
- It's my brother.
- Your brother? (laughs)
- All access.
Yeah, my dad prints the
programs for the show.
There you go.
Jeremy!
- Yeah, I think I'm
gonna hit the head first.
- Yeah, why don't you beat the crowd?
Use the executive ones downstairs.
They're so dope.
- Cool.
Later, Jeremy.
- Where are you guys sitting?
- I think we're at fifth row or something.
(Beth laughs)
- So, very important people.
The VIP pass. (laughs)
Okay. Little girl's room here.
Thank you very much.
So I'll meet you back.
You don't have to wait.
- What if I want to?
- Well then, I would consider
you a gentleman. (laughs)
- You're Alison.
That's right, I remember
from your great tense.
- That's my friend.
(Beth humming)
- You guys are morons.
She's waiting for us.
Eat shit, Hayes.
(Beth humming)
- Hello?
Hello?
What's going on?
Hello!
Someone there?
(laughs)
Thanks.
Hey, hey.
What are you doing?
- You lied.
These aren't crotchless.
- No, but you're gonna be
if you don't give 'em back.
- You have to dance with me first.
- Why?
- Because I like you.
The whole look.
The way you move.
You're like a wild animal.
Like me.
- Principal Smith is such a beast.
I mean, you should like smell it-
- Listen, Ellie.
I gotta get back to my friends
but it was great seeing you.
Really was.
- Come on, man.
King Flavor is going right on.
- Have you seen Beth?
- You really think that I'm pretty?
- Yeah.
(Beth laughs)
- I'm not missing this.
- What about your brother?
- Nah. Nah, he's too wuss.
She's bored with him.
- Listen man, Rocco's really wasted.
You know how he gets.
Let's go see the show.
- No!
No!
I'm going in.
(Beth humming)
- [Beth] You dance real nice.
- Thanks. You too.
Are you as hot as I am?
- Yeah.
- What do you think, Bud?
- [Beth] You guys.
Wait.
You guys.
Stop it, you guys!
Stop it!
- Hey, where's the bathroom?
Beth!
- [Beth] Stop it, you guys! Stop it!
- Guys, Jeremy's coming. Let's go.
- Hey.
(Buddy howling)
- Yeah!
Get in the car. Come on.
- Beth, I have to know.
- Well, they didn't rape me, all right?
They couldn't even do that correctly.
- Oh, what did they do?
- Rocco, he wouldn't let go of me,
and he just kept feeling me up.
And then Buddy...
- Buddy?
What did Buddy do? Did he touch you?
- No.
No.
No, when I was down, he got over me
and he masturbated on me. (sobs)
And he came all over...
- They can't get away with this.
We gotta tell someone.
- Who, Jeremy?
My mother?
You wanna rip my life apart?
Or do you mean the police?
'cause it's your family
that has messed up.
You think your father's
gonna want you then?
It was my fault.
I was mad at you.
I have a thing for barbarians.
(Beth sobs)
I hate being in the States.
(bell rings)
- I don't understand what the
hell was going on out there.
It was like you were running through dung.
Keep your legs up. Set your head.
It's like you haven't
learned a damn thing.
- I just wasn't concentrating, all right?
- It's mental toughness.
You don't get to just run
when you're feeling perky.
You have to hit the job today, every day.
You have to run through the pain.
- Sometimes, I can't.
- Well, maybe you should
just pack it in now.
Save me the tears.
(somber music)
- Don't worry, man.
It's gonna be okay.
Hey man, don't cut me off.
Everybody's got troubles.
- Jeremy.
How's Beth?
- I don't know.
She never showed up to school today.
- Oh, man.
Rocco really messed her up...
(Jeremy grunts)
Get off of me.
I'm sorry.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
Do you understand, if she reports,
do you understand what they'll do to me?
Do you understand?
- [Cap] What the hell is going on here?
- What you did...
- Stop it!
Who is this guy?
- Jeremy's brother.
Just fooling around, coach.
- Superstar from south of the border.
I heard about you at the Can-Am meeting.
What's your best time in the 400?
- Best?
- Yeah.
- 49.7 at the Detroit Herald games.
- 49.7.
You couldn't even break a minute today.
We'll see you at the Can-Am meeting.
Now, you get out of here.
Go.
(gentle music)
♪ If the sky was sort of red ♪
♪ It don't mean nothin' ♪
♪ If you're falling out of bed ♪
♪ Why they have you well ♪
♪ Why they have you bumped ♪
♪ What they have to do ♪
♪ What they have to dawn ♪
♪ What if he's alive ♪
♪ What if he hears the truth ♪
♪ What he hears the terrible ♪
♪ What are the lies, what are the rules ♪
♪ What are the games to play the most ♪
♪ When he hears the men on the wall ♪
♪ When he hears the truth to tell me ♪
♪ If you cry sometimes alone ♪
♪ It don't mean nothin' ♪
♪ If they take away your home ♪
♪ And if the dawn out of bed ♪
♪ It don't mean nothin' ♪
♪ The world is round ♪
♪ That's what you read. ♪
- I gotta...
- Oh, okay. Sure.
- Thanks.
Hey.
Hey, come here.
Yeah.
Does your mother know that
we're having dinner together?
- Yeah. Yeah.
I left a note. It's no big deal.
- Good.
- So is there something wrong or...
- No.
No.
I just wanted to see you.
Hey, how are things going at school?
- It's hard actually.
Canadians give more homework.
- I'll bet they do, ey? (laughs)
- Let's see, every time
I'm here, I eat the ribs.
I go home, I feel sick from the ribs.
I hear you had some
problems at the concert.
Buddy said that Rocco
was being a real jerk.
- Yeah, dad. It was real bad.
- Oh, that's a shame.
Buddy should learn to choose his friends
a little better, huh?
- What?
- So, you know what you want?
- But dad, don't you even
wanna know what happened?
- Yeah. Could you give us a second?
Thanks.
Buddy did nothing.
He swears to me that he
never even touched her.
- Dad, he jerked off on her.
- Yo, yo, yo, sh!
Come on.
Jeremy.
My God.
I'm doing everything I can
to keep this family together.
What the hell is happening to us?
Look, I'm not saying for sure.
I mean, I don't know,
but maybe from what I
hear about this girl,
maybe what happened, what took place there
was a little more mutual
than what you think.
- No, no, no, dad. That's ridiculous.
- I don't know. Do you?
- Yeah.
- Just maybe.
- No.
- I'll tell you what, I had my
attorney speak to the judge.
I want to try to get you for spring break.
The judge said he had no problem with it.
Why don't you and me go to Bermuda?
We should spend some time together.
- What? Bermuda?
- Yeah, just you and me.
Come on, you remember Danger
Cay, swimming with the fish?
- Yeah, of course I remember, but...
- It'll be great.
Just you and me, we get away
from all of this bullshit.
Let things work themselves out, huh?
Speak of swimming with the fish.
Well, what are you gonna have?
- I don't even know-
- Have the ribs. Ribs.
We'll all have the ribs.
- Ribs, okay.
- Ribs. It's a rib place.
Have ribs.
Speaking of ribs, did you see
that rack of ribs? (laughs)
I'm sorry. I'm me.
What are you gonna do?
If you can't beat 'em, swim with 'em.
Hey, whatever happens,
this will all blow over.
Everything will work out.
- I hope so.
- I know so.
- Great choice, Jer.
You know what? Go to Bermuda.
Go to Bermuda, and you know what?
While you're there, why
don't you get a tan.
Get one for your mother.
- I hope you and your dad
have a great time in Bermuda.
It's gonna be a barrel of fun.
(indistinct chattering)
- Take me to Bermuda.
- Quiet!
Let him speak.
- She's not hurt.
She didn't freak out when I
explained it to her, not at all.
She said that she understood
and that I should go.
- Because she has bigger fish to fry.
She wants half his
business. It's negotiation.
- Why can't he just give her more money?
- Because you see, Jeremy's
not really worth it.
- Look Beth, just because
your dad does not even try
to see you anymore, does not mean
you have to rag out on mine.
- Oh please, Jeremy, face it.
Daddy loves Buddy more.
- Hey, man.
Firstborn always gets
the biggest fatty, man.
- All right. All right.
Then why does he wanna
go away with just me?
Just me and him.
- To antagonize your mother.
- He knows it's her birthday, genius.
You just better hope she
doesn't put her head in an oven
and turn on the gas.
(Guylain cries)
- Look, I am going to Bermuda.
I'm going to Bermuda.
- Look, I did not make the schedule,
and I would like the
throttle the joker who did.
Opening up against the Can-Am meet
is like going against
Goliath with a paper rock,
'cause that's all we are.
A team on paper, green and untested.
So I've decided to use a
little Canadian ingenuity.
I've created a practice meet.
We're gonna compete
against Eaton Ridge Academy in Leamington.
You know that town with a
statue of the giant tomato?
Well, we're gonna stomp it.
Unfortunately, the only
day we could decide upon
was the last Saturday
of your spring break.
I'm sorry. I know that's short notice.
But if we're gonna have any chance
against those superstars
across the border,
we're gonna need 100% attendance.
Was anyone planning on
going away for the holidays?
- It figures. The Yank.
You're going somewhere with daddy?
Palm Springs, Palm Beach?
- Bermuda, actually.
- Bermuda?
- Yeah.
Maybe I won't.
- Excuse me. I didn't hear you.
- I said maybe I won't go.
- Personal sacrifice.
All right.
(all applauding)
Son, you may be more
Canadian than you think.
- Dad, no, no. It was my decision.
Mom had nothing to do with this.
Dad, I had no choice.
The whole team's going.
I mean, I had to.
Well, I don't know.
Can you just take Buddy or something?
- Buddy can't go.
He's gonna take his SATs again.
I hope a lot better this time,
or he's gonna end up in some
stinking junior college.
Oh, come on...
Jeremy, you gotta go with me.
If you don't, who am I gonna take?
I can't believe you're not gonna go.
Oh, it's fine. I'll just have to cancel.
- Dad, I'm sorry.
I'll call you back, okay?
- [Ben] Bye.
- He was really upset.
- Oh.
- Look, stop grinning.
What, do you get pleasure out of this?
- Hey, give me a break.
I am not even borderline normal.
- Well, you know what?
You said it, I didn't.
You know something, Beth?
You're not happy unless
everyone around you
is as screwed up as you are.
- What?
- Yeah, and another thing.
I figured out why no one likes you.
Because the minute someone does,
you just stomp all over them.
People have feelings too.
- Yeah, people also have assholes
and that's how you're acting.
- You know what?
Forget it. It's over.
I don't wanna see you anymore.
- Jeremy.
(gentle music)
What do you mean you don't
wanna see me anymore?
You think I'm gonna be invisible?
Jeremy!
♪ A little truth about us ♪
- [Beth] Jeremy!
♪ Ain't hard to figure ♪
♪ It's adding up to a
hell of a toll on us ♪
♪ We've been up all night ♪
♪ Lift the tempo on your own ♪
♪ Faxed and did the
pledges to solid gold ♪
♪ They got big guns in a
thugging classroom beat ♪
♪ There's people out there ♪
♪ Whose jobs depend on our misery ♪
♪ Misery ♪
♪ It's the truth about us ♪
- Thank you for such a great birthday.
It was so special to me.
Jeremy, you're so grown
up. You're almost a man.
Tell me about this girl.
- I should get to bed.
- Do you like her?
Well, I hope she's on the pill, Jeremy.
- Mom, please, please.
- Oh, don't be such a party pooper.
Jeremy, give me a nightcap.
- Mom, I don't think you need it.
- Jeremy, it's my birthday.
Get me a drink.
Did I tell you how I used to be an actress
at Michigan State?
- Yes.
- Well, there's a lot of
things you don't know, Jeremy.
Good things.
That's what I want.
Yeah.
What do you want?
- Right now, sleep.
I've gotta be at my best.
We go to Leamington in the morning.
- Well, you go to bed then.
'cause I'm coming to watch you tomorrow.
Come here and give your
mother a good night hug.
Come on, Jeremy.
Come here.
Come on.
(gentle music)
Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much for
a wonderful birthday.
(phone ringing)
- Mom?
Hello.
- [Beth] Jeremy, you're a bastard.
- What?
- You sat across from
me for two hours tonight
without saying a word,
and you made me feel like
a total piece of shit.
And you talk about feelings?
Are you gonna talk to me or not?
Don't you care at all?
- Wait, wait, wait, Beth.
What time is it?
- [Beth] It's not even midnight.
Jeremy.
- Just hold on a sec, okay?
- [Beth] Answer me, Jeremy.
- Mom?
- [Beth] Jeremy, don't do this to me.
Jeremy, talk to me.
- Mom?
- [Beth] Are you gonna talk to me? Jeremy.
- Mom, are you in there?
- [Beth] Jeremy, get on the phone.
Okay, fine.
- Mom?
- Fine, I'm hanging up.
I'm hanging up.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
(dial tone beeps)
(dramatic music)
- Come on!
Come on!
Mom!
(siren wailing)
- Jeremy.
- Hey.
- If you hadn't called, she'd be dead.
- Score one for the CoDs.
Warning, my mother's right behind.
She wouldn't let me come without her.
- Jeremy, I'm just sick.
Is Debbie okay?
- She's in intensive care,
but she's stabilized.
- Was it intentional?
- What?
- Honey, did she leave a note?
- Mom, maybe Jeremy doesn't
wanna get into this right now.
- It was an accident.
It was a combination of the
tranquilizers and the wine.
She must've slipped getting in the tub.
- I'd think up a good
story about what happened
before your father finds out.
- Okay. That's enough.
If you wanna stay, fine.
Go chat up a widow doctor or something,
but leave Jeremy alone, okay?
How you doin'?
- I'm okay.
I keep thinking, if I'd gone to Bermuda,
would this have happened?
- Come on.
You didn't just stay for her.
You had the track meet as well.
- Oh God, the track meet.
I forgot all about it.
Look, there's our doctor.
They're gonna let me see her.
So, I'm gonna go.
- Okay. Yeah.
So, I can stay if you want.
- You don't have to.
- I feel so stupid.
- It's all right.
(Debbie sobs)
It's all right.
(gentle music)
(ominous music)
Hello.
- Boo!
- Hey.
- Hi. I was hoping you'd get home soon.
Dinner is getting cold.
- How'd you get in here?
- The building manager
was pretty freaked out
about everything, so he let me into clean.
- There was a lot of blood.
I mean, you didn't have to.
- Hey, I figure, if the
Trojan women could handle it,
so could I.
Besides, I figure at a certain level,
it's all sense memory.
You know, something I can use.
- For what?
- I want to be a writer.
Big historical novels, sex, blood,
high cholesterol food
cooked under the saddle
of rampaging hordes.
- Sounds awesome.
- So far, I just keep a
daily diary but you know,
at least I talk a good game.
So listen, go downstairs and start,
and I will just wash up
and be down in two seconds.
Oh, your dad called and your
coach, messages on the machine.
- Yeah. Yeah.
I'm trying to get in touch with coach.
- Yeah.
- Does your mom know you're here?
- I left her a note.
I'll deal with her later.
I am having way too
much fun playing house.
- Where'd you get all this stuff?
- I went shopping, and
then I did your laundry.
I think I'm already a better wife material
than my mother ever was.
- Would you ever get married?
Knowing what you know, even
if you really love the person.
- Silly boy, there's
no such thing as love.
It's just different levels of feels good.
But I wish that we were married right now.
- Yeah.
Parents would love that.
We'd have to run away or something.
- Hey, well, you know,
we'd only have to hide out
until we're 18 and then there's nothing
anybody can say about it.
- Hey.
I'm sorry.
(gentle music)
♪ Well, the truth about us ♪
♪ Ain't hard to figure ♪
♪ It's adding up to a
hell of a toll on us ♪
♪ We've been up all night ♪
♪ Lift the tempo on your own ♪
♪ Faxed and did the
pledges to solid gold ♪
♪ Say goodbye to a good big apple ♪
- It's okay.
They say that sex is the
cornerstone to a happy marriage.
It's the physical action
that causes the desire
for non-physical commitment.
- If I had a wish, we'd be married.
God, I wish I had condom right now.
- I shopped for those too.
♪ Open all the good coffins ♪
♪ There's only one thing inside ♪
♪ Of being dressed in a cool box ♪
♪ Having Camelot taste ♪
♪ It's the truth about us ♪
- Hey.
I wasn't very good, was I?
- Don't worry about it.
You'll get the hang.
- You wanna try again?
(Beth laughs)
- Just relax.
(gentle music)
- Morning, everybody.
Mr. Dickens, and I'll take that hug now.
- Sit down, Beth.
We need to get started.
- Well, we can't start
yet. Jeremy's not here.
- Jeremy's not coming.
- No. Yeah, he is.
He had to pick up his mom
and then he'll be here
because he wouldn't miss our happy hour.
- No, he's not.
Quinn, was your father
released from rehab?
- No, he's coming.
- He's not.
- I'm sorry, did you sleep
with him last night too?
- Actually, the social
services took Jeremy.
After what happened to his mother,
his dad was granted temporary custody.
So...
Horace, do you wanna start today?
(somber music)
- Karen and dad are moving in together.
They're getting a bigger house.
- That's right. Throw your things around.
That's very constructive.
Look, I said you could
race for the Canadian team.
What more do you want from me?
- Dad, I don't wanna be here.
- Jeremy, you're upset.
I'm sorry, I should've gotten you myself.
I didn't realize they're gonna yank you
right out of school like that.
I thought this is what you wanted.
- No, it's not what I want, dad.
I wanna be back at my school.
I wanna be with my girlfriend.
- Girlfriend?
Jeremy, look what women do to us.
Haven't you learned
anything? Don't be stupid.
I'm sorry.
I wish there was something more I could do
to prove that to you.
Just don't give up on me, huh?
(gentle music)
I'm sorry.
(phone ringing)
- [Beth] Jeremy.
- Hey, how did you know it was me?
- Had no friends, remember?
- Come on. I miss you, don't spoil it.
- How's it going?
- Better than I thought.
I had a good conversation with my dad.
And I'm still running
for Laurier tomorrow.
Are you coming?
- Yeah, I'll be there.
- Great.
- Jeremy.
- Yeah.
- Nevermind.
- What is it? Are you
mad at me or something?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just mad that we're not sleeping
in your mom's bed.
- I love you.
(Beth sniffles)
Bye.
(cars honking)
- [Announcer] Athletes
and coaches must report in
to the scorekeepers bench on arrival.
Please have your registration forms ready.
- What's the matter, dad?
- Well, Buddy got his
SAT scores yesterday.
He needed a combined 1000 to
qualify for Michigan South.
He totally tanks it with a 970,
comes up 30 points short.
- Well, it's no big deal.
He can take it again.
- No, it is a big deal.
He can't take it again.
The only chance he has is South Kansas.
The coach from South, he said,
if Buddy can win a couple of events,
he can probably get him in,
but now Rocco's got the flu,
and Buddy feels like
he's coming down with it.
- Dad, I run and I have asthma.
- I know, I know, but
this is Buddy's big shot.
Look, see what you can do
to help him out, all right?
Be a good brother.
- Have you seen my
black and white sweater.
- Why?
- Because I wanna wear it.
- Where are you going?
- There's a track meet
at the sports complex.
- Oh, so you wanna get assaulted again?
- What?
- That's where those boys
are gonna be today, isn't it?
I know all about it.
You shouldn't have left
your diary out in the open.
Those boys are gonna pay
for everything they did.
- Well, I am not going to the police.
Oh my God!
You already did.
God, damn you!
- You're not going anywhere.
Look, I'm your mother, sweetie.
You're not gonna go anywhere.
- You're not anymore.
Just let go of me.
(indistinct shouting)
- [Announcer] Up next in the long jump,
his third and final attempt.
Benjamin Walling Jr., John Glenn High.
- Come on, Buddy. Come on, Buddy.
Do it, baby. Leap.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
That was good. That was good.
Come on, call it. Call it.
- Length of jump, 6.84 meters.
- 6.8? 6.8!
(crowd applauding)
- Thank you, thank you, thank you.
- Relax, he's doing great.
- What'd you write? Good?
Good, that was great.
- [Announcer] 6.84 meters,
that's the winning number.
- Today is my day, bro.
- [Announcer] Benjamin
Walling Jr., John Glenn High.
Second place, Michael
Rawlins Windsor Central.
(crowd applauding)
- Buddy!
- [Announcer] The next
round of the high jump
will be at a height of 1.9 meters.
And for our American friends,
that translates to six
feet and three inches.
- This is Kellog.
- [Announcer] Our first
competitor, Kellog Clifford.
Wilfred Laurier High.
- Come on, Kellog.
(crowd applauding)
- [Announcer] Clifford clears the jump.
- Great jump. Very good kid.
- [Announcer] Next competitor,
Benjamin Walling Jr.,
John Glenn High.
- Hey, Buddy.
- Let's go, Buddy.
Come on, Buddy.
All right, come on, Buddy.
- [Announcer] Oh, looks like
Walling fails to move on.
- You'll get the next one, bud.
- I just got eliminated, doofus.
- He's mad at himself.
He knows he's not his best.
He's got a cold or flu
or something coming on.
He'll just have to take the 400.
- Hey look, if he does need us
and he can always start
at junior college, Ben.
There's no shame.
- Sal, have you ever
seen a faster, big guy?
This guy's a champion.
He's the best. He's like a race horse.
You watch.
- I gotta tell you, I like
the way your younger boy runs.
- Jeremy.
- [Announcer] Spectators
and athletes are reminded
that food items are
allowed in the stands only.
- What? What did you say?
- Your younger son.
Cap Pierce tells me he's a real comer.
- Just come.
- He's gettin' there.
- Beth.
Hey.
Hey, I'm up next.
- I'm leaving.
- What?
Wait, you gotta watch me run.
I qualified for the finals.
I'm running against Buddy.
(gentle music)
- My mother read my diary.
She reported your brother and Rocco.
- Oh my God.
- Do you know what this
is gonna be like for me?
Come with me.
- The race. You gotta watch me.
- I'm doomed.
- Jeremy, your event's up.
- Make a choice. It's disappearing time.
- But Beth, you can't leave.
- Don't tell me what I can't do.
- Son, what's it gonna
be? Make up your mind.
- Beth.
- [Announcer] Will the
finalists for the 400,
please report to their starting marks?
Finalists for the 400,
to your marks please.
- Kellog.
- [Announcer] Ladies
and gentlemen, please...
- My inhaler.
- You don't need it.
The amount of adrenaline
you're gonna have pumped
through your system will see you through.
What you got to worry about
is getting a good start.
- [Announcer] Lane two, Rhodes
Raymer, Detroit Union High.
Lane three, Benjamin Walling
Jr., John Glenn High.
Lane four, Jeremy Walling,
Wilfred Laurier High.
- Go, Buddy.
- Runners, take your marks.
(gentle music)
Set.
(gunshot blares)
- False start. Lane four.
- That was Jeremy, your boy there.
(gentle music)
- I want you to do it again, okay?
It's screwing up Raymer.
I need this race.
Did dad tell you?
- Yeah, yeah, he told me.
- All right, baby.
- Stay cool, fellas. Stay cool.
- Don't look like Raymer
was too happy about that.
- Runners, take your marks.
- [Ben] Stay cool, fellas. Stay cool.
- [Announcer] Set.
(gunshot blares)
- You got it, Buddy. You got it.
Keep the pace.
- Run, run, run, run, run.
- It's yours, Buddy.
It's all yours now, baby. Take it.
- Run, run, run, run.
- Bring it home! Bring it home!
(crowd cheering)
- Yes!
- Your younger son just
ran the race of his life.
- Yeah, I wish he would
have done that another day.
- Beth! Beth!
(crowd laughing)
- Jeremy, yo.
- Beth, wait.
- What are you doing? Stop.
Would you stop?
Turn around and talk to me.
Don't you walk away from me.
Jeremy!
Get back here.
- Beth!
- How could you do that, Jeremy?
You ambushed him right from the start.
- Dad, I won the race.
Why can't you just be happy for me?
- Happy for you?
Do you know how embarrassing
this is for Buddy and me?
- Embarrassing? You know what, grow up.
- Don't ever push me,
you ungrateful, little...
- Hey, hey, whoa, whoa!
- You get out of here?
Get of my face!
- Cool down, cool down.
Go on.
Enjoy your victory.
- Yeah. Yeah, go on.
Go on. That's right, go on.
Yeah, join your little
girlfriend down there.
And your mother while you're at it.
The three of you deserve each other.
What are you looking at?
You just stay the hell
out of my family, mister.
- You're a fool.
- Oh yeah. Another Canadian, ey.
Yeah, that's it. Walk away.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh...
God!
- What a mess.
- I know, and it's not gonna
go away for either of us.
Are you coming with me?
- You know, you're a real pain.
I'm not letting you go anywhere.
- Close enough.
- You know, we're gonna get through this
because for the first time in my life,
I don't care what happens.
- For the first time, I feel
happy for somebody else.
- Oh, yeah?
Who?
- You, dummy.
You think that's love.
- Or a different kinda feels good.
- Don't mock my pain. I'm
having a breakthrough.
When I saw you win up
there, I felt like I won.
That's gotta be real love, doesn't it?
So that's a yes, right?
(upbeat music)
♪ The leg sticks out of place ♪
♪ From when I kissed your mouth ♪
♪ Your snow white skin is blemish blue ♪
♪ Around your wrist from
when I held your hand ♪
♪ You told me that it
would be the last time ♪
♪ And now I'm getting harder to fool ♪
♪ It really beats the hell
out of me why I'm with you ♪
♪ Starting off with the twisted words ♪
♪ Only spoken by spoken tongues ♪
♪ It hurts so strongly
that my heart racing ♪
♪ Pounded just like a wartime drone ♪
♪ I think about the times
when you're so nice ♪
♪ But more about when you were so cruel ♪
♪ It really beats the hell out of me why ♪
♪ It really beats the
hell out of me why I'm ♪
♪ It really beats the hell
out of me why I'm with you ♪
♪ I was too far, too
late to walk it home ♪
♪ From where you hold off ♪
♪ You promised to help me
if I have to stop this ♪
♪ Come and stop, but no one lent a hand ♪
♪ You thought a treble
way would be so right ♪
♪ I used to think that you were so cool ♪
♪ It really beats the hell out of me why ♪
♪ It really beats the
hell out of me why I'm ♪
♪ It really beats the hell
out of me why I'm with you ♪
♪ A cast, a bruise for long time's sake ♪
♪ When dues are on dues to ♪
♪ Make love down to me ♪
♪ I can remember the day
when we would stay so dry ♪
♪ 'cause that was before you broke down ♪
♪ I should ♪
♪ That should ♪
♪ It really beats the hell out of me why ♪
♪ It really beats the
hell out of me why I'm ♪
♪ It really beats the hell out of me why ♪
♪ It really beats the hell
out of me why I'm with you ♪
♪ Why I'm with you ♪
(dramatic music)