[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
Switch over to eight, Baker.
Dash two.
Push button eight.
All right.
It's just you and me, baby.
You get through this one, you'll be a pilot.
CALLIE: I'm already a pilot TJ.
I'll be a fighter pilot as soon as I
blow your ass out of the sky.
NASH: Keep your mind on the [INAUDIBLE], Baker.
CALLIE: Don't try to round in your bullshit, Commander Ash.
I know the games you play [INAUDIBLE] watch women at.
It just ain't going to work with me.
Roger.
But you got to be a woman first.
CALLIE: Are we going to talk or are we going to fight?
NASH: [INAUDIBLE], Lieutenant.
You're a the top of the class.
You're good, I'll give you that.
[CHUCKLE]
CALLIE: Don't give me anything.
Tough guy, huh?
That's right.
Let's hit it.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Shit.
Trying to [INAUDIBLE]?
[INAUDIBLE] have sex.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE].
Let's [INAUDIBLE], Baker.
[INAUDIBLE]
But it's time to go home now.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE].
[WARNING BEEPS]
Ha.
Was it as good for you as it was for me, baby?
I got to say, I didn't think you had it in you.
Just a walk in the park, Commander.
Just a walk in the park.
NASH: All right, take you home, flier.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLANKING]
[SIGH]
Hey, you guys.
What do you say, after we get our commissions,
we go get TJ and gang bang the son of a bitch?
[LAUGHTER]
Are you kidding?
He wouldn't be able to get it up.
--[INAUDIBLE] of his going to have watching
the four of us take our wings.
Yeah, even extra strength aspirin
won't cure that headache.
That's right.
Whip those buns in, Leah.
Man, every flight instructor in the Navy's
going to bust TJ's balls for letting
you guys get your wings.
He's liable to go back to flying props.
You guys are all forgetting something here.
He did train us.
But he didn't let us graduate.
We damn well earned that gold.
Kelly's right.
Sure, he tried to wash us out, but that's his job.
He's going to try and wash out anybody
who shouldn't be up there.
Yeah.
And maybe we did take a little extra because we are women.
But it only makes us better.
Maybe TJ Nash doesn't see it that way, but the way I see it,
we are at the best.
Hey, we're the Tomcat Angels.
[EXHALE]
[MILITARY TATTOO]
Lieutenant Leah Harper.
Thank you, sir.
Lieutenant Miriam Scotty.
[MILITARY TATTOO]
Thank you, sir.
Lieutenant Jade Han.
[MILITARY TATTOO]
Thank you, sir.
And Lieutenant Callie Baker.
[MILITARY TATTOO]
Thank you, sir.
GENERAL: Well done, Commander, well done.
Not only have four women attained fighter status here
today, I'm also proud to announce that, uh, two--
Lieutenants Baker and Han, respectively--
have also achieved, uh, first and second in their class.
That's another first in Navy history.
Now along with the glory also comes the work.
I have orders assigning Lieutenant's Baker and Han to
a carrier in the Persian Gulf.
Good luck.
I want to thank you all for your continued support
and for coming down here today.
Dismissed.
Good luck.
Holy shit.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You guys are really going to do it, aren't you?
You're going to go over there and barbecue
some bastard's balls in midair.
[GIGGLE]
Well, here's to it.
Yeah, just make sure it's not one of ours.
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
I mean come on.
That's not the color of her eyes.
She's just drooling with envy.
Scotty, knock it off.
Scotty is right.
You bet your sweet ass I'm jealous.
But I'm not stupid.
They're getting two of our best up there
and I'm the first to admit it.
Well, you'd better [INTERPOSING VOICES].
Yeah. [LAUGHTER]
Good evening, ladies.
I think congratulations are in order.
How are you?
Would you like [INAUDIBLE] fantastic?
Good. How are you doing?
Does that mean you're asking me to dance?
Yes.
OK.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
How come anyone doesn't ask me to dance?
Because we're [INAUDIBLE] jockeys, not star [INAUDIBLE].
[LAUGHTER]
Hi, Baker.
Hi.
Want to try dancing on the ground for a change?
Why not?
Have fun.
Walk this way.
So, penny for your thoughts, Harper.
They're not worth a plug nickel.
What?
You bummed because you weren't chosen?
No, it's not that simple.
If I got to go, I'd be leaving you, wouldn't I?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm so damn proud of you.
So I'm not just another pretty face, huh?
Come on, Jade, I'm trying to be serious.
If I get anymore serious, you're going to make me cry.
So say it.
Say what?
Say it, Jade.
Damn you, Sprinter.
All right.
I'm going to miss you.
I'm going to miss you, too.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Congratulations.
Accepted.
Thanks again.
I still don't think women should
be flying in combat, though.
Can't you just accept the gratitude and dance?
You're good.
Accepted.
Listen, I want to apologize about the cracks I made
about you being a woman, because you're
definitely a lot of woman.
Well, there was never any doubt in my mind, TJ.
I know you're not blind.
You're just a little bullheaded.
Well, I'd keep the home fires burning.
--[INAUDIBLE] you're not just saying that.
When are you going to get used to the fact that I love you?
Maybe never.
But don't stop saying it.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
It's my pleasure.
[INAUDIBLE] Callie [INAUDIBLE].
[INAUDIBLE].
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGH]
It's going to happen.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Looks like Jade and Sprinter are leaving.
Yeah, I guess so.
I should probably do the same.
I have to fly [INAUDIBLE].
Why don't you come with me tonight?
I want to show you something.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[COUGH COUGH]
Yo, babe.
Not in your lifetime.
What can I do for you, sugar lips?
Can you dance?
The Bull can dance and romance a little lady.
Would you mind losing the cigar?
No prob.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on, baby.
I know you want me.
That's perfect.
Not that's kind of [INAUDIBLE].
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHTER]
Do you want me?
[INAUDIBLE]
I can feel it.
[INAUDIBLE].
You are one strange man.
It's starting to get hot.
Whew.
I think it's been hot in here for a long time.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you want me?
[INAUDIBLE]
I think [INAUDIBLE].
Oh, yeah.
What do you think?
You look so beautiful.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
So?
So what do you think?
I don't know.
[SIGH]
My dancing that funny?
No.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I was just thinking if this was a soap opera,
those candles would be long and tall
and melting in silver holders.
And this wine would be champagne.
[GIGGLE]
This is Don Perignon.
Honey, [INAUDIBLE].
[LAUGHTER]
My favorite.
Mmm.
This is more like that old Spencer Tracy [INAUDIBLE]
flick, "A Guy Named Joe."
"A Guy Named Joe."
I don't know any guy named Joe.
No, it's a movie, remember?
He flew away and didn't leave her anything but memories.
I'm coming back, though.
You'd better.
It's going to be our [INAUDIBLE] slow dancing by myself.
Oh, really?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
How about leaving me a souvenir?
Like what?
I don't know.
Like this.
[GIGGLE]
You're going to wear it?
I'm going to dream on it.
[INAUDIBLE].
[MUSIC PLAYING]
But you have to come and get it.
You're [INAUDIBLE].
[GIGGLING]
Going to miss me?
And how.
Are you going to miss me?
Yes.
Miss me?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Huh?
Ca--
[CHUCKLE]
Can't believe Scotty the Whip actually found a man tonight.
Who?
Guy named Bull.
[GIGGLE]
Perfect.
Looks like a pit bull.
[GIGGLE]
Well.
That's what she deserves.
[CHUCKLE]
Wow.
That's the view.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE]
I come here when I'm trying to work things out.
It's so beautiful.
It really is.
So what is it you're confused about tonight, Commander?
You.
Oh, TJ.
Heh.
Your timing's, um, not the greatest.
I know, I know.
Just that I've got a vested interest now.
Why?
Because you trained me?
That's how it started.
Yeah?
And now?
It's different.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Teacher Nash, you're a son of a bitch.
Why?
At 0800, I'm going to catch the first plane flying out of here.
And you expect me to go into battle with nothing
on my mind but you?
Listen, Callie.
You are facing something out there that you cannot beat.
You can wound it bad, but you're not going to beat it alone.
That, that's why I've got to keep my mind on business.
I mean, you taught me that, remember?
Stay focused and to have tunnel vision
and to keep a clear head.
O-or was that just a bunch of flyby bullshit?
No.
That's what will keep you alive.
Then why are you trying to confuse me?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Callie, there is going to come a time
when this moment, this feeling, is all
you'll be able to hold on to.
Damn it, TJ.
If you have something to say, say it.
I love you.
Oh, TJ.
No matter what is facing you out there tomorrow,
this is what's real, right here, right now.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Stay with me.
It's time to go.
What are you going to do?
Just walk out of my dreams.
I hate long goodbyes.
Me, too.
Hate short ones, too.
[LAUGHTER]
Take care of your yourself over there.
I'll bring you to the base.
No.
Just sleep and dream about the hello.
Callie.
What I said last night, I meant that.
I love you, too.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE] the best.
Tomcat Angels.
Oh, get the hell out of here.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Keep your heads out of the clouds.
It's a good day to win.
[SMACK]
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
Wow.
We're finally here.
Did you ever think that we'd end up cruising at Mach 3, 20,000
feet over enemy territory, just hanging out?
This is it, Callie, the real thing.
I am so pumped, I couldn't get any higher without a plane.
CALLIE: Yeah, but what I want to know
is when are we going to see some action?
JADE: Hey, my sentiments exactly.
I tell you, I'd sure like to put these babies to work.
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
CALLIE: Bogie 11 o'clock, Jade.
11 o'clock.
JADE: Got it.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE].
Should have stayed in your tent, Omar.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROCKET BURN]
You got him, Callie.
You got him.
I can't believe you.
Oh, I guess that's it.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, listen up.
Listen up.
Leah, I got a letter from Callie and Jade.
For all you new grunts, that's the gals that
are doing it, your role models.
Yeah, they're over there leveling the sand
dunes and the camel humps.
But the question is, are they getting humped?
No, I think they're a little too busy for that.
But listen, "dear Scotty and Leah, we're virgin's no longer.
And it didn't hurt a bit.
Had our first encounter on a recon mission,
if you can believe it.
We got one.
For security reasons, I can't say where or when.
Will go into details when we see each other.
Tell TJ I'm on his ass and he'd better get in shape.
And give him and Sprinter hugs from us.
Callie and Jade."
Hot damn.
Uh see girls, sometimes the best
man for the job as a woman.
And they can cook, too.
Yes.
Hey, couple of cold one's comrades.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
[INAUDIBLE].
Here's looking up your credentials.
[LAUGHTER]
Well, hey, talk about your rollovers,
the girls are over there fighting
this war while we're sitting here weeping in our suds.
Listen, you two, you guys got to sit tight.
Your time's going to come.
Oh, yeah? When?
[INAUDIBLE].
Hey.
Hey, guys.
How's it hanging?
Whatever happened to feminine gentility?
[LAUGHTER]
Men happened.
LEAH: Cheer up, guys.
Your girlfriend sent a big hug from both of them.
Hey, they're over there kicking ass and taking names.
TJ, what are you thinking?
She's right.
They're putting it to them over there.
Listen, I got orders form command today.
They're forming a new squadron.
You can call it what you want.
Tomcat Angels.
It's those two and you two.
And me.
[LAUGHTER] LEAH: You?
NASH: Don't leave me hanging.
I knew you'd be the next to go, you son of a bitch.
Hey, man. Good luck.
Good luck.
NASH: Thanks, bro.
Wait a minute.
You don't have any hooters.
What are you going to do?
Get some 40D implants?
Listen, you better be ready to go in three days.
And put that smart mouth in cold storage, OK?
Yes, sir.
Hey, let's save that last dance for me.
You got it.
Let's go.
That reminds me, I've got some serious dancing to do myself.
Bull.
[CHUCKLE]
So what's on your mind?
[FIRE CRACKLING]
You know, if you want to see other women while I'm gone,
I'll understand.
You will, huh?
You know, I might have to take you up on that.
I mean, you could be gone a long, long time.
And, uh, I could get very lonely.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
If you do that, when I get back.
Yeah, well you'd better come back because my bed's
going to be very, very empty.
And very cold.
[LAUGHTER]
Better be cold and empty.
And lonely.
And freezing.
Cold.
Ice cold.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Going to miss me?
Maybe.
Maybe?
[LAUGHTER]
You'd better.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
God, I hate a man who smells like cigars.
[GROANING]
I be stinking like Abraham Lincoln.
[LAUGHTER]
But you love it, don't you?
Yes.
Will you take me to the couch?
Ready to ride the bull?
[LAUGHTER]
Yes.
Let's go, baby.
[LAUGHTER]
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
I'm going to rip this.
Baby.
[GROWLING]
Give me room, baby.
I hate a man with hair on his chest.
[GROWLING]
[INAUDIBLE].
Take me to my bedroom.
OK.
Yeah.
All right, don't lose it. Wait a minute.
Don't let me fall.
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
OK.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Watch out for the tree.
Just think of me as Tarzan, baby.
[LAUGHTER]
[INAUDIBLE] my Monet print.
Print this.
[LAUGHTER]
[INAUDIBLE].
Oh.
Take this off.
You want if off, huh?
You want it off?
OK.
[CHUCKLE]
[GROWLING]
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
[LAUGHTER]
God, you're crazy.
[GROWLING]
Wow.
Oh.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, yes.
[INAUDIBLE]
[GROANING]
Oh, baby.
Oh, Bull.
Bull, come here.
I want you.
Yes.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Bull.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, god.
I think I love you.
Oh, baby.
[JET ENGINE RUMBLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
JADE: We're always in the air and zip.
Nothing happening.
Like I'm all dressed up and no place to go.
Tell me about it.
What do you say next time we go in our birthday suits.
[LAUGHTER]
You mean you had me bare assed?
CALLIE: Don't knock it until you've tried it.
Hey, you know me, girl.
I'll try anything once.
CALLIE: [INAUDIBLE].
Yeah, me too.
Let's take this [INAUDIBLE] home, mama.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE] here anymore.
3 o'clock, Jade.
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
Baker and Jade.
He's trying to come over the top.
Don't let him behind you.
Watch your [INAUDIBLE], Jade.
He's coming in behind you.
Dive.
Oh, shit.
Callie.
I'm on my way.
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
He's on me.
Jade, Jade, I can't get this bastard off my ass.
He's got a lock on me.
Oh, this doesn't look good, mama.
[ROCKET BURN]
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
[WARNING BEEPS]
Mayday.
Eject, Callie.
Eject.
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
[BOOM]
JADE: [INAUDIBLE].
Request [INAUDIBLE].
SAILOR (ON RADIO): [INAUDIBLE].
Return to base immediately.
Return to base.
JADE: Negative, Coral.
I'll remain here until rescue arrives.
SAILOR (ON RADIO): Negative, Gunslinger II.
You have just enough fuel to get home and we too far into enemy
territory for rescue. Copy.
Return to base.
That's an order.
Hang in there, baby.
What's going to happen to her, sir?
Well, there's an enemy outpost near there.
By now, she's been picked up and is probably considered a POW.
What will happen to her, sir?
I don't know.
[KNOCK KNOCK]
Come.
Commander Nash and pilots Scotty and Harper
reporting for duty, sir.
At ease.
Good to see you, Nash.
I heard you were coming in.
Just in time, too.
Welcome Scotty, Harper.
Uh, I believe you know one another?
We heard about Baker on the flight deck on the way in.
Is there anything we can do to get her out of there?
Nothing.
It'll be up to the foot soldiers,
when and if they do go in.
She and Han got in too deep over mountain terrain for us
to get a chopper to.
She's just going to have to take her chances.
[SMACK]
The arrogance of the Americans never ceases to amaze me.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
They [INAUDIBLE]--
[CLANK]
[BANG]
--and fighting forces [INAUDIBLE].
AMIR: [INAUDIBLE], send women to do their fighting for them.
Where is your base of operations?
CALLIE: My name is Callie Baker.
My serial number is 397--
[INAUDIBLE].
Look, sheik, why don't you ask your ace, Omar, that sorry
excuse for a pilot, who it was who turned chicken and high
tailed it out of there?
Go on.
Why don't you ask him what happened to his other buddies?
Perhaps it was your partner who was so accurate, huh?
Yeah.
She got me, too.
American women are as arrogant as the men.
Even more so.
But they are only the female the species,
as far as I'm concerned.
Where is your base of operations?
Huh?
My name is Callie Baker.
My serial number is--
-Where is your base-- - --397--
--of operations?
--505776.
AMIR: Where is your base of operations?
You
[SMACK]
You have what in your country would be called a lovely nose.
Huh?
Amir.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Put her in a cell.
General.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Amir has an obsession for violence.
[FOOTSTEPS]
He takes great pleasure in destroying beauty.
He would take great pleasure with you.
Thank you for stopping him.
Beauty should be shown appreciation.
You are quite beautiful.
[FOOTSTEPS]
Would you care to come with me?
This is your choice?
Amir will return.
And make no mistake, he will extract information
he desires from you.
At this point, Callie, the information is not
worth the price you will pay.
The choice is yours.
All right.
I'll send for you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BACKGROUND NOISE]
You silly American girl.
Can't you see that Ali is just using you?
That you are of but one of many?
I didn't exactly volunteer for this gig.
Look, a word of advice, OK?
Don't play games with Ali.
When he looks into your eyes, he sees the truth
of what's really in your heart.
What are you trying to say?
Ali, he is like the desert sun.
Fierce, passionate.
If you displease him, he will hurt you.
But if you bring him pleasure, then
he might only break your heart.
Just remember one thing, once a woman has been to Ali's bed,
she is his for life.
[SQUEAK]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SLAM]
[BANG]
Don't be afraid.
Do be quiet, though.
I'm not here to harm you.
Here.
It is fresh water, and bread, and cheese.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me too.
My name is Yousaf.
And yours?
Callie Baker, serial number 397505776.
And that's all you're getting, bozo.
Bozo is a clown in America.
You're cute.
What?
You get American TV here or something?
YOUSAF: No.
I lived in America.
Pittsburgh, PA.
I want to go back.
CALLIE: Wouldn't try it where I'm at, if I were you.
No.
I won't.
If liked it so much, why didn't you stay?
My family was here.
There was pressure on me to return.
When I did, I was meant to serve.
Once this is over, I will leave.
I love my own country, but not its leaders.
I-- shhh.
[GRUNT]
I-- I better go.
I will be your guard.
If there is anything you need--
How about a ticket out of here?
YOUSAF: I can't do that.
I will be killed.
My family would be killed.
Thank you for this.
Please believe.
We are not like Colonel Amir or our leaders.
Dress well.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Nothing?
What the hell?
Three patrols, not one encounter.
Did you and Callie blow all the ratheads out of the air
before we got here?
Maybe they hid out when they heard we were coming.
I wish we could find Callie.
[KNOCK KNOCK]
Come in.
This is the latest list of POWs.
Is she on it?
No.
They have to report if they pick her up, don't they?
Yeah, they're supposed to.
We're dealing with a madman here.
Isn't there something we can do?
I wish there was.
All we can do is wait.
[BANG]
The general has requested your presence.
[CLACK]
[THUMP]
This stupid war will not last much longer, Callie.
There is word that the Allied land
armies are beginning to move.
Our planes are no longer flying.
Then he'll have to let me go.
Won't he?
The general is enamored by you.
But I want to go home.
I want my freedom.
And Colonel Amir hates Ali.
He will not want to be charged with his own acts of crime
after the war.
So there'll be no witnesses when he leaves here.
Yousaf, have I been reported as captured?
YOUSAF: No.
Can you help me escape?
You will die in these mountains.
And there is nowhere else to go from here.
Yousaf, can you report me?
I am being sent to the border tomorrow.
Should I be captured?
Yes.
[RELIEVED LAUGHTER]
Where would I report you as from?
Aircraft carrier, USS Phantom.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Shit.
She's not being released?
She's not listed as POW, dead, captured, anything.
Damn it.
They deny ever seeing her.
That's impossible.
I saw her eject.
I saw her reach the ground.
She's there somewhere.
We're going to find her.
You will learn to like my country when this is over.
We will travel.
The desert is beautiful at night.
We will make wonderful love under a canopy
of moon and stars.
You know as well as I do that I don't even belong here.
I could not persuade you otherwise.
No.
When this is over and my country asks for me,
you're going to have to let me go.
Have I been reported as captured?
The war is almost over, Callie.
And no one has asked for you.
In the future, your country's sympathetic mentality
will take over.
They will give us all the money we need to rebuild.
It will be a beautiful place to live.
Have I been reported as captured?
Am I POW?
Am I MIA?
No one knows where you are.
You are mine.
And you will stay.
You are such a bastard.
Mmph.
[PAINED GRUNT]
I am sending you back to Amir until you are
ready to be more cooperative.
Guard.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
So when the peace treaties are signed, we'll make inquiries.
And she'll be fine.
When?
When it's convenient for all concerned.
[INAUDIBLE] reason.
They haven't reported seeing Callie.
And I hate to think of what that reason is.
now something more than just sitting around and waiting
has to be done.
That's all that can be done, Commander Nash.
Yes, sir.
Dismissed.
[KNOCK KNOCK]
Come in.
Excuse me for interrupting, sir, but a prisoner of war
has just been brought on board.
Asked to be brought here specifically.
Says he's got information about missing pilot Baker.
Sit down.
Bring him in.
You, uh, you have information.
Regarding Callie Baker, sir.
Did you give this information to the commander
that captured you?
I surrendered.
Miss baker said to report the information
to the commander of this ship.
Why should we believe you?
YOUSAF: I was her guard where she is being kept.
We talked.
Son of a bitch.
I knew she was alive.
Quiet.
Go on.
You must be Jade, Callie's best friend, and Scotty,
with a mouth like camel dung.
She didn't say dung.
No.
I'm being polite.
And you are Leah.
And you must be TJ.
We talked.
She asked me to get the information to you,
when I was sent to the front.
Commandant Bowman, it has to be true.
She was brought there after her plane crashed.
She's being held as a [INAUDIBLE].
Where is she being kept?
The general has his quarters set up here,
near this abandoned factory.
It is miles from nowhere.
Escape on foot is impossible.
But she was talking about trying.
COMMANDANT BOWMAN: All right.
I'll put in a request for her right
away from your government.
My government is corrupt, sir.
She has not even been reported to them.
And Colonel Amir intends to kill her.
Take the prisoner out.
No.
Please.
Save her.
Come on.
[SLAM]
[SIGH]
All right.
This retrieval is going to have to be done through channels.
I will, however, call command and see if there's
anything stronger we can do.
But sir, we have--
That will be all, Commander Nash.
Carry on.
[BANG]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUMP]
How is my little whore?
Did you have fun last night?
Huh?
Maybe [INAUDIBLE] can make it as interesting as last night, huh?
[LAUGHTER]
Oh.
Look, we're hear and Callie's out there.
And them's the facts, folks.
The rest of it's just hot air.
Now something needs to be done.
JADE: What?
I don't know.
Somebody's got to go in there and get her out.
Who?
The US Army, the Marines, a few good men.
Where the hell are a few good men when you need them?
If we can't find a few good men, then
how about a few good women?
You're looking at the best way to get Callie out of there.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
Operation Tomcat Angels.
Listen, nobody is going to go in to get Callie but us.
We've been in this thing together all along.
And we're the ones who are going to go in to get her.
JADE: How?
Are you in?
Keep talking, commander.
All right.
Here it is.
We're still flying patrol up over enemy airspace,
over the borders where Callie's being held.
We set it up to fly patrol together, the Tomcat Angels.
We go to the border.
We break in.
We saw on the map that Callie's dune buddy showed
us that there's a small landing strip right in the middle
there.
If we can land these things on a floating football field,
we can sure as hell land one there.
And then go in and get her out.
You don't know where the troops are, the layout,
where exactly she's being held.
We take the prisoner with us.
He knows the troop placements, how many, and where Callie is.
How do we get him?
We requisitioning him for further questioning.
We can stow him away in our planes.
Look, it's 30 minutes to the border.
It's another 15 to target.
And 30 minutes to go in and get her.
And that's 45 minutes back.
We're back in two hours.
And we'll have squeezed all the information we can out of him.
It's not really a lie if you stop and think about it.
Jesus Christ, you're crazy.
We're all crazy.
You know that, don't you?
I guess I am, too.
Can we pull it off?
You got a better idea?
What about you, Leah?
I'm in.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
The prisoner that was brought in yesterday,
Yousaf, he's wanted for more questioning in the wardroom.
Yes, sir.
Prisoner, come out.
I'll escort you, sir.
That won't be necessary.
NAVY PRISON GUARD: You're sure, sir?
Absolutely.
I mean, what's the most he's gonna do, swim home?
That's not sand out there.
Yes, sir.
Come with me.
[SIGH]
[KNOCK KNOCK KNOCK KNOCK]
Anybody in here?
Come on.
There's nobody here.
We'll use the wardroom.
Come over here.
Sit down.
Too late to back out now.
Right.
Did you tell him?
Tell me what?
You're going on a little trip with us,
back to where you came from.
But I don't want to go back.
And I don't want to cut your balls off either, gangadin.
But I will if I have to.
We're going in to get Callie.
And you're our native guide.
You will bring me back?
I can't imagine the rest of this life without you, big boy.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
NASH: Tomcat patrol.
Go button eight.
Roger.
Prisoner accounted for, sir.
[PANICKED BREATHS]
All right.
About 15 minutes north of enemy HQ are a few hundred troops.
We've got to fly directly overhead.
We got 15 minutes to get in, get Callie,
and get the hell out of there.
Or we'll end up as camel burgers.
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
NASH: All right, prepare to jam.
Jam and go to 100 feet.
There's turning back now.
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
NASH (MEMORY): Callie.
There is going to become a time when this moment, this feeling,
is all you'll be able to hold on to.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCRATCH SCRATCH]
[BACKGROUND NOISE]
What, the general shops at Frederick's?
[HUFF]
[MUSIC NOTE]
How's that, big boy?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
They're for the general.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Won't you dance with me?
Seems that my prayers have been answered.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I've been thinking about you [INAUDIBLE].
I'm listening.
Well, I was thinking that I could
be quite comfortable here.
Callie.
If you are lying to me.
No.
No, I'm not lying to you.
You need a strong woman, don't you?
Don't you need someone hear with you?
You haven't changed your mind, have you?
You still love me, don't you?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes.
[SLOW MOTION TALKING]
[SMACK]
[GASP]
Don't move.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Down there.
Come on.
How many soldiers?
There's two in there.
I don't know.
Sometimes [INAUDIBLE].
Where's Callie, Yousaf?
Up above, on the first landing with the general.
This is going to have to go down fast.
Come on, TJ.
Let's use our heads.
We have to do this quietly.
She's right.
Come in like-- with guns blazing like John Wayne,
and they're liable to do the same to Callie.
Before we even get there.
JADE: What's that?
The women.
They bring the soldiers food.
Do they?
You thinking what I'm thinking?
Yeah.
Yep.
We'll take care of it.
Be careful.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
We're genies.
You've been waiting and wishing.
And here we are.
I bet you've been wishing for this for a very long time.
Just like the general, huh?
Just like the general.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
OK, all clear.
Good job.
Where to?
Come on, man.
We got to move.
Where to?
Over here.
Let's go.
[GRUNTING]
Argh.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUMP]
In here.
[GRUNTING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
In here.
Callie.
The hell's going on here.
Come on TJ, kill the bastard and let's get out of here.
Are you OK?
It is still your choice.
Stay with me, Callie?
[GUN COCKING]
No.
[GUNFIRE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Shit.
They must have heard that.
SCOTTY: OK.
How do we get out of here?
Come on.
I show you.
Come on, let's go.
Now.
You OK?
I am now.
Come on.
Let's go home.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on, let's move.
[GUNFIRE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOOM]
OK. Up there.
Run.
Give me this. Come on.
Let's go.
We got to move.
Got to move. [INAUDIBLE], show them where the plane is.
I'll meet you there.
If I'm not there in 10 minutes, go without me.
[CLANK]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on, TJ.
Come on.
Double time it, captain.
[SPEAKING ARABIC].
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Go.
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
All right.
We are up.
Yeah.
Welcome back, Baker.
It's good to be back.
You know it's a damn shame you didn't kill one more.
I'm still one up on you.
Yeah?
Well, the ground combat I went through evened things out.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
11 o'clock level.
NASH: Spread and use evasive maneuvers.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[JET ENGINES RUMBLING]
LEAH: Look at that son of a bitch go.
This is going to be better than [INAUDIBLE].
Let him go. Let him go.
[CHUCKLE]
No sweat.
[ROCKET BURN]
[BOOM]
Hope it's one of the kids [INAUDIBLE], Yousaf.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
CALLIE: [INAUDIBLE], TJ.
NASH: All Right, take it home, flier.
We are headed home.
Yep.
It's great.
SAILOR (ON RADIO): [INAUDIBLE] free whiskey.
NASH: Roger November two tango.
SAILOR (ON RADIO): Roger.
Authentication approved.
Proceed Gunslinger.
Bring them in.
NASH: Sorry about that, Corral.
Met and old friend in the desert and stopped by to party.
Yeah.
NASH: You'll see when we land, Gunslinger.
Coming in after a pleasant, but uneventful, afternoon.
Over and out.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
TJ.
NASH: Yeah?
Thanks.
Did you remember?
It's all that kept me hanging in there.
[MUSIC PLAYING]