(upbeat hip hop music)
(man scatting)
(alarm blaring)
- Yes!
(dramatic music)
(Gypsy barks)
Right on time.
It worked, Gypsy!
(Gypsy barking)
Good afternoon, guys.
All right, I've
downloaded your equations
and I've processed it
into my hard drive.
The roses are in the bucket,
so if all goes well,
this formula should keep
them from aging, right?
- Technically, it should.
But I still think you
didn't use enough-
- What are you talking about?
I have told Willie the
exact amount of everything.
My plants are living for 40
times past their usual lifespan.
So, Willie, you try it out.
- I don't know if I
like the color she used.
- Mrs. Donovan, that
looks beautiful.
And I love your hair. That
style really suits you.
- You can call me Mom. I
already told you about that.
- (sighs) All right. Here goes.
(machine beeping)
(machine whirring)
(fluid gurgling)
(dramatic music)
- You don't think this
makes me look like one
of those wanna-be-young
grandmas, does it?
- Oh, no, Mom.
I don't.
- It is absolutely
beautiful here, Barry.
You picked a wonderful
place to live, son.
- Yeah, Monique
and I, we love it.
- Guys?
You didn't say
anything about smoke.
- Willie, the smoke
will not harm you.
It is just white,
odorless smoke.
An indicator you used
too much formula.
Now you must stop it before you
lose visibility in the room.
- Okay.
- Mom, this, um, interest that
you have in the way you look,
it wouldn't have anything to do
with Dad coming
into town, would it?
- The creature?
- Is Miss Thing
staying at the house?
- If you mean Mom, yes, she is.
- You see, that's on you.
You could've told me
that she was coming.
I'd have rearranged my trip!
- So self-absorbed!
- Honestly, whenever that
man looks into my eyes,
the only thing he
sees is himself!
- I mean, she is
really something.
She can be the biggest
pain in the behind
that I have ever seen.
You know it.
- Are you gonna be able
to get through this?
- Yea, though I walk
through the valley
of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil.
For thou art with me.
Thy rod and thy staff-
- Oh. Willie, whatever
you do, don't use water!
- Well done, Herr Accreditation.
Perhaps you should have warned
Willie about this beforehand?
- [Scientist] No hair? You
ought to talk about hair.
(scientists bickering)
(Gypsy barks)
(steam hissing)
- Oh!
(suspenseful music)
(Gypsy barking)
♪ There was once
a place and time ♪
♪ When I thought
you cared for me ♪
♪ Yes, it's true ♪
- Willie?
- What do I do?
Willie?
(dramatic music)
(Gypsy barking)
- (coughing) What
did I do wrong?
(bell ringing)
(dramatic music)
(dispatcher chattering)
(siren blaring)
(Gypsy barking)
Gyps, where are you?
(siren wailing)
(dramatic music)
- [Woman] Where's
the fire truck?
It should be here by now.
(Willie coughing)
- [Willie] What have I done?
Oh, man, I'll be
grounded for life.
(siren wailing)
- [Woman] Oh, and
it's a new house, too.
(siren wailing)
(Sydney sighs)
(dramatic music)
Whoa. (coughing)
(glass crashing)
What are you guys doing here?
- [Firefighter] It's all clear!
Got one over here!
- Get off me!
You're gonna ruin my experiment.
- [Firefighter] It's
okay, son. Just relax.
- [Willie] No, you
don't understand!
- [Firefighter] All right,
let me get you out of here.
- No!
- Got one! I'm coming out!
(Gypsy barking)
(mysterious music)
(dramatic music)
- [Willie] Come
on, guys. Please!
Just a little bit more time.
Guys, why'd you do-
- You should do it more often.
- [Firefighter] You okay, kid?
- [Willie] (sighs) I'm fine.
- [Firefighter] Can you
take a deep breath for me?
- [Willie] See,
look. I'll show you.
- I think he's
okay. Thanks, guys.
Hey, kid, don't
play with the truck.
Sit.
What's your name, son?
- Will Smith.
- Now let me guess,
you were just getting jiggy
with it in the garage?
Now, your real name this time.
- I live here. This is my house.
- [Firefighter] Excuse
me, sir. Sir, you can't-
- Willie! Willie,
are you okay, son?
- Yeah, but they messed
up my experiment.
- False alarm.
- I'm sorry.
- What did you do?
- Hey, grandpa.
- Come on, let's go
assess the damage.
Leave you two alone
for half an hour,
and this is what happens?
Where's your sister?
Sydney!
- Dad? Dad, what is this?
- [Barry] Where have you been?
- What?
I was upstairs, and
all of a sudden,
I see this smoke every...
What did you do?
- What do you think?
- What? Oh.
Hi, Grandpa. I am so sorry.
I didn't even see you.
- There's my beautiful
granddaughter. (laughing)
It is amazing.
You are the spitting image
of your Grandma Cat
when she was your age.
Of course, you're a
lot more level-headed.
- [Sydney] (laughs)
Thanks, I think.
- No, no, don't get me wrong.
On the outside, she's
still beautiful.
But sometimes the
inside can effect
the way you look on the outside,
and your grandmother's
insides are twisted
and mauled and all around wrong.
And the way her
brain works, I mean,
the logic she employs is like,
on another level altogether.
- [Barry] Dad.
- What happened?
- Is everyone all right?
- Everyone's fine, Grandma.
- Mr. Einstein here was working
on another one of
his experiments.
- Oh, Willie.
How many times have I told you
to pay attention to
what you're doing?
Honey, you're playing with
dangerous chemicals here.
- I thought I was being careful.
- No, you weren't.
Now, until you learn to take
much more responsibility,
your lab equipment
is off-limits.
Understood?
Do you understand, young man?
- Yes, I understand.
- Okay, let's get
things cleaned up.
- What, what? Me?
Oh, no. Uh-uh, I have to go.
I mean, I'm already
late for work.
Why don't you let him
do it? It was his fault.
- Well, wait, wait.
You're gonna come home
early, though, right?
I'm making a family dinner.
- Yeah, sure, sure.
Just make sure there's no
meat. I don't eat meat.
- I know, I know.
- Bye, Dad. Bye.
- I'll make you
something special.
Oh, my goodness.
Look at this mess.
Willie, oh!
What have you done?
(smooth jazzy music)
Willie? Willie!
I think it's best
you get the soap box
and bring it upstairs with me.
- Should I go now?
- I think it's best you do.
- We're not finished yet.
You are grounded.
- Take it easy, Barry.
(Cat sighs)
You gonna ignore
me all week, Cat?
- How can I?
You're in my face.
- No one asked you to come
here this week, you know.
Man can't even visit
his own grandchildren?
- They're my grandchildren
just as much as they are yours.
- Yep. Same old bitter woman.
- Looking at the
same old selfish man.
(dramatic music)
(Gene sighs)
(suspenseful music)
- [Monique] Willie!
Don't forget to put fresh soap
in your grandparent's bathroom!
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music)
- (giggling) Busy afternoon?
- Busy? Maybe for this burg.
You don't know busy until
you've seen the stores in L.A.
That's busy.
- (groans) Well, Brad says
you're catching on fast.
- Hey, I'm from California.
We do everything fast.
- (giggling) Sydney, look,
I know you miss L.A.,
but there's a lot of cool
things and people here, too.
- Mm.
- Yeah, come on.
Give it a chance. You'll see.
I'm telling you, I can feel it.
It's in the stars.
Yeah, oh, yeah. I can feel it.
The moon and Venus are aligning.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah. Mm-hmm.
Yep, I feel it.
Strange and wonderful
things are gonna take place.
Oh, oh, oh!
- What?
- Oh, do you recognize
him from computer class?
- [Sydney] Yes.
(gentle music)
- Holy jumping, wow. You
can e-mail me anytime, baby.
Oh!
Oh.
- Mm, mm, mm, girls!
(record scratching)
You musta wished upon a star,
because tonight is your
luckiest night by far.
- Oh, please.
- Oh, my-
- So, seriously.
- Oh, my god!
- Girl who is so funny,
how'd you like to roll
with Mr. Milk and Honey?
- Milk and honey?
- Oh, yeah.
- Are you serious?
- I do not joke when it's
matters of the heart.
- You know what,
um, my shift's over.
So I will see you later, okay?
Call me, Julie.
- Yeah, my name's
Terrence, but that's cool.
We'll get that later.
So your friend, she seems
to be taken with me.
- Oh, taken with you, is she?
- You know what
I'm talking about.
- Yeah, I know what
you're talking about.
I'm talking about this
right here like that.
You know? Okay.
Can I get a price check, please?
(crickets chirping)
(clock chiming)
- What ya doing there, kiddo?
- Oh, hey, Grandpa.
- What's up?
- Well, since I can't
use my lab set anymore,
I'm using my computer to
do virtual experiments.
- Ooh, quite the little
scientist, aren't we?
- A bad one if you ask
anyone around here.
- Oh, then I guess you
won't be needing this.
- What is it?
- Open it up. (chuckles)
- Whoa! A real, authentic
scientist lab coat!
Thanks, Grandpa!
- (laughs) That's
for inspiration.
You're a very talented
young man, Willie.
Once you're off your grounding,
you can wear that thing,
but not before, okay?
And listen.
You got the right attitude.
You're young, you've got
your whole life ahead of you.
You've got plenty of time to
do what you have to do. Okay?
And remember one thing:
Grandpa loves you.
(gentle upbeat music)
- Grandpa?
I love you, too.
- Heavenly Father, we ask
you to bless this food
we are about to consume.
Please help it to nourish
our bodies to do thy will.
And, Father, we ask you
for special blessings
for Barry and his family
in this wonderful,
wonderful celebration
we are having right now, Father,
for those who were invited
and for those who
were not invited.
Some of us need more
prayers than others.
We ask you, dear Lord,
to bless this food.
In Your name, we pray. Amen.
- [All] Amen.
- And you were referring to-
- So, how do you like
your new town, Sydney?
- Oh, well, um, you know those
old black and white films
that we see on TV?
- Mm.
- Well, they're years
ahead of this town.
(Gene chuckles)
- Kids. You've got
to love them, Dad.
- Yeah, right.
- No meat, right?
- Right.
- Moo.
- You'll make new
friends, honey.
You've only been in this
school for two weeks.
You must make this
experience a positive one.
- Grandma.
- Hm?
- This place is so not me.
- Yeah. People here are nice.
- Dad, please.
- Willie.
- Sorry.
- Honey, you're
still gonna try out
for the cheerleading
team, though, aren't you?
- Well, yeah, I guess.
I mean, I was good when we
were living back in L.A., so-
- Hey, it's a good
place to meet people.
Especially the boys.
- You're new here, pumpkin,
and it just takes time.
Remember, the mountain
didn't come to Mohammed.
Mohammed had to go
to the mountain.
- Your grandmother's
right for a change.
You've got to go after
what you want, sweetheart.
- Right for a change?
- Oh, my bad.
Your grandmother's right for
the first time in her life.
- Listen, Mr.
Thinks-he's-so-hip,
you're such a fool!
- Well, it takes
one to know one.
- [Cat] I don't know how
they put up with you.
- Well, I don't know how
(phone ringing)
- I'll get it.
- I don't know why I even
bothered to show up here.
I knew you would be
nothing but trouble.
- Believe me, if I had
known you were coming,
trust me, I wouldn't have.
Talk to the hand.
(kids laughing)
- Oh!
- Jenny's in labor! (laughs)
(smooth jazzy music)
- I cannot believe you are
leaving them to watch us.
- What's wrong with that, honey?
- They hate each other.
- Willie, they do
not hate each other.
We had no idea this
was going to happen.
Aunt Jen wasn't due for,
like, three more weeks.
- She's never been early
for anything before.
- Well, I guess we better
hide the kitchen knives.
- Look, I promised your Aunt Jen
that I would be there for
the birth of her baby.
And we did the best that
we could. I'm sorry.
- Baby, you seen my-
- Yes, second drawer.
Where did I put my eye cream?
Honey, don't forget
your sinus medicine.
Now, what, oh, yeah.
Need my deodorant.
- Hey, Dad.
Dad, why do you always jump
when Monique says jump?
I mean, if Mom was here-
- Hey, that is not fair.
We've been over this
time and time again.
Hey, baby, look at me.
When Mom died, it was the
worst day in both of our lives.
We've got to move on.
Monique is my wife now,
and she is your step-mom
and she loves you.
- Yeah, but you never
have time for me anymore.
It's always her.
- Sugar, don't say that.
We're only going to be in
California for a couple of days.
I tell you what.
I promise you that
when I get back,
we'll spend as much time as
you want to spend together.
- Promise?
- I promise.
(gentle music)
- All right. All right.
All right.
But, I mean, if you guys are
only going for a few days,
then why is Monique packing
a month's supply of shoes?
- [Monique] Ah. Woo!
(pill bottle thudding)
(pills rattling)
♪ This is a vanishing romance ♪
♪ Gone, that magic
sparkle in your smile ♪
♪ Our favorite song ♪
♪ Is out of style ♪
♪ There's no use pretending ♪
♪ It's the ending of our dance ♪
♪ This is a vanishing romance ♪
♪ Love ♪
- [DJ] Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
This is Joanne at your jazz
hits radio station, W.J.A.Z.
You just heard from the
Tri-Ess Trio Jazz Quartet
and right about now,
I'm bringing you into
the midnight hour.
Hope you sit back,
relax, enjoy the music,
and have a wonderful evening.
(dramatic mysterious music)
- [Vickie] Morning, everybody.
This is Vickie,
coming to you live.
- [Big J] Good morning,
it's the Big J.
Happy sight and I'm feeling
right. How about you?
- [Vickie] I'm feeling good.
And the weather's good today.
- [Big J] The
weather's fantastic.
(radio chattering)
(Gene scatting)
(smooth jazz music)
- [Monique] Dad!
Dad, come on down!
Breakfast is ready!
- Okay, I'll be
right down. Whoo!
Better hurry up, guys. You're
gonna miss your flight.
- I can't believe
that Mom isn't up yet.
You know, I think I'm
gonna go and wake her.
- No, no, no, no, son.
No, I've got everything
under control.
Let her sleep.
For the whole 10
days, if I'm lucky.
(engine rumbling)
(alarm ringing)
(Cat humming)
(Cat screams)
(Cat gasps)
- Okay, okay.
Okay, just, (gasps) calm
yourself down, Catherine.
Calm yourself down.
You're, you're dreaming!
That's it. That's it.
You're asleep. Just
wake yourself up.
Yeah.
(hand slapping)
(bright music)
Okay, now, I'll just
look back in the mirror,
and, and this time, I'll be...
(Cat screams)
(dramatic music)
(Cat panting)
Huh?
(smooth jazzy music)
Now, I can work
with that. My voice.
My voice!
Oh, Lord.
What has happened to me?
Hmm.
(Cat gasping)
Hey.
Oh, my.
(Cat giggles)
(upbeat music)
♪ Hot ♪
♪ Hot hot hot ♪
♪ Baby, oh, baby ♪
♪ Where've you
been all my life ♪
♪ Hot ♪
♪ You came from out of nowhere ♪
♪ Like the speed of light ♪
♪ Hot ♪
♪ Hot thing, hot thing, yeah ♪
♪ Can I see you tonight ♪
♪ Can I see you ♪
(Gypsy barking)
It's me, Gyps.
Grandma Cat.
Surely you recognize me?
(Gypsy growling)
Maybe not.
Now, you just wait right there.
Do you know who you
are dealing with?
I am a 67-year-old woman,
and I am not gonna let my
grandson's dog intimidate me.
Whoa, what are you doing now?
Hold on a second!
(Gypsy barking)
Get! Get!
(Cat shrieks)
(locks clicks)
(gasping) No!
(Gypsy barking)
(dramatic music)
(Cat groans)
Yeah.
(Gene scatting)
(chimes tinkling)
(radar beeping)
(siren blaring)
(gentle jazzy music)
(dispatcher chattering)
- Yes, officer?
- You know what the speed
limit is around here?
- Um, no, no. I
can't say that I do.
All right, let me see some ID.
Give me your driver's license.
- Okay.
(Gene scatting)
There you go.
- This your car?
- No, no, no. This is,
uh, this is my son's car.
I just dropped him and the
missus off at the airport.
- All right, step
out of the vehicle
with your hands in the air.
- Is this one of
them speeding traps?
- Now.
- Yes, sir.
Drop your keys. Slowly.
- Look, officer,
couldn't you just give me
a speeding ticket?
- This is a lot more serious
than a speeding ticket, pal.
Where's the guy you
stole this car from?
- Look, this car is not stolen.
I told you, it is my son's car.
- Yeah? And it's
pretty obvious that-
- Back off!
Freeze! I didn't tell
you to move, punk!
We're gonna get to
the bottom of this.
- I sure hope so.
- [Dispatcher] Attention, all
units, we have a code three.
Please respond.
- You stay right here
and don't move a muscle.
Yeah, this is Officer Ratto.
I'll deal with your code three.
I've got a situation here.
I want you to run
a license for me.
- It's a miracle.
- [Ratto] Yeah, I'm having
a problem with a kid.
17-years-old.
- Or I'm going crazy.
- I got him on a
speeding ticket.
Yeah, the car's
not registered...
(smooth jazzy music)
Hey. Hey!
(radio chattering)
(upbeat music)
(tires screeching)
(suspenseful music)
(Gypsy barking)
(Gene panting)
- All right, Tracey!
That was fabulous!
Thank you very
much. That was good.
Okay, um, Sydney Donnelly?
- Donovan.
It's Sydney Donovan.
- Right.
(dramatic music)
(upbeat techno music)
- Aw, yeah. She's pretty good.
(Sydney panting)
- How'd I do?
- You was banging. I
mean, you were real good.
- Hey, excuse me. You're
the new girl, aren't you?
- Yeah-
- Well, you've certainly
got a lot of potential.
Maybe with a little
more practice.
- Practice.
- Who knows?
- I don't.
- It was a very good first
try, though. Maybe next time.
All righty, I'm sure we'll
see each other around school.
Who's next, Kim? Kim Anderson?
- Yeah, yeah, just hold on.
- Kim Anderson.
- [Kim] Coming.
- Next.
- Ash, I don't get it.
What didn't you like about her?
- (sighs) I smell an
attitude problem. Major.
- Yeah, so do I. (huffs)
- Next.
- Yo.
I saw what happened.
You cool?
Aw, man.
Well, if it's worth anything,
I thought you was all that.
Seriously.
I think Ashley made a mistake.
She's my sister, I'm gonna
talk to her right now.
- Look, look, I don't
need your help, okay?
I can take care of myself.
- You know what my coach
is always telling me?
He says you're only a
loser when you give up.
I don't think you're a loser.
Why would you want to do that?
You're real good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Well, obviously
not good enough.
(people chattering)
Look, I'm sorry, I-
- Hey, baby. You miss Daddy?
Listen, we gots to
stop meeting like this,
because people are
starting to talk.
- Oh, my god.
- Yeah, that's right.
So, girl, I know you needs me,
but I'm real busy right now.
- You know what? You need help.
- Yo, keep it down,
girl. No broadcasting.
- [Student] Hey,
you got a sister?
- Sydney.
Y'all should be in school.
- What's that?
- What's that, lady?
- [P.A. Announcer] Good
morning, Monarch High.
Today's announcements
include a follow-up
to our detentions.
Will the following
names please report to-
- Girl, he is cheatin'!
You know, I stop--
So what's up? You
trying to get down?
- Uh, down?
No.
I'm not down.
Well, I am a tad bit upset.
You would be too
if you were having the
morning I was having.
- Shut up.
- Shutting.
- Are you dissin' me?
- Uh-huh, she dissin' you, girl!
- Serious dis.
- Look, I know you
probably had a rough day.
You probably failed an English
test of something. (laughs)
- You want some of this?
- Okay now, young
lady, that is enough.
Nobody puts their hands on me.
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
All y'all.
Instead of focusing
on your studies,
something that could make
your pathetic life
worth something,
you around here acting
like some common criminal.
I know your mother did
not work her butt off
so you could go to school
acting like this every day.
Now, I am in the
middle of an emergency.
And the next time I see
you, you better be acting
like the young lady
I know you can be
instead of some hoodlum.
You understand?
(blow thudding)
(toilet flushing)
- [Sydney] Was it me?
No, it wasn't me. (sighs)
(sighs) I hate this town!
- Oh! (panting)
(bell ringing)
- Can you help me with this?
Came loose.
- Your brain's what
came loose, fool-child.
You need to go home
and thank the Lord
your mommy and daddy haven't
kicked you out of your house.
Looking like the devil himself.
You need some help.
Oh, sugar, honey,
iced tea, not again.
(student laughing)
When did kids get so violent?
- [Sydney] That sounds like
something my grandma would say.
- Sydney?
- Grandma?
- You?
Something's happened.
Oh, this is big.
- (gasps) Who the?
- It's me. Grandma Cat.
- What?
- I can't believe it myself.
But here I am.
- What?
Oh.
Oh, my gosh.
- Oh. Ooh!
- [Sydney] Willie!
- [Willie] What?
- [Sydney] Will you hurry up?
- Why are you late?
- Just get in the car, okay?
- [Willie] What's up with you?
- [Sydney] Just get in the car.
I cannot tell you
about that right now.
- Who's the freak
in the front seat?
- Don't you call me a freak
just because something
weird happened to me.
I'm your Grandmother, boy.
- Grandma?
- Did I stutter?
- Grandma Cat?
What happened to you?
You look like Syd.
- Yeah, well, guess what,
Mr. Scientist, we know that.
- Stop it!
- Tell us something
we don't know, okay?
- Oh, wow, Grandma.
Have you been in my stuff?
- Of course not.
- Oh, wow, Sydney.
We've got to hurry
up and get home
so I can run some
tests on Grandma.
No wrinkles.
- [Cat] If you touch
me one more time,
I swear I'm gonna smack
you upside your head.
Sit back.
- Yes, ma'am.
(upbeat music)
(Gene chuckles)
- Yo, I can't believe you
left a brother out to dry.
- Well, see, what happened was
I was going to go from behind-
- I don't want to hear
your fables, Judas.
Man, you should
have been stickin'-
Hey, dude, watch out!
- Whoa!
- Damn.
Oh, boy wrecked my ride.
- Yo, man, you 'aight?
- Yeah, I'm cool. I'm cool.
But this guy needs
some crazy medicine.
- Yo, let's see if
we can get him up
and bring him over to the store.
- All right.
(door knocker rapping)
(upbeat music)
- [Ratto] Good afternoon,
young lady. Your parents home?
- Uh, no.
They're away on a trip, officer.
Grandma!
Can you turn that down, please?
(laughs) Can I help
you with anything?
- You have any adult
supervision around here?
- That would be me.
- You're her twin.
- Her twin?
- Twin.
- I'm her grand-
- My twin.
Such a kidder.
- I stopped a young kid this
morning driving a Ford Explorer
registered to a Barry
Donovan at this address.
- Dad's car?
- Is Barry okay?
- Well, we'll know better
when we find the
kid who was driving.
Maybe he can shed
some light on things.
- Kid?
- Yeah, about your age.
He was carrying this
driver's license.
- Wait a minute. What
did this kid look like?
- About six foot, wearing
gray slacks, gray trench coat,
black fedora with a red
feather on the side.
Do you know him?
- That's your grandfather.
- Grandpa?
(Gene groans)
- Yo, check it.
Mr. I'm-Gonna-Go-50
In-a-20-zone is comin' to.
Word.
- Oh.
- What happened?
Oh, what happened?
I can't remember
what happened. Leo?
- I don't know, let's
see. What happened?
- Oh, I remember what happened.
You knocked me flat
on my back, sucker.
- I did?
- Yeah, you did.
Where you coming from? Damn.
- I saw what happened.
Are you okay?
Is there something
I could get you?
- Yeah, I'm-
- Well, well, well.
If it isn't little
Miss Gold Digger.
- Now, look-
- Oh, hey, hey, hey.
C'mon now, young fella.
That's no way to be
talking to a lady.
- Young fella?
- That's no way
to be talking to a lady.
- Mm, mm, mm. (sighs)
Barbecue spare ribs,
macaroni and cheese,
and jalapeno mashed potatoes.
- (scoffs) Um, Grandma?
Aren't you overdoing it?
- Well, that's what
we're about to find out.
See, these are foods I used
to eat when I was young.
Man, I haven't had spicy
food like this in 10 years.
I haven't had dairy
products in five.
Lactose intolerant.
Mm. Mm, mm mm.
Just as good as I remember.
- Grandma, I've checked
all the prescriptions
and lotions that you use.
There doesn't seem
to be anything
that could've caused
your transformation.
Now, think.
Did you use any
bit of this soap?
- (scoffs) Wait, soap?
Great, Einstein.
What do you want us
to do, take a bath?
- Well, that's the
soap in the bathroom?
I used it.
- Syd, would you just
listen to me for a sec?
- All right, I just
don't believe it.
You're gonna have to explain it.
- This bar of soap
was in the box
that my chemicals spilled
all over yesterday.
I'll have to run some tests
to see if it's contaminated.
Yesterday, I put it in the
grandparent's bathroom.
- So Grandpa must
have taken a shower
this morning using
the same soap.
- Maybe when the
chemicals mixed,
it created some kind of
fountain of youth effect.
The chemicals got in
their bloodstream and...
- [Willie And Sydney]
Instant teenage grandparents.
- No indigestion?
No upset tummy.
- Can you reverse the process?
- I don't know. I just figured
out how it probably happened.
- (sighs) All right,
all right, all right.
Just do your best, okay?
And just do it before
Monique and Dad get home.
- Wait, does this
mean I'm not grounded
from my lab equipment anymore?
- Willie, I am
giving you permission
to use whatever you need, okay?
Just be careful. And hurry.
- Cool.
- Funny guy. Mr.
Funnyman in a hat.
- [Leo] Hold on. She's
writing something.
- Yo, that dude's got game.
He's a female magnet.
Yo, I think we's gots
to be rolling with him.
- I hear that.
- I sure hope Grandpa's okay.
- I'm sure he's fine.
Just don't expect him to come
around here anytime soon.
- Why not?
- Because he's selfish
and irresponsible.
And if he's 17 again,
he's gonna want
to do it all over.
No strings attached.
- Listen, new guy,
you stick with us,
because we are the serious
players up in this one.
- Serious.
- Serious players.
- Word up, look.
We'll turn you into a mack
daddy lover, just like us.
- [Leo] Yeah, what you say?
- Well, I-
- Come on.
- I don't know about all that.
- [Leo] What's the deal?
- You all live around here?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
(upbeat music)
- See, Gypsy? It's
just another bath.
See, I'm gonna
get you all clean.
Good girl.
(Gypsy whining)
(Gypsy barking)
(gentle music)
- (chuckles) Woops.
- You look great, Gram.
- Aw, thanks, baby.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Anything, baby.
- All right.
Um, what happened
with you and Grandpa?
(Cat sighs)
- Well. (sighs)
Well.
Hmm.
You mean, why'd we divorce?
- Yeah.
I mean, Grandpa, he's so...
He's so young
and he's so fun and so hip.
- Your grandfather's a fool.
- Well, then, why
did you marry him?
- Well, he wasn't
always that way.
He was a good husband.
Faithful.
A good provider.
- Then what happened?
- (sighs) I don't know.
But enough about me, Sydney.
You're young. You
have a great life.
You live in a wonderful town.
Why do you hate it so much?
- I just do, Grandma.
I mean, I had such
a great life in L.A.
I mean, there's so many people
and everyone there, they're so
alive, you know what I mean?
Everyone's so boring here.
- Everything and everyone?
There isn't one thing you find
the least bit interesting?
- No.
(gentle music)
(door clicking)
- Welcome to Casa de Terrence.
- Okay, okay. Now,
where are your parents?
- My parents, I don't,
working, I think.
Paying the bills, you know.
- You lying, man. I thought
you said they were on vacation.
Like in the motherland,
or something.
- Man, I don't know.
Maybe they're upstairs.
Why you buggin' me?
- Yeah, uh, where's
your telephone?
- Telephone, yeah. Right there.
Help yourself.
- All right.
I love your house, man.
You always got food.
- [Terrence] Yo, straight
up. My parents is providers.
(smooth jazzy music)
So, did you see
how many phone numbers I
scored today at the mall?
Huh?
- [Leo] Huh, you
mean Gene scored.
- [Terrence] And did you see
how the honeys was peeping me?
- [Leo] Hmm, you mean
peeping Gene now.
(phone ringing)
- [Terrence] Look, they
was only peeping Gene
'cause he was hanging with us.
Check it, the honeys
see us teaching Gene-
(Gene growls)
So, if we hang with him,
we could have all the
honeys in the world.
- All the honeys?
- Like a buffet.
- That's what I'm talking
about. So what you say?
(smooth jazzy music)
(Gene laughing)
So, what you say?
- I don't know,
man. It's like...
You know I'm down for that.
- You kidding, man? Bam!
- You a genius!
- We gonna be bangin'!
You know what I'm saying?
- You're a genius.
- Yeah. All right.
- What?
- So, where you staying at?
- Well, I was gonna stay
at my family's house,
but it looks like I'm gonna
have to stay at the Holiday Hut.
- [Both] The Holiday Hut?
- No, no, no, brother.
Why stay at the hotel-ay
when you can chill right
here with the fell-ays?
- That sounds like a plan.
Yeah. That's what I'm
talking about, yeah.
(Gypsy whining)
- Gypsy!
Gypsy, it worked!
You're a puppy!
See, I told you I wouldn't do
anything to hurt you. (laughs)
It worked!
- Willie, I'm going to scho-
Who's puppy?
- It's Gypsy.
See, I needed a test subject
so I could see how to
reverse the aging process.
And it worked!
- All right, I'm
counting on you, Willie.
Now, I'm letting you stay
home from school today,
but you have got to
change Grandpa and Grandma
before Monique and Dad get home.
All right?
- Okay.
- Be careful.
Bye, Gypsy.
- Gypsy, we've got
a lot of work to do.
Let's get to it.
(people chattering)
- [Server] There you go.
- This is very upsetting, Todd.
- I really think
you're overreacting.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I am days away from putting
on the first major dance
of the senior year,
and you tell me the DJ
that you scheduled has
suddenly pulled out?
I am class president.
Class icon.
Monarch High It girl.
For God's sakes, you know that.
- Now, if you would just listen
to me for one second, I can-
- The dances that I have put
on for the past three years
have become the stuff of legend.
The Senior High School Dance
must be the pinnacle of
my high school career.
- That's why me and you are
gonna strut ourselves down
to the Orange Club.
We're gonna check
out that new local DJ
'cause I hear the boy can spin.
So you don't have
to worry about it,
'cause your brother
got it covered.
- Well, why didn't you say so?
So, Todd, who are you
taking to the dance?
- I don't know.
I was kind of thinking
about Sydney Donovan.
She cute.
- Whoa, rewind. Same
question, new answer, please.
- Same answer. Sydney.
- Todd-
- What?
- No, I cannot have my
brother dating the new girl.
- Okay, now you've
totally lost me.
What's wrong with
Sydney Donovan?
- She doesn't fit in.
Plus she hangs with
that loser girl.
- You talking about Julie?
- You know her name?
- Yes, I do. (laughs)
- Plus, you don't even know
this Sydney. You just met her.
- That is the exact reason
why I'm taking her to the
Orange Club tonight, okay?
Honeybun, let me tell
you something, okay?
You may be my big
sister and all,
but you's got to learn to
stay out of my business.
I still love you.
Go on.
- Yeah.
(people chattering)
- Hey.
- Grandma!
I don't think this
is a good idea.
- I'm young again, Sydney.
I want to, I want
to experience life.
At least until Willie finds
out how to turn me back.
- Yeah, but how am I
going to explain you?
- Look, tell people
that Oprah helped you find
your long lost cousin.
I love that Oprah.
Remember that time that woman
socked that other woman?
It was crazy.
Wait a minute, that was
Jerry Springer, not Oprah.
- All right, all right.
All right, all right.
But I gotta warn you.
School's probably a
lot different than
how you remember it.
- Honey, please.
It's still reading,
writing and arithmetic.
How much can it change?
(bell ringing)
- This is a condom.
It is a latex condom.
And we place it over the head
of the fully erect turgid penis.
We roll the condom
down the shaft
all the way down to the base.
Now, upon withdrawal,
holding on to the
base of the condom,
we easily slide
it off like this.
All right, class.
Now it's your turn.
(Cat gasps)
(hand thudding)
- Shh.
- How do you turn this thing on?
(computer dings)
Oh.
- [Computer] Wassup?
- I'm fine.
- (laughs) Grandma,
it's a computer.
- It was talking to
me, so I answered back.
(upbeat music)
(computer beeps)
(alarm beeping)
Oh, oh.
- Shh.
(Cat screaming)
(people chattering)
- [Leo] You like that, huh?
♪ You can't call me contact ♪
♪ I'm in the auditorium,
lay some fat track ♪
♪ Wassup, black ♪
♪ Oh, you like that, huh ♪
Want some of this?
Come on, baby.
That's what I'm talking about.
- Hey, Terrence.
- Hi there.
I can see your underwear.
- Am I getting a headache?
- What is with this noise?
- [Terrence] All
right, break it up.
Let me see what you got, player.
- All right. All right.
Mm, uh.
- Wait a minute, wait
a minute. Who is that?
♪ Y'all kids think this rap
stuff is new, you're fooled ♪
♪ Been doing this before
you tied your shoe, uh ♪
♪ New is old and old is new ♪
♪ And what you all call new
I already been through ♪
- Woo, he is hot.
- Oh, he certainly is.
♪ Whatever floats your boat ♪
♪ You mess with Gene and
that's all she wrote ♪
- That's all she wrote, baby!
- Excuse me.
- With this right here, you
all gotta show your money
if you want to get some
of this right here, yo.
That's my boy, yeah!
- Hi, I'm Ashley.
Great performance.
- Well, thank you.
Thank you. Um, I'm Gene.
- Some friends of ours are
going to the Orange Club tonight
to listen to some bands.
I was hoping you'd
like to join us.
- Oh, we're gonna have to
check our calendar, girl,
but I'm sure it'll be just fine.
- It's not an open
invitation, geek.
- Talking to me? Yeah, I'm
gonna sit right back down.
- Gene?
- (gasps) Oh, my gosh. Grandpa?
- Well, um...
- Yo, my man, you've gotta
make this move right here.
I mean, this is a
major hottie, you know?
I'd do it myself, but, you
know, I'm gonna hook you up.
- Oh, you know what?
I've gotta get to class.
Um, can I trust you
to get Grandpa Gene
and meet me back at
the house after school?
- Yeah, yeah, sure. I've
got this under control.
- Okay.
- You just go to class.
- So you go and do your thing.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, yeah.
- Great.
And you know, listen.
- Gene!
- Sydney!
- No.
- Cat?
- Blow away. We're busy.
- Well, go get busy with
some other fool, girl.
'Cause I need to
talk to this one.
- [Terrence] That's
what I'm talkin' about.
- Excuse me, child.
- I'll get out of
your way, girl.
- [Gene] Hey! Whoa,
whoa, whoa, hey, hey!
I didn't know it
happened to you, too.
- It was the soap
we washed with.
It got contaminated from the
chemicals in Willie's lab.
You would have known that if
you would have called home.
- Whoa, hey, Cat,
Cat. Look, look, look.
You know what? Hey, I was
planning on doing that.
But, you know.
- Well, Willie's working on
a way to get us back normal.
- What?
Why?
I like things just
the way they are.
- What?
- Cat, look at us, Cat.
We are 17 years old again!
Look at this!
- Oh, Lord.
- Hey, feel that.
- I don't want to feel nothing.
Aren't you at least
a bit concerned
with what's happened to you?
- Hey, I am 17 years
old again, okay?
I don't care how it happened,
I'm just glad it did.
- There might be
side effects, Gene.
We don't even know how
long this will last.
- Which is why
I'm going to ride this
thing out as long as I can.
I, I mean, why should
I waste my energy
trying to turn back
into a 67-year-old man?
Constantly, constantly
being reminded of my age
with every step that I take.
You know what that is?
- What?
- Booty.
- Booty?
- Will you listen to yourself?
Who are you trying to fool?
We don't fit in with
this generation, Gene.
And I don't care how
young you look or talk,
you will never fit in.
- Oh, oh, you, you know why
I haven't been home, Cat?
There's your
answer, right there.
- You know what?
This is really sad. (chuckles)
You finally look the way
you've acted your entire life.
17 years old.
- Well, I'm going to stay
17 years old, you old woman.
- Fine by me, you old man.
Do what you want to do.
- I am gonna do what I want
to do, and you know what?
I don't need your
permission to do it.
(Cat groans)
- [P.A. Announcer] ROTC
training takes place
at 4:30 tomorrow afternoon
right behind the south gym.
- Sydney! Sydney!
- What?
- Um, I was wondering
if you'd like to go
out with me tonight.
Look, there's this place,
it's called the Orange Club,
they've got all these
DJs I want to check out.
- I'd love to go out
with you, young man.
- [Todd] Would you, now?
(chuckles) Well,
all right, then.
Look, I'm gonna see you tonight.
(bell ringing)
I'm feeling good, brother.
(door thuds)
(people chattering)
(blows thudding)
(men grunting)
- Oh, oh!
Take advantage of a brother.
Living off kritz,
baby. Look at this.
Wassup? What you got?
- Ready?
- What you got?
Too slow. You're too slow.
Come on. You can't even
catch what you can't see.
- Boom!
- Look at that. Boom!
- Hey, fellas.
Hey, hey, fellas.
Homies, hey!
- Right in the belly, and
you know you got a big one.
- [Gene] Hey, my,
my bloodhounds!
My dog pound, what's
up, what's up y'all?
Hey, hey.
- Come on.
- Stick and move, baby.
Stick and move.
- My, um.
- You're too slow.
You're too slow.
- All right.
- Don't you two, you know,
want to get out of the house?
Maybe go and do a
little something?
- Come on, man, you're
messing up my combo.
- Yo, what's up, G?
- Man, is this all
y'all gonna do?
- You ain't got me.
- You know, you play
your video games
and watch your music videos.
- Uh, other than chasing
hotties, what else is there?
- What else is there?
Man, there's life
out there, man.
- Boom!
- The pulsing-
- Pushing right out of the move.
- Beautiful, unexplored,
delicious life!
- I'm gonna sit
you down, fat boy.
- Out that door, waiting
for you to taste it.
- Hey, I'm up for some grub.
How 'bout some Taco Hell?
- Naw, naw, naw. Domino's, dude.
They deliver.
- True dat, true dat.
- [Terrence] Hey,
come on. Look at that.
- [Leo] Cheap shot is the one.
Man, lose the frown lines, dude.
You got a date with
a hottie tonight.
So what's the problem?
- [Terrence] Hey, pause,
man. Stop cheating, man.
- Yeah.
- Dang.
- I've got a date with
a 17-year-old hottie.
(blows thudding)
(men grunting)
(bell ringing)
- [Terrence] I didn't
want to play anymore,
so that means you lost.
- So, what happened
at school today?
I miss one day, and I feel
like everything's changed.
The stars are aligning, Sydney.
I'm telling you, the
universe is in flux.
- Tell me about it.
Yeah, I mean...
What's wrong with you?
Your voice is generating
unstable biorhythms.
- (sighs) I don't know.
It's just that my grandmother,
right, she came into town
and I'm just trying to get used
to the changes that
we're going through.
You know what, I better go.
It looks like my
grandmother needs my help.
- So am I gonna see you at
the Orange Room tonight?
- Well, I don't know.
- Well, Todd will be there.
- Yeah, and so will a
lot of other local boys.
You know what, I
have to go, okay?
I'll just talk to
you later, bye.
(dial tone buzzing)
(Julie sighs)
(phone rings)
- Oh.
Psychic friends hotline.
No, Dionne Warrick is
not here, thank you.
- You look great, Gram.
- I do look good, don't I?
Mm. I can't believe it.
I'm finally going on a date! Me!
- Relax, Grandma.
It ain't no thang.
- Well, maybe it
ain't no thang to you,
but if the last time
you went on a date
was to see the new singing
sensation Nat King Cole,
trust me, baby, it is a thang.
(Sydney laughs)
- Whatever.
(bright music)
Ooh!
Big Mama!
Look at you!
Now, you look fabulous.
- Thank you. I have arrived.
Now, if your grandfather
can have fun,
why shouldn't I?
- (laughs) You know, Grandma,
I can not believe
I'm saying this,
but you have become
one of my best friends.
- Well, let's just hope
you feel the same way
once I'm an old woman again.
(both laughing)
(doorbell ringing)
That's my date.
- Ooh, right on time.
That's a good sign, Grandma.
So, which Monarch High guy
is lucky enough to be going out
with my 67-year-old
Grandma, huh?
Todd?
- Sydney.
How you doing?
- (gasps) Oh, my God.
What is he doing here?
- That's my date.
- No!
Grandma, no!
No, you cannot-
- Of course I can.
- No!
- Now look.
I am not gonna toy with this
17-year-old boy's heart.
Now, move.
- No, no. Grandma, no.
(knuckles rapping)
- You like this boy.
(Sydney sighs)
Baby, now-
- Grandma, that's okay-
- No.
No, it is not okay.
Now, look, he obviously
thinks I'm you.
(sighs) All right, I'll go with
him to the Orange Club now-
- Grandma!
- Hey, hey, hey!
After you get dressed,
you just hustle on down
to the Orange Club and
when the time is right,
we'll make the switch.
- I cannot believe you. No!
I am not gonna do that!
- You got any better ideas?
(knuckles rapping)
- No.
But I also don't have a dress
that looks like
that in my closet.
- But you do have something
short, black, and clingy.
Now put it on.
- No.
- And if he notices
the difference
between those two outfits,
you had no chance
with him anyway.
Now, what do you
all say? Audi 2000?
- No, we say one.
- One?
- We say one.
- What do you say?
- One.
- Well, I'll see
you later, okay?
- Bye.
- Bye. Hi, Todd.
- [Todd] You get dressed fast.
Didn't I just see
you in a sweatshirt?
- [Cat] I'm from L.A.
We do everything fast.
- Where have I been? L.A.
(dramatic music)
(car honking)
(people cheering)
(upbeat music)
And here it is, the
hottest spot in town.
Everybody comes down here,
gets their groove on.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
- Hey, what's up, Todd?
- All right then. You know?
Cool?
What, Ashley?
Don't worry about Ashley.
Let's, let's go
over here, lounge.
- Whoo, girl!
- Yeah.
- [Woman] All right!
- [Woman] You got it.
- Oh, hey! My gosh!
(both laughing)
Hey, Sydney, what
are you doing here?
I thought you said
you weren't coming.
- When did I say that?
- An hour ago on the phone.
- Oh, oh.
Well, here I am.
- There you are. You look great.
Oh, man, so, hey, have
you spotted him yet?
- Who?
- The man of your dreams.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- I think I have.
- [Todd] Here we go.
Hope I got something you like.
- Todd.
- How you doing, Julie?
- Hello, what brings
you out this evening?
- I'm here with her.
- Oh, you're here together?
- Mm-hm.
- Oh, you're here with, oh!
Sydney.
I couldn't quite figure
out what he was at first.
Then I realized,
holy cow. (laughing)
- Oh, well, well, well.
If it isn't the loser sisters.
- Sydney?
- [Cat] Guess again, lover boy.
- [Gene] Cat. What
are you doing here?
- Just ignore her
like I'm trying to do.
- What am I doing here?
What are you doing
here with her?
- He's my date.
I mean, just how
well do you know her?
Did you go to school with
her before you came here?
- Oh, yeah, we went
to the same school.
The school of Holy Matrimony.
- You know what, you're not
only desperate, you're psycho!
- Excuse me?
- Ho, ho, ho, hey!
That is enough.
- Come on, baby. Let's go dance.
(upbeat music)
(people chattering)
- These are $500
shoes. Can you keep up?
Come on.
(upbeat hip hop music)
♪ It starts from my glance
that leaves them in a trance ♪
♪ My voice pulled along,
we move to a dance ♪
♪ The tactics that I use,
chicks be feeling me ♪
♪ You end that number
for fear of prophecy ♪
♪ Some try to cop me,
it's sharp like a jacket ♪
♪ See we be teen ballers no
need for us to practice ♪
♪ Watch this, truth before
the clubbers right here ♪
♪ We about to let loose,
calm down, up in the air ♪
♪ Grab a shorty, get naughty ♪
♪ Enjoy the party ♪
♪ If you're holding
up the wall player ♪
♪ It's straight sorry ♪
♪ All the ice in the world
for the freezer close by ♪
♪ We're going to party up in
here until they call the cops ♪
♪ So drop your coat
on the hanger ♪
♪ Ladies to the dance floor
and shake your thing, huh ♪
♪ So what you never
getting, player ♪
♪ Hold on to your chick,
we'll have to take her ♪
♪ Breaker, breaker ♪
- Excuse me.
- Sydney?
- [Ashley] Uh, whoo.
- What did you do, boy?
- Gene? Where are you going?
Gene.
(snorts) This is all your fault.
- Yeah, do that again.
- Syd?
- Cat? Hey, what
happened in there, Cat?
- Sydney!
- Hey, hey, Cat? Cat?
That boy do something to you?
- Leave me alone, Gene.
- Cat, hey. Cat, Cat, just...
Can you talk to me for
one minute, please?
- We have nothing to talk about.
- I think we do.
- Look, why don't you just
go back to your date? Okay?
- Maybe I don't want to.
(sirens wailing)
(traffic whooshing)
- [Cat] I have to
talk to Sydney.
- [Gene] At least let
me help you find Sydney.
- [Cat] I said leave
me alone, Gene.
(upbeat music)
Where's that music coming from?
Maybe she's in here.
(upbeat big band music)
- [DJ] All right.
All right.
♪ Hey, there, everybody,
have you heard the news ♪
♪ It's on and jumping down
at this old house of blues ♪
♪ So leave your cares behind ♪
♪ But don't forget
your dancing shoes ♪
♪ 'Cause there's a
party going on, baby ♪
♪ Do what you want to do ♪
- Syd.
- Not now, Willie.
- What?
♪ Make your way to the parquet
and let your backbone slide ♪
♪ Ain't no wrong way to do it ♪
♪ Do whatever makes you feel ♪
- I've isolated the chemicals
in Gypsy's bloodstream.
The combination has
effected her DNA
and totally reversed
her cellular structure.
Just like with our grandparents!
♪ The band's got
the joint jumping ♪
♪ Baby, everything
is everything ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Let the boogie say
up jumps the boogie ♪
♪ To the rhythm of
the boogie to be ♪
♪ Can't you see, can't
you see, can't you see ♪
♪ Right here and now
is the place to be ♪
Grandma, Grandpa, and
Gypsy have dosages
of 15 different lethal
chemicals in their systems.
(Sydney sighs)
♪ So put it down ♪
♪ Tonight will be a
night to let it go ♪
♪ The place is rocking ain't
no wallflower in sight ♪
Since Gypsy is a dog,
the toxic chemicals
affected her sooner.
I've got to find the cure soon.
Or else Gyps is dead.
(Sydney sighs)
♪ Everything is everything ♪
♪ Let the boogie say
up jumps the boogie ♪
♪ To the rhythm of
the boogie to be ♪
♪ Can't you see, can't you see ♪
♪ Right here, right now
is the place to be ♪
♪ Ain't no need to
worry about yesterday ♪
♪ Just make a bee-line
for tomorrow ♪
♪ Put it down ♪
♪ Tonight will be a
night to let it go ♪
(whistle shrilling)
(upbeat big band music)
(dramatic big band music)
(people chattering)
- All right, all
right, all right.
I'd like to thank
everybody for coming out
to Club Charlie's tonight.
Right now what we'd like to do
is we'd like to slow it down.
So every guy, grab a girl, and
let the music take you there.
(audience applauding)
(gentle music)
- (sighs) We should go.
- One more dance.
- No.
I have to find Sydney.
And what about
your little friend?
- Cat, do you know what,
what song they're playing?
- Of course.
It's our song.
- Cat, come on, now,
baby. Don't, don't cry.
You're gonna ruin your make-up.
You look so beautiful tonight.
- Oh, you mean because
I'm young, Gene?
- No.
No, no.
The truth is I,
I always think you
look beautiful.
You were right, Cat.
I mean, I, I just
been fooling myself.
You know, just pretending to
be something that I'm not.
God, I, I miss you, woman.
I miss you.
(gentle music)
- This isn't real.
This isn't real.
- Sure it is! Cat,
I, I love you!
- I know.
You've always loved young,
new, and exciting things, Gene.
- Cat, for as long
as you have known me,
is that what you think?
- Just like you loved
that job in Australia.
- Cat, that was, that
was over 20 years ago!
- For you, it was
over 20 years ago.
But I have lived with
that job in Australia
every day of my life.
(gentle music)
(people chattering)
(door clicks)
(Sydney sighs)
Sydney.
You're still up?
- Where have you been?
- What do you mean
where have I been?
- All right, I was worried
about you, Grandma.
Todd has called, like, 15 times.
- Oh.
- And, you know,
by the last call,
he figured you ran
off with Grandpa Gene
and just left him
at the Orange Club.
- Look. a lot of stuff
has happened tonight-
- I'm not finished, Grandma.
See, um, Todd thinks
you're me, okay?
Which pretty much
blows the small chance
that I have ever
had at dating him.
You know, I really want
to be mad at you, Grandma,
but I can't.
- Oh, baby, I'm sorry.
Look, I know what
you're going through.
- (scoffs) What makes you
think you understand, huh?
Because you've been
17 for two whole days?
- I was 17 once
before, young lady.
- Yeah, a long
time ago, Grandma.
You don't know what
it's like living today,
trying to be as
pretty or as thin
as these, these models
in these magazines,
or as hip as these women
in these music videos
or trying to live
in this stupid town
filled with stupid
little people.
No, you don't
understand, Grandma.
You don't understand anything.
- Okay, you're right.
You're right, Sydney. I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have
assumed that I knew
what was going on inside of you.
- Yeah, Grandma, like
that means anything now.
I know you're sorry.
You're always sorry.
And you know what? You always
say things you don't mean.
And you know what, Grandma?
I have to say this.
I really do. You
chased Grandpa away.
And you know what?
Now, you're chasing Todd
away from me. (huffs)
(smooth thoughtful music)
(dramatic music)
(Gypsy whining)
- Don't worry, Gyps. I'm
not giving up on you.
The answer's got to
be in here somewhere.
(dramatic music)
(computer whirring)
(gentle music)
(people chattering)
- Hey, new girl.
Look, I don't know what that
was all about last night,
but if you and Gene
had something going on
at your previous school,
which I find very hard
to believe, it's over.
- Over.
- Look, the rules of this school
is that my men are off limits.
That includes my brother Todd.
Loser girl knows that
and now you do to.
- [Friend] You've been warned.
- What is her problem?
- Yeah, and my name's Julie.
(bell ringing)
You know, just like
an M.P.G.I.S. chick.
- What the heck is that?
- Most popular girl in school.
(people laughing)
(upbeat hop hop music)
I still think that you should
go to the dance tonight,
because if you don't,
Ashley will think she won.
- Yeah, but I'm not
thinking about Ashley.
- But you're
thinking about Todd.
Oh, you guys had such
a good time last night,
and, well, right up
until you ran out but.
- Julie, I have to tell
you something, okay?
Can I trust you?
- [Julie] Yes.
- Okay, listen.
My little brother
accidentally made a formula
that makes people young
and my grandparents
got exposed to it.
See, now they're our age
and that was my
grandmother last night,
who looked exactly like
me when she was my age,
but now she is my age, so
she looks like my twin.
That's who ran out
with Todd last night
because she was trying to
make my Grandpa Gene jealous
while making out with Todd,
only I ran in and saw everything
and now we're not
speaking to each other.
- What?
- (sighs) Oprah helped me
find my long lost cousin
and she was the one
who ran into the club
last night with Todd.
Not me.
- Oh. Oh!
Well, why didn't you
just say that? Jeez.
Gosh, you know. Oh, my goodness.
I, what are you gonna do now?
- I don't know.
I just have to, you know,
get my head together.
(Sydney sighs)
- Julie.
- Yeah, that's my name.
You guys are identical.
That's uncanny.
I didn't even need
my tarot cards
to tell me that. (chuckles)
Well, I think you
guys need to talk,
and I'm gonna go, so,
can you lock up for me?
- No, no. Julie, I--
- Thank you. Bye.
(Sydney huffs)
- Sydney.
- What?
- You know, I spent
the entire day
sitting in the park
thinking about you.
- (scoffs) Please.
- And you're right.
I did chase your
Grandfather away.
It was all because of this,
this job in, of all
places, Australia.
Your grandfather
wanted to go so bad.
But I was afraid.
New people, new places.
I was afraid of a change,
but I couldn't tell
him he couldn't go.
So I told him he could go alone.
And that I'd follow him.
- And did you?
- No.
(Sydney sighs)
I never intended to.
But I convinced myself
that if he loved me,
he'd come back.
And the next thing I know,
I'm, I'm filing for divorce,
something that I have
always regretted.
- I'm sorry, Grandma.
I didn't-
- It's okay.
(gentle music)
- [Sydney] You still
love him, don't you?
- Very much.
- Well, Grandma, why
don't you just tell him?
- That's what I intended to do.
But Sydney, everybody's
afraid of new places.
- I'm not afraid.
- Oh, girl, please.
You sound like somebody I
used to know long time ago.
Someone who let fear
and pride keep them
from the one they loved.
You remember that
time I told you
to make this new
experience a positive one?
(gentle music)
(sighs) I'm afraid I haven't
been taking my own advice.
- Yeah, but, Grandma,
this, this is different.
- Is it?
Baby, don't make the
same dumb mistake I did.
Now, if you like this
boy, you better tell him.
- How?
- At the dance tonight.
(sighs) Now, let's
go get our men.
(both laughing)
(Gypsy whines)
(upbeat music)
(water whooshing)
- Come on, Gypsy.
(Gypsy whining)
- Oh, I got mad love for myself.
I just want to jump
back, kiss myself.
Look at that. Mm.
- Can you see any growth?
Can you see any growth?
- Whatever, y'all.
Look at me, babe.
- [Terrence] Please,
guy, you've got to ask?
- Leo] I'm ballin'. I'm
ballin, look at this.
- [Terrence] You frontin', guy.
- Player.
- Hey.
- Player. Oh, my.
Oh, my. Why, why?
- Please, go ahead, brother.
- You're doing too
much, my brother.
- Dude, what's with this hat?
You look like you're from
the 1800s. I don't know what.
- Look, guys.
I've been thinking.
You know, this life,
it's not for me.
But I want to thank you guys,
you know, for helping me out.
It's been fun.
- Dude, come on.
Lose these frown
lines, will you?
We're your boys. For real.
Together forever.
- Ta-da!
- Hey, hey, hey.
I'm never gonna
forget about you two.
- Well, how could you?
Look at us. Come on.
- True dat, true dat.
So my man, what are you saying?
Are you leaving?
I mean, you can't
bail on us now.
We need you for the
hotties to stick around.
- That's true, we
do need you, bro.
- Look, fellas, life is
not all about the hotties.
You know, maybe when
you're young, it is.
And when you're
young, youth is fine.
But there's nothing
wrong with growing up.
(gentle music)
Understand?
- Come on, man. Come on.
Please, man?
- [Terrence] Don't go.
- Hotties, hotties. Hotties.
- [Terrence] Three of us, we
could get something together.
- You heard what I said, okay?
I gotta get out of here.
Now take care of
yourselves, all right?
- Take care of yourself.
- Whatever. Whatever.
(door clicking)
Man.
(door thuds)
Your man got problems.
I mean, what the
heck did he mean
it ain't all about the hotties?
It's all about the hotties.
- True dat.
Bam! That's what
I'm talking about.
(Gypsy barking)
- Gyps, you're okay!
Come on, Gyps, we've got to
hurry up and get to the school
so we can save Grandma.
Come on, Gypsy!
(Gypsy barks)
(smooth jazzy music)
(people chattering)
♪ Oh, oh ♪
- [Photographer] Pose for
a photo for the yearbook?
- Oh, hi.
Well, another success!
God, I'm good.
Now if you'd just take
off that silly hat,
everything would be perfect.
- [Gene] Look,
I'm sorry, Ashley,
but this is the new me.
- Oh, well, it won't
be when I'm through.
Looking for someone?
- No.
(clears throat)
- Listen, Gene, you know the
only reason that I brought you
is because there's no one
else here at our level.
So I'm warning you, if
the new girl shows up,
stay away from her.
♪ Going to have it ♪
♪ Won't you be mine ♪
♪ Oh, oh, such a fine ♪
♪ Got some game to play ♪
(engine rumbling)
(Gypsy barks)
(tires screeching)
♪ You know ♪
♪ I'm asking got some curious ♪
♪ I'm curious ♪
♪ So please say the word ♪
(Gypsy barks)
♪ Serious, baby ♪
(people chattering)
♪ I must admits I'm
curious, curious ♪
♪ Please say the word ♪
- Oh, God.
There's two of them.
- [Todd] Sydney.
- Yes.
- Well, what's going on?
Did I have a date with
you last night or-
- No, you had a date with me.
I'm her cousin, Cat.
Look, I'm so sorry I
fooled you that way.
I was just trying to
make somebody jealous.
- Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Where do you think you're going?
- Ashley, I'm sorry.
(Ashley gasps)
- Hi, Grandpa.
- Hey, baby. You look gorgeous.
- [Sydney] Thanks.
- [Ashley] (muttering)
Out of my way!
- Look, Cat, we have to talk.
And I'm not taking
no for an answer.
- No is the furthest
thing from my mind.
♪ I'm curious ♪
- Maybe you could, um, explain
this to me over a dance?
- I'd love to.
- You would?
- Yeah.
♪ I can't wait
till my tomorrow ♪
- You know what I've been
thinking about all day?
- What?
- Australia.
- Look, I'm sorry
about last night.
- No, no, no. You were right.
I mean, I've been
selfish over the years.
Only thinking about myself.
I should have come home instead
of giving you that divorce.
- No.
I shouldn't have asked for one.
I'm sorry.
- I let you get away, woman.
I've had to live without
you for 20 years.
I'm going to let
you know something.
I'm never letting you go again.
- Neither am I.
(Cat gasps)
- [Gene] You okay?
(Cat groans)
- I feel like a 67-year-old
woman. (panting)
- Cat? Oh my God, Cat.
Cat, hey. Hey, baby!
Hey, somebody, get some help.
- Give her some room.
- Get some help!
- Oh, God.
- Somebody call 911.
- [Sydney] Grandma?
- [Gene] Come on, talk to me.
What are you doing?
Go get some help, boy!
- [Todd] Give her some
air, guys, back up.
- Grandma! Grandma,
are you okay?
Syd, look, I've got the
antidote right here.
We need to get her in a tub
of some type of
water right away.
- The pool! The pool,
come on, let's go.
- [Julie] Where?
- [Gene] Come on,
let's go. Let's go.
- Where do you
think you're going?
No one walks out on me.
- Hey, Ashley, this
is not the time.
- Yes, it is.
- Move.
- Or you'll what?
(blow thuds)
(crowd gasps)
- Come on, let's go.
- Come on.
- [Friend] (gasps)
Player haters!
- [Sydney] This way, guys.
- [Willie] Go, Gypsy.
(Gypsy barks)
- All right, what do we do now?
- Um, here.
Okay, I'm gonna throw this in.
Okay, now they have to jump in.
Syd, it's the only way!
- [Cat] Whoa, what,
What's happening?
- Willie. Willie found a cure.
This is it.
We gotta go.
You gonna come
with me this time?
- Okay.
(dramatic music)
(water bubbling)
(Cat inhales)
(gentle dramatic music)
- Come on, come
on. Where are they?
(gentle music)
(Gene and Cat panting)
- [Sydney] Are you
guys all right?
- It worked.
- Good job, Willie.
- You weren't kidding
about them being your
grandparents, were you?
(all laughing)
- [Todd] Does this
happen all the time?
- [Willie] Watch
out. Come on, Granny.
- [Sydney] Grandpa, I mean it.
- Okay.
- Come on.
(birds chirping)
- Goodness, this is hot.
(Gene laughing)
(Gypsy barking)
- We're home!
- Hey!
- Hey, everyone!
- Willie!
I am your father!
- Well, what are we supposed
to do, start a parade?
(Gene and Cat laughing)
Oh, go on. Stop it, you
old fool. (laughing)
- Mom, Dad, are you guys okay?
- Yeah, everything's fine.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Sure.
- We have got to let
your parents watch
the kids more often.
- Hmm.
- Dad? They named
the baby Brett.
- Brett?
Well, what happened to Gene?
- I like the name Gene.
- And I love the name Catherine.
- Mm.
(both laughing)
- Hey, honey. Uh, what's been
going on since, uh, we left?
Can you fill me in?
- Life, Dad. Just life.
- Everybody, I have an
announcement to make.
How would you feel about
a wedding in the spring?
- Oh, sugar, honey,
iced tea, Gene Donovan.
Are you saying what I
think you're saying?
(gentle music)
- Will you marry me, again?
- Oh, Gene, I can't think
of anything I'd rather do
then spend the rest
of my life with you.
- Mm.
- Oh!
Oh, congratulations.
Oh, okay, I have got to
plan this whole wedding.
Okay, first of all,
I'm gonna have to
call Reverend Smith.
And the florist on 34th.
And Darlene is gonna
have to do your dress.
Oh, you're going to look
so beautiful in white!
- [All] White?
- Peach?
- Peach is good.
- [Gene] Yes. Much better.
- Monique. Um, I have an idea.
Why don't I help you
with the wedding plans?
- Oh, Sydney. (laughs)
I'd love that.
(both giggling)
- [Barry] I think I'm gonna
go upstairs and unpack.
- Okay.
- Your son is in shock.
- The boy is out.
(both laughing)
- See?
You know what it's all about.
(all laughing)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Is it Todd?
- Wait, can you hold
on for a second?
Thank you.
It's for Dad.
Dad, telephone!
Take a message there,
son. I'm in the shower.
- [Sydney And Willie] Dad! No!
(Gypsy barking)
♪ I can't think too
much about tomorrow ♪
♪ The past is done
and gone away ♪
♪ But there was one thing
that I'm certain of ♪
♪ I want to start
my life with you ♪
♪ Again today ♪
♪ So what do you say
we fall in love again ♪
♪ Just like it was
when we first met ♪
♪ So what do you say
we try our love again ♪
♪ 'Cause you know
we belong together ♪
♪ And I know this time
it's gonna last forever ♪
♪ Things we did to each other ♪
♪ I know we both regret ♪
♪ Words exchanged we know ♪
♪ We should have never said ♪
♪ Let's make it right
this time and start anew ♪
♪ Can you please give
me one more chance ♪
♪ To make it up to you ♪
(upbeat dance music)
♪ Hot ♪
♪ Hot, hot, hot ♪
♪ Baby, oh, baby ♪
♪ Where've you
been all my life ♪
♪ You came from out of nowhere ♪
♪ Like the speed of light ♪
♪ Hot ♪
♪ Hot thing, hot thing, yeah ♪
♪ Can I see you tonight ♪
♪ Hot thing, hot thing ♪
♪ Can I see you ♪
♪ Hot ♪
♪ Hot, hot, hot ♪
♪ Baby, oh, baby ♪
♪ Where've you
been all my life ♪
♪ You came from out of nowhere ♪
♪ Like the speed of light ♪
♪ Hot thing, hot thing, yeah ♪
♪ Can I see you tonight ♪
♪ Hot thing, hot thing ♪
♪ Can I see you ♪
♪ Hot ♪
♪ Hot, hot, hot ♪
♪ Baby, oh, baby ♪