"One day, when he was naughty,
Mr Bunnsy looked over the hedge
into Farmer Fred's field
and it was full of green lettuces."
"Mr Bunnsy, however,
was not full of lettuces."
"This did not seem fair."
Not fair at all!
So there you go.
Those are the opening words
to Mr Bunnsy Has An Adventure.
But that is not the story
you will see.
This, what you're watching right
now, is called a framing device,
a story that wraps around
the main story
like a warm blanket around a baby.
Steady there. Right!
Now, we have to get
your story started.
And it's not about cute rabbits
wearing clothes. Not at all!
In fact,
your story
is all about...
Rats!
(SCREAMING)
You've got...
..r-r-rats!
Rats!
♪ Twitching noses, cunning faces
♪ Hiding in the strangest places
♪ Always gnawing, clawing, peeking
♪ Climbing, jumping, squealing,
squeaking
Agh!
Cluck! Cluck!
♪ Greedy for your precious treat
♪ They lick the crumbs
from off their feet
♪ They undermine your soil and ground
♪ Try to catch them, can't be found!
Hey, that cat can talk!
Rats!
You've... got... rats!
Rats! Whaaat?!
♪ Nibbling here, napping there
♪ They widdle on your tableware
♪ You try to poison,
trap and shoot them
♪ Race and chase
and stomp and boot them
♪ They leap with marvellous agility
♪ No beast can match their sheer...
Er... Erm...
..adaptability?
(CHICKEN CLUCKS)
♪ Rats! Rats!
♪ You've got multiplying rats!
♪ You've...
♪ Got rats!
♪ Rats! ♪
There really aren't all that many.
You don't need many for a plague,
not if they know their business.
One rat taking a bath in fresh cream
and widdling in the flour?
Could be a plague all by himself!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
A plague?
We're doomed!
I suppose you want us to pay you
to get rid of them! Me?
Just one lone cat? Against all that?
(COUGHING)
Well, I am good, it's true,
but no, no, no, no,
one cat will never do.
Oh, what, then? What?
You need...
..the Piper.
(PIPER PLAYS MESMERIC TUNE)
(ALL GASP)
That's not the Pied Piper!
Hm! Not the real one, anyway.
Your saviour has arrived.
Come on, pony up!
Oh, it's working!
Yes!
(AWED LAUGHTER)
They're leaving! They're leaving!
Whoaaa!
Ahhh...
(SPLASH!)
(CHEERING)
Yay! No more rats!
No more rats! Whoo!
Hey! Where did the talking cat go?
(ALL MURMUR)
(ALL GASP)
(RATS COUGH & SPLUTTER)
Whose brilliant idea was the cliff?
The swimming
and the water - pfft! - up my nose?
Sorry! Sorry!
That was me! Whoa!
The idea just kind of hit me
and I ran with it!
Ah, that was fun!
Let's do it again!
Ooh! It did provide dramatic flair!
A climactic end to the affair!
Yo! Who thinks Keith here
needs to go for a little swim
himself?
All in favour?(ALL) Aye!
(LAUGHS WEAKLY)
Well, that went well!
Says the cat who's perfectly dry.
(JINGLES COINS)
But look! Cash! Money!
Ahem-hem!
That sound always spells trouble.
Ahem! Morris...
Peaches, Peaches... How many times?
It's "Maurice"!
"Mauriiice."
All right, fine, out with it.
Well, Morris, Dangerous Beans thinks
we shouldn't live by trickery.
Oh?
Is that what Dangerous Beans thinks?
You know, some think
there's a good deal too much thinking
going on, and I think I agree.
Peaches is right.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
With our newfound intelligence
comes a conscience.
We must ask,
"Is it right to trick people?"
But trickery is what humans
are all about!
They're so keen on tricking
each other,
they elect governments
to do it for them!
But does it feel right?
Ahem! What Dangerous Beans means is,
"Do we really need
to keep doing THIS?"
"Doing this"? Well, of course, no!
In fact, I don't have to be here
at all! I'm a cat, right?
There's no end of things I could
be doing, because people like cats.
Instead, I choose to help
a bunch of ungrateful rodents
who are not exactly number one
favourites with humans. Right?
But if I may remind you,
you were the ones who wanted to find
the island paradise.
(ALL GASP)
Paradise...
Bring forth the sacred book.
Hey, hey, Keith!
Hm?
The sacred book!
Oh, yes, yes! Er... Ahem!
There you go.
(ALL MURMUR IN AWE)
Ah, this is where we're headed!
An ideal land,
where animals talk
and live side-by-side with people
in peace!
Oh, look! Animals wearing clothes.
A rabbit who walks on his hind legs
and wears a blue suit.
And there's a rat called Rupert
and a stoat
who goes by the name of Howard.
And Olly the Snake
is a bit of a rascal,
but don't worry, nothing truly bad
ever happens there!
It is paradise!
(ALL GASP)
In the land of Mr Bunnsy,
there are no poisons,
there are no traps!
None of the animals
eats any of the others.
It IS paradise.
We must find this place.
Exactly!
You've been there, right, Morris?
Me? The Amazing Maurice?
Er, no, not personally, no. But I've
spoken to many cats who have.
As we all know, it's an island.
A beautiful faraway island.
And to get to the island,
we need what? Boats. Right?
And to get boats, we need what?
Money. Right?
We have to keep making money.
Understand?
(GULPS)
Fine. That's settled, then.
Keith, let's go. Oh! Our next target
is this way. OK, coming!
Oof!
(SIGHS) Perhaps... one more town.
(ALL) Yay!
(JOLLY FLUTE MUSIC)
Now, in fact, Morris was lying.
That's the beauty
of the framing device, see?
I get to tell you stuff about this
story you wouldn't otherwise know.
Like, I can tell you that Morris
never spoke to other cats
because no other cat
could speak back.
Morris was as unique as the rats!
He knew money was important, so he
lied to the rats to make more of it.
In truth,
he was building himself a nest egg
so he could make good
on his deluxe retirement plan.
And now you know Mr Bunnsy
is important to the story
because the rats believe he is real.
They think they can find a land
where all the animals talk
and live happily ever after.
"Farmer Fred opened his door
and saw all the animals
of Furry Bottom waiting for him."
"We can't find Mr Bunnsy!"
..they cried.
If that sounds ominous
it's because it's called
foreshadowing.
Which is kind of a promise to you,
letting you know
that if you keep with the story,
it's going to get...
..ugly. Really ugly!
You, my dear fellows,
are the best rat catchers around
and you've done a great job,
of course you have.
There are no rats
anywhere in the town!
Thank you, Mr Mayor!
That we can see.
Er, what's that?
It's just that,
well, the food in the town
continues to...
..disappear!
It's just...
..gone.Huh?
Poof! Uh?!
(SIGHS)
(BELLY GARGLES & RUMBLES)
We are in the midst of a famine!
What are you trying to say?
Or, in fact, saying?
What I am trying to say,
or at least imply, strongly,
is that there must be a connection!
Connection?
The rats? The food?
It's rather strange, isn't it?
Talking of strange, that, er,
new fellow in town, your employer,
what's his name, It's, er...?
Boss Man.
(LOUD RUSTLING) Yes, yes, yes.
Well, with all those clothes
and that scarf and the hat,
I-I can't really see him,
you know, your boss, I mean.
(CHUCKLES)
Strange, you say?
Er, not that strange!
Have you considered
that what you have here,
with the missing food,
is a mystery?
Mystery! Oh, yes! That's correct!
And with the rats gone,
none to be found,
that factor is simply...
..unrelated.
Unrelated!(LAUGHS WEAKLY)
Mm-hm.
(SHUDDERS)
Always nice to do business with you,
Mr Mayor!
(GIRL) Mum?
What is it, love?
I'm hungry!
How about we pick leaves from the
ground and make leaf sandwiches?
With no bread. Just leaves.
And imaginary jam.
(GIRL WAILS)
Stay low. Quiet as mice.
Remember, this is a new town.
There's bound to be new traps
and poisons.
(GRUNTS & GROANS)
Allow me.
Why do we wear clothes?
It makes no... sense!
Unless we're on stage! (HUMS TUNE)
Dangerous Beans says it's civilised.
And the concept of the belt
is worthy.
You never know
what you're going to need next.
Move on!
All right, let's stop here!
Number Three Platoon - In-Brine,
Sell-By, Sardines and Delicious,
you're on widdling duty.
Go to it!
If I don't hear ladies screaming
and running out of their kitchens
within ten minutes,
then you're not the rats
I think you are.
Number Two Platoon -
Big Savings, Best Before,
Special Offer and Do Not Enter,
you're on trap disposal.
Use caution. Never rush, never run.
We don't want to be like
the first mouse, eh?(ALL) No!
Right! What mouse do we want to
be like?(ALL) The second mouse!
Because?(ALL) Because
the second mouse gets the cheese!
You have a question?
Er, what does the first mouse get?
(ALL GASP)
(SLOW DRUMBEAT)
(RATS MURMUR)
(GULPS)
The trap. See?
And then the Bone Rat comes for ya!
The Bone... (VOICE QUIVERS) ..Rat?
Mm-mm.
All right! Go! Go! Go!
Keith and Maurice
will be in position soon.
(RAT SCURRIES)You know what
worries me, Dangerous Beans?
What is it that worries you,
Darktan?
There aren't any local rats here.
Normal rats, you know?
Rat tunnels? Yeah.
Rat droppings? In abundance!
But we've seen no actual rats.
A town like this
should be full of 'em.
Hm. It smells, doesn't it?
Yeah. It smells.
It smells like a...
A mystery.
Hm. It's still all quiet.
Sounds like the lads
didn't start their plague show yet.
50 cents for every dead rat?
They seem serious.
50 cents! Huh! Must be a rich town.
That's good. That's very good.
It means more money for me. Oh!
For us! For us, of course! (CHUCKLES)
Yeah, looks like a town
with opportunities.
But have you noticed...
..there's no food?!
That is odd! For a market town.
Yeah. Especially when you're hungry.
Which is my way of saying,
"I'm really hungry!"
Oh, look, this one's open! Ahem!
Good day to you, sir!
We're looking for... food?
Yes, well, there you go.
Right under your nose.
Oh. Well, I guess, erm,
how much for the...
Too late. Huh?
It's gone.
No, but we're very...
And now we're closed. Sorry!
Have a nice day!
Maurice, what... What do you think?
Maurice?
(GASPS) Maurice!
Agh! Oof!
It has everything you would
traditionally want in a kitchen,
except for something to eat.
Maurice, please, let's go,
before someone...
Quick, scratch me on the head!
There's a girl looking at us.
What?
Who's to say a narrator can't also
appear in the story she's telling?
Did that cat just say something?
Huh? Cats can't talk!
Everybody knows that.
Ah, I get it.
You brought the cat here
because you know there's a famine
and you're going to sell it.
There's at least two good meals
on those bones.
What? You eat cats here?
Ha! Got you!
Yep, she got ya.
Mm.
Well, there's some milk
that's not gone hard yet,
and a couple of fish heads.
That will have to do.
Do? That will be ideal!
But maybe we shouldn't eat your food
if there is so little?
No, no, no. My father, who happens
to be the mayor, by the way,
says we need to be hospitable.
So tell me your name.
Er, Keith.
Oh, that won't do!
No hint of mystery.
It just hints of... Keith!
Are you sure that's your real name?
I don't know. I'm an orphan.
Ah, yeah! Mm! That's more like it.
A mysterious past.
You were stolen at birth, I expect.
You're probably the rightful king
of some distant country
and they found someone
who looked like you and did a swap!
In that case,
you'll have a magic sword,
only it won't look magic, you see,
until it's time for you
to manifest your destiny!
You were probably found on a
doorstep. Er, actually a hay cart.
Just as good! Hey, it's customary
when somebody asks your name
to reciprocate and ask them theirs.
(SPLAT!)
I'm Malicia Grim, by the way.
Er... Hello,
erm, Malicia.
Nice, erm, to... (STAMMERS)
No! Sardines! Back!
(SHRIEKS) Rat!
(HUMS TUNE NERVOUSLY)
Sardines, no!
Easy on the tap dancing!
Sorry! I've just got these...
..d-dancing feet!
Whoa!
Ugh!
(TREMBLES)
All right.
I think it goes like this...
This rat is clearly a magical rat.
I bet he's not the only one.
Born that way, or something happened
to him, or them,
and now they're quite intelligent,
despite the tap dancing.
And the cat is friends with you...
Why would rats and a cat be friends?
There must be some kind of
an arrangement. No, don't tell me!
I shouldn't think anyone
ever has to tell you anything.
Something to do with
plagues of rats, right?
All those towns we've heard about?
You got together with Keith here
and you go from town to town
pretending to BE a plague of rats,
Keith pretends to be a pied piper
and they all follow him out
and you make loads of cash, right?
It's all a big swindle.
She's got us bang to rights, boss.
You won't tell on us, will you?
Ha!
A talking cat
and a talking, tap-dancing rat?
They'll think I'm making up stories
again
and I'll be locked out of my room
as punishment. Locked out?
So I can't get to my books. It might
not be obvious, but I read a lot.
My father says "Too much!"
(ALL) Ah!
So, here's the question -
how did you learn to talk?
In a real story,
this is where we'd get a flashback.
Flashback? What's that?
It's where you get the backstory.
Go ahead, tell me what happened.
There doesn't seem to be a way
to tell her no.
What happened? Er...
No-one knows for sure, you know,
but, erm...
Rats eat rubbish. That's what we do!
That was back when we were just
normal, everyday rats,
squeaking and squabbling.
We ate whatever we could find.
The stubs of candles, for example!
We love candle stubs!
And a weather-beaten broomstick.
That can be good to get your teeth
into. And powders and potions.
We drank green bubbly stuff
from the bottoms of cauldrons
and gnawed our way
through worn-out spell books.
Ha! Doesn't sound like an ordinary
rubbish heap!
We eventually figured that out.
The dump belonged to
Unseen University of Ankh-Morpork...
..the establishment of learning,
where magic is studied.
All the mixed-up magic leftovers
from the men in pointy hats!
I like it.
Once we got smart,
we learned to read
and gave ourselves names from
the things we found in the dump.
"Sardines."
"Peaches."
(TRIO) "In-Brine!"
What of the cat?
Cats don't eat any old rubbish.
Decidedly not!
He never ate anything off the dump,
but he did get intelligent
around the same time.
As an intelligent cat, I do vow,
and it is a point of pride,
to not eat anything that can speak.
I know just what we must do next
to solve the mystery of our town!
Huh? What mystery?
The missing food! The rats are gone!
Why else would you be in this story,
if not to solve the mystery?
We need to sneak into
the Rat-Catcher's Guild
and find out what they're up to.
Ah. I am oddly compelled to follow.
It's a gift.
I'm off to get my adventure bag.
Yah! Ready?
Let's go!
I think I love her.
(GOBBLES GREEDILY)
Er, sir?
You, er, you wanted to see us,
sir.
There are new rats in town.
Are you sure, sir?
(CHOMPS NOISILY)
The traps are empty. We...
I can feel it!
Catch them and bring them to me.
Yes, sir! Right off, sir!
You know I have a thing...
..for rats.
(SIGHS) Important safety tip.
Don't eat a dead rat
that just ate something,
that made it dead.
Dangerous Beans says
we shouldn't eat rats at all.
True. Very true.
Unless you're hungry.
But rats are always hungry.
My point exactly.
Strange.
Reminds me of, erm,
a Prattle and Johnson
Little Snapper,
but those are not round
like this one.
Mm...
Ah...
And there's no extra safety catch.
I think we need... Mr Clicky.
(HUSHED WHISPERS) Mr Clicky!
Come on, Mr Clicky.
(ALL MURMUR)
Mr Clicky!
Oy, good luck, buddy!
It's showtime, Mr Clicky!
Go, Mr Clicky, you can do it!
On the double, soldier.
What are you waiting for?
(MR CLICKY SQUEAKS)
Time to do your duty.
Mr Clicky?
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?!
Come on, lad!
You're made of metal. This...
can't... hurt.
Ugh!
Darktan?!
(ALL GASP IN SHOCK)
Wh... What?
(GASPS)
What is this?
Ingenious. Never seen this before.
It's a cage.
A cage.
(GASPS) A cage!
What's a cage?
It's used to capture a rat.
Who would want to keep a rat?
(CACKLES)
"And because of Olly the Snake's
trick with the road sign,
Mr Bunnsy did not know
that he had lost his way."
"He wasn't going
to Howard the Stoat's tea party."
"He was heading into the Dark Wood."
(BELLOWS DRAMATICALLY)
She seems to think that it's no good
looking inconspicuous
unless people can tell
that you are being inconspicuous.
The trouble is, your lady friend
thinks life works like a fairy tale.
Mm. That's harmless, though,
isn't it?
Maybe. But in fairy tales,
when someone gets hurt...
..it's just a word.
Hm?
Luckily,
I'm prepared for every eventuality.
The grapnel and the rope ladder
take up a lot of room.
And then there's the medicine kit
and the kettle, the back-up kettle,
the sewing kit...(GASPS)
..and the mirror for sending signals
and these!
Hair pins? You just push it
into the keyhole and twiddle.
Malicia, those things work
in stories, not... That's right!
Oh, dear me. So,
we're back in your story, are we?
And what am I in your story?
Mm, not sure. You're not handsome
enough for a love interest
and you're not funny enough
for comic relief.
Maybe you're just
the sympathetic friend
who serves as a sounding board to
help me resolve my ethical dilemmas.
H-How is it you know
how to pick locks?
I told you, they lock me
out of my room to punish me.
I've seen thieves at work,
"cat burglars" they call them
because they are nearly as clever
as cats.
They have complicated little tools
which are used with great care
and precision.
They don't ever just...
(LOCK CLICKS)
There we are!
That was luck.
(DOOR CREAKS)
Oh, no! I didn't expect this!
Well, it's a dirty room full of junk,
what did you expect?
I was expecting something horrible,
yet interesting.
Some ghastly clue
that would advance the plot.
The world doesn't have a plot. Things
just happen, one after another.
Pfft! There's always a plot.
You just have to know where to look.
Ha! That's it!
A secret passage, of course!
Everyone, look for the entrance
to the secret passage!
What does a secret passage
look like?
Well, it won't look like one,
of course!
Oh, well, in that case,
I can see dozens of secret passages.
Er, I don't know
how to look for something
that doesn't look like
the thing I'm looking for.
Agh!
I know it's a rather daring idea,
but suppose there might not be
a secret passage?
There has to be!
But they're hard to find.
And then you give up,
and it's when you give up and lean
against... that wall,
that you inadvertently operate
the secret switch!
Huh...
I'll just rest my arm innocently
on this coat hook.
And look! A sudden door in the wall
miraculously...
..fails to appear!
Clearly, certain villains
totally fail to know
how to design
a proper secret passage.
Keith, look!
Hey! Why is there a rat hole
in a rat-catchers' building?
I wouldn't come near this place
if I were a rat.
Yes! That often happens in stories!
The stupid person comes up
with the good idea by accident!
There's a sort of little lever
in there.
I'll give it a... push.
Agh!
(GASPS)
A trap door! Quite well-hidden.
No wonder we didn't see it!
Keith! Are you all right?
Not hurt!
Much.
It's a sort of a cellar.
I'm all right
because I landed on my head.
Here's a ladder.
Why didn't you use it?
I was unable to take advantage of it
on account of...
(GRUNTS)
..falling past it.
Where's my hat?
Ahh!
Oh, my goodness!
Huh?
Food!
(DREAMY MUSIC)
Smoked ham!
Mmm! So good!
Wow!
Over here!
(THROUGH MOUTHFULS)
I found the bakery section!
So they are stealing food...
..mostly at night,
for some undetermined purpose.
Those are the best mysteries!
The more they are solved,
the more mysterious they get.
All right, speak up.
Agh!
Just say a few words.
Or a poem maybe? What about a lim...
Agh! Peaches!
It's you! Put me down! Do you mind?
Oh! Of course!
Keith! Sardines! We're in...
Ah, don't worry, I know everything!
We're in trouble!
You won't believe what we've found!
I did ask you if you could talk,
didn't I? Yes, you did, but...
I'm quite vigilant about asking,
you know.
Yes, yes! You've made your point!
I believe you!
But we're still in trouble!
Why? What's wrong?
(SQUEAKING)
Mr Clicky?
What are you doing here? When I get
my hands on that wind-up toy...
Darktan! Are you hurt?
Ugh!
Pfffff! Just my pride.
Here,
let me handle this.
Where is he? I will crush
that useless piece of tin!
(SQUEAKING)
Stop!
I just want to talk to ya.
It won't hurt!
Well, it will just a little!
Back off, Mr Too Many Belts!
It's not cool to pick on
the little guys.
He had one job to do!
You're safe with me now.
(MR CLICKY COOS)
Huh. So this is what they do.
Yeah.
This is new. Insidious.
These traps, very cleverly designed.
It would have to be to capture you!
They are designed
to take us prisoner.
Prisoner? What for?
(LAUGHTER)
That's pretty much our business,
don't you think?
I knew you were a part of this!
Ha!
Tell us a story, story-telling girl!
You're stealing food, somehow,
for some reason.
To feed the rats you've captured,
maybe, and must be hiding somewhere.
You don't need to be clever to see
that this is a bad situation
and might need running away from
quite soon.
..so that's why the food
went missing. Get them!
Come here!
Such as now.
Oh, you think Malicia is the only
person who can comment on the story?
(SLO-MO SCREAMING)
Well, she thinks the story
is about her, but it's not.
Check out the title
if you harbour any doubts.
(SCREAMING)
Oh, I hate cats!
Rats served on a silver platter!
Get that thing off my foot!
Boss Man will be very happy!
And now the kids!
Let go of me!
Go and tie 'em up somewhere. Let go!
Hey, look! The rat.
Why is it wearing a hat? Hm?
Huh!
(SARDINES HUMS JOLLY TUNE)
Billy, look at that! A show-rat!
Oh, don't look at me like that,
like I'm abandoning my friends.
I'm a cat,
and cats choose their battles wisely!
Hey, Billy!
He'd be good for the pit.
We'll call him The Rat With the Hat!
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTING & GROANING)
(SIGHS)
(DARKTAN GROANS LOUDLY)
What are they keeping us for?
Normally, a rat is trapped
and then...
(CHUCKLING)
What's so funny, Dangerous Beans?
Maurice! I knew you wouldn't
let us down, old friend!
I've always said,
"We can depend on Maurice."
Never a doubt.
Mm. Right.
I saw you rush off to start looking
for us, even before we were caught!
Ooh! Hey!
So, what's your plan?
First, we get out of here.Excellent.
Then get as far away from this town
as possible.
Yeah. After we rescue Sardines.
You left out that part.
Yes.
An oversight.
Let me go over it again.
First, we get out of here,
then...
Ahem! Plus the boy and the girl.
They're tied up in another cellar.
We have to rescue them, too.
Oh! Humans, you know!
They'll eventually work it all out,
deals will be struck!
We have to find out
where they took Sardines.
Perhaps you heard them mention...
the pit?
(FOREBODING MUSIC)
I was in a place once,
a storage building.
Some men came in and put a big
round wall in the middle of the floor
and called it... the pit.
'(SCREAMING)'
They had a box of rats
and tipped them into the ring
and then then they put in the dogs.
Terriers. '(BARKING)'
The rats fought the dogs?
Fought? No.
Mostly they ran around and around.
It's called rat coursing.
How is it we've never heard of this?
Because there wouldn't be any rats
left to tell you.
(ALL GASP)
(CHAINS CLANG)
Right, then.
Peaches, Dangerous Beans, Maurice,
you go free up Keith and Malicia.
Nourishing, Special Offer,
Delicious In-Brine,
we rescue Sardines.
His trail will be easy to follow.
He was widdling the entire way.
So, let's go over it again,
shall we?
You don't have a knife
of any kind?
None. Or some handy matches
that could burn through the rope?
No. Sorry.
Did you even look?
I looked!
(SIGHS LOUDLY)
You know, in many ways,
I don't think the plot
of this adventure
has been properly structured.
(GROANS)
Rrrrgh!
(MAN SNORES)
Keep the pace!
(TAPPING)
All right,
I'm running out of patience.
I'm gonna start to reach here.
This would be the ideal time for you
to discover your secret powers!
Oh! Great idea! Ah, yeah!
Oh...! Yes?
I feel...
(SHUDDERS)
Huh? Huh?
No. Nothing.
Ugh! Are you sure?
When I first saw you I thought,
"He must have some amazing power
that will manifest itself
when we're in trouble."
"No-one could be that useless,
unless it was a disguise!"
No! Look, I'm the kind of person
heroes aren't.
I'm a cheat, part of a rat scam.
What I do is play music
and I do that pretty well,
thank you.
But I am not a hero in disguise.
Sorry to disappoint you.
Oh.
So, you're the commoner
who has to rise to the occasion?
You should've found someone else.
Ow! There's something behind me!
We're gnawing through the ropes!
What? Ow!
Hold still!
Dangerous Beans! Peaches!
It's about time!
Talking animals to the rescue!
Unbelievable!
This is almost too easy!
Almost like - pfft! - Mr Bunnsy.
Mr Bunnsy? What about Mr Bunnsy?
Oh, those are just books
for little kids!
There's a rat and a rabbit
and a snake
and they go around
having adventures.
They wear clothes and talk to humans
and everyone's so nice and cosy.
It is so silly!
My father read them to me
when I was a kid.Erm...
I think you'd better stop.
Morris? Of course,
now I see how simplistic they are!
No subtext, no social commentary.
Doris the Duck loses a shoe?
You call that narrative tension?
Malicia, please stop! What?
You knew! YOU KNEW!
There's no island paradise.
There never was.
You lied to us!
No, I...
Look... No, Peaches, don't!
I never had the heart to tell you.
Peaches, it's all right. No!
Peaches!
Peaches? No!
(SOBS)
Peaches! Come back!
Dangerous Beans, don't...
Peaches!
All their hopes... dashed.
Bad cat! BAD CAT!
Oh, I hate this feeling.
That you've done something wrong?
No! That I now need to do
something good to make up for it.
Like, figure out how to get you two
past the rat-catchers.
Peaches?
Peaches? (SNIFFS)
She came this way.
Peaches, please!
We can work things out.
The book is a lie! You lied to me!
The book is not what matters!
It's what we make of it!
Go away!
(SNIFFS)
I don't think we are alone
down here.
(YELPS)
If you would just stay in one place
till I get to you!
Leave me alone!
Beans?
(GASPS)
Beans? I think there's
something else down here!
(TREMBLES)
(SCREAMS)
Peaches!
Bon appetit.
Hey! It's that cat!
Enjoying your last supper?
(GULPS)
What?
Hey...
What's this? Killalot.
Oh. That sounds bad.
What?!
How did you...
Hey, you stole our poison!
Steal? No, no, no, no,
We don't steal.
We just put it somewhere else.
Set that down. That's dangerous
stuff! And tell me where you put it.
Well, now that you mention it,
I think the cat there
put most of it in the sugar.
(BOTH SHRIEK)
(GURGLING)
Oh, I knew that tea tasted funny.
(SHRIEKS) You...
Don't even think of hurting us.
We might forget
where we left the antidote.
There is no antidote to Killalot!
Oh, but there is. I know a few
experts on the topic of rat poison.
Answers. Now.
You caught rats alive
and crammed them into cages. Why?
I can feel things happening!
(GURGLING)
Don't you know anything
about poison?
Your stomach won't start to melt
for about, oh, 20 minutes?
This is great stuff.
Oh, this is inhuman! (WEEPS)
No, it's extremely human. Your
poisons do it to rats every day.
Now, tell me about the rats
in the cages.
At first, we caught a few!
For the pit!
Then?
We accidentally made a Rat King.
A Rat King?
Is it still alive?
I've never seen him afraid before.
IS IT STILL ALIVE?!
Er, w-what is a Rat King?
Rat kings are deadly evil.
A collection of rats, their tails
knotted together, and then...
We didn't mean to.
We put a handful of rats in a bucket
and later, when we opened the lid...
..there it was!
The rats, together, their minds merge
to form one creature.
It gains consciousness, power,
mind power.
It can dominate and control others.
This is a game-changer.
A Rat King? No. This is too much.
Oh, wait! Where are you going?
I, erm,
I have to go and warn the others!
(GROANS)
Antidote! Antidote, please!
My stomach feels like
there's rats running around in it!
You don't deserve it, but we left it
in that little cellar downstairs.
I should hurry if I were you.
(GURGLING & TRUMPING)
Me, too!
(LAUGHS)
How much poison
did Maurice give them?
You mean the laxative? Lots.
Where is it?
But they should be all right if they
don't take too much of the antidote.
And what did you leave down there
for the antidote?
More laxative.
I've got to find a toilet!
(TRUMPING)
Too late.
The laxative was brilliant.
But giving it to them as an
antidote, as well, that is...
Clever? Narratively satisfying?
Genius!
The genius part is,
I know where to go next.
To the forest!
The Dark Wood?
(OWLS TWEET)
Well, there are trees
and it is dark.
Why?
Don't you know? Don't you read?
There is only one thing
that can control a Rat King.
One! In the entire landscape
of literature!
We have to get it
or all of us are in real trouble.
What?
The pipe of the Pied Piper.
The real Pied Piper!
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS & GROANS)
You hear the words "Rat King"
and you get out of there.
Permanently. That's the rule.
Yep! Lucky me!
And what an end to the story!
The Amazing Maurice barely escapes
with six of his nine lives.
And these little beauties, of course!
(CHUCKLES)
Yep, huge advantage being a cat.
Actually, it's too bad for them
they're not cats.
Hey,
why am I even thinking about them?
I'm not feeling guilty
about this. I'm a cat!
Free to follow my own fate.
My next big adventure.
I think I'll go to sea.
Always fancied being a ship's cat.
Might get a little bit sick,
I suppose, but I'll get used to it.
What a twist!
And it's just getting better!
Malicia?
You've been up here three days!
Do you want some dinner?
I'm coming down soon, Dad!
I promise!
This is not the behaviour
of a normal girl.
Where were we? Oh, yes. Mr Bunnsy.
"Ratty Rupert was the bravest rat
there ever was."
"Everyone in Furry Bottom said so."
"So he was sent to find Mr Bunnsy."
"Little did he know
what was waiting for him."
This must be it.
(SHOUTING) Ten rats in 32 seconds!
Come on, give me a hand.
That's a smidgen over three seconds
per rat!
Let's hear it for
The Blitz From Bad Blintz!
Billy!
(CHEERING)
(SNIFFS) Sardines is not far.
Ready for the next round?
(ALL) Yes!
Give it up for...
..Jacko!
(DOG SNARLS & BARKS)
Are you ready
to rattle?
How long will they last?
Oh, no! This is even worse
than Maurice told!
Sardines is dog food.
Idiots! Work together!
You could strip that fleabag
to the bone!
(DOG BARKS)
(CHOMPING)
That was a quick one!
Six rats in 28 seconds!
Good boy!
All right, folks!
For tonight's main event,
we've got a real treat for you!
You won't have seen a rat like this
before.
We call him The Rat With the Hat!
(CROWD SHOUT)
(GASPS) Sardines!
Your fans are waiting!
(LAUGHS GIDDILY)
Showtime!
And here is the legendary champion,
Brute the Cute!
(CROWD) Aww!
He doesn't stand a chance!
All right, all right, calm down!
We do the Rubber-String-Thing!
You know what to do!
Everyone get into position!
Um, rubber-string... what?
You, come here! Attach the string!
Me?
I don't know if I can...
Quick! Do it!
OK! All right!
(DOG YAPS)
Ten dollars he won't last a second!
Fight!
(CROWD) Oof!
(DOG SNARLS)
(JOLLY PIANO MUSIC)
(SARDINES HUMS LIVELY SONG)
(DOG) Huh?
Get it done!
Double the pressure, half the speed!
♪ Dip-a-doo-ba-da, boo!
What is the rat doing?
The Charleston, I think.
Hurry up!
Wait!
♪ Ba-ba-ba-da, baa! ♪
Now or never! Nearly done!
Come on! Got it!
Sardines, here I come...!
I-I... Oh, YOU!
I thought that I would...
(DOG SNARLS)
Aaaggghhh!
Sardines, we'll get you out of this!
Did the rat just talk?
Don't worry. Stay behind me.
Don't move, I've got you! Huh?
(DOG SNARLS)
Go on, Brute, get stuck in!
What are you waiting for?
He's not in the right position!
I know, I know...
You've spent your showbusiness
career biting rats that ran away.
But rats that fight back...
Huh! Huh!
..they're something new.
(DOG) Huh?
$15 on the talking rat!
(CROWD CHEER)
Come on, you mutt,
or are you gonna chicken out?
(CHICKEN CLUCKS)
Attack!
Ha-ha! Smell ya later.
(DOG WHINES)
Watch it!
(BELL RINGS)
Oh, yes! A brawl!
$20 on...
(CHICKEN SHRIEKS)
Puh! Humans!
(DOG SNARLS)
Hey, little fella!
Come on, then.
(BOING!)
(RATS APPLAUD)
All in one piece? Good.
Thanks, Darktan!
Thanks to all of you!
Mm...
(GROWLS)
Ha! Welcome to the rescue squad!
Mission completed!
Let's go! But stay frosty!
(ALL GROAN)
(GENTLE FLUTE MELODY)
(OWL HOOTS)
What is that, that tune?
Huh? Oh, sorry, was feeling nervous.
It helps me...
Agh! ..if I play. Oof! Ow!
Mm, it was nice.
Say, do you have a princess, or
someone else you are in love with,
who might be impressed
by your heroics?
No, I do not.
Oh, that's too bad,
otherwise you and I
might have been an item.
How could my having someone else
mean I'm right for you?
Plot complications!
Every story needs them.
If you were doing this
for someone else,
I would be the girl
right in front of you
who's obviously much better for you
but you don't see it
and you would realise in the end.
But since there isn't anyone else,
I'm not that girl.
Malicia,
this isn't some story.
That's what everyone's been
trying to tell you.
Listen, orphan boy,
who was probably a changeling fairy
and that's why you can play
amazing music,
I'll tell you something!
I know about real life.
I know people think I'm silly,
but you know what?
Aaaggghhh!
If you don't turn your life
into a story,
you become part
of someone else's story!
And what if your story
doesn't go anywhere?
But it will. It always does.
It has to go somewhere.
(LIVELY FLUTE MUSIC)
(GASPS) There!
(MUSIC STOPS)
There he is!
(HUMS TO SELF)
That's dedication!
He wears his Pied Piper outfit
even in his down time.
(CACKLES)
He looks...
..somewhat intense!
He did once get upset
about an unpaid bill
and magicked an entire town's worth
of children into the woods,
never to be found!
And why did you not tell me that
before now?
(HUMMING STOPS)
The original fairy tales
are the best.
Really quite brutal.
(TREMBLES)
(SNARLS)
(LIVELY FLUTE MUSIC)
There it is!
That's the pipe!
(OWL HOOTS)
Ooh, nice!
Yep. That's it, all right.
I bet he has the whole forest
under his spell.
Peaches?
(SNIFFS) Peaches?
(MYSTERIOUS VOICE)
'Hello, Dangerous Beans.'
What?
Where are you? Show me!
Let me smell you!
'I'm in your head.'
What? How?
'See that small tunnel
to your right?'
'Enter it.'
'I'm up here, Dangerous Beans.'
'Come to me.'
Why?'Someone I think you know
is waiting for you.'
"And as night fell,
Mr Bunnsy remembered,
"There's something terrible
in the Dark Wood!"
(TEA CUP RATTLES)
(GASPS) Ominous!
(GRUNTS)
Hello, Dangerous Beans.
How do you know my name?
I know you better
than you might think.
And, oh, the ability
to read your thoughts does help.
Where is Peaches?
Safe.
Where is she?
Safe, I said!
I'm keeping her quite close.
(SNIFFS)
Oh, don't be afraid!
Rather the opposite.
I would like that you would join me.
Join you?
You are a marvel, Dangerous Beans.
You have a mind to rival my own,
a mind that is thoughtful and wise.
A mind that thinks for many rats,
not just one.
Oh, I send them out each night
to steal food.
The rats grow stronger,
the humans grow weaker.
That is the answer to your mystery!
Mm... One mind is only as strong
as one mind
and two minds are as strong as two,
but put three minds together...
(VOICE BOOMS)
..three minds are four minds
and four minds are eight minds...
..AND EIGHT MINDS ARE...
..one.
Where is Peaches?
No! Help me! Help!
Peaches! Peaches, I'm here!
Help me! It's all right!
It's all right, Peaches, I'm here.
Yes. Yes.
You are here.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, we want the same things,
you and I.
We have plans.
(WHIMPERS)
We want the triumph of rats
over humans!
I harbour a somewhat
different dream.
Individual rats and humans,
living together in peace,
respect and harmony.
(LAUGHS SCORNFULLY)
Like in a story book?
Yes. Exactly like in a story book.
Complete with a happy ending.
Meow!
Ugh!
(SNARLS)
(COINS JANGLE)
Oh, you want to buy your way out?
Hm, something like...
..that!
Agh!(CACKLES)
Morris! It's Maurice.
Ah, you silly cat!
Let's go!
Beans! Come on!
(ECHOES) Silly rat... Silly rat...
Silly Rat... Silly Rat...
I can force you to join me.
Join me... Join... Join... Join...
You'll never fit through!
I'm a cat! If my head fits,
the rest will follow!
(LAUGHS)
It's futile to run
when I'm in your heads!
Don't worry!
A cat always lands on its feet!
Agh!
Aaaggghhh!
(SIGHS)
Agh!
(THUD!)
Oof!
Ah! Maurice!
(MUFFLED) Amazing Maurice.
We have to get out of here!
Get out of town! Fast!
Whoa! Oof!
(THUD!)
What about Keith and Malicia?
We're dealing with a Rat King!
(ALL) A Rat King?! Oh, no!
OK, they can catch up.
(PIED PIPER SNORES & MURMURS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(GASPS)
I'll distract him.
You grab the pipe.
What? He's already asleep.
Well, then, I've done my part.
(MURMURS SLEEPILY)
(FLOORBOARDS CREAK)
I didn't do it mama, I sw...
Mmmmm!
I did... (MURMURS)
(ROUSING MUSIC)
Wow!
Look out!
Huh?
(CLUNK!)
(MUFFLED)I'm sorry, Mr Piper,
but I'm afraid I must insist
that you hand over that pipe.
(KEITH GROANS)
Oh, now, is that so?
Yes, that is so!
Or else I've got this
and I'm not afraid to use it!
That's a fork.
A knife would be too sharp
to carry around in my bag,
so it makes sense for me
to use a fork.
Sir?
(GIGGLES NERVOUSLY) Did you really
steal a town full of children?
Half the things they say about me
are not true!
Well, that's a relief!
No!
He didn't say which half.
Clever girl!
And you look tasty, too! Uh-oh!
I think he just told us which half.
Out to the oven, both of you!
(PLAYS MANIC TUNE)
Ugh!
I think he got us!
(GROANS DROWSILY)
Whaaa? The oven?
This is so Hansel and Gretel.
Now's about the time
a character we almost forgot
will appear unexpectedly
to pay his debt and save the day!
Looks like your story
doesn't have a happy end.
(MANIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
In that case, Keith,
this would be the perfect moment
for you to confess
how you truly feel about me.
How I truly feel about you?
Mm-hm!
Most of the time,
fairly annoyed.
(HIGH-PITCHED NOTES)
Agh!
(SQUEAKING & CREAKING)
(YELPS)
Aaaggghhh...
(SPLASH)
I knew I could count on you,
Mr Clicky!(KEY WHIRRS)
We got it! Let's go!
Now they have the rare
and precious weapon
to defeat the evil Rat King!
Everybody, hurry!
What's all the fuss about?
A Rat King?
Well, that doesn't sound so bad.
It is, believe me.
We need to beat it pronto.
(ALL) A dead end! How do we get out?
Everybody, calm down! Please!
(PANICKED SCREAMING)
Quiet! I'm trying to think!
Agh!
Hey! Watch it!
You watch it!
One rat can think, right?
But a bunch of rats
is just a big animal
with lots of legs and no brain.
As soon as there's trouble,
we're just... rats.
If it's any help, I'm just a cat.
Oh, you are not "just a cat",
Maurice.
Well, we've always wondered
how I got changed,
even though I never ate any magical
rubbish from the wizard's dump.
Yesss?
A mystery.
Well, er, now might be the time.
Did you ever know a rat, quite big,
one ear missing,
had a bit of a speech difficulty?
Oh, that sounds like Additives.
Right?
Oh, no!
All right! All right! I ate him!
I hadn't learned to think yet!
I was hungry!
I ate him and then I got changed,
too!
I admit it! It wasn't my fault.
I was just a cat.
Are you sorry?
Sorry?
Cats are never sorry.
They never regret anything!
Except... Except, I do!
Then, it is all right. Probably.
Yo, Maurice! Give me a hand!
Quick! Right, let's get out of here
once and for all!
What's wrong?
There...
Hello there!
Oh! Retreat!
Back away, everyone! Oh, please,
don't run off! You've just arrived.
Enough with the masquerade!
Show yourself!
Oh, you want to see me?
Well,
here I am!
(RUMBLING)
(SCURRYING)
(HIGH-PITCHED SQUEAKING)
Agh!
(BELLOWS)
Do you see me, white rat,
in your misty eyesight?
Yes, you do see me.
(CHICKEN CLUCKS)
And now, come to me,
my little bunnies!
(RATS GROAN WOOZILY)
What is happening?
I don't know!
Busy day?
(RAT SQUEAKS)
No, come on, everyone.
You have to fight it!
He's too strong!
Maurice, you could get away.
No! No! I-I would rather stay
and stand with my friends.
Er, no, actually,
you could probably get away. What?
And go get help. But we still give
you credit for your noble stance.
But I...
Ah, that fluffy tail is probably
the last we'll ever see of him.
Yep.Bye-bye.Good riddance!
Ahem! Pardon me!
Can we continue? Fine.
Come to me!
Maurice!
Keith!
We've got the Pied Piper's pipe
and we're headed back to town.
Good! I'm off to find
Keith and Malicia
and lead them back
to battle the Rat King!
Yes! Go! Go! Right! Go! Go!
OK, bye!
Yeah, let's call that
a heat-of-the-moment fail.
Yes, that never happened. Let's never
mention that, ever, to anyone.
Deal! So one more time.
Maurice! We have the pipe!
The Rat King is on the attack!
Follow me!
(SNARLS) Come!
COME!
Hey, watch out!
Oh, no!
Together, we will be strong!
I got you!
Your offer is interesting,
but what of those who aren't strong?
(SNARLS)
Agh!
Delicious!
This tickles!
Delicious indeed! The weak are food.
That is how it has always been.
A-ha-ha!
Things are becoming clearer.
No! Ugh! Fight him! For our lives!
For our future!
Yes, join us! I have great plans!
You only have plans!
Well, I have dreams!
You defy me?
Excuse me?!
What was that?
Over here!
You?! Mayor's daughter,
ya foolish child!
Will you please be quiet?
What? Your voice, it's so loud!
Just shut up!
I'm trying to hear the music.
Music?
That's right. Music.
A collection of tonal vibrations
of varying durations,
arranged in a pleasant,
some might even say compelling,
order.
(JOLLY MUSIC)
(WHISTLES BAD NOTE)
(STAMMERS)
(RATS) No! No! Agh!
Malicia,
are you sure this is going to work?
But of course. You just wait.
(RATS SHRIEK)
Humans...
Humans are the vermin of this world.
Aaaggghhh!
Keith!
Humans have tortured and poisoned
and killed,
and all of that is now given form
in me.
We must live alongside the humans!
They trap and course us
for pleasure.
We will teach them to respect
who we are. Arrrgh!
Oh, yes, we will.
With fear!
Keith! (WHISTLES) Keith! Keith!
Oy! Keith!
Oh, why didn't it work?
Keith, this is your story arc.
Remember what you've learned
and use it!
But I haven't learned anything!
Go get him!
Ugh! OK!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Nourishing!
This suuuucks!
Ugh!
Whaaaa!
Oof!
Ugh!
Sardines! Stop!
I'm taking my final bow!
Ugh!
And we would rule
that rat world together,
would we?
We would... co-operate.
Yeah, right!
You co-operate, he rules!
Smart cat.
(JOLLY FLUTE MUSIC)
The stupid kid is making me
seriously angry!
One moment. (SNARLS)
Oh, you really shouldn't have!
You obviously do not know
how a proper showdown ends
for the bad guy!
You'll be...
..destroyed!
Malicia!
You talk too much!
Now, where were we? (MUMBLES)
Oh, yes.
Join me!
Malicia?
Mm?
Keith!
I'm sorry, the pipe,
it's not working.
It's not the pipe, stupid.
Huh?
Just play.
OK.
You will obey me!
Never!
Then, feel my pain!
(GROWLS)
(HARMONIOUS FLUTE MUSIC)
Er... Mm...
W-What's that?
Oh, it's, er...
You!
Huh?
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Uh! Uh! No, no! Enough! Enough!
Enough!
Ahh, it's beautiful!
Sweet music!
Sweet, sweet music.
Over here! Hurry!
Everybody, this way, fast!
Looks like someone discovered
his secret power.
(MYSTICAL MUSIC)
That is beyond ugly!
Well played, Piper.
Well played!
But your music cannot break...
..me!
Come now, Dangerous Beans.
It is time.
No! You are nothing but darkness!
And you are nothing but a rat!
I am more than a rat!
If I am not more than a rat,
I am nothing at all!
Then, be...
..nothing.
Agh!
(GROANS)
Maurice, my friend,
maybe now it's a good time to be...
..just a cat.
(SIGHS)
You see,
the Amazing Maurice, that's me,
had longed to be a proper cat
for months.
I have so much bottled-up
ancestral fight and viciousness
flowing through my veins,
it sparks off my claws!
(HISSES)
The Rat King sends all of his power,
enough to bring down a tiger!
But now, just for a few seconds,
this particular cat
could bring down a tiger
all on...
..his own!
Eurgh!
Rrrggghhh!
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
Beans! No!
Did you save him?
I tried to save him.
Beans?
(SOBS) Beans?!
Dangerous Beans?
Please, no!
(GROANS)
Bone Rat.
Also known as The Grim Squeaker.
You've come for Dangerous Beans,
I suppose?(SQUEAKS)
No. After all we've been through?
Not gonna happen!
Argh!
(SQUEAKS ANGRILY)
All right, mister,
let's hear you talk.
I'll give you one chance.
Unnn!
Desist from attacking my associate,
Morris.
That's Mauriiiiice!
Yes, sir! Mr Death!
Yes, at once, sir.
Oof!
(SQUEAKS ANGRILY)
Good to see you again, Morris.
Hello, sir. Good to see you again,
too.
How many lives do you have left now?
Erm...
Lemme think. Er, six, sir! Six.
Very definitely six lives, sir.
But you were run over by a cart
only last month, weren't you?
Oh, that, sir? No.
Buh-Barely grazed me.
Got away with hardly a scratch, sir.
Exactly.
O-Oh. Oh, I... Yeah. I see.
That makes five lives, Morris.
Sir, please,
take two of my lives.
I would give an extra one
in exchange for the life
of this brave little rat.
That is very un-cat-like of you,
Morris. I'm amazed.
Well, I'm pretty shocked too, sir.
It's just that this one is special.
Wise and inspiring.
Your request will be granted.
We came for two lives
and two we will take.
The balance is preserved.
Thank you, sir!
Oh, sir? I'm not gonna remember
all this, am I, sir?
Because that would just be
too embarrassing.
Of course not, Morris.
Beans!
Please say something!
Beans?
Don't leave me!
Beans...
(GRUNTS)
Dangerous Beans!
I thought you were dead!
I thought so, too!
(SIGHS)
What?
(RATS COO)
Hey!
Ah!
See, the couple of a story
has to kiss
whenever there are people
celebrating around them.
But this is real life?
And a story.
Our story.
Well, in that case...
Whoa!
Mmmm!
Mwah!
(PEACHES SIGHS HAPPILY)
Mm...
(PURRS)
(GASPS) Maurice, is that a purr?
(JOLLY MUSIC)
"Ratty Rupert saved the day,
and Mr Bunnsy's hide!"
"Well done, Ratty Rupert!"
..cried the animals of Furry Bottom.
And that is how the story
of Mr Bunnsy ends.
"But how does our story end?"
you might ask yourself.
Well, in the end,
our story is all about...
♪ Rats!
♪ You've... got...
♪ ..rats! ♪
(CHEERING)
Bad Blintz has become
a tourist attraction!
Ta-da!
People travel from miles around
to visit.
And buy the souvenir mugs
and stuffed toys
and other things which have no use
whatsoever,
other than to be bought
and taken home.
There you go, dear!
The famine is over
and there's plenty of food
for everyone!
(CHEERING) And once a day,
the town's Pied Piper,
whose name is Keith and, actually,
who kisses rather well,
plays his pipes,
and the rats dance to the music
in a conga line.
Ah, Mr Clicky, my lad.
How's the family today?
(BELLS DING)
The rats have a town of their own
and get free use of the library.
And even send their little rats
to school.
In other words,
rodents live happily,
side by side, with people.
Just how Peaches
once dreamed it would be.
Due to the efforts of Maurice,
the Amazing Maurice,
and his educated rodents!
But mostly...
..me!
Meow!
♪ Hey, what you doing?
♪ I got a pocketful of rhythm
for you
♪ And if you don't know
what it is you should do with it
♪ Follow me
♪ Hey, where you going?
♪ I see you looking for your light
but you're glowing
♪ But if you take a look inside
then you'll know
♪ It's gonna set you free
♪ Set you free
♪ Oh, sometimes we get it right
♪ Ah, ah...
♪ And we all get it wrong
♪ But you're always gonna fail
♪ At being someone that you're not,
so...
♪ Be yourself
♪ Cos everybody else
♪ Is taking
♪ And everybody else
♪ Is faking it till they're making it
♪ Be yourself
♪ Cos everybody else
♪ Is taking
♪ And everybody else
♪ Is faking it till they're making it
♪ Be yourself-elf-elf-elf!
♪ Hey, it's been too long
♪ And you've been sticking out
in places you don't belong
♪ But when you find the melody
of your own song
♪ Well, sing along
♪ Sing along
♪ Oh, sometimes we get it right
♪ Ah, ah...
♪ And we all get it wrong
♪ But you're always gonna fail
♪ At being someone that you're not,
so...
♪ Be yourself
♪ Cos everybody else
♪ Is taking
♪ And everybody else
♪ Is faking it till they're making it
♪ Be yourself
♪ Cos everybody else
♪ Is taking
♪ And everybody else
♪ Is faking it till they're making it
♪ Be yourself-elf-elf-elf!
♪ Be yourself!
♪ Oh, be yourself
♪ Be yourself
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ Cos everybody else
♪ Is taking
♪ And everybody else
♪ Is faking it till they're making it
♪ Be yourself
♪ Cos everybody else
♪ Is taking
♪ And everybody else
♪ Is faking it till they're making it
♪ Be yourself-elf-elf-elf!
♪ Be yourself ♪
♪ After all
♪ That we've been through
♪ Who'd have thought
that we'd be here
♪ Take a breath
♪ And look around you
♪ Can you hear it loud and clear?
♪ Did you tell yourself a story?
♪ And seen it in your room
♪ Cos I told myself a story
♪ And I just can't believe
that we're living it!
♪ Side by side
♪ You and I
♪ This is all I've ever wanted
♪ I feel like
♪ I can fly
♪ It's some superpower magic
♪ And all my life
♪ All my nights
♪ I would give them all to you
♪ Side by side
♪ You and I
♪ This is all I've ever wanted
♪ I had dreams
♪ Of a hero
♪ Out of nowhere you appeared
♪ Sweet, sweet music all around you
♪ Everybody wants to hear
♪ Cos I told myself a story
♪ And I just can't believe
that we're living it!
♪ Side by side
♪ You and I
♪ This is all I've ever wanted
♪ I feel like
♪ I can fly
♪ It's some superpower magic
♪ And all my life
♪ All my nights
♪ I would give them all to you
♪ Side by side
♪ You and I
♪ This is all I've ever wanted
♪ And I just can't believe
that we're living it!
♪ Side by side
♪ You and I
♪ This is all I've ever wanted
♪ I feel like
♪ I can fly
♪ It's some superpower magic
♪ And all my life
♪ All my nights
♪ I would give them all to you
♪ Side by side
♪ You and I
♪ This is all I've ever wanted ♪
AccessibleCustomerService@sky.uk