Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[Keisha] This my
bitch Pritty right here.
Every time I call her, she be on the go
so I love her.
[eerie music plays]
Clear.
[Keisha] See, this
my man Var right here.
Well, we used to be cool.
He gave me all the game in the world
till my world started coming down.
Now this nigga's on the menu.
[Var] Y'all fucking bitches.
Think I'm fucking playing with y'all?
I got something for you.
[gun shots firing]
Y'all fucking bitches.
You think I'm fucking playing with y'all?
I got something for you.
[gunshots continue]
[shouting indistinctly]
Shit.
[upbeat music plays]
[woman shouts indistinctly]
Oh, shit, the fuck?
[gunfire continues]
[indistinct shouting]
I'll fucking kill you, bitch.
Where the fuck that bitch go?
Fuck, I'm tired of this
bitch getting away, yo.
[theme song plays]
♪ Pray before you eat everyday ♪
♪ Hungry niggas in the
world straight starving ♪
♪ Before you eat, say grace ♪
♪ Hungry bitches in the
hood straight mobbing ♪
♪ Pray before you eat everyday ♪
♪ Hungry niggas in the
world straight starving ♪
♪ Pray before you eat, say grace ♪
♪ All my bitches in the
hood straight mobbing ♪
♪ Shake like me ♪
♪ Bet you never seen a clique like mine ♪
♪ Shake your dick real quick ♪
♪ One slip, you're my bitch ♪
♪ You'll be staring down
the barrel of my nine ♪
♪ You ain't know we got a hunger ♪
♪ That run deeper than the scars ♪
♪ We out here living like pythons ♪
♪ They see you coming but
we fuck you with lights on ♪
♪ Suck you dry, speed off in
the truck with brights on ♪
♪ I'm from the borough
where the planes fly low ♪
♪ Where niggas committing
jokes in the name of survival ♪
♪ One hand in the air, one on the Bible ♪
♪ Money over everything ♪
♪ We preaching like gospel ♪
♪ Keep the head to the streets
for pigs in plain clothes ♪
♪ My haters pull up to your spot ♪
♪ Nigga, it's case closed ♪
♪ Sitting there smoking ♪
♪ Speed off in a Range Rover ♪
♪ Bet you never met a chick like me ♪
♪ Bet you never seen a clique like mine ♪
♪ Shake your dick real quick ♪
♪ One slip, you my bitch ♪
♪ You'll be staring down
the barrel of my nine ♪
♪ You ain't know we got a hunger ♪
♪ That run deeper than the scars ♪
♪ We out here living like pythons ♪
♪ They see you coming ♪
♪ But we fuck you with lights on ♪
♪ Suck you dry, speed off in
the truck with the brights on ♪
♪ Pray before you eat every day ♪
[eerie music plays]
[men speaking Russian]
No, no. Club scene's very good.
Solid. Money's going through, no problem.
I think we can start new accounts,
maybe even get a little
bit more of the money.
Hello?
What do you mean we got robbed?
I need Ivan. Pass me the phone.
Come on, come on.
Ivan, get some people together.
You're heading to New York.
[Keisha] See, this is Sha right here,
the neighborhood hero.
Supplying all the locals,
getting money ass nigga.
Var got this nigga on the play.
♪ I'm playing with them bands ♪
♪ I ain't talking music ♪
♪ Don't believe me ♪
♪ Just take a look at how I do it ♪
♪ I'm heading in with a plan ♪
♪ Boy, ain't nothing to it ♪
♪ Come back and do it again, boy ♪
♪ Ain't nothing to it ♪
♪ I'm playing with them bands ♪
♪ I ain't talking music ♪
♪ Don't believe me ♪
♪ Just take a look at how I do it ♪
♪ I'm heading out with a plan ♪
♪ Boy, ain't nothing to it ♪
[vacuum whirring]
Hey, Sha.
What's up, sis?
What's up?
How's everything?
Can't complain. Go have a seat.
Okay.
He in the bathroom.
He'll be out in a minute.
I'ma ask you a question, all right?
What's up?
This a serious question.
How's he holding up?
Yo, he is so annoying, all right?
One minute, he's Mr. Independent,
like I got it, I don't need no help,
all of that good stuff.
But then let me ask him
to do something for me
that he don't wanna do,
then it's like, my back hurt.
You know, I gotta lay down.
It's like, I know that he's hurting,
but he's kinda milking it at this point.
Yeah, that'll be him.
It's that Cory shit.
I'm kinda over the Cory shit, okay?
Yo, Cory!
Well listen, he's back there.
He'll be out in a minute.
I'm going to the store.
See y'all later.
Listen, Cory's a pretty tough guy.
Don't let him drive you
crazy with his bullshit.
See my face?
- Yeah.
- Exactly.
Okay, I'll figure it out.
- [she laughs]
- I'll see y'all later.
Okay, cool.
Hey, Sha.
What's going on, cowboy?
Man, she got me fucked up.
Cut it out, man.
Shit.
Let me get this for you.
I'm good, my nigga, I got it.
Cut it out, man.
I'm not no handicapped, man.
That's the same shit she
was just talking about, man.
Yo boy, I am, my nigga.
She my bitch, my nigga.
I love her, but she be
bugging though, my nigga.
She a real motherfucker.
I'm so tired. What's happening, man?
What's going on?
Shit, my nigga.
How you holding up?
I'm good, man.
Quick and Rock came through, man.
Dropping off some bread to the kid.
Left a bag for you and shit.
I mean, you know I
came to check you out,
but I also came in for the bag.
Yeah, I'm good.
What's going on with that situation?
You know, we've been out here, man.
Man, I'm not even feeling
that motivation, man.
I think this might be our time
to get the fuck up out
this shit, my nigga.
You go with this shit here,
it's this Sharif shit from Menace.
Nah, I'm serious.
I want both of them niggas dead, man.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's it, nigga.
You know how I feel, but
we should make an exit.
Get the fuck out of here, my nigga.
That's some real shit, my nigga.
Because I just did all that time.
I ran into a lot of
niggas, that same shit.
We got the opportunity, my nigga.
Come on, boy, let's get
the fuck out of here.
I mean, I understand
what you're saying, man.
But this what we gotta do.
We gotta kill these niggas.
That so?
We looking bad right now, yeah.
That's cool.
Them niggas is probably
hiding out or something.
Yeah, they hiding out.
You know they playing hide and seek game.
That's what they do.
Just be careful, my nigga.
I'm on it.
Exit. Our plan is to
exit out this shit, man.
Where the bag at?
I gotta get it.
I'll get it, man.
There you go with this shit.
All right, go ahead, bro.
Nah, you can grab that shit.
It's kinda far in the
room over there, anyway.
[dramatic music plays]
Yeah, okay.
All right.
Benny.
I gotta call you back.
I'll call you back.
[Ivan] How many years
have we been together?
Years.
I knew your father when he started.
Explain to me how.
He had a mask on.
Give me the bread.
Give me the fucking bread.
How long has she worked here?
About a year.
[Ivan speaking foreign language]
You still close at 7:00?
Yeah.
Don't worry, business as usual.
All right.
Put up a help wanted sign.
You're gonna need a new cashier.
♪ We was broke until that cheddar came ♪
♪ We was praying for some better days ♪
♪ Now my niggas getting hella paid ♪
♪ One thing never change ♪
♪ Family over everything ♪
♪ We was broke until that cheddar came ♪
♪ We was praying for some better days ♪
♪ Now my niggas getting hella paid ♪
♪ Check it ♪
Ah, Sha.
[speaking foreign language]
On time today, I see.
Here you go.
I apologize about yesterday.
I had a bunch of shit going on,
kinda lost track of time.
What's up though?
A lot of shit, honestly.
Double homicide in a barber shop?
That's quite some shit.
By the way, how's Cory?
How's Cory?
How'd you know about that?
[speaking foreign language]
You think I'm not gonna know
what's going on with you?
We make money together.
I'm disappointed.
Don't be because I got
this shit under control.
I'm not gonna let no bullshit street shit
come between what me and you got going on.
We getting money.
It really is, and this issue you have
is bringing attention.
I don't like attention.
We both know this shit
is bad for business.
Listen, I didn't start this shit.
This shit fell in my lap.
I don't want these problems
no more than you want the problems.
What I gotta do, I have to finish this.
[speaking foreign language]
And this is one of the reasons why
we're having this conversation
instead of a different one.
What would be the different one?
Recent bullshit aside,
you have potential and
the boss wanna see you.
The boss?
All this time, you had me
thinking you was the boss.
Sha, everyone answers to somebody.
I agree.
Now come on, let's go.
I have the car waiting for us.
Sha, what's important?
I'm kinda confused.
You said you had a car waiting for me.
You remember Sophie, right?
From Miami?
Yeah, we got a car and a jet for you.
We gonna fly you out there
and she gonna meet with you.
That means I gotta go
change my clothes then.
Do what you gotta do then.
All right, I'll see you.
All right.
♪ Family over everything ♪
♪ We was broke until that cheddar came ♪
♪ We was praying for some better days ♪
♪ Now my niggas getting hella paid ♪
♪ One thing never change ♪
♪ Family over everything ♪
I got some gorilla glue
and I got some moon rocks.
- [Customer] Moon rocks?
- Yeah.
[Customer] What are they?
Moon rocks, 30 a gram.
[Customer] No, I
ain't fucking with that.
This shit's 40.
- [Customer] 40?
- Yeah.
[Customer] No, I'm good, bro.
All right, I'll see you. Peace.
Yo, my nigga.
Oh shit, what's up, my nigga?
Yo my nigga, I've been in the shop, man,
like three or four fucking
times looking for you.
Son, you know, let me tell you something
about that shop, okay?
That shit is hot as a motherfucker.
Yo, listen, my nigga.
Like yo, man, I'm at the
crib counting the bag.
I look up at the fucking camera, my nigga.
Yo, these bitches is in my crib,
hammers out, my nigga,
creeping, my nigga, so you know me.
I grab the fucking full barrel.
You know what I mean?
Go to open the door,
this bitch is like this.
Nah, son. When did this shit happen?
Slams the door, my nigga.
Starts banging in the fucking crib.
I'm banging, doom, doom, doom, doom.
Yo, that shit's crazy, son.
Throws that shit to
the ground, my nigga.
Grabs the motherfucking mat,
I'm like, yo, this shit too small.
Throw that shit on the floor.
Grab the fucking chopper, my nigga.
Yo, boy, my crib turned
into fucking Iraq, my nigga.
Yo, it's funny you should say that
about these bitches, son.
You know, a couple of months ago, man,
in the barbershop here, I'm cutting hair,
this chick roll up on me asking me
something about the gambling spot.
You know what we do in the back.
Yo son, let me tell you,
that night, I'm back
there rolling dice, man.
Lose all my money, go to
the back and said fuck it.
It is what it is.
All of a sudden, I'm hearing
gunshots in the back.
In the shop?
- In the shop, son.
- Wow.
So I cracked the hammer.
You know I keep that thing on me, right?
All right, all right.
I see some bitches running out.
I caught that last bitch.
You know, I laid her ass out.
As you should, my nigga.
You steamed the shit out that ho.
Now listen, I'ma tell you what it is, man.
Some bitch named Keisha
and she rolling with a
fucking bunch of dyke bitches.
Like, this is what them
bitches do, my nigga.
But it's kinda my fault.
I created this monster,
you know what I mean?
But yo son, I'm here if you need me.
Yo, keep your head to
the ground, my nigga.
All right?
Stay up. That's what's up.
[woman sighs]
[Woman] Look, the feds,
they want any and all
information on those girls
linked to these homicides.
Mainly, they're interested
in a robbery that took place
in the full day
and an undetermined amount of cash
taken from that jewelry store.
They wanna see you in an hour.
Damn, so it's an
undetermined amount of cash.
From a jewelry store?
No tape, no jewelry taken?
They didn't take nothing.
Yeah, that's the feds.
I knew that was them.
Man, you already know.
Anderson!
Pleasure to meet you, Howard.
I've heard nothing but
good things about you.
Same to you, sir.
All right, all right.
Enough introductions.
Look, I need you guys to go out there,
get these bad guys, or rather girls.
Look, be safe.
I'll see you guys later.
[Howard] How are you doing?
I'm looking for Agent Smith.
How's it going?
I'm Agent Smith.
How you doing?
I'm Detective Howard.
This is my partner, Detective Anderson.
Boss man gave us orders to come down here
and help you with whatever you need.
All right, nice to have you aboard.
This is my squad over here.
How you doing?
Agent Lewis.
Turner.
Agent Cruise.
KB.
Yeah, so I mean, hopefully
this a two way street
and we'll get to put an end to all this.
What we got so far.
Our prime suspect is CoCo.
Hm? Nah, uh-uh.
Angel of Death.
Everywhere she go, death follows.
Really? Interesting.
What about the rest of them?
You guys know any of them?
I mean, I might have seen them,
but Keisha right here,
she attached to at least three
homicides I'm investigating.
[KB] Baby, what's up?
Of course. Listen.
I'm in a meeting right now.
Let me get back to you.
Yeah, I got you.
All right, listen.
I'ma send you the address.
Yeah, I'ma cook us something
special tonight, all right?
I'll see you later.
Well our primary suspect is CoCo,
and we're certain that she
is the leader of the pack.
I saw all four of those girls together
while I was undercover at a pool party,
but I don't have any
names for the other girls.
So you guys been onto the group?
Not the group, just the individual.
So our plan is to be part of your team,
infiltrate the whole organization
and find out exactly who they work for.
Who they work for?
Yeah, from all the intel
that we've been getting,
we're finding out that this girl, Coco,
had to have somebody much
bigger in the picture.
Couldn't have done it by herself.
Any leads to her whereabouts?
KB has the leads.
It ain't much longer before he find out
everything we need to know.
We're gonna help you any way we can
and we expect the same in return.
That's what I like to hear.
So I suggest we go ahead
and pick up the homicide suspect
and start putting the
squeeze game in play.
That's what we do.
Put a little fear factor on these dudes,
you'll start getting all
the information you want.
All right.
Sounds like a plan.
All right, bet, let's get these bitches.
- Let's get it.
- All right.
Stop.
[machine whirring]
[geese honking]
[indistinct conversation]
[Sha] Everything good?
So where we going?
You're not even talking?
I don't know where I'm going?
I guess I'm just rolling the dice, huh?
Either gonna be a head cracker or an ace.
Let's roll, baby.
[plane whirring]
[eerie music plays]
♪ It is what it is by now ♪
♪ Ten toes down ♪
♪ Don't fuck up the rear ♪
♪ It's cheaper to keep her ♪
♪ Why would I leave her ♪
♪ This ain't no rap shit ♪
♪ This is the diva ♪
♪ Thinking I'd keep her ♪
♪ We gotta speed up ♪
♪ Don't fuck up the rear ♪
♪ Don't fuck with no snitch ♪
♪ I keep my distance ♪
♪ Flexing them bitches ♪
♪ You don't wanna hit this ♪
♪ We don't pretend ♪
♪ Catching a Tim ♪
♪ Money is spent ♪
♪ I got a gift ♪
♪ Don't fuck up the rear ♪
He's with me.
[Man] Yeah?
[Carmen] Yeah, he good.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
[indistinct conversation]
Yo Po, you know this guy?
[Po] Yeah.
[rap song resumes]
What's up, mami?
What's up?
Sha, this Po.
What's up, my nigga?
What's going on with you, man?
How you doing?
Welcome to Miami, man. You good?
Yeah, I'm great.
That's what's up. This is my city, man.
Those Haitians, you know what I'm saying?
Everything good with you?
Everything great.
That's what's up, man.
You know, my girl Carmen, man,
she been sending me a lot of
great things about you, man.
That was a good job, Carmen.
It's kind of funny because this
is the first I've ever heard of you.
Yeah, well you know
what time it is though,
you know what I'm saying?
A nigga like me, man,
you gotta keep a low pro,
you know what I'm saying?
Like super low profile,
But yo, it's all good bro.
You're here now.
You're here with me, so I'm
gonna make it happen, man.
It was hard getting here.
I got searched about five times.
Thought I was coming to see the Pope.
Yo, like I said, man,
low profile is the key, brother.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Yeah, so, I'm sure she
filled you in already,
so let's get to the business.
This is how I'm gonna do this.
You buy 10 pieces, I send you 30.
I buy 10, you send me 30?
- [Po] Yeah.
- What's the catch?
[Po] Catch is, it's every two weeks.
Consistent.
What you think about that?
At the number I'm getting,
30 pieces every two weeks.
[Po] Every two weeks.
I mean, that's a little challenging,
that's hard.
I mean, I'm sure it's
not the 30 pieces, my dude.
That shit sells itself.
Is it the price?
At the end of the day, I think
you're a pretty smart dude.
[Sha speaks indistinctly]
[Po sighs]
You ain't talk to him?
[Carmen] I'ma leave that to you, Papa.
Aight, man. I think it's the price.
This is what I'm about to do.
I'll take $5,000 off these bird.
What you think about that now?
If you can take five
grand off each bird.
- Each bird.
- We're in business.
That's what's up, brother.
Only problem now,
you have some problems
I've been hearing about.
I mean, it ain't nothing
for me and my niggas
to take care of, you know what I'm saying?
I got that taken care of.
You supply the food. I got that.
I like that.
So we waiting on you then, man.
Sha, my man.
Let's go. Can I go now?
I mean, you could go now.
Okay.
[dramatic music begins]
Benny, I'm leaving.
All right, well, have a good night.
Who do you know?
[scoffs]
I'm going to start
doing whatever I want.
When I am satisfied, I'm
going to ask a question.
If I get the remote inclination
you are lying to me,
I'm going to make what I was doing before
look like fucking hand holding.
So, she talk?
[Man] Nyet.
[Vika laughs]
Vika!
[speaking Russian]
Don't kill her yet.
[Vika speaking Russian]
Go get my chair.
Okay, easy.
All I want to know is who did
you tell about duffel bag?
I don't know.
Okay, enough.
Enough of this.
If I have to get up from my chair,
I am going to cut your
fingers off one at a time.
Just tell me what I need to know.
I don't know.
[cashier grunts]
Just tell me what I need to know
and you can go home.
Okay, okay, I'll tell you.
It's Talib.
You see?
See how easy that was?
Now, I want you to tell me everything
that I need to know about this Talib.
Okay.
Very good, my dear.
You see?
I didn't want to cut
your fingers off anyway.
No, please!
Use the hammer.
[cashier sobbing]
[Cashier] No, no!
[cashier screaming]
Yes, it's me. Look him up.
So some little monkey Talib
hired some little monkey whores to the-
yes, to the bus.
Yes, I know, but look. Listen.
It took me less than 24 hours
to figure all this out
without the help of your little bitch.
You need to let me stay for good.
So I will find this Talib
and I will find these whores
and I'll be back before Sunday.
Fine. Fine.
Yes.
Yo, snap out of it.
[Keisha] See, this is my
grimy ass cousin, Muffy.
She one of the few grimy ass
bitches in the land between.
They lined some getting
money niggas for us
a few times, but there's
something about this bitch
I just can't put my finger on.
No, you don't understand.
I'ma keep it 100 with you.
What the fuck was you expecting?
The picket fence?
The motherfucking house on the prairie?
This life you living wasn't given to you.
Your mom's a G, your daddy
ain't never coming home.
You're bugging.
Like what the fuck was you expecting?
You don't understand,
this man showing me
a whole different lifestyle.
Something I never seen before,
like I ain't ever have to
resort back to the streets
ever again due to this man.
Yo, shit happens for a reason,
and in every worse situation,
you gotta take the best elements out of it
and concentrate on that.
What the fuck are you saying?
Fuck it.
Let me speak in your language, all right?
Speak English.
You gotta take the good
with the bad, Keisha.
You know that.
At this point right now,
I'm going through a lot.
I got niggas after me, bitches after me.
I don't even know which
way to go at this point.
And this is exactly
why your ass need to be
not daydreaming about fucking Jack,
staying focused, and don't
be out here slipping.
Matter of fact, did you
find out who shot your man?
Let me tell you, I had
this nigga the other night.
This bitch Kayla aunt is on my body.
I can't get away from this bitch.
Wait, Kayla's aunt?
Listen, that's the bitch
that wind up killing Jack,
trying to get at me.
She think I got something to do
with Kayla getting killed.
Like this bitch is on me!
Wait, wait, what?
Let me tell you about this.
[slow motion, indistinct conversation]
[gunshot fires]
[Muffy] Wait, wait, wait.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Let me see if I understand.
Tyler kills Kayla but the aunt blames you?
Yeah, and now everywhere I go,
this bitch just been popping up.
I can't shake her.
Popping up, like on some straight
following you shit?
Yo, you need to take care of that.
You need me to stay up here longer?
Because a bitch will cancel her shit.
I'll stay.
Nah, I got this.
I promise you, I'ma take care of this.
Let me get rid of these little
headaches I gotta handle
and I'm coming to see you
because I gotta get the fuck out of here.
Keish, look.
You got a lot of shit going on up here,
but you know my home is your home.
Yo, I gotta go.
I gotta catch this flight.
Fuck it, we outta here.
[Keisha] See, these is
my bitches right here,
Coco and Kyah.
Coco's really my day one,
and Kyah, we got cool
after this one job we did.
I kinda slept on her, but sis gets busy.
I'm thinking about it.
Ain't nothing wrong with that.
I just had to know,
but what that nigga do?
I don't know, he just be telling me
he got some dope investments
and shit like that.
How you don't know?
Here you go, acting like Keisha with it,
with this falling in love shit.
Like, do you even know his name?
I do know his name, and his name's KB.
Hm, okay.
But I'm thinking about asking him
to put us onto this investments
that he so called do,
because I'm trying to make
this money work for us.
Look, I'm all for that shit.
I ain't trying to look back.
Word, but I'm going.
Aight, you got some gas money?
I got you next time.
- [laughs]
- All right.
What's going on?
What it do? What you been up to?
Man, I been chilling.
Yeah, what's going on with you?
Same shit, man.
So where my boy?
He in the back.
Hey, yo!
Hey, what up?
I told you you'd be back for my Adidas.
Kept them out for you anyway.
[Keisha] This is Quick,
Sha right hand man.
He basically handles all the dirty work.
That's about it though.
The trip was all right.
Everything else was bad.
Just left them people.
They talking about cutting us off,
Cutting us apart from every G.
Cutting us off?
My nigga, our money's
always right in the zap.
My nigga, we always on
time with everything.
Yeah, you're right with that,
but it's not about the money.
It's about all these shootings.
I mean, about the shit with
Bug and Syme and all them.
Nigga said, "Yo, it's bad for business."
I mean, this is basically,
I didn't even think I was gonna make it
out of that motherfucker alive, yo.
Nigga was so pissed off.
The nigga even offered
the motherfucking help
to get rid of these niggas.
Why not though?
Why?
Why I wanna get deep with these people?
I mean, once the motherfuckers
come down here and do that,
what kind of debt you think
we gonna be in to them then?
I don't know.
I mean, we got our own shit.
We don't need them. No killers.
The shit about it is, them
niggas is hitting moves.
We gotta find a way to move
the way we're supposed to move.
Get on these niggas.
All y'all do is sit back and think.
We smarter than fucking Syme
and that piece of shit Bug.
We smarter than them.
Sha, get on it and get
them niggas out of here.
What's up with that
piece of shit nigga, D?
What are you paying him for?
Yo, matter of fact,
as you speaking that nigga name,
I'm about to give that
nigga call right now.
As soon as I leave here,
I'm gonna get in my car,
I'm gonna give that nigga a call.
You gonna have him get rid of them,
then we gonna get rid of him.
He's out of here too.
All right, my nigga. I'm on it.
Yo, you got them new joints, yo?
Sure, man. I ain't forget you, man.
You always say the same shit.
You know it, man.
I got you, man. I'm
finna hit you up though.
I'ma hit you up and let you know.
Hey yo, Fat Boy.
My nigga, why that shit ain't
taken care of, my nigga?
My nigga, I told you to take care
of that shit, my nigga.
That shit is not done, my nigga.
That shit is not right.
Niggas is on my neck,
breathing on my neck.
My nigga, just make sure you take care
of that shit tomorrow, my nigga.
I said tomorrow!
Asap, boy!
All right.
[Smith] All right, team. We got a call.
They're at the diner.
Cruz, I'ma need you on the west.
KB, I'ma need you on the east.
Lewis, I need you to
apprehend his girlfriend
in case he gone.
Detective Anderson, I
need you to cover me.
- Copy.
- All right?
Let's move.
[Keisha] This ill ass nigga
got his whole side of town on smash,
and gonna drop the nigga in broad daylight
in the middle of the park.
He's bugging.
That's what he got his man, Syme, for.
But this why we call him Bugowt.
I'll be there as quick as
I can get there, all right?
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Yo, I know I be busy out in the streets,
but you gotta always remember,
I'm doing it for the family.
Really?
You have to make time,
quality time at that,
for your family.
You know that.
Yeah, I know. I know.
But once I handle this shit in New York,
we gonna be straight.
Don't worry about it.
That's all I ask.
I don't ask for much. I really don't.
I'ma go up there to this
deal real quick, all right?
[sirens blaring]
[indistinct shouting]
Get off me! Get off me!
Get the fuck off me.
Stop talking. Relax
Get off me.
Get the fuck off me.
Stop talking.
[overlapping shouting]
The money's in the drawer!
[Lewis] Calm down right now!
The fuck is this?
That's your handiwork right there, man.
I got an eyewitness that
put you at the scene
with a gun in your hand.
So what?
You still gonna make this more difficult
than it already is?
So if you got all this,
why the fuck am I here for then?
Because we're trying to
figure out why you did it.
Is it because of Un or Twin's death,
or you just got some whole other shit
going on in the streets?
I see what's going on.
Y'all just trying to get something
so y'all can put something together.
But y'all ain't got nothing on me, though.
I see what's going on.
Y'all some funny motherfuckers, boy.
No, what's funny is, you sitting up here
trying to act all hard and shit.
I'm not hard.
I'm just doing what I do, bro.
It's all good though,
because you'll eventually
bitch up and give us exactly what we want.
That's a great fucking speech, yo.
That shit ever worked on anybody?
Can I?
Please do.
Robison, I need the room.
The fuck is this, good cop, bad cop?
No cop. Agent Turner, FBI.
And I'm Agent Cruise, FBI.
Okay.
I need you to listen.
You're gonna go down for this body.
We got you.
We know all about your
little operation you keeping.
The laundromat and the barber shop,
but that shit don't mean
nothing to us, okay?
It don't?
Nah, it's little money.
What we need from you is information.
[Keisha's Mom] I'm
just glad you all right.
[Keisha] See, that's me. I'm Keisha.
I'm the offspring of two hustling OG's.
My pops got life, my mom still hustling,
and they expect me to change.
Keisha, please. Be careful.
Watch yourself out there.
Mom, all right. I'm good.
You having company?
No.
[Keisha] Oh, shit.
It's Pastor Thompson.
Pastor Thompson?
I'ma go downstairs, Mom.
Pastor, how are you?
I haven't seen you in such a long time.
How are you?
I'm good. I'm good.
I'm just enjoying the journey,
taking the good with the bad, amen?
That's right, amen.
How you been, Toni?
I'm good.
I mean, I could complain,
but ain't nobody trying to hear that.
Well if you ever need an ear,
just give me a call.
Absolutely.
That's what I'm here for.
I might take you up on that.
Amen.
I know you here to see Keisha. Keisha!
So how's Kayla doing?
We lost Kayla about earlier this year.
Oh, my God!
Pastor, I am so sorry to hear that.
Thank you.
I didn't know that.
I can't even imagine the pain.
I am so sorry to hear that.
Thank you, Toni. It means a lot.
Thank you.
If you ever need anybody
to talk to, I'm here.
Thank you, Toni.
- Hey, Mr. Thompson.
- Keisha.
All right, I'ma leave you two.
Pastor, if you need me,
you know where I am.
Thank you, Toni.
Long time, no see, Keisha.
How are you?
Hey. I was so sorry to hear about Kayla.
That shit fucked-
I mean, it kinda messed me up inside,
because you know me and Kayla was cool.
We just got back in
contact with each other.
All right, well is there
anything you can tell me?
Why was she out so late?
Well Pastor, to be honest,
I was actually out of
town when it happened.
When I got back, I was just so distraught.
- How's Dez though?
- You know Dez?
She don't know anything?
You know Dez?
Yeah, Kayla brought
her around all the time.
Okay, well she's kind of off right now,
but I'm trying to bring
her back to the family.
- Amen?
- Amen.
I'm actually gonna go
see her when I leave here.
Really? You think I could
catch a ride with you?
Because I miss Dez. We gotta catch up.
No problem at all. Come on.
Let me get ready.
All right, and we can
finish our conversation.
[Keisha] All right, no problem.
Get this bitch Dez today.
Got me fucked up.
Coming, Pastor!
Good morning, beautiful.
Did I fall asleep?
Yeah, how'd you sleep?
Good. What time is it?
It's like five. Relax.
You trying to keep me here?
You wanna leave?
No.
♪ I just wanna love you, baby ♪
You sure you wanna do this?
♪ I just wanna love you ♪
♪ I just wanna love you, baby ♪
[indistinct conversation]
♪ I never been that guy
that's been caught out ♪
[song continues]
♪ I'm in my nigga's and we
smoking and it ain't a swisher ♪
♪ With some hot nigga's stay streaming ♪
♪ It's like caution ♪
♪ I just wanna love you, baby ♪
♪ I just wanna love you ♪
♪ It's like caution ♪
♪ I just wanna love you, baby ♪
♪ I just wanna love you ♪
♪ Day time, night time, you get me ♪
♪ Lights shine, bright lights ♪
♪ Can you handle it ♪
♪ You can be my baby ♪
♪ With a lollipop ♪
♪ It shouldn't take that damn long ♪
♪ For you to feel important ♪
♪ Feel that light so damn strong ♪
♪ You can feel the poet ♪
♪ Season after season ♪
♪ Haters hate for no reason ♪
♪ You don't need no
one else for pleasing ♪
[song continues]
♪ I just wanna love you ♪
♪ Fucking with a real nigga ♪
♪ I never been that guy
that's been caught out ♪
[song continues]
♪ I'm in my nigga's and we smoking ♪
♪ And it ain't a swisher ♪
♪ With some hot nigga's ♪
That was different, right?
[chuckles]
Different ain't the word.
You thirsty?
No, but I could use a shower.
All right, I got you.
I'll get you a towel.
[objects clattering]
Hey, everything's set up
for you in the bathroom.
Thanks.
You all right?
[exhales heavily]
[indistinct conversation]
[Keisha] Now this is D,
one grimy ass nigga.
This nigga ain't loyal to shit.
If the price is right,
he'll flip on his mama.
Niggas know this shit and
they still fuck with him.
His fucking girlfriend,
she got that nigga pussy whipped.
Yo, you sure that nigga's gonna be here?
I'm telling you, my
nigga, it's like clockwork.
He come here every day to check
his moms and his little stink ass bitch.
D, my nigga.
If you been doing this, why you ain't been
bringing it to our attention?
Because he's a little nigga, bro.
They give him little nigga shit to do
because he's a little nigga.
I thought it wasn't worth your time.
You ain't been around him
in a minute though, D.
I don't think they
would change up like that.
I don't think they'd change
up like that, but look.
Told you, my nigga.
It's like clockwork.
[speaking indistinctly]
[soft music begins]
♪ Got drunk ♪
♪ If I let it go ♪
[dogs barking]
[hip hop music continues]
♪ Angry niggas make me nervous ♪
♪ Bitches getting on my nerves ♪
♪ Niggas getting on my nerves ♪
♪ Angry niggas got some nerves ♪
♪ Can't trust them, make me nervous ♪
♪ It's something on my conscience ♪
♪ That got me moving cautious ♪
♪ And thought of feds coming got me sick ♪
♪ Making me nauseous ♪
♪ I'm from Queens, we already
took too many losses ♪
[indistinct conversation]
♪ Just don't make me nervous ♪
♪ I told you before, I see
how you're watching me ♪
♪ That shit be making me nervous ♪
♪ I might grip the four ♪
♪ And you know what's coming ♪
♪ If I get nervous ♪
♪ Shit be nerve wracking ♪
♪ Niggas want me dead ♪
♪ I'm nervous and y'all be stressing ♪
♪ Money on my head ♪
♪ That's 'cause my money on game ♪
♪ Nigga you with the feds ♪
♪ You asking too many questions ♪
♪ I know niggas laying out ♪
♪ And be lurking a lot ♪
♪ So before I park ♪
♪ I make sure I circle the block ♪
♪ Niggas getting merced when they shot ♪
[song continues]
♪ But the fiends make me nervous ♪
♪ Every time I serve 'em ♪
♪ And bitches make me nervous too ♪
Oh, shit.
[gunshots firing]
♪ I told you before, I see
how you're watching me ♪
♪ That shit be making me nervous ♪
Motherfucker!
[gunshots continue]
[indistinct shouting]
[gun fire continues]
Don't even do it, my nigga.
What the fuck took you so long?
You serious, nigga?
I be fucking running all over the building
like a track star, man.
You a fat piece of-
- Shut the fuck up, nigga!
Yo, where the fuck is OG and Syme at?
I swear to God-
[gun fires]
Yo, he didn't even
tell us nothing, my nigga
Man, fuck him.
[eerie music begins]
[doorbell rings]
♪ Niggas acting and they man down ♪
♪ Niggas eating and they man down ♪
♪ Niggas sleeping and they man down ♪
♪ Niggas talking and they man down ♪
♪ You ain't seen it how I seen it ♪
♪ You ain't never been in places ♪
♪ Where them real niggas run out ♪
♪ Where them real niggas bust out ♪
♪ Where them real niggas own ♪
♪ You ain't never been in pain ♪
What are you doing?
Ladies, what are y'all doing?
No, you know that's the
bitch that killed Kayla?
What's she talking about, Keisha?
Bitch, I ain't kill Kayla.
If you keep saying that, I'll
pepper your fucking face.
Ladies, put the guns down!
Even if you didn't do it,
bitch, it's your fault that she dead.
My fault?
You the one that fucking got her
[indistinct]
You killed Jack, bitch.
[gun fires]
♪ You pussy niggas that can kill me ♪
♪ Niggas turning steady,
got their turban on ♪
♪ Now they acting all religious ♪
♪ Niggas out here and they man down ♪
♪ Niggas eating and they man down ♪
♪ Niggas sleeping and they man down ♪
[bullet whirring]
[brakes screeching]
Look at you, stupid bitch.
I told you I ain't kill Kayla, bitch.
[gun racks]
But this is for Jack.
[gun fires]
You want something
from the store, my nigga?
Yeah, get me a bag of chips, man.
I'll be right back.
♪ That you might be slick ♪
♪ It's the ones that
smoke blunts with you ♪
♪ That stuck with you ♪
♪ Now they wanna grab a gun ♪
♪ And come and get you ♪
♪ The ones that smoke blunts with you ♪
♪ That stuck with you ♪
♪ Now they wanna grab a gun ♪
♪ And come and get ya ♪
♪ But you might wanna slip, wanna slip ♪
♪ I'll say a prayer ♪
♪ In the clip, in the clip, yeah ♪
♪ And this is just the
way that it is in NYC ♪
♪ The way that it is ♪
♪ Niggas assume I'm a drug dealing ♪
♪ Drug addict, low snapback
with tats and rapping ♪
♪ Rumors spread got me laughing ♪
I said barbecue.
My bad, man.
You want them?
Yeah, I'll take them.
♪ I gained every lesson
necessary angles in ♪
♪ OG now, look at me now ♪
♪ The rebound, the beat down ♪
♪ Laid the heat down ♪
[indistinct conversation]
[song continues]
♪ Stuck with them broke zippers ♪
♪ Had I not seen a way to Camelot ♪
♪ I ain't on the gram a lot ♪
♪ Post up, picture me rolling close up ♪
♪ She asking for the
zannies and the telly ♪
Yeah man, fucking need
to take a piss though.
♪ It's the ones that
smoke blunts with you ♪
♪ That stuck with you ♪
Whenever you get a chance.
[speaks indistinctly]
[music continues]
♪ Bet you mine won't slip, won't slip ♪
♪ I'll say a prayer in
the clip, in the clip ♪
♪ And this is just the
way that it is in NYC ♪
♪ Yeah they love the smell of Napalm ♪
♪ Dealing the praise like I'm eight on ♪
♪ City streets I done rolled on ♪
♪ Race against the time ♪
♪ A beautiful mind ♪
♪ This anomaly unusual ♪
♪ I am brutal with rhyme ♪
♪ So what's up ♪
♪ Player niggas playing niggas ♪
♪ Listen, I can feel
it in the air, niggas ♪
♪ If the blast don't get 'em ♪
♪ Then the wave will kill 'em ♪
♪ You unleashed the Stephen King ♪
♪ Pray for 'em, I'm gonna slay ♪
♪ Different nights from here to Lebanon ♪
♪ Been the dawn since
them bags were capped ♪
♪ Jewels on 'em since homeroom ♪
♪ I already had to
captivate the whole room ♪
♪ And I been told to pop it in 'em ♪
♪ When I couldn't fold ♪
♪ Just a cadet that ranked up ♪
♪ I always be a frontline brother ♪
♪ That was born to do it ♪
♪ In the studio recording to it, kush ♪
♪ It's the ones that
smoke blunts with you ♪
♪ That stuck with you ♪
♪ Now they wanna grab a
gun and come and get ya ♪
I knew your bitch ass was
trying to pull something.
It ain't gonna work without these, nigga.
[gun fires]
♪ Now they wanna grab a gun ♪
♪ And come and get ya ♪
What's going on, man?
What's going on?
You see what's going on, man.
I'm up in here with
this tight shit on, man.
You gotta give me a positive.
What you think is gonna happen?
I mean, I could push for
the next grand jury hearing.
Without probable cause,
they gonna have to throw it out anyway.
Listen, if no one comes to testify,
they don't even have a choice.
I really need to know
who testifying, man.
I don't need to hear that.
What I know is that we have two witnesses,
but you ain't hear that from me.
All right, all right.
You know what you doing, man.
We schedule a hearing
and I'ma take the stand and
get this shit thrown out.
Matter of fact, call my wife
and tell her and the fellas
to come on my next visit.
All right, so I'll contact you
with your next court date
and I'll call your wife as
soon as I get out of here.
All right, leave me a positive, man.
I'll do my best.
All right.
Can you put it on something else?
What you wanna watch?
I don't know, let me see.
No, we're watching this.
Come on, this is so bad.
[knocking on door]
Who is that knocking? It's late.
Oh my fucking God.
I'm coming, I'm coming. Hold on.
[knocking continues]
Yo, chill.
Shh!
What the fuck took you so long?
Yo, I got some shit to tell you.
What now, man?
Yo.
CoCo, what's good?
What's good, Mecca, with your fine ass?
All right my nigga, what's up?
What you doing here this late?
Thought you'd be with your
Mr. Investor at this time.
Yo, this shit is crazy.
What's crazy?
What are you talking about?
This nigga is a fed.
The fuck you mean, this nigga's a fed?
Yo, he dropped his wallet.
I went to go pick it up, it opened.
I seen the badge, ID, everything.
Okay, so what's up?
I don't know, I guess it's just his job.
Just his job?
This what the fuck I'm talking about.
You and Keisha in Lala
Land over some dick.
That's why I keep my bitch around.
Yo.
It's not like I'ma tell him
what the fuck we do,
so what's the problem?
What's the problem?
The problem is, you're a fucking criminal
and he's FBI.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You stupid, or you just dumb?
Yo, listen, just give me some time
to figure this shit out,
and don't tell Keisha nothing.
I'ma figure this shit out.
I mean, it's not like he investigating me.
Plus, I already let the nigga smash,
so I feel crazy as hell.
Aight, smash away. Let me walk you out.
You kicking me out?
You sounding real crazy right now.
You gotta go right now.
That bitch crazy.
Yeah, I told you.
Whatever.
Mm-mm.
What's your problem now?
You know you gotta handle that, right?
Handle what?
Nigga, that fed.
Regardless how long they
been rocking with each other,
he should have told her what he was into
from the beginning.
You trying to take that chance?
No, I got you.
I got you, I got you.
Thank you.
Let me pick something to watch now.
Mm!
[Keisha] This is Mimi, little grimy ass.
She the leader of my cousin's
little grimy ass crew.
Trust me when I tell y'all,
these bitches ain't shit.
[indistinct phone conversation]
[dramatic music begins]
Yes. No, I'm back.
I'm actually at the shop now,
tired as fuck.
Yeah, no, he call me.
[continues speaking indistinctly]
Abby, you still in here?
You getting them coins, boo?
Yeah, something like that.
Muff, can you get over here?
It's important.
All right, give me a second.
I got you, let me call you back.
What is the dilly?
What's up?
[gun shots fire]
Come here. Come here.
Come on, the fuck over there.
Oh, you got the drop on me?
Yeah, you right.
Fuck boy and fuck you, nigga.
You need a gun for me?
Bitch ass nigga.
[loud smack, object clatters]
What's up?
I don't hear you now.
Get up!
I can't get up.
Fuck me, you still talking shit, huh?
I don't need a gun?
You know what, I got something for you.
Get your ass up.
Stand your fucking ass up.
Mimi didn't tell me it
was gonna be this fun.
Running up on bitches easy.
Told you I didn't need no gun.
[bottle shatters]
Shit!
Fucking bitch!
What the fuck you do to my face?
[dramatic music continues]
[gun fires]
Nigga.
[Man] My inner self's telling
Shelly know what more about
what she acting like she know about.
You heard?
Yo, you keep talking
this inner self stuff.
[Keisha] This is Life.
Mimi little grimy ass
put him on the plate.
Now she's on his menu,
and let's see how this play out.
We keep beating around the bush.
First of all,
I don't know what the
fuck you talking about.
You talking about this bitch in my office.
Nigga, who you calling a bitch?
Babe, chill out.
Look, end of this shit,
I need her out of my office
and we need to talk.
Listen, man, me and my girl good, man.
We talking about you and
your girl who set us up,
so at the end of the day-
- Who the fuck y'all talking about?
You talking about that bitch Mimi?
Babe, please, relax.
Why your bitch talking
about my business, my nigga?
I got it, babe. I got it.
How she know about me and Mimi?
Pillow talking, my nigga?
End of the day, my girl here to help.
Your girl the one that set us up,
so let's talk about your girl.
What we doing, man?
What we doing about what?
Get your bitch out of my office or-
- Say bitch one more time.
Babe, I got it. Relax.
At the end of the day, you know what I do.
We can leave this bitch
body scattered around 285.
That's right, baby.
Body parts around the whole circle.
What you trying to do?
First of all, I ain't trying
to talk in front of your bitch.
[gun fires]
Goddamn, babe. What the fuck?
You know I fucking
hate that word, "bitch."
Yeah, but this ain't helping
the situation no better.
[door slams]
What the fuck was that?
I know I heard you
shoot the motherfucker.
No, somebody's fucking here.
Shit, ain't no point in fucking talking.
Let's keep it moving.
[Guard] Get to your station, man.
[indistinct chatter]
Come and sign the paper
and get it over with.
I don't want no bullshit out of you today.
[overlapping chatter]
Grace, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Like getting your visit?
Get to your station, Coleman.
[overlapping chatter continues]
Coleman, that's enough.
Enough touching.
Coleman, that's enough. Have a seat.
Told you I don't want none of that today.
These motherfuckers here, boy.
Do not let them stress you out.
What's up?
[Bugowt] How the kids doing?
The kids are good.
Aaron's on the honor role.
You'd be really proud of him.
Good, my boy Aaron's on this thing.
And Sax and Syme,
they make sure I'm good.
I see at least one of them once a day.
[Keisha] This is Syme,
Bugowt right hand man.
Every time I see this
nigga, I get the chills.
It's like I feel like
I killed them already.
But that was his twin.
Take your time too, all right?
Yo, feds was on me.
Word?
Word. They like, fucked up bodies.
They want them chicks, that
project chick, you know?
Chicks?
You know the chicks
with that projects shit.
I thought they was out of here.
Nah, that butch bitch got him,
but the other bitch, she out and about.
I was talking about the coliseum.
Coliseum?
- Word.
- The chicks?
- Wow.
I'm all over that.
Yo son, just chill, man.
Just chill, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
Just let me take care
of first things first.
Listen, man. They killed my twin, bro.
He got a point.
Yo man, I'ma go in
front of the grand jury
and get this shit thrown out.
Until then, just chill though, all right?
All right.
This is what I want
y'all niggas to do though,
you know what I'm saying?
[dramatic music begins]
I don't know where she's at.
I think you're lying.
It's in your best
interest to get her here.
What's gonna happen?
What's gonna happen to her?
Call her or something. Do something.
Don't worry about what's gonna happen.
See you later. See you tomorrow.
[dramatic music plays]
Mom? Mom?
[speaking indistinctly]
[music continues]
[Woman] She's not answering.
Mom?
[gun fires]
Have a seat, please.
Appreciate it.
This guy can't stop talking about you.
I just miss you so much.
I miss you too.
Seriously, I can't wait
for you to come home.
I miss you so much. Aww.
Y'all better leave him alone.
[all laughing]
Look at this.
Don't even call me.
[indistinct conversation]
Damn, look at LeBron,
always crying, man.
Damn.
Oh, good move, staff. Good move.
Keya!
Where my food at, girl?
Oh, oh, that was a good move.
That was a good move.
Relax, you acting like
you ain't eat all day.
I didn't. I'm starving.
- Listen.
- This looks good, too.
You're lucky I like you.
Everybody don't get served food.
Thank you so much.
Yo, what about something to drink?
You want me to drink my spit?
You so annoying.
Thank you.
Oh, that's a charge.
Definitely a charge.
To the line.
[phone ringing]
Oh, okay.
Yo, Juan, what up, boy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You missed my call, man.
I was trying to reach out to you earlier,
but nah, Bugowt good.
Yeah, Bugowt good.
Yeah, we actually just
came from seeing him
and all that, you heard?
Yeah, he may actually be able
to walk away from this thing,
you know what I'm saying?
But we ain't gonna chop that up now
over the phone, you heard?
Yeah, exactly.
As far as that other thing,
yeah, yeah, with the
females and my brother.
Yeah, one is off the count already,
you know what I'm saying?
There's one just floating around,
But we got a line on that one.
That one.
Aight, yeah.
So reach out to, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Exactly. Y'all get up
with me in the morning.
Laundromat. One.
Aight.
Oh, good move.
Thank you so much, sweetie.
You the best.
Whatever.
I got something for you later.
I got something for you.
Come on, watch this game with me.
Come here, sit down. Come on.
Watch this game with me.
Look, look. LeBron's a crybaby.
Every time he turn around, he crying.
Good move, good move.
[R&B song plays]
[Man] After we do this, we good.
Yo Keya, what's good?
You said you wanted to holler at me.
It sounded urgent. What's going on?
Nothing, Keisha.
I know we ain't speaking
no more, but that's on me.
I was kind of upset about
shit getting shot up
and then Tyler running
through with his big ass gun
in front of my kids.
Like, that shit was not cool at all.
I respect that. It's crazy.
But anyway, Syme and
his peeps is after you.
Who?
Syme.
- Who the fuck is Syme?
- Homeboy brother.
His twin brother.
Yo, you think he had something to do
with me and Tyler?
No, he only know about Tyler.
This nigga was in the
dead end when she died.
I was with the nigga yesterday.
I heard him like he had
the mind on the girls
and that this shit is about to be over.
What?
So you know, I had to
hit you up and put you on.
Yo, shit.
Shit's crazy.
Yo, good looking Keya, real shit.
I got you Keish.
I love you. Be careful out here.
- Thank you.
- All right?
Listen, you be safe too, you heard?
I got you.
If I find out anything else.
Make sure you hit me, for real.
- Of course.
- All right.
Be careful.
Fuck, man!
Shit don't stop.
You good, babe?
I'm good.
[phone ringing]
Yo.
What's popping? Who this?
Tiff who?
Okay.
That's what's up.
Say less, where you at?
Got you, I'm on my way
there right now, you heard?
Don't move. All right.
I've been trying to call
this nigga for four hours.
Damn, that's crazy.
Nah, that's not crazy.
I ate three bags of chips. That's crazy.
I'm trying to call this nigga.
I was just about to
call you one more time.
Shit, been busy, man.
You're not the only
that call me, my nigga.
No, I know that. I know that.
What's good though?
Cool making these runs.
I would have pulled up sooner,
but I had to spin the block.
[indistinct]
Facts.
I thought the boys on you, my nigga,
but there's two dykes in the car.
That's crazy, that's crazy.
Now I'm good with my shorty.
Your shorty ain't plotting on you?
No, I'm good with her.
I'ma take care of it though, my nigga.
Man you good?
You need me to do something?
I need you to lead me to them.
Let me follow you down the block.
I got it.
You got my map, nigga. Holler at me.
[indistinct]
How you find this dude?
This kid named Shamel got killed.
[speaking indistinctly]
[upbeat music playing]
And this is supposed to be the third?
Told me they ran down
on somebody at the daycare
and after that, they had a four.
Okay. I got you.
I did my ones and twos and I called you.
I appreciate your loyalty, yo.
You know what I'm saying?
I owe you for this one.
[hip hop song plays]
What's good now, bitch?
[gun fires]
[eerie music plays]
[KB] CoCo, I'll be out in a minute.
The last date was kind of crazy, right?
What the fuck?
[gun fires]
I guess that pussy
really was to die for.
[gun fires]
Baby.
[bag clatters]
Fuck. Fuck.
Shit.
Yo, big Tang?
Yeah, boss?
Never mind.
Oof.
Yo, what? What the fuck?
What you think, boss?
Be easy, be easy.
I'm not sure if this the feds or not,
but have them traps ready just in case.
What you think?
Definitely ain't the feds.
Listen, know one thing for certain,
two things for sure.
We gonna stand tall on this one.
You ready?
[knocking]
May I help you, sir?
You and I need to have a conversation.
May I?
Hm, even though you asked,
seems you have the
situation under control.
It seems, Mr. Talib,
that you have some property
that belongs to me.
I want it back.
And what property is that?
I have no idea what you're talking about,
Mister who you even are.
Duffel bag.
Duffel bag full of money.
Still don't know what I'm talking about?
Good.
Now that we're on the same page,
I want my money and
everyone that was involved.
Then maybe, just maybe, if I feel good,
I'll let your black ass live.
Let me live?
Mister, I been in the streets all my life.
I done been in many
wars and I always said,
when I go out, I'm going out with a bang.
The question is,
when you go out, how
you plan to go out, son?
May I?
Go ahead.
[gun fires]
[woman shouting]
This is not good.
[man speaking foreign language]
Speak, my friend.
I'm afraid that Ivan is...
Enough, enough!
Bring him home.
Bring him to me.
Yes, right away.
I tried to call KB.
He didn't even answer.
[Agents speaks indistinctly]
This shit crazy.
Shit.
[guns racking]
Yo, KB.
Yo, K.
Oh, shit, look.
Yo, I'm gonna look upstairs.
Agent down, agent down!
10-35, 10-35, agent down!
Nobody's up there.
I'ma check downstairs.
All right.
Fuck.
Yeah, hello?
You're gonna have to relax
a little bit with all that.
I pay you money to keep me informed.
Listen, you stupid bitch.
I want those bitches that took my money.
You understand?
Tell me how you expect
me to get these bitches.
Please, tell me.
Yo, the only way this is gonna work,
you're gonna have to fucking trust me.
What?
You think I'm only going to depend on you?
I lost my son, who was
trying to put it together.
I'm truly sorry, but
we gotta be careful.
There's mad shit going on.
Enough, enough! Stop, stop!
I will tell you what to do.
Don't tell me what to do!
Find out. Listen, listen!
Find out where CoCo and her friends are at
and make it fast.
I'm a very impatient man.
Stupid fucking bitch.
Fuck.
Fuck, man. Fuck!
[knocking on door]
[Kyah] Yo, who the fuck is that?
Yo, it's me. Open the fucking door.
Yo, what the fuck is wrong with you?
Yo, tell me you didn't do it.
Why? Why, Kyah?
Why the fuck you think, bitch?
I'm not trying to go to jail
because you can't figure shit out.
Yo, are you fucking crazy?
Look, I don't know what you thinking,
but we gotta get the fuck out of here.
Nobody saw me go in or out.
Yo, I been fucking with
this dude for months.
My prints, my DNA, is
all up and through there.
He's a fed. We gotta go.
Okay, okay.
You gonna call Keisha, get our shit,
and get the fuck out of here.
It's not like we don't got the money
to go wherever the fuck we want.
Look, I appreciate how you got us up out
that situation the last time,
but this ain't that.
We not calling nobody.
Get your shit and let's go.
Damn, I was just trying to
make sure we good, my nigga.
Look, we been friends
since we was little kids.
I got your back and you got mine.
It's just us.
All right, my nigga.
No Keisha, no Pritty, nothing.
No bags, we out.
Where we going?
It don't even matter.
Lets just get out of here.
All right.
[suspenseful music plays]
Yo, shorty had a crazy fat ass.
Twins?
Exactly, but you know they fucking
one of them cats from the
other side of town too though.
What the fuck is up?
You sitting down on the job?
Where's Sha at?
Don't worry about Sha.
[indistinct conversation]
We got about 15 left.
[conversation continues indistinctly]
Everything okay?
Yo, man. I was bugging though.
Isn't that that nigga G, Sha man?
The money man?
Who? Let me see.
Oh, oh yeah. That's the money man.
Show time.
[dramatic music builds]
Yo, where's Sha?
Let's do it.
Where's Sha at, man?
There's no Sha in here.
No niggas named Sha in here.
Where he at?
[conversation continues indistinctly]
[suspenseful music resumes]
Nigga looks scared anyway.
Get the fuck out of here.
Niggas a bunch of birds and shit.
[phone ringing]
Everything good?
[Man On Phone] We
got some bad news, man.
They found Quick in the alley, man.
They found his body, man.
This shit crazy out here.
Word.
[Agent] Prints came back.
It's confirmed. It's CoCo.
One of my guys was killed.
I want you to do whatever
the fuck you gotta do
to bring them in by any means.
[hip hop song plays]
Freeze!
Get 'em, get 'em!
Do not smart mouth.
Put your face on the floor.
Get your face on the floor.
[upbeat song continues]
[guns fire]
♪ Bust his head to the white meat ♪
♪ I don't fuck with rats,
I don't even say hello ♪
♪ I ain't Rafael, I ain't Donatello ♪
♪ Stand up fellow ♪
♪ Raised in the ghetto ♪
♪ They know I'm down for life ♪
♪ Word to shorty yellow ♪
[indistinct chatter]
And I found a gun.
Who the fuck gun is this?
Hi, may I help you?
I'm good. I'm just waiting for someone.
Okay.
Hello, ma'am.
We gotta ask you any
questions about your crew.
I don't have a crew,
and I don't know what the
fuck you're talking about.
The fuck she don't know
what we're talking about.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Okay, I'll be right there.
[Agent] Listen, you gonna
tell us what we wanna know
or we're gonna make sure you stay here,
as in in the morgue.
Where is CoCo and Keisha?
Get off me, fucking pig.
[Agent] Where's your crew at?
Fuck off of me.
[patient screams]
Ah! Nurse!
Get this bitch.
Yo, we good?
Yeah, you gotta see something.
Hello?
Hold on, yeah. Hold on, hold on.
♪ I declare my love and honor to you ♪
♪ Time to take this body
to the highest mountain ♪
♪ All of you ♪
♪ As the sun sets and the moon rises ♪
♪ And the day turns into night ♪
Get out, get out, get out
♪ You're all mine ♪
♪ Cross my t's and dot my I's ♪
♪ For all my life, you're all mine ♪
♪ If you believe in love,
then we should be together ♪
♪ If you believe ♪
♪ If you believe in love,
then we should be together ♪
♪ My love belongs to you ♪
[gun fires]
The fuck?
The fuck is going on?
[phone ringing]
Where the fuck is these bitches at?
Why the fuck are they not answering?
[Bailiff] Everybody rise.
You may be seated.
Okay, Miss Robison. How long?
Your Honor.
Your Honor, it appears
that my witnesses are dead.
We believe Mr. Coleman
arranged all of this.
Objection, Your Honor.
Mr. Coleman has been locked
up for the last two weeks.
What is he, a magician?
Your Honor, Mr. Coleman is the head
of a murderous drug gang.
Your Honor, even if all of that is true,
I think that the prosecutor should have
arrested him on all that.
Need I remind the
prosecutor that we're here
for a grand jury proceeding,
not an arraignment.
Listen, he's right.
We're not here for
hearsay about Mr. Coleman.
We're here to see if the prosecution
can show forth evidence
why Mr. Coleman should be indicted.
- But Your Honor-
- But Your Honor,
we do have evidence to show.
[Judge] Order!
Miss Robison, if you have
no one to come forward,
I'm bound by law to dismiss this case
because of lack of evidence.
[Robison] We just need
time to find more witnesses.
Your Honor, as pertaining to Clyde
versus the State of New York,
subtitle B, paragraph 34.
You have to dismiss this case.
[Robison] Your Honor,
we do have evidence
that has shown everything in our favor.
In addition, our witnesses
just magically disappeared
without actual evidence.
[overlapping chatter]
I have no further choice in this matter.
[Man] Your Honor, we
request a non-release waiver.
I suggest if you have
so much information
about the defendant, you make
your next case a stronger one.
Case dismissed.
Holding is full. Take him to the pin.
♪ I don't think that
nigga's still living ♪
♪ Said I live in the hood ♪
♪ Where niggas can never make it ♪
♪ South side was our side ♪
♪ Before the gentrification ♪
♪ Just give me niggas names ♪
♪ Don't need the specification ♪
♪ I get a bitch in line in the pavement ♪
♪ OG told me that he
had a hell of a life ♪
♪ He shot a nigga ♪
♪ But he still live his regular life ♪
♪ If I need a nigga gone ♪
♪ I just tell him the price ♪
♪ He gonna be on a flight
by the end of the night ♪
♪ And I'm a cold stunner ♪
♪ Off white shirt ♪
♪ I got to polo under ♪
♪ I don't know her name ♪
♪ It's crazy how I know her phone number ♪
♪ She a bird, shorty faster
than the roadrunner ♪
♪ I don't touch it if the bros want her ♪
♪ That's the code, brother ♪
♪ Gang popping out ♪
♪ We gonna slide through ♪
♪ Whatever you got, we got times two ♪
♪ Had to clap back when I see them ♪
♪ That's the job rule ♪
♪ So beat it ♪
♪ If I lose my cool, light 'em up ♪
♪ I'm fired up ♪
♪ More ladders than a firetruck ♪
♪ All black uniforms ♪
♪ Styling like a mighty thug ♪
♪ Think about robbing me ♪
♪ Pussy nigga then try your luck ♪
♪ Block 24, black mamba
when it's time for clutch ♪
♪ Who are you ♪
♪ Go and get your team ♪
♪ Bet your crew will lose ♪
♪ Mama say I'm bugging,
granny say I'm losing screws ♪
♪ Told my brother all you gotta do ♪
♪ Is tell me who to shoot ♪
♪ Threw a field day, it
turn into a funeral ♪
♪ I remember cooking up ♪
♪ But wasn't bacon in the kitchen ♪
Hey, Coleman. To the gate.
[Bugowt] That's me, that's me.
What up?
[Inmate] Where my
motherfucking lawyer at?
[overlapping chatter]
Step back.
This way.
[indistinct conversation]
Yo, what up with shorty?
How'd that turn out?
Oh, had a ball. Oh my god.
Yo, yo, yo.
My boy. Bugowt, what up?
Sax, what up?
Congratulations.
What's up, you all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
I'm all good, no thanks to y'all niggas.
You know how it go, man. I own my shit.
Congratulations, man. Welcome home.
Yeah, thanks, man.
You know what we gotta do,
we gotta do our shit.
Let me holler at you real quick.
Sax, give me a second, all right?
I got you.
What's up with your man
that was on demand,
Perez up in that joint?
Oh, he good money.
You got his number and all that?
Of course.
All right, give me his number.
Let me holler at him.
Yo, listen.
We go right from there.
Once you link with him,
ain't no looking back.
That's how he roll.
All right, so let me holler at him.
I got you, I'ma plug
that for you this evening.
Nah, right now.
I need to talk to him right now.
You gotta chill out.
Just chill out, man.
You know what I mean?
Just let me do what I need to do.
You just came home.
No, are you listening to me, though?
Let me talk to him. Let me talk to him.
I'll put you on with him, man.
Hold on, matter of fact,
this is yours, man.
I knew you was touching down.
I got that for you. Clean line.
Talk direct on there, you feel me?
Good looking, I appreciate it.
For you though, you know what I mean?
[speaking foreign language]
Hello?
Yo, Perez, what's up?
It's Bugowt.
Yo, Bugowt, what's good, man?
How are you?
Everything's good
man, what's up with you?
I seen this weird number.
I wasn't even gonna answer.
Let me see who the fuck is this.
[Bugowt] Man, no doubt.
I'm happy you out.
What's good though, man?
You ready to make some moves?
Yeah, yeah. That's
what I'm talking about.
That's what I'm talking about.
Aight. Aight, so I'm home.
Let me chill with wifey for a couple days
and the fam and all that.
Yeah, yeah.
Aight.
So you know what?
Call me at the end of the week.
So I'll put everything together
and then I'll send you out there
to get this, you know?
Miami?
All right, no doubt. No doubt.
Aight, aight.
Nah, that's you. I
got that for you, man.
Oh, word?
That's you, man.
That's a good line and everything.
Yo, listen to me.
Let me holler over here with Sax.
Yo, man, my boy home, man.
[speaking foreign language]
I'ma call you. I'ma call you.
Those bitches still
not answering the phone?
Nope.
When it's about that bag,
they was calling you left
and right though, right?
Grimy bitches.
Yo, that's enough.
I'm not even trying to
think like that, real shit.
If they have Pritty ass locked up,
they probably got them bitches too,
and real shit, I need to
lay low any fucking way.
I'm glad you're here, Keisha,
because that bitch Mimi gotta go.
You should've seen my fucking face.
Fuck your face, bitch.
You could've been dead.
Shit, I would've been dead
if that nigga wasn't
playing around with me.
So fellas, we good over here?
Serial numbers ain't on here?
Everything off.
Ain't nobody playing.
Nobody trying to get jammed up.
All right, I hear you.
Just gotta make sure.
[slow music begins]
♪ Take a ride on my side ♪
♪ You might find my heart ♪
♪ Sitting on the side of the road ♪
♪ Threw it out of the window ♪
♪ Because I don't need it ♪
♪ She broke my heart ♪
♪ Take a ride on my side ♪
♪ You might find my heart ♪
♪ Sitting on the side of the road ♪
♪ Threw it out of the window ♪
[guns firing]
♪ She broke my heart ♪
Muffy!
♪ All the shit that we been through ♪
♪ The fights that we got through ♪
♪ You leaving is doing the most ♪
♪ I guess it don't mean shit ♪
[gun firing]
♪ What happened to the ring ♪
♪ You put on your finger ♪
Yo, the last time we came on the block,
they fucking ran like fucking roaches.
What the fuck we gonna do now?
They was scramming?
I'm getting a call.
This might be good news.
I hope so.
Yo, what you got for me?
Oh, thanks. You're the best.
What's that? What's going on?
We just got a hit.
We know what's going on.
Smith is gonna love this.
Shit.
Yo, Smith. Good news.
I just got a hit on CoCo's phone.
Yes, these bitches is in Miami.
Yeah.
It's going down. Let's get them.
Aight.
[agent laughs]
Just the good news we needed.
You got CoCo?
We got a hit on CoCo?
We got a hit on CoCo.
Go get that bitch.
It's time.
What's good? What you doing?
Thought you was supposed
to be coming to the spot.
Who you on the phone with now, man?
Fuck all that shit, man.
Let me call you back.
What's up?
Yo, check it out.
This is how it's gonna go.
I just got off the phone
with my man, right?
Mm-hmm.
We got some shit popping out in Miami,
but what I need you to do
is to go out there for me
so I can handle this shit in New York
and we can have this shit rocking.
Your moms don't really
want you to do shit,
but I need you to do this for me,
know what I'm saying?
You already know I'm in shit.
You already know that.
Yeah, but last time I trusted you,
you kind of fucked it up,
so I need you to do this shit
right this time, all right?
All right, I mean, I got you.
I mean, I know what you
did to get locked up
and I'm not gonna go so the
same mistakes that you did.
Know what I'm saying?
I'ma make shit clean.
You know what I'm saying?
I'ma make sure it's done.
[man speaking Russian]
To get those bitches and our money.
[conversation continues in Russian]
♪ Still get it with my gang ♪
♪ Ain't a motherfucking thing change ♪
♪ Still rocking with my gang ♪
♪ Still get it with my gang ♪
♪ Get into it ♪
♪ Ain't a motherfucking thing change ♪
♪ Still rocking with my gang ♪
♪ Get into it ♪
♪ Ain't a motherfucking thing change ♪
♪ Still get it with the gang ♪
♪ Ride for the gang, die for the gang ♪
♪ You and I ain't the same ♪
♪ Still put in work ♪
♪ Ain't shit changed ♪
♪ If you feel that type of way ♪
♪ Blowing out your brains ♪
♪ That can be arranged ♪
♪ When the cops come around here ♪
♪ We don't never, ever say names ♪
♪ Pretty girl can bang ♪
♪ Get a ride for your change ♪
♪ Funny they were zz's ♪
♪ Now we all wide awake ♪
♪ Still pulling at the fast brake ♪
♪ I'm the shit if you ask me ♪
♪ Get you stretched like ballet ♪
♪ I'm from the south, yeah that way ♪
♪ South side niggas outside ♪
♪ Yeah it's feeling like a genocide ♪
♪ I keep telling you,
ain't a competition ♪
♪ Yeah, I got it by a landslide ♪
♪ See the hate in they eyes ♪
♪ Type of shit I despise ♪
♪ I'm just trying to live a life ♪
♪ Putting on for my guys ♪
♪ Still get it with my gang ♪
♪ Get into it ♪
♪ Ain't a motherfucking thing change ♪
♪ Still rocking with my gang ♪
♪ Still get into it ♪
♪ Ain't a motherfucking thing change ♪
♪ Still get it with my gang ♪
♪ Still rocking with my gang ♪
♪ Ain't a motherfucking thing change ♪
[hip hop song begins]
♪ I'ma slash and gash ♪
♪ Cut a hole in your ass ♪
♪ Splay your blood on the wall ♪
♪ And play tennis with your balls ♪
♪ Pause ♪
♪ That was screaming ♪
♪ And y'all remind me of it ♪
♪ When y'all be screaming y'all rap ♪
♪ That's the problem with you though ♪
♪ Y'all just screaming on rap ♪
♪ As far as me, niggas know
when I scream it's all right ♪
♪ They like it's Fat Don ♪
♪ But today I got my hulking out my guy ♪
♪ Cash rules everything around me ♪
♪ Dolla dolla bill y'all ♪
♪ I'm from South Side ♪
♪ You meet the Queens ♪
♪ With niggas that South
Side hitting schemes ♪
♪ I make y'all scream like I'm Scream ♪
♪ But this ain't no scary movie scene ♪
♪ When I do it like I'm Scream ♪
♪ I kill 'em with all the hooks ♪
♪ Everybody scream ♪
♪ They hear me on the hood ♪
♪ Give me scream ♪
♪ Killing them with the
hooks like I'm scream ♪
♪ That shit will make you scream ♪
♪ Baby you let me hit
I'll make you scream ♪
♪ Fat Don got drawn make you scream ♪
♪ I put the mask on and make me scream ♪
♪ Everybody screaming ♪
♪ And asking for more again ♪
♪ I'm calling, I'm framing ♪
[rap song continues]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull