Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
When people find out
you're a team guy,
first question they ask is,
"How many people
have you killed?"
Nobody ever asks
how many people you've saved.
[helicopter blades thrumming]
Ma'am, you okay?
Nauseous?
It's my first time
in a helicopter.
Take some deep breaths, okay?
Look out at the horizon.
[breathes deeply]
[clanking]
I'm fine.
She barfs,
I ain't moppin' it up.
[indistinct radio chatter]
Visual on location.
Danny.
All right, listen up.
We're scheduled to be
on the ground
no more than 20 mikes max.
Soon as the paperwork's
been filed,
we take the detainee
into custody,
then we bounce back
to the respondent's airbase.
Time is of the essence,
gentlemen... is that clear?
- Yes, sir.
- Roger that.
Ma'am, I need you to stay
close to us till the transfer.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Hey, you sure you're...
[indistinct]
[indistinct chatter]
We know what this guy's
deal is, exactly?
The brief doesn't say.
He's a person of interest
in a time-sensitive matter.
Not important who he is
or what he's done.
We have orders to transfer him,
double time, in and out.
Whoo! My favorite.
[laughs]
Y'all, I'm thinking
this guy can't be
as important
as y'all say he is.
Oh, yeah? How do you figure?
'Cause, well, they sent you.
It's true, Ash.
Why are you here?
[indistinct radio chatter]
All right, let's go.
Let's move.
All right, Dietler,
you watch our right.
Ash, wait on me.
Come with me, ma'am.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Tom Shields,
deputy site manager.
Lieutenant Harris.
We were expecting
[inaudible],
not a full-on SEAL team.
His charter out of Brussels
was canceled,
and your trouble.
He sent me ahead.
I'm Zoe Anderson,
one of his analysts.
We should get inside.
We're on the clock.
Sure, this way.
Poles call this place
"czarna wyspa,"
Black Island.
Used to run military exercises
out here.
We bought a hundred-year lease
from them
when they joined NATO,
and we got all the shit...
[inaudible]
We're the only ones out here?
Just us and our guests.
Who are these guys?
Foreign fighters.
You got your common
or garden variety
ISIS insurgents,
mostly European Jihadists
coming back from Syria.
Few Boko Jihadists at the back.
These good-looking guys
over here, Somalia al-Shabab.
It's the United Nations
of Terror.
I thought places like this
didn't exist anymore.
We're the last of its kind.
Five-star rating
on TripAdvisor.
What about our guy?
Mansur arrived
ten days ago.
Turkish police picked him up
trying to board a flight
to Heathrow
using a blacklisted passport.
Technically, he requested it.
Transfer him.
You're gonna need a pass.
Over here.
You gotta see the boss.
♪ ♪
This way. Heads up.
He hates surprises, you know?
Nobody told us anything
about transferring him.
Oh, I'm sorry.
This situation's fast-moving.
Strap on,
'cause you just walked
into a big measure contest.
You're gonna need a whole lot
more than "I'm sorry."
[knocks]
Come in.
I'm Zoe Anderson.
This is Lieutenant Harris.
I need immediate access
to Amin Mansur.
Have a seat, Ms. Anderson.
The issue is time-sensitive,
so I would really rather...
Sit.
I'm assuming you prefer
to stand, Lieutenant.
How long have you been
with the agency, Ms. Anderson?
Three years.
Then you should know better
than to burst into my office
and start making demands.
Well, I didn't mean
any disrespect.
I have the paperwork
for Mansur here.
Why the sudden interest?
Mansur's name
is on a wire transfer
from a known ISIL financier.
So you want us to question
him about funding sources.
No, sir.
I'm here to take him stateside.
Why?
I'm afraid
that's classified.
[scoffs]
I'm just the escort.
Just the escort.
Do you know what we do here,
Ms. Anderson?
We sort and sift.
It's our job to process
foreign fighters
before they make it back
to the world.
If we do our job correctly,
no one notices,
but if we screw up
and one of these guys
hurts the homeland,
it's all over CNN.
I understand your concern.
The detainees that come here
do not depart until
we've properly vetted them.
Now, if you want answers,
I will get them for you,
but Mansur is not leaving
this facility.
We are dealing with
an imminent threat here.
Deputy Director Finch
signed the request himself.
If you told Henry "gullible"
was written on the ceiling,
he'd look up.
I'm gonna make some calls.
All due respect,
we don't really have...
Shields.
Give her some face time
with her boy
while I sort this mess out.
♪ ♪
Don't take it personal.
He's been mad as hell all week.
First, he quit smoking,
then he got word
D.C.'s shutting us down.
Really? Why is that?
Run out of bad guys already?
New president, new priority.
Two words. Domestic terror.
Yorke's been in charge
of this place since it opened.
His wife was in the north tower
when it collapsed.
He's been running on hate
ever since.
Judging by your guests, looks
like he's not the only one.
Over here.
Stay the fuck still.
[buzzer blares]
Walk. Stop. Down.
This way.
He's been in here a while.
I don't know how much sense
he's gonna make.
Put these on.
You sure you can handle this?
[rock music blaring]
♪ ♪
[music stops]
[detainees groaning]
Lights on.
Hey, sleeping beauty.
Wake him up.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop! Please, stop!
- That's enough.
- Stop, please!
Please...
[whimpering]
Untie him, please.
- Excuse me?
- I need him untied.
Untie him.
Pretty lady here to see you.
Be nice.
No, please. Please, no.
Please.
No, no, no, please, please.
No, please. [groans]
Please, please.
[whimpering]
No, please.
[grunting]
Hey, I'm not here
to hurt you.
- I'm not here to hurt you.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- Okay, just...
- [groaning]
[panting]
Are you Amin Mansur?
I've already told you people
everything I know.
I'm not with these people.
Let him go.
Tell your men
to let him go, please
Let him go.
[groaning]
My name is Zoe Anderson.
I need you to answer
some questions for me, okay?
Is your name Amin Mansur?
Yes.
Good.
There's been
a terrible mistake.
I'm just a businessman.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Your company sells
medical scanners, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Please help me; get me
out of this place, please.
Please, please.
That's what
we're trying to do.
Okay.
You ever visited America?
- No.
- Mm.
Well, would you like to?
I could fly you to New York.
- Well, I don't under...
- Boston?
I'm not the person
you are looking for.
How about Washington, D.C.?
The Lincoln Memorial is
really nice this time of year.
I want my lawyer.
I want my rights.
I am a British citizen,
for God's sake.
Home Office revoked
your citizenship last night.
You don't have
a country anymore.
No, no, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, please. Wait! Ah!
[screaming] No! No! No!
You shouldn't have
got that close to him.
You know about death, don't ya?
Well, I am an analyst,
not a soldier, okay?
I'm not even supposed
to be here.
Nothing wrong
with being scared, okay?
It's what you do with the fear
that really counts.
And they teach you that
in SEAL school?
Yeah, second thing you learn
right after how to swim.
- Are you kidding?
- No, I'm not.
Am I, Ash?
Yeah, he doesn't joke.
He never jokes.
[Amin screaming]
Jesus Christ.
I take it you're not
a fan of Yorke's methods.
You torture someone long
and hard enough,
they'll tell you whatever
they think you wanna hear.
All you get is bad intel.
And most times,
you can learn more
with a plate of hot food
and pack of cigarettes.
I thought you said you
were just an analyst.
Sounds like
a field operative to me.
- I do psych evaluation.
- Oh, yeah?
I get inside people's heads,
work out what they want.
You know what someone wants,
it gives you leverage.
And what exactly
do you think this guy knows?
Because me and the boys
kind of feel like
we've been left
out of the intel.
You know what I'm saying?
You remember how we missed
the chance to stop 9/11?
We're here to make sure
that that doesn't happen again.
You can go back inside now.
He's a bit more compliant.
I'm gonna check
what's happening
with your transfer request.
Play nice, okay?
We do not have time for this
bureaucratic bullshit.
Next time I come out,
he will be with me, okay?
Hey, my job is to escort
you and the detainee.
That's it.
Nothing more, nothing less.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
You buy all that?
I don't know.
If you ask me, that guy
in there knows jack shit.
He's just a desk jockey bookie.
- Come on.
- Doesn't matter.
We got our orders, right?
And the paperwork?
Well, that's on her
and not us.
She comes out
and says the guy's good to go,
then we assume it's all been
squared away, right?
That's somebody else's
otherwise.
Your call,
but I still don't think
he's who she says he is.
I don't give a fuck
if he's the second coming.
Yo, we need to wrap
this shit up, man.
I wanna get home
and see my daughter.
So what is the game plan?
As soon as she comes out
with the detainee,
we fuck off back
to [indistinct],
crack open
a couple of cold ones,
and Skype the kids
before bedtime.
How about that?
Simple. I like it.
It's because
it reminds you of you.
Hey, bro, I ain't got
no self-esteem issues.
Unlike your whisky tango ass,
I got a mom who loves me.
- All right, let's pack it up.
- We all that.
I fucking hate y'all,
and I fucking hate
escort missions, man.
Come with me. Move.
Thought we were on an island
Supply truck coming
by boat to the mainland.
- How many passengers?
- One driver, one passenger.
It's due in right now?
Wasn't in the briefing.
Something's not right.
Dietler, hold position.
- Ash, Whit, on me.
- Copy that.
Let's check it out.
Sir, can you please
stop the engine?
[indistinct chatter
in distance]
Somebody copy,
for fuck's sake.
Move up. Move up.
What's going on?
Get those guys
out of the cab.
Get them both out now.
Out of the fucking truck.
Get him out of the truck...
get out of the fucking truck!
Kill the engine.
Get the driver out now.
Tell him you will shoot him
if he doesn't get out.
[gunshot]
Damn it!
Fire!
[gunfire]
[horn honking]
[alarm blaring]
Sergeant, check the back
of the fucking truck.
Check the back
of that truck, Sergeant!
[rapid gunfire]
[booming]
[people screaming]
Move!
Is it clear?
Grenade!
[booming]
[speaking non-English language]
Let's go. Go, go, go, go.
Let's take
the fight to them!
Stay on mission!
We're good to go!
Wheels up?
Negative.
[speaks indistinctly]
We need to free it up.
Copy that.
[gunfire]
[speaks indistinctly]
On the right!
Grenade!
[booming]
About fucking time.
[shouts indistinctly]
Hold your position!
Okay, get ready for extraction!
Ash, you first!
Move! Move it!
Jake, move!
Ash, move!
Move!
- I think they're here for him.
- Take his hood off.
He needs to see
where he's going.
Changing!
[gun clicking]
We're going for the helo.
You stay on me.
You stay low. You ready?
- No!
- [shouts indistinctly]
[gunfire]
[indistinct shouts, gunfire]
[shouting]
And drop them!
Dietler, you good?
Yeah, fuckin' amazing.
You good? Are you hit?
Are you wounded?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
[booming]
[shouts indistinctly]
Operations is closest.
- Okay, keep holding him.
- Yeah.
Ready to move. Stay with me.
- Can you untie me, please?
- No!
Move, move, move!
Free the prisoner.
Give them weapons.
You two, that way.
[men speaking non-English
language]
They're pulling back.
Whit, you're first.
Covering fire. Move!
Ash, move!
- You okay?
- [grunting]
You okay? You okay?
Could be better.
Move! Let's go.
Go, go! Cover us!
[gunfire]
Get him out of here, Danny!
Look at me. On three.
One, two, three.
Anderson, you too.
Go now. Go!
Go, go, go!
- They breached the camp!
- Hey, don't go that way!
Not that way!
No! No!
- SEALS! It's me.
- Comms. We need comms.
This way, quickly.
- Clear.
- I got you.
- No exits.
- Outstanding.
- Yeah, but it's impregnable.
Solid walls.
No one's getting in.
Nobody's getting out either.
Real good, buddy.
You're doing real good.
Need you to hold his wound.
Hold him back.
Let me up...
- [all speaking at once]
- Stay there, stay there.
- Stay there. You let us...
- Okay.
Okay, he's gonna...
[all speaking at once]
Up, up, up. Ah!
Can you find entry?
Can you get to it?
- Yeah.
- You done it?
Okay, buddy, we got you.
We got you, buddy.
You're doing great.
Never look back.
I got the pressure.
I got it. I got it.
- Okay.
- Doing real well, buddy.
Fucking good. We got you.
We got you. You're good.
You're good.
- I think his lung is punctured.
- I know.
Yeah. We got you, Ash.
Keep looking at me. That's it.
- We stopped the bleeding.
- You did good, Ash.
You did good.
[indistinct chatter
in distance]
[gunshots]
How are we doing, Whit?
Secure.
Good. Concentrate on me.
Look at me. I got you, bud.
I got you.
[indistinct conversation]
Some fuckin' grub tonight,
right?
We got you, buddy.
We got you.
Okay, Ash. Understand?
That's it. That's it.
We got you.
You know we're here, bro.
We got you, bro.
Fuck! Fuck!
Harris, hold him. Move, man.
All right, we're digging in.
We're digging in.
Whit, I need you
in the corridor.
You gotta lock
that shit down tight, okay?
Danny, help me get Ash
in the other room.
Get that fucking door open.
Get on the radio.
Make the call.
Get him up. Get him up.
Myro, this is Phoenix.
Phoenix calling Myro.
Come in.
Myro, this is Phoenix.
Phoenix calling Myro.
- Come in.
- Slow down.
Myro, this is Phoenix.
Phoenix calling Myro.
Come in. I can't get anything.
- Why? Is it broken?
- Jammed. I don't know.
My cell's not working.
No cell reception...
[mutters indistinctly]
SAT phone.
What about a SAT phone?
There's one
in Yorke's office.
Yorke's office?
Fuck. That's too far.
Oh, my God.
They're letting
all the detainees lose.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
That's Yorke.
They've already
overrun the base.
Shit. They're coming for us.
Man, they're gonna
come in here.
They're gonna kill us all.
This is another Benghazi.
Who's this guy?
You know that guy?
Hakim Shariff.
French-Algerian by birth.
Mercenary for hire.
Master of persuasion.
He led a team
of foreign Jihadists in Syria.
Our intel said he died
in an airstrike
outside [inaudible]
nine months ago.
Well, he looks pretty
fucking alive to me, lady.
Fuck.
They here for him?
I need to know
what we're dealing with here.
Are they here for him?
British Intelligence
flagged him up
as a low-level IS sympathizer
a while back.
That is not true.
He was radicalized
when his son died
during a U.S. drone strike
while visiting family
in Turkey.
Two weeks ago, a known
ISIL financier was killed
in an RTA in Ankara.
Local police recovered
his laptop from the scene.
They sent it to us.
We decrypted it
- and found a bunch of manifests.
- That is not true.
Shut up! Shut up!
Manifest for what?
Shipping containers
connected to his company.
[clapping]
So he exports things.
Doesn't exactly make him
a mastermind terrorist.
The business he runs
decommissions
medical equipment,
CAT scanners, things like that.
Nuclear isotopes.
Is that what we're dealing
with here?
Nuclear?
Everything we export
is regulated by the FDA.
I'm telling you.
Hey, Whit!
I need a fallback position
right here.
Take this.
There's more tangos coming.
We have been
receiving intelligence
that a cell in Europe
has been trying
to build a dirty bomb
over the last year.
- What?
- Working theory
is they are using
radioactive material
from hospital scanners.
We have a paper trail
for a shipping container
that went stateside
via the Netherlands.
We traced it to D.C.
before the trail went cold.
This is some
grade-A bullshit.
NSA picked up chatter around
the State of the Union address
tomorrow night.
And if a dirty bomb goes off
in the capitol, it will bring
all three branches
of government to their knees.
You're wrong.
Our guys caught his ass
with a flashlight.
He's nobody.
Well, it doesn't matter
if you believe me or not.
Look, this is all
just a big mistake.
I am a businessman.
I don't know these people.
I don't know anything
about bombs.
I told you to shut
your fucking mouth!
He knows where the bomb is,
but we are running out of time.
He is our one shot
to fix this thing.
What?
And if he doesn't know shit
then we're risking
our lives for nothing.
Your men sign up for that?
[gunfire in distance]
How certain are you
about this?
We have been tracking him
for three months.
I did his psych profile myself.
Well, if you did it,
for sure.
Okay. All right.
Seriously?
You're gonna base
your decision on a hunch?
My orders are to get him
out of here alive, okay?
Not in a fucking body bag.
Only thing I need you to do
is get the comms back online.
Sooner you can do that,
sooner we can all get
the fuck out of here.
What are you doing?
He is the high-profile
target,
not me, okay?
Wait. Just wait.
I'll do it.
If you try anything,
I swear to God...
you'll regret it.
She's wrong, you know.
I'm not who she says I am.
I'm telling you she's wrong.
He does anything
out of line, you shoot him.
A few down here.
They go up
around the corner there.
Ten, maybe five.
They're gonna come after us
sooner or later.
Grenades. RPGs.
We're exposed here.
Just gotta keep 'em
suppressed.
We ain't losing any more people
here today.
- We got comms?
- Negative.
We're trying.
Bad juju on this one.
Wrong intel, comms down,
Ash gone.
I'm telling you, man,
someone's sticking needles
in voodoo dolls made of us.
Don't start getting
superstitious on us.
Copy that.
We got our lucky charms then.
Oh, yeah. MK-12.
Never leave home without it.
Don't shoot!
Please, don't shoot.
They want you to surrender.
They'll let you live
if you put down your weapons.
They're not here for you.
Rules of engagement.
Give him a warning.
Do not take
another step forward.
This is your only warning.
They want you to put down
your weapons!
[gunshots]
What the fuck
do these guys want?
[gunfire]
- Danny!
- [groans]
Get up. Get up.
How's he doing?
- Fuck!
- How's he doing?
He's good.
It's just a graze. You see me?
- Oh, yeah.
- You see me?
- How you doing, Whit?
I got this.
You focus on Danny.
Up in Heaven,
St. Peter gonna say,
"How you earn your living?
How you aim to pay?"
I reply before my God,
"I earn my living
[indistinct]."
[gunfire]
Grenade!
Get up!
Move!
[booming]
- Harris.
- Yeah.
They shot me
in the fucking head.
Yeah. You know what?
You got a big
fucking head, buddy.
Oh, fuck!
I can't see, dude.
You can't see?
You got blood in your eye,
okay?
You got blood in your eye.
Don't these guys
know when to quit?
Hey, hey. Hey.
You're still in the fight.
Let's go.
You fucking frog man.
We're running low on ammo.
I know.
Can't hold here forever,
man, not like this.
I know.
Hey, I'm gonna need you
to come up with a new plan.
You're not gonna be able
to hold this line.
Get back inside!
Get away from the doorway.
Lieutenant,
I'm gonna give him up.
I'm gonna give him up
right now.
- Fuck.
- No, you're not.
Get out of the way.
We're not
giving him to them.
The only thing I care about
right now is staying alive.
If they want him,
then let them have him.
- You are scared. We all are.
- Okay, right, I'm scared.
Those guys took out everyone.
All the marines, all the PMCs.
Next, they're
gonna come in here,
they're gonna take us down too,
and there's nothing these
SEALS can do to stop them.
You understand that, right?
- Hey, my men can hold them.
- For how long?
We give him give up.
We save ourselves.
That is not happening.
Look, I need him.
I am telling you
I am not a terrorist.
Please, please.
Listen to me.
What if he dies
before you can get him out?
The whole base is under attack.
No one's gonna ask
any questions
if he gets hit
in the crossfire.
We throw his body out there.
Maybe they'll pack up
and go home.
- Calm down.
- I am calm. I am calm!
Listen, one bullet and this
is all over, clean and easy.
Sometimes it is harder
to save a life
than it is to take one.
What the fuck is that
supposed to mean?
Shields, just
calm down, okay?
Calm down.
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing? Shields.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
He is the problem.
We throw him out there.
This all goes away.
I have orders to get
the HBT out of here alive!
Listen... listen to me!
Put the fucking gun down now!
[all speaking at once]
My son, my son, my son!
They killed my son.
He was just five years old
when he was murdered.
We were at a wedding
at my uncle's house
when an American missile hit.
You send your drones
around the world
killing indiscriminately,
and you say I'm the terrorist?
Have you ever lost a child?
Have you? What about you?
When I returned home,
an Imam I had never met
before came to my house.
He told me he'd heard
about my son.
He asked me to help
some people that he knew.
- What people?
- Radicals.
They wanted to use my company
to launder money for them.
- And you let them?
- Yes, I did.
I was grieving and angry.
I'm sorry. That is all I did.
I am not a terrorist. Please.
You know where the bomb is.
No, I don't.
Please believe me.
He's lying.
[phone ringing]
That's the base intercom.
Who's out there?
I'm here, sir,
running operations.
They've got us surrounded.
- How many of you are there?
- Five, plus Mansur.
You manage to call in support?
Negative.
SAT phone's busted.
The only thing working
is the base internet.
They must be
jamming the comms.
We can't hold much longer.
Someone needs
to get to the RA.
The RA? Where is it?
Does it work?
[speaking indistinctly]
If we can recalibrate it,
we can call in support.
I'm going... damn it, Sergeant!
Hold your position!
Sir. Sir.
Sir?
Sir, are you okay, sir?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
He won't go down
without a fight.
Hey, tell me about the RA.
Where is it?
It's here.
It's here? We're here.
- Yeah.
- Can you get there alone?
I gotta try, right?
There's no way off this island
without help, and...
he's right.
We stay here,
we're gonna be overrun,
just like Yorke.
And if you don't make it?
I'll make it, okay?
All right, tell me
what I gotta do.
Tell me what I gotta do!
All right, all right.
♪ ♪
All right, you're gonna need
to recalibrate
the race frequency;
that's what will let you
get past whatever they're
using to jam the signal.
Take that.
Is there another way
out of here?
You know, like a back door
or a window?
Yeah, yeah.
Over here. Over here.
This comes out on the west wall
opposite the main cell block.
Okay, guys, change of plan.
I need you to hold this down.
I'll get extra ammo.
You do what you gotta do.
Hooyah.
You gonna be okay?
It's not just a hunch.
He knows.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Come on, hurry up.
Put him out here.
- Who are you?
- [speaks indistinctly]
[gunshot]
Who are you?
[speaks indistinctly]
Fuck you, you...
[gunshot]
[sobbing] Please.
Don't fucking move.
Hey, hey, who are you?
Ben. Ben Dolson.
I... I handle supply logistics.
Where is Mansur?
- Who?
- Mansur.
Who are you?
Please, please don't kill me.
I have kids.
What do you do here?
Detainee processing.
Do you know the name
Amin Mansur?
- Yes.
- Where is he?
A SEAL team came for him.
What did he told them?
I don't know. I swear.
I don't have anything to do
with interrogations.
Where were they
taking him to?
♪ ♪
Answer my question
and I won't kill you.
I give you my word.
[sobbing]
D.C.
The paperwork said
Washington D.C.
♪ ♪
- [speaks non-English language]
- No.
[both speaking
non-English language]
He's asking me
if I'm going to kill you.
I told him I gave you my word
that I wouldn't.
That's true.
Thank you.
He said, "I didn't
promise her anything."
That is also true.
Hey!
Go and find me Mansur.
I'll go check the gate.
Go.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
You!
[speaking non-English language]
Fuck you, Yasin.
♪ ♪
[chatter in distance]
[breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
[speaking
non-English language]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
Ahh!
♪ ♪
[shouts]
[radio crackling]
Spartan zero one.
This is Red Hammer zero two.
Do you copy?
Spartan zero one, do you copy?
Whit, I made it to the RA.
Get Shield.
We need to figure out
how this shit works.
Copy that.
[shouts in distance]
Who's there? Who's in here?
Give yourself up.
[both grunting]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[gunshot]
No one ever teach you how
to calibrate a radio properly,
Lieutenant?
Anybody else make it out?
No, but I'm gonna make sure
none of these fuckers
do either.
Spartan zero one.
This is Phoenix actual.
Do you read?
Shield took off.
Whit, that's a negative
on Shield.
Yorke's here.
It's Spartan zero one.
Do you read me?
Damn it!
They're here for Mansur.
Heard them talking.
Why do they want him?
Same reason Anderson does.
There's a bomb in D.C.
He's the only lead.
Ah, bullshit.
Well, think about it, man.
Think about it.
All these guys are properly
trained and equipped, right?
Somebody somewhere
has been giving them
logistical
and financial support.
You do not do that for nobody.
Phoenix actual,
this is Spartan zero one.
Come in.
Reading you,
Spartan zero one.
This is Phoenix actual.
We are under attack
by multiple insurgents.
Perimeter breach.
We need immediate air support.
Copy that, Phoenix.
[inaudible] minutes out.
Please consolidate hard cover.
Try to maintain calm.
Stay on the radio.
I'll lead them away.
As soon as you're done here,
you get the comms room's vent
on the west wall.
- Watch your six.
- You too.
[inaudible] over.
We will be moving
to our hard cover.
Comms will be unavailable.
[indistinct chatter]
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
three, two, one.
[rapid gunfire]
- Is it Mansur?
- It is a soldier. Find him.
Mansur. Mansur.
I don't think he's here.
Keep looking.
You two, go back that way.
Check radio.
[indistinct].
- Well?
- Nothing.
[indistinct].
Maybe he's got Mansur
and they're hiding him
in the control center.
Get Ademar.
Ademar, come here.
Come here, young one.
You're a true soldier.
You remember your lessons?
- Yes.
- Tell me.
I must listen and obey
even if I have to die.
That's good.
That's very good.
You are cub [inaudible],
and now it's time for you
to show your worth as a lion.
I was a cub once just like you,
and I educated
many non-believers
[inaudible]
Yes, just like in the book.
Just like in the book.
But we don't only speak
through our words,
through our actions.
I believe, and I'm willing to
[inaudible].
That's good.
You have been chosen
with the great honor.
A lot of our brothers would
like to be in your place.
You should be proud.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You have been given a great
responsibility,
but your reward will be
greater than you can think of.
[inaudible] will say
your name.
Do you understand?
I am blessed.
The reward of the hereafter
is the greatest reward of all.
[inaudible].
- [speaking native language]
Get those men out of the way.
[shouting in native language]
[all shouting
in native language]
"Ademar! Ademar!"]
You promise
to serve our fight.
Swallow it.
It's time.
Let's go.
Move.
Secure the exit.
[indistinct].
I want two men up here
and two men [indistinct].
Everybody move! Move!
Wait. Make sure
everything is ready.
Out of my way.
Do not let go
until very close.
[inaudible] no pain.
There's nothing to fear.
Go on.
[rapid gunfire]
Is there another way in?
Make way. Go on.
Make a path.
[speaking native language]
[rapid gunfire]
Okay, stop.
Right here.
Stop.
What are you doing?
And you, here.
Come on, guys. Focus.
[rapid gunfire]
Get me [inaudible]
and some grenades
[all speaking indistinctly]
- You ready now?
- Come on.
[shouts indistinctly]
Oh, fuck I hate flashbangs.
And you can't see shit
through the smoke.
Last mag.
You know they're gonna
charge us, right?
- Yeah.
- Right down the middle.
They're gonna come after us.
Yeah, well,
we can handle it.
Yeah, we can handle it.
We just got to be ready,
because they're gonna come
right down the fuckin' middle.
Danny,
hold it together.
We got this. We gonna
get you home to your mama.
I'ma get home to Tia.
Come on. You with me?
Booyah.
Hey, boys. Daddy's home.
Roger. Jake's back.
Copy that.
He made it.
Air support is
30 minutes out.
30 minutes? Fuck.
It's gonna be tight.
Heard them talking.
It's like you said.
They are here for him.
Well, maybe it's time to
find out what he really knows.
He tells us
where that bomb is,
we can radio it in.
You had ten days to break
him, and you got nothing.
That's not gonna change
in 30 minutes.
I lost a lot of people today
because of this bastard.
And hurting him is not
gonna bring them back.
Oh, I don't wanna hurt him.
I want to end him,
and so do you.
I can see it in your eyes.
[loud explosion]
- No! No!
- Talk!
I don't know anything
about...
George, this is not the way
to get answers.
George,
this is not the way.
I am tired of your
bleeding heart crap.
It is not about what's right.
It's about what works,
and this is not it.
I moved money for them.
[indistinct].
No! No! Ahh!
- I cannot get answers...
- Get back. Stay away from me.
Jeff, listen to me.
I need him in D.C.
to get answers.
Look, that's enough.
Let him go. Let him go.
Harris, Harris, this guy is
the reason your buddy's dead.
He is the reason
for everything.
Everything
that's happened today.
- Grab his head.
- No. No.
You ever read the Bible?
You ever here about
an eye for an eye?
No! No! Ahh!
Why are these...
No, look,
he is under my custody,
and he leaves here alive.
Yeah, you have paperwork
that says that?
That's enough.
This isn't the way
to get answers.
Yeah, watch this.
My son is already dead.
There is nothing
more that you can do to me.
You lost a son.
I lost a wife.
And I promised
I'd make you bastards pay.
So did I.
[loud explosion]
Yorke, get up here.
Quick, push up. Moving.
[rapid gunfire]
[indistinct].
[gunshot]
I'm down to my last ten.
[indistinct].
[all shouting indistinctly]
[rapid gunfire]
They brought their game.
Bulletproof.
Aim for the legs.
[indistinct].
Johnny's hit.
Go!
Let me see. Let me see.
- [choking]
- Shit.
[indistinct], get over here!
[choking]
I got you, man.
Look at me.
I got you. You're okay. Okay?
You're okay.
[rapid gunfire]
[inaudible].
[indistinct].
Your team's down.
[rapid gunfire]
I'm out!
Get back!
[rapid gunfire]
He's wearing a bomb!
Get down!
[loud explosion]
[groaning]
[coughs]
[groans]
Yorke.
Zoe.
[coughing]
Hey. Hey. Hey.
I'm the only chance
you have of getting off
this island alive.
You understand that?
You think these people
give a shit about you?
I'll take my chances.
No! Wait!
[grunts]
[groans]
[whimpering]
Okay. Okay, I got you.
I got you.
Okay.
Just relax.
You're gonna be okay.
Don't move. Zoe. Zoe. Zoe.
Don't move.
Your baby.
I know, I know. I'm gonna get
you out of here, okay?
I'm gonna get you
both out of here, okay?
It's not mine.
His wife
is 16 weeks pregnant.
It's a boy.
What?
She's in the blast zone.
Mansur's wife?
You... you have to get him
to D.C.
He won't believe it unless
he sees it with his eyes.
Okay. Okay.
[inaudible]
Look, Zoe, Zoe. Zoe.
Stay with me, Zoe.
Zoe.
Zoe!
[grunts]
Ahh!
[indistinct].
He escaped.
Follow him.
[groaning]
What do you Mansur
tell you?
What did he tell you?
Everything.
[gunshots]
[speaking in native language]
Find me that bastard,
and alive.
Shit!
[speaking in native language]
[gunshots]
This is a complete mess.
Next time we get more money.
All this vision bullshit.
[indistinct].
[speaking in native language]
- [speaking in native language]
Karim,
[indistinct].
The Americans are sending
air support.
You find and you destroy
those that are protecting him.
Don't disappoint me.
Nobody leaves this island.
Nobody.
[inaudible].
Shortly he will head
for the dock.
Maybe or maybe
he will stay hiding.
Get a man with you
and protect those doors.
Come on, guys.
Get [indistinct]. Tell him I
don't want no witnesses.
[speaking in native language]
[all shouting
in native language]
Where are you, Mansur?
Where are you going?
Let's go. Let's go.
Check the gate.
Let's go.
Yes, check the corners.
- [gasps]
- Every one.
Helicopter clear.
[indistinct] clear.
[indistinct].
- Clear.
- Search everywhere.
Okay.
[indistinct].
Wait.
Where is your gun?
I left it at the gate.
Stop.
- [speaking native language]
- Fuck.
I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything. Please.
[speaking native language]
I didn't do anything.
I didn't.
Move.
No, I swear to God
I didn't do anything.
Be quiet!
- Stay out here.
- Fuck.
- And watch the door.
Get inside.
Look, look, look.
I... I didn't do anything.
I didn't say anything
I swear to God. I didn't.
- Shut up.
- Look, I didn't say anything.
You better [indistinct]
tell everything.
- I didn't say anything.
- Shut up.
Come on, man.
[loud bang]
Augh!
[gunshots]
Let's go. Move!
No, please.
No. No, no, [indistinct],
please.
Go to the gate.
Guys, guys, I see them.
They're over here.
[rapid gunfire]
[indistinct].
I see him.
Come on.
[rapid gunfire]
Augh!
[gunfire]
Mansur. Mansur.
[rapid gunfire]
[loud explosion]
Augh.
[rapid gunfire]
Mansur, come here.
Come here.
Stop. Stop. Wait, stop.
I didn't do anything.
Look, I didn't say
anything I swear.
You tell your boss.
I didn't say.
I didn't do anything.
The problem with being an
excellent liar
is no one can ever trust
a word you say.
No. No! No!
[gunfire]
You and your team cost me
a lot of money
for this piece of shit.
Mansur.
Stop.
Stop. Stop. I'm warning you.
Stop or I'll shoot.
You won't shoot me.
You need me alive.
Don't come out.
Can't let you leave.
Stop, I'm warning you.
Okay. All right. All right.
I'm dropping the weapon.
I'm unarmed, okay?
I'm stepping out.
Stop. I'm warning you. Stop.
I'm warning you;
I swear to God.
- I need to talk to you.
- I swear to God.
Just let me talk to you.
[shouts]
Amin. Amin.
It's your wife.
Your wife, she is pregnant.
- She's pregnant.
- That's rubbish.
I haven't seen her in months.
That's rubbish. You're lying.
Four months.
That's 16 weeks.
Look, it's a boy.
You see that?
They flew them
both out to D.C. to give you
a reason to stop this.
They're both in the blast zone.
But it's not too late.
You can still save them.
You just need to tell him
where the bomb is.
They don't have time
to search the whole of D.C.
You need to help us, please.
We need your help.
If you go out that gate,
your son and your wife
are gonna be dead.
Do you understand?
They're gonna be dead.
We need your help.
You couldn't save
your other son,
but now you have a chance
to save this one.
Please.
It's too late.
It's not too late.
We can still get there.
We have time.
Put the gun down, Mansur.
Shit, you Liar. You liar.
I knew you were lying.
- No, you need to trust me.
- I knew it.
You need you to
trust me, please.
You're lying.
Everyone I lost here today
is on him.
I can't let him leave.
Yorke, you're not thinking
straight. You're injured.
You're not thinking straight.
Let me handle this.
- No, he's mine.
- Look, if you kill, him...
if you kill him, he's gonna die
believing he's one.
Is that what you want?
- You have no authority.
- It's all lies.
My wife isn't even pregnant.
She isn't even in Washington.
- Yes, she is.
- It's too late.
- She is.
- It's over.
Let him have
his revenge right now.
I'll take mine in D.C.
Please, don't do this.
Don't do this.
- No, put the gun down
- Stand down, Lieutenant.
- I can't do that.
- It's an order.
I already have
my fucking orders, sir.
[both grunting]
[helicopter blades whirring]
How do I know?
How do I know
you're not lying to me?
- How do I know?
- I can prove it to you.
As soon as we get to D.C.
I can prove it to you,
but we're running out of time.
Amin, we have your wife,
and I'm the only chance
you have of seeing her again.
Please, just give me the gun.
It's over. Give me the gun.
I don't know
what to believe in.
what to believe in anymore.
If you're lying, it'll all be
for nothing. You know that.
I'm not lying.
Just... just give me the gun.
My son.
I hope you know
what you're doing.
He's our leverage.
Can you make it to the yellow?
No, I'll get the next one.
Just do what you gotta do
to stop this thing.
I'm gonna come back
for my team.
Okay, let's go.
Move.
[indistinct chatter]
[helicopter blades whirring]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull