I'm in a lot of pain.
I never wanted this to happen.
I just want it to stop.
Greg, Greg, it'll be okay.
Let's go and get to a doctor.
Let's get outta here.
Come on, come with me.
It'll be okay.
I need your blood.
Huh?
I need your blood!
No!
- Oh God, no, don't!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
- Something in my tooth right here.
If I look familiar,
it's because I am the
older brother of Greg...
Sanders
who...
became famous after the video
known as "The Last Five Days"
kinda went viral.
My hands look
big from this angle.
So...
My name is Chuckie.
Chuck,
you can call me Chuck.
I, like many others, lost my
job recently due to the whole
COVID-19
pandemic, so, you know,
there's that.
But after talking to my wife
about some things that
have gone on in my life
I decided that it was time to
resolve or attempt to resolve some issues.
And my family has had a big
one for about 10 years now.
Weird, that's a weird plant.
This is my friend's house.
I'm staying here because...
It's close to...
the house that "The Last Five
Days" video was recorded in.
And the landlord is supposedly selling
the house after all these years
and there's a bunch of boxes and stuff
that the landlord thought maybe
some of it belonged to me,
or not me but my brother
and wanted me to go through
and see if any of it
was worth keeping so I'm gonna...
do that and like, look... at it.
Greg, I...
can't promise you that anything
is gonna come from this, but
I always found it odd
that there was never a
definitive answer to what happened
in that video.
So I ordered something...
to help stabilize my videos.
See how it works.
This looks like the place.
This thing is like jammed though.
Oh!
Mother fuck.
Ah!
There we go.
Let's go.
Someone else here.
I don't really like that.
Let's see if this works.
Apparently so.
Hello?
Uh, excuse me.
- Oh, geez.
You scared the shit outta me there, buddy.
- Oh, I'm sorry, but...
Who are you?
- Detective Sanchez.
You're the brother, aren't you?
- Probably.
Greg, Greg's brother?
Yes.
My name's Chuck.
- You look just like him.
It's just uncanny.
- One of us looks better than the other.
- We tried to get in contact with you
for about a month after the incident.
Even went to the funeral
but you weren't there.
- I was in a dark place.
I didn't get along with my family,
especially Greg.
But...
- Yeah.
I'm just here checking the
place out and there's a...
There's a special they're
doing on the incident.
- A special?
- Yeah.
- Like CNN or something?
- It's kinda like that.
It's more like a local
news network, but they...
- Is it okay if I film this
by the way?
- Yeah, sure.
That's fine.
Yeah, just...
Great.
I'm used to asking other people
if I can film them, not...
- Yeah,
I bet.
- I guess you guys had that in
common when it came to that.
So anyway...
They're set to demolish
this in about two weeks.
It's a shame though.
- They're tearing it down?
- Yeah.
- I didn't hear that.
- The owner of the place after
your brother's unfortunate passing...
He tried to rent it out to several people.
I guess the news coverage was too much.
And couldn't keep it rented
by anybody for very long.
Everybody that came just
left a bunch of shit here.
- There is a lot of stuff.
Whoa!
Can I have this?
- It's not mine to give.
- Oh.
Well it's mine then.
- Sure, yeah whatever.
- Yeah, I suppose everybody
has seen the tape.
- The owner gave you a key, you said?
- Yeah.
- How long are you...
planning on staying in town?
- I don't know.
Didn't really
plan the trip that way.
Just kinda however long it takes.
See if I can find out what's going on,
what happened...
- Really could've used your help.
- Oh, I'm no detective.
- After it happened, we
had a lot of questions.
- So...
Did anyone ever look into the,
the fruit or anything?
- Yeah, I mean there was a
little wooden box.
- Yeah.
- It's on the video.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
We did all the tests we
possibly could on Greg.
- I mean, thank you for
everything you guys do and...
- You know, again, I'm
sorry for your loss.
I don't mean to be so callous
and trying to-
- It's been 10 years, I've had...
I've had time.
- I had a card to give you.
I think it's...
Yeah.
So, if you have any questions or anything
or you need anything from me,
please just give me a call.
Okay?
- Sure.
- Sorry.
Again.
I don't know what else to say.
I'll get out of your hair.
All right.
- Yep.
Damn bird.
What the heck?
Yeah, that looks like it belonged to Greg!
Ooh, looks like it got
used pretty well, too.
Dang, Greg.
How could you afford this?
This backyard is nice.
Like...
You could throw
the best party
ever.
So...
This is the spot where
they found Greg's body.
10 years ago.
The tree looks different
than in the... video.
Maybe it's a different tree or...
Guess I could take these.
What the heck?
Yeah, 'cause that's not creepy.
That's actually really creepy.
It's the only thing in here.
No way.
This is something.
Coming.
Hi.
- Hi.
- You must be Sarah?
- Yeah.
- Nice to-
- Nice to meet you.
- Come on in.
I'm gonna film this.
That's okay, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Go ahead and take a seat on the couch.
So I don't want to take
too much of your time.
I just, you know,
wanna talk to you about
living next to my brother
while he was in school.
I know your, your family lived next door.
Right?
- Yeah.
We lived next door
when I was probably like 12 or 13
they moved in.
- Okay.
I know they,
they didn't live at
the house for too long.
You know, my brother and his friend were,
were college students renting it.
So they, they didn't have
a whole lot of money.
- Yeah.
- I think they were only there for like
a total of like eight or nine months.
- Yeah I remember when they moved in,
my parents were not
too excited to have
college boys next door-
- I'm sure college boys, you know...
They're, they're a bit rowdy.
My brother was a little
bit of a rebel, so...
- Yeah.
- What do you remember about,
you know, the night of the...
the incident where they
ended up, you know, they...
They passed away.
What do you remember about like that time?
- You know, I remember that
night but it was really
the night before that I have a memory of.
- Well you told me over the phone that
you actually might have some information
that hasn't really been
disclosed at this time.
- Yeah.
- Do you mind going into more
detail?
- Well...
My family and I had gone
for a walk the night before
they died and I kinda strayed and
went to the park that was near our house
and Greg was at the park,
which wasn't weird.
Like I saw Greg around
the neighborhood but
he was eating sand.
- Just...
- Just eating sand.
- Like handfuls?
- Like handfuls! Like
aggressively eating sand.
And I was like, I didn't know what...
It startled me.
It scared me.
It was weird and I didn't know what to do
so I just ran back with my family and
I never said anything.
- Yeah. That's, that's weird.
That's something that obviously
didn't happen on camera,
you know?
No one...
If he wandered off,
no one would know because on the tape,
that's the night that Brian went and
stayed by himself at a hotel, so
if he wasn't filming it,
no one knows what happened.
So that's, that's interesting.
And it was just at the
playground in your neighborhood?
- Just in our neighborhood park.
- Can we go and look at it?
- Yeah.
This is the park.
- This is it?
- Yeah, I don't remember
that middle part though
so they must have remodeled
since I've been here
'cause it looks a little different.
- Well, it was all those years ago,
so...
- Yeah,
it's been 10 years
honestly since I've seen it
and they must've...
They must've replaced
the sand with wood chips
'cause that was not there obviously.
- Yeah.
Interesting.
- So where was Greg
when you saw him that night?
- So I was just walking right on that
sidewalk and Greg was
right here by the swings.
- Just right there?
- Just right here.
- Okay.
Would you,
would you mind holding this?
- Yeah.
- I'm just gonna take a
little bit of a better look real quick.
- Okay.
- No, what are you doing?
No!
- I got this email from a
friend of mine who suggested
that I look into this Airbnb...
And the reason is because it
might belong to the Verbin family
or maybe even belonged to Verbin himself.
I don't know if it's the house
referred to in the original video,
but you know I figured
why not look into it?
I have nothing better to do.
Oh geez.
The camera's not on my face.
I'm sorry.
Just making a quick pit stop.
I don't feel like I would
be very good at vlogging.
I don't, I don't ever know what to say.
Like ever.
Sorry!
That is not a bad view.
All right, so I'm...
at Verbin's place.
I guess that's what I'm calling it now?
Or Verbin's vacation rental.
Whatever.
I'm not expecting to find anything
so I brought a little
something to sip on tonight
because I don't want to be bored.
Oh, I love squeaky doors.
Well, yeah, this,
this just looks like an Airbnb.
Except for this...
sheet.
That's weird.
Look a mirror.
Hi, me!
Hi, Chuckie.
Is that a hammock?
Nice!
Well, I totally know where
I'm sleeping tonight.
What the heck?
Oh man.
That was a terrible coincidence.
Let's check out the rest of the place.
Towels, for cleansing the body.
Wonder who she is?
Well this bed
looks pretty comfortable.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, that felt good after a long drive.
Holy shit.
What am I doing?
I'm not gonna find anything here.
Well, at least I got you.
This end table is a little far.
Here's to you,
Gregory.
Ah.
This is nice.
Yeah.
On second thought...
Whoop, spilled a little bit.
My bad.
Oh yeah.
Oh, I could get used to this.
Oh, geez!
I've always wanted to do this,
but I don't want, like, anyone to see.
Woo!
I put the glass down in the rocks
over there.
I just figured I'd drink from the bottle.
Oh yeah.
It's gone.
How do I get...
Whoa.
I have to pee.
Oh, I have to pee, oh!
Ah!
Gosh.
This place has the same
wine that I brought.
Oh man.
Yeah, Gregory!
Woo!
Brother!
From the same mother!
I'm okay!
Not even dark yet.
Where's the stop button?
The stop one...
I'm just gonna take like a quick nap,
like an hour.
I'll set my watch and then I'll,
I'll get serious about this.
I promise.
I just...
I need to take a little nap.
Just a little nap.
Well my nap was nice.
I decided to eat something.
That way I had something
else in my stomach.
I brought some of the
fruit from the other house.
It just looks like
any other fruit, smaller obviously,
but something you'd
find at a grocery store.
I don't know.
I haven't seen any on this property yet
but I haven't, you know,
really been outside sober.
So when I go looking
I'll keep my eyes peeled.
In the meantime.
No, I'm not eating that shit.
I'm not doing it.
Not eating it.
Nope.
I'm not eating it.
I'm not.
Period!
End of discussion.
I might still be a little drunk.
Welcome back to my vlog.
Let me try that again.
I can be more...
insightful.
Welcome back to Chuckie's vlog.
Yeah, whatever.
That soup upset my stomach, by the way.
Campbell's.
You know I read somewhere that
engraved images of Buddha is bad luck.
So just, you know, sh!
Don't tell anyone.
No one has to know.
There's a lot of various
religious artifacts
and paintings and stuff in this house.
It's kinda weird.
I don't know.
Well, whatever.
I'm gonna walk the property
before it gets too dark
and see if I can find anything, so...
Hello?
Excuse me.
What the fuck?
Hello?
I gotta get some shoes
before I go down there.
Got my gun for safety,
and this really bright flashlight.
They're gonna find my body out here.
Or actually just not my body, my bones.
There's gonna be nothing left of me.
Hello?
A lot of bugs
out here.
This is a situation
where I don't know if I'm
happy that I'm alone or I'd
rather see something out here.
What the...
Hello?
I'm almost positive I just saw someone.
Okay I don't...
I don't see anything so...
My battery is getting kind of low
so I think I'm gonna...
I'm gonna shut my phone
off for a few minutes.
I'm gonna keep following this trail and
if I find anything or see anyone else
I guess I'll keep you guys updated.
Okay, so...
Either this hat,
it just like lives here or something
or there is someone and they dropped it.
So I don't know if they like were,
were running that way but there's a hat.
A hat is evidence.
I don't wanna touch it though.
I'm just gonna
go around it, just keep going.
It looks like there's something up here
so I, I don't know what's up there,
but I guess let's just keep going and,
and see if there's anything.
All right.
Welcome back to Chuckie's vlog.
It's a working title, shut up.
I'm pretty freaked out.
There's a sign over here
that's preventing me
from going any further.
So unfortunately I guess this is,
this is where the story ends and I...
I didn't find anything.
I didn't see anyone
and it's...
The sun's almost completely down
so it's, I'm gonna just,
you know, go back to...
What the fuck?
What the actual fuck?
Hello?
Okay.
There's gotta be,
There's gotta be someone
out here somewhere.
Hello?
What is that?
Is that sand?
Hold on.
There's like...
something over there, like a ball or...
I don't know.
Kinda looks like fruit.
I don't know how deep that is.
Okay, all right.
I'm gonna cross this river.
Oh, God I'm stupid.
Okay, all right, I'm in.
I'm in.
It's fruit.
It's freaking big fruit!
Bugs.
It's really big fruit.
I don't know if it's the same fruit but
this is kinda freaking me out.
My pants are dirty now, so
just kinda trying to clean them off here.
And since I'm by myself,
I guess I'm gonna walk
around in my underpants.
Okay so I came and sat over here
because those chairs, they...
They kinda freaked me out.
I guess my tablet's over there.
I could grab my tablet.
And uh...
I don't know.
I just,
Yeah.
I'm gonna just get my tablet.
Oh Jesus.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna
just look something up.
I don't know, I feel like
I need to do something,
like... something's happening.
Hold on.
I've been sitting in this chair for
probably 20 minutes
looking up Verbin,
using Verbin's
WiFi
and I'm not really finding anything!
I don't know if there's anything to find.
I mean, something's...
something's happening but...
In the original video,
my brother ate the fruit
and then they started finding things out
because more things started
happening to them, so...
I don't wanna do this but...
I gotta eat the fruit.
I have to eat the fruit.
If there's anyone here
who thinks I shouldn't
eat the fruit, you know,
say something!
Okay, I'm not lying when I say this but
I'm a little bit freaked out about this.
Got the fruit.
I need a drink first.
Oh gosh.
Dropped the fruit.
Kinda freaks me out because
when Greg took a bite of the fruit before
things started happening right away.
Oh, what the...
What the...
Okay so I cleaned the bathroom up.
I don't know what that was.
Yeah I, I don't know.
I um...
So good.
What the heck?
Well, my nose is bleeding.
Okay, hold on.
So I put tissue in my
nose to stop the bleeding
and it seems to be working,
and silly me,
I completely forgot that
I brought a second camera
to set up and now seems
like as good a time as any
in case I get something, you know?
So I'll just leave it
right here, facing the room
and we'll see what, what happens.
This is good.
This is from the altitude.
Like I'm positive!
My nose bleeds frequently.
Actually, let's move this
over to this side.
I think I might be able to get more
of the room if I set it right there.
Yeah.
Anyway, like I said, this
is from the, the altitude
and I think I'll be able
to get a lot, you know
from right there.
Wait, what?
Okay, so...
I've been walking around the
house and a quick update.
There's nothing.
There's nothing to see.
I keep hearing things though.
It sounds like whispering or,
or maybe people are outside.
I don't know.
I guess I,
I can go check.
I didn't even think about it, you know?
Ow!
Ow, my thumb.
This is just not my day.
What the fuck?
My fuckin' nail just came off!
I don't really feel like
I'm myself right now.
Yeah, I...
I agree with you.
No, sh, sh, sh.
Why, why can't we...
Why can't we do it right now?
I just,
I don't understand.
I just wanna hurt myself.
I thought you wanted me to hurt myself.
I don't like it when you
say things like that.