[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGING] How deep is an ocean?
How far the shining star?
That's more...
[CLANGING]
[DOOR RATTLING]
[LAUGHTER]
[ALARM RINGING]
[ALARM STOPS]
NARRATOR: I live between two
worlds--
the one on the outside, and the
one on the inside.
My job is to keep those on the
inside in.
It's a thankless job.
Every day I tell myself, this is
it.
This will be my last day there.
Code seven.
How's it going?
NARRATOR: There's something
really dangerous
going down on the inside.
It's called Condition Red.
It's like a state of alarm.
That's how I feel.
Yo!
You're playing with me, man.
Think I--
[LAUGHTER]
Man--
Malone, what did I just tell
you?
You want another charge to take
back to court next?
What you gonna charge me with?
How about sodomy?
What the fuck's up with you,
CO?
You happy to be with us, or
what?
Dude is suffering from
depression.
In other words, homeboy's
bugging.
Yeah.
Get you fucking ass off there,
and get back to your cell.
Now.
It's over.
Let's go.
Hey, CO?
I don't wanna room with pansy.
Pansies?
I know you ain't talking about
me.
The only pansy I know is your
mama!
What did say about my mama?
Malone, get back in your cell.
I'll take care of him.
Fuck that.
I'll take care of him now. - Get
back in your cell.
Boyce, what are you doing?
BOYCE: I'm getting out of here.
The fuck are you doing? Get off
there.
- I'm getting out of here. -
Hold still.
Hold still!
[GASPING]
[CLATTERING]
Yo, CO?
This guilty verdict isn't your
life, you know?
[MACHINERY WHIRRING]
Dan?
Dan, listen to this--
[INAUDIBLE] telemarketing sales.
You could make up to $50,000.
What do you say?
We've got the phone lines.
We've got all the time in the
world.
Let's make some money.
[ALARM] BOYCE: Open the door!
OFFICER: Let me go!
BOYCE: Open the door!
Let him go, Boyce.
[SCREAMING]
I'll cut his head off!
Let him go!
Get out of the way!
Open the door!
No, don't do it again!
Please!
Open the door!
Get out of the way!
Get out of the way, now!
Now!
OFFICER: Please help me!
BOYCE: Out of the way!
Get out of the way!
[GRUNTING]
Freedom!
I'm free!
INTERCOM: Condition red.
Stop!
[SHOUTING]
Come on, let's go!
Stop, Boyce!
[SHOUTING]
Stop!
I said stop!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
When I tell you to stop, you
stop.
- Fuck you. - Fuck me?
Fuck you.
Come on!
I then tackled inmate Boyce to
the ground and restrained him.
That's what you said in the last
report?
Get real.
It's not going to work this
time.
This guy's trying to take this
to civil court.
And he'll win, too.
SIr, he almost took Bishop's
arm off.
Three guards and a ward full of
inmates
saw you beat the shit out of the
guy.
You're out of line, guy.
I can't have you here.
I'm assigning you to the women's
section.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello, sugar.
WOMAN: Woo!
Man.
Papi, you know you wanna take me
on detail.
I've been a very bad girl.
Oh, you know, you are gorgeous.
Come on, now.
I haven't seen a man in six
months.
Mm!
Where's the captain?
Down there.
Daniel Cappelli.
Let's see-- three years in the
Army.
Amateur boxer?
Six months in the training
academy
at Holmesburg since 1989.
Two assaults on inmates without
justification.
So you're not married?
What does that have to do with
anything?
Listen, we walk to a different
tune
around here, Officer Cappelli.
I mean, I believe there's a
difference between rehabbing
and revenging.
By the way, we're going to do a
surprise search on G block.
Something's going down.
[RINGING]
[CLANG]
[RATTLING]
Check this shit out.
What's in a name-o?
B-I-N-G-O. Bingo was his name,
yo.
That's not my name, although I
could be ya bitch of--
All my girls, they ball behind
me.
Always got my back.
Rolling on a bitch like this.
Shit outta here.
You know, like thunder--
Six, seven, eight.
One, two--
Thunder--
Five, six, seven, eight.
Then-- two, three--
Mel?
I make a bitch scurry with my
fury.
She'll be running for her life,
so think twice
before you open up your mouth.
[INAUDIBLE].
WOMAN: Stash it.
That I'm giving.
Bitch better believe that.
[WHISTLE]
[SHOUTING]
Stop!
What the fuck?
You all know where they're
going,
so don't get slick on me, OK?
I've got eyes in the back of my
head.
Get 'em out of here.
Get up.
And she going [INAUDIBLE].
She going to [INAUDIBLE].
Bitch, you going to the hole.
Been too long.
Fuck all that.
She's going down!
You know they set us up!
You know, one of them bitches
snitched!
Give me a fucking break!
Come on, man!
You know I hate this.
What do you want, a blowjob?
Do you want a fucking blowjob?
You goddamn cock sucker!
Fuck you!
Fuck you, asshole!
You are fucking--
You asshole!
Fuck you!
[SINGING IN DISTANCE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
SINGER: Die a little.
Every single day of your life.
Die a little.
Every time your baby says
goodbye.
And the world keeps spinning
around.
Ain't nothing you can do but sit
Die a little.
When you see how cruel a man can
be.
Die a little When you know you
wouldn't do differently.
And the world keeps spinning
around.
Ain't nothing you can do but sit
Hold it for me.
[SHOUTING] That'll teach you to
rat.
Let's get out of here.
[CRYING]
WOMAN: I'm so happy [INAUDIBLE].
[SINGING] Now is you is, or is
you ain't my baby?
DAN: Let's go.
Kitchen.
I already have a mother.
She lives in Chicago.
DAN: Who you obviously didn't
listen to.
Look, I just want to stay here
for a few minutes.
You know I hate this place.
Same faces day in, day out.
You got five minutes.
Yo, wait up.
I said the same faces.
You wanna hang out?
Unless you have someplace to go?
What's wrong?
Are you comfortable around women
prisoners, or women prisoners?
Wanna play chess?
No.
You're the one that caught a
beating last night, right?
So what are you doing here?
What do you mean?
In here.
In jail.
Fucked up.
Got caught.
Everybody thinks they're
innocent until justice
can be served.
INTERCOM: Intention, all areas.
All areas, you have minutes left
on phones.
What's so funny?
Just the way you said that
shit, you know?
Like a trick might talk to a
hooker with a pretty girl,
like you doing this for 'em.
Have you tricked?
No.
Not in the way you mean.
Have you?
No.
Everybody compromises
themselves, honey.
What's your name?
Officer Cappelli.
Your five minutes are up.
Let's go.
You're the boss, creature.
What did you say?
Creature.
It suits you.
You want me to tell you about
yourself?
You're not married. You live
alone.
You like busting motherfuckers
upside the head.
You don't know shit about me.
I don't envy you, Officer
Cappelli.
You're not free.
You might as well be in here
with us.
As a matter of fact, you are.
And I thought you were a nice
girl.
I am a nice girl.
Yeah, let me ask you
something--
why'd you rat on your friend?
Maybe I was trying to impress
you.
Well, it didn't work.
Damned if we do, damned if we
don't.
It's your move.
Yeah, well, I ain't saying shit
till my lawyer gets here.
You do realize that we don't
want you.
You don't need to be in jail
right now.
We will help you out, but you're
costing us.
Yeah, well, I'd say you're
getting a fucking bargain.
Bargain? You want a bargain?
I'm going to give you a bargain,
all right?
You give us a list of the names
of all the people,
the places you've transacted
with,
and we're going to let you walk.
Yeah, my lawyer should be here.
Your lawyer?
Your lawyer's the biggest
charlatan.
You know something?
I think maybe your lawyer got
himself lost on the way
over here.
Or maybe-- you know, maybe he's
having
himself lunch with some big old
Hollywood producer?
You're wasting your time.
Yeah, well, you know, he's not
your lawyer.
He's there to protect Klein and
Angel.
Who I happen to know is living
quite large out there,
while you are in here.
How do you know?
How do I know?
It's my job to know.
And Angel-- Bobby, how am I
going to--
how am I going to tell her?
I don't believe you.
Well, why don't you listen?
Cause I'll just tell you.
No, no, you know what?
She's in denial right now.
But let me tell you something,
honey--
denial's not a river in Egypt,
and you're in goddamn jail.
You want to fucking tell me
something new, go ahead.
OK. OK.
I'll tell you all about Angel,
all right?
It looks like he has found some
greener pastures.
And baby, I'm not talking about
cabbages.
Stop fucking with my head.
We ain't fucking with nothing.
It's about time you got here.
I had some extra special red
tape at the door.
Have I missed much?
You gentlemen started without
me?
You weren't here.
Can I have a word with my
client?
Sure.
Go ahead.
So tell me how it's going.
Oh, really?
[INAUDIBLE]?
Then we're gonna go.
I'm very sorry, gentlemen, but
my client isn't feeling
very well at this moment.
Have a good day.
Hey, uh, Ryan?
If you want to reach us, you
know where to find us.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Yeah?
Hey, boss, it's Gidell.
I'll take it upstairs.
He's gonna get it upstairs.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hey, stuff. No, no, no.
It's just-- you know, I've been
busy.
Yeah, I heard.
I heard it from the lawyer.
Remember, Angel, I'm here
because of you.
If it wasn't for me, you
wouldn't
have that fucking club.
You know what I'm saying?
When you gonna come and see me?
You know, I missed you last
week.
I'm busy, baby.
I'm-- I'm really busy.
Well, at least tell me you love
me.
That goes without saying.
Come on, baby.
All that we've been through?
Of course.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFING]
Hey, Danny?
Danny?
Look what I got for ya. - What's
this?
Take a look.
Oh, wow.
I love these.
Yeah?
Thanks, Rose.
I got the recipe from your ma.
I remember she used to make
them,
I could smell 'em up in my room.
Yeah, remember that?
Yeah.
How's she doing?
Not too good.
They took some tests the other
day.
They gotta operate on her again.
Aw, that's a shame.
What are you gonna do, you
know?
Well, uh, listen, I was
thinking
of going to the movies on
Thursday,
and uh, I thought maybe you'd
like to go?
- This Thursday? - Yeah.
Aw, I can't this Thursday.
It's her birthday.
[THUNDER CRASHING]
Gonna do something special?
Ah-- naw, I just thought I'd go
over to the hospital,
you know, and see her.
Yeah.
Well, maybe some other time.
Yeah, let's do it.
You'd better get in.
It's starting to rain.
Yeah.
Well, thanks again.
I'll get the plate from you
later.
See ya.
INTERCOM: Visitor for inmate
Kelly.
Mommy, you look tired.
What's wrong?
I was working those slots all
night.
Mommy, I told you you can't go
to Atlantic City all the time.
You can't do that.
That's how come you ain't got
nothing.
Oh, baby, I was depressed.
I had to do something.
How's Frederick?
You know your brother.
Chip off the old block.
He's fine.
Angel send you that money?
No.
I knew that son of a bitch was
lying again.
I told you about his kind.
He really had you singing the
blues, all right.
INTERCOM: Visitor for inmate
Ryan.
Speaking of the devil.
Oh, Daddy.
What did I tell you about coming
in here dressed like that?
Can't help looking good, baby.
You look good, people will
actually
start thinking you are good.
Hello, Mrs. Ryan.
How are you? - Hello.
I'd better go, baby.
Don't wanna miss my train.
Give me a call when you get
home.
I will. I'll call you.
Take care, baby.
So how's the rat race?
Rats are winning.
The roaches are catching up?
Mhm.
So what's up?
Nothing much.
Same old, same.
You know?
Club ain't making it.
I'm thinking of selling.
No, don't do that.
Remember, half of it's mine.
It ain't the same anymore,
baby.
Not since you left.
People keep asking me, when's
Gidell getting out,
or when's she going to sing
again?
So is that the tape?
That's the tape.
Night Song.
Opening night.
Them were the days.
Mhm.
Who's keeping you warm at
night?
The bottle.
Not the blow?
Who can afford it?
So if you could afford it,
you'd do it?
Let's drop it, all right?
So I had a little visit from
the DA the other day.
They're trying to build a case
against you and Klein.
What did you tell him?
I told 'em to fuck off.
But they said if I cooperate,
they'll
take some time off my sentence.
What the fuck would you give
them the time of day for, huh?
That's stupid, man.
That is fucking stupid.
No, what is stupid is the fact
that you fucked up.
That's what's stupid.
No, we told you a million and
one times we'd get you out,
haven't we?
Look, baby, if Klein's going to
help with more money,
you don't need to hear this
shit, OK?
Yeah.
Like the money that you were
supposed to give my mother?
What is this, a fucking
prosecution, or what?
Where is my money, Angel?
I invested it, all right?
Your mom would have drunk that
money quicker than you
can blink, and you know it.
Come on, baby.
Let's not argue, huh?
You'd better get me out of
here, or I--
Or what? What?
What? What?
Huh?
You gonna bust out?
If the cops don't get you, Klein
will.
Look, I'll go by and see your
mom's, OK?
OK?
Now come over here and give me a
sugar smack.
Give me a sugar smack, I said.
Come on.
I'm not going to take this
anymore.
I have to get out of here.
[SINGING] I thought I caught a
fleeting glance of your eyes.
[INAUDIBLE]
I turned away and knew you'd
come, and walk slowly
down the path to my garden.
You're a night song.
WOMAN: That's good.
That's what she's singing.
Check it out.
WOMAN: She looks happy there.
She don't look so happy now.
GIDELL: [SINGING] For me to
always see.
You're a night song.
An angel in disguise.
WOMAN: Who's that guy?
GIDELL: [SINGING] I can see it
in your eyes.
You want me in your life.
I'm your night bird.
[CLAPPING]
All right, ladies. Lockdown.
Let's go.
[APPLAUSE]
What's that?
Opening night at my club.
So you were a singer before you
turned to a life of crime?
Don't fuck with me.
That was my life.
And that scumbag that was here
this afternoon,
is he a part of your life, too?
What scumbag?
The one you marked your arm up
with.
Angel.
Not anymore.
Looked that way to me.
Look, you don't know shit about
me, all right?
Get back to your cell.
Back to your cell.
I want to see you in the
shower.
Girls, cut this out.
Welcome home, Melita.
Thanks for being a fucking rat.
Hey, look, I tried to save your
ass.
I ain't your motherfucking
mother.
Well, with friends like you, I
don't need enemies.
So thanks to the benevolence of
Mr. Victor Klein, who's
been a pillar of strength in
this community,
we are here to witness the
erection
of this hospital for children.
A place of healing--
a place where children far and
wide
can come for medical attention.
And so, Mr. Klein, we would ask
you to lay the first ground
effort in this dream of ours.
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
[APPLAUSE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Angel.
How are you, buddy?
You look terrible.
I've got a lot of things on my
mind lately.
Gotta learn to step over the
bodies.
You know what I mean? - Yeah,
right.
Forget Gidell. She messed up.
She was working for us.
She was working for herself.
She knew the risks.
Do a couple of years, she'll get
off on parole.
Hey, she knows she can walk if
she talks.
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
Well, then you'd better shut
her up, or I will.
Look, Victor, I just thought
maybe we could--
I don't want to discuss it.
For God's sake, get a smile on
your face, huh?
Shirley?
Shirley, I want you to meet my
protege, Angel Delgado.
Terrific guy, terrific work.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, likewise.
Can you keep a secret?
This little angel writes all my
speeches.
She's a piston.
Talk amongst yourselves, huh?
So, uh, what did you say your
name was?
I didn't.
[TAPPING]
Conspiracy, fraud, and an
accomplice to a murder.
That's not bad for a first
timer.
Wow.
You can find out anything you
want to about me,
can't you, creature?
That's right.
[SINGING]
You can kiss, too, creature.
Too bad I can't tell the girls
in G2 about this.
You do, and I'm fucked.
That's enough.
Who's going to believe a felon
over a CO, huh?
Goodnight.
Ruin a nice moment.
[MOANING]
Close that window.
I said close the window!
I was just dizzy.
Shit.
If you're dizzy, go to the
infirmary.
You want to go to the nurse?
Naw.
Send his ass to the nurse.
You're a mean bastard.
All right, let's go.
Back to your cell.
Always busting my ass.
Cappelli. What's up?
How you fdoing? - How's it
going, Bishop?
- Not bad. - How's your arm?
It's all right.
It's almost healed.
How are things over on the G
side?
Good.
Yeah?
Anything happening over there?
Any difference between the way
it is over there and here?
Yeah.
It smells better.
Oh, yeah?
Dan.
She's bad news.
I know a guard who's been
fucking around with her, man.
Percy. C74.
Confirmed.
Look, do me a favor--
mind your own business, all
right?
OK.
You know the three monkeys?
I'm all that.
I got a degree from USC.
So?
I got one from UCLA.
What's that?
The university on the corner of
Lennox Avenue.
Oh, no!
Knock it off!
Hey, work detail.
Kelly, Cruz, and Ryan.
Let's go.
Shit!
[SHOUTING]
I can't get no cigarettes?
There you go.
No, I just--
Right in there, Kelly.
There's the mop.
You know what to do.
Right here, Cruz.
Make sure that room is clean.
Yeah, yeah.
It'll be immaculate just for
you, sugar.
There's the mop. There's the
bucket.
Get to work.
What's your problem?
How many guards in this place
have you fucked?
I ain't fucked any guards.
Look, don't lie to me, you
little whore.
WOMAN: I got a good one for you.
Yeah?
This man is dying of heat in
the summertime,
so he takes off his clothes, and
he lies naked, right there,
by the swimming pool.
He just covers up his face with
the post.
Oh?
These three women walk by--
oh, they're shocked.
They look at his nakedness.
The first one says, he's not my
husband.
The second one says, he's
definitely not your husband.
The third one says, he doesn't
even live in the building.
[LAUGHTER]
Hello, sweetie.
Oh, Dan.
Oh, very good for an old lady.
Look who's here.
She had me in stitches all
afternoon, Dan.
Oh, yeah.
Happy birthday.
Aw.
Rosie, don't get old.
I'll try not to.
Which reminds me about the
fella in Florida.
He was telling his son about the
three signs of old age.
First, loss of memory.
Second-- I forgot.
So how's everything down at
work, Danny?
Good.
It's good.
Rose, you've met my other son?
Yeah.
I think you met Nick when he
was a boy.
Oh, I thought that was Danny?
No, that's his brother, Nick.
Are you sure?
Sure.
I'm his mother.
He was such a gentle soul.
So kind.
[BEEPING]
To this day, I wonder why he
was so unhappy.
Why he had to take his own life.
Oh, Ethel, now, it's the past.
Wait.
Wait here.
I got something for you.
Dan?
[INAUDIBLE]
This girl's unbelievable.
Danny, what is the matter with
you?
This is a very nice girl.
She knows how to stretch a
dollar,
and she cooks, and she cleans,
and--
oh, Danny, she wants you.
Perez.
I see that boy's handwriting is
getting much better.
Ross.
More love letters?
Why you open my shit?
Tell your boyfriend he ain't no
Playgirl material.
I know you're getting off on
his situation.
Yeah, yeah.
Whatever.
Hey, Gidell?
Gidell?
You got something here.
Don't open it here.
Is it from that dick weed--
Parker.
- Fuck. - Thomas.
I knew that motherfucker was
lying
as soon as he opened his mouth.
WOMAN: Look, honey, a black
woman
is guilty until she can prove
innocence.
Yeah, well, let me read that
chapter on conspiracy, OK?
Johnson. You afraid of German
shepherds?
I ain't afraid of nothing.
Don't make me tell no lie,
though.
You're afraid of Angel.
He's still pushing your buttons.
Anybody in there?
Gidell?
Is that you?
Yeah.
WOMAN: What you doing in there?
I'm smoking.
WOMAN: But you don't smoke.
Now I do.
Now-- [CLATTERING] Get the fuck
out of here.
WOMAN: Girl, let me in. - No.
Go away.
WOMAN: I need that cleaning
junk.
Um-- it's not in here.
Why don't you go ask Officer
Cappelli?
[KNOCKING]
- Hey, Dan. - Hey, Rose.
How you doing?
Good.
I came by to pick up the plate.
From the cookies?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I didn't even get a chance to
eat 'em yet.
Oh, well, I can pick it up
later.
You got another beer?
Yeah.
You want one?
Yeah, I'd love one.
[PHONE RINGING]
VOICEMAIL: Leave a message after
the beep.
[BEEP]
GIDELL: Hey, CO.
Hope you don't mind me calling
you at home,
but I miss you, baby.
Felt really good this afternoon.
Been thinking of new places to
do it.
All right?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye.
INTERCOM: Attention all areas,
Officer Cappelli
to the main gate.
Attention all areas, Officer
Cappelli to the main gate.
Officer Cappelli to the main
gate.
Shit.
Look, maybe we can meet
tonight, before you go home?
No.
What's wrong?
Look, this has gotta stop.
[PHONE RINGING]
[RATTLING]
Hello?
DR. BLUMENTHAL: Mr. Cappelli? -
Yeah?
DR. BLUMENTHAL: This is Dr.
Blumenthal from the [INAUDIBLE]
Medical Center.
I'm sorry, but your mother
passed away this afternoon.
Hello?
Are you there?
[PUNCHES LANDING ON BAG]
Shoot your ass up.
I'm gonna--
Nice to see you.
Going back to his--
I know.
[INAUDIBLE].
What's that about?
What's this about?
I need to talk to you.
- Not now. - It won't take long.
I just wanna-- - I said not now.
See, America's [INAUDIBLE].
What the fuck you doing in my
chair?
Oh, here we go.
It's my fucking chair now.
Get the fuck out of my chair!
[SHOUTING]
Get that bitch!
Bitch!
Fucking bitch!
What the hell is wrong with
you?
I can't stand this
motherfucking place no more!
I gotta get out of here.
[INAUDIBLE]
INTERCOM: Condition yellow at
A3.
You need stitches on that.
Come on, I gotta take you to the
infirmary.
Come on.
INTERCOM: Code seven in C94.
Yeah, and where's your chain,
huh?
I don't know. I must have left
it at home.
Yeah? With who?
What do you mean, with you?
Well, tell me about her.
Is she some college type, or
something?
Somebody to turn herself inside
out for you?
Who's telling you this shit?
Never mind.
No, no, no, no, no.
Let's backtrack here a little
bit.
You assume I'm seeing somebody
because you're
not around to watch me?
Is that it?
You think I'm afraid of you?
Hm?
Or are you getting so hard up in
here,
you want an excuse to start your
own little hanky
motherfucking panky?
I ain't stupid, baby.
And I happen to know how fucking
vengeful you are.
Who is it?
Somebody I happen to know?
You don't know shit.
You get a call from Melita, or
something?
You belong to me, you
understand?
What, are you turning into a
dyke on me?
[LAUGHTER]
What the fuck is so funny?
What makes you think it's a
woman?
What's going on?
[SHOUTING]
[ALARM]
[BABY CRYING]
Fuck!
You fuck!
I am not convinced you had no
other choice, Officer Cappelli.
You've done this one too many
times.
Besides, you're putting
unnecessary pressure
on the department.
It is the decision of this board
that you
be suspended from all duties and
pay pertaining to that
of a correctional officer,
pending
a complete psychological
evaluation
and subsequent committee hearing
to ascertain readiness
for resumption of duties.
SINGER: Die a little.
Every single day of your life.
Die a little.
INTERCOM: Your rec time is over.
SINGER: One more night passes
by.
One more day in the edge of
time.
Something makes you wanna fade
away.
Something always seems to make
you stay.
- [INAUDIBLE]. - Have a good
one.
All right.
Thank you. - It's closing time.
Joe, gimme another shot, huh?
It's closing time, Danny.
One more shot, huh?
All right.
You all right, Danny?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[DISTANT CONVERSATIONS]
[PHONE RINGING]
Yeah?
GIDELL: Where the fuck have you
been?
I've been trying to contact you
for days.
I've been here.
I just haven't been answering
the phone.
Look, I--
I can't talk too loud.
There's too many people around.
OK, listen-- every 28 days, I
get it.
That's the routine.
You know what I'm talking about?
Well, it didn't come this time.
I mean, I've gained 8 pounds.
This morning when I was washing
dishes, the Comet made me sick.
And then I want to eat
everything in sight.
You know what I'm saying?
What the hell are you talking
about?
I'm talking about our baby.
What?
Look, look--
I don't want to have a baby in
jail.
I-- I don't want to go to E
unit.
DAN: What do you want me to do
about it?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Dan.
How you doing?
Good.
Hey, uh, sorry to hear about
the suspension.
Look, I've got some things in
my locker I want to get out.
You want to go inside?
Don't think I can do that.
It'll take me five minutes.
OK.
Five minutes.
But you gotta sign in.
Pull it up.
Hey!
Where are you going so early?
Getting in early.
You look like shit.
Oh, I feel so fucked up.
I wonder why.
If you weren't so fucked up on
that shit all the time,
you'd be pretty happy.
Dang.
You're uptight.
What, did you run into the
closet lately?
Angel still paying you to be in
my business?
Look, I haven't said shit to
nobody, all right?
All right, ladies. Work detail.
Let's go.
Let's move, please.
Any day, now.
Let's go.
[SNIFFING]
[RETCHING]
[KNOCKING]
Hey, Cappelli.
I thought you were fired?
- I've been reinstated. - OK.
That's cool, man.
Look, I've got an inmate going
to the infirmary.
OK.
[SINGING] Don't got much
respect,
cause I held up my rep.
And that bitch over there is
going--
DAN: Ryan.
To get what--
Coming, coming.
At her like a Muhammad Ali,
punched her in the face,
and put her in fear.
And if my looks were a knife
fight, cut her with my stares.
And if she danced at my way,
beware, my gangsters--
INTERCOM: Attention, all areas.
Staff dining room is open.
Time on deck is 6:50.
All officers, make your lunch
reliefs.
Staff dining room is open.
- She's going to a hearing. -
Whose orders?
Captain Miller.
I didn't hear anything about
this.
What, are you new?
Yeah.
How long you been working here?
Three weeks.
I've been working here eight
years.
Open the fucking gate.
Yeah, but shouldn't we call
somebody about--
You want to call the warden?
No. I mean--
Open up!
MAN: Up.
Other one.
Gate open.
MAN: Hey, Dan?
Dan, come here.
You got a big hole in your
muffler.
You'd better fix it.
Yeah.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Come on.
Open the trunk.
I'll pay for the cab.
Come on.
This thing gets stuck.
Gotta look inside.
All right, go on.
Close it up.
Get it out of here.
Open it!
[LAUGHTER]
SINGER: How deep is an ocean?
How far is that shining star?
How strong is my devotion?
What's more real than love in
life?
I don't need all your treasures.
I want to bury all my pride.
The precious gift is freedom.
Transmission to your heart.
And there are no direct flights
going to El Paso?
What time is the flight to
Albuquerque?
That's too late.
And the flight to Tucson?
Yeah, I'll need two coach
tickets.
Johnson.
Mr. And Mrs. And I can pick them
up at the gate, right?
Right.
Thank you.
There's a flight leaving for
Tucson in 45 minutes.
If we hurry up, we can make it.
It's a half hour drive from the
border.
We can be in Mexico tomorrow
night.
OK, so that's the Lagul Hotel.
That's room 205.
Mr. and Mrs. Johnson.
Yeah.
Five minutes, right?
You can de-- you don't fucking
deliver?
What-- never mind.
Who's that?
Chinese joint. They don't
deliver.
What are you doing?
I just told you we gotta get to
the airport.
I'm hungry.
Get ready here.
I'll go downstairs and get us
something.
Can I get a refill, please?
Give me a beer.
Give me a couple of those
sandwiches to go, too.
NEWSCASTER: Action News,
Delaware
Valley's leading news program.
REPORTER: It happened in broad
daylight.
Inmate Gidell Ryan escaped right
here, through this gate,
from Holmesburg Prison.
She was missing from roll call
at 3:00 PM,
but it wasn't until 7:00 PM when
the authorities
pieced together her escape.
We believe a correctional
officer
who was recently suspended
assisted her in the escape.
REPORTER: The police have linked
a correction officer
by the name of Dan Cappelli to
the mysterious escape
from Holmesburg Prison.
Gidell Ryan was serving a six
year
sentence after being charged
with money
laundering and conspiracy.
Also implicated were several
prominent businessmen.
God dammit.
Among them was Victor Klein.
KLEIN: That bitch.
The district attorney's office
indicated
this afternoon that they're
considering
reopening this case.
[INAUDIBLE].
REPORTER: I'm Lisa Gultera,
Channel 7 News.
Gidell, we gotta get out of
here now.
What the fuck are you doing
here?
I'm the Chinese joint that
don't deliver.
You fucked her, didn't you?
Didn't you? Hm?
Hm?
You that desperate, man?
Hu?
You gotta make it with the
inmates, you fucked--
Didn't I tell you to wait
outside?
What's going on in here?
Just thanking him, baby.
After all, he was so gallant and
kind-hearted.
All that shit.
Mr. And Mrs. Johnson?
Ain't that sweet?
A honeymoon in Tucson.
Hey, [INAUDIBLE], CO.
Hey, CO?
Did he kiss like that?
Huh?
Why you always gotta do
everything you say
you're not going to do, huh?
Aw.
I do believe you have a soft
spot for this motherfucker
right here.
I just want to get the fuck out
of here with you.
It ain't that simple.
He knows I'm involved, OK?
It ain't that fucking simple!
Ain't that fucking simple.
Tie his fucking hands.
Don't struggle, you bitch.
Don't struggle.
Is that your car down there?
If that's what you wanna call
it.
Better take yours.
Can't do that.
Why not?
Cause we're gonna dump this
fucking scumbag here,
and his car.
Get in the fucking car.
Get in the car.
Get in Get in.
Angel!
Where are you going?
Angel, you are a one man fuck
up, you know what?
What was I supposed to do, huh?
She needed a ride to work, you
call.
What the fuck was I supposed to
do?
You make me sick!
Aw, shut the fuck up.
Get in the car.
Get in the fucking car!
Get in.
Shut up. Shut the fuck up.
Get in the fucking car.
Get--
I don't fucking understand you,
man.
I don't understand you. She's so
fucking ugly.
There is nothing going on.
Yeah, right.
Did Mr. Klein give her to you?
Is that what happened?
Is that why I was in fucking
jail all this time?
There is nothing going on.
I'm gonna tell you one more
time, nothing going on.
All right?
What the fuck are you looking
at?
Fuck you.
Fuck me?
Fuck you, you fuck. Don't say
shit.
You're going to make a good
father for that little bastard
that's inside her stomach.
What the fuck are you talking
about?
She's going to have a baby.
No, I'm not.
I'm not going to have a fucking
baby, man.
I just made it up.
I made it up because I had to
get the fuck out of there.
And you weren't doing nothing.
And--
You ain't fucking with me now,
are you?
No. I'm not.
Hey, asshole.
There is no baby.
I guess not.
ANGEL: You ain't got the fucking
balls for a fucking baby.
It's a sick world, huh, Danny?
But you know what?
You'll do better in the next
one.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
You like to kick?
[GUNSHOT]
Get out.
Get out!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I-- I'm--
I'm sorry about the baby.
I just-- I just--
I just needed to get the fuck
out of there.
You--
What did you call that fucking
scumbag for, anyway?
He was like, my drug man, you
know?
I thought I loved him.
I mean, one minute I'm in--
in jail, and the next minute I'm
in a fucking hotel
room with a CO that I don't
hardly know.
You know I didn't want him to
kill you, right?
There's a plane leaving for
Albuquerque tonight.
You want to come, you come.
But when we get there, you're on
your own.
You understand me?
Don't look.
Hey, boys.
You're early.
Get your coat.
Let's go.
WAITRESS: What would you like to
drink?
Will there be anything else,
hon?
Check, please.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
God, Angel, tell me this isn't
happening.
It isn't happening.
You're going back to her?
Yeah.
I'm going back to her.
[INAUDIBLE].
She's not-- she's not worth it!
Angel!
Hey, Victor.
I heard about Gidell.
She skipped with the CO, but I
know where she is, OK?
I'll take care of it, all right?
I'll take care of it.
Make sure he does it.
Then give him his bonus.
Here are your boarding passes,
Mrs. Johnson.
Gate A2.
Have a nice trip.
May I help you?
[INAUDIBLE], Mrs. Johnson.
Aren't you happy to see me?
WOMAN [ON INTERCOM]: Final call
for American Airlines Flight
938 to Albuquerque at Gate B2.
[DING]
WOMAN [ON INTERCOM]: One.
Level five.
[DING]
WOMAN [ON INTERCOM]: Final call
American Airlines Flight
938 to Albuquerque at gate B2.
Drop it.
[SCREAMING]
Get the fuck off me!
Go!
[GUNFIRE]
Hey, scumbag!
Let's do it, huh?
Let's do it now!
[SNIFFING]
Come on, you fuck!
You fuck!
Come on!
Come on, you fuck!
[GUNFIRE]
Come on!
REPORTER: And in the latest
development of the Ryan
case, federal agents arrested
Victor
Klein at his Brentwood Estate.
The grand jury indicted Klein
after money
laundering charges were made.
The death of inmate Ryan
initiated this investigation.
The whereabouts of the
correction officer that
assisted her is still unknown.
DAN [VOICEOVER]: It's strange--
I never got to know her.
Still, I will never forget her.
She helped me break a vicious
cycle.
She showed me the way out.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGING] Stronger emotions.
How far is from heart to heart?
You'll never kill my feelings.
I'd better die if I'm cold
inside.
Is Love is stronger than that.
Love is harder than burning sun.
All we need is to give love.
Transmission to your heart.
Transmission.
Transmission!