(insects chirping)
(suspenseful music)
(whooshing)
(Princess Mika screaming)
Mika, I'm trying not to drop it.
(groaning) My hands are burning.
Oh, god, it's burning!
Help!
(weapons whooshing)
(birds chirping)
(arms whoosh)
Will! Please, Will.
You gotta kill them now!
Please, Will, don't run!
Don't run!
Will.
Hold on, Dimm.
Please, don't let the pot go.
Please, Dimm, hold on!
I'm trying to hold on.
(Princess Mika whimpers)
(knife whooshing)
[Princess Mika] Just hold on longer.
Will, come on.
You gotta fight these guys.
I can't hold it.
(Thor grunting)
(man grunting)
(arms whooshing)
(Princess Mika whimpering)
(Dimm groaning)
(leg whooshes)
(foot thuds)
(Dimm screaming)
(leg whooshes)
(man grunts)
(leg whooshing)
(foot thuds)
(man groans)
(man groaning)
(foot thudding)
(Dimm groaning)
(Princess Mika whimpering)
Hold on, Princess!
I'm coming!
First, you're gonna have
to go through me, little man.
(Thor laughing)
(leg whooshes)
(foot thuds)
(body thuds)
(Thor grunts)
(hand thudding)
(Will groaning)
(Thor grunting)
Will, will you please kill this guy?
(Princess Mika whimpering)
(arms whooshing)
(Will groaning)
(fist thuds)
(Thor groaning)
(Will groaning)
(arm whooshes)
Dimm, don't drop that.
Please, Dimm, don't drop it.
(Will groaning)
(leg whooshes)
(leg thudding)
Take him out!
Come on!
(arm whooshes)
(Thor grunts)
(leg whooshing)
(foot thuds)
(fist thuds)
(Thor grunts)
(leg whooshes)
(arm whooshes)
(Thor grunting)
(foot thuds)
(Will grunts)
(fist thudding)
(foot thuds)
(fist thuds)
(Dimm groaning)
(foot thuds)
(Will groans)
(arm whooshes)
(fist thuds)
(arm thuds)
Just hold on a little bit longer.
(Will grunting)
(fist thuds)
(Will grunts)
(fists thudding)
(Dimm groaning)
(flesh sizzling)
I'm trying, Mika.
Hold on, Princess!
I'm coming!
Not unless you kill me.
(flesh sizzling)
(elbow thuds)
(Thor groans)
(fist thudding)
(Dimm groaning)
Please, just hold on a
little bit longer, Dimm.
Please.
(leg thuds)
(fist thudding)
(Thor groaning)
(Will grunting)
(Dimm grunting)
I can't hold it, I'm sorry!
Please, hurry! I can't! (screaming)
(flesh sizzling)
(brooding music)
(graphic humming)
(graphic whirring)
(computer chirps)
(computer beeps)
(whooshing)
Com-link to Crowley Gaming.
[Computer] Done.
Hello, Crowley games division.
How may we help you?
Hi. Uh... look, I was just playing
"Tai Chi Gut Buster,"
the new one, level 120,
which is the Qing Dynasty.
And my opponent, Cam Chi... it's weird,
he used a drunken monkey move.
Yeah, that's a difference
of, like, 2,000 years.
I don't know if you know that.
Our games are designed by
top martial arts experts,
there's no way a mistake like
that could have been made.
Oh, well, um, it did happen.
It was made.
Sir, why don't you
just play the game again?
What's wrong with you people?
Look, you know, I'm trying
to be nice about this,
but I'm trying to help you with your game.
You know, I know a lot
about these subjects.
[Employee] Well, thank you very much.
You know, I've noticed this
is your third complaint
this month, Mr. Singleton.
So?
Just noting it for our files.
Is that all?
Uh, no, um, one other thing.
You can suck my "fuck you."
[Computer] Com-link complete.
Jesus, "suck my fuck you"?
Where the hell did I come up with that?
(computer beeps)
(sultry saxophone music)
Come on, Will, take a
break from that for a while.
I saw you working out and
it made me so... you know.
So what?
[Woman] So horny.
Nah, I can't.
I gotta take care of Cam Chi
and his drunken monkey move.
You don't even have time
for something really quick?
Quick, hmm?
Nah, I don't think so.
Well, I mean, with you,
it's never a quickie.
It's just sometimes, you
make me want you so bad.
You're the only man that can satisfy me.
Oh, Will, I want you all to myself.
(lips smacking)
(woman moans)
[Computer] Enter keycard.
Good evening, Ms. Conroy.
(computer beeps)
I want you all to myself.
You're the only man that can satisfy me.
(remote beeps)
[Reporter] Government news,
the pentagon unveiled plans
to unite our entire defense
network under one cyber system.
No word yet which company
will be awarded the contract.
In White House news...
(reporter chattering)
(Tory scoffs)
(Tory sighs)
Will, what the fuck?
(reporter chattering)
(computer beeps)
Tory, I thought you weren't
coming home until tomorrow.
Well, I'm back.
Why do you use that thing?
You know how much it disgusts me.
But I don't use it when you're here.
(scoffs) What a perfect emotional match.
You can handle her, she doesn't talk back.
Look, Tory, I want you.
(Tory scoffs)
You're real.
This is just some stupid toy
to feed my little boy impulses.
Delete the program.
(scoffs) Delete the program?
Yeah, delete the program.
That's it.
Your favorite software is now deleted.
[Reporter] Pan German
financier Herr Heinz Dietrich
and American mogul R.D. Crowley
signed an historic agreement today,
finalizing the long awaited merger
between the world's two largest companies.
You know, Crowley is
such a fucking genius.
You should have seen the
place he put us up in.
It reeked of money.
You ever not think about work?
Well, maybe I would if I had your job.
That is so fucked up,
Tory, and you know it.
My job is perfectly fine until
I figure out what I wanna do.
And when is that gonna be?
I don't know.
You keep asking me that
and I keep telling you, I don't know.
Look, I'm sorry.
I just... I just feel like I
missed my calling or something.
I know that sounds really lame to you.
Maybe it's time for more vid therapy.
She was really helpful
last time, wasn't she?
I guess.
Yeah, and didn't she say
you should turn your obsession
with history into...?
Fixation.
No, she called it an obsession.
Whatever.
Can't you turn that into a website job?
Yeah, except nobody
cares about history today.
All right, fine, then just give up.
Look, I've got a score to settle.
(computer beeps)
(suspenseful music)
(Princess Mika whimpering)
(computer beeping)
Mika, I'm trying not...
(foot thudding)
(foot whooshes)
(Will grunts)
(foot thuds)
(man groans)
Will, come on!
Please, kill him now, Will!
(foot thuds)
(fist thuds)
(man groans)
(foot thuds)
(arm whooshes)
(Will grunts)
Will, please.
(fist thuds)
(Thor groans)
(foot thuds)
(fist thudding)
(Will grunting)
(Dimm groaning)
(Princes Mika whimpering)
(Thor grunting)
(Thor groaning)
(bones cracking)
[Computer] Illegal move, illegal move.
Forfeit match, forfeit.
- Sorry.
- Illegal move.
Illegal move.
Match forfeit, match forfeit.
If he can use the drunken
monkey move, so can I.
(ominous music)
(man vocalizing)
(door creaking)
(man retching)
(door bangs)
I can't die.
Let's go, Christy.
[Christy] Please, I'm an innocent man.
[Will] It's time.
Come my, son.
Let Jesus into your heart
and the Kingdom of Heaven is yours.
Get me the fuck out of here.
It's not even for real.
(door bangs)
[Will] Come on.
It's time to go now.
I'm going to die for no reason.
You can't let that happen.
- Look, you were given
a fair trial, you were found guilty.
It wasn't a fair trial.
Christy, you killed and ate your wife!
They found parts of her in your stomach!
It's time to pay the bill, Christy!
I was framed, I swear.
(door bangs)
Come on, get up.
Don't make this harder than it has to be.
Goddammit, Christy, move it.
♪ Mine eyes have seen the glory ♪
of the coming of Christy Pound ♪
♪ He has eaten all ♪
Let's go.
♪ Kids and now no one's left around ♪
♪ He has eaten all their parts ♪
♪ And piled their bones into a mound ♪
♪ His soul is marching on ♪
♪ Glory, glory, hallelujah ♪
♪ God, Christy Pound is coming to ya ♪
♪ His truth is marching on ♪
Hey, Christy, how you like that?
Bye, bye!
(Baracus yelling)
(ominous music)
This is it.
[Christy] Painless, right?
They flood your body with poisons.
You'll expire without even knowing it.
And when I walk through
the door, it starts?
[Will] Yeah.
Well...
guess I found a way out.
(doors rumbling)
(doors bang)
(program whooshing)
(Will panting)
(computer beeps)
You can't go offline any time you want.
The trick to virtual reality
is keeping it as real as possible.
Look, I need to
downlink, all right, man?
I owe you one.
Will Singleton owes me one.
Back to work.
(ominous music)
(computer beeps)
R.D. Crowley, please.
(computer beeping)
(machine beeping)
(air hissing)
(body thuds)
(cart rattling)
(door rattling)
(door bangs)
(ominous music)
(water dripping)
(door bangs)
(man chattering)
H.
A.
R.
R?
Yeah.
Okay, R.
H-A-R-R?
Yeah.
(Will chuckles)
Okay.
Why do you two play this fucking game?
Gotta do something to
keep the brain working.
You wanna know the rules?
No, I don't wanna
know the fucking rules.
It's called Ghost.
We each take turns saying a letter.
The key is to not finish spelling a word.
- Shut up!
- But you can't pick any word.
You know? You can't just say anything.
You can't throw out any letter
and make up a word like "goobergobber."
You got that, Martin?
Yeah, I got it.
I.
E.
E?
No way E.
E.
Challenge.
"Harrier."
Small dog used for hunting rabbits.
I should know, I used to have one.
You used to hunt rabbits?
I was born and raised
on one of the last working farms in Iowa.
Absolutely the most
beautiful place in the world.
It's gone now.
What word were you looking for?
Oh, uh, "harridan."
Scolding old woman.
[Stu] (chuckles) Why?
You have one of those?
I have a girlfriend.
She does get on my case
every now and then.
(door bangs)
No, I don't have a woman.
Just a little brother.
Well, uh, I don't mean to be rude,
but it's late, I gotta run.
[Stu] What, are you crazy?
You can do no wrong.
You shouldn't be talking
to those fucking pricks.
He'll split your head
open first chance he gets.
(machine beeping)
(Christy groaning)
(liquid bubbling)
(Christy screaming)
(liquid whirring)
(liquid dripping)
(saw buzzing)
(flesh tearing)
Dual bypass.
Check.
Cerebellum connection.
Hey, moving nicely.
This could be a new record.
You are timing this, right?
Oh, yeah.
All right, start up Subcon Shareware.
(computer whirring)
Right.
Okay, message going in.
And message coming back.
Okay, good.
Chip insertion.
Cerebral cortex interface.
(computer beeps)
We should have visual.
- He does.
- Good.
Is he interacting?
Yeah, he is.
Okay, great.
Time?
34 seconds.
Fantastic loading.
Thank you.
Okay, close him up
and let's try to break 30 on the next one.
(suspenseful music)
(birds chirping)
(sword clanging)
(gun clicking)
(Christy panting)
(water splashing)
(Christy screaming)
(gun bangs)
(birds chirping)
(machine beeping)
(man chattering)
(air hissing)
(ominous music)
(water dripping)
(door bangs)
Please let it be Heaven.
I've done some things that
should put me in Hell,
but I've also done a lot of things
that should put me with Him.
Go with the grace of God.
(doors rumbling)
(guns firing)
(suspenseful music)
(group chattering)
(gun firing)
(guns firing)
What the fuck is going on?
We're in the hole,
man, they're everywhere!
They're fucking everywhere, man!
I don't know.
(guns firing)
(gun firing)
(gun clicks)
Motherfucker, you wanna get spanked?
I'll spank you, motherfucker!
Yeah, you fuck!
Come on, yeah!
Motherfucker!
Come on!
That's right, come on,
motherfucker! (screaming)
Yeah, goddammit!
Come at me, motherfuckers!
Come on!
Come on, you fucks!
Goddammit, motherfucker!
Shit!
What the fuck are you doing here?
(gun firing)
Sit down, Will.
This will be quick.
Mr. Crowley and I have a few things
we'd like to discuss with you.
Good day, Mr. Singleton.
I regret that I'm not able
to speak with you in person.
I understand, sir.
Let's get right to it, Mr.
Crowley has a schedule to keep.
Will, we have a problem with
your interaction behavior.
How so?
Uh, allow me.
You see, Will, I designed
this virtual prison
as a system of punishment.
These criminals... well,
they must be treated
with absolute authority.
They don't have the
intelligence to grasp the idea
they are being controlled
on a cyberscape level.
You work for the program.
We do not want you to show
one single prisoner
any respect whatsoever.
They do not deserve respect, understood?
Understood?
Yeah.
Amazingly rude, Daniel.
(sighs) Well, thank you, Will.
I'll be watching.
(computer chirps)
(clock ticking)
(ominous music)
(man laughing)
(group chattering)
(door bangs)
On your way to the women's section?
(program whooshing)
What is it?
What is that?
What... what the fuck is...?
What the fuck is that?
- Relax, Martin.
It's just the program rebooting itself.
Rebooting itself.
Look, I wasn't raised to be
rebooted every two hours, okay?
Stu, I can't, uh, I can't keep talking
to you like this, all right?
Will.
(door clanking)
(door bangs)
You know what I'm in for, don't you?
Murder.
Federal agent.
(door bangs)
You're the only one I
can tell the truth to.
Stop.
I know what they tell me.
My dad died.
Payments were owed, there wasn't
anybody gonna bail us out.
I know it was stupid,
but I just couldn't
walk away from the farm.
Ten generations of my family
looking over my shoulder,
counting on me to do the right thing.
I wasn't gonna shoot anybody.
I just wasn't gonna lay there like a dog
and let them take everything I ever had.
(door clicks)
He died.
And they arrested me for the
murder of a federal agent.
Death penalty.
(door bangs)
(sighs) You are the only person
that knows the truth about what happened.
Mace was only 16, he didn't deserve that.
(Stu sighs)
So there you are.
That's some hard luck, man.
(door bangs)
You'd had done the same thing.
Wouldn't you, Will?
I don't know, Stu.
Look, I gotta go.
(brooding synth music)
(computer whirring)
(computer chirps)
(door bangs)
Will!
(ominous music)
My time's coming soon.
You'll be taking that walk with me.
That's right, Baracus,
and there's a lot of people
looking forward to that day.
Oh, yes, so many people
think I've ruined their lives.
(door bangs)
I didn't just remove loved ones,
sometimes I removed problems.
You should thank me.
You do have a unique
perspective, Baracus.
And you do, too.
Intelligence has its
own perspective, Will.
(door bangs)
[Will] Yeah, I've
got a schedule to keep.
Will, you're my only
link to the outside, Will.
I know you.
I know your capabilities
mentally, physically.
Don't waste 'em on this menial job
and those silly games you play.
Will, let me help you
reach your full potential.
I gotta give you credit, Baracus,
you always give it a good effort.
(door bangs)
Where's Stewart Lewis?
I don't know.
They put me in here.
(door bangs)
(computer beeps)
There are no unscheduled downlinkings.
You must make a schedule.
Where was Stewart Lewis transferred to?
[Coworker] Does it really matter?
(computer beeps)
[Employee] Stewart Lewis, lot
397, transferred all freeze.
Shit!
Request vidcon with Mr. Traven, ASAP.
[Employee] No available
meetings scheduled.
Will notify.
You don't understand, I insist.
[Employee] One moment.
(computer beeps)
Yes, Will, how may I help you?
Where was Stewart Lewis transferred to?
You see, this is what happens
when you make an attachment
to these kinds of people.
Get nothing but trouble.
He was transferred, I don't know why.
This program is much better.
Is that all?
I need more information, Traven.
That's all I have.
It's a closed file.
Now, I've got work to do.
Will, do not make this a habit.
(computer beeps)
Fuck!
This is bullshit.
Tory work.
(computer beeps)
[Receptionist] There's a
phone call for you, Ms. Conroy.
It's your boyfriend.
Ugh.
All right.
Yeah, what is it?
Yeah, this is a switch,
but, uh, I'm gonna be
running late tonight.
Why?
Uh, Stu Lewis was
transferred out of Idwell today
and I've gotta find out why.
[Tory] Stu Lewis?
Jesus, Tory, I've told you
about him a million times.
Well, I don't remember.
Is there a problem?
Yeah, there's a few actually,
but I'd rather not speak
about it over open air.
(laughs) Don't do anything stupid, Will.
I know that, Tory.
Look, they put him under all freeze.
What's that?
All freeze designation is usually held
for convicts turned informant.
Well, good, maybe he's
in a witness protection
program or something.
No, that's the problem, there's no way.
Stu didn't have any shaky
connections like that.
How do you know?
I mean, they all say they're innocent.
He's just another one of them.
I believe him, Tory.
(Tory sighs)
He's a criminal.
He deserves everything he gets.
Look, don't do anything
asinine over one of them.
You are a cold bitch.
Did you just call me a bitch?
Because if you did...
- Delete.
I'm gonna fucking...
(computer beeps)
All right.
Let's get down to business.
(tense music)
(flags rustling)
(machine beeping)
Request all information on Stewart Lewis.
(computer beeps)
All freeze.
Where do prisoners go
for final termination?
Taken to an unspecified location
for removal of li-li-life.
Authorize prison guard
requesting specific location.
St-st-state your clearance.
So that's where Stu Lewis is?
(computer beeps)
[Computer] All freeze, all
freeze, approach for clearance.
Verbal interaction over.
Suck off.
(computer beeps)
Th-th-thank you.
(ominous music)
(body thuds)
(computer beeping)
(door clanging)
(door bangs)
(swords clanging)
(Stu groaning)
(clock ticking)
(Daniel grunting)
(swords clanging)
(implant beeping)
(Stu groaning)
(birds chirping)
(swords clanging)
(both grunting)
(brooding music)
(clock ticking)
(swords clanging)
(Stu grunting)
(clock ticking)
(birds chirping)
(Daniel grunting)
(swords clanging)
(Heinz grunting)
(sword whooshes)
(swords clanging)
(Heinz grunting)
(Stu grunting)
(swords clanging)
(Stu and Heinz grunting)
(Heinz grunting)
(swords clanging)
(sword whooshes)
(Stu grunting)
(swords clanging)
(Heinz grunting)
(sword whooshes)
(swords clanging)
(Heinz grunting)
(computer beeps)
(clock ticking)
(Stu grunting)
(Heinz grunting)
(implant beeps)
(Stu grunting)
(program whooshing)
(Heinz grunting)
(computer beeps)
(clock ticking)
(computer beeping)
What took you so long?
People are dying to meet you.
So this is what you
do with the prisoners?
I've given them purpose, Will.
My consumer games, which
you excel at, by the way,
are controlled by the most
sophisticated programs
that can be written.
The code for these contains thousands
of gigabytes of information.
That's a mere fraction of
what the human brain holds.
People are dangerous, unpredictable.
Their survival instinct
allows them to react instantaneously.
Now that would make this an exciting play.
Jesus, you've done it.
[R.D.] I've created the world's
most realistic virtual game. (laughing)
You are a sick bastard, Crowley.
Oh, please, don't be judgmental.
You were handpicked from the
top players of my consumer net.
If you weren't so damn good...
All you needed was a little...
[Tory] Motivation.
(brooding music)
Tory.
Thank you.
I was right about you.
You are a cold bitch.
Vicious.
(sighs) You see, Will, I
knew you were intelligent.
All that was needed was to
feed you a little information,
and that's where Ms. Conroy
(lips smack)
was so helpful.
I bet she was.
I'd like to present
some of my associates.
Heinz Dietrich.
One of the preeminent
industrialists of our time.
Montgomery Valentine, the last scion
of a fine, old Southern family.
Mr. Valentine prides himself
on being a sportsman.
And of course, Daniel Traven,
your superior officer.
You can be part of the ultimate game.
Of course, your function in this game
is to provide a challenge
to these sporting men,
who have paid handsomely, I might add,
to hunt you down and kill you.
Now, you will be placed
in an historical scenario of my choosing.
Your garb and weapons will
be accurately detailed
and quite deadly.
If you dispatch the three
gentlemen, you survive
until the next scenario, of course.
Gentlemen, you get what you pay for.
Welcome to your greatest challenge yet.
(suspenseful music)
Take him to surgery.
(gun bangs)
(group chattering)
(man yelling)
(guns firing)
Our prey should be
appearing at any moment now.
(gun bangs)
Mr. Traven, I find your
attire very intriguing.
Unlike you, I like to get my hands wet.
The scale of this battle's incredible.
Crowley, you've outdone yourself.
Your program is fantastische.
And a damn fine day for a little sport,
don't you think, gentlemen?
(suspenseful music)
(gun firing)
(group chattering)
(guns banging)
(group groaning)
Ah, this is great.
You know how to load a musket?
(gun bangs)
Actually, I do.
(gun fires)
Do it quick.
Try and stay alive.
Figure a way out of this mess.
(guns banging)
There's too much smoke.
Can't see who's firing at us.
Yeah, we gotta figure
out who our enemy is
and who's on our side.
(guns firing)
Uh, Will, they made us Red Coats.
The American colonials are our enemies.
(guns banging)
Crowley's such a bastard.
This could be the French and Indian War,
which would mean the American
colonials are on our side.
We're actually fighting the French army
and their Huron allies.
(gun bangs)
Uh, we're screwed.
We don't know who were fighting
'til they come up and
shoot us in the face.
Pretty much.
(guns banging)
(birds chirping)
(gun fires)
(bullet whooshes)
(guns banging)
(gun fires)
(program buzzing)
(group yelling)
(body thudding)
(computer beeping)
Damn.
That boy has a damn fine eye.
(group yelling)
A lot of time on the farm.
(gun bangs)
You could say I'm the best shot in Iowa.
(guns banging)
Shit.
Daniel.
Dietrich.
Reload?
No, we're dead out here in the open.
Let's go for cover.
(guns banging)
(hatchet thuds)
(Daniel grunts)
(guns banging)
(man groaning)
(knife whooshes)
(body thuds)
(man grunts)
(gun bangs)
(hatchet whooshes)
(man groans)
(gun bangs)
(hatchet thudding)
(man groaning)
(hatchet thuds)
(gun firing)
(blade whooshes)
(man groans)
(man groaning)
(hatchet thudding)
(gun banging)
(Daniel grunting)
(foot thuds)
(man groaning)
(Daniel grunting)
(gun banging)
(ominous music)
(Daniel yelling)
(cloth ripping)
(man groaning)
(suspenseful music)
(gun fires)
(cloth ripping)
(gun bangs)
[Guard] Halt.
Who goes there?
As you were.
(man gurgling)
(blade thuds)
(man groans)
(body thuds)
(blade thudding)
(man groaning)
(blade whooshes)
(body thuds)
(doors creaking)
(blade thuds)
(man groans)
(blade whooshes)
(blade thuds)
(man groans)
(man groaning)
(hatchet whooshes)
(arrow whooshing)
(arrow thuds)
(gun banging)
(Heinz groaning)
(gun bangs)
(bullet whooshes)
(Daniel grunting)
(arrow whooshes)
(Stu groaning)
(knife clangs)
(Stu grunts)
(Daniel grunts)
(gun bangs)
(Daniel groans)
(computer beeps)
Things are getting interesting.
Indeed.
I am in love with the multiple prey angle.
Well, I must say I'm pleased to see
that you gentlemen are
enjoying yourselves.
Of course, more prey means more money.
I think we all understand
the tenets of capitalism.
Now, let's play.
Now, hold your horses.
I'd like to know what it is I'm hunting.
Give me the psych profile on that guard.
Of course.
He's single.
Has a normal upbringing.
And he has an acute interest in history,
which manifests itself in
obsessive VR game playing,
such as martial arts, target
practice, flight simulating.
Flight simulation?
(plane engine roaring)
I know how to fly.
I do.
Just not a real one.
(cannon banging)
(explosion booming)
(suspenseful music)
[Stu] What do I do?
What you mean?
You're the best shot in Iowa.
Let's get going.
Oh, great.
That's easy for you to say.
(gun banging)
I winged him.
(bullet whooshes)
Shit.
I gotta get out of his sights.
[Stu] Keep it steady.
I think I got him.
[Will] Damn, he's good.
(Heinz laughing)
[Stu] Watch out, he's
coming up on our tail.
(gun banging)
[Will] Did I lose him?
No.
Fine.
(bullets clanging)
I got him.
[Will] Sure about that?
[Stu] Yeah, look, he's going down.
Whoo!
(Heinz screaming)
(explosion booming)
(cannon bangs)
Dammit, anti-aircraft fire.
[Stu] My machine gun's useless.
Goddammit.
Hey, when I bow, throw our
last bomb up off my hand.
(cannon bangs)
Steady, steady... drop that bitch.
(explosion booming)
Shit, that was close.
[Stu] I thought close counted
in horseshoes and hand grenades?
Damn.
(gun banging)
(metal clanging)
Christ!
It's Valentine.
What are you waiting for?
(gun firing)
Whoa, he's in a Fokker
Triplane, we're fucked.
Not if I can help it.
(gun banging)
(Stu yelling)
(Montgomery laughing)
(bullets clanging)
Good job.
You got him off us.
(gun firing)
All right, let's go for the tank.
[Stu] Damn, he's back on our tail.
(cannon booms)
Here goes nothing.
(explosion booming)
(program buzzing)
Yeah!
Whoo!
[Stu] Wait, Will, don't get cocky.
We still got company.
(gun firing)
[Will] Damn, this guy's tricky.
(gun banging)
(gun firing)
Where the hell is he?
[Stu] Watch out, he's
dropping in behind us.
(gun firing)
Hold on, baby!
[Stu] What the hell are you doing?
[Will] Trust me.
(gun banging)
[Stu] Jesus Christ, I don't like this.
[Will] Come on, baby, pull together now!
(gun firing)
[Stu] Shit, oh shit!
(gun banging)
(engine clanking)
(plane whooshes)
(Montgomery screaming)
(explosion booming)
Not out of this yet!
Come on, baby!
[Stu] Come on, Will, you can do it!
Yeah!
Uh-oh, our fuel line's been shot out.
We're going down.
[Stu] Kidding?
(dramatic music)
[Will] It's not responding.
(plane engine roaring)
We're not gonna make it.
They're going down.
[Daniel] Who would get the kill?
Mr. Valentine would get the kill.
He shot off the round.
I don't know, man.
(clock ticking)
(wind blowing)
Oh, fine, pull them out.
That is not a kill to be proud of.
You never disappoint me, Montgomery.
I must say, you're quite a sportsmen.
I wouldn't have done it, but very good.
Personally, Mr. Traven,
I don't get a damn
about what you would
or would not have done.
However, in appreciation of my largesse,
I would hope that you gentlemen
would let me choose the next scenario.
Why, the enthusiasm you men exude
makes me wanna play myself.
If you do, Crowley, make
sure you play the full ray.
I have a surprise for you
on this next scenario, Heinz.
I think you'll love it.
Cannot wait.
(upbeat jazz music)
(group chattering)
Stay cool.
They could come from anywhere.
(guns clicking)
(woman laughing)
Nice touch.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
We gotta quit meetin' like this.
(sighs) Baracus.
This one's gonna be fun.
This a prohibition
speakeasy, all we got is .45s.
Well, that oughta make
things interesting, huh?
Please, no photos.
(camera clicks)
[Man] Back, hey, scram.
I said no photos, it
gives her a headache.
Oh, I just need one shot.
(gun bangs)
[Woman] Oh, my god.
Oh, my god, there's
blood all over the place.
- Somebody help her.
- Who is that?
We don't have to play
by their rules. See? Huh?
You dirty rat!
(gun banging)
(Baracus laughing)
You only got seven rounds.
You might wanna save your ammo, tough guy.
Yeah.
(guns firing)
(group screaming)
(guns banging)
(gun banging)
[Will] Go out the back, go out the back.
They're getting away. (yells)
(jazz music)
(gun clicks)
(gun bangs)
(group chattering)
[Will] Where are the
others, can you see?
[Stu] I think we lost him.
[Will] No, no, he's right behind us.
Come on, come on, come on.
(gun clicks)
[Showgirl] What the hell was that?
[Showgirl 2] Shh,
shh. Wait. I wanna hear.
There's gotta be a way out of here.
(group chattering)
(gun bangs)
This way, this way.
Come on, up here.
(group chattering)
It's like a labyrinth.
(door clicks)
Whoa.
(gun banging)
(program buzzing)
(body thuds)
(Nikki grunts)
(fist thuds)
Oh, god, I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it,
don't worry about it.
She's just part of the program.
Yeah, well, this part
of the program's deleted.
I'm a prisoner, too.
(gun banging)
Let's go!
(Montgomery yelling)
(guns banging)
[Heinz] Nice try, old man.
(Montgomery chuckles)
(car engine roaring)
Come on, hurry up.
(train horn blowing)
(slow tempo jazz music)
Let's go.
Keep moving.
(bell ringing)
(steam hissing)
(train horn blowing)
(train engine roaring)
Hey, how do we know you're
not one of Crowley's tricks?
We don't.
Look, my name is Nikki Pierce.
The eco warrior?
No, the convict.
All right, look, we gotta
remember these bastards
are in this for themselves.
We stick together, agreed?
(bell ringing)
(Montgomery laughing)
(slow tempo jazz music)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, play it cool.
We're in no rush.
I'm killing this bastard myself.
I told you, we work as a team.
Uh-uh, this one's mine.
(gun banging)
(gun clicking)
Shit, she's in trouble.
Hold on, hold on.
Be patient.
Let's see what he does.
(Heinz grunts)
(Nikki groaning)
Nikki Pierce.
My dear, once again, I'll
have my way with you.
But at least give me a smile, huh?
That's right, bitch.
(gun bangs)
(program buzzing)
(guns banging)
(Heinz groaning)
(group chattering)
(slow tempo jazz music)
May I punch your ticket?
(gun bangs)
(program buzzing)
(group chattering)
[Passenger] Is he dead?
- Oh, my god.
(computer beeps)
You have a sick sense of humor, Crowley.
That bitch is mine.
(laughs) Don't count on it, sir.
I'm not kidding.
Stay out of my way.
My, my. The level of
competition is getting higher.
Well, I must say, that
Baracus is quite a sharp-witted fella.
I will take great pride
in slitting his throat.
You couldn't even shoot him,
what makes you think you could cut him?
Well, at least I wasn't gunned down
by that little tot right off the bat.
Enough talk, let's go back in the game.
[Daniel] Yes, right away.
Don't be impertinent, Daniel.
Now, there are four
prime trophies out there,
let's find out who the best man is.
(birds chirping)
(chattering in distance)
(gun clicking)
(dog barking)
(upbeat ragtime piano music)
(fist thuds)
(man groans)
(body thuds)
(group chattering)
Hey, cowboy.
I haven't seen you around here in a while.
How you been?
Hiya, darling. (chuckles)
It's good to see you, too.
[Charlie] Gentlemen,
the game's five card stud.
Nothing's wild.
Let me see your money on the table.
Remember, every hand's a
winner, every hand's a loser.
Make mine a winner there, Charlie,
if you know what's good for you.
[Charlie] Yes, sir, Mr.
James, I'll try my best.
You know it.
[Will] Throw 'em down.
[Stu] Read 'em and weep.
[Charlie] A winning hand.
(hand thuds)
You know, Frank, I don't think
I could take lucky boy
here winning another hand.
Jesse don't like
losing before a robbery.
I'm sure you got a winning
hand coming up here soon.
[Charlie] Ante up, boys.
[Man] Beat that, greenhorn.
Let's see 'em, tenderfoot.
[Man 2] Call.
I think Crowley's dealing these hands.
Damn right.
I fold.
(upbeat music)
(group chattering)
Well, all right.
Now I feel lucky.
(glass thuds)
[Cole] Goddammit, boys,
let's get down to it.
(birds chirping)
[Will] I think that's the
Jesse James/Cole Younger gang.
I say we stick with them.
Best bodyguards we're gonna find.
(horse neighing)
(suspenseful music)
(gun clicking)
All right, boys, you
know what we're here for.
Let's do it.
Come on.
(horse neighing)
[Driver] All right,
folks, this is Northfield,
end of the line.
Northfield.
Oh, shit.
[Stu] What is it?
I'm afraid the James boys
didn't turn out too good on this one.
[Man] They're robbing the bank!
(gun bangs)
(gun banging)
(man groans)
(body thuds)
(woman screams)
(man yelling)
(guns banging)
(body thuds)
(gun banging)
(gun bangs)
(gun clicking)
(man yelling)
(woman screams)
Hey, Sheriff!
(gun bangs)
(program buzzing)
(computer beeps)
Scheiße.
What's happening, Crowley?
I don't pay this kind of money
to be cut down by Jesse James.
If you remember, you
helped make the rules.
Are you not majority
shareholder of Crowley Games?
Precisely, which you should keep
in mind for the next scenario.
I'm getting sick and tired of your tricks.
Perhaps you should hone your skills.
Schwein.
(gun banging)
(birds chirping)
There's Stu.
Cover him.
(gun bangs)
(gun clicks)
There's better cover in the barn.
[Stu] I don't get it.
How did you know what was
gonna go down that day?
Once again, Crowley
was true to his word.
This is an authentic historical scenario.
Great Northfield, Minnesota Raid.
Nikki, you move up front.
Stu, you take the back.
Be careful.
- Gotcha.
(suspenseful music)
Now, it's been a long
time since I've had a woman.
Especially one as beautiful as you are.
There's no time for this shit, Baracus.
I will kill you.
You're gonna have to.
(gun bangs)
Quiet.
(gun banging)
(Nikki and Baracus grunting)
(Baracus grunting)
(gun bangs)
I want you to be real quiet,
because this thing can go off.
And you know, really, it don't
make much difference to me
right now whether you're
dead or you're alive.
(gun bangs)
Now quiet.
(Nikki whimpering)
(guns banging)
(gun bangs)
(gun banging)
(Nikki grunts)
(gun bangs)
(guns banging)
(Nikki grunts)
(gun bangs)
Get off her.
Now drop the gun, real slow.
(dog barking)
(gun thuds)
The one in your holster, too.
Oh, Will,
(gun thuds)
you're such a hero.
(gun bangs)
[Will] Get over here, Baracus.
Forgetting something?
(gun bangs)
(gun clicks)
[Stu] Will, I need ammo.
(metal clangs)
(Will grunts)
(arm whooshes)
(Baracus grunts)
(knife whooshes)
(knife whooshing)
(Baracus grunting)
(knife whooshes)
(knife whooshing)
(Baracus grunting)
(knife whooshes)
(knives clanging)
(knife whooshing)
(Baracus grunts)
(Baracus grunting)
(gun clicks)
Now, Nikki, you know you need me.
(gun bangs)
(program buzzing)
(Baracus groaning)
(body thuds)
(Baracus groans)
(birds chirping)
(gun clicking)
Nice shooting, Colonel.
That was fucking pathetic.
Oh, and you're one to talk.
Twenty feet away with
a goddamn scatter gun.
Couldn't hit the broad side of a barn
if it landed on you.
Don't bother finishing.
I'm already loaded.
Stu, toss me the rifle.
(Stu grunts)
(gun clicking)
Let's go over here.
(gun clicks)
What happened down there?
Baracus is out.
Yeah, I could see that.
(gun bangs)
(Daniel groans)
(program buzzing)
(gun bangs)
(Daniel groans)
Now, I'm reloaded.
(gun bangs)
[Stu] Who shot Traven?
One of the hunters.
Look, things are getting ugly.
I'm gonna check out the back.
Keep your eyes open up front.
(sighs) Well, this sure beats
sitting in a cell all day.
(guns banging)
Mind if I ask you a question?
Depends.
(gun bangs)
What are you in for?
(gun clicking)
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have asked.
It's all right.
(gun bangs)
(gun clicking)
I almost killed someone.
(gun bangs)
What happened?
(ominous music)
I had just finished this investigation
for the Earth Health Organization,
which was gonna expose
the entire nuclear energy
industry in Germany.
(thunder rumbling)
And the strangest thing happened.
I was home that evening working
when the man behind the entire
nuclear proliferation cover-up
just barged into my apartment.
He said he wanted to congratulate
me on a job well done.
(hand slaps)
(Nikki groans)
Everything was destroyed.
(hand slaps)
(Nikki groans)
My reports, my notes were all burnt.
Everything was gone.
Everything I worked for.
(Nikki groaning)
(thunder rumbling)
He raped me.
Jesus.
(birds chirping)
What did you do?
I went to his office.
I don't exactly what happened.
I just went crazy.
By the time security pulled me off of him,
I had already fractured his
skull and broken his spine.
He was crippled for life.
But that was justified.
He deserved it.
That man was Heinz Dietrich.
Nobody believed me.
I believe you.
You gotta check this guy out.
Be careful.
Will Singleton.
I could wait you out, but
that would get boring.
And it'd be downright foolhardy of me
to come barging in there,
numbers being what they are.
So I suggest that we just
throw down the hardware
and settle this the old fashioned way.
(knife whooshing)
Hand-to-hand.
One... two... three.
(guns banging)
(program buzzing)
(body thuds)
(ominous music)
What an asshole.
(computer beeps)
That is enough!
That man has no honor!
No honor?
You shot me in the back, you bastard.
Gentlemen, you should save
your energy for the game.
You must be extremely
dismayed, Mr. Valentine.
A waste of Baracus.
That, sir, is an outrage.
That is unacceptable.
I paid for the privilege
of killing these animals,
not watching them take out their own.
I demand you put that man back in.
I shall appease you this once.
(guns banging)
(explosion booming)
(missile whistling)
(guns banging)
(explosion booming)
(gun banging)
(cannon booming)
(explosion booming)
(metal crashing)
(glass shattering)
(cannon booming)
(guns banging)
(explosion booming)
(tank engine roaring)
Will, look!
We're goddamn Nazis!
(cannon booms)
(gun banging)
Stu, check your ammo.
Nikki, check your ammo.
Give me that.
Nothing!
This must be the end of the war, 1945.
The Third Reich, it's
crumbling down all around.
(gun banging)
At this point, the Nazi
ranks were devastated.
Take a look at those kids.
They're starving.
They got no food, no
supplies, not even ammo.
(cannon booms)
[Stu] Pretty cold, too.
Yeah.
Hundreds of thousands froze to death.
You better give her that.
Here.
I can take it, dammit.
Ooh, how much can you take, Nikki?
Son of a bitch.
Killed you once, Baracus,
we can do it again.
Look, I know it seems like
we can pretty much handle
whatever they throw at us,
but we're gonna be trapped
in this virtual hell
until we find a way out of the program.
You got that?
(guns banging)
Please, can we try to just
stick together 'til that time?
Ooh, I promise to be good
until we're through with this one.
(bullets whooshing)
(cannon booming)
(explosion booming)
(bullets whooshing)
(flame hisses)
(guns banging)
(gun banging)
(cannon booming)
(guns banging)
(gun banging)
(explosion booming)
(cannon booming)
(man screaming)
(missile hissing)
(water splashing)
(explosion booming)
(gun banging)
(Heinz laughing)
(explosion booming)
(gun banging)
(man screaming)
(explosion booming)
(guns banging)
(ominous music)
(cannon booming)
(explosion booming)
(Heinz speaking in German)
(gun bangs)
(man groaning)
(speaking in German)
(gun bangs)
(man groans)
(cannon booming)
(tank engine roaring)
(cannon booms)
(explosion booming)
(man screaming)
(fire roaring)
(explosion booming)
(suspenseful music)
(man gurgling)
(fuse hissing)
(metal clangs)
(explosion booming)
(guns banging)
(dramatic music)
(Nikki groaning)
(ominous music)
She's been shot.
We have to do something.
- God.
This feels real.
We have to get her out of the program.
Shut up, I know, let me think.
(tank engines roaring)
(Nikki groaning)
Dammit, there was no way for
the Nazis to win this battle.
They were outgunned, outmanned,
yet their commanders forced the fight on.
Absolutely no surrender.
We're gonna have to do
something to change that.
(guns banging)
(group yelling)
(man groaning)
(man speaking in German)
(group chattering)
All right, look, let's try
and get her to a field hospital.
But remember, we can always
surrender to American forces.
Why don't we surrender to the Russians?
What? Are you kidding me?
The Russians took no prisoners.
They'd massacre us.
Come on, let's go.
(explosion booming)
(Nikki groaning)
(cannon booming)
(explosion booming)
(water splashing)
Come on, boys, double time.
[Group] Hup, hup, hup, hup, hup, hup.
Hang on, Nikki, we'll get
you to a field hospital.
(suspenseful music)
(cannon booms)
(explosion booming)
Halt, stop!
We've got wounded.
Don't move, I mean it.
Hang on, Nikki, it's gonna be okay.
I've got you.
[Solider] I surrender.
Okay, hurry up, get her in.
Hurry.
(explosions booming)
(group yelling)
Medic, come on, we need room.
We got wounded here.
- We need help!
We need help!
- We need... come on, come on.
Bring a stretcher.
Let's go, let's go!
- We'll take over from here.
- Come on!
- We got this, we got this.
- Double quick time.
Let's go.
- All right, we got this.
(group chattering)
All right, get a surgeon, get a surgeon.
- Right through here.
- All right, we got it.
(group chattering)
Medic, we got wounded here.
You wanna help us?
She's dying.
- Wait a minute,
you guys sound American.
Look, we're dogfaces in kraut uniforms.
Now, get to work!
(man chattering)
[Solider] Hold him down,
dammit, hold him down.
[Medic] Stop the
bleeding, stop the bleeding.
(group chattering)
(Nikki groaning)
High fracture, stop the bleeding.
[Medic 2] I need
plasma over here, dammit!
I need plasma!
(group chattering)
There's not much I
can do, she's gutshot,
it's just a matter of time.
I gotta go work on someone I can save.
[Medic 2] Tighten that tourniquet.
Too much blood.
[Soldier] We got more wounded.
I've always believed there's a way out
of anything if you put your mind to it.
[Stu] I agree.
Look at her, she's done.
We're not gonna forget about her.
Hold on, hold on.
Anomalies, all right?
There are anomalies in the program.
What do you mean?
(Nikki groans)
Like when you killed the Nazi commander.
- ASAP, let's go.
- Yeah, the program froze
like it was trying to adapt.
Catch up or something.
(Nikki groaning)
It needs time to reboot itself.
So?
Why does it do that?
Too much information to process?
[Medic] We gotta stop the bleeding.
Too much information, maybe.
I say we give it more information
than it could ever handle.
Bring it all crashing down.
(Nikki groaning)
Okay.
Don't worry, Nikki, I'll be back for you.
Come on.
(suspenseful music)
(Nikki groaning)
(guns banging)
(bones crack)
(man groans)
(cannon booms)
(guns banging)
(group yelling)
(group chattering)
(body thuds)
(gun bangs)
(guns firing)
(both groaning)
(man groaning)
(man yelling)
(man groans)
(explosion booming)
(gun banging)
(man groaning)
(gun bangs)
(man groans)
(explosion booming)
(gun banging)
(man groaning)
[Solider] Drop your weapons!
(gun banging)
(man groaning)
(man yelling)
(Montgomery grunting)
What the hell is your problem?
It's me, Valentine, you dope!
(cannon bangs)
I know.
Who do you think you are?
I won't let you cheat me!
Cut it out, you two jackanapes!
They found a way to
overload Crowley's program.
We gotta stop them.
(gun banging)
(man groaning)
(gun bangs)
(man groans)
(guns banging)
(gun banging)
(man groaning)
(bullets whooshing)
(gun banging)
(man groaning)
(group groaning)
(gun clicking)
(group yelling)
(cannon booming)
(explosion booming)
(gun bangs)
(knife clangs)
(man yelling)
(metal creaking)
(lens clicking)
(Baracus grunting)
(knife whooshing)
(knife whooshes)
(both grunting)
(Baracus grunting)
(knives whooshing)
(both grunting)
(Baracus grunting)
(cannon whirring)
(fist thuds)
(man groans)
(body thuds)
(gun banging)
(man groaning)
Come on.
You're mine.
You don't have the balls, Singleton.
(gun banging)
(Daniel groaning)
(guns banging)
(group yelling)
(suspenseful music)
(Baracus and Montgomery grunting)
(body thuds)
(knife whooshes)
(Baracus grunting)
(Baracus and Montgomery grunting)
(hand thudding)
(Baracus groaning)
(knife clangs)
(Baracus and Montgomery grunting)
(head thuds)
(Montgomery groans)
(metal clanging)
(Baracus yelling)
(blade thuds)
(Stu grunting)
(Stu and Heinz grunting)
(head thuds)
(Stu groaning)
(knife clangs)
(tank engine roaring)
Heads up.
(cannon booming)
(blood splattering)
(guns banging)
(group yelling)
(metal clicks)
(cannon booming)
(missile whistling)
(explosion booming)
(fire crackling)
(laughing) Yes!
(program whooshing)
(electricity crackling)
(explosions booming)
(explosion booming)
(implant beeps)
[Will] Let's go, we're
out of the program!
(Heinz screaming)
Nikki, look out!
(sword thuds)
Stu, grab a sword.
- Gotcha.
(Heinz groaning)
Baracus, take Crowley.
[Montgomery] We've
gotta get out of here.
[Daniel] Stand and
fight, you gutless bastard.
Traven, Traven!
This is not a game.
I don't mind running her
through to get to you, Crowley.
Daniel, please, this
brute will run me through.
(sword thudding)
(Montgomery groaning)
(body thudding)
[R.D.] Hold it!
- Will.
- Everybody stop.
I think we got ourselves
a Mexican standoff here.
Yes, it does, Baracus.
But I think we can all come to terms.
You don't seem to be in a position
to make any demands, Crowley.
It's four against two.
No, Will, every man for himself.
Enough talk. I wanna kill you, Crowley.
Now, what would that get you?
My freedom.
I give you your freedom.
You kill me, Baracus,
and you remain the little
rodent that you are.
Join me and you'll have
all the wealth and power
you ever dreamed of.
I want the woman, too.
Hold on, Crowley.
Do it and your boy here
gets his final shade.
And you need Traven to help
run this twisted operation
and help supply you with fresh meat.
You have a point there.
Traven is integral to the game,
besides being a longstanding employee.
Take this one.
Sorry, baby.
Now, let's exchange the
convict for the warden.
Let him go.
Ah, god, this deal-making's
been energizing.
(door whooshes)
(alarm ringing)
(suspenseful music)
What do you think your chances
are of getting out of here alive?
We'll take our chances.
Silly boy, these men
are just the beginning.
(sighs) I'm not going back to prison.
You probably will kill us, Crowley.
But you can be damn sure
we're gonna take you with us.
I believe you.
But what a waste.
There is one other way to
avert further bloodshed.
You see, Will, I've invested a tremendous
amount of energy and time in training you.
We're on the cutting edge of technology
and you've proven yourself
the ultimate warrior.
If you go back in the game,
your friends can go free.
- No.
- I swear it.
Will, don't do it.
We can fight our way out of here.
Will, your life is the only thing
you have to bargain with.
Make up your mind!
I can beat this guy.
Do it.
Go.
- No.
Do it, go!
Trust me!
(fast tempo suspenseful music)
(brooding music)
(dramatic music)
(funky wah-wah music)