(no audio)
(light music)
(birds chirping)
- [Renfroe] It's been said that you can never go home again.
I know that as a young boy growing up on a farm
in rural Louisiana was the greatest experience of my life.
So I decided to make one more trip
to see the old home place and remember the smell
of Mama's wood stove cooking cornbread and peas.
- How long has it been since you been here?
- Quite awhile.
(light music)
- [Renfroe] The days were long, but we didn't care
because of the fun we had as kids,
fishing and making kites out of old newspapers.
Sometime, D.J., my older brother,
would let me actually try to fly one of them.
(harmonica music)
Nutty, a young neighbor boy living with his grandparents
was the best kite flier I think I ever saw.
He and D.J. were always trying to scare me with stories
about an old panther at night.
(Renfroe laughs)
"Screaming like a woman," they'd say.
I remember a special year in my life
that changed me forever.
To this day, I think about that time
when I would sit around and daydream of snow on Christmas.
Clara Mae made a new angel for our Christmas tree that year
and I got to keep the old one.
I took it and nailed it up on the front of the barn
and every time I walked by her,
she seemed to be watching my every move,
regardless of where I was standing.
Now even as a grown man,
I still believe in angels and miracles.
It seems like only yesterday
when Papa was ringing that old dinner bell
and we'd all come running from the fields.
(upbeat music)
- Renfroe, you boys need to wash up for supper.
- Nutty always gets the fly the kite.
- Well, there's far more practicing to do, Renfroe.
I'll teach you how to do it tomorrow.
- Thanks, you better.
Have to knock you out.
(upbeat music)
- Renfroe, did you wash up?
- Yes, ma'am.
- How about we say the blessing.
Our heavenly Father, we are grateful for your blessings
and for watching over us through these hard times
across our land.
The bounties that you have given us,
we now partake of, we are ever so thankful, amen.
D.J., D.J., in the morning, I want you and Renfroe
to make sure you go out there and stack it.
We may have a real bad winter.
- [D.J.] Yes, sir.
- Papa, are you expecting it to be real cold this winter?
- It may be, Renfroe.
And we wanna make sure we're ready for it if it is.
- Well, maybe it will snow.
(upbeat music)
- [Papa] It just might.
- D.J., did you hear what Papa said last night
at the supper table?
- I heard him say you need to help me cut
and stack this wood.
- He also said it may snow.
- I figure it'll be hot enough today
when me and Nutty go down to the fishing hole
while you stack this wood and daydream about snow.
- D.J., Renfroe!
D.J., fishing, the fish aren't gonna wait forever.
Whew!
Now, why haven't y'all finished with this wood yet?
- Well, if you get over here and help us stack it,
we can get finished a lot quicker.
- [Nutty] Okay, y'all, we gotta hurry up
and get to the fishing hole pretty soon.
Those bass are just gonna up and leave us.
- Well, Renfroe's over there daydreaming about snow.
- Y'all remember last Christmas
when the third wiseman tripped and fell
at the at the altar during Christmas program?
- Why'd he trip?
- On account of his trick knee, it started acting up
and when he was kneeling down at baby Jesus' feet,
the candle flew right out of his hand
right on baby Jesus' manger,
but of course, it really wasn't the real baby Jesus.
(cast scream)
- Fire, the baby!
♪ Joy to the world ♪
(congregation laughs)
♪ Joy to the world, the Lord is come ♪
♪ Let earth receive her king ♪
♪ Let every heart ♪
♪ Prepare him room ♪
- It wasn't the real baby Jesus.
- Renfroe, Nutty's not stupid.
He knows it wasn't the real baby Jesus.
- I didn't know.
I didn't know what kind
of Bible training Nutty might have had.
- I sure would've liked to seen that.
My grandparents saw it
and said the whole thing was real funny.
My parents would've liked to have seen it, too.
(light music)
Oh well.
- Come on now, let's get out of here.
- You mean it? - Yeah, let's go.
- Yes!
Think them bass will bite?
- Oh yeah, come on.
- Come on, let's go.
Let's go!
(upbeat music)
We'll get a fish and stay away from town.
Yeehaw, whoo!
(upbeat music)
- Come on!
Last one there is a dead fish.
(upbeat music)
- D.J. and you gotta be more careful
when Nutty's around talking about Christmas here
with our parents and all.
Heard what he said about his parents.
It's gonna take him a long time getting over losing them.
- I just forgot.
We didn't mean any harm to Nutty.
He's around here so much,
I kind of feel like he's part of the family.
Don't you, Clara?
- Keep in mind what I said.
Holidays are a hard time of the year
for people who've lost folks.
Talk about, mm, fishing.
- I know it's a little bit too soon to be talking
about Christmas and all, but I believe I'll be getting lots
of presents this year.
- Getting presents isn't the chief joy
of Christmas, Renfroe.
- Then what is one of the chief joys?
- Well, gift giving is a special pleasure.
It is more blessed to give than to receive.
- [Renfroe] I believe I like getting presents best,
no matter what's more blessed.
- I've noticed you've become a little selfish here lately.
- [Renfroe] Is that trough a manger?
- Yes, it is.
And you know, Renfroe, whenever I hear the Christmas story,
I can see it all happen right here in this very stable.
Selfishness is something
you can make up your mind to overcome.
(light music)
(birds chirping)
(Renfroe hollers)
- Renfroe, will you stop it?
- Renfroe!
Got Indians after you?
(Renfroe shouts) (upbeat music)
- [D.J.] What now?
(upbeat music)
- Hey, look at me, D.J..
I'm a champion bull rider.
Woo hoo!
Coming up, come on.
Hurry up and go.
Come on, Renfroe, my grandma's faster than you are.
(upbeat music)
- Y'all wait up.
- Another panther track.
- A panther track?
- Are you sure?
- Yep, we heard it again the other night.
- [D.J.] We did.
(dramatic music)
- Are y'all sure that's a panther track?
- [D.J.] Yep, sure is a panther track.
- I think I wanna go home.
- What are you drawing, Renfroe?
- An angel, I'm making a few changes on our old one.
(rooster crows)
(bell rings)
- Renfroe Ty Madison, get out of that cupboard.
It's time to go to school, you're gonna be late.
- But Mama, I'm hungry.
- Come put your hat and coat on.
There.
That's right.
Hey, what's that drawing?
- It's my angel.
- Well, it's not Christmas yet,
but it is supposed to get cold today.
Bye. - Bye.
(upbeat music)
(bell rings)
(children cheer)
- Bye, Ms. Watson.
(upbeat music)
- Go on, go home.
- Be quiet, you big bully.
- You kids go home.
(upbeat music)
- How was your day?
- Pretty good.
- What's that?
- A secret.
- What you got?
- It's a secret.
- Tell me.
- You can't keep a secret, Renfroe.
- Yes, I can.
- No, you can't.
- I know better than that.
- [Renfroe] Give it back!
D.J.!
Buford, that's my hat.
- [Clara Mae] Nutty, no, no, no.
Renfroe, you best clear.
- D.J.'s coming, Buford.
He's gonna get you.
- Let this be a warning to you.
Don't mess with my little brother.
- Yeah, Madison, you're scaring me.
- Come on, let's go.
(upbeat music)
- I can't wait, one more week.
- One week till what?
- Well, I overheard Ms. Watson say we were getting off
for Christmas in a week.
Didn't you hear her say that?
- Yeah, I heard her.
Next time that bully Buford Reynolds picks
on another little one, I'm gonna clean his plow.
- But D.J., he's too big for you.
(upbeat music)
- But that Buford does need a good old fashioned whooping.
(Renfroe laughs)
(upbeat music)
- Renfroe, you look like you're out of breath.
- Well, I am.
And it's almost Christmas and it's still hot.
- My grandpa says he can't remember
the last time there was a hard cold winter around here.
- Yeah, Papa said he ain't seen snow since he was 11.
- [Renfroe] How long has that been?
- About 30 years.
- South Louisiana, it probably ain't gonna snow
for another 30 years.
(Renfroe pants)
- What on earth are you doing?
- Father said he read an article in Farmer's Life Magazine
that said that phonograph records when played to cows
in an experiment make them give more milk.
So I thought let's give it a try.
- [Clara Mae] Sounds like a good idea to me.
What song do you have?
- [Renfroe] Silent Night.
- That's a good song, we'll play it.
("Silent Night")
- Clara Mae, Renfroe, what is going on out here?
- Mama, it's Christmas.
- It is Christmas, Mama.
It really is.
- Yes, it is, kids.
Merry, merry Christmas!
("Silent Night")
Renfroe, get out of that cornbread.
You know, being Christmas and all, it might be a good night
to get the decorations down out of the attic.
- Yes'm, it's a wonderful night.
- [Mama] Clara Mae, you and Renfroe need
to get washed up for supper.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Clara Mae, if you'll come back
and help me put those turnip greens in a bowl.
And Renfroe, call your Pa to come to the table, okay?
Where's D.J.?
- [Renfroe] Last time I saw him, he was with Nutty.
- They were horsing around by the wood pile.
Probably went to Nutty's grandparents' house.
- [Papa] Here, I found them.
Here's the Christmas decorations.
- Oh, great, let's see what we've got.
I always forget from the end of the year
what's in this old box.
It's lots more fun to get them out now, isn't it?
- This was on the tree from last year.
- Wanna make some new ones this year?
Oh, look, here's this old reindeer.
Where'd we get this, anyone remember?
- Oh, I remember that.
That was always my favorite Christmas gift.
- It never wanted to stay on too easy.
More balls.
Well, there's some balls you can put over there.
Mary won't mind.
- [Papa] Boy, look at that poor old girl.
I thought she'd fly away before next Christmas.
- She needs to.
- [Clara Mae] Oh, she was so pretty when we first got her.
- Hey, don't, don't!
Stop it, D.J., stop it!
Don't, D.J., don't!
Don't hurt her!
- I have a surprise.
- You do?
- Yes, ma'am. - Well, what would that be?
- It's a secret.
- Ah!
I didn't know we had any secrets.
Huh, wonder what she's been making.
I guess we could make some more streamers
with this, don't you?
That might be pretty.
- I thought I'd wait another day or two,
but I decided to bring her on out.
She's the present to the family from me.
I made her in home ec class.
- Wow, she's lovely, Clara Mae.
- [Clara Mae] I made her.
- How did you get the waist to stand up so pretty?
- They have wire in them.
- Oh, let me see.
It's pretty.
- [Clara Mae] They have wire in them.
- Wow, she's lovely.
- [Clara Mae] Thank you.
- Mama. - [Mama] What, sweetie?
- If this one ain't gonna go on the tree, can I keep it?
- [Mama] I don't know why not.
- Don't tell me you're gonna start playing with dolls.
- I'm going to find a place for her outside.
No.
(Papa laughs) (D.J. laughs)
(panther screeches)
D.J., D.J.?
D.J.?
Did you hear that?
(crickets chirping)
(rooster crows)
- Boys, it's time to get up.
Wake up.
Did you sleep all right?
- Mama, did you hear anything different last night?
I heard a woman screaming.
- You ain't never heard no panther.
It sure wasn't a woman.
Mom? - [Mama] What?
- You raised him.
- I know.
(harmonica music)
- Papa, you expect that panther
to be coming through here this year?
- Suppose so, Renfroe.
He's been coming through this old creek back in here
for more than five years.
- Whew, if I could just get one shot at him,
this'll be his last trip.
Pow, pow!
(birds chirping)
(rooster crows)
(harmonica music)
- Hey, Renfroe, you hear the panther last night?
- I sure did.
- You think it was a real panther?
- [Renfroe] Yeah.
- Papa's been hearing it for the last few years.
Come on, let's get out of here.
(harmonica music)
- Come on, Renfroe.
You just wanna wait there and let the panther get you?
(harmonica music)
- Yep, it was.
Been hearing it all week.
- That must have been one really big panther.
- It's small, but it's about that big.
- Yep.
- I'm sure he could eat someone whole like Renfroe.
- Better look out, Renfroe.
(Clara Mae yells) (Renfroe screams)
(bell rings) (children cheer)
- [Children] Bye.
- [Teacher] Bye-bye.
Bye, y'all have a good night.
Bye-bye, y'all have a good day.
Bye-bye. - Bye!
Bye, you have a good day, okay.
- You better watch out, you're pressing your luck.
- Stop it.
- That was cruel.
- Hey, stop it, you bully!
- Hey, it's a fight, it's a fight.
Come on, come on!
(children cheer)
(upbeat music)
- Y'all, stop it.
Stop it right now, stop it.
- He started it.
He started it, Ms. Watson.
- Is this true, D.J.?
- Yes'm.
- Get on in that schoolhouse.
D.J.? - [D.J.] Yes'm.
You okay?
- Yes'm.
- Get on home.
- I'm coming in there, Bruce.
And I'll wring your neck if you try to jump at me.
Get back, you scraggly old rooster.
I could wring your neck.
Mama's not here to see me do it neither.
- Renfroe Ty Madison, you best not ruffle a feather
of my prize rooster.
You just don't know how to talk to him.
He is capable of listening to you.
- I'll ruffle a feather, all right.
I'll put a real tight knot on that scrawny old head.
(light music)
- Now, Renfroe, don't you forget what I told you.
(rooster crows)
(upbeat music)
(Renfroe whistles)
- Hey, Nutty, can you help me?
- Come get the ladder over there and I'll get the nail.
- Help me nail it on the top of the snow palace.
- Okay.
Oh, this looks like it'll do.
Here you go, Renfroe.
Here, hold this, Renfroe.
(dog barking)
How's that right there?
- Mm-hm, yeah.
- Ta-da! - Perfect.
(light music)
- Get your hat and coat on.
Clara Mae, get your coat.
It's time to go to town to do our Christmas shopping.
(light music)
- Whoa, whoa!
(bell rings)
- Boys, get over here
and help me unload the ham out of here.
(light music)
I wonder what we'll find in the shop today.
- Merry Christmas, everybody.
Merry Christmas.
♪ Bells on bobtails ring ♪
♪ Making spirits bright ♪
♪ What fun it is to ride and sing ♪
(light music)
- Hey, Mr. Peabody.
- [Peabody] D.J., how are you?
- Merry Christmas.
- Thank you.
Boy, that's a nice big ham.
You boys got any Christmas shopping done?
- We'll still try.
- Have a look around the store.
I got some really nice things.
- Okay.
- [Peabody] Clara Mae.
- Here, Mr. Peabody.
- [Peabody] Merry Christmas to you.
- Merry Christmas to you.
- Thank you.
How are you this year?
- [Clara Mae] Just fine, thank you, how are you?
- [Mama] Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas to you.
Renfroe, merry Christmas.
(light music)
- Hello, Mr. Peabody, Merry Christmas.
- [Peabody] How are you?
- Doing fine.
Ducky, merry Christmas to you.
Yeah, we had a pretty good year.
- Let's see here how this is going to add up.
Wow, I may wind up owing you money.
- Well, that'll be fine.
- How's everything out at the place?
- We're doing fine.
- Let's see here.
A good year for hams, so I'm glad.
Boy, well, I owe you 75 cents this year.
- How about that.
- How about a nice knife for Renfroe?
Got some good bargains.
- Young Renfroe's mother would sell me
at a bargain if she found out that I paid 75 cents
for a knife on a boy who already has one.
- But one of the blades is broken.
- You know, but however,
you didn't exactly go out of the way to tell her.
- [Papa] If 75 cents would buy two knives,
I might consider it.
- Well, I've got some real bargains in here all the way
from 10 cents to a dollar.
- Renfroe, do you think you could trade out the 75 cents
on a knife for yourself and one for D.J.
while I go down to the dry goods store?
- Okay, sir.
- Are you a pretty good trader, Renfroe?
- Oh yes, sir.
- Okay, let me show you something in here.
Oh, I've got some really good bargains in here.
Look at this knife right here, Renfroe.
This thing is just 35 cent.
You could get two of those, even have a nickel left
to buy some candy with.
What do you think about that?
(light music)
Okay, you have to be careful.
Don't cut your finger with that.
Isn't that a nice one?
You like that one?
And look at this, Renfroe.
It's only 25 cents.
You could get this one and that one for 75 cent.
It'd be an even trade.
- Well, I'll take these two. - Okay.
Okay, and wrap this one in a paper.
- Okay, and are you gonna put this one in your pocket
or you want me to wrap it?
- Uh-huh, I'll put it in my pocket.
- All right.
Are you anxious for Christmas?
- Oh, yes, sir.
- [Peabody] What else you might have gotten?
- I don't know.
- [Peabody] Well, I hope you have a very special Christmas.
- I hope you do, too, sir.
- Merry Christmas to you.
- Merry Christmas to you, too, sir.
- All right.
(light music)
Bye. - Bye, sir.
- Why, hello there, Renfroe.
- Hi, Mrs. Gibbons!
- I need to talk to you.
Can we sit for awhile?
- [Renfroe] Yes, ma'am.
- Christmas is a week from tomorrow
and I'm wondering if I can count on you
to be on the program?
- Oh, yes, ma'am, you could call on me.
- Well, after the pageant, we're going to be having a party
with refreshments and entertainment.
I thought you could do one of your imitations.
I heard you're good at them.
- I am.
Yes, ma'am, I'll try to make you up one.
- Good, and would you tell Clara Mae and D.J.
that I'd like them to be on the program also.
But I'll talk to them more about it
at Sunday school tomorrow.
- Yes, ma'am, and thank you for asking me.
- Sure, bye-bye.
- Merry Christmas.
(light music)
- Here, it's for you.
Pa don't want you to tell Mom on account
of ladies don't always understand boys and knives.
- Pa get you one?
- Well, a little one.
- Come on, let's get a ride.
(light music)
("Hark, the Herald Angels Sing")
- Isn't that right, Renfroe?
- What's right?
- You having a crush on Ms. Gibbons and all.
- It ain't so!
I ain't gonna tell you the message
that she told me to give y'all.
- What message?
You're making it up.
- What did she say to you, Renfroe?
Tell us, does she want us to be
in the Christmas program this year?
- Tell us, Mama's boy, before I put the hurt on you.
- Okay, okay, she does, she does!
She wants y'all to meet her at Sunday school
and I guess she'll give you the parts there.
("Hark, the Herald Angels Sing")
She asked me to do an imitation
that will please young and old alike.
- She'll probably want me to be a wiseman.
She'll probably want me to play my viola
which she usually ask me again.
- Oh, come on, D.J..
Everybody likes that viola.
It's a true gift and you really should share it.
- Renfroe, you haven't done imitations in two years.
You still can't do them.
- There is a brain, D.J..
("Hark, the Herald Angels Sing")
(upbeat music)
And all of the sudden, crazy Nathan started to get up
from the front pew.
- Well, it is not good Christmas spirit
to refer to poor Nathan as crazy.
I know other boys and girls call him that,
but I don't wanna ever hear y'all call him that.
- It's uncharitable, Renfroe.
- Why, 'cause he's your sweetheart?
- And that's unkind, too.
Making any kind of joke about Nathan is not nice.
- I was glad to hear the Claytons won't have to be moving.
- [Mama] How's that?
- I overheard him in the bank the other day.
Seems that President Roosevelt has opened up the WPA.
Mr. Clayton took a road job at 35 cents an hour.
He starts after Christmas.
- Well, I'm happy for them, especially the children.
Clara Mae, why don't you help me fix a food basket.
We'll have plenty and they've had such hard times.
- Yes, ma'am, I'd like that.
- I'm glad they ain't moving.
I like the girls.
- Now, Renfroe, about that imitation,
I don't think anybody wants to be reminded
of what happened at last year's pageant.
So why don't you see if you can't think of another one.
- Yes'm.
- Maybe it's uncharitable of me,
but I don't think anyone could sound as terrible
as Mr. Franz Martin.
(Clara Mae laughs) (D.J. laughs)
- Thanks, Papa, me neither.
- I understand they're sending Nathan to a special school
for handicapped children up in the mountains
after the holidays.
I hear the civic club is paying for him to go there.
Now, Renfroe, about your imitation...
(birds chirping)
(thunder rumbles)
- [D.J.] Taking all day.
- All right, get back, get back.
Nobody's gonna get a present until I give them to you.
- All right. - Hurry up!
- First one for you, Clara Mae.
- Come on, Mama.
You're the slowest person--
- I hope that's what you want.
- Grandma Ebony.
- I should've put switches in those packages, go.
Go ahead, open it, let's see it.
- First, Laura, then Grandma Ebony.
- Look! - Oh wow.
- [Mama] Patience, it's a virtue.
- [Renfroe] Gimme!
- [Mama] Do you like them?
- Oh wow, thank you. - [Renfroe] Mama!
- [D.J.] Those are nice, Clara.
- I figured for out in the garden.
One for you, D.J..
- [Papa] What is it, D.J., charcoal?
- I don't know, it's got a knot in it.
- Here's one for you, Renfroe.
- Ooh, I got a biggie.
- [Papa] Wow, look at that one.
What have you got there?
- I wonder what that is.
- Looks like a wiener to me.
- [Mama] He knows how to fly.
- Oh, I got a yo-yo.
- [Papa] A yo-yo.
- [Mama] There you go.
Whoa.
- [Papa] Renfroe, you been wanting a lasso for a long time.
Now you have one.
- Papa, here's one for you.
- Oh wow, looka here.
- Ooh, that pretty paper.
- What do you think it is, guys?
- [D.J.] I don't know.
- A velvet dress.
It's a velvet dress.
- What I'd do with a dress, Renfroe?
- Thanks, Santa!
- Have you ever played with a yo-yo before?
You look like you know how to do it.
- [Renfroe] Don't worry about a yo-yo.
- A napkin.
- No, these are handkerchiefs for Christmas for church days.
- And this one's for me.
- [Papa] Oh, great, Mama.
- [Clara Mae] Those are nice.
- Look, it's my favorite potpourri.
- [D.J.] Okay, Mom.
- They fit like a glove.
- Fit just like a glove.
- Oh look, it's beautiful!
- [Renfroe] What is it?
- Well, it's a comb, a brush and a mirror set.
- [Renfroe] What is that?
- [Mama] Look how lovely.
(Renfroe shouts)
Thank you so much.
Oh, I love it.
- [Papa] You're right, a yo-yo.
("O Christmas Tree")
- [Mama] Oh, there's another one for Renfroe.
- Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme!
- [D.J.] How many does Renfroe get?
- [Papa] What do you think it could be?
- [D.J.] What is it, Renfroe?
- [Papa] What is it, son?
- I don't know.
Stop asking me that many questions.
- [D.J.] It sounds like it's a...
- [Clara Mae] Look!
- This is the best present I've ever had.
- You're welcome, Renfroe, merry Christmas.
- Thank you, Mommy.
- You are welcome, thank you, merry Christmas.
(thunder rumbles)
("O Christmas Tree")
(birds chirping)
(thunder rumbles)
- Hush up, you old buzzard!
Don't you have any Christmas spirit?
(upbeat music)
(thunder rumbling)
- Hey there, son.
I was hoping someone would come along
and give me the correct time.
- Well, if you don't mind waiting four more minutes,
it'd be 10.
- I don't mind waiting.
I have lots of time, it's Christmas.
- Mama, can I go to the Claytons?
- That'll be fine, son, but remember
that an earache could keep you out of the Christmas program.
So put your hat on and make sure your flaps are down
over your ears, button your coat up good.
- Yes'm.
- Don't be gone too long.
(upbeat music)
- Renfroe's coming.
Hey, guys, Renfroe's coming.
- [Mary Martha] I figured he'd be around here
sometime this morning.
- [Lucy] I bet you did not.
- [Mary Martha] Hey, Renfroe, did Santa come see you?
- Sure did.
- Merry Christmas, Renfroe.
- Merry Christmas to you, too.
What'd he bring you?
- A diamond ring and a velvet dress, plus a few other things
that aren't any of your business.
- Oh man, Martha, how come you make up them lies like that?
She got the same as the rest of us.
That's what she got.
- You don't know.
I might have hidden my presents
before you got up this morning.
- Hey, Renfroe, I got an orange, an apple and some candy.
- Well, that wasn't hardly worth
hanging up a stocking for, was it?
- Oh, yes it was.
The candy and apple were good
and I'm saving the orange for tomorrow.
- Pretty nice of Santa to leave you that jump rope, Renfroe.
- That's not a jump rope, that's a lasso.
Besides that, I got a yo-yo and this.
- My word, that's beautiful!
- Reckon the same Santa Claus
that came to your house came to ours?
- Well, let's play jump rope with your lasso.
(upbeat music)
- Girls, it's supper time.
Y'all come on in.
- [Girls] Okay.
- Fried chicken, you can even serve upside down.
- With chops and with chestnuts and a mama and a dad.
- We're not having chicken tonight.
Instead, we're having fried steak, pork chops, ice cream
and chocolate pie.
- [Clarrie] Mary Martha, there you go again
making up them whopping tales.
- If you go, we won't have a rope to play with.
(upbeat music)
- [Roosevelt] Now, first of all,
let me assert my firm belief
that the only thing we have to fear is fear itself.
- Amen.
(upbeat music)
- [Clara Mae] Pass that salt.
- Mrs. Madison, you have outdone yourself this time.
("We Wish You A Merry Christmas")
- Papa, do you mind if I do my imitation at the table?
- [Papa] Go ahead, son.
- Now, I ain't gonna tell y'all what this is.
So y'all are just gonna have to guess.
- This ought to be interesting.
(D.J. laughs)
- Imitation by Renfroe Ty Madison.
(Renfroe clucks) (Renfroe neighs)
(Renfroe taps)
(Renfroe blows)
That's it, now one of you have to try to guess.
- I don't have to guess.
It's a herd of wild horses.
- Horses don't rattle, D.J..
- Well, it could be a skeleton chasing him
and his old jawbones were rattling.
(Renfroe laughs) - No, D.J., that's not it.
- I'll bet I can get it.
- [Renfroe] Bet you can't.
- I'll bet I can.
The neighing and galloping wasn't done by horses,
mules or donkeys.
It was by reindeer.
- No, no, no, not that either.
Guess I'll just have to explain.
All right, now,
snow and snow falling on a tin roof.
That's why you were so close, Papa, about that rain.
- [D.J.] Sound like a hail storm to me.
- Renfroe, dear, snow doesn't make any noise.
It falls without a sound, but then you wouldn't know that
because you've never seen snow.
- I wish it would snow.
I hear it makes real good ice cream.
- Oh, it does.
It's delicious.
It's the best I've ever had.
- This Christmas, it'll be one to remember.
It will snow, snow, snow.
(light music)
Get down, Belle, you know this tree.
Aw, it's okay.
Well, merry Christmas to you, too.
Hey, D.J., Renfroe, come on, guys.
Hurry up!
- Hey, Nutty, what'd you get for Christmas?
(Nutty sighs)
- [Nutty] Nothing yet.
- Nothing?
- Why, Christmas is almost over.
- Now, I know that, Renfroe,
but my grandparents ordered me some new clothes
and they just haven't come in yet.
(light music)
- Well, didn't they get you anything to play with?
- Well, they weren't feeling into going in town
as they had planned.
(light music)
Oh, but that's okay.
At least they're feeling better now.
And that's okay, that's much better
than any gift I could ever get.
- Too bad they didn't feel better yesterday
when all the stores were open.
(light music)
- Hey, that's pretty nice!
But I guess you'll be expecting me to believe
that it keeps time.
- Believe it and see it keeping time.
That little bitty hand there ticks off every single second.
- Hey, D.J., y'all are as good as old man Bruce Watson.
- Better, I'd say.
- Well, I need some practice.
- Hey, Renfroe, why don't you let me have a try at that?
You know, I'm willing to bet money
that that's what my grandparents were gonna get me
if they'd gone into town.
I need practice on a really nice yo-yo.
- Look, y'all, I can yo-yo from the top step.
- Why can't you yo-yo from right there?
- 'Cause the string's too long and he won't cut it.
He thinks he's gonna grow into it.
- Hey, it's nice, Renfroe,
but why can't you yo-yo from right there?
Renfroe, why don't you let me have a try at that yo-yo?
- Here, you have a try.
- Thanks.
Now, how in Sam Hill do you work this thing?
Now, how do I work this thing?
- Well, first you make a special knot in the end.
(light music)
Here you go.
- Thanks.
(light music)
- Now, D.J., it's worse than before.
Change it back.
Great, D.J..
Fix it back, D.J..
Now it's all messed up.
It's worser than before.
Fix it back.
- Only if you let Nutty play with it
for a little bit longer.
- He can play with it for a little bit longer
and that's all.
- [Nutty] How do you do it, just up and down?
- Yeah.
- [Nutty] Okay.
- John Brownit, if those ain't snow clouds,
I don't know what is.
- Renfroe, you wouldn't know a snow cloud from a rain cloud.
- Uh, look like rain clouds to me, too, Renfroe.
(thunder rumbles)
Yep, that's rain clouds all right.
- Clara Mae, don't those look like snow clouds to you?
- You're daydreaming, Renfroe.
Come on.
- Oh no, not milking again.
Nutty, return my yo-yo, I need it.
- Here you go.
Can I take a turn?
- Maybe I should at least let Nutty have it till tomorrow
or at least till after Christmas clothes, don't you think?
- You should've let him keep it, period, Renfroe.
That's what you should've done.
You could've let Nutty have it.
Hey, get up.
- But why should I?
Nutty's grandparents have more money
than most folks hereabout.
Nutty's grandpa is retired from the railroad
and probably can run and buy him all sorts of fancy things.
- But he doesn't have anything now.
And now it's Christmas.
You don't have to have all the things you got today.
You could've let Nutty have some little something.
You got a watch, you got a lasso and you got a yo-yo.
Anything you would've given Nutty
would've made him very happy.
- Course if I were a rich boy and got two or three bicycles
and a whole wagon load of other stuff,
I'd probably give him at least one of my presents.
- Ought to be ashamed of yourself.
- I hadn't heard you sing
O Come, All Ye Faithful this year.
- That's right, Renfroe, just change the subject.
I'll be singing it tonight at the Christmas program,
but you, young man, in the meantime,
you need to be thinking a lot about sharing.
♪ Joyful and triumphant ♪
♪ O come, ye ♪
♪ O come, ye to Bethlehem ♪
♪ Come and behold him ♪
♪ Born the king of angels ♪
♪ O come, let us adore him ♪
♪ Christ the Lord ♪
- And she brought forth her first born son
and wrapped him in swaddling clothes
because there was no room for them in the inn.
Glory to God in the highest and on earth,
peace and goodwill toward men.
♪ Away in the manger ♪
♪ No crib for a bed ♪
♪ The little Lord Jesus ♪
♪ Lay down his sweet head ♪
♪ The stars in the sky ♪
♪ Looked down where he lay ♪
♪ The little Lord Jesus ♪
♪ Asleep on the hay ♪
- Ladies and gentlemen, and children,
thank you all for being here this evening
and for making this year's program such a success.
Everyone did an absolutely splendid job on his or her parts.
And now, we are in for even more entertainment.
So help yourselves to the refreshments and have a good time.
(congregation applaud)
("Silent Night")
- What would you like Santa to bring you for Christmas?
- I don't know.
("Silent Night")
(violin music)
- I sell mittens by the pair.
(crowd laughs)
("Silent Night")
- I hear Nathan's going up to the special school
up in the mountains.
- Oh yeah, he's real excited
about going to that institution.
I sure will miss him while he's gone.
But while he's there, he's gonna learn all sorts
of useful stuff, aren't you, Nathan?
- What sorts of useful things?
- I don't know exactly, but I've heard
they've got experts there who can teach people like Nathan
to do some stuff by themselves.
- Well, you think Nathan would care to see my watch?
Oh yes, it's the finest thing I've ever owned by myself.
- [Sister] Cool, Nathan, isn't that beautiful?
- I never knew he could smile.
- Of course he can, he just doesn't do it very often.
Now, give the watch back and we must thank Renfroe
for letting us see it.
(light music)
(bell tolls)
- I've decided I want Nathan to have my watch.
- Why, we wouldn't dream of letting you give it up.
- Maybe Nathan would have more time at that institution
to admire it than I will at school.
- But it's the finest thing you've ever owned.
You even said so yourself.
You must keep it.
- No, I want Nathan to have it.
- It's just too generous of you.
You must be the most unselfish boy in the whole wide world.
(light music)
(bell tolls)
- Whoa, slow down there, boy.
Your mother's in the wagon and she's waiting on you.
She's getting cold.
Where have you been?
- Papa, I've got lots to tell you
and some other stuff, too.
- Well, all right.
Well, let's go see.
Let's go talk about it.
(children cheer)
Everybody in here?
Let's go home.
Come on, let's go.
(bell tolls)
(crickets chirping)
♪ Silent night ♪
♪ Holy night ♪
- [Renfroe] There is really no way I can describe how I felt
when I saw those big white snowflakes drifting down out
of the darkness that Christmas night.
I felt God must've been saying to me,
Renfroe, for what you did at church tonight for Nathan
and your act of unselfishness,
I'm sending you my Christmas gift.
And the next morning, white snow covered the ground
in rural Louisiana.
Father said it was truly God's miracle.
For a long time, D.J. and I looked for that old angel
that was nailed up on the barn.
We never found her.
♪ Sleep in heavenly peace ♪
♪ Silent night ♪
♪ Holy night ♪
♪ Shepherds quake ♪
♪ At the sight ♪
♪ Glories stream from heaven afar ♪
♪ Heavenly hosts sing alleluia ♪
♪ Christ the Savior is born ♪
(organ music)
♪ Silent night ♪
♪ Holy night ♪
♪ Son of God ♪
♪ Bless your night ♪
♪ AlD.J.mf;aj from thy holiness ♪
♪ With the Lord of redeeming grace ♪
♪ Jesus Christ at thy birth ♪
♪ Jesus Lord evermore ♪
(bell tolls)