YOU DID GOOD, CHAMP,
BUT YOU'RE RUNNING LATE.
WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
OH, GOD.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ SIGHS ]
SOME CHAMP, HUH?
I'M GOING TO NEED
A LOT MORE WORK.
HEY, HEY, HEY,
FORGET ABOUT THAT.
THOUGHT WE WEREN'T
TALKING ABOUT THAT ANYMORE?
SO DID YOU CALL?
YEAH, I DID.
SAM SAID YOU'RE LATE AGAIN.
YEAH, YEAH.
HE ALREADY GOT ALL
THE SUPPLIES READY FOR THE HIKE.
GOOD.
LISTEN, WHY DON'T YOU DO
YOURSELF A FAVOR AND RELAX
ONCE YOU GET UP THERE?
HAVE A GOOD TIME IN THE WOODS.
THANKS, JIMMY.
SEE YOU, CHAMP.
COME ON.
[ CAR HORN HONKS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
HEY, HEY, THAT'S ENOUGH, MAN!
ALL RIGHT, ALREADY!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALREADY!
[ SHOUTS ]
LOOK, BUDDY,
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO,
TO KILL HIM?
DON'T!
[ SHOUTS ]
DON'T.
I'M NOT PLAYING
WITH YOU. DON'T.
I'LL CUT YOU, BITCH!
DON'T.
LET IT GO. LET IT GO!
LET IT GO.
[ SCREAMS ]
THANKS.
YOU WERE A WHOLE HECK
OF A LOT OF HELP.
WHY DON'T YOU HELP THIS GUY?
HE NEEDS IT.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
DON'T SAY IT.
I'M NOT GOING
TO SAY YOU'RE LATE.
ME, MENTION IT AGAIN?
NAH!
WOULDN'T THINK OF IT.
WOULDN'T WANT OUR GLORIOUS
SWEEPSTAKE WINNER TO THINK
THAT BEING ON TIME IS IMPORTANT.
STOP!
[ LAUGHS ]
THEY ALL HERE?
FOUR JOINING ON.
ALL FIRST-TIMERS, THOUGH.
WONDER WHY THEY'RE THE ONES
THAT ALWAYS WIN
THESE THREE-DAY TRIPS
IN THE WOODS?
TWO OF THEM LOOKED LIKE
THEY NEVER MOW THE LAWN.
THEY PROBABLY HAVEN'T.
[ LAUGHS ]
LOOKS LIKE I'M NOT GOING
TO MEET MY MR. WONDERFUL
HERE AFTER ALL.
MORE LIKE MEETING LARRY,
CURLY AND MOE.
[ LAUGHS ]
YEAH, PUT THAT WITH
THE REST OF THE GEAR.
YEAH, I GOT THIS FOR YOU.
OH, THE LITTLE DARLING,
GOT TO MAKE UP
FOR HER TARDINESS.
NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S SOMETHING YOU NEED,
A NEW COMPASS.
I ALREADY HAVE MY OLD ONE.
BESIDES, I KNOW MY WAY AROUND.
YEAH, BUT YOUR OLD ONE'S
NOT RELIABLE.
IT IS RELIABLE.
I JUST NEVER LEARNED
HOW TO READ THE DARN THING.
GREAT. TELL THAT TO
OUR NEW CLIENTS.
SO IS EVERYBODY READY?
NO, THEY'RE JUST
STANDING HERE TO TAKE UP SPACE.
OF COURSE, THEY'RE READY.
SPACE, TAKING UP SPACE.
I SEEM TO REMEMBER
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT.
OH, YES, BETINA, HONEY,
DID YOU REMEMBER TO PACK
YOUR DIET PILLS?
HI, EVERYBODY.
I'M TIPPER TAYLOR,
YOUR TOUR GUIDE.
HI, TIPPER.
HI, HOW'S IT GOING?
GOOD.
IF WE COULD JUST HELP TO LOAD
IN OUR STUFF,
WE'LL GET RIGHT ON THE WAY.
ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
LET'S EVERYBODY GET YOUR BAGS
IN THE VAN.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GOING TO DO THAT.
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD
OUR PORTER DAYS ARE OVER?
I'M ONE OF YOUR TOUR GUIDES,
AND I'LL GUIDE YOU,
IF YOU'D LIKE,
IN YOUR FIRST LESSON.
PUT YOUR BAGS IN THERE.
BETINA! BETINA, HONEY!
WHY DON'T YOU PUT OUR BAGS
IN THE VAN?
IT'LL LOOK GREAT ON TAPE.
SMILE.
HERE, LET ME HELP WITH THAT.
OKAY?
AREN'T YOU A GENTLEMAN?
OKAY.
HI.
FIRST CAMPING TRIP, HUH?
HI, YEAH.
SURE YOU'LL ENJOY IT.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S GO.
READY TO ROLL?
YEAH, I READY.
LET'S DO IT.
BUCKLE UP.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS GROUP?
WE ARE IN THE VAN TAKING OFF.
ARE YOU GOING TO MAKE
A FULL DOCUMENTARY?
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME--
YOU ARE OR AREN'T WITH ME.
SHE WENT OUT AND
BOUGHT IT FOR ME.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
THIS IS LIFE.
AH, MR. AND MRS. PAGE?
HI.
HI, WHEN I SPOKE TO YOUR WIFE
OVER THE PHONE, SHE TOLD ME
YOU WERE LOOKING
FOR A NEW VIDEO CAMERA.
SEE YOU FOUND ONE.
OH, YEAH, SHE GOT
A GREAT DEAL.
SMILE FOR THE CAMERA NOW.
HOW YOU DOING?
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT DO YOU SAY, WE CALL
EACH OTHER BY OUR FIRST NAMES?
SURE.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
JUST KIDDING.
VINCE PAGE.
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
VINCE PAGE,
AND THIS IS MY WIFE, BETINA.
HI.
SO WE CAN CALL YOU TWO
BY YOUR FIRST NAMES?
SURE, OF COURSE, YOU CAN.
HONEY, TELL HIM YOUR NAME.
I'M LISA.
AND I'M JOHN.
WE'RE THE BECONS.
I'M MARIA.
HI, MARIA.
FREDDY MARTINEZ?
THIS IS FREDDY MARTINEZ.
HI.
[ LAUGHS ]
HI, FREDDY.
AND OF COURSE, WE CAN'T
FORGET OUR MAIN MAN, SAMMY.
HI, AGAIN, EVERYONE.
HERE'S OUR PROUD OWNER
OF T.T. HIKING OUR OWN
LITTLE DARLING, TIPPER.
HI, YOU GUYS.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE REALLY GOING
TO HAVE A WONDERFUL TIME.
LEARN HOW TO SURVIVE IN
THE WILDERNESS
AND REJOIN MOTHER NATURE
AND ALL THE GOOD
SHE HAS TO OFFER.
WILL MOTHER NATURE
PUT ME TO BED AT NIGHT?
IF YOU DON'T SHUT UP,
THEN I'LL PUT TO SLEEP.
I'LL ASK.
ALL I CAN DO IS ASK.
JOHN, ARE THERE ANY BEARS
WHERE WE'RE CAMPING?
NO, HONEY. COME ON.
WE'LL HAVE A MARVELOUS TIME.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M SCARED.
TIPPER, MY WIFE WANTS TO KNOW
IF THERE ARE ANY BEARS
WHERE WE'RE CAMPING.
NO, NO BEARS, ACTUALLY,
BUT YOU MIGHT SEE
SOME DEER, COYOTE,
MAYBE EVEN SOME SNAKES.
OH.
NO, NO, NON-POISONOUS SNAKES,
HONEST.
NO SELF-RESPECTING SNAKE
WOULD EVER GO NEAR HUMANS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
BUT YOU MIGHT EVEN SEE
SOME EAGLES. RIGHT?
YEAH.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
WE'RE JUST ARRIVING
ON EAGLE MOUNTAIN NOW,
RIGHT UP THERE, WHERE IT'S
SAID THAT THE INDIAN SPIRITS
ROAM IN SEARCH FOR THE RIGHTFUL
PLACE IN SOCIETY,
SO IF YOU'RE REALLY QUIET,
YOU MIGHT JUST HEAR THEM.
YOU'LL PROBABLY WANT TO KEEP
YOUR EYES OPEN, TOO,
BECAUSE THEY'RE OUT THERE.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU GUYS
BELIEVE IT, BUT SAMMY AND I DO.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, THE CHIEF,
HE'S A GOOD FRIEND OF OURS.
[ LAUGHS ]
BUT I'M AFRAID THAT
THE DEVELOPERS HAVE ACTUALLY
MADE THE BEARS VANISH.
ONE GOOD THING IS THERE'S
PLENTY OF SURPRISES
TO DISCOVER, I MEAN, PLENTY,
YEAH, AND THE MAIN THING
TO KNOW IS
THAT THESE CAMPING TRIPS
ARE REALLY GOOD
AT REMOVING STRESS.
YOU KNOW, THOSE PERSONAL
LITTLE BARRIERS
THAT BUILD UP ON US?
SO WHY DON'T WE JUST
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THIS TRIP
AND GO BEYOND
OUR USUAL DAILY CHORES,
RIGHT?
EXACTLY.
RE-FAMILIARIZE OURSELVES AND
GETTING BACK TO A MORE
NATURAL PACE OF LIVING.
THREE DAYS?
REMOVE THE LITTLE STRESSES
OF LIFE IN THREE DAYS?
THREE YEARS, MAYBE.
WE COULD'VE BEEN ON A CRUISE,
BUT NO, LET'S TAKE
A HIKE, YOU SAID.
TAKE A HIKE?
YOU SHOULD TAKE A HIKE.
YOU WON THE LOTTERY,
BUT I WON THE SWEEPSTAKES
THAT WON US THIS TRIP,
SO LET'S TRY AND BE CHEERY.
TIPPER, HOW LONG HAVE
YOU BEEN DOING
THESE WILDERNESS OUTINGS?
OH, BOY, FOR QUITE
A FEW YEARS, ACTUALLY.
WHEN MY DAD DIED,
I TOOK OVER THE BUSINESS.
AND TEAKY WAS
A REAL GRIZZLY ADAMS,
REAL GRIZZLY ADAMS.
JOHN, I THOUGHT
THERE WERE NO BEARS.
[ LAUGHS ]
NOW THEY'RE TALKING
ABOUT GRIZZLIES.
HONEY, THEY'RE
TALKING ABOUT HER FATHER.
SEE, GRIZZLY ADAMS WAS
A GUY WHO--WELL,
HE USED TO TAKE--
WHO WAS HE, ANYWAY?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ABOUT HOW MUCH LONGER
DO WE HAVE TO GO?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS ALL NEW TO ME.
THE SAME.
HEY, TIPPER, EXCUSE ME.
ABOUT HOW MUCH LONGER
DO WE HAVE TO GO?
OH, NOT MUCH LONGER.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
23 BOTTLES OF BEER
YOU TAKE ONE DOWN,
PASS IT AROUND,
22 BOTTLES OF BEER ON THE WALL.
WE'RE HERE!
TWENTY-TWO BOTTLES OF BEER
ON THE WALL.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE ARE.
LET'S LINE UP FOR OUR LUGGAGE
AND KEYS.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
LONG RIDE, HUH?
[ LAUGHS ]
SO WHOSE LUGGAGE IS THIS?
IS THIS YOURS? NICE.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S DO IT.
LET'S LINE UP FOR OUR KEYS.
VINCE AND BETINA?
YEAH.
ROOM NINE.
FREDDY?
YOU'RE IN ROOM SIX.
MARIA?
YOU'RE IN ROOM SEVEN.
AND SAMMY, YOU AND I ARE
ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE BUNGALOWS.
OKAY.
EXCUSE ME. WHAT ABOUT US?
OH, I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE SLEEPING OUTSIDE
WITH THE BEARS.
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT?
NO, SHE'S TEASING.
JUST KIDDING.
HERE, YOU'RE IN ROOM THREE.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU GUYS. OKAY.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP,
EVERYBODY.
YOU KNOW, THE FOOD'S
PRETTY GOOD, SO EAT UP,
GET PLENTY OF SLEEP.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED IT.
WE'RE GOING TO START
AT 5:30 SHARP.
I DO MEAN 5:30.
SHARP.
OH, I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
[ LAUGHS ]
NO, NO, NO, I'LL BE THERE.
I CAN DO SHARP.
OKAY.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYBODY.
GOOD NIGHT.
SO, DO YOU THINK
THIS GROUP IS READY
FOR THE BIG OLD OUTDOORS?
I BELIEVE ANYTHING BY NOW.
[ LAUGHS ]
BY THE WAY, I FORGOT
TO ASK YOU.
HOW WAS YOUR MORNING WORKOUT?
IT WAS BETTER.
HONEST.
YOU KNOW, I'VE HEARD
THESE LITTLE STROLLS
IN THE WOODS CAN DO WONDERS FOR
STRESS, EASE ALL THE TENSION.
YOU HEARD THAT, HUH?
UH-HUH.
YOU KNOW, I HEARD
THAT SOMEWHERE, TOO.
WHERE DID YOU HEAR THAT FROM?
[ LAUGHS ]
WANT TO WORK OUT LATER?
AH, WELL, OKAY.
LET ME SLEEP FIRST.
THEN I'LL BE FINE.
EIGHT O'CLOCK.
IS THAT A SHARP EIGHT
OR A DULL EIGHT TWENTY?
NO, I CAN DO SHARP.
I CAN DO SHARP, EIGHT O'CLOCK?
AH, YEAH, RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU AT 8:20.
[ GUNSHOTS ON TV ]
WILL YOU TURN
THAT DAMN THING OFF?
[ TV TURNS OFF ]
[ DOG BARKS ]
THAT'S TIPPER AND SAMMY.
WE ARE AT THE ROADSIDE MOTEL.
WILL YOU GROW UP?
PUT THAT DAMN TOY OF YOURS AWAY
AND COME TO BED.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
LOVE, ROMANCE, SEX.
YEAH, WE GOT IT ALL.
SOMEWHERE.
I KNOW IT'S HERE SOMEWHERE.
I THINK WE JUST FORGOT
TO PACK IT
WITH THE REST OF OUR BELONGINGS.
[ SIGHS ]
I AM TAPING TIPPER
AND OUR TOUR GUIDE, SAMMY,
DOING SOME SORT OF
WEIRD STRANGE MOVEMENTS,
YOGURT, I THINK IT'S CALLED,
YOGI, YOGA.
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, GOD.
[ VOICES MURMUR ]
ONE AT A TIME.
DID YOU GET WHAT I SAID?
HEY, JACK, WHAT'D YOU HAVE
TO HIRE THIS SLUT FOR, ANYWAY?
HMM?
DON'T CALL ME A SLUT.
CALL YOU ANYTHING I WANT.
THAT'S WHAT HE PAID FOR,
DIDN'T HE?
ALL RIGHT. THAT'S IT.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
HEY, LIKE FUCK YOU ARE.
WE PAID, YOU DELIVER.
YOU'RE A WHORE.
[ SHOUTING ]
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
YOU TAKE THAT BACK OR--
YOU'RE DOING A GOOD
JOB OF THAT NOW.
DON'T!
SHE'S OKAY, MAN.
SHUT UP!
CAN'T YOU HANDLE
A FEW DRINKS?
WHAT'D YOU DO, BOAR?
AH, MAN!
YOU HURT HER BAD, BOAR.
OKAY, OKAY.
OH, CHRIST.
I'M APOLOGIZING TO A WHORE.
REAL BIG IN THE JOINT.
SHE'S NOT MOVING.
AH, HEY, SURPRISE.
SHE'S PROBABLY DEAD.
SHE'S NOT BREATHING, JACK.
IS SHE DEAD?
JESUS, DID YOU KILL HER?
OH, NO, DON'T TELL ME THIS.
OH, NO, JESUS,
ANYTHING BUT THIS.
SHUT UP, YOU IDIOT!
SHE IS DEAD!
SHUT UP!
JESUS, IF HE SAW OR TAPED
ANY OF THAT, WE'RE FUCKED!
I'LL TAKE CARE OF
THE PHONES.
YOU FIND OUT WHAT ROOM HE'S IN.
WE CAN'T LET HIM GET AWAY.
WONDERFUL.
TAKE A HIKE.
GOOD FOR STRESS,
YEAH, SURE.
[ SIGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
JESUS!
[ LAUGHS ]
I'M SORRY. I APOLOGIZE.
I REALLY DO.
YOU SCARED ME.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WITH
THAT TOURING VAN, AREN'T YOU?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT'S ME.
YEAH, WHERE YOU HEADED?
I'VE DONE SOME
HIKING IN MY TIME.
WILLOW BASE CAMP.
I'VE BEEN THERE.
THAT CAN BE ROUGH COUNTRY,
YOU KNOW.
YEAH, IT IS.
THERE'S A LITTLE FELLOW
WITH A BEARD AND A VIDEO CAMERA.
IS HE WITH YOU?
YEAH, WHY, DID HE BOTHER YOU?
[ LAUGHS ]
NO, NO, NO, NOT REALLY, NO.
HAVE A NICE EVENING.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO FRIGHTEN YOU.
THAT'S OKAY.
HAVE A GOOD ONE.
YEAH, OKAY.
BYE.
YOU CAN'T FIND HIM?
THERE'S ONLY
20 GODDAMN ROOMS HERE.
THEY'RE ALL DARK.
I MEAN, WHAT AM I GOING
TO DO--
ALL RIGHT. LISTEN TO ME.
WE'LL WAIT 'TIL MORNING.
WE'LL TAKE TURNS KEEPING WATCH.
WE GOT TO GET THAT CAMERA.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF HER.
YOU STAY HERE 'TIL I GET BACK.
DON'T GIVE ME
ANY GODDAMN FACES.
LISTEN TO ME, LISTEN TO ME,
YOU STAY HERE,
GRAB HIM IF HE SHOWS HIMSELF.
WE GOT TO GET THAT CAMERA.
WE GOT TO GET THE TAPE.
OKAY? YOU HEAR ME?
ALL RIGHT.
MAKE SURE HE HASN'T
SAID ANYTHING TO ANYONE.
ALL RIGHT? GO.
I'M SHARP.
SHARP, I PROMISE I DID SHARP.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AH, GEEZ.
MORNING.
HI, GOOD MORNING.
HOW ARE YOU?
THANKS, JOHN.
HI.
MORNING, BETINA.
GOOD MORNING.
NICE DAY.
MORNING, SAM.
BEAUTIFUL DAY.
THANK YOU.
JUST THINK,
IN A LITTLE WHILE,
YOU'LL ALL BE FROLICKING
IN NATURE.
YES, IT'S GOING
TO BE EXCITING, ISN'T IT?
YOU CAN COUNT ON IT.
GOOD MORNING, VINCE.
WHAT? NO RECORDING OF
THIS EXCITING EVENT?
NOT RIGHT NOW, THANK YOU.
HI, VINCE.
ALL SET TO ROLL?
YEAH.
YES, WE'RE READY.
LET'S DO IT.
OKAY.
BUCKLE UP.
[ LAUGHS ]
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, GANG.
FIFTEEN-MINUTE BREAK.
OH!
TAKE OUT YOUR CAMERAS
'CAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO WANT
A PICTURE OF THIS
GORGEOUS VIEW.
BACK IN THE VAN IN 15.
ALL RIGHT?
THAT STUFF'S EXPENSIVE.
BETTER SORT OUT HOW MUCH
YOU USE.
THANKS FOR ANOTHER
VALUABLE LESSON IN ECONOMICS.
BE PART OF THIS TRIP.
WHEN YOU GET YOUR FAT FACE
OUT OF MY LIFE.
GOOD.
TIPPER?
YEAH.
COULD YOU GET A FEW SHOTS
OF ME AND MY WIFE?
OF COURSE.
NEXT STOP, BASE CAMP.
OH, GOOD. YEAH.
OKAY. SMILE.
OKAY.
HERE YOU GO.
HEY, PAL.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
LOOK, THAT'S NOT YOUR CAMERA.
WELL, IT IS RIGHT NOW.
WHAT?
YOU DON'T HAVE ENOUGH MONEY
TO AFFORD YOUR OWN CAMERA?
YOU SHUT YOUR FACE
'CAUSE THAT'S MINE,
AND I'M GOING TO
TAKE IT FROM HERE.
AND THERE AIN'T NOTHING
YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT?
YOU WANT TO FUCK AROUND?
COME ON, COME ON.
I'LL FUCK AROUND.
OKAY.
I'VE HAD IT WITH YOU.
COME ON, MAN.
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
THOSE FRIENDS OF YOURS?
PROBABLY JUST SOME
JUNKIES LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
THEY COULD SELL.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I'M STILL HERE,
AREN'T I?
OH, OH, I'LL SAY.
THAT WAS IMPRESSIVE.
TEACH ME SOME OF THAT STUFF.
FEAR, SAY GOODBYE!
I'D SAY YOU'RE BACK TO CHAMP
LEVEL MYSELF, BUT YOU KNOW,
YOU SHOULD'VE LET
THAT GUY TAKE THAT CAMERA.
WE DON'T NEED THAT ON THIS HIKE.
BELIEVE ME, I KNOW, SAMMY,
I KNOW.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
THANK YOU.
HEY, WE HAVE
A LADY RAMBO WITH US.
IS THAT PART OF WHAT
WE'RE HERE FOR?
NO, NOT REALLY.
ALL RIGHT. BREAK'S OVER.
ALL ABOARD.
NICE JOB.
OH, MAN.
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING'S
NOT RIGHT HERE,
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT
CAMERA, SAMMY.
UH-HUH.
VINCE HAS GOTTEN
PRETTY QUIET.
NO RANGERS
AROUND HERE, EITHER.
WE BETTER KEEP OUR EYES OPEN.
JUST HOPE THEY DON'T COME BACK.
ALL RIGHT .LET'S DO IT.
BUCKLE UP.
SAMMY, WHY DO I HAVE
THE FEELING THAT OUR
MR. PAIGE IS
KEEPING SOMETHING FROM US?
WELCOME TO BASE CAMP.
WAY TO GO, CHAMP!
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS, HONEY.
WHOSE IS THIS?
UH, MINE.
THERE YOU GO, UH-HUH.
THANK YOU, SAMMY.
OKAY, EVERYBODY.
LET'S ALL MAKE SURE
WE STAY TOGETHER.
ALWAYS MAKE SURE AND SEE
HOW YOUR PARTNER'S DOING.
IF WE ALL WANT TO STOP,
WE'LL ALL STOP
AT THE SAME TIME.
WE HAVE A LONG HIKE AHEAD OF US,
AND JUST REMEMBER,
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT STRANGE UNKNOWN ANIMALS
MAY BE LURKING
BEHIND THOSE TREES.
SHE'S KIDDING, RIGHT?
OH, RIGHT, YES, BESIDES,
IF I WERE A BEAR,
I WOULD NOT WANT
TO RUN INTO HER.
SHE WOULD PUNCH
THE EVER LIVING PISS OUT OF ME.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU READY?
YEAH.
ALL SADDLED UP?
THERE WE GO.
YOU READY?
UH-HUH.
LET'S GO.
ALL SADDLED UP?
YEAH.
LET'S HIT THE TRAIL.
WHEN IT RAINS,
THE WATER LEVEL IS SO HIGH,
IT JUST COMPLETELY FLOODS
THIS WHOLE BRIDGE OUT.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
IT THIS DOESN'T WORK,
AND FAST,
THEN WE'RE DOING IT MY WAY.
LOOK, DON'T WORRY.
JUST CALM DOWN. ALL RIGHT?
JUST CALM DOWN.
IT'S GOING TO WORK.
TRUST ME.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
LIKE BACK THERE
WHERE YOU GOT THE SHIT
KICKED OUT OF YOU.
SHE WAS LUCKY.
SHE WAS LUCKY,
YOU WERE LUCKY,
LUCKY SHE DIDN'T BURY
HER FOOT SIX INCHES
IN YOUR SKULL.
LOOK, I CAN HANDLE MYSELF.
OKAY?
YEAH, RIGHT. WELL, LISTEN,
THIS'LL HANDLE ANYTHING.
COME ON.
STEP FLAT ONTO THE ROPE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
YOU CAN GO ON UP THERE.
THANKS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
COME ON. YOU CAN DO IT.
COME ON.
NOW WHAT DO I DO?
JUST STEP ON THE ROCK.
GOOD. THAT'S GREAT.
OH!
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, YOU GOT IT.
ARE YOU ALL WET?
YEAH. I'M OKAY.
OKAY.
JUST GRAB THE ASSHOLE
WHEN HE MOVES AWAY
FROM THE GROUP.
WHAT IF THEY SEE US?
THEN WHAT?
THEN THEY GOT A PROBLEM,
BIG TIME.
YEAH, A PROBLEM.
HEY, SHUT UP.
WILL YOU SHUT UP?
YOU'RE DRIVING ME CRAZY?
RELAX.
ENJOY THE WOODS.
I CAN'T RELAX.
I'M RELAXING, I'M RELAXING.
I'M OUT IN THE WOODS.
LOOK, IF ONE WAS
CAUGHT IN THE WOODS
WITHOUT ANYTHING TO EAT,
THESE WOULD BE ENOUGH
TO SURVIVE ON.
HMM.
THEY'RE EDIBLE.
REALLY?
YEAH, I'D LIKE YOU ALL
TO STUDY THEM
AND LOOK THEM OVER--
REALLY?
BECAUSE YOU NEVER KNOW
WHEN YOU'LL BE NEEDING THEM.
WHEN YOU'RE OUT IN THE WOODS,
AND YOU DON'T HAVE A TENT
OR A SLEEPING BAG,
YOU USE WHAT NATURE
HAS TO OFFER YOU.
AND TONIGHT'S--
KEEP THEM IN MIND, HON.
IT MIGHT BE GOOD FOR YOUR DIET.
VINCENT, SHUT UP.
OOH, WOW, ALL THIS
EROTIC TALK, TURNING ME ON.
COME ON, HON.
IT'S TOO LIGHT OUT
HERE FOR LOVING AND STUFF.
SHUT UP!
JESUS, DON'T THEY EVER
TAKE A LONG REST?
I'M ABOUT READ TO GIVE
THEM A PERMANENT REST.
OH, NOW, THAT'S GREAT.
I MEAN, THAT'S JUST
WHAT WE NEED, ANOTHER KILLING.
NOW IF YOU JUST DIDN'T
LOSE YOUR TEMPER.
SHE WAS A STUPID BITCH.
SHE HAD IT COMING.
SHE SHOULD'VE
KEPT HER MOUTH SHUT.
OH, NO. NOBODY DESERVES THAT.
I MEAN, THAT WAS MEAN
THIS MORNING, PLAIN
AND SIMPLE MEANNESS.
WHY DON'T YOU SHUT
THE FUCK UP?
WHY DON'T I SHUT THE FUCK UP.
LET ME HELP YOU.
OOH, GOT TO WATCH
THESE MEAN TERRAINS HERE, BABY.
SOMEBODY MIGHT SEE US, JOHN.
OH, THEY COULD LEARN
A LESSON IN SURVIVAL.
THIS IS TURNING ME ON HERE.
[ LAUGHS ]
EVERYTHING TURNS YOU ON.
WAIT 'TIL I GET YOU
IN THAT TENT TONIGHT, OH!
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU SAY THAT EVERY NIGHT.
OKAY, EVERYBODY.
COME ON.
I'LL HELP YOU ACROSS.
THERE WE GO, AND STEP ON OVER,
BETINA.
OOH!
THERE WE GO.
COME ON, VINCE.
YOU CAN DO IT, FREDDY.
GREAT.
HEY, THEY'RE DOING
PRETTY GOOD HERE, HUH?
IS THAT ANYTHING
LIKE THE GUY WHO FELL 30 FLOORS?
EACH FLOOR DOWN, HE SAID,
"SO FAR, SO GOOD."
[ LAUGHS ]
SAMMY!
WHAT WOULD I DO WITHOUT YOU?
YOU'D PICK TIPS A NIGHT
INSTEAD OF TWO.
WRONG, I WON THAT LAST BET.
REMEMBER?
I DIDN'T WANT TO BET.
I DON'T LIKE TO BET.
I SWEAR TO THE GREAT MOUNTAIN,
THIS IS THE LAST TIME
I'M GOING TO BET THAT WOMAN.
NO, THE LAST TIME I'M GOING
TO BET ANY WOMAN.
THERE, I THINK I MADE
MY PEACE WITH MOTHER NATURE.
BOY, YOU GUYS
ARE DOING GREAT.
HOME, HOME ON THE RANGE.
OKAY, GANG.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS WHERE WE'RE
SPENDING THE NIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO PITCH OUR TENTS
IN A HALF CIRCLE FORM,
AND OF COURSE,
THE STREAM IS DOWN THERE,
AND IT'S THE BEST WATER
YOU'LL EVER DRINK.
WHY DON'T YOU GUYS
CHECK YOUR DUTY LISTS
AND SEE WHO'S TO MAKE THE FIRE?
OH, THAT'S ME.
GOOD. I'LL BE OVER
IN A MINUTE TO GIVE YOU A HAND.
OKAY?
OKAY.
LET'S DO IT.
PLACE STAKE "A" INTO
GROUND FOUR INCHES DEEP.
OKAY. LET'S SEE.
WHICH ONE IS THE "A"?
HERE, FREDDY,
LET ME HELP YOU.
[ LAUGHS ]
I'M TRYING TO GET IT.
RIGHT WHEN I THINK I HAVE IT,
IT DOES THIS.
OH, SHIT.
INHALE.
[ BLOWS ]
[ COUGHS ]
FORGET THE CAMERA,
DON'T PAY ANY ATTENTION
TO THE CAMERA.
SEE, SO IF YOU PULL IT
THIS WAY AND PUT IT IN HERE,
THEN YOU'VE GOT
YOUR TENT PITCHED. SEE?
NOW I'VE GOT IT.
GOOD.
I SAW YOU FIGHT
IN SAN DIEGO NINE MONTHS AGO,
WASN'T IT?
THAT WAS SOME FIGHT.
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT HAPPENED TO THAT
GIRL YOU WERE FIGHTING?
LOOK, FREDDY.
I DON'T MEAN
TO HURT YOUR FEELINGS
OR ANYTHING, BUT IT'S JUST
SOMETHING I'D RATHER NOT
TALK ABOUT. OKAY?
OH, DID I SAY
THE WRONG THING?
I'M SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO UPSET YOU.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU DIDN'T.
IT'S JUST SOMETHING
I'D RATHER LEAVE ALONE. OKAY?
I'M SURE YOU UNDERSTAND.
RIGHT?
I WON'T MENTION IT AGAIN,
SCOUTS HONOR.
YOU'RE A DEAR.
MAY I BE OF HELP?
OH!
OH, YOU SCARED ME.
I WAS JUST READING THIS,
BUT I'M NOT GETTING
VERY FAR, IT SEEMS.
PROBLEM?
I CAN'T FIND THE "A" STAKE.
TONIGHT.
I'M NOT WAITING ANY LONGER.
IT'S YOUR FUCKING FAULT,
NOT MINE.
NOT MINE. OOH.
JESUS, BOAR, YOU KNOW,
YOU GOT NO SENSE OF LIFE, MAN.
WHY DON'T YOU SHUT UP?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
I MEAN, LOOK AT THAT.
THEY'RE EATING STEAKS.
I MEAN, THEY'RE COOKING
AND EATING STEAKS.
WHEN WE GET THAT CAMERA FREAK,
I'M GOING TO GRAB ME SOME FOOD.
AH, SMART, REAL SMART.
WE GRAB NOTHING BUT HIM.
YOU GOT IT?
EAT YOUR SHIRT.
[ SCREAMS ]
BETINA, WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
CALM DOWN! WHAT?
A BUG! IT FELL ON ME!
LET ME LOOK.
OH, IT'S A BUG, ISN'T IT?
IT'S POISONOUS!
IT'S OKAY.
YOU CAN SHOW ME.
IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
IT'S NOTHING.
OOH!
[ LAUGHS ]
A PRACTICAL JOKE,
THAT'S ALL IT WAS.
COME ON.
SHE HATES SPIDERS.
I HAD TO GET IT ON TAPE.
MY FRIENDS WILL LOVE IT.
VINCE, YOU HAVE THE SENSE
OF HUMOR OF A BAD CHILD.
DO YOU KNOW THAT?
AND I'M NOT GOING
TO TELL HER WHAT YOU DID.
I DON'T HAVE THE HEART,
AND I REALLY DON'T CARE
WHAT THIS RELATIONSHIP
OF YOURS HAS COME TO
BECAUSE IT'S NONE OF
MY BUSINESS,
BUT WE HAVE
TWO MORE DAYS OUT HERE,
AND IF I SEE THAT CAMERA
GET US INTO ANY MORE
TROUBLE, THEN YOU'VE HAD IT.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
YEAH.
I MEAN, IF IT EVEN AFFECTS
ANY OF THE OTHER MEMBERS,
EVEN UPSETS THEM,
THEN YOU'VE HAD IT, BUDDY.
YOU GOT IT?
DID HE HAVE BUGS
ON HIM, TOO?
DIFFERENT KIND.
HE IS THE MOST MORONIC,
CHILDISH, STUPID ASS FOOL
I HAVE EVER SEEN IN MY LIFE.
[ LAUGHS ]
HE NEEDS TO BE SPANKED
WITH A GODDAMN BROKEN BRANCH.
DO YOU THINK IT'S FUNNY, SAMMY?
IT'S SOCIAL RETARDS LIKE HIM
THAT CREATE A CRAZY WORLD
AND BLAME EVERYBODY ELSE
AS IF THEY'RE THE ONES
WHO'S CRAZY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
YOU THINK IT'S FUNNY?
IT'S NOT FUNNY, SAMMY.
WHAT THE HELL IS SO FUNNY
ABOUT IT?
YOU THINK IT'S FUNNY?
DO YOU REALLY THINK
IT'S THAT FUNNY?
YOU SHOULD'VE
LET HIM TAKE THE DAMN CAMERA!
AH, GEEZ.
THAT'S FUNNY, HUH?
YOU KNOW, MAYBE THAT IS FUNNY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT ONLY FUNNY,
BUT THE NEXT TIME THAT LITTLE
TWERP DOES ANYTHING ELSE,
I'M GOING TO KICK
HIS BUTT, BIG TIME!
WHY DIDN'T YOU HELP ME?
IS IT TOO MUCH TO ASK YOU
TO PUT THAT DAMN THING DOWN
AND HELP ME?
YOU WANT A RECORD OF
OUR TRIP, DON'T YOU?
BESIDES, IT'LL GIVE YOUR BRIDGE
CLUB SOMETHING TO REMEMBER.
I COULD'VE BEEN
BITTEN TO DEATH.
AH! AH!
RIGHT THERE.
THERE'S NOTHING THERE.
OKAY.
AW, MY SWEETIE PIE.
HMM.
HAVING FUN YET?
NO.
NO?
BOY, THIS OUGHT
TO KEEP YOU KIDS DRY ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE
THE SOUND OF THAT RAIN
ON YOUR ROOF, BUT FOR ME,
ALL I'VE SET UP IS
A BED OF LEAVES,
A WOOD COVERING WITH
WOODEN LEAVES AND
MY BEDROLL'S ALL OUTDOORS.
IN THIS RAIN?
HELL, IT AIN'T GOING
TO RAIN TONIGHT.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
I KNOW.
I'VE LIVED OUT HERE LONG ENOUGH.
[ THUNDER ]
YOU AND SAMMY ARE REALLY GOOD
AT THIS OUTDOOR LIFESTYLE.
YEAH, IT SEEMS
PRETTY NATURAL TO ME, I GUESS.
I WAS ACTUALLY BROUGHT UP
WITH IT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S SO DIFFERENT
FROM THE CITY LIFE.
YEAH.
I LIKE THE CHANGE,
KIND OF LIKE THE WEATHER.
ONE MINUTE, IT'S STORMING.
THE NEXT MINUTE, YOU WANT TO GO
INTO THE STREAM AND TAKE A DIVE.
HMM.
'CAUSE IT'S SO HOT
FROM THE SUN.
WE'RE OUT HERE IN THE RAIN.
WHAT THE FUCK
AM I DOING IN THE RAIN?
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
DOING 20 YEARS, REMEMBER,
YOU IDIOT?
I WAS THINKING MAYBE IT
WAS JUST TO GET WET.
OH, I DON'T WANT
TO HEAR THIS.
YOU GOT IT?
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
ALL RIGHT.
SHUT UP, RIGHT?
DON'T PLAY ME, JACK.
IT'LL BE DRY IN ANOTHER HOUR.
YOU'LL SEE.
WHAT ABOUT KEEPING WARM?
WELL, SIMPLE,
I JUST ASK BEARS
TO LOAN ONE OF THEIR FUR COATS.
HE'S SAYING A JOKE, RIGHT?
RIGHT, HONEY.
YOU DON'T BORROW FUR FROM BEARS.
[ LAUGHS ]
I KNOW THAT, DUMMY.
I MEANT ARE THERE
ANY BEARS IN THE WOODS?
JUST ME, BABY.
RARR!
[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT DO YOU DO, FREDDY?
INVESTMENTS.
I HAVE A PHONE STUCK
IN MY EAR ALL DAY LONG.
OUCH!
GOD.
YEAH, VINCE HAS GOT SOMETHING
STUCK IN HIM SOMEWHERE.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT,
BUT IT'S NOT IN HIS EAR.
OH, BOY.
I MEAN, REALLY,
LOOK AT HIM OUT THERE.
HE'S THE ONE COMPLAINING,
WANTING TO GO HOME
BECAUSE IT'S RAINING,
AND HE'S STANDING THERE
IN THE DRENCHING RAIN
FILMING THE TREES
LIKE THE ABOMINABLE SNOWMAN
IS COME JUMPING OUT AT HIM?
[ LAUGHTER ]
SERIOUS, YES.
DO YOU THINK THIS RAIN
WILL LAST LONG?
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE.
THESE MOUNTAIN STORMS SEEM
TO BRING A VARIETY
OF DIFFERENT EXPERIENCES.
[ LAUGHS ]
UH-HUH.
IT MAKES THE FOREST
SO BEAUTIFUL, THOUGH.
IT IS.
DANGEROUS IN SOME WAYS,
BUT I REALLY LOVE IT.
IT'S SO GORGEOUS.
I DON'T KNOW.
I STILL PREFER IT
TO THE CITY LIFE.
I'M STARTING TO LIKE IT.
LIKE WHEN I WAS KID--
UH-HUH, YEAH.
--IT WAS GREAT.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU MEAN.
IT REALLY IS NICE.
OW, I'LL TAKE THAT.
I CAN SEE YOUR CARDS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE ALL THINKING.
WHAT?
YOU THINKING I NEED TO
LOSE A LITTLE WEIGHT.
NO!
YEAH, YEAH, BUT IT'S
BABY FAT, AND SOME OF
IT'S WATER WEIGHT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
IF I GAIN ANY MORE
WATER WEIGHT, THEY'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO BUILD A DIKE
ACROSS FROM MY BUTT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'VE TRIED AMPHETAMINES,
YOU KNOW, THOSE DIET PILLS.
YEAH.
ALL THEY DID WAS
MAKE ME EAT FASTER.
[ LAUGHING ]
OH, YOU KNOW THAT
OPRAH WINFREY DIET?
I WENT ON THAT DIET.
I HAVEN'T LOST ANY WEIGHT YET.
I HAVE THIS OVERWHELMING
URGE TO HOST A TALK SHOW.
SO, TELL ME, SIR,
HOW MANY YEARS HAVE YOU
BEEN WEARING WOMEN'S UNDERWEAR?
OH, JUST TWO.
[ LAUGHING ]
SO THEN YOU GAVE UP
A HIGH PAYING JOB
TO DO THIS LIFESTYLE?
WELL, THERE'S MORE TO IT
THAN THAT, FREDDY.
TIPPERS DAD AND I
WERE CLOSE FRIENDS.
HE TAUGHT ME A LOT ABOUT WHAT
WAS IMPORTANT IN LIFE,
AND I WAS A LITTLE FED UP
WITH BUSINESS PRESSURES,
AND I TOOK OFF.
IT WASN'T EASY AT FIRST,
BUT I GOT THROUGH IT.
MY HEALTH RETURNED,
AND I'M HAPPY,
AND I LIKE THIS LIFE,
I LOVE THIS LIFE.
GOOD.
YEAH.
THAT'S NICE.
WELL, IF YOU'LL
ALL EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE A LOT OF THINGS
TO LOOK OVER
BEFORE TOMORROW'S ADVENTURES.
I THINK I'LL JUST SAY
GOOD NIGHT NOW.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYBODY.
GOOD NIGHT.
EVER SINCE I WON THAT
DAMN LOTTERY, WE HAVEN'T BEEN
FRIENDLY ANYMORE.
BETINA, HONEY, YOU CAN'T
CONTROL HIM WITH MONEY.
MEN DON'T LIKE THAT.
WELL, NO, IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
LISTEN, YOU MADE HIM
QUIT HIS JOB, AND YOU SAY
HOW THE MONEY GOES
AND WHERE, AND THAT
MAKES YOU THE BOSS.
THERE'S NO PARTNERSHIP,
AND I KNOW YOU WON THE MONEY,
BUT IT'S HIS, TOO.
YEAH, BUT WE'VE
TALKED ABOUT IT.
UH-HUH.
IT'S NEVER EASY WHEN
YOU NEVER HAVE MUCH,
AND THEN SUDDENLY,
YOU HAVE ALL YOU NEED,
EVERYTHING--
UH-HUH.
--EXCEPT FOR THE REAL THINGS.
THE THINGS THAT COUNT.
YEAH.
UH-HUH. I KNOW.
MY DAYS OF DANCING
AND LIVING LIKE A GYPSY
AND NO HOME WITH SOMEONE
THAT MEANS ALL TO YOU,
YOU KNOW, I HAD SO MANY MEN
BUT I NEVER FOUND
THE SPECIAL ONE,
AND THE FUNNY THING IS
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS SAY
THIS IS THE ONE, AND IT IS,
AND IF YOU DON'T,
THEN YOU END UP ALONE,
AND YOU'RE NOT MUCH USE
TO ANYONE.
MARIA, LET ME HAVE A SLUG
OF THAT STUFF.
[ COUGHS ]
I UNDERSTAND ALL THAT,
BUT CAN'T THAT BE A COP-OUT?
THINGS GET ROUGH IN LIFE,
COMPETITION.
YOU ALWAYS THINK YOU HAVE
TO MAKE IT, SO YOU--
VINCE.
--TURNED YOUR BACK
ON IT ALL.
VINCE. YOU DO YOUR THING,
I'LL DO MY THING.
AMEN.
I'M TURNING IN, YOU GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, SAMMY.
THANK YOU.
GOOD NIGHT.
SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
SLEEP WELL.
[ SIGHS ]
THAT'S IT FOR ME, TOO.
I'M TIRED.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT, VINCE.
SLEEP WELL, MAN.
OKAY. YOU, TOO. TAKE CARE.
VINCE, HONEY,
TIME TO GO TO BED.
YEAH, BE THERE IN A MINUTE.
[ MOANING ]
JESUS, YOU SCARED
THE LIVING SHIT OUT OF ME.
I KNOW THAT SHE
LIKES TO BE ALONE AT NIGHT.
SHE WANTS TO BE ALONE,
REALLY ALONE.
I WAS JUST PASSING BY.
SIMPLY BE SURE
YOU DON'T DO IT AGAIN.
GOOD NIGHT, VINCE.
[ SCREAM ]
[ YELLS IN KOREAN ]
I'M SORRY.
LISA, I'M SORRY, PLEASE.
PLEASE DON'T, LISA. DON'T.
PLEASE, FORGIVE ME, LISA.
[ YELLS IN KOREAN ]
LISA, PLEASE
FORGIVE ME, PLEASE.
WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT'D SHE SAY?
I DON'T KNOW, SAMMY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND KOREAN.
JOHN, WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
SAMMY, IT'S REAL PRIVATE.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY.
SHOW'S OVER.
BACK TO YOUR TENTS.
GOT A LOT OF WORK TO DO
IN THE MORNING.
GOOD NIGHT.
WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I LOVED HIM SO MUCH.
I KNOW.
WE WERE JUST MARRIED,
AND NOW I FIND OUT.
WHY DIDN'T HE TELL ME
BEFORE WE GOT MARRIED? WHY?
[ SIGHS ]
I UNDERSTAND, HONEY.
I REALLY DO, LISA.
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST
ONE OF THOSE THINGS
THAT SOME OF US HAVE
TO GO THROUGH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
SOMETIMES YOU COME OUT ON
THE OTHER SIDE A BETTER PERSON,
SOMETIMES.
I HATE HIM.
NO, YOU DON'T.
YOU'RE JUST HURT, DEEPLY HURT.
COME HERE.
SAMMY, I NEVER LOVED ANYBODY
SO MUCH IN MY LIFE.
UH-HUH.
I'D DIE FOR HER.
SAMMY, IT WAS MY
BACHELOR PARTY.
THERE WERE A COUPLE HOOKERS,
AND I GOT DRUNK, LOTS OF BOOZE,
AND I HAD SEX
WITH BOTH OF THEM.
OH!
[ LAUGHS ]
MY BUDDIES, THEY SET
THE WHOLE THING UP.
YOU KNOW, I FIGURED
I'D GET HER OUT HERE,
AND I COULD TELL HER,
AND SHE'D UNDERSTAND.
OH, GOD, YOU SAW WHAT HAPPENED.
YEAH, WELL,
YOU'RE NOT THE FIRST GUY
TO GO OFF ON A FLING,
YOU KNOW.
MAYBE SHE'LL FORGIVE YOU.
NO, SAMMY, I KNOW.
IT'S A KOREAN THING.
THEY HAVE A VERY STRICT
WAY OF LIVING.
THEY'RE VERY PRIVATE.
HMM.
BUT SAMMY, I VIOLATED
SOMETHING THAT WAS SO SACRED.
HMM.
I FIGURED WITH MARRIAGE,
I WOULD HAVE TO LEAVE
MY FRIENDS BEHIND.
I TRIED TO HANG ONTO THEM.
BOYS, IT'S NICE WHAT'S GOING
ON OUT THERE FOR FRIENDS
THESE DAYS.
I TELL YOU,
I HAVE ONE HELL OF AN AMENDS
AHEAD OF ME.
WELL, JOHN.
WE MAKE OUR TOMORROWS.
LET'S GET AN EARLY START.
OKAY?
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT, SAMMY.
SAMMY, THANKS A LOT.
I APPRECIATE IT.
DON'T WORRY. BE HAPPY.
HI.
SO ARE WE SURVIVING?
WELL, EXISTING
WITH HOPES ANYWAY.
YEAH.
COME ON.
LET'S TAKE A HIKE.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
I'LL LIVE MY LIFE OUT HERE
IN THE WOODS WITH YOU.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT'S QUIET.
FOR YOU, I DON'T SEE IT
FULL-TIME.
I DON'T KNOW, SAMMY.
EVERY TIME I SEE HER
TWISTED BODY,
IT JUST TAKES ME RIGHT BACK.
DARLING, YOU GOT TO GO ON.
IT WASN'T INTENTIONAL.
YOU GOT TO GO ON.
I KNOW. I TRIED.
I REALLY DO TRY.
BUT FREDDY, OUT OF ALL PEOPLE,
HE RECOGNIZED ME.
HE WAS THERE AT THAT MATCH,
AT THAT MATCH.
YOU KNOW,
WHEN HE MENTIONED IT TODAY,
I JUST FELT
MARILYN'S WHOLE LIFE
GO RIGHT THROUGH MY BODY.
SHE'S PARALYZED FOREVER,
AND I DID THAT,
MY VERY BEST FRIEND.
SHE EXPECTS YOU TO WIN
FOR THE BOTH OF YOU.
SHE WANTS THAT, HAS NO REGRETS.
WHY SHOULD YOU?
SIMPLE.
BECAUSE I'M HERE,
AND SHE'S LAYING THERE.
LOOK, CHAMPIONS USE
WHAT THEY KNOW TO WIN.
THEY GET BEYOND IT,
AND THEY GO ON WITH THEIR LIFE.
IF YOU KEEP HANGING ON
TO HER PARALYZED
STATE OF MIND,
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN TO YOU,
PARALYZED, WITHOUT A FIGHT
EXCEPT WITH YOURSELF,
WITH YOUR OWN MIND.
IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
YOU'RE THE CHAMPION.
WHAT'S IT GOING TO BE?
LIFE IN THE BIG CITY,
EXPENSIVE, EXCITING,
MORTGAGES, IRS,
DRUGS, PSYCHIATRY.
[ MUTTERING ]
OH-NO.
IT'S THE SAME
IN ANY LANGUAGE.
WHERE'S THAT TAPE?
SIMMER DOWN.
DON'T HURT ME.
IT'S UP IN MY TENT.
JUST GO GET IT.
DON'T THINK ABOUT WAKING
THE OLD LADY, MAN.
DON'T EVEN DO IT, OKAY?
I WON'T, I WON'T.
I PROMISE.
SHH.
ARE YOU GOING TO KILL ME?
I'D LIKE TO.
BOAR.
SHUT UP!
YOU TELL ANYONE ABOUT THIS?
NO, NO! I WON'T.
I HAVEN'T SAID ANYTHING.
I MEAN IT. I WON'T!
SHUT UP, YOU BIRDBRAIN!
NOW LISTEN TO ME,
YOU MAKE A PEEP,
YOU TELL ANYONE ABOUT THIS,
AND I'LL KILL YOU.
I'LL KILL YOUR WIFE,
I'LL KILL YOUR CAT,
I'LL KILL YOUR DOG.
I'LL KILL ALL OF YOU.
YOU SAVVY?
YOU DON'T EVER WANT
TO SEE ME AGAIN.
YOU'LL REGRET IT.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
GO ON BACK NOW.
GO ON. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
[ SHOUTS ]
JESUS, YOU NUTS?
DO YOU WANT
TO WAKE UP EVERYBODY UP?
YOU'RE CRAZY TO THE LIMIT,
YOU KNOW THAT?
TAKE YOUR HANDS OFF ME
OR I'LL BREAK 'EM OFF.
LET'S GO.
SO YOU DECIDED
TO SLEEP OUT UNDER THE STARS
AFTER ALL, VERY IMPRESSIVE.
YEAH, YEAH.
YOU TALKED ME INTO IT.
YEAH, BUT YOU SHOULD'VE
LET ME HELP YOU MAKE YOUR BED.
THOSE ARE THE WRONG
KIND OF LEAVES.
NO, NO, REALLY, IT'S OKAY.
THESE WERE FINE.
I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU'VE BEEN LAYING
IN POISON OAK.
SHIT!
[ LAUGHS ]
THAT'S JUST WHAT I NEED.
JUST KIDDING, RELAX.
COME ON.
GET SOME COFFEE IN YOU.
GET SOME OF THAT GOOD OUTDOOR
AIR IN YOUR LUNGS.
YOU'LL LIVE LONGER.
YEAH, LIVE LONGER,
YEAH, THAT'S THE PLAN.
SO HOW DID YOU
SLEEP LAST NIGHT?
WITH MY HEAD UP MY ASS.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
I WAS HOPING FOR
SOME CHANGES IN THIS TRIP.
MORNING, JOHN.
MORNING, SAMMY.
HI.
WHY DON'T YOU CRACK IT OPEN?
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. CRACK THE EGG OPEN.
WHY DON'T YOU TAPE US
TAKING THE TENT DOWN?
ARE YOU TIRED OF
THAT CAMERA ALREADY?
NO, NO,
I JUST DON'T FEEL LIKE IT.
WELL, LET'S MAKE SURE
WE HAVE EVERYTHING, OKAY,
THAT WE PACKED EVERYTHING.
YES, DEAR.
OH, HEY,
WHY DON'T YOU GET US,
FILM US, TAPE US, COMING DOWN
WITH OUR PONCHOS ON?
YES, DEAR, YES, DEAR.
I THINK THAT'D BE GREAT.
OKAY, GUYS.
LET'S LEAVE THIS CAMPSITE JUST
THE WAY WE FOUND IT,
IF NOT BETTER. OKAY?
YES.
GOD DAMN LITTLE
SON OF A BITCH.
I'LL KILL HIM.
HE GAVE US SHIT, MAN.
IT AIN'T HERE.
WELL, WAIT, DID YOU PLAY
IT ALL THE WAY THROUGH, HUH?
WHAT DO I LOOK LIKE?
YOU THINK I'M STUPID OR WHAT?
I'M TELLING YOU, IT AIN'T THERE.
OH, NO, NO.
THAT LITTLE ASSHOLE.
[ YELLS ]
WHAT COULD HE BE THINKING?
HE THINKS HE'S GOING
TO GET AWAY WITH THIS.
LET'S GO.
WAIT, WHAT ABOUT THE OTHERS?
WHAT ABOUT THEM?
THEY'RE THERE.
THAT'S WHAT ABOUT THEM.
I AIN'T NEVER GOING
BACK TO THE JOINT.
GET THAT?
GET THAT THROUGH
YOUR THICK HEAD. NO WAY!
AND LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
YOU WOULDN'T LIKE IT THERE,
JACKIE BOY.
YOU WOULDN'T LAST
FIVE MINUTES AFTER LOCKDOWN
BEFORE SOME 290-POUND GREASY,
BALD-HEADED SON OF A BITCH
WANTS TO PUT HIS DICK
IN SOME VERY STRANGE PLACES
BELONGING TO YOU.
LET'S GO.
290 POUND, JESUS.
AH, SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO, BOAR?
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO KILL THEM ALL, ARE YOU, HUH?
GEEZ. OKAY.
LET'S GET BACK TO CAMP
BEFORE THEY BREAK.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO, HUH?
YOU GOING
TO TAKE THEM ALL ON, HUH?
GODDAMN IT!
AW, SHIT!
COME ON!
WE CAN CATCH THEM.
LET'S GO.
SAMMY, I UNDERSTAND
THAT MOUNTAIN STORMS
CAN COME UP QUICKLY
IN THESE PARTS.
IS THAT RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT CAN HAPPEN.
DID YOU HAVE A GOOD SLEEP?
NO, NOT REALLY.
YOU SEEM SO QUIET TODAY.
IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
OH, DON'T KNOCK IT.
TAKE GOOD WHERE IT COMES.
COME ON, JOHN.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
BRING IT UP, BRING IT UP.
YOU'RE OKAY.
GRAB THE ROPE.
GET HIM.
JOHN, YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
[ LAUGHS ]
I GOT YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
AH, JUST LEAVE HIM HERE.
HE AIN'T GOING ANYWHERE.
GUYS, ONE STEP AT A TIME.
PUT YOUR FOOT DOWN,
YOUR HAND ON THE ROCK
AND STEP ON DOWN.
YEAH.
OKAY. LET'S HELP EACH OTHER.
HERE WE GO.
COME ON, BETINA.
YOU CAN DO IT.
GREAT. YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
OKAY. YOU GOT HER?
THERE YOU GO.
JUST WALK RIGHT ALONG THAT EDGE.
BE VERY CAREFUL, VERY SLOW.
JUST BE CAREFUL ON THAT ROCK.
OKAY. HERE WE GO.
OKAY, LISA.
I KNOW YOU CAN HANDLE THIS.
FOLLOW BETINA.
BE VERY CAREFUL.
STAY CLOSE TO THE SIDE.
OKAY?
HERE WE GO.
THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, VINCE.
THANKS, JOHN.
THANKS FOR HELPING.
I'M OKAY.
YOU OKAY, VINCE?
YEAH.
SLIDE ON YOUR BUTT THERE.
GOOD JOB.
GOT IT?
YEAH.
GOOD.
[ CHATTERING ]
SEE THE CLOUDS MOVING?
OH, YEAH.
WE'RE IN A CLOUD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
SHUT YOUR FACE
IF YOU WANT TO KEEP IT
LOOKING THE WAY IT DOES.
JUST ONE MORE CHARGE
AT THIS ASSHOLE.
YOU'RE THE GUY FROM
THE MOTEL, AREN'T YOU?
WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH THE GUN?
[ SHOUTING ]
[ GUNSHOTS ]
NO, LISA!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SHOUTING ]
YOU LIKE DOING THIS, DO YOU?
LISA!
WELL, LOOK AT THERE.
WE GOT US A CLIFFHANGER.
GET BACK NOW, DAMN IT!
I TOLD YOU TO GET BACK!
OH GOD!
BRING THE LITTLE SHIT
OVER HERE.
VINCE, WHO ARE THESE GUYS?
THAT'S RIGHT.
VINCE AIN'T SMART AT ALL.
IF THEY KNOW THAT,
IT CREATES A PROBLEM,
A VERY BIG PROBLEM.
NOW WHERE IS THE TAPE?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TAPE
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT,
BUT JUST GIVE IT
TO THEM, VINCE.
I DON'T HAVE IT. IT'S--
WHERE?
ONCE THEY KNOW WHERE IT IS,
THEN IT'LL BE ALL OVER WITH.
IT WON'T MATTER ANYMORE.
YOU'RE THAT KUNG FU BITCH,
AREN'T YOU?
TOUGH GAL, HUH?
I LIKE THEM TOUGH.
LET ME JUST GO DOWN
AND GET THE GIRL
AND JUST PUT THAT GUN AWAY
BEFORE SOMEBODY GETS HURT.
OH, NOW THERE'S
A FUCKING GOOD IDEA!
I TOLD YOU TO GET AWAY
FROM THERE!
GET THE FUCK OVER THERE!
JACK, JACK, TAKE HIM BACK
TO WHERE HE HAS THE TAPE.
I'LL STAY HERE.
LISTEN.
I'LL KEEP THEM COMPANY.
LET'S BOTH GO BACK,
GET THE TAPE BACK.
THEN WE SPLIT.
WHAT ABOUT THEM?
THEY KNOW.
NO, THEY DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL GO, BUT YOU BOTH
HAVE TO GO WITH ME
OR ELSE YOU'LL GET NOTHING.
GREAT.
BIRDBRAIN HAS AN IDEA.
ALL RIGHT, BIRD.
DON'T BULLSHIT ME THIS TIME.
AH!
THERE'S PLENTY MORE
WHERE THAT CAME FROM!
I'LL GO WITH YOU
IF YOU WANT ME TO.
THIS AIN'T NO CIRCUS, LADY.
STAY PUT!
WHERE'S SAMMY?
HE'S BACK THERE
HE'S GOT A HEADACHE.
DO NOT FOLLOW
OR I WILL KILL HIM.
BELIEVE THAT.
COME ON.
OH, MY GOD.
LISA, HONEY, YOU'RE GONNA
BE FINE.
JUST FINE. STAY STILL!
I'LL GET THE LIFELINE.
HURRY!
JESUS CHRIST!
NO, THIS ONE'S MINE.
GIVE IT TO ME.
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S MINE, IT'S MINE.
FREDDY, COME HERE NOW!
BETINA!
PUT IT AROUND YOU.
GET IT AROUND YOU GUYS.
OH, MY GOD, LISA!
JUST STAY CALM.
STAY WITH ME RIGHT THERE.
STAY WITH ME. I'M COMING.
TIE IT AROUND YOU, FREDDY.
I GOT IT.
RIGHT WITH ME, BABE.
OKAY, LISA.
HE'S COMING DOWN.
OKAY. RIGHT WITH ME, HONEY.
HE'S GOT YOU.
OKAY, JOHN.
JUST TELL US WHEN.
OKAY. OKAY. I GOT YOU.
OKAY. GO, GO, PULL.
BRING HER UP, BRING HER UP.
COME ON. BRING HER UP.
OH! WE GOT YOU NOW.
BRING IT! GET IT!
COME ON, BIG JOHN!
COME ON, LISA!
OKAY, OKAY. LET GO.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT VINCE?
BETINA, IF WE DON'T GET
TO HIM IN TIME,
THEN THEY'LL KILL HIM.
JUST STAY CALM, BETINA,
AND STAY WITH ME.
[ CRIES ]
SORRY! I'M SORRY!
LISTEN, MARIA.
MARIA, LISTEN TO ME!
WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
NOW, DARN IT, LISTEN TO ME,
ALL OF YOU!
LOOK, JUST STAY CALM
AND STAY WITH ME.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
LOOK, COME WITH ME
AND KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN
FOR SAMMY.
NOW!
OH, MY GOD! SAMMY!
SAMMY!
IS HE OKAY?
OH, MY GOD.
HE'S OKAY, HE'S OKAY.
HE'LL LIVE.
OR LITTLE SHIT OR ANYTHING.
HEY, CALL YOURSELF BIG BIRD
IF YOU LIKE.
MAKES NO DIFFERENCE TO ME.
BULLY. YOU BULLY PEOPLE.
YOU PUSH PEOPLE AROUND.
YOU DESTROY THEM.
FIND THAT TAPE.
MY PATIENCE'S IS PAPER THIN,
BIG GUY, YOU BIG PAIN
IN THE ASS.
WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU
SMILING ABOUT?
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE THIS CLOSE
TO BEING A SMALL PART
OF HISTORY?
GO AHEAD.
WHAT ARE YOU
SMILING ABOUT NOW?
I'D LIKE TO OFF YOU
RIGHT NOW.
IN FRONT OF
THOSE RANGERS OVER THERE?
[ LAUGHTER ]
THIS ASSHOLE
IS SOMETHING ELSE.
HE'S ABOUT TO GET CREAMED,
AND HE'S LAUGHING ABOUT IT.
I THINK YOU'RE LOSING IT,
LITTLE SHIT.
NO, NO,
IT'S YOU WHO'S LOSING.
IT'S YOU WHO'S ALREADY LOST IT.
YOU HAVE LOST EVERYTHING
THAT LIVES.
THAT'S LIFE.
YOU'RE A NUT, YOU'RE A ZERO,
YOU'RE A BIG NOTHING ZERO.
BOAR, DON'T!
SEE, WE'RE RIGHT OUT
IN THE OPEN.
SOMEBODY MIGHT SEE US.
SMILE.
LOOK RIGHT HERE AND SMILE.
FORGET YOUR TAPE,
YOU DUMB FUCKHEAD.
HE'S RIGHT, BOAR.
COME HERE.
YOU JUST STAY WITH ME.
WE'RE GOING TO BE REAL CLOSE.
GET OFF IT!
COME HERE.
YOU JUST STAY RIGHT HERE.
[ PANTS ]
ARE THEY GOING TO THE VAN?
I THINK SO.
VINCE SAID HE HAD THIS TAPE
THAT THEY WANTED,
AND HE WAS TAKING THEM THERE.
COME ON.
I KNOW A SHORTCUT.
[ PANTS ]
[ COUGHS ]
WHERE THE FUCK
DID YOU PUT IT?
THINK YOU WON YOUR LITTLE
WORD GAME THERE, DON'T YOU?
YOU AIN'T GOING TO LIKE
WHAT'S COMING NEXT.
[ PANTS ]
DAMN IT!
WHERE THE HELL DID YOU PUT IT?
DON'T DO THIS TO ME!
OKAY, BIG SHIT.
YOU WANT ANOTHER ROUND.
NEW GAME, WHICH HAND DO YOU WANT
TO LOSE FIRST, HUH, THIS ONE?
HUH? NO GOOD?
HOW ABOUT THIS ONE, HUH?
OKAY. DECIDE WHICH HAND.
TOO LATE. THIS ONE!
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ SCREAMING ]
NO, I'M NOT GOING
TO LET THIS HAPPEN!
JESUS.
[ SHOUTS ]
VINCENT, DON'T DIE ON ME!
DON'T LET HIM DIE ON ME!
ENOUGH REST, BIG SHIT.
GET UP THERE!
WHERE IS THE TAPE, HUH?
WHERE'S THE TAPE?
OKAY. WHICH WAY, HUH?
THIS WAY?
YOU LIKE THIS ONE BETTER?
OR THE OTHER SIDE.
--THE TAPE.
I CAN WALK!
NO, YOU CAN'T.
LET ME GO!
[ PANTS ]
THE TAPE OR JACK,
JUST GET US--
[ SHOUTING ]
[ YELLS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
NO!
HEY!
GET UP, FREDDIE!
NO!
[ CRACKING ]
BETINA!
UNDER HERE, UNDER THE VAN!
[ SCREAMS ]
SAMMY, GET HIS LEGS.
GIVE ME A BIT OF ROPE.
NO!
[ SHOUTS ]
BITCH!
COME HERE!
NO! NO!
YOU'RE BLEEDING!
[ CRIES ]
[ CRYING ]
OH, SAMMY.
YOU DO SHARP
BETTER THAN ANYBODY I KNOW.
YOU'RE REALLY SHARP.
GOD, VINCE, WHY DID YOU
WANT TO KEEP
THAT HORRIBLE TAPE?
THOUGHT I'D SELL IT TO CNN.
ON ONE OF THOSE REALITY SHOWS.
I WANTED TO DO SOMETHING
FOR MYSELF.
I WANTED TO MAKE
MY OWN MONEY FOR A CHANGE.
YOU CAN TAKE CONTROL
OF THE MONEY.
I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU WANT.
I'LL EVEN GO ON A DIET.
NO, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO THAT.
I LOVE YOU JUST THE WAY YOU ARE.
[ CRIES ]
WELL, BOYS,
THE FIGHT IS OVER.
DON'T TRY ANYTHING.
HERE, FREDDIE.
HOLD ONTO THE TAPE.
ALL RIGHT.
BE CAREFUL.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AH, TIPPER?
YEAH?
OH!
ARE YOU OKAY?
AH, TIPPER, COULD YOU
TAPE THIS FOR ME?
AH!
LOOK, VINCE, DON'T PUSH
YOUR LUCK NOW, BUDDY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SHE'S QUICK, SHE'S TOUGH,
SHE'S BACK.
MAGNIFICENT MIMI LESSEOS
IS BACK.
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT STRANGE UNKNOWN ANIMALS
MAY BE LURKING
BEHIND THOSE TREES.
SHE'S TAKING
A GROUP OF TOURISTS--
FIRST CAMPING TRIP, HUH?
--ON A TOUR--
ALL SET TO ROLL?
--THROUGH THE WILDERNESS.
GOOD, THAT'S GREAT!
ONLY THIS TIME,
THE GREAT OUTDOORS--
SHE IS DEAD!
--IS ABOUT TO CLOSE IN.
WE GOT TO GET THAT CAMERA.
WE GOT TO GET THE TAPE.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
AND AS THE WOODS GET DEEPER--
SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT HERE.
--THE DANGER GETS DEADLIER.
WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH THE GUN?
YOU TELL ANYONE ABOUT THIS,
AND I'LL KILL YOU.
NOW, A CHAMPION WHO NEVER
LOST FACES AN ENEMY
WHO'S NOT PLAYING GAMES.
TOUGH GAL, HUH?
I LIKE TOUGH.
CHAMPIONS USE
WHAT THEY KNOW TO WIN.
THE RULES ARE SIMPLE:
YOU WIN, YOU LIVE.
YOU LOSE, YOU DIE.
RIGHT HERE AND SMILE.
[ GUNSHOT ]
AH!
IF WE DON'T
GET TO HIM ON TIME,
THEY'RE GOING TO KILL THEM.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR MERCY,
LOOK SOMEWHERE ELSE.
YOU AIN'T GOING
TO LIKE WHAT'S COMING NEXT.
I'M GOING TO KICK HIS BUTT.
BECAUSE MIMI BELIEVES
IN WOMEN'S RIGHTS, LEFTS,
AND UPPERCUTS.
MAGNIFICENT MIMI LESSEOS
IS BEYOND FEAR.