[police radio chatter]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- All inmate visitation hours
will be ending soon.
♪ ♪
[buzzer blares]
- What's up, son?
You finally found some time
to come see your old man?
- No, Dad.
I'm only here because Mom
wouldn't stop bugging me
to come see you.
- Yeah, your mom was telling me
Andy's getting big.
He's running around.
You know, the last time
she was here,
she was showing me
some pictures of the--
you know, like, the different
things you guys were doing--
- Well, sounds like
you're all caught up, then.
Right?
- Ah, come on.
I really don't want this time
to be like this.
- Family.
Let me tell you something, Dad.
I dropped out of school
to take care of my family
'cause you were too busy
in the streets.
Our family?
- I don't wanna fight with you
or hurt you guys.
I've changed, Juanito.
Watch when I get out.
- Changed for what?
For us?
We're grown, Dad.
There's no need to change
for us anymore.
Sometimes, people,
they make bad choices
because of the situations
they put themselves in.
- Yeah, I know.
I know.
And we all know what you chose.
♪ ♪
- You're a good man.
You've grown into a good man,
and I'm proud of you.
- Proud of me.
You don't even know me.
♪ ♪
- Here's what I know.
You're nothing like me.
And I'm proud of that.
[line beeps]
♪ ♪
[upbeat Spanish music]
- Hurry up with those orders.
- All right, all right.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What is this On Demand?
- What do you mean, on demand?
- "What do you mean, on--"
all of a sudden,
you don't know?
- Mom.
- What is this movie
right here?
- It was one movie,
and it was for $3.99.
[child cries]
That's not even nothing.
- Then how come there's five
of them in here, huh?
Baby, explain to me
why your mom thinks
that she can put movies
on demand when we have Netflix.
- Hey, little--
- She doesn't pay her bills!
- Hey!
- We end up paying!
- Hey, little girl,
what you mean "explain to Mom?"
What, you think I don't know
how to use the TV
and pay the bills?
- Mom!
- Obviously, you don't.
Come on, baby, what's up?
Baby, that's it?
Oh, my God.
You got him crying.
- Look, instead of crying
about it,
go wash that pot so I can cook.
- I told you it's soaking!
- Well, then, do the other one,
'cause if not,
it's not gonna be--
- I'm over here
trying to figure out the bills!
- All right, so go
do your bills and stop talking.
- Then how come
you're not telling me about it?
What other bills we got
that I don't know about, huh?
- I don't know.
Go look at 'em.
- We got this.
We got this phone bill?
Huh?
- Hey.
Did Juanito pay
the cell phone bill?
They don't say he did.
- How is Vero--
how is he
supposed to pay the bills
when he's been working all day?
- What did you say I said?
- I said how is your brother
supposed to be paying bills
when he's working all day?
- Don't worry about it.
I'll pay it tomorrow.
And why you gotta open
your big mouth like always?
- Yeah.
I'll pay it tomorrow.
- Vez, this is your problem.
You're always fixing her shit.
That's your problem.
- Fuck you!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Come here, baby.
No, fuck you!
Why don't you contribute
around here?
The baby's freaking crying.
- Hey, hey.
- What, baby?
- What's this?
- What?
- What is this shit?
- Oh, you don't have to worry
about that.
- What do you mean
it's nothing to worry about?
We're getting kicked out.
- Are you kidding me?
- I know, but if we just pay
what's due, we'll be okay.
- How the fuck are we past due
on our rent?
Is there something
you're not telling me?
- [cries]
Mama.
I've been helping your
grandmother with her bills.
She's gonna pay us back.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Plus they can't kick us out.
- Yeah, Mom,
but why didn't you tell me?
- Because I didn't want you
to worry.
- So you used our money.
What the fuck, Ma?
I could've come up with some
extra money or something.
- I didn't want you to worry,
okay?
I'm gonna take care of it.
Don't worry about it.
We have, like, 30 days,
maybe even more.
- I've completely forgotten.
Like we have
that fucking luxury, right?
- Baby.
- This is bullshit.
- I didn't know anything, baby.
- Fuck!
- Okay?
Your mom kept this shit
from me, all right?
- What?
- Bullshit!
- Juan.
- I didn't know, okay?
I didn't have any fucking--
- You didn't know
about grandmother?
You didn't know
that I was helping?
- No, I did not know
she was...
♪ ♪
[phone buzzes]
[phone chimes]
♪ ♪
[lock clicks]
- Wow.
I don't want no trouble.
- Moy?
- Hell, yeah, high speed.
- Oh, shit.
'Sup, man?
It's been a minute.
- What's going on, man?
- What's up, man?
Shit.
Damn, Juanito.
Got you doing bitch work
up in here, man.
- Yeah, right, homey.
It's not even like that, dawg.
- [scoffs]
Man, you could've fooled me.
Let's go get a drink, my boy.
- [sighs]
All right.
- Come on, man.
Hop in.
[rap music playing]
- So,
when'd they let you out?
- I didn't think
they were ever gonna.
I don't know.
Two, three weeks ago.
A month.
Long enough to get back
into business stuff.
Ain't no stopping me.
[sighs]
I see you ain't doing shit.
- [laughs]
Yeah, I'm just trying
to get by, man.
Make ends meet, you feel me?
- Man, you ain't gonna
make nothing meet
doing what you doing
over there, man.
- Yeah, well, I got a family
to take care of now.
- Word is you knocked up
Adriana.
Snagged that bitch
right up, man.
Or was it the other way around?
- All right, look, man,
you need to chill the hell out
with that shit.
You fucking play too much, man.
- [chuckles]
Good for you.
Got your little family,
your little job.
It's good to see you
doing good, though, man.
- Yeah.
[sirens wailing faintly]
♪ ♪
Thanks.
All right, man.
Well, good luck, homey.
I appreciate the ride.
- Good talk, man.
Hey.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Motherfucker, I can help you
get some real paper.
Man, fuck this place, man.
♪ ♪
- I ain't even trying
to play that game, homey.
- Ain't no fucking games
I'm playing.
The fuck do you think this is?
I'm trying to get you paid.
[chuckles]
What happened
to my down-ass homey?
♪ ♪
Offer don't last long, bro.
You know where to find me.
♪ ♪
[phone buzzing]
- [sighs]
- Shit.
Fuck.
[Spanish music playing]
♪ ♪
We opened two hours late
because of you.
- Come on, it was an accident.
I--
- I got a family
to take care of.
Two businesses to run.
I wanna sleep in.
But I gotta be here.
Go home, Juan.
- Raul.
- Go home.
- ♪ It's a game ♪
♪ Game that we play ♪
♪ This is just a game ♪
♪ Play ♪
♪ I'm never gonna
trust nobody ♪
- ♪ Nobody ♪
- ♪ Just my Nina
and her older brother Shawty ♪
♪ And that's the way we roll ♪
- ♪ Roll, roll, roll ♪
[knocking]
- ♪ And that's the way
we roll ♪
- ♪ Roll roll roll ♪
- ♪ People like to judge
the book by its cover ♪
♪ But you don't know me
and my brothers ♪
♪ We rep for the West,
never settle for less ♪
- Who the fuck is it?
- It's me, Moy.
Juanito.
[rap music]
♪ ♪
- Look who the fuck it is.
You almost got shot
coming around here, man.
- Man, get that shit
out of my face, bitch.
♪ ♪
- Ah, man,
we ain't friends anymore?
Come on, man.
I'm just joking, man.
Come in, nigga.
Close that door.
- ♪ Who the hell got a flow
like this ♪
♪ With the beats that hit
and my squad too sick? ♪
♪ Hundred on my dash
when I smash in the whip ♪
♪ Nothing but the gas
when I rep my shit ♪
- Come on.
- ♪ They hate to see
a Mexican victory ♪
♪ Everyone feeling me,
please stop the misery ♪
♪ The industry judging
my color of skin ♪
♪ Ski mask off,
a mistaken identity ♪
- So what's up?
- You need to hold the fuck up
and let me tell you.
♪ ♪
You, my friend,
are gonna be doing drop-offs
and pick-ups.
The first drop you're going to
is with Flaco and Chino.
You remember those fools?
They're down as fuck.
Help me set up shop.
We're plugging
some big players.
You're lucky I like you, bro.
Letting you in
on this operation.
I'ma text you the address
where to find these fools.
From there, they got you.
Know what I mean?
- Yeah, I got you.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[mariachi music]
- Adriana.
What's up?
It's Moy.
- Oh, shit.
Hi!
Hey.
- What's up?
How you doing?
- I'm good.
Good.
Good to see you.
- Yeah.
- How you been?
- All right, but damn.
You look bad as fuck.
No disrespect.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Last time I saw you, you were--
- [laughs]
A lot younger.
Yeah, I got a kid now
and all the stress
that comes with it.
- I hear that,
but he's a lucky guy--
the father, I mean.
- It's Juanito, my lucky guy.
J?
- No.
- J.
- [laughs softly]
Juanito.
Fuck, I didn't know that.
- [laughs]
- Homey always had a way
with the ladies, I guess.
All right, well,
it was good seeing you.
Tell my boy to come find me.
All right,
let him know I miss him.
- Okay, I will.
♪ ♪
- Hey, you need a ride?
- Nah, it's okay.
- You sure?
I don't mind.
- No, no, no, they're probably
just running late.
- Well, it kind of looks like
they forgot about you.
Come on.
I didn't park too far.
We get home.
Hopefully J's there.
We all catch up,
like old times.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
- ♪ Yeah, I bang, I roll ♪
♪ I'm really tryna get it ♪
♪ Bitch, I bang, I roll ♪
♪ This is how I'm livin' ♪
- We're here.
- Where we at?
- For real, Moy?
I gotta get home.
Take me home.
- Now, don't be like that.
Let's just kick it
for a little bit.
- Kick it?
Fuck no.
Take me home.
- You too good
to kick it with me now?
You weren't too good
for my ride.
- Oh, fuck no.
That's what this is?
No, no.
I'm fucking out of here.
Thanks for the ride.
- Where the fuck
do you think you're going?
- Get the fuck off of me.
[grunts]
[yelps]
[intense music]
[rap music playing]
♪ ♪
- What's up, dawg?
Been a long time.
You ready or what?
Moy said we got old J back.
Crazy old Juanito.
- Yeah, let's just make
some shit happen, man.
- We gonna make
some shit happen out here,
then we're gonna head out
to Boyle Heights, a'ight?
- Hey, when we get there,
don't say shit.
Just let us introduce you.
- Yeah, all right.
- So what's up, Juanito?
It's been a long time
since you've been around.
Too scared to kick it
with the homies or what?
- Nah, it's not even
like that, dawg.
- [laughs]
All of a sudden.
Thought you forgot
about the homies.
- Hey, bro, shut the fuck up.
We're almost there.
- Hey, you trippin'.
Hey, bro, don't listen
to this dumb fuck.
♪ ♪
- So what's up?
This the spot or what?
- Yeah, we usually post up here
and wait for these fools
to arrive.
- Good.
Let me get off and take a piss.
- [clears throat]
- Hey, look, man,
I don't think I can go
to Boyle Heights anymore.
- You ain't going nowhere, bro.
- [urinating]
[dramatic music]
- This shit don't work
that way.
- What the fuck, Chino?
- Shut the fuck up!
Oh, fuck.
Fuck you!
[both grunting]
Motherfucker!
[all grunting]
♪ ♪
The fuck?
Fuck him.
- What the fuck, man?
What the fuck?
Why the fuck was J
beating your ass?
- Fuck you, and fuck him too.
I'm gonna smoke this nigga.
- Nah.
He look dead to me.
- I don't give a fuck.
- Leave him the fuck alone.
Nah.
Not even worth it.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
It's not even
the right neighborhood.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
- [grunts]
[rap music plays]
♪ ♪
- Fuck, bro, we need
some fucking bud, dawg.
Money.
- Fucking homey,
let's go get it lit.
You know what I mean?
Rob a bank.
- You're not down.
- Fuck no.
What, for you to get caught,
Juanito?
If we want all that...
- Fool, it ain't a bank,
but it'll get us some...
[dramatic music]
[lighter clicks]
♪ ♪
Hey, Moy, you ready?
- Fuck it, homey.
It is what it is.
- Let's get this shit
over with.
♪ ♪
[ATM beeping]
- All right, dawg.
All you gotta do
is empty out the fucking cash
and give it to the homey,
understand?
- Hurry the fuck up, fucker.
I ain't got all day.
- Okay, okay.
- Hurry that shit up.
- Nah, nah, nah, you good.
- Hurry the fuck up.
- It's processing.
[panicked breathing]
All right,
here, here, here, here.
- I ain't with that shit.
Hurry up.
How much you got, Moy?
- Hold up, homey.
- Moy.
- Two bills.
- Two bills?
Are you fucking kidding me?
- It's all
it'll let me take out.
- Nah, fuck that, nah.
You fucking kidding me?
200 fucking dollars?
Are you fucking kidding me?
- I swear, please.
Please just don't hurt me.
- That's fucking bullshit.
Moy, grab the keys,
grab the wallet.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
- Hey, what are you doing?
I'ma call the cops.
- Fuck that shit.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
♪ ♪
Fuck.
[breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
[grunting]
[groans]
[door thunks]
Fuck.
- Juanito, what happened?
- Oh, my God.
- My God, Juanito!
- Oh, my God, what the fuck?
- Mom!
- Where's Adriana?
- What happened?
What happened to your head?
- Where's Andi?
- Oh, my God, go get a towel.
Go get a towel for his head.
- Where's Andi?
- Juan, what the--
♪ ♪
Juan, what happened?
Where's Adriana?
- Wait, what?
- Where's Adriana?
- You don't know
where she's at?
- No!
- Fuck.
- Oh, my God,
what happened to your head?
What's going on?
Juan!
- Fuck!
- Hold on.
- Where you going?
Juan!
Juan, open the fucking door!
Juan, what happened?
- Mom!
- Fuck.
- You gotta tell me
what happened, mijo.
- [grunting]
Where's Adriana?
What happened?
- Fuck.
[intense music building]
- Open the door.
- Fuck.
♪ ♪
[rap music playing]
[hard knocking]
♪ ♪
- Yo, bro.
You fucking hear that shit
or what?
- What?
The fucking knocking, bro.
Who the fuck is knocking
on your fucking door right now?
[hard knocking]
[mutters]
Fucking Moy.
Stupid fucking Moy.
♪ ♪
Yo, who the fuck is it?
- You're hearing things,
stupid.
Ain't nobody out there.
[gunshot]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[gunshot]
- Piece of shit.
You set me up!
- [laughs]
Damn!
That's the Juanito I remember--
fucking ruthless,
not this chicken shit.
- Man, fuck you!
You tried to kill me.
- [laughs]
No.
He did.
♪ ♪
Quit talking, man,
and pull the fucking trigger.
- Man, I had your back!
- Had my back?
I remember doing
hard fucking time,
caged like a dog,
while you got let out.
- Man, we both did time.
Don't give me that fucking shit.
- Time?
You were 16.
They fucking tried you
as a fucking minor.
That's a fucking
slap on the hand.
I was 17,
just a few months older,
and they tried me
as a fucking adult.
Because of you, motherfucker,
I lost years!
You got your fucking bitch,
your fucking son,
a fucking life.
- Like I said,
we both got caught up.
How the fuck was I supposed
to know how they tried us?
We were kids.
We were fucking kids.
- [laughing]
♪ ♪
Thank you, Juanito.
- For what?
- [laughing]
Had a lot of anger towards you.
I fucking hated you.
[laughs]
But I forgive you now.
[laughing]
♪ ♪
Letting me use
your fucking whore-ass wife.
Yeah?
[laughs]
Helped me release
a lot of tension.
[laughing]
♪ ♪
[dramatic musical flourish]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Adriana.
Adriana.
Babe?
[crying softly]
I'm so sorry, baby.
[police radio chatter]
- I got a family
to take care of now.
♪ ♪