(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
FOSTER MOM: You little
monsters, can you not hear me?
Are you deaf?
You're not listening to me!
Can't you hear me?
Listen to me, now stop!
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
POLICEMAN: Police, open up!
FOSTER MOM: Why are you here?
POLICEMAN: You're
under arrest for assault
and battery of minors.
- Ma'am.
- I didn't do anything.
Get away from me.
Tell them the truth.
I didn't do anything to you
kids.
You hear me?
I was your last chance, nobody
wants you!
Your family didn't even want
you!
POLICEMAN: You have the
right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and
will be used against you
in the court of law.
FOSTER MOM: I have
some rights you know!
Don't worry, I'll make sure
you're taken care of, I promise.
(POLICE CAR SIREN WAILING)
Have a good night Kerry.
Oh, Jaylene I got another case
for you.
What's her story?
Mom was killed in a motorcycle
accident two years ago.
The little girl called the cops
when the foster mom went
after the foster brother.
And where is he now?
They found temporary placement
for him.
Her name is Tulsa.
You need to find a replacement
before you leave tonight.
Kerry, you know that's
impossible.
I mean, all of our beds are
full.
Try Michelle at the Atlanta
Mission.
Sometimes she's willing to
foster kids
for short term emergencies.
The sooner you find her
placement,
the sooner you can start your
weekend.
Have a good night Kerry.
See you Monday.
Tulsa hi, I'm Ms. Jaylene.
I'm gonna be your caseworker.
How's Michael?
He is staying with
relatives in South Georgia
for now anyway.
They should know he's scared
of the dark
and sometimes he wets his bed
but if you read to him,
it'll calm him down.
You two got pretty close
didn't you?
I know Jesus will take care of
him.
Do you believe in Jesus Ms.
Jaylene?
Yes I do.
You know, you are pretty
mature for a nine year old.
Well Tulsa, it is my job to
find you a safe place to stay.
Oh, you don't have to.
I'm going to stay with my
father.
- Your father?
- TULSA: Mmh mmh.
I don't seem to have any
information on your father.
Do you know where you lives or
his name?
Have you ever met him before?
No, but I found his picture
of him in my mama's Bible.
That's mama and that's my
father.
Is your father's name Tommy?
All right boss, we're out of
here.
We'll see you on Monday.
Hey Tommy, you good?
Yeah.
♪ How on earth did it
all go down like this ♪
♪ I've got no words to make
sense of it ♪
♪ My shield my fight for
righteousness ♪
♪ Could not protect me from
myself ♪
♪ I'm looking for the higher
power ♪
♪ To be my mighty tower ♪
♪ Save me from myself oh yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm-a fall seven more
times ♪
♪ And it ain't nobody's
fault except mine ♪
♪ There's only one way out ♪
♪ Please Lord forgive me ♪
♪ I'm down on my bended knees ♪
♪ And I need your love ♪
♪ Mercy is your medicine ♪
♪ Help me turn around again ♪
♪ To you my friend ♪
♪ How long did I fool myself ♪
♪ Believing I I didn't
need nobody's help ♪
♪ A fool trusts in his
power and his wealth ♪
♪ Until he's brought down low ♪
♪ Unto a shadow of himself ♪
♪ The arrow was sent to
intervene ♪
♪ It pierced my bones and
shook me from my dream ♪
- JAYLENE: Tommy?
- Yeah
Tommy hi, it's Jaylene.
I'm sorry I know it's late
but we need to meet up.
Now is not a good time.
I have your daughter.
You said I have a daughter?
I'm fine by the way,
thank you for asking.
And yes like I told you,
this little girl claims
you're her biological father.
The only proof she has is this
photo.
She doesn't even know your name.
Sandy?
What happened to her?
A motorcycle accident two
years ago.
You didn't know that?
No.
Wow, we had some crazy times.
Yeah, I know.
She wrote to me for a couple
months after I deployed,
but that was like 10 years ago.
Tulsa is nine
Tulsa?
She has no other family.
Her most recent placement
was a really bad situation.
So what do you want me to do?
I'm not saying you're her
father, but if you're willing,
we can do some tests to confirm
that.
As for right now, she just
really wants to meet you.
Then what?
I don't even like kids.
I am in no position to be a
father.
Then just be her friend.
So, that's Tulsa.
- TOMMY: What's she doing?
- JAYLENE: Praying.
- For what?
- Probably for you.
Come on.
Are you all right?
Be careful next time okay?
JAYLENE: Tulsa sweetie,
this is Tommy Colston.
TULSA: My father!
Tommy wanted to meet you.
Yeah.
You look different than
your picture, you're scrappy.
Tulsa sweetie, Tommy has
agreed to do some tests
to see if he's your father.
He doesn't have to, he is.
It's time for me to go home now.
Look kid, I wouldn't be good
for you right now, trust me.
It sounds like we've
got a lot of work to do.
I'll get my things.
What's happening?
Let's just take her to
your place and show her.
(GARAGE DOOR SCREECHING OPEN)
So this is my garage.
(BRIGHT MUSIC)
It's filthy.
It's a garage.
You own this place?
TOMMY: No, I rent this place.
I live in the apartment
upstairs.
Is this it?
Hey, kid wait!
(DOOR CREAKS SHUT)
I wasn't expecting company.
Forever?
Okay, I'll stay.
She can't, I mean you
wouldn't?
Tulsa sweetie, it's not that
simple.
No.
You don't have a place for me
to stay,
but it's okay now, I found my
father.
Sweetie, it's much
more involved than that.
That's right, yeah, tell her.
I mean, there needs to be
meetings,
interviews, background checks.
And I'll definitely
fail those, all of them.
I mean, this place needs to
be cleaned up and inspected.
We'll be ready.
Don't worry, we'll fix you.
Is my room down there?
Don't!
You can't just leave her here.
She's right, we don't have
any place for her to stay.
Just for a little while
until I figure this out.
I know you, you'll take great
care of her.
Are you serious?
What do I do with her?
The Tommy Colston I know
is a charmer, charm her.
Charm her?
You left her with him?
There was nowhere else for her
to go.
Besides, he's her father.
You don't know that for sure.
A non emergency DNA test
takes six to eight weeks,
maybe even longer.
There's not even anyone
who can vouch for this man.
I know Tommy.
I will vouch for him and I
will constantly check on them.
If anything happens to this
child,
it's your license on the line or
worse.
Jaylene, Jaylene did you hear
me?
Yes, I hear you
I'm all unpacked!
Great.
Where you in the Army?
The Marines.
What's the difference?
How much time do we have?
You know, you shouldn't smoke
or drink?
It'll kill you.
So will children.
Can I ask you some questions?
Do I have a choice?
Are you a criminal?
No.
What's your favorite color?
Black.
What's your favorite movie?
"Black bear".
What do you do for fun?
Yoga.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Nope.
Do you want one?
If you weren't a
mechanic, what would you be?
Life coach.
You know, you're a little
Didi you know that?
What's a Didi?
So what you got there?
Ooh, I get it, that's yours,
that's cool.
It's mama's Bible.
All the answers you'll ever
need in life are in this book.
Did you love my mama?
Yeah.
Me and your mom had a lot of
fun.
She called those her wild
days before she found Jesus.
I didn't know He was missing.
Everybody needs Jesus.
He's needed here.
Yeah, well, it's getting
a little too crowded in here
if you asked me.
Well, I'm going back to bed.
You think you can find something
to do?
Wake me up only if the place
catches fire
and do not touch anything,
anything.
(BRIGHT MUSIC)
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
What are you doing?
Getting ready for the
inspection.
(DOORS SLAMMING SHUT)
They're all gone.
What's gone?
All your alcohol and
cigarettes.
I threw them out.
What the hell?
Language, you should
have your mouth washed out
with soap for that.
Whisky's stronger.
Look little Didi.
My name is Tulsa.
I don't care.
I told you to stay out of my
stuff.
It's time to get clean and
organized.
Are you gonna help or not?
What are you doing now?
Laundry.
What do you know about
laundry?
As much as you know
about being a parent.
I told you, I got rid of all
your alcohol,
including everything you hid.
I gotta go.
You don't need that stuff!
(CELLPHONE VIBRATING)
- Hey Jaylene.
- JAYLENE: Hey Tommy,
how's Tulsa doing?
She's upstairs probably
sprinkling Holy water
all over the place.
She's trying to make a home.
Can't she stay with you?
Unfortunately no, she can't.
Besides, I believe every
girl needs a father.
Call me if you need anything
tonight,
I'll check in on you tomorrow.
Tommy, Tommy?
TOMMY: Yeah
I know this must be a
shock, but you got this.
Yeah.
The Lord is my shepherd,
I shall not want.
He makes me lie down
in the green pastures.
He leads me beside the still
waters.
He restores my soul.
He leads me in the paths
of righteousness through His
namesake.
Yea, though I walk through the
valley
of the shadow of death.
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm awesome.
(BRIGHT MUSIC)
♪ Amazing grace how sweet the
sound ♪
♪ That saved a wretch like you ♪
TOMMY: Quiet!
It's time for church.
There are no churches in this
town.
You're lying, now get up.
I made breakfast.
I'm not going to know any
church.
And take a shower, you stink!
You stink.
And shave that scruff.
I'm gonna drop you off at the
orphanage.
So, from now on I do the
laundry.
I told you I got rid of them.
(DOOR CREAKS SHUT)
Of course.
Since you're not going to
church,
I made a list of chores for you.
You can start by mowing the
grass.
I may have saved one pack of
cigarettes.
If you mow the grass, I'll
tell you where I hid them.
I'm not playing your
little games understand?
(LAWNMOWER RATTLING)
Come on, there's still some
left.
Gimme me my cigarettes.
This and that.
What?
No, just give me my cigarettes.
You'll get the rest once you
do that.
Don't forget to do this part.
Hold on, I'll give you a ride.
(MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARING)
- Hop on.
- No.
What's wrong now?
It's not safe, you're
not wearing a helmet.
You even know where you're
going?
TULSA: God will lead me.
God will lead you.
You can't just walk in
there, it's not your church.
That's the cool thing about
church, it's for everyone.
Come on, you'll see.
No thanks.
Hey, I'll meet you out front
after the service, okay?
How's Tulsa this morning?
Oh, she's great.
She's just giving Jesus honor.
Jaylene, I don't know how
much longer I can do this.
She is the most stubborn,
arrogant, hardheaded,
know it all I've never met.
It sounds like someone else I
know.
That reminds me, we need to
register her
for school tomorrow.
Wait, does that mean she's
staying?
Just for the time being.
Try to make the best of it.
Goodbye Tulsa.
You keep praising the Lord.
Tommy!
My dear, you were a gift
from my heavenly Father this
morning.
Thank you Bishop Franklin.
Are you the father of
this wonderful little girl?
That's what they tell me.
Well sir, you have a little
angel here.
Yep, my little angel.
I hope to see you again.
Not so fast, get on.
I told you it's not safe.
Trust me.
Ta-dah!
Put your bible.
All right, throw it up here.
All right, you hold onto me real
tight.
(MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARING)
♪ I'm holding on to
the hope that one day ♪
♪ This could be made right ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been shipwrecked ♪
♪ and left for dead and I
have seen the darkest sights ♪
♪ Everyone I've loved seems
like a stranger in the night ♪
♪ Well I'm sailing home to you ♪
♪ I wont be long ♪
♪ By the light of moon ♪
♪ I will press on ♪
♪ I wanna hold her in my arms ♪
(TULSA LAUGHS)
We still have a lot to
be before the inspection.
It can wait.
Can I ask you a question?
More questions?
Go ahead, shoot.
Why are you so scared to go to
church?
Are you like Godphobic?
Godphobic?
Is that a thing?
It seems like your thing.
Listen Didi, I'm not scared of
anything.
I just know it doesn't work.
TULSA: How do you know?
I just know.
Maybe God's at work right
now and you just don't see it.
Okay, can I ask you a
question?
Go ahead, shoot.
That foster mom,
did she hurt you?
It's okay if you don't
wanna talk about it.
Michael, he's my foster
brother.
He had an accident in the bed
that night.
We tried to wash the sheets
before she found out,
but she caught me.
You did the right thing.
This Michael, he means a lot to
you?
He's very special to me.
You want some more?
Maybe we should go home.
Good idea.
Let me help.
There!
It's a really sad painting.
You should go to bed,
you have school tomorrow.
Who's Lisa?
I said go to bed.
Look, you wanted a dad,
well I'm being a dad, go!
Listen, if anyone comes in, get
payment.
I'm bleeding here and now with
Tulsa.
Someone shows up, says you're
a daddy
and you believe 'em?
I mean, I'd want proof.
Yeah well, they're doing
tests.
How long have you known Tommy?
My entire life.
How old are you?
35.
ID.
You ever done time?
I'd rather not talk about it.
Who's the lady?
She's my sister.
What's her name?
Trixy.
Well, if you are a nice
brother,
you'd buy Trixy some clothes.
Come on Tulsa, time for
school.
We'll continue this later.
Man, who is that kid?
What's wrong?
It's just, do I have to go?
Well, if it were up to me, I'd
teach you
how to rebuild a carburetor
and I'd put your butt to work.
What now?
I've been in five different
schools since mama died.
The girls can be kind of mean.
Mean like, mean how?
Like they beat you up?
Yes, but with their words.
Well, you may not wanna tell
everyone
at the lunch table they're going
to hell.
Save that for your second day.
Okay, look kid you gotta
treat school like prison.
Go up to the biggest, baddest
girl
and punch her in the face.
Okay no, not really.
But, yes punch her in the face.
It's all in the attitude.
You know I got an idea.
We've got to make a quick stop
before we go to school, okay?
(BELL RINGING)
I do have other
appointments Ms. Sanders.
Mr. Colston's a new father.
I'm sure he just wants to
make sure everything's okay
for Tulsa's first day.
(UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC)
Principal Workman, this is
Tommy Colston and Tulsa.
- What's up?
- I mean good morning.
- Good morning.
Well, let's go ahead and get
started.
Tulsa, this is Riley.
You'll be shadowing her on your
first day.
Hi Tulsa, I like your jacket.
Thanks.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
She's gonna be okay right?
She will.
You're doing fine Tommy.
Establish a routine, pick her up
everyday
at the same time, help
her with her homework.
Foster kids like her are
really sensitive to anything
that triggers feelings of
abandonment.
I clearly don't know what I'm
doing.
I gotta get this, one second.
I can't believe it!
By the way, did you
guys see that new girl
in the leather jacket?
I hope she doesn't
get grease all over us.
I know right?
- (GIRLS LAUGHING)
- Hi girls.
You better watch what you say.
That little grease monkey is my
daughter
and the last three little brats
who teased her mysteriously
disappeared.
I know right?
Like they disappeared,
disappeared.
Psychopath!
It's nice that you're
defending Tulsa,
but let's try not to threaten
any more minors okay?
It was just a pep talk.
(JAYLENE LAUGHS)
(TRAIN WHISTLING)
Tulsa!
Forgotten.
Oh, it's so sad when that
happens.
My ride is just late.
Maybe your dad got arrested.
Yeah, he's probably in jail.
I'll tell him to say hi to
your mom.
Oh, I got the cutest dress
for the daddy, daughter dance.
We're going shopping this
weekend.
Are you and your dad going?
Of course not, her dad can't
even remember to pick her up.
Tulsa, Tulsa, Tulsa wait up!
I'm sorry, I was working.
Time just got away from me.
Just say it.
Say what?
That I don't mean anything to
you.
That's not true.
Then why didn't you look for
me?
Look for you?
I knew you'd be here.
Not here, when I was born.
I didn't even know you
existed.
You didn't want to know.
Fathers are supposed to be
there always, no matter what.
They're supposed to protect
their kids,
play with them, teach them
things.
I can't even ride a bike.
Hold up.
I had this stupid dream
that I knew you would love me
and take care of me.
I feel so stupid.
Just go and ask Ms. Jaylene
to take you somewhere else.
TOMMY: What?
I know I'm a lot to handle and
a pain.
I get it.
Just tell me the truth.
No, I want you to stay.
I'm sorry kid, it's my fault.
I'll do better, I promise.
That's easy to say.
You never got a chance
to be a kid did you?
We're gonna take care of that.
So how was school?
You knock out any bullies?
Arg, school is overrated.
You know what they say?
C's get degrees.
Ms. Jaylene went a
different way with her advice.
What's that?
Some daddy, daughter
dance at your school.
What do you say?
You and me, let's go.
Mama says dancing leads to
fornication.
Fornication?
Do you even know what that
means?
Okay no, but I know it's bad.
Well, not all dancing is bad
Didi.
You gotta have a little fun.
No I'm not going.
And why do you keep calling me
Didi?
You can't dance.
That's it, you can't dance.
Listen, I'll teach you.
You will be the coolest kid
on the dance floor, I promise.
Come on.
We still have a lot to
do before the inspection.
We should hurry.
Yes ma'am, but just remember
the rhythm is gonna get you.
No, seriously, it is going to
get you.
Tommy, what's the capital of
Alaska?
What?
The capital of Alaska?
I need to know for homework.
Let me think.
You okay?
Give me a second.
(TOILET FLUSHING)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Yeah, I'm okay kid.
I'm clean.
So you say Jesus, He's always
with us?
Yeah.
So is He here with this now?
Right.
Like right here?
No, right here.
Wow.
- Colston (SCOFFS).
- Mr. Garcia.
(SCOFFS) Mr. Garcia?
I thought you forgot about all
my name.
I mean, I haven't received any
rent check
in the last three months.
What's up with that?
You'll get your rent.
I just need a little time to
collect
on some invoices that's it.
Who's that?
That's my kid.
- Tiny, can you?
- Tulsa, let's take a break
and go out back.
Listen, you have until
the end of the month
or you're out that's it, okay?
You'll get your rent.
MR GARCIA: You better!
TINY: Hey, watch what you're
doing.
Tiny, when's the last
time you washed your hands.
What's today?
Last week.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(MID TEMPO MUSIC)
Tommy, dinner's ready!
Dinner's ready!
(GATE CREAKS OPEN)
Tommy?
Tommy wake up, wake up!
I'm sorry Lisa
It's me Tulsa!
Tommy, wake up!
You've got to beat this Tommy.
You were doing so good.
I'm sorry.
Promise me you'll get help.
I don't wanna lose you Tommy.
I'm not gonna lose you either.
I didn't deserve that.
No, no you didn't,
but it's what you needed.
Tommy Colston, good to
see you again young man.
Bishop.
What's a little grease
among friends (CHUCKLES).
Hey Tulsa!
Actually, I'm here to see you.
You know, I've been exactly
where you are right now.
Yeah?
Where's that?
Lost, we're all in
the same boat my friend.
When I was in the Army, I was a
mess.
I used to get so drunk and I'd
wake up
in some nowhere bar and
walk half the day looking
for my car.
I would too if I joined the
Army.
(LAUGHS) All right.
With all due respect Bishop,
I believe there's a God, I do.
I just don't trust Him.
Life, it's just a big storm.
There's no lighthouse.
There once was a man who was
shipwrecked
in middle of the sea.
He was in a fierce storm and
he just knew he was gonna die.
So he cried out, "God save me!"
And all of a sudden, his ship
caught fire.
He jumped overboard and
clutching to a piece of a hull,
I mean angry and scared.
And he cried out again,
"Why did you abandon me?
"I asked for help and you burnt
my ship."
And all of a sudden,
this huge ship just cuts
right through the storm
and pulls the man to safety.
And the captain said to the man,
"It's a good thing that
your ship caught fire
"'cause if it hadn't, we
never would have seen you."
God's ways are above our ways.
His thoughts above our thoughts.
Who can know the mind of God?
God could have wiped us all
out, the whole human race.
But instead he said,
"No, they are worth it."
God doesn't need us, He wants
us.
That's why Jesus came
and died on the cross.
We're saved by love Tommy.
It doesn't always come in
the form of a lighthouse
or lightning in the sky.
Sometimes our ship needs to
burn before we're rescued.
And sometimes the answer just
may come in a small voice.
I really need to get this car
done
if that's okay with you.
I'm gonna leave this for
you right here, just in case.
I recommend you start
with the book of John.
Tulsa, Tulsa!
Sorry kid.
(SOMBER MUSIC)
Hey kid.
I'll take care of you.
It's what I'm afraid of.
(BRIGHT MUSIC)
Practicing your moves?
I wasn't dancing, I was.
How do I look?
You still have your
scruff, but you look good.
Like a nice criminal.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
I look GQ Didi, GQ.
Don't forget that.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(DOOR CREAKS SHUT)
- Hello Ms. Murray.
- Mrs. Murray.
Mr. Colston, Tulsa.
Hello.
Now, Ms. Jaylene has
given me a little background
on your situation.
How's everything been going?
Everything's great, right
Tommy?
Of course, we are blessed.
Just so blessed to be here
with God in our hearts.
What Tommy is trying to say
is that we are very blessed
to have found one another.
Yes, yes, praise Him, praise
Him!
For we are blessed.
Shall we sit?
Please, my chair.
Yes ma'am.
Thank you.
Are you hot Mr. Colston?
Yeah, yeah, I'd like to think
that I am.
No, you seem flushed.
Are you nervous?
- Yes.
- No.
- No
- Yes.
Tommy's not been feeling well.
The flu maybe.
I'm sorry, excuse me.
Perhaps I should reschedule.
No Ms Kerry, I know
this place is not normal
and Tommy's really nervous right
now,
but he's a really good father.
Sure, he's far from perfect,
but each day he wakes up and
works harder than the last.
Please, give us a chance.
Tell Mr. Colston, I hope
he gets better really soon
and I mean really soon.
Yes ma'am, he will.
Thank you Mrs. Murray!
Ms. Jaylene will be in contact
with you
until I'm able to do a good home
study.
- Goodbye, for now.
- Bye!
(DOOR CREAKS SHUT)
Tommy.
Oh hello, can I please
speak to Mr. Chainsaw?
(BRIGHT MUSIC)
Oh hello, my name is Trixy
at Colston customs.
I know, I sound a lot younger
than I am.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I just wanted to let you know
that you have been entered in
a chance to win a custom bike.
Yes, yes that's right.
We're having the drawing
here at the garage
but you need to be here to win.
Bring two forms of ID,
oh and a credit card.
Thank you, thank you, thanks,
thank you,
thank you very much.
What's all this.
Oh, it's a drawing they're
having for a custom bike.
- Drawing?
- Mmh mmh.
Excuse me.
Okay, I don't know what's going
on here,
but we are not giving anything
away.
Where's Trixy?
Yeah, Trixy will know.
I am Trixy.
Tulsa, what are you doing?
Getting the rent money.
- You lied?
- No, Trixy lied.
Tiny, help me up.
Thank you all for coming,
but I must confess, there's no
drawing.
This is bull, I'm leaving.
You can't leave.
I have all your keys,
but you'll all get them
back once everyone here
has paid their bill.
What are you talking about?
BIKER: I paid JB when I
picked up my bike last week.
Me too!
I paid him in cash.
I always pay my bills.
JB, you stealing from me?
I gave you the money.
You were just so strung out,
you probably don't remember.
Is everyone lying?
Search him Tiny.
Come on, hey!
Yo, I was keeping this
place running before
that little brat showed up.
If you ever talk about my
daughter like that again,
you will leave here on a
stretcher.
Okay, this ain't over Tommy.
Give them their keys back
Trixy.
Take your keys.
Tulsa, you can't do that
again.
It worked didn't it?
I'll make dinner.
Wait, it's been a great week.
First the inspection, now the
rent,
we're going out to celebrate.
Can I invite someone?
TOMMY: Was your pizza good?
TULSA: Yeah.
TOMMY: Do you want another
piece?
No.
Kerry wasn't 100% convinced,
but you are safe for the time
being
which is good enough.
To good enough.
- Cheers!
- To good enough, cheers!
What's wrong?
I think the ice cream's
spoiled.
Mine tastes fine.
Smell it.
(TULSA AND JAYLENE LAUGHING)
I can't believe I fell for
that.
Rookie move Tommy, rookie
move.
What was Tommy like in high
school?
Oh, here we go.
He was a renegade, always
cutting it up
in the parking lot with his
friends, challenging authority.
Okay, she's heard enough.
But, this one time after
school my truck wouldn't start
and your father saw me
crying and he came over
and he asked me to pop the hood.
He fixed it in like two minutes.
The red silver auto?
Mmh mmh, it was my father's.
He had passed a year before.
I remember that?
(GENTLE MUSIC)
Didi, this song, it's time
for your first dance lesson.
- No.
- Come on.
No way.
Whoa, whoa, what is all this?
Tell this one here to go
to the daddy, daughter dance
with me.
I don't wanna go, okay.
She doesn't wanna go
because she can't dance.
Oh well, I would've loved
to have gone to a dance
with my father.
Come on, let's show her how
it's done.
♪ I feel it inside my soul ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Something was missing
but now I'm whole ♪
♪ I found my family ♪
♪ When I'm with you I know I'm
home ♪
♪ Ooh oh oh ooh ♪
(GATE CREAKS SHUT)
(GATE CREAKS OPEN)
(MID TEMPO MUSIC)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
(DOOR CREAKS SHUT)
TULSA: Dear Michael,
I miss you so much.
I can't wait to see you again.
I pray for you every day.
Always remember Jesus loves you.
I'll try and call you
when Ms. Jaylene gives me your
number.
I pray one day we can
be together as a family.
I love you very, very much, love
Tulsa.
P.S., remember, don't eat the
crayons,
they give you diarrhea.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
There you are.
Tiny needs your help.
Why did you lie to me?
Lie to you?
What are you talking about?
I haven't had a drink,
no cigarettes, no pills.
No, why did you lie about me?
You knew about me all along.
Wait a second.
Where's this coming from?
I found this in your desk
drawer.
I told you to stay out of my
stuff.
You knew I was out there.
You didn't care one bit.
This isn't you.
TULSA: Then who is it?
This is my son.
I have a brother?
Where is he?
He's gone.
Where'd he go?
I told you to stay out of my
stuff.
This is none of your business.
Tommy, stop!
- Hey handsome!
- Hey.
So what'd they say?
Well, I figured out
what's wrong with me.
And?
I'm pregnant.
Pregnant?
Yeah, the clinic thinks
I'm about four months.
It's a boy!
She said he looks healthy.
I mean, of course I have to
go see a real baby doctor.
You should come.
Yeah, you should definitely
come,
if you want to.
Hey, tell me you're happy?
Tommy, I need to hear you say
it.
Okay look, we'll stop
everything.
We'll get clean.
I've already got my meds
adjusted.
I can get my moods under
control, I promise.
Really, just like that?
Tommy, I want this.
I want it with you.
This is your son.
Is it?
What?
What do you mean?
Tommy, talk to me.
Get rid of it.
(LISA CRYING)
You don't mean that.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Lisa, it's me.
I'm sorry, I was stupid.
Please just come home.
We'll figure all this out.
Just come home, please.
I love you, just come home.
♪ Come on home ♪
♪ Home to me ♪
♪ And I will hold you in my arms ♪
♪ And joyful be ♪
♪ There will always always be ♪
♪ A place for you ♪
♪ At my table ♪
♪ Return to me ♪
♪ Wonder where I might begin ♪
♪ Hear a voice upon the wind ♪
♪ She's singing faint but
singing true ♪
♪ Son there ain't nothing you
can do ♪
♪ But listen close and follow me ♪
♪ I'll take you where you meant
to be ♪
♪ Just don't lose faith ♪
♪ Come on home ♪
Hey kid.
Are you okay?
I'm okay Didi.
TULSA: Where are you?
I'm out looking at orphanages,
but no one will take you.
What are you doing?
I'm looking at nursing homes,
but no one will take you.
You're not getting into any
trouble out there are you?
No trouble, I'm just
taking care of some things.
I'm coming home Tulsa, I'm
coming home.
♪ There will always always be ♪
♪ A place for you ♪
♪ At my table ♪
♪ Return to me ♪
(DOOR CREAKS SHUT)
Hey kid.
So, where were you?
I just had to get some
closure.
You wanna talk about it?
Please?
A girl named Lisa painted this
painting.
She always said it was a
portrait of me.
The ship in the middle of the
storm.
A man without a home.
Who is Lisa?
She was my girlfriend
and the mother of my son.
So what happened to him, your
son?
I wasn't ready to be a father.
And Lisa, she was fragile.
And I pushed her.
I pushed her until she broke.
I'm still not ready to be a
father.
Let's be honest,
I'm no good.
I'm no good for you.
You're perfect for me.
Tommy Colston, you're the
best dad in the whole world.
And I love you.
I love you too kid.
Whatever happens, you're
home now Tommy, you're home.
Now, about this Jesus thing.
For God so loved the world,
He gave his only begotten
son that whoever it is.
♪ I won't fear the wind and the
waves ♪
♪ My eyes are fixed upon your
face ♪
♪ I'm safe in your love ♪
♪ You're the God that anchors me ♪
Remember, punch 'em in the
face.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Oh, score!
All right Tommy, you ready?
Let me try, I wanna try.
- Are you ready?
- This better not
be a joke.
No joke, you ready?
Ta-dah!
A bike!
But I don't know how to ride.
Well, that's what a dad is for
right?
Okay, ready.
♪ Oh you're the God that anchors
me ♪
Kick that back.
You won't let go?
I won't let go, I promise,
okay.
Pedal hard, good job!
All right ready?
There you go.
♪ And I will I'll trust in your
promises ♪
♪ And I know you are God ♪
♪ You are God ♪
I'm gonna be late for school.
Calm down Didi, just give me a
minute.
School is just a few blocks.
I can walk from here.
That's not a good idea.
Just wait in the truck.
I'll be fine, please?
I'm not a baby.
I can walk three blocks on my
own.
Okay, but look look both ways
twice
and don't ride with any
strangers.
No one stranger than you?
Ha ha!
Bye!
Be careful.
(CAR ENGINE ROARING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Oh my God.
Oh my goodness, oh my
goodness, oh my goodness!
Don't move her, don't move
her.
Don't move her!
Sweetie, sweetie, how did this
happen?
I didn't see her!
I hit her!
Sweetie, come on, open your
eyes!
Come on, come back to us!
(AMBULANCE SIREN WAILING)
(CELLPHONE VIBRATING)
Tommy.
What?
Where is she right now?
Tulsa, Tulsa!
WOMAN: Please stay back sir.
That's my daughter.
She was hit by that bus.
She's alive, but unconscious.
We're sending her to Children's
Healthcare of Atlanta.
Tulsa daddy's here.
Are you okay?
Tulsa, daddy's here okay.
I'm here, daddy's here.
Tulsa wake up.
Daddy?
We're gonna get you
taken care of okay, okay?
I hurt.
I know you hurt baby.
I love you.
I love you Tulsa.
There's no room.
Head to the hospital.
(AMBULANCE DOORS SLAMMING SHUT)
(AMBULANCE SIREN WAILING)
I should have never let her
walk to school by herself.
Tommy, it's not your fault.
She's gonna be fine.
We have to believe that.
Tulsa's family, Tulsa's
family?
How is she?
Come here.
Right now Tulsa is in a
medically induced coma.
She's in critical condition.
She did sustain several
injuries, now the least of which
is the one to her head.
Now, that's the one I'm
concerned about.
She has a major subdural
hematoma.
What is that?
It's bleeding inside the
skull, around the brain.
It causes a lot of pressure.
We have to relieve that
pressure.
I wanna see her.
Yeah, and you can but not now.
What your little girl needs
right now is a lot of rest.
What she doesn't need is any
sort of stimulation, okay.
So I want you to wait here
and I'll keep you posted.
- All right.
- Hey look, I'm sorry
that this happened.
- Thanks Doc.
- Yeah.
Is everything okay?
(AMBULANCE SIREN WAILING)
Mr. Colston, you may go in
and see your daughter now,
but just so you know, she's
still not awake, okay.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Right this way.
(HEART RATE MONITOR BEEPING)
I'm here Didi, daddy's here.
(SOMBER MUSIC)
Excuse me sir, could
you give me a moment?
Come home Tulsa.
Okay, she's finally awake,
but she's a very sick
little girl, all right.
But she's demanding to see you.
Now, before you go in there,
I want you to know
that your daughter has a
very long road ahead of her.
So, take it easy on her, all
right?
- All right.
- Sure.
- Thanks Doc.
- You're welcome.
I missed you.
I looked both ways twice, I
did.
It's not your fault.
My head, it hurts really bad.
I know it does.
We're gonna get you fixed, okay.
I don't know if I can.
Yes, you can.
You're a fighter Didi.
Here, we're in this together
Didi.
Why do you call me Didi?
I'll make you a promise,
when you get out of here,
I'll tell you.
Deal?
Deal.
I'm gonna take care of you.
That's what I'm afraid of
(LAUGHS).
I love you.
I love you too.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Hey there.
Bishop Franklin!
- Tommy.
- Bishop.
You up for a visit?
Good, 'cause I brought
some friends with me.
You liked the so much the first
time you came to our church,
I thought that we'd come
and sing it for you today.
Ready family?
♪ It is well ♪
♪ With my soul ♪
♪ It is well with my soul ♪
♪ When peace like a
river attendeth my way ♪
♪ When sorrows like sea billows
roll ♪
♪ Whatever my lot thou
hast taught me to say ♪
♪ It is well it is well ♪
♪ With my soul ♪
♪ My sin oh the bliss of
this glorious thought ♪
♪ My sin not in part but the
whole ♪
♪ Is nailed to the cross ♪
♪ And I bear it no more ♪
♪ Praise the Lord praise
the Lord o my soul ♪
♪ It is well ♪
♪ With my soul ♪
♪ It is well with my soul ♪
♪ It is well ♪
♪ With my soul ♪
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
- Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
How is she today?
Her head, she's still in a lot
of pain.
You think that's what Dr.
Holden wanted to see us about?
I don't know.
This is for you.
- Mr Colston.
- Doc.
Let's talk.
Okay, Tulsa is not
responding to treatment.
The pressure is not being
relieved in her brain
as we had hoped it would.
The pressure is just too great.
Now, if this should continue,
she is going to slip into an
actual coma.
Yeah, but she seemed to
be improving last week.
I understand that but
sadly it's not uncommon
for a patient to rally right
before a major setback.
So what do we do?
I mean, there's gotta be some
options.
Yes, there's a procedure that
we can do
to relieve the pressure
but I need to tell you
that this procedure can be
fairly risky.
How risky?
I'd give it a 50% chance
of healthy recovery.
And the other 50?
That would be either
permanent paralysis or worse.
So what you're saying is
if we do nothing Tulsa dies.
And if we have this
procedure she could also die.
I understand that this is not
good news,
but it is what we're dealing
with.
In the meantime, what we'll do
is we'll manage Tulsa's
pain as well as we can.
We'll do everything we can
to relieve the pressure
on her brain and we
will hope for the best.
But, right now I do recommend
that you have a serious
conversation with Tulsa, thank you.
- I'll do it.
- Tommy.
She's my daughter, I'll tell
her.
We need to pray for a miracle.
(BRIGHT MUSIC)
♪ He's always there with me ♪
♪ Even if I don't see ♪
♪ He'll catch me if I fall ♪
♪ He'll be with me through it
all ♪
(CHILDREN CLAPPING)
♪ He'll catch me if I fall ♪
♪ He'll be with me ♪
TOMMY: Do you understand?
TULSA: I think so.
It's okay to be scared.
I'm not scared.
I mean, I wanna see Jesus and
mama.
I really do but.
But what?
I don't wanna leave you
(SOBBING).
Will you forget me?
Forget you?
Are you crazy?
Forget my own?
I would forget my own
name before I forget you.
Besides, we're gonna beat this.
You're not in this alone.
I just wanna let you know,
you're the best dad in the whole
world.
I love you Tommy Colston.
And I want you to remember this
moment,
remember me, right here.
I know I don't deserve you.
You're the most precious person
God could've ever brought
into my life.
I wish I could make all this go
away.
I love you.
Pain management seems to be
going fine,
but Tulsa is really not
responding to the treatment
so if you're gonna opt for the
procedure,
you need to tell me
sooner rather than later.
I've talked to Tulsa and
she's willing to risk it.
Okay good.
I'm gonna schedule her for
Saturday.
What can I do?
What you can do young lady
is you can make sure this one
goes home
and get some rest that's
doctor's orders.
He's right, when's the
last time you were home?
Tiny has got the garage under
control.
I'm not talking about the
garage,
I'm talking about you and your
health.
You need rest.
When he gets my daughter to be
okay.
You heard the doctor said
to go home and get some sleep.
I will.
Tell me, if you could do
anything in the world right now,
what would it be?
That's easy, I'd go to the
daddy, daughter dance with you.
I wish we could, but you know
we can't.
She's asleep, why don't you
just go home for the night?
My home is when I'm with her.
Yeah, but you're no good
to her or anybody else
if you go down with exhaustion.
Now, come on and get
yourself up out of here.
I'll call you if anything
changes.
It's okay.
You gotta take care of you too.
It's gonna be okay.
Thanks nurse.
Get some rest Tommy.
(MOTOR CYCLE ENGINE ROARING)
What can I get you to drink?
Whisky neat.
♪ Farther along we'll know all
about it ♪
♪ Farther along we'll understand
why ♪
♪ So cheer up my brothers ♪
♪ Live in the sunshine ♪
♪ We'll understand this all by
and by ♪
♪ Tempted and tried I wondered
why ♪
♪ The good man dies the bad man
thrives ♪
♪ And Jesus cries because
he loves em' both ♪
♪ We're all cast-aways in need
of ropes ♪
♪ Hangin' on by the last
threads of our hope ♪
♪ In a house of mirrors full of
smoke ♪
♪ Confusing illusions I've seen ♪
♪ Where did I go wrong I sang
along ♪
- Tommy.
- What do you want JB?
Where's your little brat?
♪ Some will courageously escape ♪
♪ The seductive voice
with a heart of faith ♪
♪ While walkin' that line back
home ♪
♪ There's so much more to
life than we've been told ♪
Hey, let him go!
Stay out of this Tiny!
My friend, my business!
Tiny, it's time to go.
Tommy, come on, come on.
♪ Go down to the river and let
it run ♪
♪ Wash away all the things
you've done ♪
♪ Forgiveness all right ♪
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Colston, free to go!
How'd you hear?
Tiny called.
I gotta get to the hospital.
Tommy wait, you can't.
Social services have been
notified of your arrest,
Kerry dissolved your placement.
- They can't do that?
- Unfortunately they can.
Tulsa's still award of the
state.
Can you come with me and
supervise?
I would, but I've been
placed on indefinite leave.
Tell me what to do?
I don't know.
All I know is there's a sick
little girl who needs her dad.
(SOMBER MUSIC)
I trust you now.
She's just a little girl.
She's so good.
She loves you.
Just take me instead.
Why her?
What can I do for her?
What do I do?
Thank you.
Mr. Colston, I'm sorry,
you're not allowed to visit.
Mr. Colston!
Don't you dare!
Let that man see his little
girl.
I'm not gonna break the rules.
Girl, if you don't put that
phone down,
the law won't be the only thing
that gets broken around here.
Put the phone down now.
Please God, please.
Hey you.
What's going on?
I'm here to take you to
the daddy, daughter dance.
Will you go with me?
Are you serious?
This better not be a joke.
How?
Don't worry about that.
I'll take care of it.
You sure you're up for it?
We Colstons, we go big
or we go home.
That's my girl.
- Knock, knock?
- Ms. Jaylene!
Tommy, if you'll excuse us
ladies,
we have a dance to get ready
for.
Roger that.
Thank you.
You ready?
Mr. Colston, your date's
waiting.
You look so beautiful.
Just like your mom.
You ready?
I've waited for this my whole
life.
The only problem is how
are we gonna get out of here?
Why don't you try the side
door?
You have her back by
midnight and for the record,
I don't know anything about
this.
(TULSA LAUGHS)
(GENTLE MUSIC)
- You ready?
- Yeah.
I'll get you up okay.
Nice and easy.
♪ I'm holding on to hope that
one day ♪
♪ This could be made right ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been shipwrecked ♪
♪ Left for dead and I've
seen the darkest sights ♪
All right, I got you.
♪ Like a stranger in the night ♪
You ready for this?
Good, let's do this.
♪ I'm sailing home to you ♪
♪ I won't be long ♪
♪ By the light of moon ♪
One, two, three.
♪ Until I find my love ♪
♪ Trouble has beset my ways ♪
Hey, play this.
No way, I have my own
playlist.
Now.
Yes sir.
How are you doing kid?
I don't know if I can.
Just step on my feet.
I'll lead you, okay?
Okay,
You can do this.
Get ready, put your feet.
Okay, okay.
(TULSA GASPS)
There we go.
All right, okay.
♪ And take my cover ♪
I think this is what heaven
feels like.
You're crushing it Didi.
I told you the rhythm was gonna
get you.
I'm officially out of the
hospital so what does Didi mean?
Didi is short for devil dog.
Devil dog?
The Germans in World War I,
gave the Marines the nickname
devil dog
because they fought so fiercely.
It's a badge of honor.
You fought for me.
You fought for my soul.
You fought for us.
I love you Tulsa Colston.
I love you daddy.
♪ I know you are good ♪
You okay?
We should go.
Okay, I got you.
I'm just gonna pick you up.
I got you.
CROWD: Tulsa, Tulsa, Tulsa,
Tulsa,
Tulsa, Tulsa, Tulsa, Tulsa,
Tulsa, Tulsa, Tulsa
Tulsa, Tulsa, Tulsa,
Tulsa, Tulsa, Tulsa.
TOMMY: Everything's gonna be
okay.
What's this?
This is for later.
MAN: It's time sir.
TOMMY: I love you Tulsa.
I love you Tommy Colston!
And I'm proud of you.
(SOMBER MUSIC)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
TULSA: Dear daddy, we both
know
that life is not fair sometimes.
But, we can always trust that
God is good.
Spending time with my daddy
was the best dream come true,
only better.
Kids need a great dad you know.
You must stay strong
and not blame yourself
for what happened, it's okay.
By now, I'm in heaven with mama
and Jesus.
Don't worry, I'll find your son
too.
Tell Tiny I miss him and
he needs to wash his hands.
Also, you need to take Ms.
Jaylene out on a real date.
And I know you like her.
One more thing, please, please,
please adopt Michael, promise
me.
I'll see you on the other side.
Until then, I love you and I'm
proud of you Tommy Colston.
Your daughter, Tulsa Colston.
Did Tulsa have everything
figured out?
She always did.
I stopped in at work today.
You're back from leave?
No, I stopped by to officially
resign.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize, you're a good
man Tommy.
- No I'm not.
- Yes you are.
You risked everything
for that little girl.
You loved her
and you cared for her all
the way until the end,
even though you knew she
wasn't your daughter.
I saw the test results.
That test means nothing to me.
She will always be my daughter,
always.
So what's the next chapter
of your life look like Tommy
Colston?
I don't know.
(BRIGHT MUSIC)
Hey bud, how are you doing?
How you doing?
- Huh?
- Good.
Ready, one, two, three.
Ta-da!
There you go.
TOMMY: Good job!
♪ The sound of laughter in the
house ♪
♪ Light the fire gather around ♪
♪ Join together sing it loud ♪
♪ Raise the glass and joyful be ♪
♪ Hold the last word family ♪
♪ Ooh ooh oh oh ♪
(MID TEMPO MUSIC)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Farther along we'll ♪
♪ Know all about it ♪
♪ Farther along we'll understand
why ♪
♪ So cheer up my brothers ♪
♪ Live in the sunshine ♪
♪ We'll understand this ♪
♪ All by and by ♪
♪ Tempted and tried I wondered
why ♪
♪ The good man dies the bad man
thrives ♪
♪ And Jesus cries because
he loves em' both ♪
♪ We're all cast-aways in need
of ropes ♪
♪ Hangin' on by the last
threads of our hope ♪
♪ In a house of mirrors full of
smoke ♪
♪ Confusing illusions I've seen ♪
♪ Where did I go wrong I sang
along ♪
♪ To every chorus of the song ♪
♪ That the devil wrote
like a piper at the gates ♪
♪ Leading mice and men
down to their fates ♪
♪ Some will courageously escape ♪
♪ The seductive voice
with a heart of faith ♪
♪ While walkin' that line back
home ♪
♪ There's so much more to
life than we've been told ♪
♪ It's full of beauty that will
unfold ♪
♪ And shine like you struck
gold my wayward son ♪
♪ That dead weight burden weighs
a ton ♪
♪ I go down to the river and let
it run ♪
♪ Wash away all the things
you've done ♪
♪ Forgiveness alright ♪
♪ Farther along we'll ♪
♪ Know all about it ♪
♪ Farther along we'll understand
why ♪
♪ So cheer up my brothers ♪
♪ Live in the sunshine ♪
♪ We'll understand this ♪
♪ All by and by oh yeah ♪
♪ La la la la ♪
♪ But still I get hard
pressed on every side ♪
♪ Between the rock and a
compromise ♪
♪ Like truth and pack of
lies fightin' for my soul ♪
♪ I've got no place left go ♪
♪ 'Cause I got changed
by what I've been shown ♪
♪ It's more glory than
the world has known ♪
♪ Keeps me ramblin' on ♪
♪ Skipping like a calf
loosed from its stall ♪
♪ I'm free to love once and for
all ♪
♪ And even when I fall I'll get
back up ♪
♪ For the joy that overflows my
cup ♪
♪ Heaven filled me with more
than enough ♪
♪ Broke down my levees and my
bluff ♪
♪ Let the flood wash me ♪
♪ And one day when the
sky rolls back on us ♪
♪ Some rejoice and the others
fuss ♪
♪ 'Cause every knee must
bow and tongue confess ♪
♪ The son of God is forever
blessed ♪
♪ This is the kingdom
and we're the guests ♪
♪ So put your voice up to the
test ♪
♪ Sing Lord come soon oh yeah ♪
♪ Farther along we'll ♪
♪ Know all about it ♪
♪ Farther along we'll understand
why ♪
♪ So cheer up my brothers ♪
♪ Live in the sunshine ♪
♪ We'll understand this ♪
♪ All by and by ♪