HE'S Q ( footsteps echoing )
( thunder rumbling )
( truck horn blaring )
LET'S REVIEW THE MOTION FOR THE INSANITY PLEA
ON THE BASIS OF THE PREVIOUS TESTIMONY.
Attorney: IT'S ALL IN THE FILE, YOUR HONOR.
ACUTE PARANOIA, SCHIZOPHRENIA.
MY CLIENT DOESN'T EVEN REMEMBER
COMMITTING THE CRIME IN QUESTION.
EVEN A POLYGRAPH PROVED THAT.
- OBJECTION, YOUR HONOR. INADMISSIBLE. - SUSTAINED.
WE ALL KNOW EVEN POLYGRAPHS LIE.
THANKS FOR THAT PIECE OF INFORMATION. APPRECIATE IT.
IN ANY STAGE, YOUR HONOR,
I DON'T KNOW HOW RELEVANT
MR. McNAMARA'S SO-CALLED ECHO PET SCAN ANALYSIS
- IS GONNA BE. - I CAN MAKE IT VERY RELEVANT,
IF COUNSEL WILL JUST GIVE ME AN OPPORTUNITY TO STEP UP.
- STEP UP. - THANK YOU.
THE DEFENDANT DID, INDEED, MURDER STACY SMITH.
THE ONLY QUESTION IS,
WAS HE INSANE AT THE TIME?
I CALL DR. LAZARRE.
HELLO, DOCTOR. YOU KNOW THE PROCEDURE.
YOU GOT FIVE MINUTES.
HELLO, JONAS.
FINALLY GETTING TO SEE ME.
THEY'RE SAYING IT'S HARDER FOR YOU SHRINKS TO GET INTO THIS PLACE
THAN IT IS FOR US SICK FUCKS TO GET OUT.
YET HERE YOU ARE.
INTRIGUING, ISN'T IT?
YOU WERE IN COURT.
YOU SAW THE EVIDENCE, YOU AND YOUR FANCY LAWYERS.
BUT THAT WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU.
HUH?
YOU STILL HAD TO COME HERE AND SQUEEZE IT OUT OF ME.
DO YOU FEEL ANY REMORSE?
LET ME SEE. REMORSE.
I'M SORRY I CUT POOR SARAH LETTINGS INTO SO MANY PIECES,
BUT THE BITCH HAD IT COMING, I SWEAR.
MAN, SHE HAD A BEAUTIFUL SCREAM.
IT'S A SHAME.
YOU HAVE DOUBTS, DON'T YOU?
BIG FUCKING DOUBTS.
BUT NOT ME. NOT WHERE I'M GOING.
THERE WAS A SEAT WAITING FOR ME
DOWN IN HELL THE MINUTE I WAS BORN, DOC.
ME, MY LIFE...
WOMEN, DEATH.
THIS PLACE, THESE CHAINS.
ALL PREAMBLE. 35 YEARS OF PURGATORY
JUST TO SEE HOW MANY POOR SOULS
I CAN DRAG DOWN WITH ME.
I'M GOING TO THE SHOW NOW,
AND YOU CAN'T TOUCH ME THERE.
NOBODY CAN.
BUT YOU.
YOU'RE STUCK HERE WITH YOUR MISERABLE DOUBTS.
( Jonas sighs )
I KNOW WHY YOU CAME HERE.
I CAN SEE RIGHT THROUGH YOU.
SOMETHING... SOMETHING IS EATING YOU ALIVE.
WHAT ARE YOU GETTING AT?
YOU'RE NOT HERE TO SAVE ME.
YOU'RE HERE TO SAVE YOURSELF.
YOU'RE HERE TO SAVE YOURSELF!
- PLEASE... - YOU'RE HERE TO SAVE YOURSELF!
JUST GIVE ME ONE MORE MINUTE.
JONAS!
SHH!
I'M NOT GONNA HURT YOU.
IAN, LOOK INSIDE YOURSELF.
JUST LIKE OLD TIMES, EH, BUDDY? JUST LIKE OLD TIMES.
THE AMERICAN JUSTICE SYSTEM! WHOO!
KNOCK OFF ALL THE CRAZIES. LOCK 'EM UP.
YOU SET ME UP.
TURNSTILE TO NOWHERE SYSTEM.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
NOTHIN'. YOU SUMMED IT UP PERFECTLY.
YOU'VE BEEN KEEPING AN AWFUL LOT TO YOURSELF LATELY.
YOU ALL RIGHT? YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, I'M FINE. - YOU'RE FINE? YOU'RE SURE?
- I SAID I'M FINE. - ALL RIGHT, HE'S FINE.
COUNSELOR, GENTLEMEN, WHAT'LL IT BE?
MARTINI EXTRA DRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT? WHY DON'T YOU MAKE THAT TWO?
ONE FOR MY OLD PAL HERE. THE DOC, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU SAY? ONE FOR OLD TIME'S SAKE?
JUST COFFEE.
STIRRED OR SHAKEN?
( imitates James Bond ) SHAKEN, NOT STIRRED.
I'M SORRY YOU LOST YOUR GRANT.
TERESA TOLD ME.
I KNOW HOW MUCH THAT RESEARCH MEANT TO YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
SOMEBODY UP THERE ON THAT BOARD...
- MARTY. - DOESN'T LIKE ME.
COUNSELOR, YOUR DRINK.
I'D LIKE TO CHANGE MY ORDER.
SCOTCH, DOUBLE.
I WANNA MAKE A TOAST
TO ALL THE THINGS THAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN.
COME ON, JOE.
- FOR OLD TIME'S SAKE. - WHY DON'T WE DO THIS TOMORROW?
I GOTTA GET BACK TO THE OFFICE.
YOU ALWAYS GOT WHAT YOU WANTED,
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES TO WOMEN.
DON'T START WITH THAT, IAN.
DON'T YOU START WITH THAT.
DON'T START WITH THAT.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT. DON'T START, DON'T START.
DON'T START ANYTHING AGAIN.
- DON'T START... - I'M YOUR FRIEND.
- I WANNA HELP YOU. - I DON'T WANT ANY HELP.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I DON'T WANT ANY FUCKIN' HELP.
WHAT DO YOU WANT? WHAT, WHAT?
TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT.
I WANT TO BELIEVE IN SOMETHING.
IAN, WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I GOTTA GO.
I KNOW WHERE YOU'RE GOIN'.
I'M NOT GOIN' THERE.
Woman: I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE IT'S JUST ME.
MAYBE SOME PEOPLE ARE JUST BORN BROKEN.
BUT I'M NOT CRAZY, AND I DIDN'T TRY TO KILL MYSELF
TO GET ATTENTION OR TO MAKE A POINT.
I JUST WANTED TO FEEL BETTER.
I'M SICK OF EVERYBODY TELLING ME TO JUST GET OUT OF BED
AND DO SOMETHING FOR MYSELF.
IT'S LIKE, ALL OF A SUDDEN,
I'M JUST GONNA BE HAPPY. MY TROUBLES WILL JUST GO AWAY.
HOW CAN THEY SAY THAT WHEN THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT IT FEELS LIKE?
COULD YOU TELL ME WHAT THE PAIN IS,
OR WHERE IT COMES FROM?
I DON'T KNOW WHERE IT COMES FROM.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S PHYSICAL PAIN.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE SOMEONE'S STEPPING ON MY FOOT ALL THE TIME.
IT'S THE KIND OF PAIN YOU FEEL LIKE,
WHEN YOU'RE A KID, AND YOU'RE SCARED OF THE DARK,
AND YOUR MOM MAKES YOU SLEEP WITH THE LIGHTS OFF
SO YOU'LL GET OVER IT.
SO YOU LIE AWAKE IN THE DARK,
JUST TERRIFIED OF THINGS YOU CAN'T SEE,
BUT TOO SCARED OF YOUR PARENTS
TO JUST TURN THE LIGHTS ON.
SO YOU STAY AWAKE THE WHOLE NIGHT,
WAITING FOR THE SUN TO COME UP,
HOPING YOUR MOM'S GONNA COME IN AND CHECK ON YOU.
IT'S HARD FOR ME TO EXPLAIN IT.
IT'S LIKE... IT'S LIKE THE SUN NEVER CAME UP,
AND NOBODY EVER CAME BACK FOR ME.
SO I'M JUST STUCK WHERE I AM.
IS IT SO UNREASONABLE TO THINK THAT, AT SOME POINT,
SOMEBODY WOULD GET SO TIRED OF BEING THAT WAY
THAT THEY WOULD JUST WANNA END IT?
I SAW A MOVIE ONCE WHERE A PERSON SAID,
"YOU CAN'T CHANGE A BAD HAND OF CARDS.
SOMETIMES, YOU JUST HAVE TO FOLD."
HEY, HEY, HEY. COME ON, COME ON, CUT THAT OUT.
YOU GUYS CAN FAWN ALL OVER EACH OTHER LATER.
THIS GUY MICHELSON, HE'S GOT SO MUCH MONEY.
YOU GUYS, COME ON, IT'S GETTING LATE.
NO! NO, NO, NO, NO. YOU CAN'T GO. YOU JUST GOT HERE.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S OKAY. YOU STAY. I UNDERSTAND.
BUT I'M TIRED, SO I'M GOING HOME, OKAY?
THANK YOU.
SEE YOU LATER.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY TO DRIVE?
( all laughing )
YEAH, I'M FINE, I'M FINE.
I'M A BIG GIRL. SEE YA LATER.
- BYE, JOE. - BYE, WENDY.
I'M SORRY. JUST EXCUSE ME FOR ONE SECOND, OKAY?
STARTING KINDA EARLY, AREN'T YOU, DOC?
WENDY!!
HELENE... CANCEL ALL...
APPOINTMENTS FOR THIS AFTERNOON.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY APPOINTMENTS THIS AFTERNOON, DOCTOR.
( phone ringing )
TERESA LAZARRE'S OFFICE. THIS IS ANNA SPEAKING.
YES, HELLO. MAY I SPEAK WITH MY WIFE, PLEASE?
TERESA, IT'S IAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT? TELL HIM I'M NOT HERE.
IAN, SHE DOESN'T WANNA TALK TO YOU, OKAY?
- JUST ASK HER TO COME TO THE PHONE. - NO, IAN.
I DON'T WANNA TALK TO YOU. I WANNA TALK TO MY WIFE.
DON'T YELL, IAN.
- DON'T FUCKING HANG UP ON ME! - ( glass shatters )
PUT MY GODDAMN WIFE ON THE PHONE, GODDAMN YOU!
DOCTOR?
JOE, THESE ARE READY FOR YOUR SIGNATURE.
AND DR. IAN LAZARRE'S OFFICE IS ON LINE TWO.
SOUNDS IMPORTANT.
YEAH, HELENE, HI. IT'S JOE.
ALL RIGHT, CALL HIS EX-WIFE.
JOE, YOU HAVE A MEETING WITH KRAVITZ IN TEN MINUTES.
STALL HIM, ROSIE.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHO ELSE TO CALL. THERE WAS THIS BIG CRASH.
DOES HE HAVE ANY EXTRA KEYS?
- WHAT? - KEYS, GODDAMN IT. KEYS!
I DON'T KNOW. HE NEVER GAVE ME ANY.
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
JESUS CHRIST.
HE'S IN MY HEAD.
HE'S IN MY HEAD!
GET AN AMBULANCE.
JONAS IS IN MY HEAD AGAIN.
- OH, JONAS... - WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
HE'S IN MY HEAD AGAIN, JOE.
JESUS CHRIST.
JONAS IS IN MY HEAD AGAIN.
JONAS KELLAR IS DEAD. HE'S DEAD AND BURIED.
HE TOLD ME. HE SAID IF I CLOSED MY EYES...
YOU GOTTA LEAVE IT ALONE.
I'M ALL ALONE.
HELENE, GET IN HERE.
HELENE, YOU CAN TAKE THE DAY OFF.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M DR. TOBIAS.
I ASSUME YOU'RE WITH MR. LAZARRE.
YEAH. HE OKAY?
HE HAS A DEEP LACERATION ON HIS LEFT FOREARM,
SOME SELF-INFLICTED CUTS, AND HE'S LOST A LOT OF BLOOD.
HE'S STABILIZED NOW, THOUGH.
Woman on P.A.: DR. TOBIAS, YOU'RE WANTED IN I.C.U.
HE WRITES HIS OWN PRESCRIPTIONS, DOESN'T HE?
- YEAH. - IT'S NOT GOOD.
YOUR FRIEND NEEDS HELP.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, HE'S OKAY.
HE GOT A LITTLE TOO DRUNK, CUT HIMSELF.
THAT'S ALL THEY TOLD ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT HE'S GOING TO SAY, DON'T YOU?
HE'S GONNA SAY IT'S MY FAULT
BECAUSE I WOULDN'T GO BACK TO HIM.
IT'S EXACTLY WHAT HE'S GONNA SAY.
I CAN'T TAKE ANY MORE OF THIS, JOE.
HE EXPECTS ME TO ALWAYS BE THERE FOR HIM WHEN HE HITS THE BOTTOM,
AND I JUST CAN'T DO IT ANYMORE.
LOOK, TERESA, MAYBE IT'S BEST THIS HAPPENED.
HE'LL LISTEN TO YOU THIS TIME.
MAYBE I DON'T WANT HIM TO LISTEN.
MAYBE I JUST WANT HIM OUT OF MY LIFE.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO FIND HIM SOME HELP.
MAYBE PUT HIM SOMEPLACE WHERE HE CAN GET BETTER.
IF IT'S EASIER ON YOU, I'LL DRAW UP
POWER OF ATTORNEY DOCUMENTS.
HE'LL JUST RUN CIRCLES AROUND REHAB. WE BOTH KNOW THAT.
THERE'S A PLACE.
I KNOW THIS PLACE, IT'S VERY SPECIAL.
WE'VE GOTTA HELP HIM.
ALL RIGHT. WHATEVER YOU THINK'S BEST.
( monitor beeping steadily )
OH, IAN. WHAT HAVE YOU DONE NOW?
IT CAN'T GO ON LIKE THIS.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
( inhales sharply )
YOU HAVE TO JUST GO AND BE THE LIFE OF THE PARTY.
LISTEN, HONEY, JOE AND I WERE TALKING,
AND WE FOUND A PLACE FOR YOU TO GO.
YOU KNOW, TO GET BETTER.
AND ONCE YOU'RE BETTER, THEN...
LISTEN, I KNOW THAT YOU'RE TIRED, SO I'M GONNA GO.
TRY TO GET SOME REST, OKAY?
TRY NOT TO THINK SO MUCH.
YOU ALWAYS THINK SO MUCH.
TERESA.
IS THAT MR. LAZARRE? - YES. I'M JOE McNAMARA.
I'M RACQUEL CHAMBERS, AND THIS IS JAMES.
- JAMES. - JOE.
THIS IS MRS. LAZARRE.
IT LOOKS LIKE MR. LAZARRE IS A VERY LUCKY MAN
TO HAVE A WIFE WHO CARES SO MUCH.
- SHALL WE? - OH, LET ME.
IT'S OKAY. I GOT IT NOW.
WE'RE GONNA CALL YOU IN A COUPLE OF DAYS,
AND TELL YOU HOW HE'S DOING.
HE'S GOING TO NEED SOME TIME ALONE.
MR. LAZARRE. I'M JAMES.
WELCOME TO BLACKHURST.
WE'RE GONNA GO INSIDE NOW.
THERE'S NO VISITING FOR THE FIRST WEEK,
THEN ONCE A WEEK FOR AN HOUR AFTER THAT.
AND THERE WILL BE NO PHONE CALLS FOR THE FIRST THREE WEEKS.
BYE NOW.
THAT'S IT.
Racquel: HELLO, MR. LAZARRE.
DID YOU HAVE A NICE TRIP?
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE A WONDERFUL TIME HERE AT BLACKHURST.
JUST RELAX.
I FEEL LIKE WE JUST COMMITTED HIM.
IAN, I'M GOING TO GO AND GET YOUR CHART AND THE KEY.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- YOU WON'T NEED THESE. - TAKE IT EASY.
THIS.
MY WATCH?
YES, THAT GOES. AND THIS.
AND THIS.
JAMES.
MY WATCH?
WELL, IAN, SOME PATIENTS, THEY USE THE SHARP EDGES
TO SLASH THEIR WRISTS.
TIME'S A KILLER.
SWISS WATCHES SEEM TO WORK THE BEST.
- JAMES? - YES.
HERE WE GO, IAN. YOUR NEW HOME.
WELL, NICE AND CLEAN. NO SHARP EDGES.
THIS ROOM NEEDS CURTAINS.
YOUR SHOES.
LOG HIM IN.
HERE WE GO, IAN.
IAN, WILL YOU GIVE ME YOUR HAND?
THANK YOU.
IAN, CAN YOU MAKE A FIST FOR ME?
THANK YOU, JAMES.
WHAT IS IT?
YOU CAN TELL ME. I'M A DOCTOR.
I LIKE DOCTORS.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN A NURSE?
OH, I'M NOT A NURSE.
I JUST LIKE WEARING THE UNIFORM.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE.
NOW YOU JUST RELAX.
IT'S ONLY A SEDATIVE.
DIAZEPAM?
PROMAZINE?
MORPHINE?
- SHH. - I'D LIKE SOME MORPHINE.
SH.
I'M SCARED.
LET ME OUTTA HERE!
LET ME OUT OF HERE!!
OH, LET ME OUT OF HERE!
PLEASE LET ME OUT OF HERE!
LET ME OUT OF HERE!
TAKE THESE OFF.
NOW JUST TAKE IT EASY, SWEETIE.
YOU'RE OVER THE WORST OF IT. YOU GAVE US A SCARE, THOUGH.
WE DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE GOING TO MAKE IT.
WHO AUTHORIZED RESTRAINING?
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO RESTRAIN PATIENTS IN DETOX.
I COULD'VE BEEN ASPHYXIATED.
LISTEN TO ME. IT TOOK SIX MEN
JUST TO KEEP YOU FROM TEARING OUT YOUR OWN STITCHES.
ARE YOU READY TO GET UP?
DOCTOR WANTS TO SEE YOU SOON.
COME ON, IAN, LET'S GO.
- HOW LONG HAVE I BEEN ASLEEP? - THREE DAYS. COME ON.
- UP WE GO. - THREE DAYS?
WHAT IS IT?
THOSE ARE NASTY.
IAN, YOU WERE CONVULSING,
AND THE DOCTOR TOLD US TO TIE YOU DOWN.
WHO'S IN CHARGE HERE?
- IAN, JUST CALM DOWN. - WHO'S THE DOCTOR?
DR. RENQUIST IS YOUR DOCTOR,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO SEE HIM SOON. THEY ALL DO EVENTUALLY.
THE VERNON RENQUIST?
THERE. ALL BETTER.
IAN, YOUR WIFE, SHE'S VERY PRETTY.
MY WIFE'S DEAD.
THERE. THAT'S BETTER, ISN'T IT?
JAMES IS GONNA TAKE YOU TO THE CAFETERIA,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO EAT SOMETHING.
I WILL SEE YOU LATER.
WHAT ARE YOU IN FOR?
SORRY. BAD JOKE. WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
IT'S A VERY NICE DAY, ISN'T IT?
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN HERE?
TWENTY WEEKS.
TWENTY WEEKS. THAT'S A LONG TIME FOR DETOX.
WHAT KIND OF THERAPY...
ARE YOU DOING? INDIVIDUAL OR GROUP?
WHAT HAVE THEY GOT YOU ON?
PROZAC OR RITALIN?
DOC, THE RULES ARE, YOU GOTTA EAT.
YOU SAYIN' YOU'RE NOT GONNA EAT?
OW. THAT HURTS.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'? - COME ON WITH ME.
WHO'S YOUR SUPERVISOR?
( keys jingling )
ARE YA HUNGRY?
YEAH.
STAY RIGHT THERE.
( thunder rumbling )
WENDY, WENDY.
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE NEEDING THIS ABOUT NOW.
THANK YOU.
HE'S VERY STRONG.
HOW MUCH SEDATIVE DID HE SEE YOU ADMINISTER?
IT WAS 25 MILLIGRAMS OR SO.
HE THOUGHT IT WAS CHLORPROMAZINE OR SOMETHING.
DID YOU TELL HIM WHAT IT REALLY WAS?
NO.
WENDY.
HE KEEPS CALLING FOR WENDY.
- WHO IS SHE? - HIS FIRST WIFE.
TRAGICALLY KILLED IN A D.U.I. ACCIDENT.
HE MUST HAVE LOVED HER VERY MUCH.
APPARENTLY SO.
YOU KNOW, I THINK HE'S BEGINNING TO LIKE YOU.
WON'T BE LONG NOW BEFORE YOU'RE PART OF HIS DREAMS.
ISN'T IT TIME THAT YOU TOLD HIM?
TOLD HIM WHAT? THAT HIS DREAMS AREN'T REAL?
THAT'S HIS ONLY LINK TO SANITY.
IF HE KNEW WHAT WAS IN THAT SYRINGE,
HIS WHOLE WORLD WOULD COLLAPSE.
HE'D REMEMBER TO LIE.
WE'D LOSE HIM, HE'D BE GONE.
NO.
LET HIM KNOW THAT YOU'RE UPPING THE DOSAGE.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK WILL BECOME OF HIM?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE SEEMS TO BE SEEKING SOME KIND OF TRUTH
IN HIS HEAD.
HE MAY BE CLOSE TO AN ANSWER.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND OF PEACE HE'S GONNA FIND
WHEN HE FINALLY GETS THERE, IF EVER.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
( thunder rumbling )
( phone ringing )
( ringing continues )
IAN, IT'S FOR YOU. IT'S YOUR WIFE.
CAN YOU IDENTIFY THE BODY, SIR?
WHY ASK HIM? BODY'S BURNT BEYOND RECOGNITION.
EVEN THE CORONER HAD A DIFFICULT TIME
MATCHING UP THE DENTAL RECORDS.
- MR. LAZARRE? - YOU OKAY TO DRIVE, DOCTOR?
DOCTOR?
( water running in toilet )
HEY!
HEY, THIS AREA'S OFF LIMITS.
- I WANNA USE THE TELEPHONE. - COME WITH ME!
- GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME! - COME ON!
LET GO OF ME!
WHAT SEEMS TO BE THE PROBLEM?
DR. RENQUIST.
YES,
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE A CALL.
I JUST WANTED TO CALL SOMEBODY.
YOU WANT TO LEAVE US, DON'T YOU?
NO.
I JUST WANNA CALL SOMEONE.
WELL, THERE'S A TELEPHONE.
YOU WANT TO USE IT? GO AHEAD. USE IT.
GO AHEAD.
- GO AHEAD. - I UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
IT'S REVERSE PSYCHOLOGY 101.
GO AHEAD. USE THE TELEPHONE.
STEP OUT OF LINE, AND WE PUNISH YOU. IT'S VERY SIMPLE.
WE HAVE A "THREE STRIKES, YOU'RE OUT" RULE, IAN.
ONLY HERE, OUT MEANS IN.
YOU STAY IN FOR AS LONG AS IT TAKES.
DO I MAKE MYSELF CLEAR?
THIS ISN'T REHAB.
YOU DON'T HAVE THE RIGHT TO COMMIT ME.
REALLY?
I'LL HAVE TO SEE ABOUT THAT.
James: IT'S OKAY. IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
GOOD EVENING. CAN I GET YOU A DRINK BEFORE DINNER?
COFFEE.
SAME FOR ME.
SO HAVE YOU TALKED TO IAN? IT'S BEEN A WEEK.
I'M SURE HE'S FINE.
HE'S A FIGHTER. HE'LL MAKE IT.
IF HE DOESN'T...
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, IF HE DOESN'T?
I DIDN'T WANNA UPSET YOU,
BUT I THINK YOU OUGHTA KNOW.
I GOT A CALL FROM IAN'S DOCTOR, DR. RENQUIST.
HIS RECOVERY'S NOT GOING VERY WELL.
- APPARENTLY, THERE'S SOME PROBLEMS. - WHAT KIND OF PROBLEMS?
NOTHING SERIOUS. NOT YET. IT'S JUST...
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT? JUST SPIT IT OUT.
LOOK, TERESA,
I THINK YOU'VE GOTTA EXPECT THE WORST.
IF HIS REHAB ISN'T SUCCESSFUL,
THEY'RE GONNA HAVE TO TAKE THE TREATMENT TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN? - NONE OF US WANTS THAT TO HAPPEN.
AS YOUR FRIEND,
AS IAN'S BEST FRIEND, AND HIS APPOINTED LAWYER,
WE GOTTA START THINKING ABOUT OUR RESPONSIBILITIES,
LEGAL AND OTHERWISE, TO IAN.
GREAT.
SO, JOE, CAN I BUY YOU A DRINK?
YEAH.
WELL, GOOD MORNING, IAN.
HOW ARE YOU THIS MORNING?
NOT TOO GOOD.
I'M SORRY TO HEAR THAT.
THANK YOU, JAMES.
IS THAT FOR ME? THAT'S VERY THOUGHTFUL.
DR. RENQUIST SAID THAT YOU WERE FEELING A LITTLE ANXIOUS EARLIER,
AND THAT WE SHOULD GIVE YOU SOMETHING TO HELP YOU SLEEP.
THAT'S VERY PROFESSIONAL.
DID YOU EVER THINK OF WORKING FOR A PRIVATE PRACTICE?
- IS THAT A PROPOSITION? - NO.
LAY DOWN.
AND RELAX.
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
OKAY, IAN.
WHAT'S IT LIKE WORKING FOR DR. RENQUIST?
OH, HE'S A WONDERFUL MAN. A WONDERFUL MAN.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE YOU'D BE WITHOUT HIM.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT HIS RESEARCH?
HE HELPS PEOPLE LIKE YOU.
- HE HELPS PEOPLE. - YES.
PEOPLE WITH PROBLEMS,
AND SECRETS,
AND PEOPLE WHO CAN'T SLEEP.
HOW DO YOU KNOW I CAN'T SLEEP?
WELL, UH...
IAN, I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU THIS SHOT,
AND YOU'RE GONNA FEEL... YOU'RE GONNA FEEL BETTER.
WHAT'S IN IT? WHAT IS IT?
I AM A DOCTOR. I CAN TAKE IT.
I KNOW THAT YOU CAN.
- TELL ME WHAT IT IS. - I KNOW YOU CAN.
I CAN'T CLOSE MY EYES.
THANK YOU, JAMES.
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
OKAY, IAN.
WHAT'S IT LIKE WORKING FOR DR. RENQUIST?
WELL, HE'S A WONDERFUL MAN. A WONDERFUL MAN.
JONAS, PLEASE.
PLEASE.
GET ME OUT OF HERE!
ARE YOU FEELING A LITTLE LESS ANXIOUS?
HMM?
YOU LIKE PEOPLE TO FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.
DON'T YOU?
BUT THERE AREN'T ENOUGH PEOPLE WHO DO.
YOUR WIFE DOESN'T.
DOES SHE? NOT LIKE THIS.
WHAT'S IT GONNA BE?
YOU WANNA STAY IN, OR YOU WANNA STAY OUT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
NO, IAN, THE QUESTION IS,
HELP.
- HELP YOURSELF FOR ONCE. - PLEASE.
GET ME OUT OF HERE.
( voice echoes )
GOOD MORNING, IAN. HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
SWEET DREAMS?
NO.
OH, I'M SORRY.
WELL, THE GOOD NEWS IS,
THAT THE WEEK IS UP, AND YOU HAVE VISITORS.
THEY'RE WAITING FOR YOU IN THE CAFETERIA.
THIS WAY.
SO, IAN, THEY'RE ALL WAITING FOR YOU.
TERESA AND JOE.
NOW, IAN, YOU STAY HERE. I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
SHALL WE?
AFTER YOU.
( no audible dialogue )
YOU HAVE 15 MINUTES.
JOE SPOKE WITH DR. RENQUIST YESTERDAY ON THE TELEPHONE.
HE FELT IT WOULD BE NICE IF WE CAME UP FOR A VISIT
TO SEE HOW YOU'RE DOING.
HOW DO I LOOK?
LOOK, WHY DON'T YOU GUYS TALK?
I'LL BE BACK IN A WHILE.
HE'S CONCERNED ABOUT YOU.
- YOU SCARED HIM PRETTY BADLY. - DID I?
SIT DOWN.
YEAH, AND ME, TOO.
TERESA, I--
PLEASE. DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
YOU NEED HELP.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO SAY.
ALL THESE YEARS,
TREATING PEOPLE.
LECTURING OTHER PSYCHIATRISTS
ON HOW TO TREAT PEOPLE.
OH! LOOK AT ME. LOOK AT ME. DID I DO THIS?
IAN, PLEASE STOP.
LOOK AT ME. ALL THE GRANTS, THE FELLOWSHIPS,
THE RESEARCH, EVERYTHING.
I'M WORSE NOW THAN WHEN I STARTED.
I CAN'T EVEN HELP MYSELF.
NO ONE EXPECTS YOU TO.
LOOK AT ME.
I CAN'T EVEN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HERE.
JUST LET THEM HELP YOU.
I WANNA GO HOME.
I DON'T BELONG HERE.
TERESA, I'M SCARED OF THIS PLACE.
IT CAN BE BETTER. I DON'T WANNA BE SICK.
I DON'T WANNA DRINK ANYMORE.
LISTEN TO ME. IT WILL BE BETTER.
GOD, IAN. LISTEN TO YOURSELF.
DO YOU EVEN HEAR WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
YOU DON'T EVEN REALIZE YOU HAVE A PROBLEM, DO YOU?
WE HAVE TO GO.
I DON'T WANNA BE ALONE.
I CAN'T STAND BEING ALONE.
IAN, PLEASE.
FINISH WHAT YOU STARTED.
- PROMISE ME ONE THING. - WHAT?
WILL YOU BE THERE WHEN I GET OUT?
I DON'T KNOW.
WE'LL SEE.
QUITE A PLACE, IAN.
KILLER NURSING STAFF.
JOE, WE HAVE TO GO. IT'S GETTING LATE.
- IS SHE OKAY? - I DON'T KNOW.
LISTEN, I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT ALL THIS, BUDDY,
BUT TERESA INSISTED SHE KNEW WHAT WAS BEST FOR YOU.
I TOLD HER THAT I THOUGHT YOU COULD SOBER UP FINE BY YOURSELF,
BUT SHE SAID THIS WAS GONNA BE GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU'VE GOTTA GET ME OUT OF HERE.
JOE, YOU GOT TO GET ME THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
I WILL, I WILL. NO PROBLEM, NO PROBLEM.
HEY, YOU NEED ANYTHING, YOU CALL ME, ALL RIGHT?
TAKE CARE OF TERESA, WILL YOU?
I WILL.
I'LL SEE YA, ALL RIGHT?
WELCOME, IAN.
HOW DO YOU FEEL TODAY?
WELL, LET'S SEE.
ACUTE WITHDRAWAL, AND ASSOCIATED SYMPTOMS
OF DETOXIFICATION SUBSIDED ABOUT A WEEK AGO.
THE ONSET OF CHEMICAL DEPRESSION
TOOK PLACE SHORTLY THEREAFTER,
AND OCCASIONAL BOUTS WITH NAUSEA,
WHICH WAS TO BE EXPECTED.
PAIN IN MY KIDNEYS FROM THE JUNK THAT YOU'VE BEEN GIVING ME.
OTHER THAN THAT, I'M ON TOP OF THE FUCKING WORLD.
GOOD. I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE EXPECTED THAT
FROM A DOCTOR WITH YOUR BACKGROUND AND QUALIFICATIONS.
HOW ARE YOUR SPIRITS, IAN?
MY SPIRITS?
MY SPIRITS.
IS THAT A FUCKIN' JOKE?
YOU WANT ME TO LAY DOWN ON THE TABLE,
AND TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT?
I'M SURE YOU WILL.
HOW DID YOUR FIRST WIFE DIE?
NO. I DON'T WANT TO GET INTO THIS FUCKING GAME.
YOU KNOW THAT I'M ALL CLEANED UP.
I DON'T HAVE TO BE HERE.
LOOK, I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP YOU.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR YOU TO BE SO DEFENSIVE.
WE'RE ALL FRIENDS HERE.
OH, YEAH, WE'RE ALL JUST ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY.
DON'T YOU THINK I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
I'VE TREATED ADDICTS FOR YEARS.
ONE THING I KNOW IS YOU DON'T RESTRAIN OR PHYSICALLY ABUSE
PATIENTS IN REHAB.
NOW LET'S CUT THE SHIT. CALL MY WIFE AND TELL HER
TO GET ME THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
PERHAPS YOU'RE HAVING A LITTLE TROUBLE UNDERSTANDING
WHAT WE'RE ALL ABOUT HERE AT BLACKHURST.
HELL, SHIT, I AM.
YOU'RE A VERY SPECIAL CASE, IAN,
AND FOR REASONS THAT MIGHT EVEN SURPRISE YOU.
YOU KNOW, YOU THINK TOO MUCH.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S ASSUME THAT YOU GO BACK HOME.
EVERYTHING'S BACK TO NORMAL.
THEN EVENTUALLY, YOU'LL GO OUT TO DINNER,
THE WAITER WILL ASK YOU WHAT YOU WANT TO DRINK.
AND AT THAT MOMENT, YOU WILL HAVE YOUR DOUBTS.
- BULLSHIT. - THEY ALL DO.
AND YOU'LL SAY NO,
BECAUSE YOU FEEL SO CONFIDENT ABOUT YOURSELF.
AND EVERYONE WILL SAY, OH, GOOD OLD IAN.
HE'S FINALLY CLEANED UP HIS ACT.
YES, IAN, YOU THINK YOU'VE BEATEN IT.
BUT THE TRUTH IS, THE CLOCK IS TICKING.
YES, THE FUSE IS BURNING.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE THAT DRINK SOME TIME.
YES, YOU KNOW IT'S INEVITABLE.
BECAUSE YOU STILL HAVEN'T FOUND WHERE THE TRUTH LIES.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
SO I'VE GOT A DRINKING PROBLEM.
PEOPLE HAVE PROBLEMS.
BUT MINE IS NOT A NEUROLOGICAL OR A BIOLOGICAL DISORDER
THAT NEEDS SOME GODDAMN DRUG.
I AM NOT A MENTAL PATIENT.
AND YOU CAN'T KEEP ME HERE!
NO, I'M NOT CRAZY.
I'M NOT CRAZY.
- I'M NOT CRAZY. - ALL RIGHT, IAN, JUST RELAX.
I'M NOT CRAZY. I'M NOT CRAZY.
I'M NOT CRAZY. OH, GOD!
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN GOOD. YOU'LL SEE.
( Ian weeping )
WHAT IS THAT? WHAT IS IT? WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S WHATEVER YOU WANT IT TO BE. - NO!!
OH, I'M NOT CRAZY!
I'M NOT CRAZY.
Joe: JUST LIKE OLD TIMES, EH, BUDDY?
( maniacal laughter )
IAN, FRIENDS DON'T LET FRIENDS DRIVE DRUNK.
JUST LIKE OLD TIMES, EH, BUDDY?
SOME FRIEND.
YOU BIT YOUR TONGUE.
SHE KNEW HIM.
IT'S OKAY, IAN.
- SHE KNEW HIM. - JUST RELAX.
TELL US ABOUT YOUR DREAM, IAN.
YOU'RE BEGINNING TO UNDERSTAND, AREN'T YOU?
BEGINNING TO SEE THE TRUTH.
IT'S NOT WITHDRAWAL THAT YOU'RE SUFFERING FROM.
IT'S YOU.
IN HERE.
TRUST WHAT'S HAPPENING TO YOU, DON'T FIGHT IT.
( alarm blares )
RIGHT HERE.
SORRY, GUY. YOU ALL RIGHT?
THERE YOU GO.
LITTLE FOOTSIES IN HERE.
HUH? LET ME SEE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, IT'S OKAY.
THERE'S A WHOLE LOT GOIN' ON
IN THAT LITTLE BITTY MIND OF HIS.
JAMES, THAT'S ENOUGH NOW.
OKAY.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE OKAY.
YOU'RE GONNA GET BETTER SOON.
YES, YOU WILL.
YES, YOU'LL SEE.
YOU TRUST ME.
TRUST ME.
DOCTOR, I DON'T THINK THAT'S APPROPRIATE.
NOW, NIGHTY-NIGHT.
JOE, IT'S TERESA.
I MEAN, MRS. LAZARRE HERE TO SEE YOU.
SEND HER IN.
HI. THIS WAS A SURPRISE.
- JOE, LISTEN, WE NEED TO TALK. - WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IT'S ABOUT IAN. I NEED TO SEE HIM AGAIN.
YOU SURE THAT'S A GOOD IDEA?
YOU KNOW HOW FRAGILE HE IS.
SOMETHING IS NOT RIGHT. I KNOW HIM.
HE WOULDN'T GET LIKE THIS.
LOOK, TERESA, YOU'RE NOT BEING VERY OBJECTIVE.
DID YOU MEAN WHAT YOU SAID ABOUT THE POWER OF ATTORNEY?
ABOUT TAKING THE TREATMENT TO THE SECOND LEVEL?
LOOK, I DON'T WANNA DO THAT ANY MORE THAN YOU DO, BUT...
BUT?
LOOK, WHY DON'T WE TALK ABOUT IT TONIGHT?
I'LL COME OVER, OKAY?
FINE. I NEED TO SEE HIM.
YOU WILL, YOU WILL. WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT OVER DINNER.
OKAY.
JAMES, WOULD YOU GIVE US A SECOND, PLEASE?
ARE YOU SURE?
LOOK AT HIM. HE'S NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
IT'S OKAY.
WHERE DID RENQUIST FIND YOU?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ON THE STRIP?
TURNING TRICKS FOR A FIX.
IT'S OKAY.
IAN, I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN A CERTIFIED NURSE, ARE YOU?
ARE YOU?
IAN, LET US HELP YOU.
IF YOU WANNA HELP ME, YOU'LL HELP ME GET OUTTA HERE.
James: DINNERTIME. ARE YOU READY?
HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY.
( phone ringing )
HELLO.
HELLO?
WHO WAS IT?
I DON'T KNOW. PROBABLY A WRONG NUMBER.
UM, LISTEN, I HAVE AN EARLY DAY TOMORROW.
ALL RIGHT.
I JUST NEED TO GO OVER SOME POWER OF ATTORNEY DOCUMENTS FOR IAN.
- JOE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING? - COME ON, COME ON.
( phone ringing )
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME GET THIS?
- HELLO. - JOE?
WHO WAS IT?
OH, NOBODY. JUST A PRANK CALL.
STRIKE THREE, IAN.
LET ME OUTTA HERE!
YOU'RE SO CLOSE TO THE TRUTH.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
( truck horn blares )
JESUS CHRIST, LADY.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I'M FINE. SORRY.
I'M SORRY THAT YOU HAVE TO SEE HIM LIKE THIS.
OH, MY GOD, IAN.
- POOR GUY. - ( silence )
TERESA!
HE'S FIGHTING SOME KIND OF BATTLE IN HIS HEAD.
SOMETHING TO DO WITH THE DEATH OF HIS FIRST WIFE.
WENDY?
SHE WAS DRUNK. SHE DROVE HERSELF OFF THE ROAD.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
WELL, NOT IN YOUR HUSBAND'S MIND.
TERESA!!
HE'S SO AFRAID OF REALITY
THAT HE'S CONSTRUCTED A WHOLE PARADOXICAL DREAM WORLD
WHERE HE CAN PLAY OUT THE PAST.
IN OTHER WORDS, IT'S HOPELESS.
TERESA, PLEASE!
I DON'T KNOW, MR. McNAMARA.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
I'VE BEEN TREATING PATIENTS LIKE THIS FOR OVER 30 YEARS.
I STILL DON'T HAVE THE SLIGHTEST REASONABLE ANSWER.
HE'S FIGHTING THE TREATMENT.
HE'S FIGHTING FOR HIS LIFE.
- I'VE SEEN ENOUGH. - YOU OKAY?
YEAH. I'M FINE.
TERESA!
I CAN'T HELP YOU.
I'LL BE OUT IN A MINUTE.
I CAN'T HELP YOU, TERESA.
IAN.
IAN, GET INTO BED NOW. NOW, GET IN THERE.
COME ON. WHAT'S IN THERE?
WHAT'S IN THAT HEAD OF YOURS?
LET ME OUTTA HERE, RENQUIST!
LET ME OUTTA HERE!
LET ME OUT OF HERE!!
( Ian's voice echoing )
( wordless scream )
LET ME OUT OF HERE!
LET ME OUTTA HERE!
RENQUIST, LET ME OUT OF HERE!
WENDY.
YOUR WIFE WAS HERE TODAY.
YES, JUST TAKE IT EASY.
WENDY'S DEAD.
NOW, IAN, JUST TELL ME WHAT YOU SEE.
WELCOME TO NOWHERE.
I WANNA KNOW THE TRUTH.
I THOUGHT YOU CHANGED YOUR MIND.
CAN'T YOU SHOW ME?
WHEN THINGS GET BLACKEST,
AND YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE TO TURN...
REMEMBER, WHEN YOU CLOSE YOUR EYES,
ALL YOU HAVE IS YOURSELF.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING? - DON'T ASK, DON'T ASK.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT? - YEAH.
I ALMOST GOT MYSELF KILLED.
I RAN INTO THE TRUCK.
I MEAN, I ALMOST RAN INTO THE TRUCK.
I THINK I HAD TOO MUCH CHAMPAGNE.
- I KNOW. - ( both laughing )
BIT OF A RUSH, ISN'T IT?
NO.
NO. JOE!
DON'T!
NO.
JOE. DON'T.
STOP. JOE, DON'T!
( screams ) JOE, DON'T!
OH, NO, NO.
( screaming )
LOOK AT IT.
- NO! - ( bones snapping )
OH, NO.
WENDY.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
DON'T TELL ME THIS IS ONE OF MY DREAMS.
IAN, YOU PUT THAT NEEDLE DOWN.
THIS ISN'T GONNA SOLVE ANYTHING.
THIS ISN'T ONE OF MY DREAMS, IS IT?
NO.
THEN GIVE ME THE KEYS.
James: SHIT.
ORDERLY.
ORDERLY!
OPEN IT!
OPEN THE DOOR!
( pounding continues )
POOR GUY HAVIN' NIGHTMARES AGAIN, HUH?
WHY BOTHER? THAT MOTHERFUCKER IS CRAZY.
LET HIM ROT WITH THE REST OF 'EM.
COME ON.
ORDERLY! OPEN THE DOOR!
LET'S GO OUT THERE!
GEEZ, IAN.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'VE BEEN GIVING ME.
A NEUROLEPTIC?
AN ANTI-PSYCHOTIC?
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO GET ME OUT OF HERE.
IAN, LOOK, JUST GO BACK TO YOUR ROOM. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU'VE BEEN MAKING REAL PROGRESS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO RUIN EVERYTHING NOW.
I THOUGHT PERHAPS YOUR TREATMENT
WAS GONNA BRING ME THROUGH A DEPRESSION, AN OBSESSION.
BUT THE NIGHTMARES MADE IT CLEAR.
IAN, DON'T YOU SEE WHAT'S HAPPENED?
YOU'VE BECOME PARANOID, DELUSIONAL.
YOU THINK EVERYBODY'S AGAINST YOU.
THE DRUG DIDN'T CAUSE YOUR NIGHTMARES.
YOU YOURSELF DID.
LOOK, THE SO-CALLED DRUG IS JUST A CATALYST.
JOSEPH McNAMARA IS CRIMINALLY INSANE.
HE'S GOT PATHOLOGICAL ENVY.
HE'S... HE'S GOT A VENDETTA AGAINST ME.
WHAT YOU'RE DOING IS UTTERLY HOPELESS.
HE COMMITTED MURDER, AND HE RAPED MY WIFE.
CALL SOMEBODY FOR MY LUGGAGE.
I'M CHECKING OUT.
OPEN IT UP.
ORDERLY, OPEN THE DOOR!
GO AND CALL SECURITY.
WAIT A MINUTE. DON'T YOU HURT HIM.
- HE PUT HIS HANDS ON YOU. - DON'T HURT HIM.
STOP THIS NONSENSE, IAN.
YOU'RE A SICK MAN. LET ME HELP YOU.
ALL THIS TIME, I NEVER KNEW
IF I WAS DREAMIN' OR I WAS AWAKE.
JUST THINK, I COULD BE DREAMIN' RIGHT NOW.
TAKE IT EASY, IAN. THIS IS NO DREAM.
NO, IT'S A FUCKIN' NIGHTMARE.
JOE PLAYED US ALL LIKE A HARP.
YOU'RE DELIRIOUS. PLEASE, IAN.
I NEVER FELT BETTER IN MY LIFE.
( security alarm blaring )
GET ME OUTTA HERE,
OR I'M GONNA GIVE YOU...
Woman on P.A.: DR. RENQUIST, PLEASE REPORT TO SECURITY IMMEDIATELY.
DR. RENQUIST, PLEASE REPORT TO SECURITY IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL DO IT!
- Racquel: IAN, STOP. - I'LL FILL HIM FULL OF THIS SHIT.
- NO, IAN. - GO AHEAD, IAN.
GO AHEAD. IT'S ONLY A NORMAL SALINE SOLUTION.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THAT'S ALL IT EVER WAS.
EVERYTHING YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH, EVERYTHING,
WAS INSIDE YOU. THERE WERE NO DRUGS.
- YOU'RE LYIN'. - IT WAS ALWAYS YOU, IAN.
CALL THE POLICE. HE'S GONE OFF TO KILL HIS LAWYER.
JOE, WHAT IS IT?
WE HAVE TO TALK. IT'S ABOUT IAN.
WHAT'S SO IMPORTANT, IT COULDN'T WAIT TILL MORNING?
RELAX. WHY DON'T YOU GO FIX US A COUPLE OF DRINKS?
JOE, I REALLY DON'T THINK THAT'S APPROPRIATE.
YOU REALLY THINK I ENJOY DRIVIN' ACROSS TOWN THIS TIME OF NIGHT?
I'M JUST TRYIN' TO HELP HERE.
SORRY.
ALL THIS STUFF WITH IAN IS MOVING SO FAST.
WELL, ONCE THE PAPERS ARE SIGNED,
IT'LL BE OVER.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I WAS THINKING.
THERE'S GOOD AND BAD IN ALL THINGS.
ALL PEOPLE.
YOU CAN KNOW A GUY HIS ENTIRE LIFE,
AND NEVER REALLY GET TO KNOW HIM.
HIS DARK SIDE.
ANYBODY'S CAPABLE OF ANYTHING.
JOE, DON'T.
I CAN'T GET OVER IT.
HOW MUCH YOU LOOK LIKE WENDY.
YOU HAVE THE SAME EYES.
SAME MOUTH.
JOE, STOP IT. YOU'RE SCARING ME.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
WE CAN DO WHATEVER WE WANT.
IAN'S OUT OF OUR LIVES FOREVER.
- NO. - NOT SO FAST.
- NO! - JOE, NO!
GET OFF!
NO. PLEASE, NO.
OH, GOD, YOU'RE SO BEAUTIFUL.
YOU'RE SO GODDAMN BEAUTIFUL.
I ASK MYSELF,
WHY ARE THE GIRLS ALWAYS FALLING FOR THE DOCTORS?
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH THE LAWYERS?
- JUST GIVE IT A FUCKING CHANCE. - ( neck snaps )
GET OFF OF HER!
YOU KILLED HER.
SHE TRUSTED YOU.
CAN'T KEEP A GOOD MAN DOWN, HUH?
YOU NEVER COULD MEET DEFEAT.
NO WONDER YOU ALWAYS LIKED ME BEST.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, SO DID TERESA.
YOU ALWAYS HAD SUCH GOOD TASTE.
- YOU KILLED WENDY. - YEAH.
- TERESA TRIED TO TELL ME. - WHAT CAN I SAY?
LUNATIC ESCAPES FROM MENTAL INSTITUTION.
YOU COULDN'T HAVE BEEN MORE ACCOMMODATING.
COME ON, FRAT BOY, COME ON. BATTER UP!
Renquist: MR. LAZARRE IS A VERY SPECIAL CASE.
HE WAS QUITE TROUBLED ABOUT SOMETHING THAT HAPPENED
TO HIM IN HIS PAST.
SOMETHING SO DISTURBING THAT IT CAUSED
YEARS OF ABUSE, YEARS OF DENIAL AND TORMENT.
ROBBED OF AN ANCHOR, A LINK TO REALITY,
MR. LAZARRE COULD NO LONGER DISTINGUISH
BETWEEN WAKING AND SLEEP
OR NIGHTMARE AND SIMPLE FANTASY.
QUITE SIMPLY,
HE LOST HIS MIND.
THE MAN IS TOTALLY AND COMPLETELY DELUSIONAL.
I'M AFRAID...