Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
- Brian.
- Hi, Miss Reif.
- Is your mom running late?
- Yeah.
Oh! Well, you don't have
to sit out here all alone.
You know, next time she's late,
come see me in your old
classroom, right?
You know, we can start
your homework...
go over history lessons, yeah?
Yeah. What's that?
Oh, this is a surprise for
my friends that I'm meeting.
Do you want to see it?
- Yeah, sure.
Well, that looks good.
Hey, put that phone away.
I mean, you still like
reading, don't you?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Well, I...
just finished my first
children's book.
And I want you to be
the first to read it.
"Little Snow was a smart
and a happy little puppy.
He had a beautiful coat of fur.
...nice and smart
and happy too."
Hey, Brian.
Do you see that janitor inside?
Yeah.
I want you to go up to
her and tell her
that she is not to mop the
floors until after you leave.
You could've slipped
and really hurt yourself.
I need you to be a big
man here, you know?
Teach people how to respect you.
Stand up for yourself.
Go on.
Go on. I'll be right here.
- Hi.
- Hey.
What's he doing?
That woman was mopping
right where he was walking.
He almost slipped
and really hurt himself.
- Oh, God.
- I know.
Well, he's such
a sweet kid, right?
And he's the first to help
his classmates
when they're struggling and
it's just, with kids like him,
I really try and get them
to be assertive.
Stand up for themselves.
Especially when it involves
their safety.
Right, okay. Thank you.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi, honey.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
- I'm tired.
- I know, buddy.
Go get your stuff,
we'll go home, okay?
Thank you for keeping
him company.
- No problem.
- You're gonna make a great mom.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Have such a good night.
You too.
Hey, Brian. Don't play too
many video games, okay?
Okay. Bye.
This is a prepaid call from...
Jeff.
...an inmate at the County
Correctional Facility.
All phone calls are subject
to recording and monitoring.
To decline this call
press 9 now.
And to accept this call pr...
Hello?
Hello.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
Can I help you?
Oh, no. I'm good.
Thanks.
Yeah, are you lost?
No. I'm just meeting a friend.
Okay. Who's your friend?
Kim.
Oh!
I'm sorry. I'm meeting Kim too.
Why?
No, I organized the meeting.
The get-together.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- It's good.
- Yeah, she mentioned to me
that she was... she was inviting
someone else, um...
I'm Emily.
- Hey. Leslie.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. Um, do you
need any help with any of this?
- Oh, sure. Yeah. Um...
- Yeah.
Do you want me to carry this?
- No, no, no. I got that.
Um, you can take this.
- Sure.
And I'll give you this too.
Thank you.
- Yeah.
Um, so, how do you know Kim?
Oh, I work with her down
at the store.
Oh, wonderful. Yeah, she...
she said she was looking
for someone to help her out.
- Yeah.
- So, how long have you been in town?
Um, about two weeks,
but I used to come through here
all the time on my way
to Jackson Hole.
So it's really familiar.
You married?
No.
- What?
Um, well, any guy that wants
to marry me is fucking crazy.
And I don't feel like
dating a crazy man.
So, no.
- Well, do you like
the burly type
or the lanky type?
- Um...
- Hm?
- I don't know, lanky?
- Oh!
Well, I've got seven guys off
the top of my head
who would kill for
a date with you.
No. They're all friends
of my husband's.
They're great guys.
- All right.
Well, just let me see
pictures first,
'cause I'm not about
the blind date.
I'm sorry, of course.
Remind me after the meeting.
- Okay.
We are upstairs.
Wow.
- Leslie!
- Sorry.
Um, so, how do you know Kim?
Oh, I taught her kiddos.
- Oh, are you like a teacher?
- You bet.
Oh, so, you must be like
really smart.
Yeah.
Knock knock.
Oh, yay!
- How are you?
- There they are.
Look at those pretty girls.
Here, let me take this from you.
- Got it.
- Thank you.
We have been snackin'
and waitin' for 25 minutes.
I'm sorry, there was a
straggler at school.
You know how that goes.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh my God.
This bitch is hilarious.
- Marjorie.
- And she brought pie.
- I did!
- I've got an insane sweet tooth.
You love to outdo yourself.
You're so good.
I thought this was, you know,
the perfect thing
for our first meeting.
You know, my way of saying
thank you for coming.
Oh, fuck. That looks amazing!
Leslie, we're in a church.
Oh, sorry. I'm sorry.
It just, it looks so good.
Wait, is this for real?
Why? Can no one take
a joke anymore?
Why is everyone so serious
all the time?
Okay.
- Let's dig in.
- This is not meant for decoration.
- Let's eat it.
- We should make this a tradition!
Pie for the meetings.
- ...as soon as I can, I guess.
Alice, thank you so much
for talking to Father Marcus.
This is perfect.
- Oh, so easy! Don't mention it.
Everybody, this is Leslie.
She has been helping me
and Dylan out at the store.
It's so nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Leslie, will you grab me
like a little cupcake
or something?
Oh, yeah. Do you need help
sitting down?
- I might.
- You look like you're caring a little...
- Well...
- ...a little extra.
I am. Thank you so much.
- Look at this.
- Isn't that beautiful?
Oh, my goodness.
She worked all day and made pie?
- Oh, my goodness.
- Thank you, Alice.
Oh, my goodness.
Hm...
Ah!
- So good.
- Butter.
- Mm-hmm.
- Am I right?
- Yeah.
I mean how can something...
so delicious be so bad for you?
I am really, really happy
that we are finally doing this.
Yes.
Um, today I just want us to...
introduce ourselves, you know,
get to know each other.
There's...
There's no agenda
that needs to be accomplished.
We are here to support
each other
through this
multicultural warfare.
- That's right.
- Mm-hmm.
Now, I... I have been
brainwashed
to feel ashamed of my heritage.
To feel...
guilt for the prosperity
that our husbands, our fathers,
our brothers,
created in the Western world
and that everyone else
benefitted from.
We're all brainwashed.
All of us.
Um... I'm a teacher down
at the school and...
Um...
I, um...
I really want to be a mom.
And, um...
getting pregnant is taking
a little bit longer
than we expected, so...
maybe God is giving me a
higher purpose, right?
- That's right.
- Right.
This club.
Yeah.
Well, I like the name.
It has a sense of moving
through generations.
Yeah. Um...
Well, do we want to go around
and introduce ourselves?
Sort of, I don't know,
throw out ideas
for what we might
want this to be.
Um...
- I...
- Caught you off guard.
I'm Marjorie, um...
I'm actually not sure
I belong here.
I'm sorry, I don't want
to make you mad.
Just...
- No. You can never make me mad, Marjorie.
No, I mean that.
No, this doesn't have
to be anything
other than what you
want it to be.
I mean, is there a
particular reason
why you did come today?
Oh, I just wanted advice
with a work thing.
Um? Well, do you want to
explain what happened
and we can talk it out?
Um... yeah.
Okay, so...
I work in town, um...
Well, first off I want
to say I don't hate her.
I don't hate anyone, um...
But, yeah, I work in town
and I take the bus
an hour each way
and I have been busting
my ass for two years
and... so that I could
get manager pay.
And it's not her fault,
but um...
but this Colombian girl,
she started around
the same time as me.
Me a little bit before her,
well...
so she got promoted
and I didn't.
- Of course.
- That's not fair.
That's how I felt.
So did the Colombian
woman stick up for you
and say, "Hey, she was hired
before I was?"
Nope.
No, so, I...
Quick question.
Nobody's gonna post
about this, right?
Oh, Marjorie. Our constitution
was designed to protect you.
- Yeah.
- Right?
You have feelings.
Those feelings,
they're not wrong.
Right. Hmm...
Right. So, anyway, I decided
to stand up for myself...
- Good.
- And I asked my manager
why she got promoted
and I didn't.
And he said it was because
she has better
leadership skills than I do.
Um... I don't know
what happened,
but I just kinda snapped,
you know?
Mm-hmm.
- It's 'cause she's brown.
- Thank you!
And nobody would stand up
for me.
You know, my co-workers
didn't have my back
and I... I just felt crazy.
No. No, you're not
crazy.
You're not crazy.
- Yeah.
No, it's just like diversity.
Inclusion.
It's like they're speaking
in fucking code.
You know what I mean? It's on
every fucking form, you know.
Every government form,
every employment form.
Every fucking receipt.
You know what I mean? And...
Yeah, so I just, I don't
know what to do and I...
I guess that's why I'm here.
Hey.
Thank you for sharing.
And for speaking
up for yourself.
I'd like to also add, you know,
Mexicans and Blacks can get away
with saying things like,
you know, "White people
are so awful."
All the time.
- Yes!
Or "White..."
This is my favourite.
"White people are the worst."
And no one says anything.
But the minute we offer up
any sort of critique...
Ouh! People shout, "racist."
Yep.
Marjorie just know
you are in good company, okay?
We all kind of feel how you feel
and anything you gotta say,
you're safe to get it out here.
You know, it's like...
the Asians come over,
they take over companies...
get us sick, I don't say
anything, you know?
And then...
urban kids, right? They can't
even spell their name
and they get into better
colleges than me.
And it's like okay still, fine.
I don't say anything.
- Mm-hmm.
- Now every brown bitch gets special treatment
because they've convinced people
to feel sorry for her
and it's like...
I...
then I'm the racist?
It's like, there's nothing left
for me in this country.
Yeah, I'm a good person.
I work hard.
But I refuse to grow old
this poor
and have people tell me
that I've got it good!
I don't.
I'm struggling.
I work paycheque to paycheque.
Oh, boy.
Oh, it is wonderful to see
young people in the movement.
I can't believe
you're not married.
Oh, well, don't worry
about that.
We're gonna help with that.
Leslie is in the same boat.
I know plenty of
great single men
who'd just eat you up.
Well, it's slim pickings for me,
but I got a couple if you
don't mind older.
Actually, I only
date older men so...
Hey! Listen up.
How about we all
come to the meeting
with a list of, like,
10 great guys.
Yes, great. Great.
- Yep. Alice.
Hi. I'm Alice up
on Owen Street.
And, um...
I'm tired.
I spend a lot of my time alone.
In my own thoughts.
We're really not supposed
to live like that.
So... I hope that we
can keep growing
and keep bringing new people in
because just being here with
you all,
hearing your inspiring
ideas, Em...
I already feel more like myself.
Oh, me too, hon.
It is so hard being
a mom. You can be so isolated.
I mean, that's why
we need to recruit.
Yeah, we gotta keep growing.
You don't have to be
going through this alone.
Maybe talk to your friends.
Start building a little
bit more community.
Help them pick up groceries.
Have them help you pick up kiddos and...
- Yeah.
You know, you can really
introduce concepts anywhere.
- And of course...
- At yoga class.
Yeah!
Right. That's perfect.
I mean, they're the ones
who started Black Lives Matter.
They're the ones who are
creating this divide.
They lit a fuse and then let
their kids run wild with it.
Emily's life matters.
So does mine.
All lives matter.
Yes.
We have better doctors.
We live longer.
We take better care
of each other.
These are facts.
Does acknowledging facts
make me a bad person?
No. Jeez, no.
- Oh, my goodness, no.
Come here.
- Thank you. Hi.
- I'm Jessica.
Well, I wasn't sure
what to expect
but Miss Emily was
real persistent.
Um... okay, okay.
My daddy was
the chapter President
of the KKK in Valentine,
Nebraska,
and I have been
a member my whole life.
I'm more active in Storm front
since our lives are online.
And I don't normally
tell people that
because I know what people
think about us
and, you know, the media
loves to portray us
as these like big scary
monsters.
But am I really that scary?
I'm a mother of four,
pregnant with number five right
here, and...
this club just really
appeals to me,
because, well, it's like I
always say, it starts with
the mommas and what they're
teaching their babies.
God bless you.
Thank God.
And I'm not here
to cause a fuss.
I'm not here to say,
"Oh, you know, lynch 'em all,"
you know, like people
might think.
No, I'm just...
I'm just here to talk
common sense.
- Multiculturalism doesn't work.
- That's right.
It's never worked,
it's not going to work.
They sure as hell
don't like us, and...
- the feeling's mutual.
- Exactly.
- So...
- I got two kids.
You're a momma too?
- Yeah.
- Oh!
Here, I'll pass
this to you then.
I wanted to have more, but,
you know, they are expensive.
So, you know, you try
to get loans,
but, you try getting a loan
from the Jew banks.
They love saying no.
They love it.
I mean, I cannot laugh.
It's true, though.
I mean, I don't know
when it happened,
but we founded this country
in 1776, right?
That's right.
And now we're watching
it being taken
from under our noses
in plain sight.
Mm-hmm.
Dylan, you know,
he runs our store
and we can barely stay afloat.
You see it.
I mean, it's because all the
illegal immigrants, they steal.
Yes, they do.
And... oh, God!
It's just the whining
and the disrespect you get
from these coloured kids
who come into the store.
They just come and barge in,
and they're so freaking loud.
They're... what is the point
of being so loud?
And they're doing it
just to make sure
you can't think straight.
I think an ethnic state
is the most successful state.
I think that's how
you ensure unity.
I think that's how you
regulate the markets.
Mm-hmm.
I've got a journalism degree.
Hm?
That's nice.
- And I was thinking about,
you know, using it to help out
our group.
And first thing you got to do,
obviously,
is take the media
back from the Jews.
- Mm-hmm.
- But Emily and I were thinking
about starting a newsletter or a
magazine that contains some of our ideas.
And if we can get 'em
on the shelves,
we can start reaching people.
- Yeah.
- Right.
I didn't meet you.
I'm Kim, by the way.
Hi, Kim.
Good to meet you.
Leslie.
Oh, me? Sorry.
I'm Leslie.
And...
I'm sorry, what am I supposed
to say?
Tell whatever you want.
Whatever you want.
Why you're here.
Yes, there are no wrong
answers, Leslie.
I mean that. Okay?
- Okay.
Well, I'm here because, well,
Kim invited me, honestly.
And...
you know, I've been
lucky that I've...
I've been very lucky with
the friendships that I've made.
I guess it's karma
for my shitty family.
But, um...
when I was in prison, I got
close with a group of people
that really got
my head straight.
And I really miss that way
of life, you know,
being told what to do,
where to go,
it just makes sense for me.
So...
a friend of mine knew that
I needed that out here,
so she introduced me to Kim.
- Mm-hmm.
And that's what she is to me,
you know, my stability.
And, I love her kids
like they were my own.
They love her.
- I would kill for those babies.
And...
you know, I want to have
a family like that one day.
Yeah, I mean, they just...
They took me in.
No questions asked, so...
- No, no.
- I'm just here to help.
- Aw!
You know, in any way that I can.
Aw! Thank you
for sharing, Leslie.
- Yeah.
- For being here.
Um...
I would also like to add this.
- Really important.
- Yes. Yeah.
You know, these... these libs say that
they're fighting for women's rights, right?
They're just trying
to make us masculine.
Well, think about it.
Who would a guy rather be with?
Hm?
Marjorie?
Leslie?
Or some, I don't...
blubbering brown whale
coming in from God knows
what country,
with what type of disgusting
disease.
Ew!
For our men's strength
and resources...
they get this.
- Ephesians 5.
- Yes. Yes.
Now this, this is the only
gender balance
that has proven to build
strong families.
Yeah.
And we need strong families.
Aw, honey.
You know, it goes
back to the 1960s
with the, you know, the...
the decay of the traditional
family which had this...
Hm.
- It really messed us up.
- It did.
You are such a resource.
Beauty and brains.
Look at that.
I just want to take
a minute here
to acknowledge all the work
you did in organizing this
and getting all of our butts
into one room.
Making pie.
Listen, you're really making
a difference, okay?
For me anyway.
- Thank you, Kim.
- Yeah.
- And you make really great pie.
I'm gonna take notes
and I'll email everyone
afterwards.
No. I don't...
Maybe we shouldn't have
a trail like that.
I'm sorry. What have we done
that's wrong?
No, name one thing
that we've said here
or done here today
that's illegal. Tell me.
- You're right. I'm sorry.
- No. Tell me.
- Um, I...
- No. I'm sorry.
I just, I'm more...
- Emily.
Maybe we can talk about
the newsletter.
Um, I would really appreciate,
I don't know about you guys,
but I need home schooling
materials immediately.
Because you should hear what
they are teaching my children.
Oh, I can only imagine.
I can only imagine.
I will help you with curriculum.
It's...
it's actually always been a...
a dream of mine to write
a children's book.
- Aw!
- Really?
You know you should, um...
You should just make
your own school.
You know, like, really,
really like dream big.
- Yes!
- Put it all out there.
Yes! That is a great idea,
Leslie. Thank you.
Yeah.
Um, I...
I've actually already
started on the book.
What?
- Yeah.
Just, you know, after school.
Sort of sketching, um...
- Oh, my gosh.
- Let me see.
- It's really rough, but...
- Oh my God.
These are amazing, Emily.
- He's a cute dog.
Aw!
How did you learn how
to draw like this?
My brother.
He's the real talent.
How creative you both are.
All right.
The magazine.
- Yes!
Should we, like, make a list
of all the illegal immigrants
around the area?
So everybody knows where
they live and stuff.
Um, no, no!
Hold on.
That's the idea and, you know,
everything thus far
has been a step in the right
direction in the magazine,
but we want to be careful with
this first issue, right?
We want to engage
the mainstream, right?
We can't come on
too strong, okay?
Soft on the outside
so vigorous ideas
can be digested more easily.
Hm.
Now we are the best
secret weapon that no one
checks at the door
because we tread quietly.
Hm.
I don't know where this fits
into everything,
but I think it's important
to scold
the spic and African parents
in front of their kids.
That way the child will
see the parent
as the root cause for
their embarrassment
and naturally distance
themselves
and their similarities as they
assimilate more quickly.
I'm sorry.
Wow, Alice...
Oh my God.
- Alice.
- It's on me.
It's all down my back.
- I'm so sorry.
Emily.
I'm so, I'm so sorry.
No, I'm sure it's my
fault in some way.
- Jeez.
- I got it.
Oh, my gosh.
- Father, thank you...
- Please go.
- I'm sorry, we...
- Please.
I don't want any trouble.
- I don't understand, what...
- Please, just... I mean it.
Just go right now
and I won't report you.
But right now.
Good. I'm glad I didn't
ruin the sofa too.
Ladies! Ladies.
What?
- Should be we go back to my place for some wine?
Yeah! I would love
to, but I can't. Kiddos.
- Ow!
- Next time.
- Yeah, I'm sorry. Lars and I have a date night.
- Ow!
- We'll do it again.
- I mean, I'm game.
- You sound like an ape
when you speak like that.
Oh, God, yeah.
I guess you're right.
Well, I'll help you work
on that.
I wish I could.
Really do, but duty calls.
Do we need to clean up?
Oh, God!
No, leave it.
- Are you sure? Okay.
- Yes!
They have staff. Um, Leslie,
my dear, are you gonna join us?
- Yeah.
- Oh, great!
- Yeah, sure.
- Great.
We should get the guys
together sometime soon, yes?
Find me one first, would you?
I have always loved
James for you.
Wait, wait, the guy that works
at the gasoline store?
- Yes. Yeah, that's the redhead.
- God. Horrible hands.
- Marjorie!
- Do you think I would like him?
- Beggars can't be choosers.
- I mean, if you like short and fat fingers.
Yes, I think you'd really
like him.
Sometimes I do.
Okay. Well, then James
is your guy.
No, Leslie.
Don't listen to her.
James would be great for you.
- He's sweet.
- He deserves a good girl.
I get it, I get it.
I just want to see
pictures first.
Yeah. It's always weird when
you show up
and they're kind of like
fucking ew looking.
Trust me.
- Yeah. Or then when they smile
and you see their teeth.
- Oh my God.
Oh my God!
I know exactly what you mean.
I've walked out because
it's like, ugh!
Here. Do you want some?
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Always pack some extras.
- Oh!
- Yeah?
- It really gets you down to the bones.
- Ah!
- Look at that moon.
That was the first time
I've been in a church in...
I think since I was like seven.
Well, I'm surprised
I didn't burn up
and go straight to hell. So...
God.
I feel the same way actually.
Yeah.
- God has maybe forgiven us.
I don't know.
I mean, he should after
going through that.
Thank you. Ladies, I'll email
you all with the notes later.
So nice to meet you both.
- Jess, safe home.
Have a wonderful night, ladies.
Jess!
You're so bad.
Oh!
Um, thanks for inviting me.
It actually was kind of cool.
Well, it was either this
or kill myself.
Kim, are you going to the store?
- Yeah, for a minute. Why?
- We need some more wine.
- Yeah. Always more wine.
Can we get a ride
with you real quick?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Do you guys mind a quick detour? I'm sorry.
- Not at all!
- Shotgun!
Damn it!
I was just going for it!
Okay...
Hey!
Oh, no. Yeah.
No, it went great.
Yes, yes, yes, but, Kimmy
is actually giving me a ride
to the store to pick
up some things.
So can you pick me up there?
Great. Oh, um... Yeah.
And actually some of the girls
are gonna come over
for some wine.
Is that okay?
Yeah, well, I don't know.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. All right.
Yeah. I love you too, babe.
Bye. See you soon.
See you soon.
- Craig... Hey!
Craig is excited to meet
my new friends.
- Oh, he's a sweetheart.
- He is.
Thank you for coming
on into the mom van.
Sorry it's so messy.
I didn't expect company.
Also, sorry about the smell.
It's pretty much our family's
locker room.
So, that's why it smells
like feet, I guess.
I'm used to this smell.
The backroom at the store
smells like it too.
It's really Dylan. She says
it's the kids, it's not.
Oh, no!
Throw him under the bus.
- You're funny.
Thanks.
So, how long have
you been teaching?
- About five years now.
- Wow, that's a long time.
- Yeah.
- What grades do you do?
I do kindergarten.
Yeah, really early.
- That's so cute.
- I know!
- They're so, so little.
- They're so little.
They're so sweet! Ah!
I love it.
That's awesome.
What age do you
teach? Sorry.
Kindergarten. Yeah,
so like five or six
depending on, you know...
- Yeah, yeah.
...their birth date. Yeah.
Hey, you know...
I actually have all of
these vintage clothes
that I've been wanting to sell
and make an online store.
- Oh?
- And...
I don't know, like,
I was thinking maybe
we could put the money
for it towards...
the school or the magazine,
or something like that.
- Oh.
- That's a really good idea.
- You know, towards the cause.
- You would do that?
- Yeah.
- I mean, I can contribute stuff too.
I've got a lot of stuff
lying around.
That would be awesome.
- Yeah.
Yeah. And I mean, I still need
to take pictures to post them, but...
I mean, I don't know, maybe...
maybe you'd want to.
I mean, you're so pretty.
You're basically like a model.
- What?
What? No.
- Yes!
- You're being silly!
- Emily, you have literally
the best genes
of anybody I know.
Just fishing for compliments!
- Kim. No.
- You don't look like that.
- I am not!
- You're like Barbie made real.
Yeah!
I should just take you guys
around with me all the time.
But seriously,
we all have great genes, right?
Yes, we do.
Marjorie, I...
I don't mean to be staring
at your tits,
- but you have great tits.
- It's true.
And I'm not a dyke.
Small but mighty I always say.
So will you do it?
Will you model the clothes?
Yeah. Yeah.
Gosh, I just...
Ah, I want my own school!
You'd be perfect.
You really would.
- I don't know, ladies.
- If there's anybody who could do it...
And you know what?
If niggers can have
their own colleges
and Jews can have their
own community centres
and Islam can have its own laws,
we can have our own goddamn
elementary school, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Amen.
Um, Leslie, do you have
a type of wine you prefer?
Um... I don't really.
Okay.
- Red, white, rosé.
- Oh, rosé.
I'll be in.
Okay.
Did you do the...
I called him, he's
coming on Tuesday at 3 o'clock.
Okay.
I'll ring you up.
Thank you, Kim.
- Oh, hey!
- I can do it myself.
- They're closed.
- Excuse me.
- We're closed.
Really? We're just gonna
be real quick.
We're just getting
a bottle of wine.
I don't care how quick
you're gonna be.
We're closed.
- You're checking her out.
Yeah, but I work here.
I'm sorry. Do you speak English
or do we need to speak
slower for you?
What?
Look, I had a long
day at work too.
I understand.
Let's just...
Can I just get a quick
bottle of wine?
- I'll get the most expensive one.
- This is my store
and I can refuse service
to anyone.
I understand that...
but legally you need
to have a better reason
than being an old, tired cunt.
- Lily, stop.
- Excuse me?
What? Did...? What?
Are you fucking serious?
Let's go.
You just walk into
our store saying that shit?
- Come on.
- Let's go.
You always just take it.
Stand up for yourself.
That's his sister.
Let's go.
No.
Buy your wine.
You said you're going to buy...
the most expensive
bottle of wine.
I mean...
isn't that what
she said to you, Kim?
- Uh, yes.
- Yeah.
That's what I heard.
You don't need to get it.
Come on, let's go.
It's all right.
I got it.
That's $300.
Well, that's a really good deal.
That's fucking ridiculous,
Anne. Come on, let's go.
Hold on.
Hold on, hold on.
Okay.
We're good.
Thanks.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
The only people who carry
$300 in cash
are either whores or thieves.
Or waitresses.
Sorry, wait a second.
What even are you?
Yeah. Kinda looks like
a chink fucked a wetback.
Whatever you think I am
is how you're gonna treat me.
So I guess that's what I am.
- Just let us go.
- Hey!
Say thank you, faggots.
We're sisters.
You fucking idiot.
What the fuck did
you just call me?
- Don't fucking touch her!
- Get off of me.
Get off of me!
- Get off!
- Get off of me!
Let go of her fucking purse,
you fucking animal.
Get the fuck out.
- Get the fuck out!
- Come, let's go.
- Get out!
The fuck!
- Fuck you!
- Emily Reif,
you know what they do to rapists
like your brother in prison?
He's never gonna be able
to take a solid shit again.
- Fuck you!
Holy fucking shit!
Are you fucking kidding me?
No. She's a fucking slut!
She's a fucking liar.
Hey. Hey! Hey!
- She's a liar.
What's going on, Kim?
Disrespectful.
That was so fucking disrespectful.
- You're okay?
The fuck!
- What's going on?
Your brother would
never touch that girl.
- What's going on?
- Much less rape her.
- She was threatening me.
- Who was threatening you?
- The bitch who put Jeff in jail.
She was just in here.
She just walked in here.
I didn't know what she wanted.
She walked in here
with somebody else.
And I didn't recognize
her at first. But...
I got it. I got it.
Hey, we had a long week, okay?
Let's go get some
wine and go home.
- Wait...
- Okay?
Craig, Craig, you should
freaking see all of 'em.
They hang outside of Clark's
and they just...
they are so loud
and like animals.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Drinking all this...
- So you know these guys?
- No, I don't know 'em.
But she went to school
with Anne.
I... I didn't know
the other one.
Hold on, hold on!
It's okay.
That bitch needs to shut her
carpet munching fucking face.
Okay? You know where she lives?
- I... yeah.
- Yeah? Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Let's go. Come on.
All we'll do is take
a shit in her tub
or like, steal her fucking
passport or something.
- Hey. Hey.
- She'll never know that it's us.
- Come on, now.
- No.
She cannot talk
to her like that.
- She can't use that disrespect.
- Sweetheart, let's go home.
- We shouldn't.
- No. We should.
What do you mean, you shouldn't?
I can go alone,
if everyone wants, okay?
I can just do it myself.
But she cannot be talking
to you like that.
No. You know what,
I'm fucking game.
I'm sorry, I'm in.
I'm in.
- Emily.
- It'll be fun.
- Teach the bitch a lesson.
- I'll do it if you do it.
- Yeah. Fuck that shit.
- Just for a minute.
- Okay. Yes, yes, yes.
I'll go.
- Yes!
- I'll go. I'll go. I'll go.
- What are you...
- This is just like high school!
- Let's go get supplies.
Oh, man, we're riding again.
What?
I didn't say anything.
Then what's with
this mopey thing?
Huh?
Do you know what you're
talking about here, sweetheart?
It's a practical joke.
No.
It's a fucking felony, honey.
Look at me.
We had a rough call
from the doctor this week...
and I think maybe
we're not thinking straight.
But that's why we'll go home...
- This has nothing to do with that.
You're so fucking stupid.
You want to be
a little fairy here?
No, that's fine, okay?
You want your wife...
to look at you every day
like a pussy bitch?
No, I can live like that.
Yeah.
But I'm not sure that you can.
- Okay.
Okay.
- You need to be a big man here...
and teach people how
to respect you.
Nobody talks to your wife
the way that she did,
because that is
disrespecting you.
Do you understand me?
Yeah.
Hey.
Hey, look at me.
Do you want me to look at
you like a fucking faggot, babe?
- No.
- No. No, you don't.
Okay.
Yeah.
You guys are gonna make
the tallest, prettiest babies.
- Oh, Kim.
- You are.
Are we ready?
We're gonna do it.
- I'm ready.
- Leave your phones.
- Hey. Hey!
- What?
- Leave your phones here.
- Why?
So they can't trace
that you've been there.
That's really smart.
Okay. Okay, Craig. That's
actually really, really smart.
- Copy that.
- Yeah.
Cheer up, softy.
Let's fucking do this.
Fuck.
I love you.
- Oh, God.
- My lady.
- Why, thank you, my dear.
- Your chariot awaits.
Here I come.
Ahem.
Hell yeah.
- Ladies.
- Yeah.
Oh my God, I can't
believe we're doing this!
- No. Kim.
- What?
- This stays here, right?
- Yeah, obviously.
- Of course it does.
- Yeah. Of course, Em.
I can't believe
we're doing this.
I love you guys.
Let's turn that music on.
Oh my God.
I fucking love this song.
Yeah!
It's so fucking good.
Hey. Hey. Shh! Shut up.
Kim, can you turn
the music off, please?
Fucking Jesus.
Turn it off, please.
Fuck.
- Sorry.
- Craig...
Buzzkill.
You know, it's not a big deal.
Okay, it's a little
bit of a big deal
that Alice spilled
all over me...
and ruined my favourite
sweater, but...
- I think it'll come out.
- Yeah.
I just feel like she's
kind of clumsy.
Is she the person that we
want to have taking our notes?
Yeah. She is physically
clumsy, but she is organized.
- Hey, hey, hey. Slow down.
- What?
- It's right here. Slow down.
- Sorry. Where? Left, right?
What?
- Right. Right. Turn right.
Yeah.
Turn it slow. It's steep.
Oh, dear, that is steep.
Holy fuck.
Kim, we can talk about
Alice later, okay?
- All right.
- Wait a second. Wait a second.
This bitch lives on the hill?
Yeah.
She lives on the hill.
What?
- I'm in a fucking duplex.
And she lives on
the fucking hill.
Yeah. Yeah.
All of this is hers.
- Jesus.
- I bet she can see the lake from up here.
- She can.
- How do you know that?
We just passed
by a sign that said:
"Leave all your troubles
behind."
I check up on her.
You know, I keep tabs on her.
I'm in trouble.
You gotta let that go, baby.
Fuck that shit.
Is this the only entrance
to the property?
Well, to the street.
Yeah.
That's fucking risky,
don't you think?
If somebody comes home,
we're stuck here.
Well, then, okay. Well, then,
someone needs to stand watch.
It's simple. This is it. This is it.
- Kim, hold on.
Fucking shit.
- That's it? - Yeah.
That shed is fucking bigger
than my fucking apartment.
Are there pets in there?
I don't think so.
No.
No. I don't know.
She lives by herself?
Yeah, I don't know.
Yes, she lives by her...
- It really matters that you know that.
Yeah. Okay.
She lives by herself.
She inherited this place
when her mom died.
So, yes.
She lives here alone, Craig.
Prosecutor over here, Jesus.
Just an inquisition here.
Fuck. All right.
It's as good a time
as any, I guess.
Five minutes and not a second
longer than that.
Hold on.
I'm gonna wait outside.
I don't want to know
what the fuck you guys
were doing in there.
When I come get you,
we're leaving. Okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay?
Yes.
Yes, this is my sexy man!
Oh my God.
There's the fucking lake.
- He's gonna stand watch for us.
- That is fucked up.
I'm sorry,
but I have a question.
Just pull it up here
and kill the engine.
If she isn't even home,
why do we only have
to be five minutes?
Is she a good idea?
Honestly.
- Craig, she is fine. She's fine.
Craig, she works hard.
She's totally solid.
Craig, you need
to fucking loosen up, man.
Yeah, Craig.
I'm solid.
Five minutes and not
a second longer than that.
What do you think of that?
I'll bring the wine.
- Jesus, man.
- Babe!
We're just fucking having
a good time, man.
Babe, use your upper
body strength.
- Kim, you're in the back.
- What? Okay.
Fuck.
She has a kayak!
- Shut the fuck up.
Why do we need to be so quiet?
She's not even home.
- Just shut the fuck up.
I know, right? So dumb.
- Hold on. Hold on.
What? What?
I fucking hate this.
I have a really bad feeling.
There's too much space
between the house and the road.
We're not gonna get
everybody out unseen.
Emily...
Does she have a dog?
I don't know.
- Shut up. Shut up.
- It's a puppy.
What?
You can't take a dog, Craig?
Shh, shh, hey, buddy.
He's so cute.
Wait, should I grab a rock?
And we can fucking throw
it through the window.
No.
You should look for
a hide-a-key.
A hide-a-key?
What the fuck is that?
Seriously?
- Leslie! Shh...
- I found it.
It was really right
the fuck there?
Really right the fuck there.
I'm surprised this bitch
hasn't been burgled before.
Shut the fuck up.
What?
He's excited to see us.
- Get the dog.
Hello. Hello.
Come here.
Oh.
It's a big house.
Oh my God.
- Baby.
- Oh my God.
- Oh, wow.
Look at these floors.
That's beautiful.
Hey. Hey.
Four minutes
and I'm gonna wait outside.
- Cool.
- Kim, I'm not fucking around. Okay?
- I know.
- Man, you have lost a lot
of your sense of humour
these days.
Oh my God.
She has a washer and a dryer.
- Nice.
- Front loaders.
I wonder if it's one
of those smart ones
where you can control
it on your phone.
What I would give...
never to go
to the laundromat again.
That's shitty art.
Aw, sweet baby.
- This is very shitty art.
- It's shitty art.
- Let's see if we have anything to...
Yes!
Save one of those beers for me.
Will you?
- Maybe. We'll see.
- Sweet baby. Look at this baby boy.
Look at this sweet baby boy.
- He's cute.
He's so scared.
Where is your mommy?
She left you alone.
- Why did she leave you alone?
- Wait, what are we...
- Jesus Christ!
- Fuck, Marjorie.
Fuck me.
- Let me in.
Get in here.
I'm sorry, am I being too loud?
Craig. Craig!
Fuck!
Are you fucking kidding me?
How do you turn...
Fuck.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I always wanted
a fucking piano...
but we could never afford one.
Oh, fuck!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It just... fell.
I'm sorry.
- What did you do?
- I just dropped the glass.
- Just clean it up, okay?
Okay.
I'm cleaning it up.
No, this piano is a...
- Kim.
- Yeah? Yes, Emily.
- Help me find the passport.
I'm gonna check upstairs.
Can you hide in here?
Yeah.
I always wanted
to play piano, but...
It's freezing up here.
- Kim!
- Yeah!
- Are you upstairs?
- Yeah.
- Did you find anything?
- Not yet.
It's dark.
And, ooh, cold.
It's very...
Did you check under the bed?
Yeah. I just did.
But I didn't see anything there.
You checked the... Ouch!
See? See?
- What is with this ceiling?
- Us, tall, blonde models
gotta worry about that,
don't we?
- Kim. Did you check in here?
- No. I mean, no, not there.
- Oh, God.
- Found her underwear drawer.
Eww! I bet they smell.
Let's see.
It's like...
What? - I found it! I found it!
- You found it?
- I found it. - Wait!
- Oh my God! You found it.
- You found it?
- What are we doing with this?
Yes.
- We found it!
We found the passport.
'Cause we know
this bitch is not American!
Oh, we found the passport!
I'm just playing
the fucking piano.
Jesus Christ.
- Who has a lighter?
- No, no, no. Let me do it.
- Oh my God, are we burning it?
- Hey! - Let me do it.
- Kim.
- I saw matches.
- That was not five minutes, Craig.
It absolutely was.
Please, can we go?
- It wasn't five.
- We shouldn't burn it here
because there's
like smoke alarms.
Leslie!
Sorry. I'm not gonna
burn the house down.
- Emily! Let's go! We'll burn it...
- Oh, my gosh.
Let's burn it in your
fire pit at home.
- Shh!
- But we should check...
Shh!
What?
- Hide.
- What?
- Hide right now!
- Oh my God.
- Hide and get out when you can.
- Oh my God. This way.
- Fuck! - Shit.
- Fuck!
Oh, shit.
- Move, move, move.
- Shit.
Fuck!
I fucking told you.
Is that better?
Fuck!
Willie?
She's leaving.
Stop her. Get her.
Get her.
- Get her.
- Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Shit.
Oh my God.
It's okay.
Just don't move.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
- Grab a chair.
- Here.
- Put her right there.
- I got it.
I got it.
- Give me your hands.
- Shut the fuck up. It's okay.
- I'm sorry. It's okay.
It's just a practical joke,
okay? It's just a joke.
I'm sorry.
We're leaving. Okay?
- Emily. What the fuck?
- We're leaving. What are you fucking doing?
What do you think I'm fucking doing?
I'm fucking holding her down.
Kim, let's go.
Let's go.
- Sorry. Let's go.
- Let's fucking go.
Kim, what the fuck
are you doing?
Shut up or I will
fucking kill you!
Do you fucking hear me?
This is all because you
fucking sassed us back there.
Do you fucking understand this?
This is not funny
anymore at all.
This is big trouble.
- Okay. It's okay.
- What are we doing?
- Okay, I love my fucking job.
- Em?
- And Terry needs me.
I don't want to go
to fucking jail.
It's okay. Just stop it.
Just stop it, Craig.
Stop whining and whimpering
like a fucking cunt!
I'm sick of it! - Emily!
- We were just joking around.
- What are we doing?
- What the fuck are you doing?
What do you mean,
what am I doing?
I don't know what I'm doing.
I'm trying to help.
Kim!
Let's go.
- Where is he going?
- He's fucking scared.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Hey. Hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
- Stay. Stay, stay.
- Help!
Leave me alone!
- Shh! It's okay.
- Stop!
I'll explain.
I can explain, okay?
We're gonna go inside now.
I'm gonna explain.
Just please, come with me. Come with me.
- Stop! Stop! Please stop!
Yeah, just come inside
and I'll fucking explain it to you.
Okay? Please? Just
come with me. I'm sorry.
I'm fucking sorry.
I'm sorry. It's just...
Hold still. Okay?
Please! Fucking please!
- Please stop!
- I don't wanna fucking hurt you.
Okay? Please don't make me
fucking hurt you.
Okay? Okay?
Just come on.
I'm sorry.
I'm fucking sorry.
Let's go inside.
Here. Okay?
Okay.
What the fuck?
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Stop it.
Did you just shove
me, you fucking bitch?
What the fuck is this?
Hey. Hey.
Hey, babe.
Get the fuck off of me.
Get the fuck off of me!
Craig, where are you going?
Craig, Jesus!
- Craig!
- Craig! Craig!
Craig! Craig!
We don't need him. Okay?
We don't fucking need him.
You don't need him.
You are better than him.
He is a little fucking pussy.
Do you understand?
We don't need him.
Shut up, shut up.
Outside.
Everyone, outside to talk.
Don't move. Don't move.
Outside now.
All of you.
We are fucking watching you!
Do you fucking understand that?
That gun is on you at
all fucking times! Kim!
- Yes. - Keep it on them!
- Yes.
I got them. I got them.
Okay.
They're moving closer.
We gotta scare
the shit out of them.
They have seen our faces.
They know who we are.
Is that really gonna work
if we just scare them?
Yeah. We just have to scare
the shit of them.
I don't know.
She's tough,
you know, she has...
Then we really scare
the shit out of them.
I can't, I can't.
Kim. Kim.
I need my babies.
I can't.
I understand.
And you can do this.
I need you.
I can't do this alone, Kim.
Okay?
- Stop looking at me!
Okay, I need you to calm
down and think.
- Yeah. Yeah, I am calm!
- Okay? You're calm. Okay.
I think it's the only way.
Emily, it's the only way.
We just gotta go really hard and scare the
shit out of them and just fucking commit.
I mean, is there anything
else we're not thinking of?
They weren't supposed
to be fucking home.
Okay, listen. Okay.
Everyone just needs to relax.
All right? This shit isn't
that complicated.
Kim. Kim, you are tight
with every single fucking cop
that comes into the store.
I have seen it.
If they ask us anything,
we'll deny it.
All right?
- Yeah.
We will get rid of
all of our evidence.
Get rid of our fingerprints... everything
that we ever fucking touched in here.
Get rid of our trash
and that's it. All right?
It's their word against
ours with no evidence.
And trust me, by the time I'm
fucking done with these bitches,
I swear to God, they will
fucking leave town.
All right? All right?
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna fix this.
Kim, I'm gonna fix this.
All right?
And this part will be fun.
Oh my God.
- We need to...
- Okay.
- Shh.
Let's scare the shit
out of them.
We clean up.
And we're out.
- We should leave right now.
We should leave right now.
- Yeah.
Then leave.
Just go.
Shit.
Okay. Are we gonna do it?
Why would you show up for a
meeting dressed like a fucking whore?
Disrespect!
Get the fuck in here!
- Oh my God.
Fuck! Will you help
me? Please, Marjorie?
I just wanted some fucking
wine! Jesus fucking Christ!
- They're touching each other.
- Okay. I got it!
I got it! Kim!
I got it!
- Jesus Christ!
- Let go. Let go.
- Get the fuck off of her.
- Jesus.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Stop moving!
This is all because you decided
to stand the fuck up
for yourself.
Calm down.
Emily. Emily.
- Hey, little bitch.
Hey, little bitch.
I need your fucking phone.
I need to play some
fucking music.
Oh! Hold on.
You know what?
I bet you her phone
is in her purse.
Wonder if you have any
more whore money.
Okay. Fuck. Okay.
This is the United
States of America.
- Oh, shit.
- It's not your fucking country, is it?
- Okay. Wait. Will you take her phone?
- Wait.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yeah. That's...
What kind of tunes
do you like, honey?
- Emily! Emily, please just let my sister go!
- Got it!
All right, let's see...
- Oh, wait...
- Got it.
You want us to let
your sister go?
You want her to be let go?
Okay. Maybe we should
let her go.
Well, you know what actually,
you look so frail.
How about we feed her?
- Yeah.
Maybe get some food
in her. It's protein.
Yeah.
How about you, Marjorie?
How about we feed her?
Shut up.
Get the fuck away from me.
Stop moving.
Stop fucking with your sister.
Calm down.
I'm not gonna break you.
I'm just gonna fucking feed you.
Get her fucking hands.
Open up.
Open your mouth.
Here you go.
How about a banana?
Yeah. You wanna come
with us and eat a banana?
- Have some banana.
- I think she's finding it a little dry.
A little liquid.
Oh. There it is.
Here you go.
Are you fucking thirsty?
Get it open.
Here you go.
She's thirsty.
Your hair is so dry, baby doll.
Did you steal that
whiskey from my fucking store?
Let's moisturize it for you.
There you go.
Stop moving! Stop it!
Marjorie!
What are you doing?
I'm taking a video
with her phone.
What are you doing?
What did you not understand
about leaving no trace?
- Well, I just thought it was a fucking video.
- Jesus fucking Christ.
Hey! Look at me.
Look at me.
Were we ever here?
- Were we ever here?
- Were we ever fucking here?
- You liar.
- Are you ever gonna fucking say anything?
You are a lying little
whore, aren't you?
Were we ever here?
She's choking.
- She's choking.
She is choking. Oh my
God. Hit her on the back.
Hit her on the back.
- Get it off.
Get it off.
A little help here!
Fuck! Fuck!
What is wrong with her?
- What is wrong with her?
- What is wrong?
- Get her up.
She's choking.
Oh my God.
What's wrong with her?
Peanuts! Peanuts.
She's allergic to peanuts.
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck!
Get her EpiPen in
the purse in my room, please.
I'm sorry.
I can't hear you.
Please. Please. Please. I can't...
I'm sorry, what were you saying?
Lily. No, no, no.
Oh my God.
What the fuck is that?
Hurry!
Oh, no, no.
Fuck. Holy shit.
Fucking shit.
- Oh my God.
- Look at me.
- Lily. Lily. Lily.
Look at me, Lily.
Open, no. No, no, no.
Stay with me, baby.
Stay with me.
I love you, baby. Don't...
Epinephrine
for allergic reactions.
Hurry!
Give it to her!
Kinda looks like we're
too late though.
No.
Oh, no, no, no.
- Fuck. Fuck!
- Oh, no, baby.
- Shit. Oh my God.
- Lily.
- Oh, my fucking God.
- Lily, wake up.
- What's happened to her?
- Oh, no, no, no.
What did you do?
Oh, God.
You did it to yourselves.
She fucking resisted.
She fought back.
It would've been easier for her if
she'd stopped and had some respect.
- Why did you do this?
- It's her fault. It's her fault.
No, baby. Wake up,
Lily. I love you.
No, no, no, no, no.
Wake up. Wake up.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Kim, what are you doing?
- We have to make sure that...
- Take these.
- Okay.
- What are you doing?
We have to make sure this
place is spotless.
We have to wipe down
every surface.
We have to take all
of our trash.
- What about her?
- I am not losing my kids.
Do you understand me?
I'm not.
None of this has gone
the way I wanted it to go.
Try to relax! Okay?
You! You!
You did this!
- I didn't do anything!
- You did this!
You trash!
We did this for you!
- No, I didn't!
- You did this! You did!
We did this for your
ass so fuck you!
Shut up! Shut up!
It is nobody's fucking fault!
We didn't fucking know
that she was fucking
allergic to peanuts.
So shut up!
Marjorie.
Marjorie!
Get in here!
Kim.
- What?
Come here.
We all need to get
gloves on, okay?
What?
Put gloves on.
Oh my God.
We need to make it
look like a rape.
What?
No one's ever gonna suspect
women if they're raped.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm not gonna fucking do it.
Kim, I'm not asking
you to do it.
I can't...
We should go.
No!
We need to clean up our mess.
Look, it's no one's fault, okay?
Just do it.
I'm going to.
- I am helping clean.
- I need a fucking carrot.
I'll just keep cleaning.
Oh, God.
We shouldn't have worn shoes.
I'll tell you that much.
No. No. No.
Shut the fuck up.
Shut up!
No! No!
This is how you learn.
You deserve it.
Oh, God.
Oh my God.
Bitch.
I'm... I'm really sorry
that I yelled at you.
Okay?
- Okay.
I was just really,
really panicked.
I know.
And you didn't do
anything wrong.
And I don't think I can do it.
And...
I know that you're
really strong.
So...
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll do it.
I'll do this for you.
And then you'll model
my clothes for me.
What?
My clothes.
For the online store.
You'll model them.
Oh, God.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna throw up.
Kim.
Go outside
and find something for the body.
Okay?
Oh, Jesus. Fuck.
Fuck.
I found this.
I don't know what to do.
- That works. That works.
Okay. Okay.
- Marjorie.
- What?
Come help me.
- What the fuck?
All of our trash goes in here.
Okay?
Oh my God.
Oh my God. Oh my God.
Breathe.
I need you to breathe.
Okay?
Can you carry these cans?
- Okay.
- Can you carry these cans?
Okay. Good. Good.
Where are we taking them?
- We're taking it to the lake.
- Okay.
And the bag needs to sink, okay?
- Oh, fuck.
- Can you carry these?
Breathe.
- Okay. Yeah.
Breathe. Breathe.
Okay. Okay.
I'll just take them to the car.
Take them. Okay.
Fuck.
Guys, we have to go.
Right now.
All right.
Fuck, they're heavy.
- Push it.
- I got it. I got it.
Don't slip, her fucking
spit's all on the floor.
Oh, fuck. Fuck.
Fuck. Fuck.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Okay...
Got to clean.
Got to clean this.
Fuck.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Okay...
Okay, okay...
Emily, hurry up!
What the fuck are you
doing in there?
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Fuck...
Fuck!
Go! Get out.
Go. Okay.
Okay, stay. Stay. Stay.
Okay. Okay.
Oh, fuck.
She is fucking heavy!
Marjorie, will you help me?
Get your shit together.
Jesus!
Marjorie, just take another
fucking shot or something!
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Breathe. Breathe.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Listen to me.
- Okay.
- We need you to get in the car.
Get in the car.
- Okay. Yeah.
Okay.
Are we good?
We're good.
Just get in the fucking car.
Get in the fucking car!
- Did you get everything?
- I got everything.
After we dump them,
we gotta come back here and
we gotta clean everything.
- Okay.
- Carefully.
Okay?
- Okay.
Yes.
Every single inch
and we'll erase fingerprints.
- Everything will be spotless.
- Everything.
It will be fine.
No one.
No one will know we were there.
No one will ever find out.
Okay?
Oh, fuck.
You're okay.
We're okay.
Huh...
Is...
- Is your boat...
- Where are we going?
Where is your boat? I
don't... It's by the pier.
- Which pier?
- The one by that abandoned house.
By the... Okay.
We're gonna take
them there, okay?
We should just be
burying them in the woods.
With what, Leslie?
With a fucking shovel!
Where are we gonna get
a fucking shovel?
I bet you they fucking had one!
- Will you just shut the fuck up?
- Fuck you!
- Shut the fuck up!
- You are the one who fucking told us...
- Shut up!
- ...so don't piss me the fuck off!
- This is your fucking fault!
- You are screaming at me! Fuck you!
I did this for you!
I have good ideas!
I could get the fuck out
of this car right now,
then you're on your fucking own!
- Okay. Okay.
- Do you understand me?
No, no, no. Please.
Calm down. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Test me again, Emily,
and see where it
fucking gets you.
Kim, are we almost there?
- Are we almost there?
- Yes. Yes.
Marjorie, if you reach
into the glove compartment...
there should be
a headlamp in there
from one of my kiddos.
Okay.
Just...
- I got it.
- Did you get it?
- Yeah, I got it.
- Okay, good.
I'll get... I'll get out,
and...
Wait for the car to pass us.
...and open the gate.
Yeah.
Kim.
Come on.
Okay.
Marjorie, sorry I need that
headlamp that my boy left in there.
- Listen. - What?
- You're gonna need this.
Yeah. Thank you. You're
gonna pull the car around...
and bring the bag down to
the shore and meet me, okay?
Okay.
No...
Fuck.
Fuck!
God damn it.
Oh!
Fuck.
Fuck me.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay...
Fuck.
Okay.
You're okay.
We need to get them on the boat.
I'm pushing.
- Yeah.
- Got it?
I'm coming.
I'm coming. - Emily, you okay?
- Oh my God.
Coming. I'm coming.
I'm coming. Whoa!
Be quiet.
- Okay.
The house is abandoned.
No one's gonna fucking hear us.
- One, two.
- Three.
- Fuck.
- Okay.
You get on that side, Kim.
Okay, so pull.
We're pulling it.
- Push.
Keep going.
We got to get out of the mud.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Marjorie, get in
the back and help.
Okay.
I'll go around.
- Get up.
- Get in there.
Jesus. I'm trying to!
Help!
Okay.
See?
You needed a fucking friend.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
One of you in here with me.
I'll go.
Shit.
Okay.
Push us. Ready?
One.
Idiots!
Fuck you, Marjorie!
Fuck you.
Just fucking go.
It's getting too deep.
I can't push any farther.
Emily?
One, two, go!
Sorry.
One, two, three.
Fuck.
- Three.
One, two, three.
Here?
- Further.
- Here?
Jesus Christ.
Here?
Here. Okay.
Here.
Help me.
- I'm helping.
Fucking...
We did it.
Leslie, we did it.
Let's go.
Turn. Turn.
One, two, three.
Hold on.