(suspenseful music)
(engine rumbles)
- Fuck you!
(yelling)
- How much ya gonna give
me to fuck with this guy?
- Enough.
- And a hardy good evening to ya sir.
Tonight's cover charge
is gonna be 50 bucks.
- That's right, 50 bucks.
- Funny.
- I don't think you heard me.
50 bucks.
- You heard the man, 50 bucks.
- Yeah I remember when
I had my first drink.
Good night guys.
- I think you need to have a
better attitude around here.
(whacks)
- Thanks for the advice.
- Doors right over here.
(upbeat music)
- What the fuck was that man?
- Hey look, did that hurt?
Cause man it looked like it hurt.
- Fuck you Beeves.
- Fuck you butt head.
(rock music)
- What can I get you?
- Could you tell me where
the nearest hotel is?
- Yeah that south of here, south.
- About how far?
- What am I, a goddamn travel agent?
Pal I'm running a bar in a saloon,
what do you want to drink?
- No thanks.
(rock music)
I'll have a beer.
- That'll be five dollars.
- Five dollars?
- Five dollars.
- For one beer?
- For one beer.
(rock music)
What can I do for ya lady?
- A scoli and tonic.
- We don't have any scoli this is a joint,
those bottles are for show.
It's a bikers bar, beer and
wine now what can I get ya?
- [Lady] How about a glass of water?
- Water, I'm not running
a charity joint here.
- What are ya, out of glasses.
- This one's on the house.
- Thanks.
- It's service like that that'll
keep me coming back here.
- Chopsticks.
- Chop.
(laughs)
- [Man] I told ya to stay outta here!
- Yeah I got ya outta here
right here motherfucker.
Why don't you make us old man.
- This china man thinks
he owns this place.
(laughing)
- Hey jerky boy you still owe us 50 bucks.
- What's your name little girl
and don't tell me you're with this guy.
- I think she's ignoring you Lurch.
- Are you ignoring me,
or are you with this guy?
- Now why would I want
to ignore a drunken,
idiotic, slob, like you.
- I think she like you brother man.
- I think I need to
teach you some manners.
- I don't think so.
(whacking)
(crying out)
- Fuck this.
(yelling)
- No more bikers, no more bikers!
- You alright?
You better get outta here.
(engine rumbles)
(chatting)
- Hey wait.
Where ya going?
- I've kinda had my fill of
this place if you know what I mean.
- Yeah but you must be going somewhere.
- Mexico.
- Can I come along for the ride.
- Let's go.
(rock music)
(engine rumbles)
- [Lady] Where'd you learn
how to fight like that.
- I read a book.
- Looks like you wrote the book.
Thanks.
- Are you a regular there?
- God are you serious?
My boyfriend ditched me.
- Ditched you?
- Yeah we were fighting so I
told him just to let me out.
So you gonna drive all
the way to Mexico tonight?
- Bartender said there's some
hotels just south of here.
- Would you.
Wanna share a room?
- What would your boyfriend think?
- Screw him.
- You don't seem to be afraid of much.
- I'm not.
This.
- Thanks you should have told me.
Could have saved me some trouble.
I'm Jim.
- Stephanie.
(engine rumbles)
- afraid your boyfriends gonna show up?
- You never know.
He can be psychotic sometime.
So where you from?
- Up north.
- Where up north?
- Seattle.
- Got family?
- No.
- Ah.
You're the real mysterious type right?
- I'm just running from
my psychotic girlfriend.
- Okay no more questions.
Mind if I turn out the light.
- Go ahead.
(suspenseful music)
- You know you don't seem
to be afraid of much either.
(suspenseful music)
How do you know I won't try to rob you?
- Instinct.
(romantic music)
You always carry a gun?
- No.
- Only on dates.
- A woman's intuition.
(dramatic music)
- What does your intuition tell you now?
- To stay out of trouble.
(somber music)
- Stephanie.
Stephanie?
Damn.
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music)
Thanks for the ride.
- Hey man, you don wanna
partake in some speed?
- That's okay.
- Hey more for me!
Rock and roll!
(cheering)
(phone beeping)
- [Phone] Operator four
nine what city please?
- Hollywood, do you have a
number for Shara Williams?
- [Operator] Checking Hollywood,
I'm not showing listing
for a Shara Williams.
- Could you try Stephanie Williams?
- [Operator] I'm sorry there's
still no listing for that.
- Thanks.
(upbeat music)
- Excuse me.
Can I help you?
- No thanks.
(suspenseful music)
(door bell rings)
(barking)
(rattles)
(upbeat music)
- He's doing here?
- I don't know.
(upbeat music)
Should we call the police?
- I don't know.
(creaks)
- Hello!
(suspenseful music)
(cries out)
(shatters)
(crying out)
(whacking)
(suspenseful music)
- Holy shit.
- Freeze, let me see your hand, now.
Hands in the air or you will be shot.
Up turn around.
Against the wall.
- Shit.
He's a God damn lieutenant.
- He was trying to kill me.
- Did I say you could
move you son of a bitch?
- [Male Cop] I'm gonna go call it in.
(sirens)
- Doyle's here.
- [Female Cop] Yeah I heard about him,
he's the new captain
transferred in from 77 right?
- [Male Cop] That's him.
(chatter)
Captain Doyle, I'm officer
Roland, this is officer Sullivan.
- So what do we have here?
- Detective Bill Wilson, central division.
He was dead before we got here.
- Aw shit.
What the hell was he doing up here.
- Off duty, who knows.
The house is trashed the
suspects not saying anything.
- Where is the suspect.
- He's inside.
- One hell of a fuckin'
party, who lives here?
- The cars registered to a Shara Williams,
neighbor across the street saw
the suspect driving the car and then saw
him hopping the fence to the backyard.
- You read him his rights?
- Oh yeah.
- Okey dokey.
Where is she?
- And who are you?
- Who am I?
I'm gonna be your worst fucking nightmare
until you start breaking it
down for me do you understand?
Now where did you get the car?
- I'm done talking till I get a lawyer.
- That's very good,
you're a very mart man.
But you're gonna fucking need one.
- So you're her boyfriend,
you take her to the cabin
and you dump her is that it?
- No that's not it.
She told me her boyfriend
stranded her up there.
Look I didn't even ask
her to come with me.
- So where's she at now?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
You have her car, you're in
her house I mean where is she.
- I told you I don't know.
- Did you kill her?
- What?
- No I didn't kill her.
- I think you did kill her.
- I believe my client
has answered that question sufficiently.
- I believe your client is full of shit.
Who the fuck you were with last night?
The tooth fairy?
You wake up, she's gone but she leaves
you the keys to her brand new Beamer?
- She stole my car.
- What did you dive a Rolls Royce.
- Did you report it stolen?
I gotta tell you something son,
I think you're trying
to make a fool of me.
So you're driving a stolen
car, the owner is missing,
her house has been ransacked
and we got a police officer dead.
- That was self defense,
he was trying to kill me he got behind me.
- I got kidnapping, burglary,
grand theft auto and possibly
two counts of murder on you.
And I'm gonna see to it
personally that it sticks.
Take him down to CJ.
Get him the fuck outta my sight.
- We'll have you bonded in 24 hours,
don't worry I'll file
the necessary paper work,
everything they've got is circumstantial.
(buzzing)
(ringing)
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
- What the hell is this?
- Shut the fuck up.
- You guys are crazy.
- Just get up against the wall.
Don't move hot shot.
You gonna talk to us now.
- What what?
- You gonna tell us where
she is or am I gonna have to hurt you?
- I told you I don't know anything.
- Have a seat, stay a while.
Come on relax.
Now where is the tape?
(whacks)
(cries out)
Where's the tape?
- I don't know what you're talking about!
- Are you fucking stupid?
(whacking)
(cries out)
where is the tape?
Where is the tape?
This is fucking unnecessary,
where is the tape, and where is the girl?
Where is the tape and where is the girl?
- Alright, alright I'll
tell you where the tape is.
- Good.
- I'll tell you where the tape is.
- You're not so damn tough after all hm?
- He's a fucking pussy.
(whacking)
(crying out)
(dramatic music)
(shatters)
- You okay?
- Son of a bitch just broke my nose.
- Oh shit go, go, go.
(dramatic music)
(barking)
(crying out)
(gun fires)
(dramatic music)
- Stan!
(whacks)
(crying out)
(dramatic music)
(gun shots)
- Fucker!
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
5813 I've got
a officer down at 1400 north baldwin copy.
- [Radio] Copy that five alpha 13.
(suspenseful music)
(shatters)
(dramatic music)
(sirens)
- What the hell happened?
- He kicked out the back window.
We pursued him into this ware house
and he's gone, he might have gotten
a couple miles by now if he's fast.
Stan's in the yard in the back.
- Why didn't you call for backup Marvosa.
- He went to fast!
- Jesus what the hell were you thinking?
- It happened to fast, he's sitting
there quiet as can be and then boom,
we fanned out Stan must
have let his guard down,
I shot him, I shot him!
- I don't know how you
usually work Marvosa.
But this sounds like
damn sloppy work to me.
- This could have happened to anybody!
- Bullshit!
We have another cop dead Marvosa,
there is no excuse for this.
I want this son of a bitch back
in custody tonight do you understand?
- Yes.
- Do you understand!
- Yes!
- Does everybody understand?
We have a cop killer on the loose people.
I want to set a wider perimeter.
Three miles.
I want units at Baldwin,
Temple, Austin, and Nelson.
We are looking for a male in his 30's,
six feet, one inches tall,
185 pounds dark hair,
possibly wounded and cuffed.
Move out.
Give me a cigarette.
- Yes sir.
- No, no don't ever do that.
I don't smoke.
(suspenseful music)
(train horns)
(chattering)
- At least we got a blood
trail so we know he's been hit.
- I told ya I hit him.
- So we find his stiff ass in an alley
or we nail him at a hospital somewhere.
Ah Zydowski, it's about time.
- You won't like this.
I ran the prints from the house,
no police record on your suspect at least
not in our files but there
is match on the girl.
- Yeah?
- Her prints belong to Stephanie Field
convinced for soliciting two years ago.
- A hooker.
- That's not all.
- According to the computer
she died of a drug overdose last year.
- Ah a dead hooker, that's great Zydowski
you computer gals are really on the ball.
Listen call the print lab in at the FBI,
let's run the prints
through their library,
see if it's less screwed up than ours.
- Captain.
- Yeah?
- Garret found these in the alley way.
- Marvosa!
- Ya?
- What the hell is this huh?
Apparently we're dealing
with Houdini here?
- Must have gotten the keys off Stanton.
- Surprise, surprise.
I don't need this shit.
- Fuck this I'm gonna find him on my own.
- We're all gonna fan out.
Let do a sweep of the alleys Runyon.
- Yes sir.
- Marvosa let's be careful out there huh?
Don't take any chances.
Call for fucking back up this time.
(dramatic music)
(sirens)
(upbeat music)
(ringing)
- [Receptionist] Agent
Donovan LAPD on line one.
- Put 'em trough.
- This is Donovan.
Uh hu.
Okay put it through the main line
I'll access the file, hold on a second.
(suspenseful music)
Bingo.
(beeps)
I'm not finding anything on Jim Trudell.
Nope there's no file.
Alright thanks.
Give me agent Craig.
Yeah this is his baby.
(ringing)
- Hello?
- Yo DT.
- [DT] Yeah?
- It's Marvosa.
- [DT] What the fuck you calling
me so early in the morning for?
- I'm waking your ass
up, shut up and listen.
- Yeah waking my ass up,
I've been up all night
chopping cars getting ready
for the next shipment.
- That bitch had a partner.
He killed Stan.
Killed Wilson and he
just got away from me.
- So what?
- So what, they got enough
to shut our ass down.
- Yeah you mean shut your ass down.
- No I mean our ass mother fucker.
If I go down everybody
goes down especially you
and you're crew because
you're gonna get no trucks,
you're gonna get no protection,
maybe you'll get ten to
twelve you understand?
- So what the fuck do you
want me to do about it man?
- Hey listen I'm down town.
When we get the information on
this fucker I want you to come
down here and kill his ass
dead, we gotta get to him first.
- I've been up all night,
I gotta get some sleep.
I got plans today.
- Yeah, change them.
(upbeat music)
(beeping)
- [Phone] 911.
- I think my fathers
having a heart attack.
- [Phone] What is your address sir?
- A 22 Santa fey.
- [Phone] We'll have an
ambulance over there right away.
- Please, hurry.
I don't think he's gonna make it.
- [Phone] We'll be right there.
- Thanks.
(beeps)
- [Phone] Operator 487, can I help you?
- Operator I'd like to
make a collect call.
(ringing)
- Hello?
- [Phone] This it GT operator.
Will you accept a collect call from.
- Jim Trudell.
- Who?
- [Jim] Jim Trudell, Bravo company.
- [Operator] Will you
accept the charges sir?
- Yeah I guess.
- Tubbs it's me.
- Well where are ya, are ya drunk?
- No I'm in trouble.
- Well what's the matter?
- I met this girl I think
she's mixed up with some dirty cops.
They're trying to kill me.
- Aw man you are drunk.
Look I know it's been a long time
and I'd love to play
catch up but I gotta go.
- Tubs listen, I don't have anyplace
else to go, you gotta help me.
- Well what'd you get yourself into.
- It's a long story can we meet someplace?
- It's like seven o'clock in the morning.
- I'll have to call you back.
(sirens)
(suspenseful music)
- [Man] You sure it was A22 Santa Fey?
- [Man] Yeah that's what dispatch said.
- [Man] Aw man.
- [Man] This fucking early in the morning.
(suspenseful music)
(engine rumbles)
- Jesus, it's him!
(suspenseful music)
- [Man] Requesting backup.
- Back inside, police now, move.
(suspenseful music)
(tires screeching)
(sirens)
(suspenseful music)
(gun shots)
Damn it.
(suspenseful music)
(sirens)
- Did ya hit him?
- We wouldn't be in such a hurry if I did.
Go, go.
This is 6815 get me some one
from maintenance own here.
I want to know every place this damn thing
leads and get me back up
at every bridge cross over.
(suspenseful music)
(sirens)
(dramatic music)
Fucking guy does a great
cop field imitation.
(fire crackling)
(horn honks)
- Captain Doyle this
isn't looking to good.
- City maintenance said it he
could be anywhere if he did
make it into the system.
- This guy could not escape
a full scale man hunt.
(boat horns)
He isn't in this alone.
He's hold up somewhere or he
planned to get away somehow.
And I don't like people
getting away from me.
Meet me back at head quarters,
let's find out who this Jim Trudell is.
Who he knows where he's from, the works.
- Where ya going?
- I gonna check something out, Runyon.
(sirens)
(suspenseful music)
(engine rumbles)
How's it going?
See anybody come through here recently?
A guy?
About how long ago?
- About ten minutes.
- Thanks a lot.
(upbeat music)
- I already told I mean.
I mean the guy was just
like looking for trouble,
basically you know, shoving people around.
He was an asshole.
- And he took a swing at you?
- Yeah I mean the guy was a psycho.
I mean I was just there
to protect the girl.
- Did he harm the girl?
- Hell he probably raped her in some lot
and them dumped the body somewhere
I mean the guy was a real, he was a real?
- Wacko.
- Jeez you know that's not
what the bar tender told us.
(whacks)
Now you listen to me a seed.
If you don't want to
spend about a year in jail
for making a false report you'll
start giving me straight answers.
You understand that?
- Alright, alright we were just
like fucking around with him.
- Yeah he was fucking with him.
- Well.
I was just trying to
have some fun you know.
- What did he do to the girl.
- Nothing, he didn't do nothing.
- He just left and she went after him.
- She went after him?
- I don't know, I didn't see it.
- Yeah he was out by then.
What you were, you were out.
Man guy clocked ya.
- Take their statement
and get them outta here.
- What ya pushing me for?
- I hate your guts.
- Man.
(ringing)
- Hey man, heard about this morning.
I heard Doyle really went off on you.
You know I don't know if I like
that son of a bitch more
than I did Fletcher.
- Aw now come on, Doyle's just in from
the 77th he's just trying to be a hard ass
and he's just trying to prove himself.
- Marvosa.
- Ya.
- Come with me.
- Don't you take any shit from him.
- I don't take any shit form
anybody Meadows you know that.
So what the sisters have to say?
- That Shara Williams left the
bar with Trudell on her own.
- So what, lot of girls left the bars
with Ted Bunion that never
stopped him from hacking 'em up.
- Yeah but what was a
Hollywood hair dresser
doing some 60 miles away in some dire bar?
- She's no hair dresser
she's a fucking whore.
Come on, she picks him up, takes him home.
Fucks him, he kills her
dumps her body he steals
her car he busts into her house,
that's when Wilson finds him.
- Something else I don't understand.
Why the hell was Wilson up in Hollywood
in the first place last night.
Find that out for me alright.
- Excuse me captain.
- What?
- There's a guy waiting in the briefing
room who wants to speak with you.
- Who is it?
- I don't know, RT says he's with the FBI.
- FBI, what the fuck do the feds want?
- Aw let's go cheese cake,
checkout time was an hour ago, let's go.
Come on daddy warbucks let's go.
Drug addicts.
That's the guy.
- Can I help you?
- Captain Doyle?
- [Doyle] Yeah.
- Special agent Craig, FBI.
- That's detective Marvosa.
- Hi.
- [Craig] Hi.
- What can I do for you?
- Well your department called
the bureau regarding some
information on a Shara Williams.
- Ah Shara Williams yeah,
I heard nothing came up.
- That's right nothing on her.
But we did a little digging on Jim Trudell
at the request of the sargent Zydowski?
- Zydowski.
- Zydowski, sorry.
Jim Trudell, 31 years old, no priors.
He's been working in the
military for ten years.
- Agent Craig we ran the ID.
I could have told you that.
- I don't think you understand.
I don't mean he was shuffling
papers in some office.
I mean Jim Trudell worked
classified assignments.
Special forces, sabotage
mostly until last year.
He was brought out by espionage charges.
Charges that were later dropped.
He left he service and
we lost track of him.
- Wait a minute, wait a minute.
What are you getting at?
Are you telling me this guy has
some sort of agenda down here?
- I'm telling you the Breuer
considers all threats very seriously.
And as long as Jim Trudell is on
the streets he is a clear
threat to the public at large.
- But if what you say is true
why would he have killed
two police officers?
- Well that's the point
you see, he's slipped up.
But I'm sure if our departments
work together we can get
to the bottom of this.
- Cooperate?
- Every step of the way.
- If you guys want in fine.
Just remember this is my jurisdiction.
Marvosa.
- Captain we got a positive ID
of Trudell about 15 minutes ago in Venice.
- Okay guys we're back on the road again.
Notify all units we're on our way,
agent Craig you're my guest.
- I'm right behind you.
(dramatic music)
- Ya it's Marvosa, get down to Venice.
(upbeat music)
- [Phone] Operator can I help you?
- Operator I'd like to
make a collect call.
213 555 0972.
- [Tubs Answering Machine] Hi this is Tubs
sorry I can't answer the phone right now
but I'm out, leave a message.
- [Operator] Sorry sir, I'm
getting an answering machine.
- Thank you.
- How about you man?
You gonna pitch in something?
(sirens)
Hey asshole, hey.
- Alright ladies and gentlemen listen up
we all know who we're looking for.
I want everybody to play
it cool till the time
is right to make a move.
Let's not pull any gang buster
shit or we might loose this guy again.
- Or worse we might have a
hostage situation on our hands.
- If you can trail him
to a remote area, do it.
We all want a piece of this guy
but let's keep our heads and stay within
the law, we've got people
everywhere out here.
- These crowds are gonna be a bitch sir.
- I'm sure you can handle it,
right now I wanna do
an alley to alley sweep
beginning at the north and
south ends form Mariner to 30th.
Foot units you will
continue on the board walk.
That's it people, move out.
- I'm gonna take the south end.
- Fine.
(dramatic music)
- [Craig] Shall we?
(upbeat music)
- Yeah?
- [Marvosa] Who is this?
Give me DT.
- Hold on a second, DT.
It's for you.
- Yeah?
- [Marvosa] DT where you at?
- We're in Vinence.
- [Marvosa] Good good good, you set to go?
- Yeah what do you think?
- [Marvosa] Alright I want you
to stay by the phone alright?
- Whatever.
- [Marvosa] Don't hang up on me
man I want to stay in constant
contact with you, I want you.
(clicks)
- [Man] I pulled this freak out
of the trash bin ten minutes ago.
Wait a minute, that's him, that's him!
(dramatic music)
(sirens)
- Unit 51 request backup,
suspect spotted south, found on speedway.
(engine rumbles)
(sirens)
- Call for back up, well
cut him off the alley!
(sirens)
- DT he's on speedway get down there.
- Okay we're on our way.
He's on speed way let's go.
(clicking)
(engine rumbles)
(suspenseful music)
(sirens)
- He went that way I can't go anymore.
Go that way!
(sirens)
- Freeze!
(suspenseful music)
(sirens)
(gun shots)
(suspenseful music)
(whacks)
(cries out)
(tires screeching)
(gun shots)
- Shit.
(suspenseful music)
- Shit!
Where the fuck did he go God damn it.
(gun shots)
(suspenseful music)
(whacking)
(crying out)
- Where is he?
- I heard gun shots over there.
(suspenseful music)
(ringing)
- [Marvosa] DT where are you?
DT where are you, can anybody hear me?
- [Jim] Is that you Marvosa?
- Yeah who's this?
- Trudell, I just got your number.
- Fuck.
(sirens)
- Shit, what the hell is this.
- It's a car jacking, he took the car.
- What car?
- Gray Mercedes Bendz,
all jazzed up and shit, the guy's crazy.
- Son of a bitch.
- Did you get a license number?
- No but it was a brand new van.
- Which way'd he go?
- That way.
- That way, is he alone?
- By himself.
(sirens)
(suspenseful music)
(upbeat music)
- This is 6815, we have a code 37
black Mercedes Benz I need
an air unit right away,
last seen around Shell court.
(upbeat music)
(clicking)
(knocking)
- Holy shit.
- Hello Tubbs.
Can I come in.
- Yeah sure, come on in man,
you scared the hell out of me.
You know I thought I dreamt
that phone call this morning.
What the hell you been up to buddy?
Dude you look like shit, are you okay?
Jimmy you flipping out
on me, what going on?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- No.
- Look Jimmy you know I haven't seen
you in eight years, you show up on my door
like you're on drugs or something
the least you could do is tell
me what the fuck going on.
- Two cops are dead.
- What?
- I killed two cops.
- Oh shit, shit, shit.
Jimmy I don't know about this
man, I mean are you sure?
- Yeah I'm sure.
- Jimmy do you realize what
you've done that's like
death penalty shit.
- It was self defense
Tubbs, they were dirty.
I stumbled onto some auto theft
ring they were involved in.
You've gotta help me.
- Alright, alright you
saved my ass enough times,
what do you want me to do?
- I hope you haven't lost
your touch with this stuff.
- Shit what I have now made
our set up look like tinker toys.
I've been skipping through internal
revenue records all day, I
even got video strip poker.
So where do you wanna start?
- A girl named Shara Williams.
- Captain Doyle did
you read today's paper?
- No Zydowski, I did
not read today's paper,
it will just irritate the hell out of me.
- Well read this.
- So?
Something I don't know already?
- Well it's just kind of
a coincidence isn't it,
Stan and Wilson both started in 83,
both in area six, both in Vice?
- Hey they found the Mercedes Trudell
used in his getaway, it's
in a parking lot in Venice.
- Good, good we'll get it
to the nearest station,
hold it for prints.
You coming?
- Round trip or one way?
(chuckles)
- Where the hell is Marvosa?
- He said he was searching out some lead.
- Get his ass down to the garage.
Some lead.
(upbeat music)
- What's up man, what's going on?
What happened to DT?
- DT got shit canned so did
Droopy, the other two are dead.
- Damn.
Who's this fucking clown huh?
- I don't know, I don't know
where she got him I don't
know where he comes from.
He's very good, he given
me a real pain in the ass,
I could have hoped enough Mercedes
today to make half a million bucks.
I gotta get rid of this guy.
- We will, we get rid of him like that.
But you know what?
This time you gotta pay
you know what I'm saying?
If you want the pros it's gonna cost ya.
- It's gonna cost everybody
if I get shut down,
that's just the price of doing business.
- What ever homes, it's
gonna cost you 50 Gs.
That's it, 50 Gs is it on or what?
Hey homes, don't waste my
time is it on or what ey?
- You're on.
- Starting to bug me man.
- Not today man.
- [Radio] 5813 report to Burtell
tow n' pound lot 401 north Magnolia.
- Hello, 5813.
- [Radio] Please report to Burtell
tow n' pound lot 401
north Magnolia right away.
- I'm on my way.
(engine rumbles)
- So how do you know they
can't catch ya on this thing.
- I don't, but I'm pretty sure.
It's kind of a long story
but I cloned the serial link up
with the binary code scrambler,
sent it through a network main frame.
So if they do try to trace it
it'll be to a pick and save on Peeko.
- I knew I could count on you Tubbs.
- Yeah well I got a lot of free
time, you know what I mean.
Bagel?
- No thanks.
- Okay county tax records are showing
that a 601 Oxford court is owned by a
Atlantic trust corporation
with a PO box in Dc.
Nothing here about a Shara Williams.
- How about Marvosa and the others?
- I'm gonna have to
access the LAPD mainframe
but we gotta be careful,
that ones kinda tricky.
So what happened to ya
Jimmy, I figured you'd
be in some far off place somewhere
living life on the edge
like the good old days.
- I gave up all that, got
tired of all the lies.
They tried to stuff me in Levenworth
to cover there asses on
a botched assignment.
Got so I couldn't tell who to trust.
Somethings never change.
- Yeah well no ones gonna cover
your ass this time either.
- So what else is new?
- Yup.
I got something here.
Personal records here on
Wilson, Stanton, Marvosa.
Addresses, and phone numbers.
Bingo, I'll cross reference
them to see what we got.
(suspenseful music)
- Agent Craig, we got a call.
(whirring)
- So what do we got in there?
- What don't we have in here?
We have Cd player, radar
detector, cell phone.
Automatic weapons.
- What is this?
- Get away car, did you
say cell phone Zydowski?
- [Zydowski] Yeah.
- Well that just may be out ticket.
- What do you mean?
- Maybe Jim Trudell called
someone from the car.
- He'd have to be pretty
fucking stupid to do that,
I mean he knows hat we're
gonna find the car right?
- Maybe but it would be even
stupider not to check it out.
- Marvosa why don't you get
that information for us,
call the phone company find out what calls
were made on this extension
over the past 48 hours.
- You got it.
- Well I guess it's safe to assume
this guy has some sort of weapon on him.
- Well he had quite the
election to choose from.
The question is who's his next target.
- Marvosa.
When did you join the force?
- What?
- When did you join the fore.
You know the police
force the place you work.
- 1984, why what the fuck
difference does that make?
- Did you start out area six?
- Yeah.
- So you must have known
Wilson and Stanton huh?
- They worked Vice I seen 'em around.
- Well don't you think
that's a little odd?
- What?
- Well it's kind of a
funny coincidence isn't it?
- They had to start someplace.
- Where did you start Mavosa?
- Traffic.
- [Man] Doyle.
- Yeah?
- We got some hacker
accessing your personnel
files of detectives Wilson and Stanton.
Yours to Marvosa.
- The fuck are you talking about?
- Do we have an address.
- Yeah.
- Alright this could be or guy Trudell.
Get a swat team on that
building right away.
Come on let's get down there
and find out what the hell is going on.
Craig you stay with Marvosa.
- Hey, hey Jimmy check this out.
Look Marvosa makes calls
to their fax number
over seas and this is
Switzerland country code.
- A bank?
- I don't know maybe he's
selling swis army knives,
I can't access that but look at this.
These are their local account
records for Wilson and Marvosa.
- Stealing cars is big business.
- Yeah well they certainly
ain't police salaries.
(ringing)
Hello?
- [Stephanie] I want to
speak to Jim Trudell.
(dramatic music)
- I think you to he wrong number.
- [Stephanie] Jim I know you're there,
you've got to get out of there right now.
The police are on the way meet me at
the ware house on the corner
of silver bay and Nohiot
park as soon as you can.
- What's going on?
- You'll find out soon enough.
- Shit, shit, shit, shit
they're gonna skin me alive.
- That was her the girl, we have to go.
- No I'm not going anywhere.
- Tubbs these people mean business.
- Look I told you I'm not going anywhere,
I've got my whole life in this place.
- Stop being so damn stubborn.
- Look I can't help you
anymore Jimmy I'm sorry.
(clicking)
- I don't got anyway to get there.
(suspenseful music)
- It's a Harley down in the garage,
I don't exactly use it anymore.
- Thanks for everything Tubbs.
- Don't forget the helmet.
You don't want a ticket on your record.
(suspenseful music)
(sirens)
(engine rumbles)
Who the fuck are you?
Don't you guys ever knock?
- Where is he?
- Long gone.
- You don't mind if I don't
take your ord for that do you?
- No, no look around all you want,
just walk softly I got a cake in the oven.
(dramatic music)
- [Radio] 6815 do you copy?
- 6815 go.
- [Radio] We've got a unit on
the scene reporting this
address is coming up short.
Looks like a pick and save you copy?
- A pick and save?
- They must be kidding.
- Am I hearing you correctly?
- That is correct captain.
- We're on our way anyway,
I want to see this with my own eyes.
What the hell is going on.
- So he's long gone huh?
- Yeah I asked him not to tell me
where he's going, I told
him I didn't want any part.
- Got a license for this weapon?
- Yeah I got it registered
with the DMV last week.
- Then you're a smart man.
- That's right.
And that's all I'm gonna say.
- You got some balls
man, you got some balls.
(gun shots)
(engine rumbles)
(suspenseful music)
- Hi Jim.
- Hands in the air please, FBI.
- Understand there's a lot
of people looking for you.
I know how that feels.
- Why did you set me up?
- I didn't.
I thought maybe you'd be smart enough
just to leave everything alone,
I left you the keys to the BMW.
- Well you thought wrong
and now I'm public enemy number one.
You got something to say to that?
- Yeah it was my life that
was in danger not yours!
- What the hell are you talking about?
- I'm a witness.
- A witness to what?
- Six months ago a police officer
was found dead in a hotel room.
Charlie Fletcher.
Blew his brains out.
He didn't leave a note,
maybe you heard about it.
- No but I'm listening.
- It wasn't a suicide he
was killed by professionals.
I was in the bathroom when it happened.
- Well didn't these professionals
figure he had a girl in his room?
- Yeah they did.
One girl.
- Don't go yet.
Not yet.
- I'll be back.
(dramatic music)
Charlie Fletcher liked to move
around a lot but he was a regular.
And he always paid for the kink.
I had to call another
appointment and cancel,
Fletcher wanted to party all night.
And he made it worth my while.
- Hey Marvosa, what he hell
are you doing here man?
- [Stephanie] But then I
heard the front door open.
And I heard voices.
(gun fires)
And a gun shot.
- Listen don't kill me
man, I didn't do it.
Please don't kill me,
listen I didn't do it.
(gun fires)
- [Marvosa] You been a bad boy,
now you're a dead motherfucker.
Sleeping with a 14 year
old girl you bad boy.
- [Stephanie] It seemed
like I waited forever before coming out.
And when I did.
There they were.
No struggle no commotion just dead.
- [Jim] Then what you'd do?
- [Stephanie] I just waned to get out,
I grabbed my stuff up and then I found it.
- [Jim] Found what?
- [Stephanie] I noticed
something behind the curtain.
It seemed like Charlie liked
to watch over and over again.
I got it all on tape.
That's when I met him.
Told him what I had.
The FBI set me up in a new place.
The cops found me somehow so I ran.
That's when I met you.
- So what happened to the tape?
- It's in a safe place.
- So you know about Stanton,
Wilson, and Marvosa.
- Oh yeah, they were fancy and luxury
cars and making sure the
thefts weren't followed up on.
- You found all this out
and you didn't do anything?
- Well I didn't go after
them if that what you mean.
They came to me.
Once the detectives found
that empty video camera in the motel room.
- What?
- Hi.
Hi.
- Sorry about this, I
didn't want to do this.
I didn't want to get in this deep.
But money talks you know what I mean?
(dramatic music)
- You know you're crippled buddy
was a brave man, it's
to bad you killed him.
- You son of a bitch!
- Hey, hey, come on now,
we still got work to do.
Now Stephanie I know you
made copies of that tape.
And now you're gonna
show us where they are.
(gun fires)
(shatters)
(whacking)
(crying out)
- [Stephanie] Come on let's go, let's go!
(dramatic music)
- Where the fuck where you?
(gun shots)
(dramatic music)
(whacking)
(crying out)
(gun shots)
(whacking)
(crying out)
- Let's go!
(dramatic music)
Come on.
(gun shots)
(dramatic music)
The van, come on.
(engine rumbles)
- Come on let's go.
(suspenseful music)
(gun firing)
- Get the fuck out of there.
(yelling)
(suspenseful music)
(gun shots)
(shatters)
(yelling)
(suspenseful music)
(honking)
(alarm ringing)
- The gate.
(rattling)
Shit, come on.
Get behind the dumpster.
(suspenseful music)
(whacking)
(crying out)
- Jim look out!
(gun fires)
- Shut the fuck up you stupid bitch.
You've been giving me a real fucking
headache for about two days you know that?
And now I'm about to give you one.
(whacking)
(crying out)
Come on, come here.
(gun shots)
(dramatic chord)
(sirens)
- I thought you were shot.
- I was just faking it.
(crying)
(sirens)
- Haven't you ever heard
of a bullet proof vest?
Don't even try it, don't even try it,
I will fucking kill her!
I will cut her!
(dramatic music)
(gun fires)
- Trudell, put the gun down.
(chattering)
- There's plenty more
where this came from, here.
- What is it.
- I don't want to ruin the surprise.
- Ah yes, more surprises that
all I need, tag this Runyon.
With time it's looking
better and better everyday.
- You alright?
- I'll live.
- Good cause I have
several thousand questions
that the two of you are
gonna answer for me.
- Great maybe this time you'll believe me.
- Maybe I will.
You know you would have made
one hell of a cop Trudell.
- Wasn't in the cards.
- Let's go.
- You know there's something
I've been meaning to ask you Stephanie.
- Yeah?
- Where the hells my car?
- Uh.
Have you ever heard of the Liefolk river?
- [Jim] No.
- [Stephanie] I didn't either.
I'll make it up to you.
Promise.
(chuckles)
(upbeat music)