[ Clicking ]
[ Record Needle Turning
On Turntable ]
♪ [ "The Girl Can't Help It"
By Little Richard ]
[ Men ]  ♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ She can't help it
[ Little Richard ]
♪ If she walks by
the menfolks get in close ♪
[ Men ]
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ If she winks an eye, the
bread slice turn to toast ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ Yeah, she got a lot
of what they call the most ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ The girl can't help it
She was born to please ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ And if she's got
a bigger man to squeeze ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ Won't you kindly be aware ♪
♪ The girl can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ Yes, she mesmerizes
every mother's son ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ If she smiles, the beefsteak
become well done ♪
[ Sizzling ]
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ She make Grandpa
feel like 21 ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ The girl can't help it
She was born to please ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ And if I go to her
on bended knee ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
[ Toy Squeaking ]
♪ Oh, won't you kindly be aware
that I can't help it ♪
♪ I can't help it ♪
♪ Because I'm hopin'
obviously ♪
♪ That someday
the answer will be ♪
♪ The girl can't help it
'cause she's in love with me ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
[ Screaming ]
♪ If she walks by
the menfolks get in close ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ If she winks an eye, the
bread slice turn to toast ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ She got a lot
of what they call the most ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ The girl can't help it
She was born to please ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ And if she's got
a bigger man to squeeze ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
♪ I am hopin'
obviously ♪
♪ That someday
the answer will be ♪
♪ The girl can't help it
'Cause she's in love with me ♪
♪ She can't help it
The girl can't help it ♪
[ Kissing Sound ]
Hey, hey, hey, rock and rollers.
Whoa !  It's 3:00.
What time is it ?
[ All Shouting ]
It's Danny the K time !
- Kapow !  Okay.
- [ All ]
Kapow !
What do you say we head off
to the hop with Fats Domino ?
Come on, everybody.
Let's do the stroll !
♪ Come on, baby ♪
♪ Be kind
when you say good-bye ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
♪ You're the one to blame ♪
[ Girls ]
Wow !  Ooh !
♪ You broke my heart ♪
[ Guy ]
Whoo !  Way to go !
♪ When you said we'll part ♪
[ Girl Laughing ]
Yeah !
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
[ Cheering ]
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
[ All Laughing ]
[ Whispering ]
There's the TV studio.
Hurry up, everybody.
♪ Good-bye
Ain't that a shame ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
Sireena, what
are you doin' ?
You know we can't go in there.
Yeah, coloreds
aren't allowed.
Well, I was just peeking.
I mean, I'm allowed to peek.
There are no laws against it.
Are you kidding ?  Have you
ever heard of a "peeking Tom" ?
[ Together ]
That's "peeping" Tom.
Whatever.
Well, we gotta get Danny the K
to notice us.
I'm sure, just by standing here,
he will notice us.
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
Yeah !
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
[ Girl ]
Go, Cookie !
Dance !
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
- [ Girls Laugh ]
- [ Crashing ]
- ♪ You're the one to blame ♪
- [ Girl ]  Yeah !
- [ Danny ]  Oooh !
Tony !
All right, all right, all right.
Let's hear it for the fat man...
who was last week's guest and
still number ten on the charts !
[ Cheering, Applause ]
By the way, I'm still Dan the K
for you people out in TV-land
who don't know that.
And I'm here to startle
your mind and get your body
movin' to the beat.
Am I right ?
[ All ]
Yes !
Are we rock and roll ?
[ All ]
Yes !
Kapow !
[ All Shouting ]
I say we find one of
our June Taylor dancers.
Huh ?
Mmm.  Bop !
[ Laughs ]
[ Gasps ]
Hey.  So, girls, are you
comfortable ?  Talk to the
Dan-man, little chickey-doodle.
What's your name ?
Susan Doyle.
Well, you gotta be loud
enough so the people
at home can hear you.
Susan Doyle.
And, Susan, what school
do you go to ?
I go to Lakeview High.
Go, Crocodiles !
[ All Cheering ]
Oooh !
Crocodiles give the Dan-man
the heebie-jeebies.
[ Kids Laugh ]
Ha-ha-ha !  Susan, you got
any special interests ?
Music.  Music's my life.
Ooh.  That's what I love
to hear.  And, Susan,
what's your friend's name ?
My name is--
Tony Fazio.
Tony, you remind me of somebody.
Anybody ever tell you that ?
- Kapow !
- An impression !
Don't tell me.
The Three O'Clock Hop !
Kapow !
Oh !  Ed Sullivan !
[ Kids Laugh ]
Hey, don't feel bad !
That's just some
of the Dan-man's shenanigans.
Susan, you like Fats Domino ?
Yeah, but we like
Ruth Brown better.
A-A-And Connie Francis !
Oh, we love Connie Francis !
Well, what do you say I play
a little Connie Francis
later on in the show ?
Whoa !  Okay, kids,
it's now the moment
we've all been waiting for.
That's right.  It's a word
from Wellneck's Pharmacy.
Yes, if you have
an acne problem, Wellneck
will make it their problem.
Take it away, zit city !
♪ Shoo-do, shoo-do
Shoo-do, shoo-do
Shoo-do ♪
♪ Shoo-do, shoo-do
Shoo-do, shoo-do ♪
♪ Shoo-do ♪
[ Motors Revving ]
[ Motors Stop ]
Hey !
You know, we ought to stick
together, 'cause, uh, they won't
let us in there neither.
But you're trouble, buddy.
We're talent.
[ Laughs ]
Ooh !  You're
trouble, Lucky.
I am.
All right !  You ready
for a special guest ?
- [ All ]
Yeah !
- Eddie Cochran !
[ Kids Cheering ]
♪ [ Bass, Percussion ]
[ Gasps ]
Look at him !  Oh, God.
He owns the world, you know ?
I can't wait to get out of here
and graduate and, and,
and be somebody.  You know ?
Yeah.
Come on, come on.
♪ Well, c'mon, everybody, and
let's get together tonight ♪
♪ I got some money in my jeans
and I'm really gonna
spend it right ♪
♪ Well, been a-doin' my homework
all week long ♪
♪ And now the house is empty
and my folks have gone ♪
♪ Whoo
C'mon, everybody ♪
[ Girls Scream ]
♪
More deviled eggs,
anyone ?
Oh, yes.  Have you been
reading those Campbell Soup
labels lately ?
Those recipes.
Oh, my goodness,
the cream of asparagus ?
Yes !
Ah, with those
little toasted almonds ?
Scrumptious.
I'll tell you,
I found a lifesaver.
Chicken a la king in a can.
♪ [ TV Continues, Indistinct ]
The whole thing ?
In a can ?
The chicken, the noodles,
the gravy.
Oh.
All you have to add
is the potato chips.
[ Laughs ]
Well, life is certainly
getting easier for us girls.
[ Hostess Laughs ]
Look, Margo.
There's your Susan !
[ Margo ]
It can't be.
Oh, it is.  It's Susan.
My goodness, I've never
seen her move that way.
♪ [ Continues ]
I'm surprised you
let her dance on that show.
They let Negroes sing
on that show.  Live.
In front of the children.
- You're kidding.
- [ Gasps ]
I like the way they dance,
though.  It's very expressive.
[ Inhales, Chuckles Awkwardly ]
Really, it's too wild
for my taste, though.
[ Clears Throat ]
You know Danny Klay, the host,
is an ex-con.
No !
Yes.
He spent time in juvenile hall.
I did my research.
I like to know
what I'm talking about.
What is this country
coming to ?
Mmm.
[ Shudders ]
Margo, it's your move.
- [ Clears Throat ]
Margo !
- ♪ C'mon, everybody ♪
- [ Guest ]
Margo ?
- Margo ?
♪ [ Drums ]
Okay, as you go off
into the night,
and you park your car
along that ridge,
watch the submarine races.
This is Danny the K reminding
you to be nice to your baby.
♪ [ Drums Continue ]
And if you are,
maybe she'll be nice to you.
- Yummy.
- [ Kids ]
Ooh !
Eddie Cochran, get out here.
[ Kids Cheering ]
Take a bow, pal.
Sweet dreams.
Man, what a waste of time,
dancin' on TV.
On the Road.
Man, you been readin'
that book for months.
Let me see.
Hey.  So I'm a slow reader.
Shoot me.  Finally made it
to the last page.
Check it out.
"So in America,
"when the sun goes down,
and I sit on the old
broken-down river pier,
"watchin' the long, long skies
over New Jersey, and sense
all that raw land...
"that rolls in one
unbelievable huge bulge
over to the West Coast,
"and nobody-- nobody--
knows what's going to happen
to anybody...
"besides the forlorn rags
of growin' old,
"I think of Dean Moriarty.
I even think of old
Dean Moriarty,
"the father we never found.
I think of Dean Moriarty."
Poetry.
Let me see that.
"Dean was very quiet
and preoccupied,
"lookin' at the old bums
in the saloon...
that reminded him
of his father."
Man, I hate books.
♪ Da, da, da
Da, da, da ♪
♪ Da, da, da, da
Come on, everybody ♪
♪ Da, da, da
Da, da, da
Da, da, da, da ♪
♪ Come on, everybody ♪
All right, all right.
Where's the band
practicin' tonight ?
Cookie's !
Oh, right.
And after I make dinner,
do the dishes
aput my brothers to bed,
I'll have plenty of time
to practice.
Cookie, doesn't your
mother do anything ?
Yes, drink.
[ Tony Snorts ]
Well, what about
your garage, Tony ?
Yeah, you got a big one.
Garage, that is.
[ Susan Laughs ]
Wouldn't you like to know,
nest-head ?
Ooh.
My father won't let me within
three feet of that garage.
He's got his prized '48 Hudson
in there, and the two of them
are gettin' very close.
Hmm.  Well, we gotta find
someplace to practice.
♪ You saw me standing alone ♪
♪ Do, do, do-do-do
Blue, blue, blue, blue moon ♪
♪ Without a dream in my heart ♪
♪ Do, do, do-do-do
Blue, blue, blue, blue moon ♪
♪ Without a love of my own ♪
♪ Do, do, do-do-do ♪
♪ Bom-ba, bom-ba
Dang, a-dang-dang ♪
♪ Blue moon ♪
C'mon.
♪ Blue, blue moon ♪
[ Gasping, Laughing ]
♪ Blue moon
You knew just ♪
♪ What I was there for ♪
♪ Do, do, do-do-do
Blue, blue, blue, blue moon ♪
- ♪ You heard me saying
a prayer for ♪
- ♪ Do, do, do-do-do ♪
♪ Someone I really
could care for ♪
♪ Do, do, do-do-do, ooh ♪
♪ Wah, wah, wah, wah ♪
♪ And then suddenly
you appeared ♪
♪ Ah dih-dih do, ah dih-dih do ♪
♪ Before me ♪
♪ Ah dih-dih do
Ah dih-dih do ♪
♪ The only one ♪
♪ Ah dih-dih do ♪
♪ My arms will ever hold ♪
♪ Ah dih-dih do, ah dih-dih do
Ah dih-dih do ♪
♪ Whisper please adore me ♪
♪ Ah dih-dih do, ah dih-dih do
Ah dih-dih do ♪
♪ And when I looked
the moon had turned to gold ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Blue, blue moon ♪
♪ Blue moon, do, do, do-do-do
Blue, blue, blue, blue moon ♪
♪ Now I'm no longer alone ♪
♪ Without a dream in my heart ♪
♪ Do, do, do-do-do
Blue, blue, blue, blue moon ♪
- ♪ Without a love of my own ♪
- ♪ Do, do, do-do-do ♪
♪ Bom-ba, bom-ba
Dang, a-dang-dang
A-ding, a-dong-ding ♪
♪ Blue ♪
♪ Blue, blue moon
Blue moon ♪
Hey !
♪ Do, do, do-do-do
Blue, blue moon, blue moon ♪
Hey !
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Do, do, do-do-do ♪
♪ Blue, blue moon, blue moon ♪
[ German Accent ]  Didn't
I tell you not to do that ?
♪ Do, do, do-do-do ♪
♪ Ba-ba-da, ba-ba
Stop !        Bom-bom-bom ♪
♪ A-dang, a-dang-dang
A-ding, a-dong-ding ♪
♪ Blue moon ♪
All right !  All right.
[ Cheering ]
All right !
Okay.
You asked for it.
I'm calling the cops.  Ah.
[ Kids Groan ]
Oh, hey, come on.  You--
You don't have to call the cops.
Mr. LaGrange, music is good
for your business.
- People love to hear music.
- Not your music.
What the hell do you mean
by that ?
Calm down.
You people stay out
of this neighborhood.
[ Sighs ]
You don't belong here.
You got your own place.
- Mmm.
- Am I making myself clear ?
Mm-hmm.
Hmph.  Yeah.
Perfectly clear.
All right.  Go home.
[ Inhales Loudly ]
Leave us alone, huh ?
Mmm.
- Pig !
- [ Kids Gasp ]
Why don't you go back to
Nazi Germany where you belong ?
[ Kids Muttering ]
Who said that ?
I did.  What are
you gonna do about it ?
[ Exhales ]
[ Chuckles ]
- Nazi Germany ?
- [ Kid ]
Yeah !
Well, it was... the worst thing
I could think of.
Let's go, you guys.
I'm gonna take the bus.
Sue.  I got homework.  I'll see
you guys tomorrow.  Bye, Cook.
[ Giggling ]
Hey, Red.
Yeah, I-- I liked the way
you did that.
What, is there somethin' wrong
with just talkin' to me ?
I don't think we have
anything to talk about,
Mr. Desperado.
How 'bout I just give you
a little ride home, and, uh,
we'll see
if we need conversation.
'Cause I don't want a ride.
You could ask me tomorrow, and
I still wouldn't want a ride.
Or you could ask me
the day after tomorrow
or a week from Tuesday,
and I still
wouldn't want a ride.
[ Laughing ]
You're so desperate.
Get used to it.
Come on, Cookie.
Hey, what is it about me
that you don't like ?
I mean, is it my hair ?  Is it
my cycle ?  'Cause, you know,
I'd change it all for you, Red.
You want to know
what I don't like ?
I don't like your
shiny motorcycle...
or your shiny hair...
or your shiny,
slippery...
personality.
[ Choking ]
Can you understand that ?
No.  Can you understand
that, Bubber ?
What ?
She won't hitch a ride
with me.
She's a waste of time, Lucky.
Hey, anytime you want to dance
for like, real, call me.
'Cause I'm a fine dancer.
I'm a real fine dancer.
I think he's kinda cute.
Yeah.  Kinda.
All right, all right, all right.
Let's go.  We got five minutes
of cartoons left.
Let's get the gourmet in here.
Oh, oh, Klay.  Listen.
You gotta stop the kids
from dancing so close.
I'm gettin' calls.
From who ?  The Marines ?
Ha-ha.  It's not funny.
From their parents !
They don't like to see their
kids dancing close like that.
Huh ?  I keep getting the calls.
Now, what if they stop
watching ?  Th-Th-The parents,
I'm talking about !
Parents buy products, and if
parents stop buying products,
then sponsors cancel.
And if sponsors cancel, then I,
among others, lose my job.
You're out of breath,
Lipsky.  You gotta watch
your health.
Take a deep breath.  Relax !
It's good for ya.
Come on.  Pull up a bleacher.
[ Exhales ]
Don't you remember
being a teenager ?
being lonely ?
I mean, real lonely ?
So you head off to the U.S.O.
to chase some skirt.
And when you get there, every
dame in the joint is gorgeous.
And one always comes up to you
and asks you to dance.
You can't say no.
Even if you don't
have the moves.
And then, the moment
you've been waitin' for.
You're holding her
in your arms...
as close as you can.
You feel her body...
pressed right up
against yours.
Think about it, Lipsky.
Has there ever been
a better moment ?
Huh ?
[ Inhales ]
B-B-But that's the U.S.O.
We-- We don't do that here.
This is television.
This is rock and roll,
and it goes directly
to your libido.
Oh, look !  Spare me the smut.
We got a big responsibility
here.
There must be...
hundreds of people watching us.
You gotta give them
good, clean, healthy teenagers !
Watch your health, Lipsky.
[ Man ]
♪ My life ♪
♪ Don't seem so endless ♪
You're usin' an awful lot
of big strokes there, Susan.
♪ [ Continues ]
That's not my nose
you're painting, is it ?
It's my interpretation
of you, Cookie.
It's an artist's prerogative.
If you say so.
Well, it's how Salvador Dali
would paint you.
Hmm ?  If you say so.
It's part realistic,
part abstract.
Like my life, in other words.
[ Laughs ]
Do you think
I should cut my hair ?
No, I don't know.
I kinda like it.
I mean, it adds height.
I mean, I think that's
a good thing for me.
Right ?
Oh, yes.  Very good.
I mean, your eyes--
they go to my hair...
and not my body.
But-- But you've
got a great body, Cookie.
I do ?
Yeah.
♪ In lonely years
I find my dreams are of you ♪
What do you think that biker
Lucky does all day ?
Mr. Desperado ?
[ Chuckles ]
Nothin'.
Absolutely nothin'.
Well, how can a guy do nothin'
all day ?  Wh-What kind of guy
does nothing ?
A juvenile delinquent.
[ Laughs ]
Well, pretty soon I'll be moving
away from juvenile delinquents
and guys named Lucky.
Maybe I'll meet
some cute college guy.
Some guy named Walter.
Yeah.  You know, I could go
for a college guy named Walter.
- Or-- Or Herman.
No.  Or Allen or Henry.
- Yeah.  Mm-hmm.
- Or Brian.  Yeah !
- Cookie, put the sax up
and pose.
Oh.  Oh, sorry.
♪ Happy days are here ♪
♪ My face is full of gladness ♪
You know, I plan to go as far
away from here as possible.
Can I visit you, Susan ?
Wherever you go ?
[ Knocking ]
How many times
have I asked you to knock ?
I did knock.
- What is it ?
- It's Cookie.
- ♪ Now that I have you ♪
[ Gasps ]
♪ Now that I have you ♪
A-As Dali would do it.
Why can't you
paint a pretty picture ?
Like a--
Oh, a little, furry kitty
with big sad, droopy eyes,
whiskers and--
[ Smothered Giggles ]
One quick question, Susan.
What were you doing
dancing on that show ?
What show ?
You know, I--
I better go home now.
I gotta set the table.
I'll look exactly the same
tomorrow.  Bye.
Bye, Mrs. Doyle.
[ Sighs ]
You told me you were going
to the library.
I'm going to have to talk
to your father about this.
Dinner's in half an hour.
I'll need some help
with the table.
Sireena, where you been ?
Sorry, Mama.
Now, you know I get worried.
Do you think we got
enough potatoes here ?
How many people did the reverend
say we had to feed ?
About 30.
You know, Mama,
I'm gonna be
a famous singer one day.
I'm gonna sing on TV,
on the Danny Klay show.
This ain't gonna
be enough potatoes.
I'm gonna have to mix
some celery in here.
Mama, didn't you just hear
what I said ?
I said I'm gonna sing
on the Danny Klay show.
Sireena, you are gonna sing
in church.
Now, church is where you
gonna be singin', okay ?
Mama, church ain't a career.
Church can't make you
famous.
Mahalia Jackson's famous.
I don't wanna be
Mahalia Jackson.
I wanna be like Fats Domino.
Girl, you better keep your feet
on the ground.  Hmph.
[ Chuckles ]
You ain't gonna be Fats nobody.
Mama, you were gonna
be a singer once.
Don't you remember
how that feels ?
No, I don't.
Okay, let's just forget
this whole conversation.
I won't have any dreams.
Mmm.  What's the point ?
I'll just do what I'm supposed
to do:  Stay in the house
and have a dozen kids...
and peel potatoes
for the rest of my life.
Sireena, will you use
your head ?  But now, listen.
You see any Negro singin'
on that Danny Klay show ?
Yes, ma'am.
Fats Domino.
Fats Domino !
One fat Negro.
[ Scoffs ]
And he just got lucky.
Ah, no.  You stick with your
schoolbooks, and you'll be fine.
[ Sighs ]
Mama, you just tryin'
to get me to stop dreamin'.
Well, baby.  Sometimes
it's better that way.
[ Sighs ]
More creamed onions, anyone ?
No, thanks, hon.  I'm fine.
Oh, maybe just a little.
That's--
That's perfect, dear.
Frank, we've got a problem.
- Susan lied to me about
going to the library.
- I didn't lie.
She told me she was going to the
library, and she went dancing
on that Danny Klay show instead.
- Now, what do you
think of that ?
- I-I-Is that a trick question ?
I don't think this is
the first time she's lied.
Oh, come on.
It's not so horrible.  I knew
you wouldn't let me go dancing.
I didn't want to hurt your
feelings, so I didn't tell you.
They have Negroes
on that show, Frank.
They let Negroes sing in front
of all those white children.
Hey, you have
Ella Fitzgerald records.
But I would never
go see her in person.
- Agh !
- I mean, you should
see this, Frank.
They really dance wild
on that show.
Dad, it's rock and roll.
It's got drums !
It's got a beat.
Yeah.
It's--
African.
What ?
Is Elvis Presley African ?
I mean, the way they dance
is pretty wild.
It's like some kind
of foreplay !
[ Fork Clatters ]
I can't believe you said that !
- Mom, you're perverted !
- Susan Doyle,
you go to your room.
Foreplay ?  Dad !
Is that out of line,
or am I crazy ?  Huh ?
You know, one question
at a time, all right ?
WHat was your--
You had a first question.
Don't ever call me perverted.
I am your mother.
You just don't get it.
[ Sighs ]
Susan.  I have had a life.
Your father was a Navy man.
I was only in the Reserves,
honey.  It wasn't--
I know when something isn't
right, and this dancing thing...
I'm sorry.
is not right.
[ Sighs ]
Fine, fine !
I'll just go dance
in my room...
and have foreplay
with my pillow.
Dancing African foreplay.
Agh !
[ Door Slams ]
I'm frightened, Frank.
She's out of control.
Oh, honey.  It--
It's just a phase.
That's all it is.
It-- It's just a phase.
That's all.  Mmm.
Yea, Crocodiles !
[ Together ]
Do, do, do, do, do, do !
Pamela Jordan.
[ Laughing ]
Do you really think
she's a slut ?
Let us define slut.
Do we have to ?
[ Laughs ]
♪ A pig, a tramp, a sleaze ♪
Well, maybe she's just
really beautiful...
and has a wonderful personality.
[ Snorts ]
And I look just like Sandra Dee.
The girl is a tease, Susan.
A major tease.  [ Snickers ]
Cookie !
Hi.
Hi !
[ Pamela ]  Hi !
Okay.  Maybe she doesn't
have intercourse,
[ Gasps ]
but getting felt up
is a definite possibility.
You think so ?
I mean,
look at that sweater.
Who cannot touch
those things when they're
right in your face ?
Hi !
Hi.
- Uh, Susan Doyle.
- Sireena Cooper.  Yeah.
You know what ?
You guys have great voices.
We all thought so.
Yeah.
I don't get it.
Why you bein' so friendly ?
[ Exhales ]
I don't know.
I guess it's
just my nature.
Sorry we bothered you.
Come on.  Let's go.
[ Girls Whispering ]
Look what you did.
Hey !  Hey, wait a minute !
Um.  Thanks for calling
that butcher a pig.
Yeah, my pleasure.
Do I sense
a little tension here ?
- I'm not tense.
I'm not tense.
Well, I'm not tense.
Okay.  I--
[ Horn Beeps ]
I'm tense.
Susan !  Cookie !
Whoa !  I'm sorry.
[ Gasps ]
God !
- In half an hour
be at Tenth and Maple.
- What ?
- That's Tenth and Maple.
You got it ?
- I can't !
- I gotta pick up
my brothers in half an hour.
- You have to be there !
- What's at Tenth and Maple ?
- Just do as I say.  Girls ?
You be there too.
- [ Sireena ]  Us ?  Why ?
- Hey, what's at
Tenth and Maple ?
For me to know
and you to find out !
[ Horn Beeps ]
- Watch it !
- [ Cookie ]  That's Tony.
He's crazy.
He's in our band.
- You got a band ?
- Yeah.  See, we have
somethin' in common.
Yeah.
Hi.
[ Sighs ]
Hello.
Okay.  So what is this place ?
It's my Uncle Paul's now.
It used to be Woo's Chow Fun.
But he bought it from Mr. Woo.
He's turning it into
an Italian restaurant.
Oh.
Until then,
he said we can use it.
For-- For anything.
For practice !
Well, yeah, for that.  For--
For hangin' out.
All right !
For performin'.
For everything !
You brought our stuff.
Well, yeah.  I thought
you might want to jam a little.
And I-- I got you
this mike.  There.
Oh, thanks.
God, I can't wait for Cookie to
get here.  I want to practice.
[ Piano Key Plunks ]
Yeah, well, how about
we mess around a little till
she gets here, all right ?
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
Hey, Tony.  Um.
We need to wait, though,
until we're ready to play a gig.
You know, we need to get
a couple of routines goin',
and then we need to practice
until we get 'em down cold.
Like the pros do it.
Like Eddie Cochran.
They use their heads.
That's what we need to do.
[ Clears Throat ]
♪ [ Drum Riff ]
[ Tony ]
Ready.  One, two--
Whoo !
Nothin' like the smell
of old egg foo young.
Danny the K ?
Mmm !  Are you sure
you're in the right place ?
Hey.  I pride myself
on that.
We're old pals.
[ Clears Throat ]  Danny ?  Uh,
Mr. Klay ?  Uh, Tony Fazio here.
I'm the guy who called you.
Remember me ?
Vaguely, yeah.
- I used to eat here !
Woo's Chow Fun, right ?
- Yeah.
- Kapow !
- Mmm ?
- Uh, only now it's...
Tony Fazio's Palace
of Rock and Roll.
Well, I'd get rid of that
egg foo stink first.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sniffing ]
Well, so what brings you out
here, anyway, Mr. the K ?
Oh.  Tony here gives me
a little ring.  Tells me there's
a band he wants me to see.
I like new music.
Puh !  I'm here.
Two of you.  That's unique.
You got a name ?
Um, yeah.
Yeah, we got a name.
We're the, uh--
♪ [ Drumroll ]
- "The Eggrolls" !
- The what ?
Yeah, "The Eggrolls."
It's a fitting name,
don't you think, Danny ?
Yeah.  The-- The Eggrolls.
So let's hear what you got.
Right.  One--
Uh, well, actually, you know,
uh, we're not really all here.
- There's really more of us.
- [ Whispering ]
Susan !  Hey, Susan.
Well, listen.
You call me again...
when you've got a whole band.
Hey, Danny.  How about
a drum solo until the rest
of the band gets here ?
- Hey, give it up, Tony, huh ?
- Hey, hey, hey.
You little chickadee, you.
[ Whispering Excitedly ]
Never, ever give up, because
Dan the Man will help anybody...
if I think they're ready, okay ?
[ Sireena ]
Okay.  One, two, three.
♪ Look in my eyes ♪
♪ And tell me you
lo-o-o-ove me ♪
♪ Tell me you wa-a-a-ant me ♪
♪ Or, darlin', I'll be gone
Gone, gone, gone ♪
- ♪ Ooh ♪
- ♪ Go-o-o-one ♪
- Kapow !
- [ Backup Singers ]  ♪ Ooh ♪
- [ Sireena ]
♪ You've still got time ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ So make up your mind ♪
♪ What's it to be ♪
♪ Do you want me ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I don't need much ♪
♪ Only your touch ♪
♪ Come and love me, please ♪
♪ Or, darlin', set me free ♪
♪ Look in my eyes ♪
See there, Ethel ?
See ?  That's what
we need on TV.
♪ And tell me ♪
♪ That you're the one for me ♪
That's my Sireena.
Well, what do you know ?
What's she doin' on TV ?
Well, maybe she's talented.
You talkin' about talented.
Yesterday she was sittin' here
peelin' potatoes !
♪ [ Continues ]
What's she doin' on TV ?
She's singin', Amanda !
I know that, Ella.
How'd it happen ?
How do I know ?
Maybe she auditioned.
Sure like that dress.
I made that dress.
It's really nice.
I made it for church,
thank you.
Amanda, singin' for God
is one thing.
But singin' for money !
Ella, you gonna
go straight to hell.
Amanda, I am your
oldest sister, and
I refuse to believe...
that God is gonna punish me
for thinkin' practical.
You know, we both should
have thought practical.
We were good singers.
We could have been famous.
We could've had a career.
♪ Lo-o-o-ove me ♪
♪ Tell me you ♪
♪ Wa-a-a-ant ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Me, babe ♪
♪ Or, darling
I'll be gone ♪
♪ Gone, gone ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Go-o-o-one
Ooh ♪
♪ Look in my eyes ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
[ Cheering ]
Sireena and the Sirens !
All right !  You saw it here...
[ Customer ]
You must be real proud, Amanda.
at the Three O'Clock Hop !
Let's hear it for them !
Sireena and the Sirens.
It was wonderful !
[ Danny ]
Whoa !  You don't get
anything like that...
anyplace else
but right here !
Keep it goin' !
The girls are great.
Huh ?
- Aren't they great ?
- I don't know.
Is she that good ?
I think so.
[ Danny ]
We'll be back right after this.
Oh, Ella.  I don't know.
You gotta be careful how
you talk in front of Sireena.
You know, you gotta talk
reality to her.
She'll get ideas.
Don't talk pipe dreams to her.
Amanda, if it wasn't for
my pipe dreams, I don't know
what I would do.
Well, we both know
what her life's gonna be.
[ Man ]
Hey, Tom ?  Roll camera one
over here and leave it.
Hey, Danny.  Wait up.
Hey, those girls were good.
I think we got a find, buddy.
Look.  Don't "buddy" me, Klay.
Okay ?  What were they doing
on the show ?
[ Laughs ]
Hey !  You should be happy
you didn't have to pay 'em.
Weren't they great ?
We got calls.
You always get calls.
No.  Not like these.
We can't have everyone
on the show.  You understand ?
No.
I'm talking about Negroes
fraternizing with our people.
Our people ?
Are you serious ?
Yeah.  Yeah.
Yeah.  And it's not just me.
I got calls.  A lot of 'em.
People think that you're
rocking the boat.  Now, we never
had a Negro problem here before.
You're an asshole,
you know that ?
You watch your mouth, Klay !
I'm just doin' my job !
Right.
Right.  Your job.
They're part of our
community, man.
They all live in this town
with us.  Or do you just
drive your shiny Cadillac...
through their neighborhoods
with blinders on ?
I hate guys like you !
You get your hands off of me.
You know, when I hired you,
people told me you were trouble,
but you were good at what
you did, so I didn't listen.
I gave you a shot.
But you know what ?
You failed.
You're fired, you weirdo.
Get outta here.
You know something, Lipsky ?
I was hopin' you'd say that.
See you around.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
Susan, dinner's almost ready.
Yes ?  May I help you ?
I'm a friend of Susan's.
Really ?
- No, you're not.
- Did you dance
on that show again ?
He's not from the show,
Mom.
They call me Lucky.
Lucky Mullins,
Mrs. Doyle.
God, you have
unbelievable nerve.
And you have
an unbelievable figure.
You oughta wear threads
like that more often.
You know, it suits you.
Oh, I do.  Just not around
guys like you.
Susan.  I think
we have to talk.
It looks like you have
a very comfortable home here.
Yes, sirree.  Very comfortable.
[ Clears Throat ]
Don't worry.
I can handle him.
What, were you born in a barn ?
You know, you're right.
I do have to work
on my manners.
How's this ?  Uh, you
have a very comfortable
couch, Miss Doyle.
Is that better ?
Or would you rather
I call you "Little Red" ?
You're a lucky girl,
you know that ?
You got it all.
Oh, yeah.
And you've got nothing.
Well,
maybe not right now.
But, uh,
when I want somethin',
there's no stopping me.
You can't always
get what you want.
But sometimes you can
get what you need.
[ Shouting ]
Susan !
Looks like you...
need your mama.
Sorry if I've disturbed you,
Mrs. Doyle.
It was sweet, Susan.
I think I saw a knife
in his pocket.
You hang out with people
who carry knives ?
- [ Laughs ]
- What, may I ask,
is so funny ?
Wh-What, did you think
he was gonna kill me ?
Chop me up
into little bitty pieces ?
Okay.  You listen to me,
young lady.
If I don't see an immediate
change in your behavior,
I am going to tear up every
college and university
application you have,
and you are going
to spend next year
at City Junior College,
living right in this house
where I can keep an eye
on you.
Do you hear me ?
You can't do that.
I can do anything I want.
I am your mother.
I hate you.
Susan !  Susan !
Susan Doyle,
you come back here !
Hi.
Did you run away from home
or something ?
Yes.
No.  I'm just kidding.
I wish.
Well, you're not m-mad
at me, are ya ?
Uh-uh.
I'm mad at the mother
from the ocean floor.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, well,
you can join the club.
Here, let me cheer you up.
I'm gonna make us famous, Susan.
Just like Eddie Cochran.
What do you think ?
Hey, with us and Sireena,
we got a hot double bill.
Where did you
get that picture ?
You don't remember,
but we were takin' it.
Last year, we took it.
We were horsin' around ?
You know ?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This concert is
Saturday night.
Yeah.
That's the day
after tomorrow, Tony.
Yeah, so ?  We're ready, Susan.
We've always been ready.
I don't know.
I don't know.  Th-That's goin'
a little too fast.  I'm--
Susan.
I'm just a little confused.
You know, that's all.
I'm just--
[ Inhales ]
I'm confused.
I know the feeling.
♪ I wanna go home ♪
♪ Where I belong ♪
♪ 'Cause now ♪
♪ I'm just a lonely ♪
♪ Teenager ♪
♪ When I was 16 ♪
♪ I ran away ♪
♪ All alone ♪
♪ Gone astray ♪
♪ What can I do ♪
♪ What can I say ♪
♪ A lonely ♪
♪ Teenager ♪
♪ Now I'm 17 ♪
♪ And I'm still alone ♪
♪ Wonderin' if
I should go home ♪
♪ Or maybe stay out ♪
♪ On my own ♪
♪ A lonely ♪
♪ Teenager ♪
♪ I'd love to go back home ♪
♪ Where I belong ♪
♪ I know I'll be all right ♪
♪ If I just stay
out of sight ♪
♪ I wanna go home ♪
♪ Where I belong ♪
♪ 'Cause now I'm just ♪
♪ A lonely ♪
♪ Teenager ♪
[ Knocking ]
[ Dad ]
Oh, Susan.
Good night.
It's me.  Dad.
Can I come in ?
Sue, are you there ?
Hi, Susan.
Listen, um,
your mother and I
are really worried
about you.
You know, honey.
Your mother loves you
very, very much.
Dad, she doesn't trust me.
How could she love me ?
Oh, honey, she trusts you.
It's-- It's-- It's
the music, you know.
Tell me
about this music.
The music ?
Come in !
All right.
Um, the music.
Rock-and-roll music.
Oh, I don't know, Dad.
Haven't you ever listened
to something that sets
your body on fire ?
You know,
it touches you
in places that you
didn't even know existed ?
[ Laughs ]
Well, that's
rock and roll, Dad.
You know, it's got this
ba-ti-ti-ba, ti-ba,
this beat, you know.
Ba-na-na, da-da-da,
and I feel it
from my head to my toes.
And it gives me--
It gives me power.
You know,
now that you remind me,
I-I-I think
I had that feeling once.
Yes.  It was great.
I loved it !
It was--
It was wonderful.  Yeah.
- Now that you remind me,
that's it.
- See, that's it !
That's my life !
I can't live without that, Dad.
Wow !  That is interesting.
I-I'm gonna
pass that information
along to your mother.
I mean, it's really
good to have a, you know,
a-a-a passion
about things, you know.
Well,
anyway, these are, uh,
these are yours.
And, uh--
Thank you.
[ Whispers ]
Lucky !
You can't do this.
You gotta leave me alone.
You don't belong in this
nowhere town, Susan,
any more than I do.
You're better than this.
You shouldn't be here, Lucky.
Didn't you listen to what
you just said to your father ?
What you said about the music ?
'Cause I did !
I get that same feelin'.
I know what
you're talkin' about.
See, I understand.
No.  Look, Lucky.
I have plans,
and you're not in them.
Susan, look at me.
See, I think
we're a lot alike.
I may be bad, but,
um, I'm not evil.
Come with me.
[ Chuckles ]
No.
You just remember.
I understand,
and they don't.
I understand, Susan.
[ Sighs ]
[ Backup Singers ]
♪ Bum-dobie, do-wa
Bum-dobie-dobie, do-ah ♪
♪ Wa-wa-wa-wa, ah-ah ♪
♪ Tra-la-la-la-la
Ooh, diddly, diddly-dum
Dum, dum, dum, dum ♪
♪ Dum-be-doobie, ooh
Dum, dum, dum ♪
[ Both Grunt ]
[ Man ]
♪ Dum-whapa, dum-whapa
Dum, dum, dum ♪
[ Backup Singers ]
♪ Boomp, whup, whup
Shi-wanna, wanna ♪
♪ Ooh-ah-ah ♪
♪ To-wammie, do-bah
Wham-a-land, a-ding, dang ♪
♪ Ba-ba-ba-ba
Ding, d-d-d-ding ♪
♪ Mu-mu-mu-mu
Shooby-oobie, oobie-doobie
Oobie, bop, bop ♪
♪ Um-die, um-dum
Ditty, ditty, ditty
Dum-de-dum ♪
[ Man ]
♪ Bing, bang
Walla-balla, hong kong ♪
[ Backup Singers ]
♪ Dum-ditty dit-dop
And ditty, ditty ♪
♪ Wah-wah, shoop, shoop
Shoo, do, do, do ♪
♪ Dum, ditty, dum, wah, wah
Doobie, doobie ♪
♪ Bop, bop, bop, bop
Shi-bop, shi-bop, shi-bop ♪
♪ Mama, mama, mama, mama
Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
[ Man ]
♪ Numa, numa, numa, numa
Numa, numa, numa, numa ♪
[ Backup Singers ]
♪ Boom, shi, boom, ting-a-ling
A-ting, a-ting-tang ♪
♪ Dang, dang, a-dang, dang ♪
[ Man ]
♪ Bo, bo, bo-de-bo, do ♪
[ Backup Singers ]
♪ Rockin' and sockin'
And a-reelin' and boppin' ♪
♪ With a-wang-dang, doodle-de
Bop-di-bing-bang ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
[ Whispering ]
Catcher in the Rye.
Gone.
The Invisible Man
by Ralph Ellison.  Gone.
[ Whispers ]
Hi, Joyce.
Hi, Margo.
Norman Mailer,
The Naked and the Dead.
And he's Jewish.  Gone.
What are you doing ?
Books are a big influence
on our children.
It's up to us to channel
that influence properly.
[ Gasps ]
Are you sure you want
to read Fitzgerald ?
He was a terrible alcoholic,
you know.
I had no idea.
Gone.
[ Book Thudding
In Wastebasket ]
Margo, I didn't know
Susan could sing.
Sing ?
This is Susan,
isn't it ?
And she's singing
in a club.
Is this really
a good idea, Margo ?
Well, it's only one night.
What harm could it do ?
[ Regular Voice ]
What harm ?
[ People ]  Shh !
[ Whispering ]
Do you know how many unwed
teenage mothers there are ?
Oh, you don't think--
Of course !
With that jungle music
that they play, that's
what the beat is all about.
If they dance to Pat Boone,
a good clean boy,
that would be one thing.
But they're
playing with fire,
Margo.  Jungle fire.
But, that's
just my opinion.
Are you going
to hear her sing ?
I don't know.
I certainly would.
This club has
to be checked out.
We have to know what
our children are doing.
Don't we, Margo ?
♪ Well, do you want to dance
under the moonlight ♪
♪ Kiss me, baby
all through the night ♪
♪ Oh, baby
do you wanna dance ♪
♪ Do you, do you, do you
[ Wolf Whistle ]
do you wanna dance ♪
[ Tony ]  That's one dollar.
Hi, Tony.
♪ Ah-ah-ah-ah ♪
Go ahead in, girls.
Have a great show.
Thanks.
Cookie,
where's Sireena ?
I don't know.
Where did all these guys
come from, Susan ?
Are-- Are they as gorgeous
as I think they are,
or am I just lonely ?
Cookie !
Hi, girls.
Hi.
Hi !
Do you think my dress
looks too tight ?
Oh, tell me the truth now
'cause I'll go home and change.
- [ Tony ]
Hey, girls.
- Hi, Tony.
Regina, great dress.
Uh, where's the rest of it ?
[ Girls ]
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Guy, Tony.
You are so rude !
[ Both Gasp ]
Now, you just can't sing, honey.
You got to dip.
[ Laughs ]
And scoop.  That's right.
You gotta scoop
when you come up.
That right, Ella ?
That's right.
Sireena, your mama and I
could have been famous.
The Baldwin sisters.
We weren't too bad,
were we, Amanda ?
No, we weren't, Ella.
But your mama
had a higher callin'.
Course, all I wanted to do was
become rich and famous.  That's
what I call a higher callin'.
Will you come on ?
Let's show her the step.
Come on.  Count it off.
"Blue Moon."
You got the top note.
Yeah, but wait a minute.
On the count of four.  Okay ?
All right.
One.  Two.
One, two, three--
♪ Blue moon ♪
♪ You saw me standin' alone ♪
♪ Without a dream in my heart ♪
♪ Without a love of my own ♪
Turn around.
Scoop and dip.  There you go.
♪ Blue moon ♪
♪ You knew just what
I was there for ♪
♪ You heard me
saying a prayer for ♪
♪ Someone I really
could care for ♪
That's it.  That low note.
You couldn't hit that.
[ Man ]
Bring back the Baldwin sisters.
Okay.  Thank you.
You got that, baby ?
Yes, ma'am.
Dippin' and-- and a scoop.
Yeah, but, honey,
you got to dip
a little better than that.
I tell you what.
Shake your hip a little bit.
They like that.
[ Laughs ]
Uh-uh.  Uh-uh.  There will be
no shakin' of hips, Ella.
Okay.  Forget the hips.
Just smile a lot.
Okay.  Well,
how do I look ?
Oh, baby, look at you.
You look all grown up.
Come here.
Thank you, Mama.
All right now.
You sing pretty now, okay ?
Are you sure you can't
come tonight, Mama ?
Now, I told you I couldn't
make it tonight.
I gotta work.
Okay.
But I'm gonna come
the next time.
I promise.
All right, I'm proud of you.
I gotta go to work now,
Sireena.
All right.
[ Woman ]
Bring it on.
Shake your hips.
[ Chattering ]
I've never been
to this neighborhood before.
It's so Chinese.
I hear
they have great food.
Oh, and I love those
little slippers they make.
Those little silk ones.
Mrs. Doyle.
Good to see you again
so soon.
You must be here
to cheer Susan on.
[ Gasps ]
Such a good mom.
Do you know that boy ?
Don't even ask.
Come on, Margo.
Go do it,
daddy-o.
Come on.
[ Cookie Giggles ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Microphone Whines ]
Hey, hey, all you
"tops of the pops" lovers
out there.
Welcome to what
used to be Woo's Chow Fun's.
And like they say,
no woos is good woos.
[ Chattering Continues ]
[ Susan, Cookie Laugh ]
[ Coughs ]
Hi, I'm Tony Fazio.
[ Susan, Cookie Cheering ]
Susan, it's your turn.
Oh, no.
Give it another shot.
Maybe I can help.
Danny, you came !
[ Laughs ]
Hey, you called me 100 times.
You're a very persuasive man.
Now this better be good.
[ Girl ]
Danny's here.
[ Danny ]
Hey, hey, hey !
Danny Klay here.
[ Applauding, Cheering ]
Now I know what you're thinking.
This is kookie.
What's a famous cat
like this...
doing in an old
Chinese restaurant
on a hot Saturday night ?
Well, I'm here to listen
to sohot rock and roll.
- Kapow !
You got me.
Now you know The Chantels,
The Shirelles, The Chiffons,
The Orlons,
Reparata and The Delrons.
Well, I got from my own
Three O'Clock at the Hop Show,
Sireena and the Sirens
right here.
[ Cheering, Applauding ]
And-- And--  Still want
to be called The Eggrolls ?
I hate that name !
Yeah.
Some other surprises.
[ Applause, Cheering ]
Hold it.
What, Officer Paisley ?
You aren't going to let us
into the sock hop ?
No, Lucky.  I don't
want any trouble in there.
You're saying
that I'm trouble ?
That's what I'm saying.
You dig that, Bubber ?
He-- He's sayin'
that we're trouble.
Paisley thinks anyone
who isn't a cop is trouble.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, please.
You gotta let me in.
I'm singing tonight.
I'm Sireena.
Oh, sure.
Go on in.
And you go home,
if you can find one.
You know, Paisley.
If it wasn't for punks like me,
you wouldn't
have a job.  Dig ?
Hey.  Take that attitude
someplace else, Mullins.
It is my privilege to introduce
to you for the first time...
in front of more than
one human being, The Eggrolls.
[ Applause, Cheering ]
♪ I could cook
and make the beds ♪
♪ Think I'll make rock and roll
instead ♪
♪ A different life's for me ♪
♪ I'm gonna live my fantasy ♪
♪ So, c'mon, Mother
don't you cry ♪
♪ I'll sing a rockin' lullaby ♪
♪ And for each tear you spill ♪
♪ I'll make a song
You know I will ♪
♪ Yeah, you oughta
know me better by now ♪
♪ Well, you oughta
♪ You oughta know me better
oughta know me better by now ♪
♪ They say my eyes ♪
♪ Are much too wide ♪
♪ That I should take the path ♪
♪ My mama already tried ♪
♪ Well, I wanna be good ♪
♪ Do what a girl
knows she should ♪
♪ But music's part of me ♪
♪ So I gotta set it free ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, you oughta
know me better by now ♪
♪ Yeah, you oughta
know me better
oughta know me better by now ♪
Take it, Cookie !
[ Girls And Guys ]
Go !  Go !  Go !  Go !
[ In Unison ]
I'm shocked !
I'm absolutely shocked.
Officer Paisley, you've
got to put a stop to this.
Now what is it
you want stopped ?
It's just music.
We would like
to make a complaint.
A noicomplaint.
You have to be prepared
for things like this.
And I am prepared.
This looks like
a real complaint, girls.
Oh, yes.
That is a real complaint.
- What do you want me to do ?
Close the place down ?
- Yes, we do.
[ Chanting Continues ]
Go !  Go !  Go !  Go !
♪ Well, you ought to know me
better by now ♪
♪ Yeah, you ought to know me
♪ Well, you oughta
know me better
oughta know me better by now ♪
♪ Yeah, you oughta
know me better ♪
know me better, oughta
know me better by now ♪
[ Cheering, Whistling ]
This is Lieutenant Paisley.
I'm gonna need some backup.
I'm at Woo's Chow Fun.
All right, I told you there's
hot rock and roll right here
in this city.
The Eggrolls !
Okay, just wait around a minute.
I got another group that will
knock your socks off.
Sorry, folks.  Sorry.
We've been ordered to put
an end to the festivities.
- Everybody go home !
- Why ?
What's going on ?
We had a noise complaint,
Mr. Klay.
You gotta stop the music.
Come on, kids.  File out.
Hey, hey, hey.  Wa-wa-wait.
There's nothing around here
but empty buildings.
Who would complain ?
[ Man ]
Who kicked us outta here ?
- That's confidential, Mr. Klay.
- [ Man ]  Why we gotta leave ?
You-- You-- You can't send
these kids out onto the streets.
- [ Shouting In Agreement ]
- We gotta be allowed
to play our own music.
[ Shouting In Agreement ]
So I say,
let's contest this complaint.
[ Shouting In Agreement ]
Rock and roll.
We won't go.
[ Everyone Chanting ]
Rock and roll.
We won't go.
Rock and roll.  We won't go.
Rock and roll !  We won't go !
Move 'em out !
[ Chanting Continues ]
[ Police Officer ]
Move it outside !
[ Glass Shatters ]
[ Chanting Continues ]
I said move it !
Rock and roll.
We won't go.
[ Confused Yelling ]
They're busting up
the cop car, man !
Riot outside !
♪ C'mon, everybody and
let's get together tonight ♪
♪ I got some money in my jeans
and I'm really gonna
spend it right ♪
Oh, my God !
♪ Well, I been doin'
my homework all week long ♪
You come home
with me now !
No !
Hey, man.  Stop !
Hey, stop it.  Go on !
♪ Whoo, c'mon, everybody ♪
[ Groans ]
♪ Well, my baby's number one
but I'm gonna dance
with three or four ♪
You're coming home now !
Let go of me !
♪ When you hear the music
you can't stand still ♪
♪ Your brother won't rock
but your sister will ♪
♪ Whoo, c'mon, everybody ♪
You've got to arrest Danny Klay.
He's over 21.  He's responsible.
If you won't do it,
my friends and I will
make a citizen's arrest.
Mm-hmm.
♪ Well, we're really gonna party
but we gotta put
a guard outside ♪
♪ 'Cause if my folks come home
they're really
gonna have my hide ♪
♪ There'll be no more movies
for a week or two ♪
♪ No more runnin' around
with the usual crew ♪
♪ Who cares ♪
♪ C'mon, everybody ♪
[ Siren Wailing ]
Stay where you are !
♪ C'mon, everybody ♪
[ Grunts, Groans ]
- ♪ C'mon, everybody ♪
- [ Grunting ]
See ya, Susan.
[ Grunting ]
♪ C'mon, everybody ♪
Sorry, Mr. Klay.
No, I understand.
You're just doin' your job.
Those people are wrong.
[ Siren Wailing
In Distance ]
♪ C'mon, c'mon
c'mon, everybody ♪
[ Police Officer ]
Put him in here.
Where you guys takin' him ?
Back to the station.
[ Crying ]
I am here today
to tell you...
that rock and roll
is evil.
It's dangerous.
It works on the libido.
It's a nasty temptation,
and furthermore, it's too loud.
We are asking this television
station to be a pioneer,
to be the first on the air
to vow to never again...
allow rock and roll
to be broadcast on the airways.
[ Knocking ]
Who is it ?
Your best pal.
Oh, yeah.
I see you know how to keep
yourself on the front page.
Oh, yeah.
Whenever I need attention,
I just get myself arrested.
You got chocolate
on your mouth, Eddie.
Yeah ?
Mm-hmm.
You got it.
What do you want ?
I got a way to get everybody
in this city to watch your show.
[ Sighs ]
And as a bonus, make myself
very rich and famous.
Oh, I don't know
if I want to know your way.
Don't I recall firing you ?
Now, just hear me out.
You know those screwballs you
got on the channel right now ?
Already I don't
like your way.
No, you're gonna love this.
Now, you and I both know that
rock and roll is no more sexual
than a Frank Sinatra song,
and we both made it through
puberty unharmed, right ?
Well, maybe you didn't, but--
That's a joke, Lipsky.
Now, I'd like to use
the American justice system...
to show what people
think of rock and roll.
Let's put on a trial.
Right here at the station.
We get a prosecutor,
we get a defender,
and we let the American people
vote by phone.
I can see all the publicity,
can't you ?  Court television.
Court television ?
[ Gavel Pounds ]
I, Judge Patrick Eugene Boone,
officially declare this court
now in session.
Thanks, Judge.
Hey, hey, hey !
Is everybody
ready to plead the fifth ?
And that's not Beethoven's.
[ Audience ]
Ready !
Boy, have we got an exciting
hour for you this afternoon.
Yes !  We got conflict,
we have love, we have hate,
we have suspense,
but best of all,
we got music.
[ Audience ]  Yeah !
Kapow !  Now listen up
while we get ready to embark
on a highly irregular procedure.
We're going to put a form
of music, specifically
rock and roll, on trial.
Now is this a free country ?
[ Audience ]
Yeah !
So why should music
be left up to one man
or one kid's opinion ?
Or should parents be allowed
to censor this music
in their own homes...
and remove it from the airways ?
[ Audience ]
Boo !
Now with this trial,
the jury is you people at home.
You see these jurors
in the juror box ?  They
represent you.  That's right.
So at the end
of this so-called trial,
you call in your decisions,
we tally the results
and then, voila, rock and roll,
guilty or innocent.
You be the judge !
All right.  Is everybody ready ?
[ Audience ]
Yeah !
But first, if you
wanna be the proud owner
of a brand-new Cadillac...
with just ten dollars down,
listen to this.
[ Man ]  And we're clear.
I feel like
[ Sighs ]
Della Street.
Her hair
is always so perfect.
Yeah, well, I don't
feel so good about this.
Me neither.
[ Man ]
Three, two, one.  Air.
- Take it away, Judgey-doodle.
- Thank you.
The prosecution may now call
his, uh, her first witness.
Thank you, Judge Boone.
I'd like to call Danny Klay
to the stand.
Kapow !  I swear to tell
the whole truth and nothing but.
Mr. Klay, where were you
at 8:00 p.m. on Saturday night ?
Well, I was at Woo Chow Fun's,
like everybody else.
Any more questions ?
Yes.  What was
your function there ?
My functiwas to let people
know about the music
these kids are playing...
and help them raise money so
they had a place to play it in.
- Yea !
- Thanks, Danny.
Did it ever occur to you that
the parents of these children...
might not be in support
of this music ?
Objection !
Can I do that ?
Can I object ?
I'm a witness
and a defender.
Yeah, you can do that,
but your objection is overruled.
Oh-h-h-h !
Uh, can I get a cup of coffee
and some of that
famous peach cobbler ?
Shh !  Can't you see
we're watching TV ?
Excuse me, but does the sign
outside say restaurant ?
We're a restaurant
after the show.
[ Woman On TV ]  Who was
the leader of this destruction ?
[ Danny ]  Leader ?
[ Woman On TV ]
I think it was you.
What are you watching ?
My daughter.
And my niece.
Here, have a seat.
Isn't it true
that you spent three years
in the detention center,
and the other night you were
arrested for inciting a riot ?
Hey, uh, I'm not on trial here.
I would like to object again,
Your Honor.
It is a little out of line,
Mrs. Togar.  How is this
relevant ?
I want to show the character
of the man who is supposed to be
a role model for our children,
yet he leads them somewhere
other than church and home.
But what does this
have to do with the music ?
Hey, that's a good point.
Let me show you,
Your Honor.
Ladies.
I am going to prove
that this music
is a drug,
a very addictive drug
that controls your mind
and your body...
and puts you in a state
of unrelenting ecstasy.
- Where can I get some ?
- [ Laughing ]
Notice these children:
healthy, normal,
all-American.
Now.  Observe.
♪ Ah-h-h-h ♪
[ Record Scratches ]
By stopping the music,
we can carefully
examine what happens
during a rock-and-roll song.
Some of you may
want to turn your sets off...
because what I am
about to show you is shocking.
This is grinding.
- [ Laughs ]
- Grinding.
Think about it.
If I have offended anyone,
I am sorry.
Judge, I would
like to call to the stand
a victim of rock and roll:
Margo Doyle.
Do you love your daughter,
Mrs. Doyle ?
More than anything.
How has the music
changed your life ?
It changed everything.
All my life I wanted
a little girl that I could
dress up and show off.
And for years I had that.
She was a wonderful little girl.
She loved school and playtime
and putting on my makeup.
And now I can't
talk to her anymore.
All she wants to do
is listen to that music...
and express herself.
She's 17.
What could she
possibly have to express ?
She has a wonderful house
and great clothes.
Why can't she
just be content ?
It's that music.
[ Crying ]
I rest my case, Your Honor.
[ Crying Continues ]
[ Judge ]
The public defender
may call his first witness.
Thank you,
Your Honor-doodle-you.
Okay, this trial is being done
in a show business style,
right ?
Right !
So my clients would like
to plead their case...
in that show business style.
Okay, are we ready
to break a leg, clients ?
Yeah !
Kapow !  Come on down, okay ?
Yeah.
I hope that means
that the show is over.
No, no, no.
That means my daughter
is about to sing now.
Would you just watch the show ?
You don't need
any coffee anyway.
It'll stunt your growth.
I'm full grown !
And I want some coffee
and some pie !
No, no.  Wa-wa-wait a minute.
Come on now.  Come on.
As soon as this is over,
I'm gonna make you some food.
I promise.
Sit down, baby.  Come on.
All right.  Ready ?
Let's rock and roll.
♪ All around the world
rock and roll
is all they play ♪
Yeah !  Yeah !
Whoo !
♪ All around the world
rock and roll
is all they play ♪
Yeah !  Yeah !
♪ You can hear
that jukebox jumpin' ♪
♪ All night long
through the day ♪
♪ All the flattop cats and
their rock-and-roll queens ♪
♪ Just a-rockin' and a-rollin'
in their red blue jeans ♪
♪ All around the world
rock and roll
is here to stay ♪
♪ Whoo-o-o ♪
♪ You can hear that jukebox
jumpin' all night long
through the day ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- Yeah !
♪ There ain't never no time
for romance ♪
♪ They only want to dance ♪
♪ People all holler
when they hit the floor ♪
♪ Go, cat, go ♪
♪ All around the world
rock and roll
is here to stay ♪
Whoo-hoo !
♪ You can hear
that jukebox jumpin' ♪
♪ All night long
through the day ♪
Go, Cookie !
All right.
Yeah !
♪ They do the bop ♪
♪ The Texas Hop ♪
- ♪ Shim, sham, shimmy ♪
- ♪ And they never, never stop ♪
♪ All around the world
rock and roll
is here to stay ♪
Come on now !
♪ Here to stay ♪
♪ You can hear
that jukebox jumpin' ♪
♪ All night and
all through the day ♪
Whoo !
♪ There ain't never
no time for romance
The people want to dance ♪
♪ People all holler
when they hit the floor ♪
♪ Go, cat, go ♪
♪ All around the world
rock and roll
is here to stay ♪
Yeah !
♪ You can hear
that jukebox jumpin' ♪
♪ All night long
through the day ♪
[ Cheering, Applause ]
[ Applause, Cheering ]
- Order !  Order !
- [ Applause, Whistling ]
I rest my case.
So now the outcome
of this trial...
is up to you, the jury.
[ Phone Ringing ]
So just call HArrison 7-555.
Pamela Jordan.
Thank you, Pamela.
All right, it's in your hands.
Cast that vote.  Rock and roll.
Innocent or guilty ?
Hello !
My vote is innocent.
Innocent !
Here.
Now you better vote.
That Sireena.
That's your niece, right ?
And my daughter.
She's good, ain't she ?
Yeah.  She's real good.
She's very talented.
In fact, I'd like to meet her.
Thomas Taylor,
Vice President,
Scepter Records.
Here.  Let me see that.
Are you really
from Scepter Records ?
The home of
the Shirelles Scepter ?
Yeah.
[ Laughs ]
One cup of coffee
coming up !
And how would you
like some ice cream to go
with that peach cobbler ?
Ladies and gentlemen,
the verdict has been reached.
You, the jury, have found
rock and roll to be...
♪ [ Drumroll ]
not guilty.
[ All Gasp ]
Uh, may we
have it quiet, please ?
Quiet, please.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I'm afraid there's
a discrepancy in the voting.
[ Murmuring ]
What do you mean ?
The vote's the vote.
Whoa !
Whoa there, Mr. Klay.
You're just the announcer.
I'm the judge.
It seems that since
we were unable to see the faces
of the jurors,
according to the tabulators,
some people may have voted
more than once.
[ Audience Protesting ]
It is therefore
the decision of the court
to overturn the vote.
- [ Protesting ]
- You can't do this !
This is my show.
They can't do that !
Oh, yes, they can.
They've done it before.
[ Audience Booing ]
This court finds
rock and roll guilty.
No !
That's not fair !
No.  That's wrong.
Boo !  That's wrong.
Boo !
And we find Danny Klay
guilty of incitement to riot,
perverting the morals
of a minor, etc., etc., etc.
[ Danny ]
This is not justice.
This is a joke.
This is a joke.  In America,
everybody has to have a voice:
children and adults alike.
Let them know how you feel !
Keep the phones ringing.
We can't keep this happening.
We can't !
Cut to commercial.
You can't arrest me !
This is not a real trial !
It's not reality !
It's just a television show !
[ Audience Protesting ]
If you want it to end,
turn off the television.
Turn off the television !
It's not real !
[ Protesting Continues ]
You know
what time it is ?
Midnight.
So you leaving now ?
[ Sniffles ]
I'm gonna
miss you, Susan.
I'm gonna miss you too.
See ya.
So you gonna
write to me ?
Of course, I'm gonna
write to you.
[ Motorcycle Approaching ]
Do you think I'm ever
gonna meet anyone ?
Ever ?
[ Engine Revving ]
So where ya gonna go ?
I don't know.
Cookie, we're desperate.
Get used to it.
♪ C'mon, everybody ♪
♪ Well, c'mon, everybody and
let's get together tonight ♪
♪ I got some money in my jeans
and I'm really gonna
spend it right ♪
♪ Well, I been doin'
my homework all week long ♪
♪ The house is empty
and my folks are gone ♪
♪ Whoo, c'mon, everybody ♪
♪ Well, my baby's number one
but I'm gonna dance
with three or four ♪
♪ You know, the house'll be
shakin' from the foot beats
steppin' on the floor ♪
♪ Oh, when you hear the music
you can't stand still ♪
♪ Your brother won't rock
but your sister will ♪
♪ Whoo, c'mon, everybody ♪
♪ Well, we're really gonna party
but we gotta put
a guard outside ♪
♪ 'Cause if my folks come home
well, they're really gonna
have my hide ♪
♪ There'll be no more movies
for a week or two ♪
♪ No more runnin' around
with the usual crew ♪
♪ Who cares
C'mon, everybody ♪
♪ Well, c'mon, everybody and
let's get together tonight ♪
♪ I got some money in my jeans
and I'm really gonna
spend it right ♪
♪ Well, I been doin'
my homework all week long ♪
♪ The house is empty
and my folks are gone ♪
♪ Whoo, c'mon, everybody ♪
♪ Well, we're really gonna party
but we gotta put
a guard outside ♪
♪ 'Cause if my folks come home
well, they're really gonna
have my hide ♪
♪ There'll be no more movies
for a week or two ♪
♪ No more runnin' around
with the usual crew ♪
♪ Who cares
C'mon, everybody ♪
♪ C'mon, everybody ♪
♪ C'mon ♪
♪ Everybody ♪
♪ C'mon, c'mon
c'mon, everybody ♪
♪ C'mon, everybody ♪
[ Kissing Sound ]
[ Chattering ]
Mr. Taylor.
Just as soon as you finish,
if you don't mind.
Uh, Amanda.  Amanda,
don't let them sign anything.
There too many
blank spaces here.
We need a better understanding.
We're not gonna make
any mistakes this time.
Mr. Taylor, I wanna
ask you a few questions.
Who has publishing rights
on here to the songs
that the girls have written ?
Oh, Mr. Taylor.  Those greens
can wait until we straighten out
this green, all right ?
[ Chuckles ]
Now, another question.
I'd like to know--