I wish we could just
stay out here all day.
Yeah, me, too.
No such luck.
Well, we'd better
be heading in.
I never should have
given you that watch.
Clea, you don't know where
that old '50s bowling shirt
of mine is, do you?
Nope. Sorry.
What's cooking?
A Turkey loaf for the picnic.
It's a recipe
from my home ec. Class.
I just hope
I know what I'm doing.
It smells promising.
Don't look at me.
Why? Is something different?
Very funny, dad.
You better start doing
or undoing
whatever you need to
to get ready.
( Horse snorting )
Oh, I love you, Zad.
You're such a good horse.
Oh, Luis, we need to drive up
to Eureka Springs tomorrow
pick up that Dutch mare.
Okay. Hey,
that makes six boarders...
It's almost
a full house.
( Neighing )
Luis:
Ho, ho...
Easy, easy.
Good.
Nora?
You can come on in, Neal.
The horses aren't
going to attack you.
I thought I might wear
that old '50s bowling shirt
this afternoon
with a pair of chinos.
What do you think?
Sounds good.
You'll look great.
Do you know where
the shirt is?
Your guess is
as good as mine.
How about helping me
look for it?
Sure, when I'm done here.
Neal:
We have to leave
in an hour.
Maybe you should have
thought of it earlier.
I'll look
for it, dad.
You don't need
to do that, Simon.
It's no problem.
We could probably
get this into a ducktail
if you really want
to go the distance.
Neal:
Sure. Clea's
going for broke.
Why not me?
Cool.
Are you sure you don't want
to ride in the parade
with us this year, Nora?
I'm positive,
but I admire your persistence.
I won't ask again.
Oh, yes, you will.
Luis, did you check
on Perseus' leg?
Yeah, we should wrap it.
Nora:
Let's do that now.
I'll get the liniment.
Luis:
I don't think we
have enough gauze.
Whoa!
Don't say anything.
I feel ridiculous enough.
No.
If I was visiting
from another planet
I'd probably think
you were very hot.
Oh, well, I'm sure you
mean that as a compliment.
Well, of course.
How was your ride?
Oh, it was great.
How come you never
take me riding?
We'll go tomorrow.
Really?
Sure.
Hey, it's t-minus-50.
Let's hop to it.
Yes, sir.
Are you on schedule?
I'm t-minus-80.
Too bad.
You'll have to go like that.
( Gasping ):
I'm on schedule.
( Drumming )
( Band playing
"stars and stripes forever")
( Honking )
Here they come.
Nora:
Your dad's
in hog heaven.
Look at him.
( Nora laughing )
( Jazzy bluegrass playing )
...kicking and screaming
into the 21st century.
We are the only
insurance company
without an
email address.
Now, wait a minute.
I am this close to being
computer literate.
Clea's giving me lessons.
I surf the web.
The net. You surf the net.
I've been
threatening
to quit
unless Neal
starts pulling
his weight at the office.
Don't get
your hopes up.
He still can't
program our VCR.
A few more years,
I'll have it nailed.
I don't want anything to do
with any of it.
This Turkey loaf is world-class.
Clea is gonna be happy.
She's been working
on it since dawn.
Where is she?
I'll give her
my review.
She went to talk
to her boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
You let that child
have a boyfriend?
She's 15, oz.
It seems like
yesterday
you were 15.
Your mom would come by
and carp about all the boys
you were seeing.
It's me you're talking
about there, Iris.
Iris:
Somebody get me
out of this.
It's okay; Nora never listened
to her mother about the boys.
I was just being consistent.
I never listened to my mother
about anything.
Hey, you looked very
cool out there today.
Not too dorky?
No, cool.
Oh... well, then, maybe
I'll keep my hair like this.
Don't push it.
So, who wants cherry pie
and homemade ice cream?
Pile it on.
Nora?
I couldn't, Iris, thanks.
Neal?
Absolutely.
Uh...
On second thought,
I better pass.
Oh, come on,
one little piece?
I'd hear about it later.
Poor Neal, he's so abused.
Simon.
Just in time
for pie a la mode.
Oh, sounds good, Iris.
Woman:
This crust is
out of this world.
What's your secret?
She could
tell you,
but then she'd have to kill you.
Iris:
I use crushed
almonds.
Come on, Nora,
let's go make the rounds...
Do a little P.R.
Hey, mom, let's dance.
What?
Come on, dance with me.
( Laughing )
Okay.
How about sneaking a
little piece of pie now?
Yeah, with a big scoop
of ice cream.
Having fun, George?
I always have fun.
Is, uh, Nora here?
Right over there.
Mr. Wetzel, Mrs. Wetzel,
how are you doing?
Neal.
I'm about to burst.
You got a policy for that?
Sounds like I'm too late.
I'm not too late
for hail season though.
Good afternoon,
Mrs. Kramer.
Good afternoon, Neal.
I hear you're retiring
next spring.
You looking
forward to it?
Oh, I'll miss
my students.
I'm sure Simon
is wishing
that I'd retired
last year.
Oh, no, now...
But there really
is no reason
for him to have failed
that first exam.
As I wrote in the note
that I sent home with him
Simon is a very
bright boy.
He's just not applying himself.
Right.
Right. Well...
I'm sure he'll shape up.
I know he will.
I want to talk to you, Simon.
I ran into
Mrs. Kramer.
Explain yourself,
Simon.
Ah, I'm sorry, dad
but trigonometry's
just really hard.
I'm not talking about
your grades, Simon
although I'm very unhappy
about that.
I'm talking about the note
Mrs. Kramer sent
home with you.
The note to your
mother and me.
You just
threw it away?
You didn't think
we'd find out? How long
did you think
you could keep it from us?
I knew about the note, Neal.
Simon gave
it to me.
He's promised
to work harder.
He's got the rest of the
semester to catch up.
And all of this
was to be kept from me?
No, I just thought
you'd get upset
and make too much of it,
so, I didn't say anything.
Dad, dad, don't be mad at mom.
This whole thing's my fault.
I'm the one who's flunking trig.
Simon, you don't need
to keep running interference
for your mother, okay?
And as for you...
I'm not angry.
I'm just disappointed.
I expect you to
make up for it.
There will be studying
in this house every day.
Riding will be confined
to the weekends
and if your grades
aren't up to snuff
there will be no riding at all.
Am I clear?
Yes, sir.
( Sighing )
Neal?
I'm sorry I didn't
show you the note.
I know I spoil Simon.
I'm sorry I wasn't by
your side this afternoon.
I know you
wanted me to be.
It's just that all
that embarrasses me.
Maybe I'll be
braver next year
if you still want me.
( Sighing )
You know,
if someone could explain
the point of trig to me,
maybe I could get into it.
Well, once you pass,
you'll never even have
to think about it again.
Trigonometry doesn't
exist in the real world.
Really?
You know,
that's enough.
Let's go
for a ride.
Oh, I can't.
Dad grounded me.
I promised him
I'd study.
But you promised me
we'd go riding.
That was before I got busted.
So, why can't you do both?
Easy, easy,
easy, easy.
There you go.
( Nickering )
Hey, slow down.
You'll spook
the new horse.
You wouldn't really mind
if we went for a ride,
would you?
( Sighing )
Did you get your homework done?
Yes, he did.
We both did.
Almost.
"Almost" means
you didn't, Simon.
Simon:
"Almost" means almost.
We won't be out long.
We can finish
when we get back.
Please, mom?
It's such a
beautiful day.
All right. Half an hour, okay?
Deal.
Oh, can I, can I ride Zad?
Sure.
Half an hour means half an hour.
No "almosts."
Clea, you're an idiot!
Loser!
Loser, huh?
Look, no feet!
( Grunting )
Simon.
Simon, I know you're going
to leap up and scare me.
This isn't funny.
Simon?
Simon.
Such a sweet horse.
We've heard a lot of
good things about you.
( Both chuckling softly )
Clea:
Mom! Mom!
What happened?
Zad threw Simon.
Where is he?
At the bend
in the river.
Get help.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Simon?
Simon!
( Panting )
Simon. Oh, my baby!
Oh, god, no!
Oh, god, no! Simon!
Oh! Simon!
Simon! My baby!
Oh, my baby!
( Sobbing hysterically )
( Sobbing ):
My baby...
My baby.
Clea?
What's wrong, honey?
No, no. Slow down.
I can't understand...
Something's
happened to Simon.
Clea, what is it?
Nora...
How did it happen?
Zad never bucks...
Never gets spooked.
I don't know.
I don't know anything
about horses.
I've always been afraid
of their riding.
You're saying what
happened is my fault?
Of course not.
Nora, please, please.
It's not
a question
of blame.
Oh, I see.
You're letting me
off the hook.
Nora, please,
don't do this.
( Sighing )
Can I help?
( Knocking )
( Door opening )
You sleeping?
No.
I kind of figured
you weren't.
You feel
like talking?
No.
Well...
We just have
to get through this.
We have to.
( Sighing )
( Crying ):
Get through it.
We'll find a way
to get through it.
( Nickering )
( Crying )
Go!
( Gunshot )
Dad?
Stay here.
I heard a shot!
Zad's gone.
Nora?!
Mrs. Mahler!
( Crying )
Nora...
Give me the gun.
No. No, let me.
Let me have the gun.
Let me!
I want to die!
Give me the gun!
Let me!
I want to die!
( Sobbing )
( Sobbing continues )
Woman:
We've given your wife
a strong sedative.
It's just taking effect.
She'll sleep the better
part of tomorrow.
I'd like to keep her
under observation
for a couple of days.
She's in no shape
to leave here
and I think it
would be unwise
for her to attend
your son's funeral.
She'd never forgive me.
Then, you might
want to postpone it
a few days.
When she's
ready to leave
I'll give her
an anti-depressant
to help her
get through
the days ahead.
( Sighing )
What about the years ahead, Tom?
I think there's maybe
no heartache greater
than outliving
your own child.
You don't ever
recover from it.
You just learn
how to endure it.
Neal, if it's any comfort
Simon's death
was instantaneous.
He didn't suffer.
Well, then, I guess
he'll be the only one.
( Rooster crowing )
( Ignition bell dinging )
Luis...
( Whinnying )
The horse come back?
Oh, not yet,
but she will.
I don't want it here
when Nora gets home.
If it comes back,
take it to the auctioneer.
W-W... sell zad?
Nora doesn't want to see
that horse again, ever.
Are you sure...?
Just do it.
( Horse nickering )
Mrs. Rhymer...
Hmm?
There's a call for you.
Oh.
Thanks.
Hello?
No more.
If you don't eat, they
won't let you go home.
I just want to sleep.
All right.
Oh, excuse me.
( Softly moans )
Do you know this is
the same room you had
when they took
out your tonsils?
Mama?
You're not dreaming, baby.
I'm really here.
Oh, mama.
Simon's dead.
I know.
I know, honey.
( Crying )
( Sighs )
Want to go to your house...
Unload your stuff?
Climb over two months'
worth of junk mail?
I can wait, thanks.
Sorry I didn't
bring you anything
from new Mexico.
I thought I was going
to be there a while longer.
It's okay, grandma.
I can't get it
to register...
In-in my head.
Maybe because
I wasn't here, but...
I just can't accept
the fact that Simon
has suddenly
ceased to exist.
How's clea taking it?
She's said maybe
ten words to me
since I came.
That's eight more
than she's said to me.
I think she's still in shock.
I don't know what
to say to her.
I want to be incredibly
strong and reassuring,
but when I try,
nothing much comes out.
Oh, good grief.
From friends and neighbors.
Couldn't they have
spread it out a little bit?
Like over the next five years?
( Phone rings )
Hello.
Oh. Sure.
Okay.
Well, I'll pick
something out.
Does it have to be a suit?
Simon hates...
Suits.
Look...
I'll pick
something out, okay?
Bye.
I could use Nora
to help with this.
Well, Nora didn't
put herself
in the hospital,
doped up and tied to a bed.
She went crazy, Maggie.
You can't believe...
( Sighs )
Well...
You weren't here.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to be
second-guessing
you and the doctors.
Well, maybe I am.
But don't you think Nora would
come out of this a lot faster
if she were home here,
with her family?
I don't know.
I don't know how to
pull Nora out of this.
Nora always decides
what's best for Nora.
And that's reason
to abandon her now?
Come on, Maggie.
I haven't abandoned her.
You haven't exactly taken charge
of her, have you?
That's an interesting
criticism coming
from someone
who allowed her daughter
to be raised by a grandmother.
Nora demanded to live here
with my mother and the horses.
You don't think I'd rather
have had her with me?!
I was out of line.
I'm sorry.
We need to be
allies in this.
Apology accepted.
This might be chicken,
but I wouldn't swear to it.
It's fine.
Whatever.
( Sighs )
You can second-guess the doctors
if you want to, Maggie
but I'm putting
my faith in them.
I don't pretend to know better.
( Moaning )
Hello, sleepyhead.
How you feeling?
( Moaning )
Don't want to...
You don't want
what, sweetie?
You can't make me...
Make you what?
It's no use.
What's no use, Nora?
To go on.
This can't be right.
I'm busting you out of here.
There.
I'll take it
up to her.
Wait a minute.
Okay, now go.
( Sighs )
Room service.
I don't want anything.
Too late... it's here.
Don't be cheerful, Neal.
I can't stand it.
Did you take
your medication?
Yes...
But it didn't
bring Simon back.
It's not going
to do that, honey.
Then how is it going
to make me feel better?
Nothing is going
to bring Simon back.
We have to find a way
to go on without him.
What if we can't?
Nora, there are things
that have to be done...
Today.
We have to decide what
Simon's going to wear.
I have to go to sleep.
I have to go
to sleep now.
I can't do this alone.
I have to sleep now, Neal.
( Sobbing )
Luis...
Do you think
zad will come back?
She did come back...
Yesterday.
I took her
to be sold.
She'll be all right.
She'll get
a new home.
Your dad thought it would
be best for your mom.
I guess maybe
he's right.
Mom loves zad.
She loved Simon more...
And zad killed Simon.
( Quiet conversations )
( Woman laughing loudly )
Oh...!
( Conversations grow louder )
Excuse me.
Let's leave them alone.
It's my fault.
You won't say it
because you're afraid to,
but we both know
it's my fault.
It's not your fault.
Yes, it is.
I taught him to ride.
Maybe not well enough.
I didn't always make him
wear his helmet.
( Sniffling )
I let him out that day
against your wishes.
If it's not my fault,
whose fault is it?
It's no one's fault.
I don't want
to live here anymore.
You don't really mean that.
I don't want
to see this place
as long as I live.
( Sobbing )
I want to sell the farm
and the horses.
We can return the boarders
to their owners
and help Luis
find another job.
Nora...
Don't you think
maybe this is
the medication talking?
I'm not on the medication.
I didn't take it.
I wanted...
( Sighing )
To remember today.
I wanted to be clear.
I'm clear.
Maybe it is a good idea.
You know...
Leave here
for a while.
Move into town
till Nora feels better.
I don't have
a cold, Neal.
I lost my son.
I am not going to feel better.
I lost my son,
too, Nora.
Clea lost her brother.
Maggie lost her...
It's not the same.
I was in labor...
For 48 hours.
Simon almost died.
I almost died.
We have a bond.
It's ours.
We had a bond.
I think you
should leave here
for a while.
The three of you
move into my house,
and I'll come out here
and take care
of the farm
till we're all ready
to switch back.
Is that all right
with you, clea?
I don't have to ask if
it's all right with you.
You've never
liked this place.
Never less than now.
You'll have more privacy
than you've ever had.
You'll be a whole floor
away from us.
That's fine.
Clea, I was thinking...
Fran is really
overworked.
How would you like
an after-school job
in my office
at a fair wage?
I'd like it a lot, dad.
Good.
Here, let me
take that up.
Neal?
I think I'll stay
in my old room for a while.
Your grandparents built this
farm up from nothing, Maggie.
Now, you just can't
throw it away like
last week's garbage.
My mother didn't
leave the farm to me.
She left it to Nora, and
this is what she wants.
Well, selling the farm
won't help.
She loves it here.
Can't you make her see that?
I've never had much influence
on Nora.
No one ever has,
except my mother... and Simon.
Her owners found
another stable
that will take her.
Only three more
boarders left.
Don't get rid
of Nora's horses.
Just go ahead and put
them over in my barn.
They'll be there for her
when she comes back
to her senses.
Okay.
Oz:
Hey, Louie.
I could use
an extra hand
over at my place.
Have you ever milked a cow?
Well, how hard could it be?
Well...
Why don't you
just come on over
and find out?
Thanks.
( School bell ringing )
It's so weird, Justin.
I spend all day with kids
and teachers who knew Simon
but no one
even mentions him.
People just don't
know what to say.
His friends are all
probably hating me
because I'm still alive
and he's dead.
Clea, you sound
like a nut
when you talk like that.
I don't want to hear it.
I mean it.
How come you never
let me talk about it?
'Cause it's a bummer.
Look, I'm really sorry
that Simon's dead
but no one's to blame
except for the horse
that threw him.
I'm sorry.
I know it's not
your problem.
Don't say that.
Hey.
I'll pick you up
after work
and we'll go do
something fun.
Whatever you want.
Okay?
All right.
Fran:
You won't volunteer
so I'll ask.
How are things at home?
The move into town
hasn't helped.
If anything,
she's worse.
I don't know how
to take care of her.
Who's taking care of you?
I can't worry
about me right now.
I have too much else
on my mind.
Look, I shouldn't be
saying this,
but that's never stopped me.
You're on your own
in the best of times.
Nora is never there for you.
She always just thinks
of herself.
No.
There's another Nora
that you don't really know...
The Nora I fell in love with.
Where's she been
all these years?
Oh, she's still there, Fran...
Somewhere.
That's what keeps me
in the game.
( Door opening )
Fran:
Hey, pumpkin.
Hey, Fran.
Hey, dad.
Neal:
Hi.
You have gotten things
so organized around here
I actually had time to go
and get my nails done.
Ooh, nice.
There you are.
Clea's with Justin.
We're on our own.
I stopped by Castelli's
and picked up some dinner.
You want to eat now
or should I keep it warm
in the oven?
I don't care.
Whatever you want.
What I want, Nora
is for you to come back
to the world.
Our world.
Our world had Simon in it.
It doesn't exist anymore.
Well, maybe what we need
to do is make a new start.
A couple of months ago
I got a feeler
from the home office
asking me if I’d
be interested
in the job of regional
manager in Seattle.
I said no.
I knew there was no way
you'd ever leave
the farm.
Today I found out
the job is still open.
Everything
would be different.
A new city, a new home.
A new beginning.
Take it.
We don't have to decide
right this second.
It's a good job,
isn't it?
I don't want to do
anything you'd regret.
It's fine, Neal.
Take it.
You really mean that?
( Thunder crashing )
Woman:
I can give you a reason
for every dollar he's got.
Do you know he tried to
drive us out of our home
because he doesn't
like music?
That's sort of a
stinker, isn't it?
Woman: And how.
Believe me, the name of haskell
is pure poison around here.
Man:
Hmmm.
( Thunder crashing )
Luis:
Oz...! Iris...!
Fire!
( Ringing )
Hello?
Okay, Maggie,
I'll be right there.
What is it, Neal?
Fire at oz and Iris'.
I'm coming with you.
I'm coming, too.
I called the fire trucks.
Where are they?
Well, they'd better
get here quick.
Louie, get back.
We got to get the
animals out of there.
( Background chatter )
( Whinnying )
Let's take them to our barn.
( Glass breaking )
Iris:
Could have been
worse, I guess.
That's the way you have
to look at these things.
It could have been worse.
Iris, remember that
big fire when we were kids?
Wiped out half the farms
this side
of highway 96.
Burnt all your crops
and then stopped just
before it got to the house.
Yep. My mother
refused to leave.
She stood her ground
with this big garden hose
looking the fire in the eye
and just daring it
to mess with grace Hammond.
( Chuckles )
She was a
brave lady.
Oh, she was just
a stubborn one.
Woman:
Iris?
Oh, now what are
you two doing here?
You both have to be
at work in the morning.
Oh, don't you
worry about that.
I told them
you saw lightning
hit the toolshed.
That's right,
followed by flames.
It was definitely caused
by lightning.
Mm-hmm.
Well, we'll regroup in the
morning, assess the damage.
I'm sure glad
you're here.
So am I.
Nora and clea
haven't come
back yet?
Mmm, not yet.
You're safe now.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Could you
get him some hay?
Yeah, sure.
You're so
beautiful.
It's okay,
it's all right.
See? It's all right.
No reason to be scared.
Come on, boy, it's okay.
I want to talk to you
about something...
And I want an honest
answer, okay?
It's nothing bad.
I hope.
There's a chance...
And I don't know how
real it is right now
but it's a chance...
That I might get offered a job,
a good job, in Seattle.
Your mother's
in favor of it
but I wouldn't do it
against your will.
You'd leave mom and me?
No, we'd all go.
The idea is to make
a fresh start...
Leave the bad
stuff behind us.
I think it would be
good for your mother.
For you, it would
mean leaving Justin
and your friends...
Your grandmother.
Of course, she spends
half her time traveling.
She could just work Seattle
into her schedule.
Can I let you know?
Of course.
It's a lot to think
about, I know.
( Humming tune )
( Vehicle approaching )
Hey, Perseus...
You sweet old guy.
You got pretty scared
last night, didn't you?
Good boy.
( Nora sighing )
Oh, zad.
Shane gorman said that he saw
you and Alyson blubbering
in the hall before school.
"Blubbering"?
Was that his word or yours?
I don't know.
What's the matter?
Well, it better be
his word, that's all.
Oh. Okay, it
was his word.
Justin, have you ever
suffered a loss?
And I'm not just talking
about your CD collection
which you stupidly
left in an unlocked car.
Wait a second.
Are there suddenly two
classes of people here?
Those who have
lost a loved one
and those
who haven't?
Maybe.
Look, clea, how long
is this going to go on?
I can deal with
it for a while
'cause I care about you
but I can't spend the rest
of my high school days
weighed down by
a lot of drama.
Justin, if you had ever
given me a ring or anything
I would be throwing it
in your face right now.
Don't you want me
to walk you to work?
I'd rather crawl there over
broken glass than go with you.
You see what I'm talking about?
All this drama.
( Sighs )
If I did go, I wouldn't
leave you high and dry.
I've been grooming you
to be an agent, anyway.
We'll just speed it up.
Get you licensed and ready
to take over the agency.
Nora's actually going
along with this?
Absolutely. She
can't function here.
Moving away
is the best solution.
Leaving behind all the reminders
of what happened.
I'm not trying
to sound like a therapist,
but... have you given
any thought to staying here
and dealing with it?
It's easy
to say things like that.
Try living it, Fran.
That's my point... try living it.
The pain is
going to Seattle
right along with the
rest of the baggage.
Your running away is no way...
Take the new job, dad.
I called about the job.
They're going to fly
me up to Seattle
to meet the staff.
When do you go?
End of the week.
They're treating it
almost as a formality.
I'd say the job is mine,
assuming we come to terms.
That's exciting, Neal.
Isn't that exciting, clea?
I'm excited.
This is going to be good...
For all of us.
Man:
Hi, Neal.
Hi, Dennis.
Good to see you.
You, too.
I've got a couple of people
I'd like you to meet.
Okay.
This is, uh,
pat Patterson.
Neal Mahler.
Hi. How are you?
And this is
Lynn Davis.
Nice to meet you.
By the time I get rid of all
the junk I've been hoarding
I can probably move to
Seattle with a backpack.
Well, don't throw those out.
I want to go through them
all again.
( Sighs )
Will I ever be able
to look at him
without feeling
a knife in my heart?
I don't know.
Probably not.
Well, couldn't you just say yes?
That's what mothers are for...
Give maternal reassurance.
Like you do with clea?
I'm very maternal with clea.
She just doesn't need
a lot of it.
She's very self-sufficient.
Oh, well...
When you're on your own
you darn well better
be self-sufficient.
Well, what is that
supposed to mean?
It means what it means.
Well, thanks.
That clears it up.
Okay...
Let me put it this way.
How much time have you spent
with clea since Simon died?
I'm with her every day.
But have you actually
talked to her about Simon?
About her feelings?
Have you held her?
Reassured her?
She doesn't turn to me
for that, mother.
Why are you attacking me?
It's not an attack.
It's just an observation.
I'm someone who looks at you
and sees herself.
What?
When Neal called me in Santa Fe,
he said, "Nora needs you."
Those words rang in my ears.
I'd never heard them before.
( Chuckles softly )
"Nora needs you."
You never needed me.
Not since you were
a little child.
Or so I thought
because you never
came to me for things.
As I traveled back here...
During that...
Long night ride home
the closer I got, the more
I began to... to panic.
I didn't know how to help you.
What to say
or what to do.
( Sighs )
But... I needn't have worried.
I don't have to do anything...
Because you haven't
turned to me.
In the weeks
since I've been home, we...
We haven't even talked...
I mean heart-to-heart.
On one hand,
that's been a relief...
And on the other,
it's just made me feel empty
and... useless.
Oh, don't ever feel that, mama.
I know you're there
for me if I need it.
I just don't need it.
Oh... that's just it,
my darling... you do need it.
You just don't know how to ask
and I don't know
how to make you.
Well...
I have some clothes
in the dryer.
Will we have
horses in Seattle?
No.
I haven't been
riding since...
I know.
Neither have I.
Do you think
it would be all right
if I took Perseus out?
No. I'd rather
you didn't.
Just once...
Before we leave?
I don't know.
Please?
Well, maybe
if you wear a helmet.
You want to come with me?
No, I...
I don't think I'm ready yet.
Do you know how long it's been
since we went riding together
just you and me?
Eleven and a half months.
Please come with me, mom.
Mr. Mahler?
Yes, hello.
So glad you could make it.
As you can see,
it's all been freshly painted.
So, it's very, very clean.
All the furniture
is top of the line.
It's fully stocked
with glassware and China...
Kitchenware.
All of the appliances
are new,
and you have your
own washer and dryer.
Uh, two bedrooms and,
uh, two full baths.
We can arrange
a cleaning service if you like
and there's
reserved parking.
I'll take it.
Good.
( Crickets chirping )
( Screen door creaking
and shutting )
There you go, oz.
Thank you, ma'am.
Iris.
Oh, none for me.
If oz overindulges,
I'm the designated chef.
( Chuckling )
Is an English saddle
easier or harder to ride?
It's probably harder
at first.
Some people think
it's more graceful.
Would you say that I'm graceful?
I'd say potentially
that you're very graceful.
Well... would you teach me
to ride English?
Oh, clea...
We don't have a lot of time.
But we could start tomorrow,
right after school.
Okay.
( Chuckles )
( Acoustic guitar strumming )
( Crickets chirping )
( Door creaking )
( Muted guitar strumming )
I love hearing Luis play.
It's soothing,
like a warm bath.
I envy people who
have musical talent.
Yeah, my grandmother
made me take piano lessons.
I had to practice
every day
which I regarded
as punishment
seeing as I just wanted
to be out, riding my horse.
I wish I hadn't been
such a stubborn little brat.
( Guitar strumming continuing)
( Creaking )
( Crickets chirping )
( Chimes tinkling )
Here you are.
Did you know that when
the breeze blows this way
you can hear
the wind chimes
from oz and Iris'
walnut tree?
I never noticed that.
Me, neither...
But I've been noticing things
I never did before.
So, now, I can end up
missing all of it.
( Chuckles )
You having second
thoughts about leaving?
No.
Are you?
That's good.
Right.
I've been discovering
things, too...
Amazing things...
Like the fact that you
can play the guitar.
It's not that hard.
Luis has been teaching me
and Simon for about a year now.
I'm not talking
about how hard it is.
I'm talking
about the fact
that I was
completely unaware.
I thought I knew my
children inside out.
I don't even know
how much I know
and how much
I don't know.
You've never talked to me
about... Simon's death...
What happened...
How you felt
how... you feel.
I realize I've been selfish
treating this as...
My own personal tragedy
not thinking about what you
might be feeling...
But I can
listen now...
If you want.
Thanks, mom.
( Distant dog barking )
I'm back.
Clea?
Nora?
You're right,
it's more... graceful.
Don't worry, you'll
get the hang of it.
Really?
Sure, it just
takes time.
It's good... your
first time posting.
( Nickers )
I wish we...
Wish what, clea?
Nothing.
Wish what?
I wish things
were different.
( Car horn honking )
( Horse neighing )
I missed you, daddy.
Missed you, too,
honey.
You look good, Neal.
Neal:
I am good.
I wasn't sure
where you two were.
I called Maggie.
She didn't mention
you were out riding.
Well...
Now you know.
( Hooves departing )
Looks like I missed
a heck of a cookout.
Mm-hmm,
oz outdid himself.
I'm going to miss
Oz's barbecues.
oz and Iris.
But me you're not
too sure about, huh?
Nah, I'll miss
you a lot, Maggie.
When we buy our new house,
we'll make sure
there's a terrific
guest room for you.
With a private
bathroom, please.
And monogrammed towels.
( Chuckles )
I think you'll like
the temporary apartment.
It's got a great view.
The furniture is nothing
to write home about
but it shouldn't
take us too long
to find
a house we like...
And I checked out
your new high school.
It's big but modern
not the urban nightmare
you were dreading
and the kids look
just like the kids here
except more colorful hair.
( Chuckles )
My new secretary made
a list for you, Nora...
Of all the
um...
Okay...
What am I not getting here?
Nora:
Neal...
I'm not as sure
about this move
as I thought I was.
I know you've been...
Working hard, doing
what you felt was
in all of our
best interests
and I went
along with it
but I wasn't thinking
very clearly.
And now you are.
Yes, I believe I am.
Neal, you need to understand...
Understand what,
Nora?
That you're impulsive
and self-absorbed?
I understand that.
I've always understood it.
This isn't
just about me.
Since you've been gone,
I've gotten closer to clea
in a way that I'm ashamed
to say I never have.
You're trying to bring clea
into your camp.
Nora:
I don't have a camp.
Neal:
Sure, you do.
It used to be
you and Simon.
It was never like that.
Oh, yes, it was, and now
you're recruiting clea?
Well, I won't
let you do it.
Clea and I
will leave here
without you.
Clea:
Dad...
I don't want to leave home.
( Sighs )
I had nothing to do with this.
Nora:
Neal...
Listen to me...
Neal:
You expect me
to give in, like I always do,
like I always have.
You had to board horses.
You had to teach the children
to ride.
I gave in to you every time,
crumbled before the will
of the almighty Nora.
Well, not this time.
You go ahead.
You stay here with your mother
and your daughter
and your precious horses!
I'll be in Seattle.
( Door closing )
( Car engine starting )
( Sighs )
Clea:
Dad. Dad!
Dad!
No.
( Crying )
Maggie:
Neal?
Come to gloat?
You finally got rid
of me...
20 years later
than you wanted,
but, hey,
you can't have everything.
I never disliked
you, Neal.
I know you're
a good man.
I was just
always afraid
that you couldn't
handle her.
She's tough!
I could never
handle her.
I was afraid when
the chips were down,
you... you wouldn't
know what to do...
And the chips are
down now, Neal.
You've got to fight
to keep your family together.
I am fighting...
For myself, for once.
Yeah, but don't
just walk away.
Go back to the farm.
Face her.
Talk it out.
Oh, I see...
It's up to me.
I have to reach out.
I have to go
back, give in
accommodate.
That's not
what I'm saying.
Well, not anymore.
Never again.
Bye, Maggie.
Mmm, this is so good.
Mm-hmm.
I never remember
you making a pot roast
before, mama.
I must have once.
Maybe when you were
in grade school or something.
I remember grandma
used to make huge
meals every day.
Yes, and grandma was
also a size 16.
( Chuckles )
So, how was school today, honey?
It was okay.
You want to ditch
your homework?
Go catch a movie
at the mall?
Maybe grandma
wants to join us.
Yeah. Let's just leave
the dishes and go.
No, I'd better study.
What am I going
to do with her?
You all done?
Yeah.
Thanks for dinner, grandma.
Leave that, honey.
I'll clean up.
You go study.
I'll be upstairs.
( Sighs )
( Clea sobbing )
It's too late.
I heard you.
Tell me.
All right, then.
You just nod your head
yes or no, okay?
Are you crying
about your dad?
I know you
miss him, honey
but you're going
to visit him soon.
And it's not your
fault he's gone.
But it is.
It is.
All of it is
my fault, grandma.
Everything that's happened.
Oh, honey, why would you
want to feel like that?
I don't want to feel it.
It's true.
Everything is horrible,
and it's my fault.
Oh, no, not everything.
You and your mother
have gotten closer.
That's only because
she doesn't know.
Know what?
What, baby?
That I killed Simon.
Oh, clea!
I killed Simon.
It's my fault
that he's dead.
Clea.
( Knocking )
I talked him into riding
and then...
I made him race me,
which he didn't even want to do
but I made him...
( Sobbing )
And then...
Zad balked, and Simon fell,
and it was because of me!
No, it's not your fault.
It was an accident.
You didn't kill him.
You can't carry
that with you.
Oh, clea,
my sweet clea.
Why did you keep that
in all this time?
Oh, mama.
I am so sorry.
That's okay.
That's okay, baby.
You'll be okay.
I'm right here.
Nora:
Thanks for the hay, oz.
I appreciate it.
No problem.
Iris and I are glad
that you decided
not to sell the farm.
You know, I've
lived my whole life
next to your family.
Just wouldn't be the same.
No, nothing will ever
be the same, oz.
Simon's death
saw to that.
It took him away and...
Now it's taken away Neal.
You're laying that weight
on Simon's shoulders?
Let that poor boy
rest in peace.
What are you saying?
You heard me.
I spoke plain enough.
Don't blame your marriage
problems on a dead boy.
Your marriage had
just as many problems
while he was alive.
Now, you just
hold on a minute.
Listen to me.
I don't claim to know
everything that goes on
between a man and a woman
but turn the clock back
to that last day
before the accident.
Now, you tell me I'm wrong.
( Sighs )
( Typing )
( Door opens )
Mom, have you been
waiting for me?
No, I'm a little early.
I'll just be a minute.
Take your time.
( Resumes typing )
Fran:
I can pick up
the pills, too.
No, mother,
I won't forget.
All right. Bye-bye.
Hello, Nora.
You've made the place
look nice.
Didn't change
a thing.
You haven't been
here in a while.
Do you hear from Neal?
Practically every day.
He calls to check
on clients,
see how I'm getting along.
Does he ask about us?
Of course.
Why do you think
he's really calling?
Nora:
That's when Neal
got the award
from the chamber
of commerce.
I'd forgotten about that.
You weren't there.
You were busy that day.
Oh.
So, how's he doing?
Is he doing okay
up there?
How okay do you think
he could be without his family?
You don't like me much, do you?
Not much.
But I like Neal
and I want what's
best for him.
I don't think he's going to be
able to get over Simon's death
without your help.
Aren't you going
to ask me in?
Dirty socks and stuff.
You know, bachelor pad.
I've seen your
socks before.
It's nice.
Especially the art work.
Glad you like it.
If I'd known
you were coming,
I'd have gotten
the mu shu combo.
Comes with extra egg roll.
I don't need
food, Neal.
What I need is you.
My whole life...
You've always
just been there...
Like the air I breathe.
You don't appreciate air
till you're suddenly
short of breath,
and then it's all
you can think about.
Home isn't home without you.
I didn't know that
till you were gone.
( Sighs )
I need you so much.
It's still just
about what you need.
You haven't asked
about me.
I was going to ask.
I want to ask.
I don't mean just now.
I mean ever.
Well, that'll change.
I know I've got work
to do, Neal.
I'll do it.
I don't want it to be work.
I want it to be instinctive,
but that can't happen.
Leopards don't change
their spots.
You're so angry.
Why are you so angry?
Well, you can thank
yourself for that.
You do blame me...
For all of it.
Look, you came here
to get me to come back.
Well, forget it.
You've made your choice,
I've made mine.
Go home, Nora.
I used to love taking care
of the clients.
I was good at it, too, but now
I've got to get out and sell
which requires
Patience and tact...
Two of my greatest virtues.
I'm sure you've noticed.
Maybe it gets easier
with practice.
Maybe.
( Door opening )
Uh... can I
talk to you?
Alone?
I'm a potted plant.
( Sighs )
Look, uh, you said
if I'd ever given you
a ring or anything
you'd be throwing
it in my face.
So, uh...
Don't throw it
in my face, okay?
I miss you.
I even miss
all the drama.
And I can deal with it
as long as you need me to.
Come here.
( Clea sighing )
This should be pretty sturdy.
Thanks.
You need any
help packing?
I got it.
Do you think
it'll rain up there?
I think that's
a pretty safe bet.
So, when you're up
there this weekend,
why don't you take
a good look around?
See how you like
it up there.
You mean see how I like it
for more than just a weekend?
Just think about it.
I made reservations
for tonight at a restaurant
that's supposedly very upscale.
I've never been,
so you'll be the judge.
Dad, what do I know?
In elk Springs,
upscale is anyplace
that doesn't have a
drive-through window.
And we've got tickets
for the ice show tomorrow night.
Dad, I really appreciate
you going all out for me
but what I want to do is
have a look around town...
The high school, and...
The high school?
I want to know what it'd
be like to live here.
Clea, did you and your mother
have a fight or something?
No.
I want to come home.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You and your mother
live at home.
No.
Home is where you are.
I want to be home with you
wherever that
has to be.
And your mother?
I think she feels
the same way.
So...
Why don't we ditch
the fine dining
and check out
the fast food joints
because I need to know
what Seattle burritos
taste like.
What's going on?
Well, we came back early.
Oh, so I see.
I'm glad.
She's out riding.
( Footsteps approach )
Something
happen to clea?
No, no.
Clea's fine.
She's here,
back at the house.
Is this where you found him?
Yes.
I never came out to look.
I wasn't ready for him to die.
I haven't come
to terms with it.
I'm still filled
with anger and grief...
That I haven't let myself feel.
I think I have to do that
before I can do anything else.
I'd like to do it with you.
If you'll let me.