I was there when everything changed.
Forty years ago.
It was our third world war,
and humanity was determined to end itself.
Then, on the edge of annihilation,
an alien saved us.
He smashed our tools of war.
He forced us to stop fighting,
and shut down World War III
in one fucking day.
We called him
Marvelous Man.
For the first time in history,
world peace appeared possible.
- Good evening, America.
- Mom?
I'm award-winning journalist Van Dawson,
and this is Van Dawson Tonight.
We eagerly await
the 40th anniversary of Marvelous Man Day.
The day Marvelous Man
appeared from the sky
to single-handedly end World War III.
Will our first superhero
continue to remain staunchly neutral
in human conflicts?
Will he act against
the expansionist hive mind Anubis?
Will he condemn President Nick Nukem's
aggressive military rhetoric?
We now go live to the Citadel of Justice,
where Marvelous Man is moments away
from giving his yearly M Day address.
M Day!
People of Earth...
this is Marvelous Man.
Come on! Come on! Check this out!
Look at that. That's my hero!
For four decades,
I have protected you.
I saved you.
Boom!
I don't feel anything.
I'm a prisoner in this bulletproof skin.
Why does Marvelous Man look so sad, Mom?
And when I close my eyes,
this is what I hear.
Please, help me!
Why? Why didn't you save us?
- Why didn't you save us?
- Where are you?
- You're supposed to be our savior!
- Where are you? Where are you?
- Where are you?
- Our savior!
If I sleep,
people die.
Real inspiring speech, Cal.
Wait, is...
is that caltronite?
No!
What?
I'm tired of hiding.
I'm tired.
So I've found my escape.
No. Don't do this, Cal!
I found it.
- No!
- What happened?
Mom!
- Cecilia?
- Yeah?
Are we live?
Marvelous Man is dead.
Um...
Clear my schedule.
What we have just witnessed
is obviously a dark day for mankind.
There are no words to properly express
what just happened
and what we have lost
as a nation,
as a species,
as a planet.
Fatality.
The Guardians of Justice will save you.
♪ He's the greatest president
We've ever had ♪
♪ Abraham Lincoln can leave his bed ♪
♪ Nick Nukem ♪
My fellow Americans,
an immigrant from another planet
came to our shores
and made not only a life for himself,
but created a lasting legacy as well.
In the wake of his death,
America will continue
to protect the legacy of Marvelous Man.
We will prevent
the escalation of nuclear conflict.
We will curtail the homosexual epidemic
that is gripping our great nation.
Asshole!
And I promise you
that even with Marvelous Man gone,
our enemies will continue to fear us.
God bless you, and God bless America.
We're fucked, people!
Aw, Phil.
Now that Marvelous Man is gone,
who is going to save us?
People on the streets are going crazy.
It's as if the whole world has...
has lost all hope.
The year is 1960.
Marvelous Man has brought
rapid technological advancement,
causing social turmoil and an escalation
of street-level violence.
In this asphalt jungle,
we join a lone vigilante, the Knight Hawk,
conducting a crusade against
costumed crime kingpin The Demander.
In this moment of peril,
a god aligned himself with a man.
Together, they would forge a friendship
that became the cornerstone
of the Guardians of Justice.
For our next segment,
an exclusive interview with the former
CIA operative who stole a god's heart.
America's princess, now America's widow,
Laura Louis.
And we're live in three, two...
Ms. Louis, you have my condolences.
The world shares your grief.
How are you processing
what your husband has done?
He wouldn't do that.
He wouldn't do that to the world,
to the Guardians,
to me.
I think there can be no question
Marvelous Man committed suicide.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
I've been watching it and re-watching it
over and over and over again.
He was murdered.
Murdered?
Shocking revelations
from Marvelous Man's widow.
Was Marvelous Man murdered?
We will investigate
the allegations tonight at ten...
Suicide or murder?
The world demands answers. The last 24
hours have shaken our planet to its core.
If you're right, then there's one question
the world needs answered.
Who, if anyone, killed Marvelous Man?
We need to hear
from the Guardians of Justice,
and specifically
from Marvelous Man's second-in-command.
Knight Hawk, where are you?
Computer,
call the Guardians.
King Tsunami here.
Speed here.
Golden Goddess.
Mm. Awsome Man present.
Sorry. I'm eating a taco.
Blue-Scream online.
Black Bow here.
With Marvelous Man gone,
it's time to suit up,
assume control of the Guardians,
and protect the planet.
Golden Goddess!
She's the princess
of the god realm.
The Speed!
The only person
faster than Marvelous Man.
Black Bow!
Expert marksman
and reality star.
Blue-Scream!
Whose sonic scream
contains immense power.
King Tsunami!
Overlord of the oceans.
Awsome Man!
Who possesses a magic word
that gives him the power of seven gods.
Together, we form
the Guardians of Justice.
With Marvelous Man gone,
there's a power vacuum
that could rip this world apart.
We can't have that happen.
Yeah. How are we gonna do that? All of us
combined are not equal to Marvelous Man.
Speak for yourself, human.
Oh, come on. Don't fight.
You're a fucking fish.
What can you do? You can talk to fish.
"Oh, wow! I'm so fucking powerful!"
Pathetic street whore.
I'm a king, and I demand respect!
Enough!
You're supposed to be role models. Heroes.
Try and act like it.
Blue-Scream's right.
None of us compare to Marvelous Man.
But if we work together as a team,
we could save this world.
We can honor our fallen Guardian.
We could strive to be
marvelous.
Everyone knows Marvelous Man
didn't just protect a city or a town.
He protected the world.
Now that's on us.
Awsome Man, Speed, Golden Goddess,
you're the only ones fast enough
to handle an international crisis.
There's a squad of cyborg T-Rexes
on the loose in Syria.
Take them down and bring them to justice.
Consider it done.
A massive mudslide
has thousands trapped and dying.
Awsome Man, the Red Cross
needs you in Thailand.
The Hawk drones
will back you up with supplies.
Activate.
You can count on me.
Speed, I need you
to pick up Blue-Scream and drop him in LA.
A new street drug called "Mellow Devil"
is causing people to lose their minds.
- We've got to extinguish the fires.
- You got it.
He can't do that alone.
I should go with him.
- I'll be fine. Speed, let's go.
- I'm on my way.
Wait, Speed!
After you've dropped Scream in LA,
I need you to get back here,
because we've gotta get
Black Bow to Peru.
Wait, wait, wait. What am I,
the Guardians' delivery boy?
You're whatever the Guardians
need you to be. Now, move!
And me?
The Scottish Skull
has hijacked an American submarine
off the coast of New Zeamar.
Walker! How did you break this feed?
Despite what you'd like
to believe, Atticus,
there are people smarter than you.
Addison Walker.
She runs a private military group
funded by a few dozen corporations.
Her objective? Maintain global
economic stability at all cost.
She's playing chess
and only she gets to see the board.
What do you want?
As you know,
Marvelous Man was leading negotiations
for a worldwide nuclear disarmament.
Since his death, those negotiations
have spun out of control.
That sounds
like your problem,
not mine.
Oh. It's going to become
everyone's problem soon.
Because of the questions
surrounding Marvelous Man's death,
every country is pointing the finger
at one another.
China is saying Russia had him killed.
Iran and Iraq are sure
the job was done by the Americans.
That doesn't even make sense.
The steps that lead us to war rarely do.
The only way this ends
without an all-out nuclear holocaust
is if you find out
who really killed Marvelous Man.
So you don't think
it was a suicide?
I don't.
But from what I hear, neither do you.
I don't have an opinion.
And I won't have an opinion
until my investigation is completed.
Yes, but I know the problem
is you're looking in the wrong place.
Are you fucking with me or what?
You need to look
at the Guardians themselves.
The Guardians?
What do you know that I don't?
Time is running short.
Find the answer.
Or I'll arrest you
and every one of your super friends
before declaring martial law
on the world.
Knight Hawk to Guardians.
Complete your mission
and report to the Hawk's Nest.
♪ We do not need forever ♪
♪ Honey, we've got now ♪
♪ Tell me God is dead ♪
♪ I'm safe, let's go to bed
And think something, somehow ♪
♪ Wake me when you're gone... ♪
Jesus Christ!
That's fucked up, man.
I know. I know. But think about it.
Marvelous Man is dead. Right? Huh?
So, you think if we wore his skin,
we'd be bulletproof?
I mean, I guess. I-it's like
a bulletproof jacket. You know?
It... it still goes through.
It hurts like shit.
No, it doesn't!
At least, I think it doesn't.
Shit. I mean...
'Cause his whole body is bulletproof.
It's impenetrable, man. All right?
If you wore his skin, you'd still be
a doughboy with shit muscles.
Oh, fuck you. Fuck you.
You know how much I've been lifting.
Yeah, yeah.
You're lifting beer and donuts, man.
- That still counts.
- Yeah. In your world.
What's the count at?
Three and a half.
Look at this one.
- Smiley face?
- Uh-huh.
- Shit.
- Oh, well...
Another smiley face.
Oh, okay.
Look at this one here.
Fucking ground beef.
How's that wife of yours, man?
She's good.
She's a little stressed out.
Kid had an accident. You know?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Hey, when it rains, it pours.
Tell me about it.
I'm missing that single life though.
Yeah. Look at this one here.
The eyeball's out.
Oh.
Single life?
You are missing it.
- Hey, I forgot to ask you...
- What?
- Another smiley face.
- Yeah.
How was that...
how was that date the other night?
What date? Oh, yeah!
The one with the big old...?
Yeah, the tig old bitties.
Oh, man, she was... Crazy, but she was nice.
Yeah.
I fucking love titties, man.
I know you do.
Oh. Look at this. Oh sh...
- Stinks!
- That smells like shit, man.
- Oh, man!
- Fucking maggots and shit.
Oh, yeah.
Oh. Look at this one.
Shit.
Got a splitting headache,
I guess. I don't know.
That's disgusting.
Check this one out here.
- That's not right, man.
- Oh, man. Faceless.