♪
[brushing on canvas]
- [baby cooing]
- AW...
[laughs]
OK. OH...
- [cooing]
- OOH, MY LITTLE MAN.
YES, YES, YES.
[kissing sounds]
[laughs]
[cars honking]
[classical music]
- BRITT, WHERE WERE YOU
LAST NIGHT? WE MISSED YOU.
EVERYONE ASKED FOR YOU.
- WEREN'T YOU THE ONE
WHO TOLD ME
THAT I HAD TO BUILD
MY BODY OF WORK?
I WAS HOME WORKING.
- NICHOLAS SAID YOU WERE
UPSET ABOUT SOMETHING.
- NO. I'M FINE.
- YOU KNOW, I RAISED TWO KIDSON MY OWN RIGHT HERE.
THEY'D CRAWL AROUND THE FLOORBETWEEN THE LEGS OF THE ARTISTS
AND CLIMB IN MY LAP WHILE I WAS
TALKING TO INVESTORS.
IT WAS A GREAT EXPERIENCE.
- I-- THIS KID IS--
HE'S A GIFT.
IT'S JUST HARD, YOU KNOW.
- I'VE RECOMMENDED YOU
FOR THE ARTIST ACADEMY
FOUNDATION GRANT.
- YOU WHAT?
- IT'S WORTH $25,000
IF THEY ACCEPT YOU,
AND, OF COURSE,
A MAJOR EXHIBITION.
- [sniffs]
[sighs]
[birds tweeting]
- MORNING, MAMA.
- OH, GOOD MORNING.
[laughs]
[kissing sounds]
- READY FOR BREAKFAST?
- OH, DARLING, I'VE MADEA DECISION ABOUT THANKSGIVING.
- OH, GOOD. WHERE DO I
MAKE A RESERVATION?
- NO, NO, NO.
I'M GOING TO COOK.
- ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
- ABSOLUTELY.
NOW, WILL YOU BE A PEACH
AND CALL CONNIE AND MERLE,
BECAUSE I HAVE SO MANY THINGSTO DO.
OH, CALL BRITT.
- WHY DON'T YOU CALL BRITT?
- I THINK IT WOULD BE BETTER
IF YOU DID.
[phone rings]
- HELLO?
- BRITT, IS THAT YOU?
- BARELY.
- DID I WAKE YOU?
- WHAT TIME IS IT?
- IT'S TWO IN THE AFTERNOON.
- I WAS JUST NAPPING
WITH HENRY.
WHAT IS GOING ON, VALETTA?
IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
- OF COURSE, EVERYTHING'S
ALL RIGHT.
I-- I JUST HAVEN'T HAD
A MINUTE TO CHECK IN ON YOU.
I-- YOU KNOW HOW IT IS HERE.
I'VE BEEN VERY BUSY.
ALWAYS LOTS GOING ON.JULIAN HAS HIS BUSINESS DINNERS.
I'M PICKING PEOPLE UP,
DROPPING THEM OFF.
CUB SCOUTS.DAUGHTERS OF AMERICA MEETINGS.
UM...
I'M AT MAMA'S.
- AND HOW IS MAGGIE?
- OH, SHE'S FINE.
- SO, WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO SAY, VALETTA?
- THANKSGIVING'S COMING UP.
- YEAH?
- SO SHE WANTS ALL OF US HERE.
- YEAH.
- MAMA SAYS SHE'S GOING TO
FIX DINNER HERSELF.
- IT WOULD ALMOST BE WORTH
COMING TO SEE THAT.
- BRITT, YOU KNOW HOW LONG IT'S
BEEN SINCE YOU'VE BEEN HERE?
- OK. I'LL THINK ABOUT IT, OK?
- GOOD.
WE'LL SEE YOU THEN.
- I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
AND, UH, VALETTA?
- YES?
- THANK YOU FOR
THE WAKE UP CALL.
- ANYTIME.
[beeps off]
[sirens wailing]
- YOU HAVE GOT STRONG HANDS.
- BABY, THESE ARE MORE LIKE
WORN IN.
- [laughs]
OH, NO.
IT'S REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
- I KNEW I LIKED HAVING YOU
AROUND.
YOU'RE AN EASY AUDIENCE
TO PLEASE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I'D DO WITHOUT YOU.
- YOU KIDDING ME? IF I DIDN'THAVE YOU TO LOOK AFTER HENRY...
- HEY, WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS DO
FOR ONE ANOTHER.
[knocking]
- I'LL GET IT.
IT'S PROBABLY NICHOLAS.
- HI.
- HEY.
- SORRY I'M LATE.
- IT'S OK.
HE'S SLEEPING,
AND I ALREADY FED HIM.
- GOOD.
HMM. I'LL TAKE HIM
TO THE STUDIO.
HEY, HENRY.
HOW'S MY BOY?
- HEY, NICHOLAS.
HOW YOU DOING, MAN?
YOU WANT SOMETHING TO DRINK?
- NO, THANKS, MARION. NO.
CAN I TALK TO YOU
OUTSIDE FOR A MINUTE?
- YEAH.
- GO AHEAD.I GOT EVERYTHING COVERED HERE.
- SO, HAVE YOU THOUGHT
ABOUT US AT ALL?
- ACTUALLY, VERY LITTLE.
- THAT'S FUNNY.
- [laughs]
- SERIOUSLY,
THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE TO CONSIDERIN ALL THIS, YOU KNOW.
- YEAH, HENRY AND I
ARE GETTING ALONG JUST FINE.
- I KNOW YOU'RE FINE,
BUT HE NEEDS A FATHER.
- HE'S GOT A FATHER-- YOU.
- OK, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- DO WE REALLY NEED TO
DO THIS AGAIN?
- I WANT YOU, BRITT.
I WANT MY SON.
I WANT TO BE LIKE
A REAL FAMILY.
- I LOVE YOU.
I DO.
I CAN'T TALK ABOUT THIS NOW.
AND MY MOTHER WANTS METO COME HOME FOR THANKSGIVING,
SO IF I GO,
I'M GOING TO BRING HENRY.
- REALLY?
- YEAH.
- WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S VERY GOOD.
WANT ME TO GO WITH YOU?
- [laughs] OH, NO.
I CARE ABOUT YOU WAY TOO MUCHTO SUBJECT YOU TO MY MOTHER.
- MM.
YOU NEED SOME MONEY?
I MEAN, I SOLD A COUPLE
PAINTINGS THE OTHER DAY.
I--I'M ABLE TO HELP, YOU KNOW.
- I DON'T NEED ANYTHING.
I'M FINE.
- CAN I CALL YOU
WHEN YOU'RE THERE?
- I DIDN'T SAY I'M GOING.
[cutting sounds]
- I SURE HOPE BRITT SHOWS UP.
IT WILL BE THE FIRST
REAL THANKSGIVING
WE'VE HAD IN YEARS.
- REMIND ME, WHICH SIDE OF THEKNIFE DOES THE SPOON GO ON.
- IT GOES ON THE OUTSIDE.
KNIFE PROTECTS THE SPOON.
[stirring]
SIT DOWN BECAUSE
HERE IT COMES.
- MMM. LOOKS GREAT.
DON'T YOU EVER GET TIRED OF
TAKING CARE OF
YOUR SISTER-IN-LAW?
- WELL, YEAH,
BUT WHO ELSE HAS THE PATIENCETO DEAL WITH YOU?
- [laughs]
[liquid pouring]
[car honking]
[plane landing]
[tires screeching]
[muted overhead announcements]
- WE'RE HERE.
- BRITT!
OH, FINALLY!
- HEY.
- I'VE JUST BEEN WAITINGAND WAITING FOR YOU TO GET HERE.
- OH.
OOH, THIN AS A STICK.
- OH, PLEASE!
- DON'T THEY FEED YOU
IN THE BIG CITY?
- I EAT LIKE A PIG.
- WHERE'S THAT KID?
both: [laughing]
- HENRY?
THERE WE GO.
[sighs]
THIS IS HENRY.
- WHAT A HANDSOME DEVIL
YOU ARE.
- MEET YOUR AUNT BILLY
WHO'S GOING TO BE ON HER
BEST BEHAVIOR, AREN'T YOU?
- NOT A GHOST OF A CHANCE.
[laughs]
HEY, COME ON.
LET'S GO INSIDE.
- I'LL GET THE BAGS.
- NO, LEAVE 'EM.
I'LL GET 'EM LATER.
WELL, HENRY, HERE WE ARE.
HOME.
[laughs]
WHY DON'T YOU COME
IN THE KITCHEN WITH ME.
I'VE GOT SOMETHING
REALLY GOOD FOR YOU.
[laughs]
WE SURE ARE GLAD YOU'RE HOME
WHERE YOU BELONG, KIDDO.
OK, HERE YOU ARE
IN AUNT BILLY'S KITCHEN.
[buckles clinking]
- CAREFUL. DON'T HACK THE LIMBS.CUT THEM.
I DON'T WANT THEM LOOKING
ALL CHOPPED UP.
- YOU SHOULD HAVE BEEN
A GENERAL.
PATTON WOULD HAVE WORSHIPPED
AT YOUR FEET.
- [laughs]
HELLO THERE.
- HEY.
- HOW DID YOU GET HERE?
- TOOK A CAB.
- WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ANYONE?
I WOULD HAVE HAD YOU PICKED UP.
- OH.
- IS HENRY WITH YOU?
- YEAH, HENRY'S WITH ME.
- BRITT, YOU TOOK A CAB
WITH A BABY?
- YEAH.
- YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THOSE DRIVERS.
THE CABS ARE FILTHY.
A GIRL'S NOT SAFE
IN ONE OF THOSE THINGS.
- VALETTA.
- NO.
WHEN JULIAN AND I GO
TO THE AIRPORT,
WE ALWAYS HIRE A LIMO.
- OK, FINE.
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
- I'M TRYING TO GET THIS PLACEINTO SOME SORT OF SHAPE.
[sighs]
MAMA DOESN'T WANT TO
SPEND ANY MONEY ON IT,
AND IT'S GETTING RUNDOWN.
I MEAN, HERE IT IS NOVEMBER.
ALL OF THIS SHOULD HAVE
BEEN DONE MONTHS AGO.
- LOOK'S PRETTY GOOD TO ME.
- THAT'S BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
IT'S IN TERRIBLE CONDITION.
THE HOUSE NEEDS PAINT
AND A MILLION OTHER THINGS.
SHE JUST HAS NO IDEA WHAT NEEDS
TO BE DONE AROUND HERE.
- HOW IS MAGGIE?
- YOU HAVEN'T BEEN
TO SEE HER YET?
UH, SHE'S GOOD.
SHE'S OVER THERE
WORKING IN HER FLOWER BEDS.
- SO, UM, YOU GOING TO
BE HERE FOR A WHILE?
- NO, I AM OUT OF HERE
AS SOON AS I CAN GET THESE GUYS
TO FINISH UP.
LITTLE JULIAN HAS
PIANO PRACTICE.
BUT WE'RE ALL COMING FOR DINNER.- OH, OK.
THEN I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
- MM-HMM.
UH, BRITT?
DON'T FORGET TO DRESS
FOR DINNER.
- [laughs]
OK. DRESS FOR DINNER.
RIGHT.
- [sighs]
- MAGGIE?
- BRITT.
IT SEEMS LIKE FOREVER.
YOU COULD HAVE CALLED
NOW AND THEN.
- SO COULD YOU.
- NOW LET ME GET A LOOK AT YOU.
YOU'RE PENCIL THIN.
- YOU'RE LOOKING WELL.
- [laughs]
THESE WRINKLES KEEP MULTIPLYING
LIKE HOUSEFLIES.
GROWING OLD IS FOR THE BIRDS.
- IT'S HARD FOR ME TO
IMAGINE YOU OLD.
- WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
I WON'T GIVE INTO IT.
[laughs]
YOUR FATHER AND I USED TO
BE OUT HERE FOR HOURS AND HOURS
WITH ALL THESE LEAVES FALLING.
WE'D BE RAKING UNTIL
OUR BACKS WERE ACHING.
[laughs]
YES, I'M GOING TO PLANT
ZINNIAS HERE THIS SPRING.
IT WAS YOUR FATHER'S
FAVORITE FLOWER, YOU KNOW.
- SO HOW YOU BEEN FEELING?
- PEOPLE MAKE SUCH A FUSS
ABOUT GETTING OLD.
THAT'S ALL THEY EVER
WANT TO TALK ABOUT.
NEXT SUBJECT.
- WHY DO WE HAVE TO
CHANGE THE SUBJECT?
- I DON'T WANT TO MAKE THIS
HOLIDAY INTO A WAR ZONE, BRITT.
DO WE UNDERSTAND ONE ANOTHER?
- I DIDN'T START ANYTHING.
- DO WE UNDERSTAND ONE ANOTHER?
- I'M GOING TO GO CHECK
ON HENRY.
- IS THAT YOUR BOYFRIEND?
- NO, IT'S MY SON, REMEMBER?
- OH, CHARLIE WAS SO HANDSOME.
- WHAT DOES DADDY
HAVE TO DO WITH THIS?
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THE OLD PLACE?
- NOTHING SEEMS TO CHANGE.
WANT TO COME MEET
YOUR GRANDSON?
- WELL, NO. I'LL MEET HIM
AT DINNER, DEAR.
[cell phone rings]
- HELLO?
- CLAIRE GOODMAN EISENBERG,
HAVE YOU BECOME
A BORING OLD BITTY?
- [laughs]BRITT, WHERE THE HECK ARE YOU?
- [laughs]
I AM RIGHT HERE AT HOME.
- OH MY, HENRY.
IS HE WONDERFUL?
- HENRY'S BEAUTIFUL.
HE'S...HE'S BEAUTIFUL.
- OK, I HAVE TO SEE YOU.
- TOMORROW?
- PERFECT.
UH, GET YOUR BEHIND OUT HERE
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING,
AND WEAR YOUR BOOTS.
- SEE YA.
[clicks off phone]
[sighs]
- WE'LL TALK ABOUT THIS LATER.
COME ON, SWEETIE.
- [cooing]
- HEY, BRITT. LONG TIME NO SEE.
- [laughs]
HEY, JULIAN.
- OH, MY GOODNESS.
- LOOK AT HIM.
- OH MY GOODNESS! HELLO!
[kissing sounds]
OH, WHAT A BEAUTIFUL BOY.
- WELL, HE HAS YOUR EYES.
- I THINK THEY'RE NICHOLAS'S.
- WHERE IS THIS NICHOLAS
ANYWAY?
- HE'S IN L.A.
- WELL, HE LOOKS HEALTHY.
- HERE, YOU WANT TO HOLD HIM?- NO, NOT RIGHT NOW.
- [baby gurgles]
- COME ON.
COME ON IN THE KITCHEN
WITH AUNT BILLY.
YOU CAN HELP ME OUT.
- OK, MAGGIE, HERE YOU GO.
- THANK YOU.
- SO WHAT'S YOUR POISON, BRITT?
BOURBON?
- I'LL JUST HAVE
SOME WHITE WINE.
- SURE.
- WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
IT JUST SEEMS SO DOUR.
- I THINK IT'S YOUR BASICSYLVIA PLATH NUMBER, ISN'T IT?
- [laughs]
- [sighs]
COULD WE PLEASE NOT DO THIS
TONIGHT?
- COLOR. JUST GIVE ME
LOTS OF COLOR ANYTIME.
WHERE DID YOU FLY IN FROM?
- DETROIT. PHOENIX.
I MADE A PRESENTATION
THIS MORNING
AT OMNIDEC IN SAN FRANCISCO.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU DO IT.
I'M WORN OUT
JUST GETTING OFF THE PLANE.
- THE PORTERS AT THE AIRPORT
SEE MORE OF HIM THAN I DO.
- COME AND GET IT
BEFORE I CAN SKATE ON IT!
[crickets chirping]
- SIT UP STRAIGHT, JULIAN.
- OH, AND PLEASE DO NOT
USE YOUR SALAD FORK
FOR THE HAM.
- HEY, RELAX.
IT'S NOT A STEAK DINNER.
- HE NEEDS TO LEARN
TABLE MANNERS.
HE MIGHT BE AT A FUNCTION
SOME DAY
WHERE IT WILL COME IN HANDY.
- YOU DON'T KNOW WHEREHE'S GOING TO BE IN 20 YEARS.
LET HIM BE A KID, RIGHT.
[laughs]
- NO, NO.
- WELL, WE CERTAINLY KNEW
WHAT YOU WERE GOING TO BE.
YOU PRACTICALLY JUMPED
OUT OF THE WOMB,
RAN AROUND THE CORNER
TO THE ART SUPPLY STORE.
AND VALETTA YOU CAME OUTWITH A CHECKLIST IN YOUR HAND.
all: [laugh]
- I THINK SOMEONE
NEEDS A CHANGE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- WHY DON'T YOU TAKE HIM
UPSTAIRS?
IT'S INAPPROPRIATE.
- HE'S A BABY.
EVERYBODY DOES IT.
EVEN YOU, MAGGIE.
- YOU COULD USE
THE DOWNSTAIRS BATHROOM.
- HMM.
- OK.
EVERYTHING UNPLEASANT
OUT OF SIGHT.
THAT WAY, IT DOESN'T EXIST.
[baby yells]
- SIT UP STRAIGHT, JULIAN.
- OH, BILLY ALWAYS MAKESTHE MOST SCRUMPTIOUS COBBLERS.
MM. BUT DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
WE DON'T WANT HER
TO GET THE BIG HEAD.
[laughs]
- OUTSTANDING COBBLER, BILLY.
- OK, HAVE ANOTHER HELPING,
KIDDO.
OK, COFFEE COMING UP.
- LET ME HELP YOU.
[dishes rattling]
- MAMA, HAVE YOU GOTTENYOUR THANKSGIVING MENU TOGETHER?
- WHAT ARE TALKING ABOUT, DEAR?
- WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO SERVE?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING, DARLING.
- THANKSGIVING DINNER?
YOU'RE COOKING IT THIS YEAR,
REMEMBER?
- OH, WELL.
I THINK I'D LIKE
TO GET A NEW DRESS.
- WELL, YOU CAN DO THAT, TOO.
- IF DINNER'S TOO MUCH
TO HANDLE, WE CAN DO IT.
- I DON'T LIKE TO
MAKE A BIG FUSS.
- WELL, THEN DON'T.
- BILLY, WHAT'S FOR DESSERT?
- MAGGIE, WE ALREADY
HAD DESSERT.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME MORE?
- YES, YES. I WOULD LIKE
SOME MORE, THANK YOU.
- WHAT THE HECK WAS THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- MAGGIE.
- THE FORGETFULNESS?
- FORGETFUL?
TODAY IN THE YARD
SHE COMPLETELY LOST IT.
AND THEN AT DESSERT--- SHE'S OLD. WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
- SO YOU'RE JUST GOING TO
DISMISS THIS?
- WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
- I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
- ARE YOU PLANNING ON
STICKING AROUND?
BECAUSE IF YOU ARE THEN
BE MY GUEST, JUMP RIGHT IN.
[birds tweeting]
[laughing]
- HOW'S DONNY?
- HE'S GOOD.
HE'S GOOD.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER
FOR SO LONG
WE KIND OF SPEAK IN CODE.
[laughs] NO ONE ELSE CANUNDERSTAND WHAT WE'RE SAYING,
BUT WE CAN.
IT'S GOOD.
IT WORKS FOR US.
SO TELL ME THE TRUTH. HOW DOESIT FEEL TO BE BACK HOME?
- I HAVE A RECURRING NIGHTMARE
THAT I'LL BE STUCK HERE
FOR ETERNITY.
- WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
I'D END UP HERE.
BUT I GET TO RAISE MY KIDS
AROUND ANIMALS AND NATURE.
AND IT'S NOT TOO SHABBY.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
I'VE LEARNED TO LOVE
THE SMELL OF HORSE MANURE.
- HEY, RACE YOU TO THE POND.
both: [laughing]
- YA-HOO!
- HI-YA!
[laughter]
- COME ON!
both: [laughing]
- [screaming]
WHOA! WHOA!
both: [laughing]
- I DID SO BEAT YOU!
- YOU DID NOT!
[door opens]
- MAMA?
- OUT HERE!
- I BROUGHT YOUR DRY CLEANING.
- OH, THANK YOU, DARLING.
DID YOU READ THE BUSINESS
SECTION THIS MORNING?
- UH, NO.
- BECAUSE THERE'S AN ARTICLE
THAT MIGHT BE INTERESTING
TO JULIAN
ABOUT SMALL TECH FIRMS.
- UH, MAMA, I NEED TO
ASK YOU SOMETHING.
- OF COURSE, HONEY.
WHAT IS IT?
- [sighs]
WERE YOU AND DADDY...HAPPY?
I MEAN, ALL THE TIME?
- WELL, NO. NOT ALL THE TIME.
WELL, WE HAD MANY
WONDERFUL MOMENTS.
WHY?
- WELL, I THINK THAT JULIAN...
- OH! I DON'T BELIEVE THAT.
JULIAN LOVES YOU,
AND HE'S AN HONEST MAN.
DON'T YOU THINK HE'D SAYSOMETHING IF THAT WERE THE CASE?
- [laughs]I HAVE TO PICK UP LITTLE JULIAN.
SOCCER.
- VALETTA?
THERE ARE NO EASY ANSWERS.
YOU WORK THIS OUT.
IT'S WORTH IT. TRUST ME.
[horses snorting]
- I'M SO EXHAUSTED
I'M CROSS-EYED.
- WELL, NOW YOU'RE A
DUES-PAYING MEMBER
OF THE MOM'S CLUB.
IT'S JUST THE WAY IT IS.
- WHAT IF I DON'T WANT TO BE
PART OF THAT CLUB?
- NOW, WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
YOU'RE IN IT FOR THE LONG HAUL.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY CHOICE.
- I JUST FEEL LIKE I STILL HAVE
THINGS I WANT TO DO.
- YEAH, WELL, WE ALL DO.
- I JUST THINK MAYBE
I MADE A MISTAKE
BRINGING A KID
INTO MY WORLD.
- HOW HARD IS IT?
- IT'S HARD.
[laughs]
- WELL, CAN YOU GET BY?
- YEAH, BARELY.
- DOES NICHOLAS HELP YOU OUT
AT ALL?
- IF I LET HIM.
I'M JUST HAPPY THAT
HE LOVES BEING WITH HIS SON.
- IF YOU GET A GUY
WITH EMOTIONAL STRENGTH,
YOU GOT HANG ONTO HIM.
I MEAN, YOU CAN'T
PUSH THIS ONE AWAY, BRITT.
IT'S SO GOOD
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
IT'S GOOD TO HAVE YOU
HERE AT HOME.
[phone rings]
- HELLO?
- HOW ARE YOU?
- UNDER SIEGE.
- YEAH, I BET.
[sighs]
HOW'S MY BOY?
- HE'S STINKY
I'VE BEEN TOLD.
I'LL LET HIM TELL YOU HIMSELF.
HEY, IT'S DADDY.
- HI, HENRY, IT'S DADDY.
- HE HAS NOTHING TO SAY
THIS MORNING.
- I MISS HIM SO MUCH.
AND YOU.
OK, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
SAY ANYTHING.
JUST...
JUST KNOW THAT I'M THINKING
ABOUT YOU A LOT.
WILL YOU CALL ME
IF YOU WANT TO TALK?
- YEAH, I WILL.
- OK, BYE.
- [cooing]
- HI.
HI.
GOOD MORNING.
- GOOD MORNING.
HOW'S HENRY?
- TOOK HIS WHOLE BOTTLE
LIKE A TROOPER.
- I WAS ONCE ENGAGED
TO A LOUT
WHO REQUIRED SEVERAL BOTTLES
A DAY.
[laughs]
- HEY, THAT LOOKS NICE.
- THANKS. IT'S A START.
- [sighs] DID YOU EVER
WANT YOUR OWN FAMILY?
- I HAD A FEW OFFERS
IN MY DAY.
BUT THE TIMING
WAS ALWAYS OFF.
THEN YOUR FATHER DIED,
AND MY LIFE CHANGED.
- I REMEMBER YOU SPENT
THE NIGHT IN MY ROOM
THE NIGHT HE DIED.
- YEAH, THIS PLACEKIND OF FELL APART AFTER THAT.
MAGS TOOK TO HER ROOM,
AND, YOU KNOW, IN THOSE DAYS
WE WEREN'T PARTICULARLY
FOND OF ONE ANOTHER.
I WAS KIND OF THE BLACK SHEEP,SHOWBIZ AND ALL, YOU KNOW.
- DO YOU MISS IT?
- LISTEN TO ME, KIDDO,
MY CAREER WAS JUST
ONE PEG SHORT OF HEARTBREAK.
YEAH, I DID OK FOR
A LITTLE WHILE.
THEN THAT WAS OVER.
AND I GOT INTO TROUBLE,
REAL TROUBLE.
AND ONE VERY, VERY BLEAK
THANKSGIVING
YOUR FATHER CAME ALONG
AND BAILED ME OUT.
THEN I LEARNED HOW TO COOKAND HOW TO BABY-SIT YOU GIRLS
AND GOT A FAMILY IN THE BARGAIN.
I'VE ALWAYS LOVEDTHIS HOLIDAY FOR THAT REASON.
- YEAH, BUT DIDN'T YOU EVER
GET SICK
OF TAKING CARE OF
ALL OF US?
- YEAH, ALL THE TIME.
- IS THE PLAYHOUSE STILL OPEN?
- YEAH. WELL, THE KEY'S
RIGHT THERE.
YEAH, IT'S BEEN AGESSINCE ANYBODY'S BEEN IN THERE.
WHY DON'T YOU GO ON.
I'LL WATCH HENRY.
- [baby cooing]
[plate clinks]
♪
[door squeaks]
[sliding on floor]
- BRITT?
BRITT! ARE YOU READY
TO GO SHOPPING?
- COME HERE.
- OH, HEAVENS.
BOY, THIS PLACE IS
FALLING APART.
- LOOK AT THIS.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU PAINTED THISOF DADDY?
- [laughs]
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
I NEVER WAS ANY GOOD.
- YES, YOU WERE.
- [laughs]
OH, PLEASE.
I SHOULD HAVE JUST ADMITTED
IT WAS A HOBBY.
- YOU CAN SEE HE WAS
DRINKING TOO MUCH.
- WHAT A THING TO SAY.
- COME ON, EVERYBODY KNEW
HE HAD A PROBLEM.
WE JUST NEVER TALKED ABOUT IT.
- OH, BRITT.
WHY ON EARTH AREN'T YOU DRESSED?
- IT WILL JUST TAKE A MINUTE.
- WELL, PUT ON SOMETHING NICE.- OK.
- AND TRY NOT TO LOOK LIKE
A GANGSTER.
[sighs]
[cars honking]
THAT MAKES ME SO DARN MAD.
- YOU'RE HOLDING UP TRAFFIC.
- THEY'RE JUST SO IMPATIENT.
[stomping]
[brakes squeal]
[cars honking]
- I COULD JUST SPIT.
- LET ME DRIVE, OK?
- YOU'RE ALL IN SO MUCH
OF A RUSH.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
LEAVE IT TO ME.
[car honking]
WHERE THE DEVIL
IS THIS PLACE?
IT WAS ALWAYS RIGHT HERE
ON THIRD.
- WE'RE NOT EVEN ON THIRD.
THIRD'S BACK THERE.
IT'S WAY BACK THERE.
- I'VE BEEN THERE 100 TIMES.
YOU DON'T THINK I KNOW
MY OWN TOWN?
- WE CAN DO THIS ANOTHER DAY.
- NO, WE'RE GOING TO DO IT
TODAY, BRITT.
[car honking]
[brakes squealing]
[car zooms past]
LOOK AROUND. YOU MIGHT FIND
SOMETHING YOU LIKE.
- YEAH, I BROUGHT SOMETHING
WITH ME.
- TAKE A LOOK BECAUSE
YOU MIGHT FIND SOMETHING
YOU CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT.
[laughs]
AND YOU NEED SOMETHING
FOR THANKSGIVING.
- IT'S THANKSGIVING,
NOT NEW YEARS.
- MAY I SHOW YOU SOMETHING?
- NO, THANKS.
- YOU'RE THE WRITER.
NO, ARTIST. YOUR MOTHERTALKS ABOUT YOU ALL THE TIME.
- REALLY?
- OH, YES.
THIS JUST CAME IN.
IT'S EXQUISITE.
- NO, THANK YOU.
- OH, THAT'S DARLING.
WHY DON'T YOU GET THAT?
- UH, IT'S NOT REALLY ME,
THANKS.
- OH, BUT IT'S PERFECTLY
LOVELY. MY TREAT.
- NO.
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
YOU NEED SOME COLOR.
[sighs]WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THIS ONE?
- GOOD, BUY IT.
- OH. [laughs]
IT'S VERY EXPENSIVE.
- WELL, YOU SAID IT WAS
A SPECIAL OCCASION.
- ALL RIGHT, YES.
I'LL TAKE IT.
- WILL THERE BE ANYTHING ELSE,MRS. CALHOUN?
- BRITT, DON'T YOU WANT
THAT DRESS?
- IT'S REALLY NOT ME.
- YOU'LL WISH YOU HAD.
WRAP THIS UP, MARTHA,
AND THE OTHER ONE AS WELL.
- MAGGIE, I DON'T WANT IT.
- WHEN YOU GET HOME,
YOU'LL CHANGE YOUR MIND.
[laughs]
YOU AND YOUR SISTER VALETTA
ARE NOTHING ALIKE.
VALETTA WOULD HAVE HAD THISOUT OF HERE IN A SPLIT SECOND.
AND, OF COURSE, HER CLOSETS
ARE ALREADY OVERFLOWING
WITH EVERYTHING
UNDER THE SUN.
POOR JULIAN.
HE MUST HAVE TO WORK OVERTIME
TO PAY FOR THE--
THE, UH...
BUT, YOU KNOW, THE...
[breathing heavily]
WHAT IS THE WORD?
- DRY CLEANING BILL?
- YES, THAT'S IT.
- HERE YOU GO, MRS. CALHOUN.
IS THAT GOING TO BE
CASH OR CHARGE?
- IT WILL BE CHARGE, DEAR.
- MAGGIE, ARE YOU FEELING
ALL RIGHT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I WAS JUST TRYING TO DO
SOMETHING NICE FOR YOU.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I'M TALKINGABOUT.
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG.
- OH, HERE IT COMES.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
TAKE THIS BACK?
- I AM NOT TALKING ABOUT
THE DRESS, AND YOU KNOW IT.
- WELL, THEN I'M GOING TO
TAKE IT BACK.
- NO, MAGGIE. STOP IT!
STOP!
[ripping]
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
[seat belt clicks]
[sighs]
KEYS?
- I DON'T MIND DRIVING.
- I'M DRIVING. KEYS.
[engine starts]
- YOU USED TO BE
SUCH A HAPPY LITTLE GIRL.
- I'M NOT A LITTLE GIRL
ANYMORE.
- AND YOU'RE NOT HAPPY EITHER.
- I'M FINE.
- YOU AND YOUR SISTER
ARE SO DIFFERENT.
- BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
WE CAME FROM THE SAME PLACE.
- I JUST KNEW YOU WERE GOING
TO GET INTO TROUBLE
ONE OF THESE DAYS.
YOU WERE ALWAYS OUT
ALL NIGHT LONG.
- [scoffs] I WAS A TEENAGER
HAVING FUN.
- I REMEMBER ONE CHARACTERWITH LONG HAIR DOWN HIS BACK,
AND HE'D COME AROUND
ON A MOTORCYCLE.
- [laughs] OH, YEAH,
WELL HE'S A STOCKBROKER NOW.
ARE YOU HAPPY?
I'M SORRY I'M SUCH
A DISAPPOINTMENT TO YOU.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
NOTHING'S EVER GOOD ENOUGH
FOR YOU.
- CAN'T WE HAVE AN AGREEABLE
THANKSGIVING FOR ONCE
AND NOT DREDGE UP
A LOT OF UNPLEASANT THINGS?
- WHY NOT?
WE'VE BEEN DOING IT
FOR YEARS.
[door unlocks]
- I MADE A LIST OF THINGS
WE NEED FOR THANKSGIVING.
YOU AND VALETTA CAN GO
TO THE STORE FOR ME.
- FINE.
- [sighs]
I'M DONE IN.
- YOU WANT SOME TEA?
- OH, THANK YOU, BILLY.
THAT WOULD BE NICE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE
WHAT WE NEED HERE.
[tea trickling]
- HOW WAS HENRY?
- OH, HE'S AN ANGEL.
HE'S SLEEPING.
- OK, IF THEY HAVE
ANY FRESH CRANBERRIES,
GET THOSE FOR ME.
- OK. SEE YOU LATER.
- SOMETIMES BRITT
AND I ARE JUST--
- SHE'S FROM A DIFFERENT PLANET
THAN YOU AND VALETTA.
- DO I HOLD HER TO
SOME UNREASONABLE STANDARD?
- WELL, YOU SURE HAVE BEEN
TOUGH ON HER.
AND WITH THAT OTHER THING
HANGING OVER YOU,
YOU NEED TO WORK THINGS OUTWITH HER BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
HOW MUCH LONGER ARE YOU
GOING TO IGNORE THE TRUTH
AND ADMIT THAT WE HAVE
A PROBLEM.
- WE?
WE DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM.
I DO.
- LISTEN, MAGS,
WE'VE MADE OUR PEACE,
YOU AND I, RIGHT?
AND IF TWO OLD BAGS LIKE US
CAN GET ALONG,
YOU CAN FIND A WAYTO GET ALONG WITH YOUR DAUGHTER.
SHE'S A GREAT KID.
SHE'S A GOOD MOTHER.
- I ALWAYS THOUGHT YOU WERE
OFF-CENTER.
I SUPPOSE THAT'S WHY YOU TWOHIT IT OFF FROM THE BEGINNING.
- I'M OFF-CENTER?
WELL, ISN'T THAT WONDERFUL?
- [laughs]
- YAMS. WE NEED YAMS.
- THERE. RIGHT THERE.
I'LL GET IT.
- I CAN'T READ HER HANDWRITING.
OH, CRANBERRIES.
THERE WE ARE.
OH, THEY DON'T LOOK
VERY GOOD, DO THEY?
- I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT MAGGIE.
SHE HAD A LITTLE EPISODE
AT THE DRESS SHOP THIS MORNING.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- SHE WAS TALKING,
AND THEN SHE JUST WENT BLANK
AND FORGOT WHAT SHE WAS SAYING.
THIS IS BORDERLINE ALZHEIMER'S.
DON'T YOU THINK WE SHOULD
TALK TO A DOCTOR ABOUT THIS?
- YOU KNOW HER.
SHE HATES DOCTORS.
LOOK, WE ALREADY
TALKED ABOUT THIS.
SHE'S OLD.
OLD PEOPLE HAVE LAPSES
IN MEMORY.
[laughs] HECK, I FORGET THINGSALL THE TIME.
- YEAH, BUT YOU DON'T FORGET
THAT YOU HAD DESSERT
30 SECONDS AFTER
THE PLATE'S CLEARED.
- [sighs]
[rings]
EXCUSE ME.
WE NEED A BIG TURKEY.
EVERYTHING HERE
LOOKS KIND OF PUNY.
CAN YOU DO BETTER?
- I'LL SEE WHAT I HAVE IN BACK.
- IF YOU WANT TO TAKE MAGGIE TO
THE DOCTOR, BE MY GUEST.
- THERE IS SOMETHING WRONG.
- SHE'S STRONG.
WE'RE KEEPING AN EYE ON HER.
NOTHING'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
- HOW'S THIS ONE?
- FREE RANGE?
- YES, MA'AM.
- I GUESS IT WILL
HAVE TO DO.
[carts rattling]
- THANK YOU.
- WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
- HE'S CARRYING OUR GROCERIES.
- [laughs]
YOU THOUGHT HE WAS CUTE.
- HEY. IF YOU'D EVER WORKED
FOR MINIMUM WAGE,
YOU WOULD UNDERSTAND.
- WELL, THANK GOD I DIDN'T.
- DO YOU EVER GET
SICK OF THIS PLACE?
NOTHING EVER CHANGES.
- I THINK IT'S PEACEFUL.
NOBODY'S SLEEPING
IN DOORWAYS.
YOU HUNGRY?
- YEAH.
- GOOD, WE'LL STOP AT THE CLUBON THE WAY HOME.
- I'VE GOT A BETTER IDEA.
LET'S GET THESE HOME FIRST.
[country music playing]
[patrons chatting]
[lighter flicks]
- IT'S A DUMP.
- THINK OF IT AS CHARACTER.
- I HOPE WE DON'T PICK UP
SOME AIRBORNE DISEASE.
- HEY, I HAD SOME GREAT TIMESIN HERE, AND I'M ALIVE.
- I THINK I'D HAVE MY DOCTORDO A FULL WORK-UP IF I WERE YOU.
- [laughs lightly]
SEE THAT BOOTH OVER THERE?
I USED TO MAKE OUT
WITH JOHN HARDING IN THERE.
MY LIPS WERE RAW
BY THE TIME I GOT HOME.
- NOW THERE'S AN APPEALING
MEMORY.
- [laughs]
EXCUSE ME, COULD WE HAVE
TWO CHEESEBURGERS,
EVERYTHING ON 'EM,AND A COUPLE SHOTS OF TEQUILA.
- NO ONIONS FOR ME.
- EVERYTHING, PLEASE.
- YOU'VE CLEARLY LED
A MORE BOHEMIAN LIFESTYLE.
- WELL, IT WASN'T
THE COUNTRY CLUB.
- MY LIFESTYLE MAY NOT
APPEAL TO YOU,
BUT SOMEBODY HAD TO BE AT HOMETAKING CARE OF MAMA.
- [sighs] SO TELL MEWHAT'S GOING ON WITH HER NOW.
- EXCUSE ME.
TWO MORE, PLEASE.
I CAN HANDLE IT.
- ALL RIGHT.
- I'M GOING TO BE HONEST.
SOMETIMES I GET TIRED OFBEING THE ONE TO LOOK AFTER HER.
WHY SHOULD I DO IT ALL?
- BECAUSE I DON'T LIVE HERE.
[dog barking in distance]
[cooing]
[gurgles]
[birds tweeting]
- BRITT? BRITT.
YOU HAVE A LONG DISTANCE
PHONE CALL.
[phone beeps]
- HELLO?
- HOW ARE THINGS BACK HOME?
- WEIRD. HOW ARE YOU?
- WE HEARD FROM THE FOUNDATION.
- AND?
- YOU'VE GOT THE GRANT.
- [screams and laughs]
- ARE YOU OK?
- I GOT THE GRANT.
I GOT IT! I GOT IT!
- ARE YOU THERE? BRITT?
- OH!
HELLO? HELLO?
- LOOK, HAVE
A HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
YOU DESERVE IT.
WE'LL GO OVER THE DETAILS
WHEN YOU GET BACK.
- OK. THANKS!
[clicks off phone]
- OH...
- I GOT THE GRANT.
- THAT'S MY GIRL.
- [laughs]
- OH! OH, DON'T TELL ANYBODY.I WANT IT TO BE A BIG SURPRISE.
I'LL SAVE IT FOR DINNER.
- OK. BUT I'M NOT SURPRISED.
- OH...
[lawnmower motor]
[buzzing]
- IT DOESN'T NEED
TO GO THAT WAY.
IT JUST NEEDS TO GO THIS WAY.
- YOU KNOW, MY CAR AUTOMATICALLY
HEADS STRAIGHT FOR
YOUR MOTHER'S HOUSE THESE DAYS.
YOU'RE ALWAYS HERE.
- YOU LOOK SMUG.
- YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW.
- HOW DID IT GO?
[kissing sounds]
JULIAN! COME ON, TELL ME.
- OK, OK. I DID IT.
I SOLD MY IDEA TO OMNIDEC.
- THAT'S FANTASTIC!
- IT GETS BETTER.
THEY WANT TO BUY ME OUT.
- WHAT?
- AND THEY WANT ME TO STAY ONAND RUN THE NEW COMPANY.
- ARE YOU GOING TO DO IT?
- IT WOULD BE HARD TO PASS UP.WE'D BE SET FOR LIFE.
- BUT IS THIS GOING TO MEAN
MORE TIME ON THE ROAD?
- FOR A WHILE.
- [sighs]
ALL THIS TIME ON THE ROAD,
IT'S HARD ON US.
- VALETTA, THIS IS A GOOD THING.
MY WORK, IT'S FOR BOTH OF US.
- I MISS YOU.
- [sighs]
[sighs]
[laughs]
- WHO'S IN THERE?
- IT'S JUST ME.
- WHAT THE DEVIL ARE YOU
DOING IN HERE?
YOU'LL GET FILTHY
AS ALL GET OUT.
- I WAS JUST LOOKING FOR
SOME OF OUR OLD TOYS.
I THOUGHT HENRY
COULD USE THEM.
- WHAT WERE YOU LAUGHING ABOUT?
- THIS.
- OH!
[laughs]
- YOU SHOULD HAVE BURNED THAT.
- WE SHOULD KEEP IT
FOR YOUR SON.
- DON'T YOU DARE SHOW THAT
TO ANYBODY.
- [laughs]
- GIVE ME THAT.
- YOU KNOW, YOUR FATHER
TOOK THAT ON VACATION.
WE WERE IN SAN DIEGO.
- IT SEEMS LIKE HE DIED
A LONG TIME AGO.
- NOT FOR ME.
- EVEN WHEN I LOOK AT
HIS PICTURE, IT'S...
IT'S HARD FOR ME
TO REMEMBER HIM.
- HE WAS SO THRILLED
WHEN YOU CAME ALONG.
WE DIDN'T EXPECT
TO HAVE ANOTHER CHILD.
HE THOUGHT YOU WERE
A TREASURE.
OH, LET ME SEE THAT SILLY THING.
- YEAH, YOU PAID MONEY
FOR THIS?
- I BEG YOUR PARDON.
I WAS THE RAGE OF
THE THANKSGIVING BALL
AT THE CLUB.
- UH-HUH.
- OH.
IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
- VALETTA, WHAT ARE YOU DOINGOUT HERE?
- UM, I'M JUST...
WAITING FOR THE LANDSCAPERS.
THEY'RE-- THEY'RE NOT FINISHED.
- I TALKED TO MERLE
AND CONNIE.
THEY SAID THEY'RE GOING
TO BE HERE FOR THANKSGIVING.
- THAT'S GOOD.
[chair leg scrapes]
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'M JUST NOT SURE
HOW IT'S GOING TO TURN OUT.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TELL
BRITT ABOUT MAMA, YOU KNOW.
- THE RIGHT TIME
WILL PRESENT ITSELF.
- IT'S GOING TO BE HARD.
I'M NOT SURE IF
I'M READY FOR IT.
- YOU JUST KEEP ONLOVING YOUR MOTHER SWEETHEART.
THAT'S ALL YOU NEED TO
CONCENTRATE ON.
- I'LL HANDLE IT.
[crickets chirping]
- [sighs]
MMM. I'VE REALLY MISSED
YOUR CHICKEN, BILLY.
- OOH, WAIT 'TIL YOU SEE
WHAT'S FOR DESSERT.
- I HAD SOME GOOD NEWS TODAY.
I FOUND OUT THAT, UM,
I'M THE RECIPIENT OF
THE ARTIST ACADEMY
FOUNDATION GRANT.
- HMM.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- THAT'S GREAT.
- IT'S AN IMPORTANT GROUP
OF PEOPLE
WHO RECOGNIZE ARTISTS
THEY BELIEVE
SHOW EXCEPTIONAL PROMISE.
YOU KNOW, BIG WIGS!
- WELL, I'M SURE EVERYONE HERE'SVERY PLEASED FOR YOU, BRITT.
HOW DOES IT WORK EXACTLY?
DO THEY GIVE YOU MONEY?
- THERE'S MONEY INVOLVED, YEAH.
- CAN YOU LIVE ON IT?
- FOR A WHILE.
- REALLY?
ENOUGH FOR RENT AND FOOD
AND EVERYTHING?
- WELL, I DON'T NEED THAT MUCH.
THERE'S ENOUGH FOR HENRY.
- WELL, HOPEFULLY YOU'LL SELL
SOME OF YOUR OTHER PIECES
AS WELL.
- WELL, AS LONG AS WE'RE
PASSING OUT GOOD NEWS,
I HAVE SOME.
I SOLD MY COMPANY TODAY.
- OH, JULIAN.
CONGRATULATIONS.
- I ALWAYS KNEW ALL THATFLYING AROUND LIKE A BOOMERANG
WOULD SOONER OR LATER
PAY OFF IN A BIG WAY.
- [laughs]
- HE CERTAINLY HAS
PAID HIS DUES.
- OH, I WISH YOUR FATHER
WAS HERE, GIRLS.
HE'D BE TICKLED TO DEATH
FOR YOU, JULIAN.
HERE'S TO MY SUCCESSFUL
CHILDREN.
- HERE, HERE.
[pats leg]
- [laughs]
- YOU STILL UP?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO
TO GET HER ATTENTION?
BECAUSE SOMETIMES
I HATE HER.
- OH, PLEASE DON'T SAY THAT.
YOU KNOW, WE ALL HAVE
OUR FAULTS, INCLUDING YOU.
TOMORROW'S RUNNING OUT.
YOU NEED TO MAKE YOUR PEACE
WHILE THERE'S STILL TIME.
- HOW? HMM?
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DO THAT.
- JUST OFFER HER
WHAT YOU'RE BEST AT.
- [sniffs]
[baby whines]
- WY DON'T YOU LET ME
PUT HENRY TO BED.
YOU WORK A WHILE.
YOU'LL PROBABLY FEEL BETTER.
COME ON, HENRY.
- GOODNIGHT, BABY.
- OH.
[rain and thunder]
[thuds]
[thunder rolls]
[laughs lightly]
- MAGGIE! MAGGIE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I CAN'T FIND MY HAIR BRUSH.
- MAGGIE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN MY YARD?
LEAVE ME ALONE.
LEAVE ME ALONE!
- IT'S ME. IT'S ME!
IT'S BRITT. IT'S ME, MAMA.
- [sobbing]
- MAMA.
- [crying]
- COME HERE.
STEP UP, STEP UP.
THERE YOU GO.
GOOD. COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
- [sobbing]
ARE WE GOING TO FIND CHARLIE?
- NO. DADDY'S NOT OUT THERE.
OK.
[thunder rolls]
[distant thunder]
- HOW'D I GET OUT HERE?
[sighs]
- SO ARE WE GOING TO
TALK ABOUT THIS?
- [sighs]
THE DOCTOR SAYS THAT
I HAVE...
YOU KNOW, I'M LOSING IT.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- ALZHEIMER'S.
- DID YOU GET
A SECOND OPINION?
- OH, YES.
- YOU COULD COME BACK WITH ME.WE COULD GO SEE A SPECIALIST.
- NO MORE DOCTORS.
I DO THE BEST I CAN
WITH A BAD SITUATION.
AND I'M NOT GOING TO LET THISRUIN THANKSGIVING.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
- YOU KEPT ME OUT OF YOUR LIFE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
HURT ME MOST OF ALL?
YOU DIDN'T TELL
YOUR OWN MOTHER
THAT YOU WERE HAVING A BABY.
- I WANTED TO PUNISH YOU.
- [laughs]WELL, YOU CERTAINLY SUCCEEDED.
WELL, I KNOW I MADE MILLIONS OF
MISTAKES WITH YOU GIRLS.
MY DEAR SISTER FEELS
SHORTCHANGED
EVER SINCE YOU CAME ALONG.
I GAVE YOU EVERYTHING
YOU WANTED, EVERYTHING.
AND WHAT DID YOU DO?
YOU LEFT.
- I COULDN'T BREATHE.
- OH, COME ON.
- THE ONLY THING
I EVER WANTED FROM YOU
WAS YOUR APPROVAL.
FOR YOU JUST ONE TIME
TO SAY YOU WERE PROUD OF ME.
- YOU'LL MAKE MISTAKES TOO,
MY DEAR.
MARK MY WORDS.
OH, YOU'LL COME UP WITH
SOME NEW BEAUTIES
WITH THAT SON OF YOURS.
- KNOW WHAT? YOU'RE WRONG.
I'M NOT GOING TO DO THIS
WITH MY SON.
[thunder rolls]
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF YOU LOVE ME.
- [gasps]
HOW COULD YOU SAY THAT?
- MY WHOLE LIFE...
I FELT LIKE
I NEVER REALLY HAD A MOTHER.
AND NOW I'M LOSING YOU.
SO I REALLY DO NOT
WANT TO FIGHT.
- IN A YEAR OR SO,
I WON'T RECOGNIZE HENRY,
AND HE WON'T KNOW ME.
I JUST THOUGHT THAT
DISTANCE WAS THE BEST SOLUTION.
I'M SCARED.
I'M SO SCARED.
[sobs]
- [sniffs]
THE BEAUTY OF CHILDREN
IS THAT THEY LOVE YOU
ANYWAY.
YOU'RE HIS GRANDMOTHER.
YOU WILL ALWAYS BE
HIS GRANDMOTHER.
- WELL, THEN LET'S MAKE
THIS THANKSGIVING
A CELEBRATION,
A GLORIOUS CELEBRATION.
- OK.
- WE WILL, MAMA.
WE WILL.
- I DO LOVE YOU
WITH ALL MY HEART.
- I LOVE YOU TOO.
[birds tweeting]
- OH, HONEY!
PLEASE BE CAREFUL!
THAT HEIRLOOM
IS IRREPLACEABLE.
MAMA WOULD JUST CROAK
IS ANYTHING HAPPENED TO IT.
- CAN'T WE FINISH SETTING
THE TABLE IN THE MORNING?
- [laughs]
ON THANKSGIVING,
I THINK WE'RE GOING TO BE
A LITTLE BIT BUSY COOKING.
LOOK, I JUST WANT TO GET
EVERYTHING LAID OUT
BEFORE THE FLORIST GETS HERE.
- THE FLORIST?
- YOU DO THINGS YOUR WAY,
I'LL DO THEM MINE.
- [sighs]
WELL, YOU DO MAKE THE MOST
OF EVERY EVENT.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
- WELL, THIS IS
THE FIRST HOLIDAY
WE'VE ALL BEEN TOGETHER
FOR YEARS.
I WANT TO MAKE IT NICE
FOR MAMA.
FRANCOIS?
- [speaking French]
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING THERE?
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE HERE--
NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU GET HERE RIGHT NOW.
DO WE UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER?
[clicks off phone]
- HAVE SOME LEMONADE.
- YOU'RE A LIFESAVER.
- YOU'RE ALMOST DONE, YOU KNOW.
- THERE'S A MILLION
THINGS TO DO.
I'LL NEVER BE DONE ON TIME.
- KIDDO, COME HERE.
YOU'VE BEEN SAYING THAT
SINCE THE DAY YOU WERE BORN.
NOW, DON'T FROWN SO MUCH.
YOU'RE GOING TO WRINKLE UP
THAT PRETTY FOREHEAD.
- [sighs]
- SWEETIE?
- YEAH.
- HAVE I TOLD YOU
I LOVED YOU TODAY?
- OH, NO, NOT YET.
- WELL, I DO.
WRINKLED FOREHEAD AND ALL.
- [laughs]
[kissing sounds]
[sighs]
[crickets chirping]
- BRITT?
[knocking]
HI, WE'RE GOING FOR BARBECUE.WANT TO COME?
- CAN YOU FIX A TORN DRESS
FOR ME?
- SAY NO MORE.
I'LL DO IT WHEN I COME BACK.
OK?
- AUNT BILLY?
I KNOW.
MAGGIE TOLD ME.
- OH. WE'LL GET THROUGH THIS.
- I WANT TO HELP.
- YOU ARE HELPING ALREADY.
YOU CAME HOME.
[baby crying]
[crying]
- HERE WE GO. YES.
SWEETHEART.
[cooing]
- HEY. WHAT ARE YOU
DOING UP?
- I WAS AWAKE, AND I FOUND
A PARTNER IN CRIME.
[laughs]
WHAT ARE YOU PAINTING?
- CAN'T SEE IT YET.
IT'S NOT FINISHED.
- OH.
[laughs]
- [baby cooing]
- OH, HENRY'S SUCH A GOOD BOY.
OH. HERE, SWEETHEART. HERE.
- COME HERE.DID YOU WAKE YOUR GRANDMA UP?
- [laughs]
NO.
- SIT DOWN.
- OK.
- I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU.
- OH.
THANK YOU.
[laughs]
- IT'S A MEMORY BOOK.
SO YOU CAN FIND THE PAST
WHENEVER YOU NEED TO.
- [sighs]
[talking low to baby]
- [stamps foot]
[laughs] OK.
EVERYBODY?
LET'S GET GOING.
LOTS TO DO.
- HAPPY THANKSGIVING
TO YOU, TOO.
- HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
LET'S GET TO WORK.
♪
GOOD, GOOD.
PERFECT, PERFECT.
THANK YOU.
[laughter]
[sighs]
- NO! NO! OOH!
OH NO!
OH!
[laughing]
[struggling and laughing]
OH!
[laughs]
- [cooing]
- IT'S REALLY GOOD.
- [laughs]
- [sniffs]
NO!
- OH!
[laughs]
[laughter]
- BYE-BYE.
[muted TV announcer]
- YES!
- [gasps]
[crack]
- YOU DROPPED SOMETHING.
- THANK YOU.
- GO!
- [screams]
- OH! OH! OH!
- [growls playfully]
[birds tweeting]
- HONEY, CAN YOU, UM,
HELP ME, PLEASE?
- YEAH.
[laughs]
YOU KNOW, SWEETIE,
YOU DID A TERRIFIC JOB.
[kissing sounds]
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- DO YOU STILL LOVE ME?
- WHAT?
- WHEN YOU'RE OUT THERE
ON THE ROAD,
HAVE YOU EVER...
- I LOVE YOU.
THERE'S NEVER BEEN ANYONE
BUT YOU.
- YOU'RE GONE SO MUCH,
AND NOW YOU'RE GOING TO
BE GONE EVEN MORE.
- I'LL NEVER SEE YOU.
- SO I'LL STAY HOME.
- CAN YOU?
- YEAH. I'M THE BOSS.
I CAN DO ANYTHING.
[ice clinking]
- THANK YOU.
[doorbell rings]
OH! THERE THEY ARE.
HELLO!
- VALETTA, HI!
[laughs]
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
[spritzing]
[distant conversation]
- [cooing]
- WOULD YOU LIKE TO
ESCORT YOUR GRANDMOTHER
DOWN TO DINNER?
I FORGET THINGS, YOU KNOW.
SO MAYBE YOU COULD HELP ME OUTIF I FORGET SOMEONE'S NAME.
- THESE ARE FOR YOU.
- LOOK WHAT YOU DID.
[baby screams]
WELL, HERE SHE COMES.
- AW...
- COUSIN MERLE. HI, DARLING.
[kissing sounds]
- OH, MAGGIE.
YOU LOOK SENSATIONAL.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
- WELL, HAPPY THANKSGIVING
TO YOU.
WHERE THE DEVIL HAVE YOU BEEN?
NOW, HAVE YOU MET...
- HEY, HELLO!
- HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
- OH, WELL, HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
- HOW YOU DOING?
- I'M GOOD. I'M TIRED.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I'LL SURVIVE.
- WHERE'S YOUR SISTER?
- SHE'S IN THE BACK.
♪
[laughing and talking]
- OH, MAGS, YOU LOOK GREAT.
- WHAT A LOVELY LIE.
[laughs]
WELL, TONIGHT I'M
IN A RECEPTIVE MOOD.
SO LAY ON THE COMPLIMENTS.
[distant conversations]
- EVERYONE!
[claps]
EVERYONE, DINNER IS SERVED.
all: OH!
- IF YOU WILL MAKE YOUR WAY
INTO THE DINING ROOM,
YOU'LL FIND YOUR NAME
AT YOUR PLACE.
[laughs]
[chattering]
- THAT IS SO BEAUTIFUL.
- SWEETIE, WHERE ARE WE?
all: OH!
- OH BOY.
- IT LOOKS SO WONDERFUL.
- IT LOOKS PERFECT.
- HOLD ON. WAIT!
[sighs]
- [baby coos]
- SORRY.
[whispers]
- VALETTA, WOULD YOU SAY GRACE,
PLEASE?
- OF COURSE.
DEAR GOD,
WE THANK YOU
FOR OUR FAMILY
AND OUR FRIENDS
AND ALL OF OUR MANY BLESSINGS
AND THIS FOOD THAT
YOU SO GRACIOUSLY PROVIDE.
AMEN.
all: AMEN.
- NOW, I WANT YOU ALL TO KNOW
THAT THIS IS MY FIRST
THANKSGIVING TURKEY EVER.
[laughter]
AND I DON'T THINK IT'S
GOING TO POISON YOU,
BUT I CAN'T BE SURE.
SO I'M GOING TO HAVE
THE FIRST BITE.
[laughter]
MMM!
DOES ANYBODY ELSE
WANT SOME TURKEY?
- OH, YES!
- I KNOW I DO.
[chattering]
- [laughing]
[scattered conversations]
[clinking on glass]
- EXCUSE ME, I'D LIKE
TO SAY SOMETHING.
THIS IS A VERY SPECIAL
THANKSGIVING.
IT'S THE TIME OF YEAR WHEN WETURN TOWARDS HOME AND FAMILY
FOR COMFORT AND SOLACE.
AND TO HAVE MY WHOLE FAMILY
TOGETHER
UNDER ONE ROOF
IS MORE THAN ANY MOTHER
COULD ASK.
NOW, IT'S NOT ALWAYS EASY
WHEN WE GET TOGETHER.
WE SOMETIMES CAN'T ACCEPT OURFAULTS AND OUR TRANSGRESSIONS
AND, BELIEVE ME,
THEY ARE MANY.
IT GETS MESSY,
AND WE GET DISCOURAGED.
BUT I DO BELIEVE
THAT WITH FAMILY
WE HAVE THE CAPACITY
TO FORGIVE AND BE FORGIVEN
AS IN NO OTHER PLACE
IN LIFE.
TIME AND MEMORY
ARE SO FLEETING.
WE MUST SAVOR EVERY MOMENT
BECAUSE IT COULD JUST
SLIP AWAY
WITHOUT OUR EVER NOTICING IT.
HERE'S TO MY FAMILY.
- HERE'S TO YOU, MAMA.
all: [sipping]
- [sniffs]
[sighs]
- HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
- [laughs]
- I HOPE THERE'S
SOME LEFTOVERS FOR ME.
[laughter]
- WHAT-- I--
- OH...
- WELL, MEET THE FAMILY.
[laughs]
UH, MY SISTER.
- HI.
- AND JULIAN.
- HI, HOW ARE YOU?
- CLAIRE.
- [laughs]
- GOODNIGHT.
all: GOODNIGHT!
- DID YOU GET ALL THOSE
LEFTOVERS?
- I DID.
THE TURKEY WAS FABULOUS.
- WELL, I'LL CALL YOU NEXT WEEK.- OK, OK...
- GOODNIGHT.
- TAKE CARE NOW.
- THANKS FOR WORKING
SO HARD.
DON'T FORGET WE'RE HAVING LUNCH
AT THE CLUB.
- I WON'T.
I'LL CALL MARY...
- HI.
- HEY.
- LOOKS LIKE YOUR MOTHER
HAD A FUN DAY TODAY.
- YEAH. IT'S A GOOD DAY FOR HER.- HMM.
- YOU KNOW, I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D SAY THIS,
BUT I'M REALLY GLAD
I CAME HOME.
- GOOD.
- AND I'M GLAD YOU
CAME HOME TOO.
[kissing sounds]
HENRY NEEDS HIS FATHER.
- WHAT ABOUT HIS MOTHER?
- YEAH, SHE NEEDS HIM, TOO.
- GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
- OK, BE CAREFUL DRIVING HOME.GOODBYE!
- GOODNIGHT.
all: [laughing]
- OOPS!
- [laughs]
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
- WELL, COME IN, DEAR.
- A PRESENT.
- THANK YOU.
[gasps]
OH!
OH, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- [sighs]
I HAVE TO SAY SOMETHING.
I LOVE YOU.
AND I WANT TO HELP YOU.
BUT YOU NEED TO DO SOMETHING
FOR ME.
YOU NEED TO LET ME
HELP YOU.
- CHILDREN AREN'T SUPPOSEDTO TAKE CARE OF THEIR PARENTS.
I'M AFRAID, BRITT.
I HAVE NO CONTROL OVER IT.
AND ONE OF THESE DAYS
I WON'T EVEN REMEMBER
WHO YOU ARE.
- JUST AS LONG AS YOU KNOW
THAT I LOVE YOU.
- OH...
[sniffling]
NOW, I WANT TO SAY SOMETHING
TO YOU.
I'M SORRY.
I KNOW I HAVEN'T BEEN
THE EASIEST PERSON
TO GET ALONG WITH.
AND I'VE BEEN HARD ON YOU
AT TIMES.
BUT I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
AND YOU'RE A WONDERFUL MOTHER.
- I REALLY WANT TO BE HERE
FOR YOU.
- I KNOW YOU DO, DEAR.
AND I'M GOING TO DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES TO BEAT THIS.
- YOU BETTER
BECAUSE HENRY IS EXPECTING YOUAT HIS GRADUATION.
- I'M SO GLAD YOU CAME BACK.
IT MEANS SO MUCH TO ME.
- THIS IS MY HOME.
- OH...
[crickets chirping]
♪