(jazz music)
(film rolling)
(somber music)
- Look at it from the bright side Desa Rae.
For the past six months,
this has been a long and tedious divorce process.
This settles the deal.
Aside from one real estate deal still pending,
everything else is done.
Just read it and sign by the tabs.
- Thanks for everything.
Let me know when the rest of the paperwork comes.
Maybe Reggie's attorney will get them to us soon.
- It's over, hon.
Listen, that in and of itself should put
a smile on your face.
- [Desa Rae] Thanks.
- At least you're getting alimony and,
and, some of that money
that Reggie's getting from
those properties he was hanging on to.
- That might sound good to you,
but all I ever wanted was a faithful husband.
That was just too much to ask.
Thanks.
(somber music)
- Oh, oh, my God.
Thank you. - You're welcome.
- There you go. - it got it, thanks.
- Give me a second to talk to her, okay?
I'll be there in a minute.
- Okay, baby.
- Mm-mm. - Mm.
- Hello.
We're not talking to each other anymore?
Is that what's going on?
- If it pertains to Latrel, then yes.
And what are you calling me for anyway, Reggie?
You got what you wanted,
that's pretty obvious.
- We both got what we needed.
I'm sorry it had to be this way.
(door squeaks)
(somber music)
(flame blasts)
♪ Everything is two fold
♪ What's joy is pain on the other hand ♪
♪ What happens when the one
♪ You truly love is the main cause of your suffering ♪
♪ I need you like I need air to breathe ♪
(gun fires)
♪ I need you to save me from me ♪
♪ I'm caught in your wave
♪ I'm drifting away
♪ I need you to save me
♪ Please don't let me drown
♪ Main cause of your suffering
♪ When the one that you love
♪ Is the main cause of your suffering ♪
♪ Give me all of your lies
♪ 'Cause you're my demon in disguise ♪
♪ I learn to love you 'cause you keep me ♪
(siren blares)
♪ My life
♪ But your poison looked so ripe ♪
♪ If I want you and you're bad for me ♪
♪ My perfect storm
♪ My beautiful catastrophe
- Did I tell you we supposed
to be linking up later on?
- Oh, nah, you didn't tell me.
- Aw, man, the sooner the better, bro,
'cause, uh, I am not trying
to be doing all this shit getting all dirty.
- Man, I know that's fuckin' right.
- We supposed to be in here protecting that shit, man.
- Damn, I knew I should have went somewhere else.
Ain't no way I'm a be back at work in time.
Look at this, look at this fool, look, look.
(bangs hood)
You.
- Uh-oh.
- That is all you, bro, that is all you.
- Sorry for the wait, love.
We moving as fast as we can.
- Did you just call me love?
Listen, is your supervisor inside?
I need to talk to somebody about this wait.
- Oh, he inside. - Okay.
- But I wanna know is why you lookin' that mean?
You too fine to be all uptight and shit.
Besides, I can get you together.
I'm like the man around here.
My name Bud.
- Oh, you're the man around here.
Okay, thanks, mister, but, oh,
it looks like I'm next.
All right, thank you, Mr. Bud (clears throat).
Geez.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Hi, are you the owner?
- No, I am not,
but what can I help you with?
- No, I'd rather speak to the owner.
- Well, it's gonna be a minute.
But I'll see if he got time to talk.
You wanna have a seat right here?
I'll go get him.
- Mm-mm, I wouldn't put my purse in that chair
nor my ass, thank you.
- Suit yourself, little mama.
I'll be right back.
- Roc!
- Girl, I know.
- How you doing?
Can I help you out?
- Yeah, are you the owner?
- No, but my boy said you was looking for me.
- No, I need to speak to Bud's supervisor
because, look, all I need is a simple oil change
and this wait is ridiculous.
I need to go.
- Petty.
- Petty? Did you just call me petty?
No, I'm gonna tell you what's petty.
This slow service is petty,
our conversation is petty
and this toilet that you seem
to think is a chair is petty.
I know I should've went somewhere else.
Don't worry about it.
- Yes, you being real petty.
But she ain't lying.
Listen, I been standing here
for almost two fuckin' hours
and these niggas still ain't done with my car.
- Craig, do me a favor, man.
Can you go ahead and get her situated?
- Yeah, I got you. - Appreciate it.
- And which one's your car?
- Okay, my car is right there.
Listen, I need to get to work by two,
so you need to really be quick.
- First of all, nothing I do is quick.
I'll make sure you get to work on time.
Matter of fact.
Yeah, I'm a need a car.
Nah, yeah, that's cool.
All right.
My boy's gonna be here in five minutes.
- No, no, no, that's okay,
you don't have to do that.
- I insist, all right.
Just go ahead and sit over there.
Matter of fact, let me get your keys from you.
- Thank you. - I got you.
- All right.
- Oh, I needed these, thank you.
- Yeah, thought you might need those.
- Is this it? - That's it.
- Okay, oh, thank you for everything.
- Absolutely.
(drills whirring)
So what you think, I hooked you up, right?
- Yeah, it looks nice.
Oh, thank you for the car,
it was really nice.
- Aw, yeah, nah, that's the homie, that's cool.
- So how much do I owe you?
- Nah, look, I told you it was gonna be
on the house, right?
Look, there is something I do want from you.
- Oh, what's that?
- Your name.
- (laughs) Desa Rae, why?
- All right, Desa Rae.
So maybe I can get your number,
take you out to dinner?
The movies?
- No, no, I don't think so.
- Hold up.
That's how you gonna treat
a nigga who fixed your shit?
- No, you should never classify
yourself as the N word
and as for me rewarding you for an oil change,
that's not gonna happen.
Besides, how old are you anyway?
- Aw, shit, I'm 29, how old are you?
- My age don't matter, so.
- Hold on, hold on.
I'm trying to figure out
why you ashamed to tell me how old you are.
- Ashamed? - Yeah.
- You old as fuck.
- Give me my ID.
- Let me get out your way.
Damn. - My door.
- I hate to see you go,
but you know you fine as hell, right?
- Listen, but you know what?
- What's that?
- There's something you can do for me.
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah.
- [Roc] What's that?
- I need you to fire Bud.
He's bad for business.
- I hate walking around like a bitter bitch,
but whenever I think about Reggie
and dealing with this divorce
and how he played me,
it just irks my soul.
- You know what?
After 20 years together,
you have every right to be mad.
Okay, he cheated on you.
But it's time for you to move on.
You can't keep on being bitter.
You say it don't bother you,
but clearly it did.
What you can control, though,
is how you handle it.
You gotta go out.
Latrel is in college now.
This is the perfect time for you.
- Girl, please, I am not a partier.
You know I like to stay at home with my peaceful books
and my cuddle bed.
- Boring.
Listen, come out with me tonight
to this birthday party.
And it'll only be for a few hours
and after that I promise you
you can get back to your books and your Tinder
and whatever happened to that guy you were talking to?
- Oh, Marcus, yes.
I still talk to him,
but I don't know.
Something's off with him.
I think he's hiding something.
- You always got an excuse, girl.
Get it together and come out with me tonight.
I promise you you gonna have a good time.
- Okay, fine, just send me the location,
I may surprise you.
- All right, Ms. Bougie.
I'm a send it to you now.
I hope I see you later.
- [Desa Rae] Bye.
(upbeat music)
(phone dings)
♪ I would write your name in the sky ♪
♪ 'Cause you light up my life
♪ And you're bright like the (indistinct) ♪
♪ Looking softly into my eyes
♪ You ignite every fire that's burning inside me ♪
♪ Ooh, is this forever, baby
♪ Can we be forever, babe
♪ We be forever
♪ I would write your name in the sky ♪
♪ But you take me so high
♪ I see that already
- Monica, it was so good seeing you again.
Girl, you are true life saver.
Thank you for that information.
- [Monica] No problem.
- I gotta meet my friend, I'll see you girl.
- All right, boo.
- Hey.
- Oh, my God.
Listen, I almost fell out this seat.
I can't believe you out that house, Des.
- I told you I was coming.
What was that all about?
- Oh, you know, we used to work together
at the law firm and they got
a lawsuit going on against a company
so I'm just giving her some intel.
Oh, you told me about that.
Girl, I need a lawsuit.
You need to hook me up.
- [Monica] Okay, well.
- But, as for getting me out this bed
in this dry club,
I'm so mad you got me
to come out outta here.
- Well, listen, there's no Prince Charmings in here,
but, you know, you might find you
a little one night stand or something.
- Well, I could use some D right now.
- [Monica] Yes, you can.
- 'Cause especially since things
didn't work out with Marcus.
You know he called me a bitch?
- [Monica] That bitch called you a bitch.
- That bitch, I know, he is a bitch.
But, anyway, I need a drink fast.
- [Monica] Well, all right, I'll get you
a Long Island iced tea and some of these ones
and zeros could look like a 10, you know what I'm saying?
- Yes.
- [Monica] You all right?
- Hey.
Oh, hey, yeah.
- [Monica] Get a drink, okay.
- All right, we'll see you in the back, man.
- Hell, yeah. - Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- [Monica] You all right?
- Yeah, I'm good, I'm good.
Hey, talk to me.
Just pretend like you're talking to me.
- I am talking to you.
- [Desa Rae] I know, but continue talking to me.
- Why you acting so crazy?
What's going on with you, girl?
- Yeah, I didn't think I would see you
in a spot like this.
- I'm sorry, do I know you.
- Oh, here we go.
- Okay.
- I'm Roc.
- How you doing, I'm Monica.
- I'm good.
Look like your friend Des caught
a little amnesia, huh?
Matter of fact, bartender.
- [Bartender] What can I get you, brother?
- Yeah, let me get them two
of whatever they're having tonight.
- Okay, anything you need.
- Just make sure they hooked up.
Matter of fact, I'll take the usual.
Just make sure they hooked up all night, all right.
- [Desa Rae] All right.
Okay, all night.
- I like this already.
- Yeah, let me know if y'all need anything.
- Okay, thank you.
All night.
(Monica laughs)
So, you acting like you having
a dry spell and you been
in the house with that tall, dark-
- I have not.
- Man, hiding him from the world.
- No, let's just enjoy the drinks
like the man said.
- Okay.
Somebody getting some dick tonight.
- Not so fast.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna bust Johnny's ass,
what you talkin' about.
- Bust, nigga, that's kinda gay.
You spot niggas at a table
and you talking about bustin' ass.
That's like, ain't no girls,
he talkin' about bustin' ass.
Ain't at the table, there's five niggas,
he's talkin' about bustin' ass.
- What's happenin'? - What's good, my nigga.
- Hey, bro.
- [Man 2] Hey, get your man.
He on some shit.
- [Man 3] Nigga need some pussy in his life, dawg.
- Where y'all at, where y'all at, what's up?
- I'm about dime up,
take your shit, too, nigga.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Let's see what I got for that, okay.
- Hey, yo, what time is my shipment arriving through?
- Uh, should be around 12.
Look, this time, I'm a be at the spot
to make sure all the shit go smooth, aight?
'Cause that L we took last time,
that shit could never happen again.
But y'all can blame this nigga, Butch,
for trustin' too many fake ass niggas,
come on, man.
- Yeah, nigga, and I keep telling you
to keep my name out your fuckin' mouth
'cause I don't trust no damn body.
I keep tellin' your stupid ass,
you gotta take risks in order
to get shit done.
You wouldn't have made it that far
without doing that.
So how about you stay the fuck off my back, nigga.
- Who this nigga talkin' too, dawg?
This nigga brain must be too tight.
He talkin' to you.
He was lookin' at you, bruh,
he gotta be talkin' to you.
He ain't talkin' to me.
I'm just sayin', I'm straight, bro.
Hey, get your mans, bro, get your mans, come on.
- Ain't nobody on your back.
That was some messy shit you got us in.
You need to own up to it.
- Facts.
- Lettin' them nigga slide in.
Coulda got us fucked up.
They played you like a puppet.
- Nigga, every time we together
y'all niggas keep bringin' up shit from the past.
Hey, I owned up to my mistakes
and I handled the motherfuckers.
Look, we ain't lose no money
and the bag still dropped.
Y'all keep bringin' this shit up,
I promise you, I'm a start knockin' niggas
the fuck out.
- Man, sit your ass down, dawg.
I'm promise you I'm a start knockin niggas the fuck up.
This nigga been in the gym
for three days think he gonna fight somebody.
- All I know,
you niggas ain't beatin' that shit there, though.
- Damn, man.
- Come on, man.
- Fuckin' around with y'all niggas, man.
I'll celebrate my good fortune while it last, baby.
- [Man 2] This nigga, this nigga cheatin',
come on, man.
- [Butch] What's up, man?
Cut another one, man.
I know y'all niggas got some more money
in that bitch, man.
- [Man 3] Yeah, roll up a dice game, man, come on, y'all.
- Last time I checked, there's still
a party going on, right. - Straight up, man, let's go.
- Man, aight, bottle's on this nigga, dawg.
- Let me buy one on this nigga.
Look, I'm a get some more girls,
some more bottles, we lit.
Get some bottles, nigga, come on.
- Yo, Butch.
You need to watch your motherfuckin' tone, homey.
I'm the last one you wanna include
in any threats you got.
As for the rest of you niggas.
Shit, he ain't mine.
Shit, we been boys since we was kids, right?
- Straight up.
- All right.
You already know my uncle ain't callin'
for nothin' but peace.
- Ain't my fault, Roc.
- I'm sorry, Roc.
Apologies, Mr. Roc.
Can you please forgive me?
Sitting over here apologizing and shit.
Come on, yo.
- This nigga sweatin'.
- Come on, let's go.
- That nigga gonna beat yo ass.
- Oh, wait, I can't find the camera.
- Take it, oh, no, not that.
Take a picture of us.
- Cheese, bitch.
- This a moment 'cause you out the house.
- I know.
- You outside.
- I told you-
- You outside, girl,
and I can't believe,
you gotta document this
'cause no one gonna believe it.
- Let's take a toast.
- Hey, little mama, take a dance
with me real quick.
- No, no, no, I don't feel like dancing.
- [Man In Red] Come on for the soul stop.
- [Desa Rae] No, I don't feel like dancing.
- What y'all got going on, bruh.
- Watch out cornrows.
That's not even your truck to save, bruh.
Mind all of y'all fuckin' business.
Who the fuck business is it?
(glass breaks)
- [Des Rae] Hey, Roc.
- [Monica] That was crazy.
- You good?
- [Desa Rae] Yeah, I'm good.
- She's all right.
I got my girl, you good.
- I'm good.
- All right, he gots to go.
- [Desa Rae] Are you good?
- [Monica] You know I'm good.
You know how I get down.
I had it for my girl,
you know what I'm saying.
If that was me-
- What would you do?
- I'd have swung on him.
I would've been like.
- What you gonna do?
Catch her. - Oh, my God.
- That's all right.
- How much did you have to drink?
Here, I'm a take y'all home.
- You smell good.
- [Roc] Why is she smelling me?
- Get her home, come on.
- Get my purse.
- [Desa Rae] I got your purse.
- All right, my phone.
- I got your phone.
Thank you so much for bringing us home
from the club.
And attitude or not,
I really appreciate it,
it was really sweet.
- Nah, it's all good.
I don't really mind helping out, all right.
But, um, ain't nobody worried
about that little attitude.
You already know I could tell
what's in your eyes, right?
♪ I always said you had the beat of my heart ♪
♪ Of course you've always known this ♪
♪ From the very start
♪ 'Cause no one can come between us ♪
♪ Try to tear us apart
♪ 'Cause the love we share is true ♪
- Wait, oh, my God, wait.
That wasn't supposed to happen, shit
- Yeah, it was and, baby, there's so much more.
♪ The things that you do
♪ I want your love, girl
♪ Don't get it confused, baby
♪ Finding me a circle
♪ Gotta pop me open
♪ With your love it was the magic potion ♪
- Do you have condoms?
- Let me go check the truck.
- Okay.
(door closes)
Hey, hi, I'm so sorry for misleading you,
but I can't do this.
Listen.
- Listen, you gotta stop overthinking everything.
All right, tryna make sense
of every little move that you make.
All right.
How about you let me take you out.
You know, go to dinner or something like that.
You already know we ain't got nothing
but time on our hands.
- Okay, I'll let you know.
I know where to find you.
- [Monica] I wanna feel it.
Dang, where'd he go?
- Desa Rae Jenkins.
I called you four times today
and you have not answered your phone.
Why are you playing games?
You know we have to finalize this situation
with the rental property.
- I don't have to answer your calls, Reggie.
That's what we got attorneys for.
- You know it's clear
that you tryna be a pain in my ass.
All you have to do is sign
this one piece of paper.
My attorney's gonna be out of town for weeks.
I need this done today.
- No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not signing anything
until my attorney has plenty
of time to look over the paperwork.
And I'm sorry that you're upset
that I didn't call you,
but do you remember a time
when you didn't answer my calls
because your little heifer was annoyed?
As I said before,
it it pertains to Latrel
or my alimony check,
which by the way hasn't hit my account.
Where's my money, Reggie?
- Desa Rae, this is complicated, okay.
I am trying.
Lord knows I'm trying.
But I need you to be patient with me, okay?
You already have the house.
My financial situation is not
as secure as it used to be, all right?
Now I need you to sign off
on this one last piece of property
and I promise you gonna get what's due to you.
But I need you to stop being mad
at me for walking out on marriage
that was failing for years.
- No, it failed because you got caught cheating
and you're little heifer is the one
who told me she was pregnant by you.
- Oh.
- You know, give me your little funky paper.
Uh-uh.
Turn around.
Here.
Happy?
- Yes, was that so hard.
- Leave me alone.
- Yo, what's up with you, girl?
Give me my bear.
- Your bear?
- Yeah, my bear, you bought it.
- Yeah, I did buy it.
- For me. - It's my bear.
- Exactly.
- Did you tell your mom yet?
- I sent her a message.
I need to call her for real.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- Hey, Ma, did you get my message?
- No, I haven't checked my messages yet.
- Well, I was just calling
to let you know that I probably won't be able
to come home this weekend
or even next weekend.
- What? Latrel, are you serious?
- Come on now, baby.
I went to the grocery store
and I bought all this stuff
and I have tickets for tonight.
You sure you can't come?
- Yeah, I'm sure, Mom, I'm sorry.
I messed up on this test
and I need to retake it.
- Well, your butt is lucky he's letting
you take it over again
so you better do good on it this time.
And I guess I'll just save all this stuff.
- All right, Ma, I love you.
- [Desa Rae] All right, I'll talk to you later.
- See you.
- Why you laughing like that
when I'm on the phone with my mom.
- I messed up on a test.
- Man, everything was smooth the other day.
Shit, from what I heard probably was dope as fuck.
I just wish we had a chance
to make bigger moves in LA.
You know DJ talkin' about
the feds ready to make some moves,
so look like we gotta lie low
on this here for a minute.
- Yeah, but you can't trust everything
that nigga say.
Nah.
Send Gage and Butch down there.
Let them see what's going on.
'Cause I need you to keep
your hands as clean as possible.
Listen, nephew, I ain't never gave a fuck
about them other niggas out there.
But you, you my fam.
So you know I got to have your back, right?
- Yeah, you know I got your back, too, right, Unc.
- For shit loads.
- But you know what?
I think I am gonna send Gage and Romo.
Butch been acting funny.
I don't know what's going on with him,
but I got my eyes on him
just in case some shit go down.
- See, that's what you gotta do.
You got to watch these motherfuckers, Roc.
I know they your boys and everything,
but I don't fuck with none of them.
See, I don't let niggas get too close to me
and you shouldn't either.
Always keep them niggas at a distance.
Don't never let them motherfuckers forget
that without me and you,
they wouldn't be shit.
Never let 'em forget that shit.
- Girl, listen, I told you
that what happened, didn't I?
Didn't I tell you that was gonna happen?
You be playin' too much.
- Bitch, you loud as hell.
Why don't you take that shit
the fuck outta here.
Don't you see us in here talking?
You need to have some respect.
- Wait, who you calling a bitch
and respect you for what?
Who the hell is you?
Yeah, a nobody, girl, you know this motherfucker.
- Who am I? Who am I?
Bitch, I'm glad you asked.
You see I'm the motherfucker
who pays your bills.
As a matter of fact,
I'm the motherfucker responsible
for keeping your son in private school.
Now the real question is,
who the fuck are you besides
some slick talking bucket head bitch
who happened to get pregnant
by my nephew.
- Let me call you back.
Roc!
Are you handling this shit or should I?
- Shit, first of all your ass was being rude.
Being loud as fuck.
Man, look, I don't mind fighting
your battles for you,
but this time, yeah, you on your own.
- Well, ain't that a bitch.
Fuck you and fuck you, too.
Come on, Lamar, get your shit together, let's go.
They being disrespectful and I'm a hurt somebody.
- He ain't going nowhere.
I'm a bring him home later on.
- I'm not doing this shit with you.
- See, what I think about that, I told you.
You better pump your motherfuckin' brakes.
- Roc.
- I'm tired of your shit right now.
- Chill out, dawg.
- Get the fuck outta here.
- Get the fuck up outta here, man.
You already doing this shit.
- Fuck you.
- What's going on with you?
- I told you about that.
- Man, if you don't get up outta here,
he gonna hurt you.
Man, leave.
We'll talk later.
- Man, look, you need to get rid
of that bitch, I'm telling you.
She's disloyal and disrespectful
and I don't tolerate that shit, Roc.
- Yeah, that makes two of us.
You all right, man?
- You all right. - You good, man.
- Man, you all right, right?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- You just pop up on people.
- Yeah, what you over here doing?
- What are you doing?
- Shit, I came to check up on you.
- Well, I got a lot going on.
I got a leaky faucet and I've gotta clean up
this garage so I don't have time to talk.
- I mean, I ain't no plumber,
but let me help you out with that.
Look, matter of fact,
how about we make a bet? - What?
- If I don't finish in an hour,
you gotta let me take you to dinner.
- [Desa Rae] Okay, well, if I win, I get to choose.
- Come on. - Let's go.
- No, I told you he just showed up.
But I'm so glad he did because Reggie said
he'd fix the faucet and you know how that is
and Latrel canceled.
I don't even know what's gotten into him.
- It's called growing up
and living your best life, girl.
Let it go.
He'll come home when he's ready to.
And as for Reggie's sorry ass, whatever.
It's probably better that he wasn't even there.
I can only imagine what Roc is looking like right now.
- Oh, my God, he's so beautiful.
He got all these tattoos
on his chest and his back.
But, girl, I definitely know why they call him the Roc.
I felt that the other day.
- [Monica] Send me a picture.
- A picture?
Okay, wait, wait, I gotta sneak it.
- [Monica] Girl, damn, come on,
hurry up and send that picture.
Got me over here like a damn .
(camera clicks)
(phone dings)
- Mm.
Lord have mercy.
I'm about to pass the hell out.
Girl, what are you gonna do with all of this?
Please tell me
and do not continue to waste that man's time.
I know how you operate, girl.
- I will take that as a compliment.
I don't know what I'm gonna do with him.
He's so young.
But, I mean, I don't know.
Maybe we can be friends.
- [Monica] That all depends on what you want from him.
I mean, personally I think you're just wasting his time,
but what I do suggest is you get off
the phone right now and start
to get to know him a little better
and by next week, I need to know
what that sex is like on a scale of 1 to 10.
All right, gotta go, bye.
- Talk to you later, bye.
You done?
- Yeah, man, that faucet wore me out.
- I see.
So, I knew this was gonna take longer than an hour.
- I mean, it barely took over an hour,
but I mean, I did lose the bet.
- Yes.
- So I'll do whatever you want.
- Anything?
- Anything. - Okay.
- All right, so after you take a shower,
I can get you some clothes from my son's room
and then we can go out.
- From your son's room?
- Yeah, from my son's room.
- Yeah, no, I got some clothes in the car.
- Oh. - It'll be all right.
- You keep clothes in the car?
- Yeah, better than your son's room.
- Just hurry up.
(bright music)
- This is crazy.
I can't believe you got me
to come to some shit like this, man.
I should have thrown a suit on or something.
Oh, you look fine.
You lost a bet so suck it up.
You enjoy it. I saw it.
- Man, you gotta be like
the only black person I know
to come to some shit like this.
- No, my son loves it and I saw you, too.
You like it.
- Man, look, the only way I'm a like this
is if Drake or Hole shows up-
- Drake.
- And you know that's not happening.
- Whatever.
So, maybe next time you could take me
into your world.
- My world? - Yeah.
- You better be careful what you wish for.
- Okay.
Thanks again for going with me to the musical.
I know you didn't wanna go,
especially since your butt fell asleep.
- Man, I did fall asleep, man.
- Yes, you did.
- But you know I used to always go to 'em growing up.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, my grandma, she used to always take me.
Then, but life happens and, shit, here I am.
- Yeah.
Life does happen and if
you ever wanna talk about it, I'm here.
- Shit, what I wanna talk about is up inside.
- Yeah, I bet you do.
- No, I'm tired.
I had a good time, but maybe next time
the plans are on you, okay?
Goodnight, Roc.
Roc, come on now.
Don't do that stuff around here, Roc.
Roc, the police are really active, so be easy.
And don't look at my ass when I walk away.
(door closes)
(engine revs)
♪ I feel like I'm prison
♪ For God's sake
♪ I feel like I'm Craig
♪ I miss the nights we spent together ♪
♪ Doing just whatever
♪ I thought that we would last forever ♪
♪ Hand in hand just together
♪ Baby I miss you, do you miss me, too ♪
♪ I know things have changed
♪ They ain't the same
♪ But what we gonna do
- Now this one's dope.
- Yeah, I love this one.
- The artist really did their thing on this.
Man, imagine something like that in your house.
- I would love this in my house.
But I would actually like
to know the artist's inspiration behind it
and you can see it in her eyes.
And since you come here so much,
I'm sure you know already (laughs).
- Matter of fact, I do.
I did that.
- Oh, you did that.
Oh, with your crayons, okay.
- For real. - Whatever.
- Nah, inspiration came Maha Rue.
She got a lousy ass husband
and like five kids or something like that.
I mean, you could tell she's stressed.
Just look at her face.
- Yeah, she does look constipated.
- Right.
- But, if you could really draw something
like this, I would love for you to draw me something.
- Come on, you know I got you.
- Good.
- But for real, though.
I just brought you here
'cause I thought you might like coming
to a spot like this.
- Oh, I like it, this is me.
- Right up your alley, right?
- Yeah.
But, you don't have to try to impress me
when I'm already impressed.
- Man, quit playing, come on.
Let's get outta here.
I'm gonna take you somewhere else.
- Oh, day part two.
- Day part two.
♪ I miss you more than you can know ♪
♪ And I'm still learning
♪ Learning to do this on my own ♪
Cheers.
How you like this spot?
- I love it.
Okay, this is more like it.
You score one point with me.
- One point?
- Yeah, one point.
- After everything I did for you.
- What'd you do for me?
- Hold up.
First of all, I fix that busted ass car
that you have, all right,
and that little leaky faucet.
What, then we went over to the art gallery
and now, look, we having some
of the best food in the city.
- Okay, two, maybe three,
but it'll take you a while
before you catch up with me.
- I can't even give you nothing yet.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Jackson.
- I didn't do nothing.
- No.
- I gave you a kiss.
I made you smile.
I took your mind off things.
I even gave you my shoulder and, plus,
I'm about to give you some
of this chocolate cake.
Let me see your mouth.
I bet there's a lot that you can do with your mouth.
- Yeah, show me some mouth.
- Okay, but you got cavities bad, I see it.
- [Roc] I ain't got no cavities.
- I see them.
- I'm a show you what I can do with my mouth, come on.
- No, let's go dance, come on, come on, come on.
- Wait, wait.
You still haven't told me where you been all day.
I been texting your phone like crazy.
- Where I been ain't your business, girl, chill out.
- No, mm-mm, no, I'm serious, no.
- What are you doing? - No.
- If you didn't wanna do it,
what the fuck you come here for.
See, that's why I stop fuckin' with your ass.
Always acting like a little kid and shit.
- Since when did you stop fuckin' with me, Roc.
What, two minutes ago?
- Come on now.
I just got a phone call.
Maybe it was something urgent, man.
- Fuckin' me is urgent.
But you need to take me somewhere special
and start treating me more like royalty.
- Come on, girl, you are royalty.
- Yeah, okay.
- And fucking you is always urgent.
- Mm.
- Come on.
- Let me do it.
I been waiting weeks for this.
Damn.
- You are a life saver, girl.
I've been sitting on this paperwork
for weeks and Latrel needed it ASAP.
- Well, you know, you'll be right on time.
No worries, plus we all know
you been really busy with Mr.-
- I only saw him one time this week.
He's supposed to come out here later today
for dinner, but I don't really feel like cooking.
I think I'm gonna order some Chinese.
- Ooh, Chinese.
You know I'm always hungry.
That sounds good.
- Reggie, what are you doing here?
- Hey, relax, all right.
I was gonna knock,
but since I had my key I decided
to let myself in.
Just came by to drop off your check.
- Oh, yes. - Ooh, a check.
- God is good, won't he do it all the time.
- Girl, I'll give you a call tomorrow.
- Yeah, good luck with that one.
- Right.
- [Monica] Bye, Reggie.
- Goodbye, Monica, stay prayerful.
- Excuse me? What are you doing?
- Getting something to drink.
- No, you need to call before you come,
knock when you get here
and you can't just go in my refrigerator getting
whatever you want.
- You are always complaining.
Can we ever just get together
without you griping about this or that.
- Oh, uh-uh.
(doorbell rings) Hold that thought.
Let me get that. It's probably Monica.
Oh my God, you're early, really early,
I said eight, not six.
- Nah, you said six.
I mean, I'm a little late, but,
who's car is that?
- Um, that's my ex-husband's car.
He shouldn't be long,
but you think you can come back at eight?
- You must be one of Latrel's friend.
- Oh, yeah, this is one of Latrel's friends.
He just stopped by to see if Latrel was here.
It's one of his workout buddies from the gym.
- Yeah, yeah, I used to work out with him.
It's nice meeting you.
- Nice meeting you, too.
What'd you say your name was again?
- Roc.
- Roc. - Yeah.
- I'll be sure to tell Latrel
when I see him in a couple of weeks.
- Definitely. - Right.
- Thanks for stopping by.
(engine revs)
- Well, it's time for me to go, as well.
But came by to drop off your check
and let you know that I really do appreciate you whether
you know it or not.
- Well, thanks for coming by, Reggie.
- You're welcome.
- Have a good day.
(soulful music)
(doorbell rings)
God, I'm so glad you came.
I had no idea my ex was gonna pop over here
so I mean, biggest apology.
He just popped up unannounced
and just came and walked in the refrigerator,
but I told you hey, nuts.
You just gonna stare at me?
You not gonna say anything?
- Girl, you promised me dinner, right?
Yo, where's my food at?
- I got us some Chinese food.
I ordered food so we could eat.
- Man, I don't even eat Chinese food.
Shit, you told me to come here at six, right?
- No, I told you eight
and everybody eats Chinese food.
I had no idea my ex was gonna come by here.
- [Roc] Right, probably too busy fuckin' that nigga, right?
- Okay, I don't like your attitude
so if you came over here just to argue,
you can just go, rise up, you just go.
- Mm-mm.
- Stop, Roc, wait, stop.
Relax.
I don't want you to go.
10 points, not two.
You made me smile when I didn't think I could smile.
You made me feel the most beautiful
I've ever felt in my life.
I don't want you to go tonight.
I want you to stay.
- Stay? - Stay.
- Man, look, stay for what.
Look, let me tell you something.
It ain't gonna be all this back
and forth shit in this relationship.
It's either you in or you out.
- I'm all in, Roc.
I just need you to get all in, too.
Stay.
♪ Sitting here wondering where this will go ♪
♪ Where this will go, yeah
♪ Am I better off running wild
♪ Or would you prefer taking it slow ♪
♪ Tell me, girl
♪ Black dress with her hair tied back ♪
♪ Just how I like it
♪ Miracle how it lasted
♪ Lady, is this perfect timing
♪ Why don't you stay, stay, here, here tonight, tonight ♪
♪ Why don't you say, stay, here, here tonight ♪
♪ Destiny called as we locked into each other's eyes ♪
♪ Fate told me women like you
♪ Are one of a kind, yeah
♪ Confident, sexy as you're walking in ♪
♪ In the present of novelist
♪ I'm losing my mind, yeah
♪ I know that love is hard to find, yeah ♪
♪ So why don't you stay, stay with me ♪
♪ Here, here tonight, tonight, here tonight ♪
♪ Why don't you stay, stay with me ♪
♪ Here tonight
- Desa Rae Jenkins,
you got five seconds to put some clothes on
and tell his punk ass to leave.
- Reggie, what the fuck are you doing here?
Put the gun down.
- And tell his ass to leave.
I knew he wasn't one of Latrel's friends.
He don't hang with drug dealers.
- Look, I don't know what y'all got going on outside.
I'll be back for the dinner
that you promised me, though.
- Motherfucker, do you know who you fuckin' with?
You think I won't shoot you.
- Guys stop.
- Hold up, hold up.
I been standing here for two whole minutes.
I know you ain't got it in you to shoot that thing.
- Don't you tell me, fool.
I assure you when the police arrive
won't shit happen to me
for blowing your fucking brains out.
- Get that shit out my fuckin' face.
- Stop, no, Roc, just go.
- Man, where'd you find this lame ass nigga at?
- Just get outta here, just get outta here.
Stop, Reggie, Roc, please, please.
Roc, just go, please.
- He got one more time.
I'm about to light some shit up.
- [Desa Rae] Just go.
Please just go.
- Yeah, I'd like to see you try.
Desa Rae, what the hell is wrong with you messing
with a young ass nigga like that?
Hold old is this nigga,
young enough to be our son?
How could you be that desperate.
- Desperate?
No, the only thing I'm desperate for is getting rid
of your ass.
Now get the fuck out, Reggie.
And where's my goddamn key?
And get your fucking gun.
Fuck.
- Man, you should have killed that nigga.
I'm surprised you didn't,
'cause if it was me, I woulda shot that bitch, too, dawg.
- Yeah, Des cool, man,
but her husband ain't shit, though.
- Obviously. - Yeah.
- Matter of fact, I'm a need y'all
to get some information on him.
Yeah, him and his son.
- For sure, bro, we got you.
- All right, what's up with that trip to Cali, though?
Oh, boy was lying or what?
- Nah, man, it's definitely some heat coming.
I've even seen some fast like around two
of the spots that Uncle Ronnie connects be at.
Somebody snitchin' for sho for sho.
Man, we just been low key
for two motherfuckin' long
for that shit to do down like that.
Plus, we got police on payroll.
That shit shouldn't be happening, man.
- Nah, not really.
I mean, we got some of 'em,
but not all of 'em.
- Look, Roc, maybe we should just chill
for right now, you know.
Like shut the shop down for a little bit.
Just until all this shit blow over.
Maybe. We'll see what's up.
I'll take to my uncle,
see what he's talking about.
I'll keep y'all posted.
'Cause if the feds that close to the connect,
it's just a matter of time
before they making a move.
- Shit, maybe for all of us.
Ain't no telling when or where
these motherfuckers start showing up at.
- Can I talk to you in private
for a moment, please?
- All right, I'm a get at y'all in a minute.
I'll let y'all know what I'm talking about.
- All right, stay there, man.
- What's up with that shit?
- See, this exactly why I ain't got no baby mama.
- [Roc] What's going on?
- You tell me.
I mean, you got this whole vibe
like something bothering you, like what's good?
- Man, look.
I just feel like something big's about to change.
And I just can't tell if it's good or bad.
- Okay.
Something as far as what?
You afraid something's gonna happen to you?
You referring to us.
I'm asking you this because you don't touch me no more
and when we have sex,
you just bust your nut and call it a day.
It never used to be like that, Roc.
Talk to me, please, like.
Is there somebody else?
- Man, come on, there's always somebody else.
Man, you know that.
Look, you told me as long as I take care of you
and little Roc, that's the only thing
that matter, right?
I mean, those are your words, not mine, right?
- I know what I said.
But that's when I felt like I had your heart
and I don't have it no more, do I?
- Look, they only person I love is
that little boy running around here, all right?
I mean, I appreciate you
for bringing him into this world,
but listen, don't start complaining now.
All right, you got everything you need around here.
- I'm still your baby moms.
It don't matter who you with.
(phone rings)
Hey, you busy?
I'm a need you to look into something for me.
All right, all right, bye.
- You stay spoiling me, man.
First steak, now this.
- Well, I like spoiling you,
especially since you helping Stella get her groove back.
- Stella?
- Stella, like the movie, Angela Bassett.
Never mind, whatever.
- I don't know that movie.
You know I don't go to the movies like that.
- Whatever.
- Too busy with other things.
Yeah, I been fuckin' the shit outta you.
- Stop, stop talking about it.
Listen, so I been thinking, you know,
since we decided to not to the one night stand here.
- Yeah.
- You still here, you know, what are we?
Are we friends, are we lovers, are we playmates?
- Here we go.
- No, I got questions,
especially since I changed
the locks and Reggie won't be busting up in here.
I wanna know what are we?
I got questions.
- All right, look, for real.
We can't say we friends, right?
- Mm, no.
- Fuck way too much for that.
And we can't really say we dating.
'Cause, I mean, that shit just sound corny as fuck.
- Okay, so-
- I mean, the only other thing I could think of
is you be my peace, I'll be your happiness.
- I like that, peace and happiness.
- You like that?
- I like it.
Okay, so the woman that's giving you peace wants
to know what do you do when you're not here
and why have you never invited me to my place
and where are your parents?
I got questions, I wanna know.
- Yeah.
Uh, I don't know.
You know I lost both my parents, right?
- No.
- Yeah, I lost my mom around the age of six.
Yeah, she was a drug addict.
My pops, he was locked up ever since
I was like seven years old.
But, with my Uncle Ronnie, though, yeah.
He's the one who raised me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, he's cool as hell.
You gotta meet him one day.
- I'd like to.
So, what is it you do?
- Ah, man, look, I just shake and move,
you know, that's it.
- Well, I'm sorry to hear about your parents.
I lost my parents, too.
It hurts.
If you ever need to talk about it, I'm here.
You know I'm always here.
- Yeah, look.
- But, no, no, no.
I need to understand
what's this shaking and moving thing.
What does that mean?
- Shaking and moving.
It just means I got a few people
that work for me, that's it.
- No, no, what does that,
is what you do legal?
Do you kill people or-
- Shh.
- Or should I be worried about any-
Why you asking all these questions, baby?
Look, you starting to sound like the cops.
- I wanna know.
- Look, just so you could ease that mind.
I've never killed nobody. - No.
- Nah.
- Okay.
- But look, forget all that.
Matter of fact, we about to go take a shower.
Come on, I wanna take you somewhere, baby.
- What? Okay.
♪ Time and time again we try
♪ To tell ourselves these good lies ♪
♪ Let's come together
- Ms. Ellen.
- Hey, baby.
- How you been?
- I'm good love, how are you?
- Good, did you have a chance
to take care of that for me?
- Absolutely I did.
- Awesome, hey, look,
I also wanted to introduce you, this is Des.
- Oh, this is who you been telling me about.
- Nice to meet you.
- Oh, nice to meet you.
Oh, Roc, you ain't tell me how gorgeous she is.
- Now stop.
- Look at you and, girl, look at this figure.
Girl, do you know how many people would kill
to have some curves like that?
Listen, baby, I got the perfect red dress for you.
It's my favorite,
but we gonna let you decide.
Come on, let's go.
- Just go try it on, man.
♪ See it fit me real good
♪ Then it looks great
♪ It's a vibe that you can't replicate ♪
♪ I know I look good, no time to waste ♪
♪ No time to waste
♪ Walkin' down the street
♪ With my fit so fly
♪ A pretty high girl catchin' all the eyes ♪
♪ Jumpin' new gear, got a hot supply ♪
♪ I don't follow trends
♪ They follow mine
♪ Roll out the carpet
♪ A moment to be captured
♪ Pose for your photo
♪ But you paying after
♪ I bring the fire
♪ I'm stopping traffic
- Roc Dawson.
Long time no see.
- Nina Davis, shit, I'm surprise
you ain't seen me around.
What you doing up in here?
- Oh, I have no doubt
that you've been around.
And it look like you still getting around to me.
So, uh, what's up with you and my girl Vanessa?
- Man, look, you know we talk every day.
Man, we got a whole kid together.
What you talkin' about.
- I know.
I was just asking because you came in here
with somebody that don't look like Vanessa
and that's a lot of bad.
- Goddamn.
- Oh, my God, Roc, this is gorgeous,
did you see this?
Do you like this?
- Nah, I really like that one.
- I love it.
Wait, did she tell you how much this cost?
It's so expensive.
- [Roc] Miss Ella, do me a favor and bag it up.
- Oh, Roc, no, wait, Miss Ella.
No, Roc, you don't have to spend money
like that on me.
- Look, didn't I say I was gonna take you somewhere.
Just let me do this for you, all right?
Miss Ella, look, put these three dresses
in a bag.
- I got you.
♪ I know I look good
♪ I know I look good, yeah
All right, Nina, get your broke ass outta here, man.
Walk on down the street.
- [Nina] That's what I'm telling V.
(club music)
- That's why they fuckin' Bud up.
- Man, I still ain't heard from the dudes, bro.
- Romo ass probably scared
that cow was gonna knock his head off.
I was just putting it on another bottle.
- What you say?
You know I got it, dawg.
There ain't nothin' to this nigga.
- Hell, yeah.
Hey, look, you know I appreciate
y'all motherfuckers, right?
- Man, you already know, dawg.
- Oh, here we go.
- Dang.
- Hey. - I noticed.
- Matter of fact, hold this real quick.
I'll be back, dawg.
- Where the fuck is you going?
- I see somebody.
- Man.
- Hey.
- You look good, damn.
What took you so long, man?
My boy said you took a couple hours
to get ready?
- Nah, it was an hour.
His driving was tragic.
- Man, guard that body, though.
They about to pick.
Hey, everybody, I wanna introduce you to something.
This is Des.
Say what's up, man.
- Hi. - What's up, Des.
- She belong to me
so don't be trying nothing.
Yeah, yeah.
- I'm glad you said something.
- Hell yeah.
- Hey, um, you okay?
- Yeah, everything's good.
Why, what's up, what's going on?
- I don't know, you seem a little weird tonight.
- No, I'm straight.
I smoked some weed, but, why, what's up?
- So you told them that you own me?
I don't belong to anybody, Roc.
- That shit ain't had nothing
to do with no ownership, all right.
You already know I smoke weed,
so I don't know what the big deal is, man.
Can we just go over here
and try to have a good time.
- I don't have to try to have a good time.
I'm gonna have a good time.
Show me to my seat.
Excuse me.
- My dawg.
- Hey, so you know I forgot
to tell you about Archie, right?
- Archie?
- This nigga, talkin' man, hit him up
in two weeks or something like that.
Two weeks.
- Two weeks go by
this motherfucker stop answering the phone.
- It's always something with this.
Come to find out this nigga dog died
and he had to plan a funeral for it.
I told you, bruh.
- I feel you, dawg.
- Motherfucker, man, I told you stop fuckin' with it, man.
He tried to run that same bullshit on me.
Talkin' about he had to plan a dog funeral.
Man, if you don't dig a hole
in your backyard and put that dog in there
and come on.
- I wish that nigga would say that shit to me, dawg.
I'll busy his bitch ass
right next to him.
- That's the shit that I was talking about.
- Hell, yeah.
What, you don't want any?
- I'm a go to the bathroom.
- You want me to get you something to drink?
Or something to eat.
Whatever you need, just let me know.
- No, thanks, all right, I'll be back.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Excuse me.
(men chattering)
(toilet flushes)
Desa Rae, what are you doing here?
- I'm sorry, I don't mean to stare,
but that is a real beautiful dress you have on.
- Oh, thank you.
- [Woman] You mind sharing where you got it from?
- Oh, a friend of mine bought this for me
but I'm not sure where they got it.
- I like your dress, too.
- Oh, thank you.
A friend of mine purchased mine's also.
Let me go back over there.
You have a good night, though.
- You, too.
- Roc, you got this bitch
in the bathroom got the same shit I got on.
Are you fuckin' kidding me.
You are fuckin' playin' with me, bitch.
I'm a fuck you and that bitch up.
You got me fucked up.
- What was that all about?
- Just some chump chick looking for attention, man.
Shit, what took your ass so long?
- In the bathroom?
I don't think you want details.
- Come on.
Come over here, man. - What's up, baby boy.
- Everything good.
- Sorry, I'm late, man,
but one of my companions had me held up a little bit.
- It's all good, man.
Hey, look, I need to get at you
about something important later on.
- Oh, that's good.
- This is Des.
Des, this is Uncle Ronnie.
- It's so nice to meet you.
He's told me so much about you.
- Well, goddamn, you did good nephew.
- Oh, man.
- You did damn good.
Shit.
I guess my only question for you is please tell me
you got a sister, cousin, auntie,
or something at home for me, huh?
- No, it's just me
and Roc has already made claims on me.
- You damn straight about that.
- I see, carry on.
- So what's up, you tryna go dance or something?
- No, I don't feel like dancing right now, maybe later.
- Man, come on.
Look, if you ain't tryna do it,
I know somebody would.
- Oh, okay.
Well, I suggest you do that
'cause I don't feel like dancing right now, Roc.
- Mm.
- Nephew, I'm a need you
to get your bitches in check, man.
Why do you let this chick go on like this, man.
I thought I taught you better than that, man?
Damn.
- [Desa Rae] Bitches.
- Hey, look, I apologize for what he said.
But, you need to watch your slick ass mouth man.
All I was trying to do was go dance, all right.
- Hey. - Hey.
♪ Happy birthday to you
- [Man 2] Speech, speech, speech.
- [Man 3] Say somethin' bro.
- Nah, y'all crazy, man.
I appreciate you.
- Hey, happy birthday my nigga dawg.
You already know, man.
- Your birthday?
We spent the whole day together.
Not one time did you say it was your birthday.
- Yeah, look, it's like, not like
you woulda heard me anyway,
all that damn complaining.
- You know what, I'm outta here
and are you gonna call a car to come get me
or do I need to call somebody?
- Man.
- Get me outta here.
- [Man 2] Yo, yo, yo.
Where you going, bro.
What's up?
(all chattering)
- Man, all I was trying to do was
just celebrate my birthday
with you up in there.
But you over here acting all uptight and shit
like you way too good for everybody.
Man, look, hold up.
Most of them motherfuckers in there
would die for me, all right.
- I don't care, Roc, I don't have any issue
with anybody in there.
Except for your Uncle Ronnie.
He was wrong and so were you.
Just leave me alone.
Go back in the party
and find a little heifer to slap in her face.
(guns firing)
- Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Hey, drive this bitch, nigga, shit.
Baby, you hurt?
(horn blows)
(Des Rae cries)
Hey, pull up the fuckin' camera, man,
and find out who them niggas was.
Yeah, tell Uncle Ronnie to call me back.
All right.
Shit.
Baby.
(siren blaring)
- So, look, Roc just made the call, all right.
He said he need these niggas up outta here today.
So we gotta catch 'em while they slippin'.
Is you ready or nah?
- Shit, you want me to kill
these niggas in broad daylight.
- Nigga, you actin' like a real bitch.
Look, you said you wanna be down
with the set, right?
So this what the fuck you gotta do, nigga.
- All right, bet.
(dramatic music)
There the nigga go right there.
(guns fire)
- [Desa Rae] I know.
- [Monica] This food is so good.
Good choice.
So, listen, I'm a be quiet.
I'm a let you tell the story
and I'll tell you what I think at the end.
- Okay, all right, so we're at the club
and I'm chillin', but it's like Roc is
a completely different person.
He's all cursing and yelling
and he's like nigga this and nigga that.
And he's high as hell.
- [Monica] No.
- And then I meet his Uncle Ronnie.
Within the first five minutes,
he calls me a bitch.
- What? - Yes.
And then if that wasn't enough,
that whole shoot out thing, I was done.
I was scared as hell
and I haven't talked to Roc.
He called me once, but I didn't answer.
I mean, what am I supposed to say?
- All right, I'm a tell you what I think
and I'm a keep it down
'cause I know Latrel is downstairs trying to sleep.
But you can't be around this.
This is not you.
When it comes to somebody like Roc,
this is his lifestyle.
This is who he is.
A lot of time women,
we think we can change man.
We think we can come in, fix them up,
that's not workin' like that.
You don't need to even be in the environment, okay.
And when it comes to this Uncle Ronnie,
he called you a bitch?
- [Desa Rae] Right.
- [Monica] I'd of slapped the shit outta him.
- You know I should have.
I wish I did. All the guys like-
- Hey, Auntie.
- Hi, what's up handsome?
- What y'all be doing?
- Listen, you need to come home more often, okay.
Worry about that
'cause you know your mom here about
to have a heart attack worried about you.
- He act like they don't feed him up at school.
(Monica laughs)
- Yeah, I know, but all that basketball
and studying be taking up most of the time.
- He's so good.
- Good.
- I probably won't be back till my dad's wedding.
- Wedding?
- Woop.
- Oh, he's getting married?
- My fault, I thought you knew.
- I'm a just eat my food.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's not, I mean, nothing to be sorry about.
- Girl.
(doorbell rings)
- [Roc] You just happened to be
at the wrong place at the wrong time.
- You know, say what you want, Roc,
but what I'm telling you is I don't want
a mover and shaker.
I don't want somebody
that goes around high all the time and hoses people.
And anybody that has a mentor like
your Uncle Ronnie can't do nothing for me.
I think you should just go.
Who are you, Roc?
And what do you want from me?
Are you some kind of kingpin?
- No, man, I need you to save me.
I need you to save me from all this bullshit.
- Listen, I swear you have so much potential,
but I don't know who that was at your birthday party.
Who was that?
- I mean, tell me what you looking for.
If it's one of them corporate type of dudes.
Maybe you just need to go back to your ex, Reggie.
But you can't, right, 'cause he getting married.
- What do you know about Reggie?
- That's why your ass be so-
- Okay, you've been watchin' him or somethin'?
- Damn straight.
- Okay.
- I know that's why you trippin' off
of him all the time, too.
- You know, I'm not gonna argue with you
about your bad boy behavior
and you not gonna make me feel guilty
about no falling in line like your hos.
I'm done, Roc.
If you don't leave, I'm gonna call the police.
- Wait, what?
- Get out of here.
Go, get out of here, Roc.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- I don't wanna do this with you.
(Desa Rae cries)
- Look, I know you different, all right.
I don't wanna do this shit with you either.
- Listen, I can't save you.
I can't even save myself from
the pain from my failed marriage.
- So I guess we just fuckin'.
♪ 'Cause I only want you
♪ Baby, yeah, I only want you
♪ 'Cause I only want you, yeah
♪ 'Cause I only want you
♪ Baby I only want
- What's up, my nigga, you got a minute?
- Yeah, more than a minute,
what's going on, man?
- Well, here's the deal.
I just got word that the feds
been fooling around with my businesses.
Which means shit might hit the fan
and I'm a need you to have my back like never before.
- Come on, man, you know I got your back.
You ain't gotta ask me no shit like that.
- Shit, I don't know, Roc.
You been kind of distant lately.
Kind of hard to get a hold of.
- Man, this is about Des?
Come on, bro, I ain't talked to her
in a couple of weeks.
But maybe my lifestyle's just too much for her.
- Good, celebrate and let that bitch walk.
Listen, nephew.
What you need to do is get you a fine young bad bitch,
one that knows how to respect a nigga
and keep her fuckin' mouth shut.
- Yeah, hey, Unc, let me take this right quick.
- All right.
I bid you nephew.
- Yeah, hello?
Yeah, I didn't think your ass was gonna call.
- One question.
How many hos have you been sleeping with, Roc.
- Man, why you asking me some dumb ass shit like that.
- I said how many.
- Look, that ain't your fuckin' business, man.
- I swear to God if you gave me something
you will never hear the end of it.
It is my business and you better tell me.
I will sue your ass.
- You better go check one
of them other niggas you fuckin' with.
'Cause I know I'm good.
- And trust me when I say you better hope
to hell you didn't.
I'll be in touch.
(hip hop music)
(phone rings)
- Tracy, put your motherfuckin' mama on the phone now.
(phone beeps)
(phone rings)
- [Recording] Please leave your message after the tone.
- I'm leaving work in about 30 minutes.
Meet me at the Love Market near the house.
It's important.
I can't believe you lied to me about this.
You need to man up and be prepared
to answer some questions.
You better be there.
Oh, hey, Mr. Cummings.
- Hey, how you doing?
- I'm leaving work in a little bit,
but I'll be in early.
Can you check your schedule
just to make sure everything's set?
- Yes, I will and I'd like to apologize again.
Lay offs happen, you been with us 13 years,
but it's business.
I hate to see you go.
You still have two weeks here with us.
- I appreciate that
and I know it's not your fault.
- Okay, just business.
- Thank you.
Have a great day.
- Damn girl, you got a minute?
- Oh, I though I had one,
but I went to the doctor
and he gave me something I can't get rid of.
- Can't get rid of, girl, what you talkin' about.
- Oh, you know what I'm talking about, yes, you do.
Look at this.
- Man, don't nobody care about no damn test, man.
- Roc.
- You know I stay strapped up,
I don't know what you talkin' about.
- Don't put those in my bag, Roc, no,
it's too late for condoms.
Look, I need you to stay focused.
I really tested positive,
I went to the doctor.
Look, you're not getting it.
I need you to buy this.
I need you to get serious.
- Girl, what you putting all
this stuff in this bag for.
- Yes, listen.
- I ain't buying all this stuff, man.
- Listen, listen.
- Oh, shit.
Oh.
Fuck.
You pregnant for real?
Damn, girl.
You know I got you, right?
- You promise?
- I promise, man.
For real, look, whatever you need.
All right?
Oh, shit.
How you feeling?
- I'm scared.
I mean, we haven't been cool, Roc.
And I didn't even think I could get pregnant.
- Damn, girl, hey, I'm a buy whatever you need.
Where's that bag at?
All this shit up in there, hell, yeah.
Come on.
- I know you're worried,
but I'm happy for you and Roc.
There's something about him that I like,
even though he definitely got some issues.
- Yeah, I like him a lot, too,
but, unfortunately, we're just two broken people trying
to make it whirl.
You know, I didn't even think I could get pregnant.
Can you imagine how surprised I was?
- Mm-hmm, well, you know what?
There's nothing you could do now
but have that beautiful baby for the both of y'all
and I am so excited, you know.
I'm a spoil that child so much.
I already went shopping.
Check it out.
- Oh, my God, thank you so much.
You know, I'll take it over
to his penthouse tomorrow.
Can you believe I've never been to his penthouse?
I've been kind of reluctant
about going all in with him.
- Well, I can't really blame you for that.
I mean, he's got something more going on
that we don't even know about,
so you do have to make sure that you're good.
- Yeah.
- I want the father of my baby
to be all that he can be
and Roc has told me
about his broken childhood,
lives in the streets
and he talked about getting his GED.
You should see this playhouse
he built for the baby.
It looks like a palace.
It's so cute.
He's so good with his hands.
It has these trellises and-
- Ooh, girl. - Shut up.
- You got me up in here about to cry.
But you know what, some real shit.
Roc's backstory is really
the story of so many people in our community.
A lot of these young boys are just lost.
You know, they don't know how to love.
They just trying to survive day by day
and also protect themselves.
So I'm really hoping this baby changes things for Roc.
Yeah, I hope so, too.
I just gotta figure out how I'm gonna tell Latrel.
I don't even think he knows I'm dating somebody.
I'm sure Reggie's nosy butt said something.
- Girl, do Reggie still be popping up on you?
- No, I haven't seen him since
the time he busted in on Roc and I.
I guess that prompted him to hurry up and get married.
- He really went through with it?
- I don't know and I don't have time to care.
I'm over Reggie and I'm so happy I can finally say that.
- Girl, I know that's right.
- No Reggie.
(doorbell rings)
Hey. - What's going on.
- You finally made it through, huh?
- Oh, what?
Oh, my God, Roc.
I am shocked.
I had no idea your place looked like this.
And this looks nothing like
the mechanic shop you call your castle.
- First of all, the shop is my castle.
All right, and before you say anything,
you already know, I was about to raw somethin' up.
- Whatever, Roc.
You can have your little weed.
Anyway, just know that smoking is not good
for the baby.
- Man, I ain't never known a baby to come out high.
I'll make sure I keep my distance, though.
So, is it a boy or a girl?
- I don't know yet.
But I don't care.
As long as the baby looks like you, I'm good.
- And you already know as long
as she looks like you, I'm good, too.
- Well, I have something for you.
First, this one is from Monica.
There you go, hold it up.
Hold it so I can read it, yeah.
My mommy is sweet, that's me,
but watch out for my dad,
'cause he gotta watch out for you.
- Man, y'all be wildin', for real.
Tell her I said thank you.
- I'll tell her.
All right, now this one is from me.
- Okay.
- Just trying to help you out.
- See.
"The Pleasures of Loving."
Hold on, you think that Roc Double D Dawson
needs help with this?
Come on, man.
- Did you see the book?
I'm just trying to help.
Well, okay, wait.
So I got this one to make you laugh,
but this is one I really wanna give to you.
- Man, I could really use this.
- You like it?
- Yeah, I do, thank you.
- Good.
All right, so, I wanna see the rest of the place.
- Come on.
- You show me where the magic happens.
- Right up here.
- This way?
- Yeah.
I swear, after looking at this book,
it looks a lot harder than I thought,
but I'm a definitely put some time aside,
make sure I study for this thing.
Well, you know, I'm here for you
if you need to study.
- Yeah, but.
- I can help.
You ever thought about opening a construction business?
What you did with our daughter's playhouse,
you got skills.
- Oh, you like that?
- Yeah, I like it.
- It's crazy just because
I've always meant to be an artist, though.
You know I like to draw.
- There you go again.
- I'm serious, man.
- You're serious.
- Yeah, you don't think I could draw?
- No.
- You know the art gallery that we went to?
- Yeah.
- You know that's my piece, right?
- Roc, no.
No, way.
I know that you didn't do that.
Man, look, let me show you something.
(Desa Rae laughs)
- Whoa.
Oh, my God, are you serious?
- You like that?
- Roc, this is stunning.
Can I keep it?
- Hell, yeah, man, you know
you can have whatever you want.
- What I want, I want love, peace and happiness.
I know that's what you want, too.
- Yeah, you know I got you, right?
- You better.
- [Man On TV] This is my damn money
and I do exactly what I please.
- What up, Unc.
- The shit done finally hit the fan, Roc.
Them motherfuckers are coming for me.
And this time I can't do shit about it.
Now I've already talked to Clint down
at the station.
Them motherfuckers want me to turn myself in
and do the time.
But look at me.
I'm an old man now and time ain't on my side.
Fact is, a motherfucker could die
in that motherfucker, man.
- Come on, Unc,
you know it ain't going down like that.
Everything you did for these dudes in this community,
what about the kids at the rec center.
And Clint's fat ass,
all that money that you put into his pocket,
man, come on, dawg.
What about Congressman Jerry?
I know there's something he can do.
He can only do so much, Roc.
Especially since the shit coming from the top.
The motherfuckers just jealous, man.
I'm making too much money.
I got too big.
And they not gonna stop until they get me
and if not me, the next nigga in charge
and that will be you.
- Man, look.
Whatever you need, just let me know, all right.
- I need you to take the fall
and do the time.
(dramatic music)
(Roc knocking)
♪ It feels so right
♪ And I will take this opportunity ♪
- You're late, real late.
But I'm so glad you're here, come on.
I'll do it.
Listen, I have a surprise for you.
Let me show you.
Ta-da, you like it?
- Aw, man, this is dope.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, but why you throw it up so early, though?
Thanksgiving ain't what,
for another couple weeks?
- I know it's early,
but I'm excited about little Roc coming over
for Thanksgiving dinner.
He's still coming, right?
- Man, I thought he was,
but I don't think Vanessa's having it.
You know I be just trying
to keep the confusion down.
- All right, I'm sure I'll see him at same point.
- But nah, come over here.
I just wanna talk to you.
You look tired.
You want me to get you something.
I can go grab you something.
Nah, I'm straight.
I just wanna talk to you for a little bit.
- Okay.
You all right?
- Yeah, um, looks like some things are going on
with the business.
And my Uncle Ronnie,
it looks like he's gonna get caught up with the feds,
so they ready to make some move.
- Well, I know you don't wanna hear me say this
about your uncle, but he deserves everything
he has coming to him.
That man is evil.
One day you're gonna see he's done more bad
in your life than good, Roc.
- I keep trying to tell you,
if it wasn't for him I probably wouldn't even be here.
- Okay, I get it, there's another side, but-
- Nah, but.
- Wait, what are you trying to say?
What is it?
- Looks like I might be going away for a little bit.
- Going away?
Going away where, Roc?
What are you talking about?
Please don't tell me you're saying what I think
you're gonna say.
- Man, I don't think my uncle could do 5 to 10 years.
- 10 years?
10 fucking years, are you kidding me, Roc?
Roc, I'm pregnant with our baby.
You won't even be here when she's born.
She won't even know who you are, Roc.
- You saying it's a girl?
- Yeah, a beautiful baby girl
and her photo and some stupid stuff is
in this stupid box.
I can't believe I been so stupid.
No, don't you baby me.
You need to go with your Uncle Ronnie
because I know he's behind this.
Get outta here.
(somber music)
- Dawg, why the fuck you brought us here, dawg.
- Shit.
- Look, though, what happened though.
So the bill come.
Motherfucker like almost $400.
- [Man 2] Four what? Damn.
- Girl bought about like 10 Long Islands.
A surf and turf.
Shit, but I ain't trippin', though.
You know I was for the fuck.
(all chattering)
So I go for my bread.
I don't even know where my loaf at.
I had to think like
I must have left it in my other shooter.
So I'm like, hey, I'm telling her like
hey, shawty, just pay the bill.
Talking how you old broke ass nigga.
I knew you y'all didn't,
you a loser.
All right, hey, bitch, I-
(gun cocks)
- Hold up, nah, we good.
- I gotta ask you.
Why does everyone treat you like you're some kingpin?
What the hell is this?
- Sit down.
I ain't talked to you all week.
How you feeling?
- Awful.
I came here to see if you changed your mind
or if I could help you change it.
- Well, I don't know if there's anything you could do.
The trial's already set to start next week.
I'm gonna spend as much time with you as I can.
- No.
No, that's only gonna make it worse.
Look, I don't think you realize
how hard this is, Roc.
Our daughter won't even know you.
She deserves to be raised by her father.
Do you realize by doing this,
you're choosing your Uncle Ronnie over your children.
- Man, you don't get it.
Look, my kids are already taken care of, all right.
Just like you will.
- And you don't get it, Roc.
I don't want your money.
I don't need it.
Roc, I need you, please baby, don't do this.
I'm begging you, Roc.
- Why, 'cause you love me?
What, do you love me?
- Stop, I don't know.
I don't know.
I only loved one man and that was my husband.
I've never even been with another man
until I met you.
- Look, if anything changes, I'll let you know.
I can't make any promises.
- Baby, you keep saying that I'm different and I am.
Look at me, Roc, please.
When you say that you want me to save you,
save you from what?
- Man, save me from myself.
- Okay.
Okay, well, so let me do it, please, babe.
Give us more time, Roc.
I know you want this and I know you need this, please.
- Look, I know what I need.
I also know what I don't need, all right.
If anything changes, I'll let you know.
(phone buzzes)
(Desa Rae cries)
- [Gunman 1] You should kill that bitch ass nigga now, man.
- [Gunman 2] You better not move.
(dramatic music)
- All right, what the fuck is this, dawg.
I'm already having a bad ass day.
- Caught this nigga creeping around outside.
You know you been looking for him
since that incident with your bread.
- [Gunman 1] Maybe you can ask this nigga
why he feel brave enough to come around here.
- Roc, I swear I didn't take the money.
I swear I didn't.
Tell these fools we good.
We good, ain't we?
That's why I'm here so we can talk about this shit.
Fuck that nigga, man.
- See that's the problem, though.
I'm already done talking about this shit.
- Please don't do nothing you gonna regret.
I got kids.
My daughter birthday next week.
I didn't take the money.
I could take you to the niggas who did
and I could make sure you get all your money back.
- This nigga lying, Roc.
I'm telling you.
- Dumb motherfucker.
I already got my money back,
all 100 Gs, plus some.
- So we good.
- Yeah, we good.
Matter of fact.
(gun cocks)
Nigga, what day is your daughter birthday on?
- It's on Wednesday.
- And what's her favorite color?
- Purple.
- Nigga, who the fuck you yelling at?
Matter of fact, Craig,
on Wednesday, won't you go find
a nice little purple teddy bear for this nigga.
Deadbeat ass nigga.
Shit, my pops died when I was seven, too.
Must be some lucky kind of number or whatever, right?
- Fall back, nephew.
Don't waste no bullets on this nigga.
We got bigger fish to try.
Besides, I got a lot of heat on me now,
so I don't need no messy shit going on, Roc.
So tuck your toy and let this shit go.
- Guess, it's your lucky day, right.
- [Victim] Thank you, you not gonna regret this.
- Shit, we all lucky.
And how many times I gotta tell you niggas
who's in charge around here.
Shit like this don't go down unless I say so,
so squash this shit and let's go.
You two, Craig, with your simple-minded ass.
- Yeah, you might be the one
in charge around here, Unc,
but I'll make the decisions for this motherfucker.
(gun fires)
All right, clean this shit up.
- Fuck this nigga.
- I'm just glad I didn't go through with that wedding.
You know, she lied to me about having an abortion?
I'm not not happy with our relationship.
- When you said you had something to talk about,
I thought it was about Latrel.
Is this what you came over here to talk to me about?
- I came by to see how things were coming with your job.
Latrel told me you got laid off.
You doing okay financially?
- Yes, I'm fine
and when I need some extra money I will get another job.
In case Latrel told you also,
I'm going up to see him this weekend
and Monica's gonna go with me.
- That's cute.
Is your little thug passion boyfriend going to?
Or is he just gonna stay back
and sell more drugs to kids in the street?
- Well, guess what?
His kid is right here in my belly
and she's gonna be beautiful.
Now, listen, I gotta go.
- What? - We gotta get outta here.
- Hell, nah, Desa Rae.
You pregnant by this fool?
Hell, nah, you gotta be playing.
- You can go in, the door unlocked.
(Desa Rae knocks)
- Mm, Roc, somebody here to see you.
(door slams)
- [Roc] I'm a be all right.
- Hey.
- Hey, what's going on.
- I need to talk to you.
It's really important.
This letter came today.
I want you to open it.
I want you to open it and I want you to read it.
- What is this?
- I sent your information to an art collector
and they are interested in your work, Roc.
You do not have to live like this.
- Damn.
This is crazy.
Hey, I really regret breaking up.
- I know, baby, don't say anything, it's me.
I should have said it at the shop.
I do love you and I don't want you to do this, Roc.
Please, I'm begging you.
Don't do any of this.
- Hey, man, I need you to go out
and get that paperwork you asked about.
Man, you high?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Is this bitch giving you a problem?
- Bitch?
I should slap the-
(Desa Rae screams)
- She's carrying my fuckin' baby, bro.
- The only reason your ass ain't dead is
because you pregnant with his baby.
- Hey, get up outta here, man.
Unc can fuckin' hurt you, dawg.
- You better get control of your bitches, dawg,
I done told you.
Family over everything, nigga.
(Desa Rae cries)
- I'm not coming back here anymore.
I'm not coming to see you in jail.
And you not gonna see your daughter.
You either choose between your Uncle Ronnie and us, Roc.
You can't have both.
I'm sick of it.
Who you with, Roc, him or us?
- Man, I'm always with you,
what you talking about?
- No, you need to choose.
(dramatic music)
- So Your Honor, for the past three days,
we've listened to Ms. Evans make a bunch
of false accusations without any merits.
My client, Ronald J. Dawson,
is not the man that Ms. Evans wants everyone
to believe he is.
Ronald hasn't caused nothing.
Rocky Dawson's on the stand,
now question him.
- Mr. Dawson, approach the stand, please.
Raise your right hand.
State your name for the record.
- Rocky Dawson.
- Mr. Dawson, do you solemnly swear
to tell the truth, the whole truth
and nothing but the truth, so help you God?
- I do.
- [Judge] Have a seat young man.
Counsel, you may proceed.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
Mr. Dawson, I'd like you to take
a few minutes and tell us about Ronnie.
- My uncle was like a father for me.
You know, like the father I never had.
He definitely cared for me more
than anyone else did.
He was always looking out for everybody,
especially all the kids in the neighborhood.
- Mr. Dawson, please tell the truth.
Let's get this evil man put in jail.
- Yes.
- Ms. Evans, another outburst like that
and I will hold you in contempt of court.
Counsel, you may proceed.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
So, as I continue, Mr. Dawson,
I wanted you to tell us
about the type of you and
your uncle's relationship over the years.
Something's happened and you became very upset,
is that correct?
- Yeah, that's correct.
I just saw a lot of opportunity to make some money,
you know what I mean,
to have some doors opened
that probably wouldn't have been opened.
He didn't like the direction I was going in,
but I don't know, I guess I just got greedy
and just stared doing shit.
- Watch it, watch it.
- Things that many would probably disapprove of.
- So what you're saying is the charges
that Ms. Evans are trying to pin
against my client for the past three days
should be directed towards you?
Remember, you're under oath.
To be clear, Mr. Rocky Dawson,
it should be you in jail
for first degree drug trafficking,
assault with a deadly weapon.
Last but not least, tampering and murder?
- Not murder, but everything else, yeah,
I'm 100% responsible for.
My uncle had nothing to do with it.
- Ladies and gentlemen, I think the burden is clear
of who's guilty and who's not.
Justice will finally now be served.
Your Honor, arrest this man.
- Bailiff, take him away.
- Damn.
(somber music)
- Go ahead little, man.
We got you, bro.
(somber music)
(woman cries)
♪ Ah, yeah
♪ Oh, oh
♪ Mm, mm, mm, oh, oh
♪ I've been waitin' my whole life ♪
♪ I been waitin' so long
♪ I feel the storm getting closer ♪
♪ I pray that I'll be strong
♪ Because when it rolls away
♪ The wind it blows away
♪ I'm still here
(phone rings)
- [Recording] Hello, this is a pre-paid collect call from-
(phone beeps)
♪ Always hearing tomorrow
♪ I saw my dreams and made it right now ♪
♪ Without a hat to borrow
♪ Oh, because when it rolls away ♪
♪ The wind it blows away
♪ I'm still here
- In the light of the moon
a little egg laid on a leaf,
see, where's the egg, you see the egg?
That's a egg, say egg.
(phone rings)
Say egg.
Hello?
- [Recording] Hello, this is a pre-paid collect call from.
- [Roc] Roc.
- [Recording] Hello, this is a-
- Yeah, hello?
- What do you want?
- Yeah, I'm trying to figure out
why you ain't answering my calls
or responding to any of my letters.
- I don't know where your letters are
and if you care anything about your daughter,
you wouldn't be in there.
- Did you even get a chance to read them?
- It doesn't matter Roc.
Is there anything else?
- [Roc] I can't believe you still mad.
You know I'm in this motherfucker, right?
Hey.
So you still got feelings or what?
(phone beeps)
(baby coos)
(gentle music)
(dramatic music)
(tires screech)
- Take this street money.
Stay the fuck away from my family.
- That's the last time you gonna try me, bitch.
(dramatic music)
- They look so adorable together.
- Yes, they do.
- I know you're so happy Latrel's coming
to see you more.
- To see me?
No, no, no, no, he comes to see his little sister.
I have a hard time getting him
to go back up to school.
- Isn't it amazing how things turn out?
I mean, you could have never predicted
all of this would happen,
but it's been such a blessing.
- I love it, I'm happy.
- Me, too, man, you got me having baby fever
like I want one.
- You? You want a baby?
- Girl, if I could put the wine down.
- That's not gonna happen.
If you do, just stay away
from those that resemble Roc.
They are big trouble.
I still can't believe we rolled up
on Uncle Ronnie like that.
- Oh, my God, girl,
we are Thelma and Louise, too lit.
- You are my ride or die for sure.
- Every day, all day, mm-hmm.
- He could have killed us.
He's a little crazy.
- Have you spoken to Roc?
- No, it's been a while.
It's been about a month.
The letters stopped, too.
- Are you worried?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I try not to think about it, so.
(baby screams)
Latrel, put her down.
- I got it.
You think you could phone Mandy.
I think she's calling.
- You want me to get your phone?
- [Latrel] Yes, please.
- For Mandy.
- Ooh, as in get out Mandy.
- Yes, girl.
Girl, he's just like his father.
As an athlete, it opens many doors.
- Yeah, and a lot of legs, too.
- I'll be right back.
I'm the mama.
I send you to get stuff.
This girl done called you six times, Latrel.
Them people swear they in love.
Where's the dip.
Here we go.
(Desa Rae screams)
Oh, my God.
- You could've at least invited me to the party.
- I didn't know you were out.
- I'm out now.
Who you with, Des?
- Oh, God.
(dramatic music)
(gun fires)
♪ With the word in a disarray
♪ I wanna hold you real close
♪ Begin to make you feel safe
♪ If love was found
♪ Out on the battlefield
♪ Baby send me, I'll go
♪ Baby there ain't nothing I won't do ♪
♪ Baby I will, baby I will
♪ Baby I will
♪ You know you never gotta ask a question ♪
♪ About my love
♪ Oh
♪ Baby I will, baby I will
♪ Baby know that you ain't never gotta worry, no, no ♪
♪ If I gotta stand down
♪ On the front line
♪ Like a soldier at war for the third time, yeah ♪
♪ I'll put up the fight for you ♪
♪ Baby I will
♪ If I had to go
♪ Out to a third world
♪ Fighting embassies
♪ I ain't letting nothing come between ♪
♪ Me and you
♪ There's no war
♪ I'm not willing to fight for you ♪
♪ As long as that reward is a piece ♪
♪ Of your love, baby yeah
♪ You gotta know
♪ Baby I will, baby I will
♪ Baby I will
♪ Baby you ain't never gotta question my love ♪
♪ Oh
♪ Baby I will, baby I will, baby I will ♪
♪ Baby know that you ain't never gotta worry, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ If I gotta, baby
♪ Like a soldier at war
♪ For the third time
♪ We ain't got no choice baby
♪ I'll put up the fight for you ♪
♪ Baby, I will, baby I will
♪ Baby I will