Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
ALEXIS:
My name is Alexis.
And when I hear certain sounds,
I don't just hear them,
I see them.
And the very first time
it happened,
my whole life changed.
[♪♪♪]
[Song playing]
Always ready to help.
Dad injured?
Well...
[Sighs]
He's fine, right?
Well, physically, yes,
but it hasn't been easy for him.
War is like living
through a brutal accident.
Remember your accident?
That's not the same.
I lost my hearing.
Sweetie,
he needs to feel your love.
[Sighing]
Just be careful, please.
[♪♪♪]
Man,
I wish Jordan can come back,
we're getting killed.
Can we go catch a game?
[Sighs]
Or just wait
for another Space Jam.
...either.
Go to your room.
You all bore him.
At least, me losing my hearing
means I can't hear you.
Kevin, tell your sister
to look at me.
Do what your mother tells you.
YOUNG ALEXIS:
Dad.
Do what your mother tells you.
I can't hear you.
Do as your mother tells you!
[Sobbing]
Do what your mother tells you,
baby.
[Sobbing]
Sorry, honey.
Moody soon-to-be-teen.
Welcome home.
[♪♪♪]
[Yelling]
[Grunting]
[♪♪♪]
[Taking deep breaths]
[Chuckling]
[Gasping]
[♪♪♪]
[Indistinct chatter]
Hey, are you okay?
ALEXIS: I knew that people
would never understand
what I saw or felt,
but all I could think of
was that I needed
to feel it again.
[♪♪♪]
The heartbeat of your work.
I find percussions and drums
to be the bridge
of musical science.
It is the human touch elevated
to a language.
Sounds carry messages
and percussions do that.
And a beat, by the way,
doesn't only come
from instruments,
a beat can come from anywhere.
Like how a heartbeat
is a melody,
each surface has its own tune.
Mr. Bell will be back next week.
We'll resume
our compositions then.
MARIE:
Got you, okay.
Hi.
Yeah!
ALEXIS:
Hey, roomie.
Sorry, I'm late.
[Chuckling]
Oh, yes.
Tonight's gonna be dope.
Mmhmm.
You are one sick puppy,
did you know that?
Yeah.
Mmhmm.
I got the mixer, let me get it.
Okay.
Hmm.
[Marie chuckling]
MARIE:
Nope.
No snooping
at my Frankenstein project.
What are you talking about?
This looks awesome.
[Chuckles]
Anyway, the mixer.
Or as a French would call it
"la table de mixage".
Oh, I learn something new
every day.
Mmhmm.
Uh, that little mixer
is really effective.
Yeah.
Modeled it so that every channel
can be separately recorded
in raw formats.
Yes.
Yeah.
I'll grab the rest
of my favorite wires.
Hell yeah.
Uh, huh-huh.
[Chuckling]
And your weird little experiment
deserves it.
Okay.
I'll see you at 7:00.
Uh.
[Sighing]
No.
No, uh.
[Music playing in background]
Hey, how's it goin'?
Hi.
Thanks, good.
Yeah.
I think it works.
Everything works, yeah, yeah.
So if you have any problems
at all, then just bring it back
and we'll open it up
and take a look.
Uh, yeah, it's total, so yeah.
[Indistinct conversation]
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
[Sighs]
[♪♪♪]
Excuse me?
Can I turn this on?
Yeah.
Do you know how
to work one of those?
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
Just be careful,
it's kind of an oldie.
[Chuckling]
No problem.
[Clearing throat]
Thank you.
It's funny, people usually go
for Star Trek.
You're a total natural.
Thanks for letting me play.
Have a good day.
MUSIC STORE CLERK:
You, too.
Okay.
[Chuckles]
[Clears throat]
Yeah.
You ready?
Thanks for getting me into this.
[Chuckling]
Alright.
So where do you
wanna put the camera?
Mm.
Oh.
Uh, no, wse're not filming.
Only sound.
All we need is a table
and some power.
Hmm, alright, just over here.
You can use that table.
Great, thanks.
Okay.
[Sighing]
[Alexis clears throat]
Yeah, it's great.
Okay, we're all set.
We're recording?
Yep.
Alright, over to you.
We need more.
[Man grunts]
Uh, we need to be able
to hear them properly.
DOMINATRIX:
Back in your lane, young lady.
I know what I'm doing.
It'll be loud enough.
[Grunting]
Back in your lane, lady.
[Chuckling]
[Man grunting]
[Sighing]
[♪♪♪]
Keep going, harder.
DOMINATRIX: We're getting close
to his limit.
Please, this is great.
What else can you use?
You remember the signal.
[Grunting]
Keep going, please.
Harder.
[Man grunting]
ALEXIS:
Harder.
[Grunting]
Why are you stopping?
That's his limit.
He did the signal.
He's fine, I'm not done.
Dude, he's had enough!
We have plenty of material...
I'll tell you
when I got what I need.
Thank you so much for your time.
We'll get out of your hair
in a minute.
[♪♪♪]
MARIE:
You're still not talkin' to me.
We got people to take part
in your sound experiment,
that's what matters.
What?
It's my fault?
The guy had enough.
These people push themselves,
Marie, that's their shtick.
You didn't let me push them.
[Chuckles]
Okay, these people have rules,
the most important being
we respect their limits.
Okay, I know you are this
super-experimental rad artist
with sounds
no one has ever heard of,
but you haven't even listened
to it.
Why would I?
I don't think it worked,
I didn't get enough.
Well, that's what you get
with $100
and people from the internet.
I know, okay?
I just...
I need powerful sounds.
Just listen to it.
Come on.
Please.
Fine.
[Sighing]
See?
[Chuckling]
MARIE:
Fig.
I can work with that.
MARIE:
Yeah?
Yeah, you were right.
Thank you.
[Chuckling]
I couldn't have done it
without you.
I'm so proud of you.
Uh.
Thanks.
[Chuckles]
Um,
I'm gonna let you get to work.
[Clearing throat]
Let me know
if you need anything.
You know where to find me.
Yes, I should be good.
I'll... I'll see you at home.
MARIE:
Okay.
Oh, can I keep the recorder
for a bit?
Of course.
Thanks.
Okay, see you later.
Bye.
[♪♪♪]
Oh!
[Grunts]
[♪♪♪]
[Sighs]
[Man grunting]
[Indistinct speech]
Hey, what's up?
What's your problem?
DRUNK ASSAILANT:
Oh, come on, you're all alone.
Stay the fuck back.
[Chuckling]
You know what I want?
Fuck off!
[♪♪♪]
Now,
you've got what you wanted.
[Grunting]
[Taking deep breaths]
[♪♪♪]
Good morning.
Is Marie here?
Oh, she's in there.
I'm Duke, by the way.
You want a hit on this?
Alexis.
I'm good.
- Hi.
[Chuckling]
You just got in, didn't you?
ALEXIS:
Yeah, pulled an all-nighter.
Yeah, you did.
Uh, sorry, can I still
borrow the recorder and cables?
MARIE:
Yeah, I said it was fine.
Yeah, you did.
[Chuckling]
Come on,
you just wanted a morning hug.
ALEXIS:
Love awkward moments.
[Marie chuckling]
- Good morning.
- Mm, morning
[Chuckling]
Go get some rest.
Okay, yeah.
Your wife?
No,
just my bondage party partner.
Coffee?
Yeah.
Wait.
[Indistinct chatter
in background]
[Taking deep breaths]
DR. SEARS:
So the sound just stopped
and you lost your hearing again?
Yeah, it was abrupt
and I panicked.
Any idea
what triggered the event?
You tell me.
Well, looking
at the tympanic membrane,
the damage remains the same.
As you know,
when you recovered your hearing,
it was because
the connection somehow resumed,
not the membrane healing,
and it won't.
And you also know
the connections
in there are fragile.
It does mean they can come on
and off a small stimulation.
I told you once you're
approaching 30,
more tests
might become necessary
as things tend to escalate.
This might be
an early warning sign.
[♪♪♪]
[Indistinct chatter in distance]
Hi.
What's your name?
What the fuck
are you doing here?
This place is no place
for a young girl.
Let me help you, okay?
Are you hungry?
Here.
Eat this.
You're a sweet girl.
They don't let me talk
to sweet girls no more.
It's okay.
Irene?
[Shushing]
Just eat.
[Coughing]
Just eat, okay?
Just eat.
[Coughing]
[♪♪♪]
Let's get you inside.
[Coughing]
[♪♪♪]
YOUNG ALEXIS:
I can't hear you.
MRS. REEVES:
Welcome home.
BARRY:
Do what your mother tells you!
YOUNG ALEXIS:
Dad, I can't hear you.
[Chuckling]
[♪♪♪]
I shouldn't get up.
[Taking deep breaths]
I need you.
Please, help me.
[Taking deep breaths]
[♪♪♪]
[Grunting]
You know,
I taught a class this week
about how beats are...
[Fred grunting]
A language
to tell stories.
[Sobbing]
[Fred grunting]
[♪♪♪]
[Fred yells]
[Fred grunting]
[Taking deep breaths]
[♪♪♪]
[Yelling]
[Crying]
[♪♪♪]
[Grunting]
[Chuckling]
I'm so proud of you.
[♪♪♪]
[Taking deep breaths]
Oh wow.
[♪♪♪]
[Chuckling]
Havin' a good day, huh?
Yes, I am.
Where have you been
the past couple of days?
You know, working
and experimenting.
Looks like it's paying off.
Mm, Marie.
[Chuckling]
I've been stuck for so long,
but I finally
had a breakthrough today.
I am feeling so inspired.
Well, we should celebrate.
Come.
You know that I want to,
but I'm...
I'm in the flow, I'm not yet...
Oh, come on!
There's lots of people out,
people who love you.
There'll be cute guys,
cute girls.
Oh.
[Sighing]
One for all.
Flattery will get you anywhere.
Fine.
[Chuckling]
I mean
after all I've done for you,
you owe me a drink.
Basically, a musical pawn shop.
[Chuckling]
- Oh.
- Your face.
Oh my God.
Oh.
Fuck you.
[Chuckling]
Fine.
The first drink is on me,
but then you agree
to come with me
to this club
where I'm playing later.
Shut up, that's awesome!
Yes!
Um, I'm gonna invite Duke, too.
Great.
[Indistinct chatter]
This is so exciting!
[Chuckles]
I'm gonna go get drinks, okay?
Cool.
Thanks.
MARIE:
Yeah?
Hey, so I've been meaning to ask
um, Marie says you make these
like dope experimental tracks.
I'm still tryin' to figure out
like my sound.
What's your inspiration?
My family died.
♪ Don't be afraid ♪
♪ When I'm pressin'
against your body ♪
♪ It's only 'cause I wanna be,
I gotta be yours tonight ♪
♪ 'Cause I want you, boy ♪
♪ And I need you, girl,
I should ♪
♪ Get you off of your feet ♪
♪ And switch it up,
keep people dancing ♪
♪ 'Cause I want you, boy ♪
♪ But I need you, girl,
I should ♪
♪ Get you off of your feet ♪
♪ And switch it up,
keep people dancing ♪
[Grunting]
[Taking deep breaths]
♪ Got a secret you can tell me ♪
♪ Close your eyes
if you feel me ♪
♪ It's between you and me, girl ♪
I need you.
♪ Like who really care
what your guy say ♪
♪ I won't melt in the summer ♪
♪ I won't change
with the weather ♪
♪ Go outside with a visor ♪
♪ Shine your light in my world ♪
♪ When I'm pressin'
against your body ♪
♪ You gonna feel some assertion,
but don't be afraid ♪
♪ When I'm pressin'
against your body ♪
♪ It's only 'cause I wanna be,
I gotta be yours tonight ♪
[Indistinct radio chatter]
[♪♪♪]
Speakers.
OFFICER LIN:
Huh?
Those are XLRs
and those are
for speaker cables.
Some drunk hobo nearby said
he heard the music,
only kind of witness.
This place is a wasteland.
It's kind of genius really.
Glad you admire that psycho.
No, I... didn't mean...
SONYA: Lin, bag tag, get the
team to swab all over again.
Take pics of everything.
OFFICER LIN:
Yes, ma'am.
The precision, the overkill.
[Sighing]
It's not over.
[♪♪♪]
No scratching!
Fuckin' asshole.
[Sighs]
[♪♪♪]
[Puffing]
Thank you.
Thanks for your business.
JAROD:
Come again.
Okay, so that is why I wanted
to talk about synesthesia.
If someone is able to see
sound,
then it's no longer just
an auditory experience, right?
It becomes something deeper,
more profound,
more connected
to the world around us.
Are you about to levitate,
Mr. Bell?
[Laughing]
MR. BELL:
Uh, no.
No, actually, I'll wait
till the next lecture
do that for you.
Uh, alright,
so in the last 10 minutes
or so that we have left
I wanna talk about an email
that I got from someone
who will remain anonymous.
Uh, last week apparently,
Alexis talked about beat making
as a form
of human communication,
human language, right?
Yep.
Maybe we could
turn the class over to Alexis
and let her finish her lecture.
- MR. BELL: Alexis?
- Hmm?
MR. BELL: You wanna take over
and finish your lecture?
Oh, sure.
MR. BELL:
Great.
Um, I'm not prepared.
No, you'll do great.
- I get to sit.
- But... sure.
Okay, um, help me out, guys.
My job might be on the line.
[Laughing]
It is.
[Chuckling]
You know what?
Let's try something else.
I'm going to play you guys
something experimental
that I've been working on.
Alright, let's give it a listen,
guys.
[♪♪♪]
What the fuck?
Are those animals
being slaughtered?
MR. BELL:
Alright, alright, thank you.
Everybody,
thanks for your feedback.
Let's just stop for a second.
Alexis, can you turn that off,
please?
Can you please stop and...
and sorry, but what...
[Chuckles]
What on Earth was that?
Yeah, okay, I understand
that might be
a little bit different
than what you guys
have heard before.
Is this a joke?
No, look, let me explain.
What's wrong with you?
[♪♪♪]
Hey, babe, are you home?
Are you okay?
Phew, okay.
ALEXIS: Hey, you've reached
Alexis, leave a message.
Hey, babe um, I heard
what happened in class.
Students are fucking jerks.
Um, call me back
when you get this please, okay?
Bye.
[Sighing]
Yes!
[Clears throat]
Hi.
You're the person
who put the note
on the noticeboard
for a... for a tenor singer?
JAROD:
I'm Jarod.
Hi.
Oh, I'm so glad you found it.
I was worried no one
was gonna come.
So uh, what is it?
What's the pay?
Uh, 100 bucks, couple hours max,
testing material.
We are going
to explore your range.
Cool.
Left some food for the cat,
so I'm good on time.
Sweet.
150.
Oh.
Uh, let's see.
That's 100 and...
...31, 2... 132.
Alright.
Great.
Where do you want me?
Head into the booth, please.
Close the door.
And don't worry
about headphones.
Alright, go ahead, warm up,
vocalize
you know,
whatever your routine is.
Oh, well, I like to vocalize
to our national anthem.
Great.
JAROD:
♪ O say can you see ♪
♪ By the dawn's early light ♪
♪ What so proudly we hailed ♪
♪ At the twilight's
last gleaming ♪
♪ Whose broad stripes
and bright stars ♪
♪ Through the perilous fight ♪
♪ O say does that
star-spangled banner yet wave ♪
♪ O'er the land of the free ♪
♪ And the home of the brave ♪
That was beautiful.
What are those?
They will record the music
as it travels through you.
Your emotions, your energy,
it'll capture all of that.
Never heard of that.
[Chuckles]
Okay.
Can I put these on you?
Sure.
Okay, so this is gonna go
on your temple.
Relax your face.
[Sighing]
Okay.
JAROD: Hey, I should charge you
extra for this, you know?
What?
I should charge you extra
for this, you know?
[Alexis chuckles]
That's not a joke.
Do you know Amazing Grace?
[Chuckles]
I'm serious.
Yeah, I mean, who doesn't?
Uh, fun memories.
My brother was so whiny,
like every time he was sick,
he would not shut up
until I sang it to him.
Oh, that's really sweet.
[Blows air]
Music heals all, right?
Oh, no, no, no, he did it
to put me on show
in front of our mom.
[Scoffs]
Conniving little cunt.
Well, whatever, it inspires you
so I would love to hear it.
♪ Amazing grace ♪
Oh, no, stop.
Uh, humming first please,
I'll cue you into the lyrics.
[Humming]
ALEXIS:
Slower!
[Humming]
Okay, lyrics now.
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
JAROD:
♪ I once wa... ♪
Somethin' wrong?
No, don't stop,
please keep going.
♪ I once was lost ♪
♪ But now I'm found ♪
JAROD:
♪ Was blind ♪
♪ But now I see ♪
[Grunting]
Uh, I think there's some...
Thing wrong
with your device uh...
There's a electrical feedback
happening on this...
Keep singing, Jarod.
Hey, can you...
Can you get me out
of this thing?
Hey, fucking...
[Jarod grunting]
Trust the experiment,
keep singing.
[Yelling]
Hey, what is this fucking glue?
[Jarod grunting]
Fuckin' bitch,
turn this fuck thing o...
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
[♪♪♪]
So what have we got?
His head exploded.
Took two dozen shots
of various residues on the walls
and floor.
The victim's name
is Jarod Korkansky
according to an expired
driver's license in his wallet.
OFFICER DAVIS:
e's a record store owner.
How does a head explode?
Not sure.
Those electrodes,
they're all over.
Some attached to debris
and some to him.
Not connected
to anything, though.
Forensics?
The whole soundboard
was doused in bleach.
I'm surprised
it didn't catch fire.
So we got nothing.
I'm sending all DNA samples
to the lab.
We'll see if any
don't match the victim.
Great, I won't hold my breath.
Something to do
with the factory?
Definitely.
[♪♪♪]
Hello?
[Sighing]
Where are you?
Hi!
Oh!
Hi, what are you doing here?
Um, I was in the neighborhood
and I thought maybe you wanted
to get some lunch.
I can't.
Sorry.
[Chuckles]
[Sighing]
Are you sure it's healthy
for you to be spending
this much time here?
It's fine.
If you don't mind I really need
to get back to work.
[Sighing]
Okay, I'm just... I'm...
I'm really worried about you.
You haven't texted me back,
you haven't been home
in two days.
Well, I'm fine.
You're fine?
Yeah, seriously, I'm fine.
I really need to get back to it.
I'll see you later.
I'm gonna be out late tonight,
so lock the door.
Okay, I'm gonna be out, too.
With Duke?
MARIE:
Why don't you like him?
It's not like we're serious.
Okay.
Bye then.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Chuckling]
What's up?
Hey.
Hey, I'm surprised you called.
I thought you were busy.
I'm glad I did.
You seem enthralled
by the works.
Yeah.
I need a mortgage
for one of those.
I'm here to support a friend,
but I'd much rather
spend the evening with you.
Oh, so this is a date?
Well.
[Indistinct chatter]
What's that you're drinking?
This is a pinot noir.
Oh.
Well, garçon, I'll have
a pinot noir, s'il vous plaît.
Oh, lady of the world.
[Chuckling]
[Indistinct chatter]
So no bondage party partner
tonight?
Uh, no.
She's working,
so... yeah.
But she seems nice.
Yeah, she's my little weirdo.
[Indistinct chatter]
[♪♪♪]
She mentioned something to me
about like her family dying.
Yeah, um...
[Chuckles]
It's fucking horrible.
She was like 10
and all she has left is this RV
and a garage downtown.
Fuck me.
That's dark.
[Sighs]
I need more wine.
[Chuckling]
Yes, me, too!
Sorry, that was really loud.
Um, a bottle please, quickly.
WAITER:
Okay.
[Marie chuckling]
Bad luck.
[Chuckling]
Um, sorry, I'm gonna be back
in like two minutes.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
[♪♪♪]
[Slurping]
Hey, sorry,
I need like two more minutes.
He's being a stickler.
I'm really trying
to get my hands on that.
Okay, go for it.
[Takes a deep breath]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Slurping]
[♪♪♪]
ART GALLERY ATTENDEE 1:
Somebody do something!
ART GALLERY ATTENDEE 2:
Stop scaring him!
[♪♪♪]
[Screaming]
ART GALLERY ATTENDEE 3:
Jesus Christ.
I don't know why you're
standing here,
get out of the way!
Oh.
Oh my God.
[Indistinct speech]
Oh my God, oh my God.
[Indistinct chatter]
Somebody call 911!
What the fuck are you doing?
[Screaming]
[Indistinct radio chatter]
SONYA:
That's it for now.
If you remember anything else,
please contact me.
Uh, can I go now?
Can we drive you anywhere?
No, I'm gonna walk.
Thanks.
Please call me
even if you just need to talk.
Okay, thanks.
[Sighing]
[Indistinct radio chatter]
[Sobbing]
[Sniffling]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[Sighing]
[Chuckling]
What a fucking date, huh?
[Sighing]
Did the cops make you feel
like a fucking suspect?
Yeah, a bit.
[Sighing]
They have to do that
with everyone I guess.
It's like
just rule out the possibilities.
[Sighing]
Did you see Alexis in there?
What?
I don't know what I saw,
it was crazy,
but I saw a girl
by the fire escape
like staring at the harpist.
Looked like her.
Did you say this shit
to the cops?
No, of course, I didn't.
'Cause you
can't unsay that shit.
I mean we were drinking wine,
we were talking
about her family being murdered,
maybe you were projecting,
but that shit's fucking nuts,
you can't fucking say that.
What were you saying?
I didn't see her then.
I couldn't have seen her.
I gotta go.
- I gotta go.
- Marie!
- No.
- DUKE: Marie, wait!
- No!
[Indistinct radio chatter]
[Indistinct whispering]
[♪♪♪]
Clear the scene.
Lin, pictures.
[♪♪♪]
Bag.
[Grunting]
[Coughing]
[Sighing]
ALEXIS:
Mornin'!
What are you doin' up so early?
I heard some noise and...
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
It was horrible.
What happened?
I went to this art gallery
opening with Duke last night,
and there was this...
this harpist, and she like...
She like cut her fingers
and her arms on the strings.
That's insane.
Are you okay?
And it was a panic.
There was blood everywhere,
and Duke and I were
the only people
who were helping her.
Fuck.
You weren't there last night,
were you?
I know it sounds crazy,
but...
Duke said he saw you
in the crowd
and I told him he was
a fuckin' lunatic, but...
Um,
I don't think he's a lunatic,
but I was not there.
No.
My RV and my shitty salad
did not feel
like a fancy gallery opening,
that's for sure.
I...
[Sighing]
[Sniffling]
How do you get it out
of your head?
I don't know.
I wish I did.
I just really
don't wanna be alone right now.
Okay, come here.
Oh.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It's... you're fine.
I'm such a mess.
Stop.
[Chuckling]
[Sniffling]
There you go.
Ugh, Duke.
[Sniffling]
He's saying
he can't sleep either,
he's so sorry, blah, blah, blah.
MARIE:
Wow, he heard that she survived.
Oh my God.
What a relief.
[Sighing]
I wanna get some more...
some more hot water.
I'm going.
[Grunting]
Fuck.
[♪♪♪]
[Clears throat]
God, I'm so tired.
You should take a nap.
You know, I have an idea.
I have to run a few errands
for Mr. Bell, okay,
and then I'll pick up some food,
and we can watch a movie,
and in the meantime
just get some sleep, okay?
No, I'd like to come.
No, it's okay,
I'll be right back.
See you later.
[Kissing]
Okay.
[Sniffling]
[Sighing]
Hey, Duke.
What are you doin' here?
Marie, text me.
Oh, okay.
She actually just fell asleep
in my RV.
She's... she's really shook
after what happened last night.
Yeah.
[Sighing]
Look, last night was fucked up.
I do really care
about Marie, though.
She really needs us right now.
[Sighing]
I'm really glad you came.
[♪♪♪]
Marie told me about this place.
It's cool.
Fuck!
[Grunting]
[Gasping]
[Taking deep breaths]
[Grunting]
I don't wanna do this.
This was not part of my plan.
[Yelling]
But I will not let you stop me
from completing it.
[Grunting]
[Yelling]
[Taking deep breaths]
Fuck you!
[Grunting]
It won't be for nothing.
[Duke yelling]
You made me do this.
[Grunting]
[♪♪♪]
[Yelling]
[Duke grunting]
[Taking deep breaths]
[♪♪♪]
[Yelling]
[Sobbing]
[Grunting]
[Laughing]
[Duke grunting]
[Taking deep breaths]
[♪♪♪]
Thank you.
[Taking deep breaths]
[♪♪♪]
Hey, babe, you back?
[Sighing]
[♪♪♪]
Ugh.
What the fuck.
Hi.
Oh shit, sorry, I got swamped.
It's okay.
Are those new?
No.
They're from my family's
living room.
- Oh.
- I had them serviced.
Don't they look good?
Yeah.
How are you feeling?
Uh, better I guess.
I think it was a relief knowing
that the girl's alive.
I bet.
I need to talk to you
about something.
Over there.
Okay.
What's up?
Okay, um, don't be mad,
but I went into your room
looking for you,
and I saw this old iPod
on a nightstand,
and I thought you know,
maybe your music
could calm me down.
But on it was this recording
of a boy being punched
and it was weird,
and it was like a... a drum beat,
but on a kid,
and then there was
this little girl giggling,
and I thought maybe
that was you.
I mean it reminded me
of the other night
with the couple.
MARIE:
Is that like your thing?
No.
[Chuckles]
The couple was different.
They were enjoying themselves.
MARIE:
Yeah, but the little boy wasn't.
I was young.
The orphanage
was a fucked up place
and when kids heard
I killed my dad, they...
Kids are assholes.
Yeah.
And that boy was a bully.
But you were...
you were enjoying it.
Yeah, I was
enacting my revenge
and making music.
In my young mind,
that was cathartic.
I was experimenting.
I'm sorry that happened to you.
Thanks.
I'm sorry again
that I've been so off
with you lately.
[Chuckling]
It's okay.
I just...
[Grunting]
Oh, I missed you.
I missed you, too.
I need you
more than you realize.
[Chuckling]
Me, too, obviously.
I mean it.
I'm not very good
at letting people in.
I know.
Shut up.
[Chuckling]
I'm just... I'm just...
[Taking deep breaths]
I'm so distracted trying
to create and...
And deliver this music that
has been burning in my soul.
Mmhmm.
And with the students,
and I found out I might be
losing my hearing again, and I...
Wait, wait, wait, what?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
Thanks.
Okay, well,
I'm gonna be here with you,
and we're gonna take care of it,
we're gonna figure out
what to do.
It's gonna be okay,
I mean whatever you need, okay?
Thank you.
[♪♪♪]
I love you.
[Chuckling]
I love you, too.
Oh.
Oh my God.
[Taking deep breaths]
[Screaming]
MARIE:
Oh my God!
Oh my God, what the fuck!
MARIE:
Oh my God, oh my God!
I wish you hadn't seen that.
Oh my God, what the fuck!
[Sobbing]
Excuse me,
do you need some help?
[Taking deep breaths]
Welcome back, sleepyhead.
Let's see.
Alright.
Lavaliers, two wireless mics.
One's checked out
by documentary team,
the other by... oh.
Who?
Oh, it's uh, Marie Sotker,
she runs the workshop.
Uh, she checked out the mic
as well as some
recording equipment.
[Chuckles]
Excuse me.
Fuentes.
Okay, I'm on my way.
[Taking deep breaths]
Why did you kill Duke?
Duke isn't dead.
[Chuckling]
MARIE:
What?
He's part of my music.
Your fuckin' music?
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Untie me!
MARIE:
I wish you could hear
what I hear.
Help, please!
[Shushing]
[Taking deep breaths]
No one can hear you, okay?
[Grunting]
MARIE:
Please.
I have to get back to work now.
MARIE:
Please.
Please, please, please,
let me go.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
Please, please, Alexis,
what are you trying to do?
What are you doing?
[Marie grunting]
MARIE:
Please.
It's okay.
MARIE:
Please.
[Sobs]
It's okay.
[Grunting]
[♪♪♪]
Love you.
We don't have much time.
Has anyone had access
to your harp?
I mean I just had it serviced.
By who?
Alexis.
DAISY:
Alexis Reeves.
She teaches
at the university I go to.
Did you leave your harp
with her?
DAISY:
Yes.
[♪♪♪]
[Indistinct radio chatter]
Clear!
[Takes a deep breath]
Lin,
send forensics to the garage,
we have a body.
No, it's a man.
He was at the art gallery.
Otherwise, the garage is empty.
No RV here.
She might be on the run.
Put a BOLO out.
[♪♪♪]
DISPATCHER: Suspect RV located
at Dockweiler Beach.
Proceed with caution.
Copy.
Unit 88 en route.
[♪♪♪]
[Indistinct chatter
and laughter]
[Indistinct chatter]
[♪♪♪]
[Taking deep breaths]
Fuck.
Fuck!
[Indistinct chatter]
[Grunting]
Fuck.
[Duke grunting]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Screaming]
[Chuckling]
[Taking deep breaths]
Marie.
[Chuckling]
Hey, are you okay?
[Grunting]
STRANGER:
Hey.
What the...
I'm gonna call 911.
[Screaming]
[Indistinct chatter]
[♪♪♪]
[Screaming]
[Grunting]
[Sobbing]
[Indistinct radio chatter]
[♪♪♪]
[Crying]
SONYA:
Police!
Out of the way!
Get the fuck away!
Marie, it's Detective Fuentes.
Please, stop moving.
Stay where you are,
I'm here to help you.
[Grunting]
Where's Alexis?
Stop, let me take a look
at what she's done to you.
[♪♪♪]
[Grunting]
Stay with me.
No.
Wake up.
Marie!
[♪♪♪]
[Indistinct chatter]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[♪♪♪]