Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
But this city of Houston...
This state of Texas...
This country of the United
States was not...
built by those who
waited, and rested.
Is it that man in his quest for
knowledge and progress
is determined
and cannot be deterred.
The exploration of space
will go ahead whether
we join in it or not.
And it is one of
the great adventures..."
"It's one small step for
man..."
"No national conflict
in outer space..."
"One giant leap for mankind."
"It's hazards are
hostile to us all.
"Its conquest deserves
the best of all mankind..."
Pandemonium has swept across
the globe as reports come in
that an asteroid has collided
with the moon,
knocking it on a
trajectory towards earth.
Emergency lockdowns are
being imposed in major cities
as law enforcement struggles
to maintain control
of the escalating chaos amongst
fear-stricken citizens.
Many countries have reported
power grid disruptions,
major earthquakes and
tidal flooding
along coastal cities
with many forced
to evacuate and
seek higher ground.
Increased theological activity
and volcanic eruptions
have caused extensive damage
to cities and communities
along major fault lines.
The moon is expected
to collide with the earth
in less than three hours.
And we will continue to see
the increased effects
of its gravity as it
approaches our atmosphere.
The outlook of survival
for our species
and the continued existence of
planet earth looks grim, but...
Hey, Jim...
Our field reporters are
already starting to...
Is this thing for real?
NATO and cooperating
governments comparing data,
joining forces to determine
how and if
a disaster of
this magnitude...
[cellphone rings]
This is Captain Lawson.
Paul's coming to airlift you
to the XVision Spaceport
in Nevada to stop this thing.
You are recommissioned
to fly with
the XVision space fleet
effective immediately.
Well, tell Global Defense
we face total annihilation
in less than two hours.
NASA's initial projection of
the mission window is 3.5.
No, Colonel, this isn't
some meteor in Tunguska.
The sheer scale of
this will wreak havoc
before it even strikes.
Gravitational fluctuations,
earthquakes,
volcanic eruptions,
E.M.P.s
all around the world.
And if the moon
reaches our atmosphere,
friction will
super-heat the air
and incinerate everything
on earth.
You get to XVision ASAP.
Paul's responsibility is
to brief you on the rest.
Hey, Jumbo.
Good to see 'ya.
Come on, we gotta go.
Hey, who's that?
My brother.
Come on.
[rumbling]
Whoa, whoa!
Was that because of the moon?
No. Gravity disruptions are
causing the earthquakes.
Come on, Bob.
We'll get you to the base.
My tab for the last two weeks.
[rumbling]
Oh!
[shouts]
We gotta help him.
No!
- Help me get him outa here!
- There's no time.
[moans]
Bobby, I'm gonna
get you outta here!
All right, grab my hand.
Come on?
I gotta pull you now!
[shouts]
Come on!
- [grunting]
- Come on, Bob.
Soak the gauze in antiseptic.
Oh, Jim, it hurts...
Hang in there, Bobby.
Look, Jim, I hate to say it,
but you were right
about everything.
I mean, everything.
The size of the asteroid,
when it would actually
strike the moon.
You called all of it.
- Keep feeding it to me.
- Okay.
Look, I might not get another
chance at this to apologize.
Jim, it wasn't your fault,
your co-pilot's death.
Look, we don't have time
for ancient history right now.
It's not ancient history, Jim.
It's only been a year.
And, look, if I had a
time machine, I would go back
and I would...
I should have listened
to your report, okay?
Jim, it wasn't you that
crashed your lander.
It was gravity from
a distant asteroid.
- We know...
- Just knock it off!
Look, I'm trying
to apologize here!
Like when you reported
that it was a year away
from striking the moon,
I should've never
had you discharged, okay?
It's my fault.
[alarm sounds]
God.
[sighs]
Hey, hey, hey, stay with me.
Yeah, I don't do blood.
Is Mom safe?
How are your wife and kids?
Yeah, Mom's safe.
I had our office in D.C.
take Mom down to the Pentagon.
Juni and the kids are there too.
I didn't have the heart
to tell them that,
if we can't stop this thing, it
doesn't matter where they are.
But, uh... Stacey's safe too.
Yeah, her new boyfriend took her
down to the Camp Pendleton Base.
Good.
Hand me the tape.
All right, we've got
about 15 minutes
before we reach the base.
Admiral Keller, this is Colonel
Hauser, Pentagon Command.
It's my understanding that
Paul is currently en route
with Jim Lawson
and you are keeping tabs
on their progress, correct?
That is correct.
We are currently tracking
them via satellite and have
an ETA of approximately
15 minutes.
Good. As you liaison
to the D.O.D.,
I've given you a lot of latitude
in developing your program,
but today I am assuming full
command of your department,
do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
As of now, our databases
are synced so that we
are both tracking
Lawson's progress
and the path of the Moon
in real time.
Communication interruptions
are inevitable.
We will
attempt to cover setbacks
relative to Operation
Godfather.
All pilots are standing by
on threat level Delta.
Am I gonna be okay, Jim?
Well, I stopped
most of the bleeding.
Look, we have one hour
and 42 minutes
'til the moon reaches
the atmosphere.
Well, Hauser recommissioned me.
So you obviously need me to do
something your team can't do.
As hard as it is for me
to admit, yeah, we do.
As soon as you were discharged,
NASA and JPL still insisted
on using your antimatter engine
design for our drone fleet.
Now, given your reputation
Hauser was reluctant,
but NASA pushed her.
30 minutes before I saw you,
Hauser ordered us to launch
a drone fleet into orbit
to try and stop the moon.
So you're using
antimatter engines as bombs?
It's not gonna work.
No, not bombs, Jim.
NASA, the DOD, the entire
world is scraping
the bottom of the barrel
to try and stop the moon.
I mean, nukes won't stop it,
an exploding antimatter
engine won't stop it.
Where are we going, Jim?
I just need to know
so I can tell
some friends and some family.
Look, you're going to a
base called XVision.
You'll be safe there.
Yeah, I know what XVision is.
What I don't know is how are
you planning to stop this thing?
Look, I saw the news.
We're all gonna die, aren't we?
No.
Look, you'll be safe
at the base, okay?
And we do have a way
to stop the moon.
How are you gonna
stop the moon?
That's not even possible.
[gasps]
It is possible.
We have a spacecraft
with an engine on it
with special fuel
called "antimatter".
We're talking to
the military right now
on how to turn it on and start
a reaction to stop the moon.
He's talking about
a huge nuclear bomb!
No. I'm not talking about
a huge nuclear bomb.
All right, let me dumb
this down to you, Bob.
Imagine a racetrack, okay?
But, instead,
it's a closed tube.
And the atoms are cars running
in the opposite directions.
Now when they crash
into each other,
they explode and release energy.
Now that energy...
Bob, pay attention, please...
now that energy creates a thrust
kind of like a jet engine.
Now there's these little things
in the space called "neutrinos"
that are floating around
that will trigger the reaction.
They're gonna be acting
like the springs
that launch the cars
around the track.
And Hauser remembered what
you said a year ago,
that if somebody
deliberately destroys
the engine's cadmium
regulator...
A bombardment of neutrinos will
run the reaction out of control.
That's it.
So you're gonna
overload an engine,
create a black hole and
pull the moon back into orbit.
That's the plan.
Hold on.
A black hole, that's gonna
destroy everything, won't it?
No, Bob, it's not gonna
destroy everything.
There's places on earth
like the one in Switzerland
where they have the large Hadron
Collider.
They split atoms every single
day to create many black holes.
This is not good.
Look, just calm down.
Calm down, Bob!
If you keep exerting yourself,
you're gonna make
your injuries even worse.
Calm down?
This is all your fault!
Jim told me all about it!
Bob, look, relax!
Even if they had more time,
they know this is
just strategic suicide.
Yeah, it was dead last
on their list.
But they have no other
choice and no time, Jim.
Admiral Keller, we have a visual
on some of the drone's damage.
Are we certain that the
antimatter engine
affixed to the top of the
drone is still functional?
Affirmative, the antimatter
engine is functional
but it is programmed
to conserve power
and send a distress signal
if the drone
becomes terminally damaged.
And Paul Lawson's plan...
I have a room full of trigger
happy Joint Chiefs
still doubtful of
our proposed fix.
A nuclear strike will
not stop the Moon.
Clearing the lunar asteroids
with conventional missiles
and using the antimatter drive
to create a Black Hole
is the only way forward.
Okay, but if you don't
launch before an E.M.P
or magnetic pole reversal,
your missiles will be disabled.
The mission rides on you,
Admiral.
Five minutes after launch,
the meteor's destroyed all
the drones except for one.
Now it's dead in space on the
edge of the moon's far side.
But its antimatter engine
is sending
a distress signal right now.
They need someone
who'll reactivate it.
No, they need you
to reactivate it.
Our engineers are somewhat
familiar with it
and they could do basic
diagnostic tests and controls.
But you're the expert
on how it's built.
Jim, you're the only one
that can guarantee
that the reaction will
run out of control.
We're already encountering
E.M. disruptions.
They're only going to intensify.
So I'm sure the Pentagon's
planning a strike?
Yeah.
Hauser's coordinating a global
conventional weapon strike
into a lunar debris field
to clear a path for you
to reach the stalled drone.
And XVision will provide
a space fleet
leading you right into orbit.
But as the moon gets closer,
it's gonna reverse
the earth's magnetic pulse,
detonating the
missiles prematurely.
Okay, we have to ensure that
my launch precedes that
so we don't
compromise the mission.
It's not my first rodeo.
We've timed it so by the time
you get in your spacecraft,
the missiles will launch.
By the time you get to orbit,
they will dissipate,
leaving you a clear path
right to the stalled drone.
All right. Make sure Hauser
uses the Pentagon's
Colossus satellite dish
to maintain communications.
They'll cut through most
of the magnetic noise.
Colossus satellite dish
will already
be aligned to your jet path.
I got it.
All right.
One more thing.
Under no circumstances,
can Global Defense
change your mind
about a nuclear option.
A nuke and its gamma rays
will fry me and the spacecraft
and the mission ends.
Well, Hauser stopped all
that talk... for now.
Although China and
Russia are considering
a nuclear strike regardless.
[sighs]
Of course.
Yeah, it's the Russians.
What do you expect?
If it wasn't for XVision
and NASA's global reputation,
hell, they might not
have held off at all.
[rumbling]
Hold on!
We're about 30 miles out
from base.
That power surge
blew the circuit.
It damaged the propeller.
Damn!
You ever flown these
things before?
It's just basic aeronautics.
Roll, pitch, yaw.
All right.
The rotor's running 19,000 rpm.
Well, we have to equalize it.
- Where's the main circuit?
- It's right here.
The drone's default is
arc flight at 260 knots.
We're not flying coast to coast.
We don't need to account
for the earth's curvature.
There.
All right, I turned off the arc.
That stopped an rpm increase
to the other three rotors.
Now they can match the damaged
rotor without damaging our ETA.
Good.
You know, you place way too much
blind faith in these machines.
Yeah, well, I guess it could be
another thing we disagree on.
- Lawson to Base!
- [static]
Repeat, Lawson to Ba...
Lawson to Base!
Repeat! Damn it!
The E.M.P.s are already
getting our satellites.
Or they could have been
struck by lunar asteroids.
Yeah, that could be it.
[explosion]
No! No!
[alarm sounds]
Oh, God!
Jim!
Lawson to Base, come in!
Lawson to Base, do you hear me?
Lawson to Base!
[grunts]
Oh, sh...
Paul, you okay?
Ah! Ah!
Buckle up, we're going down!
Oh, Jim!
Jim!
[explosion]
Let's stop here.
This is Private
First Class Malcolm
requesting emergency evac.
Over.
This is Squadron 229.
We have a report of major
damage to Camp Pendleton.
Camp Pendleton was just
destroyed in a major earthquake.
Requesting emergency evac
to the nearest bunker.
Evac denied, we are under
strict orders
to only address the
most dire threats.
We're also getting reports
the earthquake triggered
a massive tsunami.
You will need to get
to high ground immediately.
229, we are en route
to a communications hub
to maintain
the southwest network.
I understand, private,
but all units
are for essential support only.
Unless you're directly
supporting the Pentagon,
we cannot evac. Copy?
This is communications support
for the entire region.
Denied, private.
We have direct orders from DOD
that all assets
are dedicated
to the larger threat.
Hey, tell them you're traveling
with Stacey Lawson.
I'm Jim Lawson's wife.
He's the astronaut they
recruited for their mission.
229, I have Stacey Lawson
accompanying me.
She is astronaut
Jim Lawson's wife
and Jim Lawson
is mission critical.
Denied, Private Ninan.
Command says she's not
mission critical.
I'm sorry, there are
no available units
for a one-off rescue.
Are you really
Jim Lawson's wife?
I am...
Or was.
We separated.
[sighs]
Well...
They have
a communications dish
outside the Pentagon
called Colossus.
It's huge.
It transmits deep into space.
But with the fragments of the
moon deflecting the signal,
they'll need us
to reroute all the hubs
across the country to boost
their signal, including ours.
That's what this is for.
It'll convert
our regional signal
into something they can use.
You ready to keep running?
Absolutely.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
All right.
So base still has our
approximate location.
As soon as they see
a distress signal,
they send us
a rescue unit, so...
Thermal imaging
should still be able
to pick us up on the ground.
But they're gonna need
a clear place to land.
Let's get out in the open.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
There goes our rescue detail.
The EM disturbances
must be getting worse.
- They look like our UMVs.
- Glad no-one was on board.
Man, if we don't get you
airborne soon, we're done.
Yeah. If we don't get
a missile strike,
our chances of success
are cut in half. Come on.
Come on what?
Base has got to be
about five miles away.
I think we're about a mile
from George's mechanic.
George's mecha... what?
Dad's Air Force buddy?
Yeah, the guy who fixes your
base's cars for a handshake.
That was some
sweet deal you made.
We can use his phone,
grab one of his cars.
Let's go.
[sighs]
I hate running.
- Hey.
- God...
What are you doing?
- What?
- What is that?
I don't like hair in my face.
You carry that thing with you?
- Yeah.
- It's very fashionable.
Oh, sweet boots.
You get 'em at Costco?
I hope it makes you run faster.
Come on, Sally!
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Oh...
Oh, I felt all that.
How long did that take us?
What?
How long did it take us?
Six minutes.
That's not even that bad.
Let's keep going.
Let's go. Come on.
- [gun cocks]
- Whoa, whoa!
You're not running.
You're emptying your wallets,
giving your money to J.J. here.
And then you're
getting zip-tied.
Look, we don't have
any time for this.
- Okay, we got...
- [grunts]
- Hey!
- All right, all right.
All right.
The only way you two clowns
are out this far
is if you're working for
that Air Force Base.
You know, we got your
little alert back in town.
And we know you're lying
about the end of the world.
You got us, okay?
We work for the air force...
Move, and I will blow your
brains all over this ravine!
I knew your private military
was out here
trying to take over
this whole region.
I read about it
online for years now.
We don't know anything
about that, okay?
We're just trying to get
to the base to fix it.
Hands up!
We're just trying to get
to get to the base
to fix it, all right?
Wait a second...
[laughs]
Hey, Annie.
Look who it is.
It's that CEO.
That's him.
Look, we don't want any trouble.
Put your wallet on the ground!
Both of you!
All right, all right, all right.
Now!
Guys like you, Elon Musk,
Mark Zuckerberg,
pigs feeding off society,
crushing our brains.
You had your time lying to us,
lying about taking
expeditions to the moon.
Yeah, we've been
watching you, too.
We know you been keeping tabs on
every citizen in this country.
[chuckles]
So why don't you tell me?
How does it feel, Paul Lawson?
J.J., I knew we would
find private military
out here patrolling.
Now's the time.
Take a video.
The revolution starts here.
Guys, we are
a spacecraft company, okay?
There really is a threat to the
United States, the whole world!
He's lying, J.J.
Good thing I'm recording this.
Oh, oh, wait!
Don't kill us!
Paul, the bullies when
you were eight, you remember?
- You two shut up!
- Shut up!
Hey!
Wait, wait, wait!
What?
How does that work?
I don't know,
you yell loud enough,
they think you gonna
tell 'em something important.
Worked when you were
eight, worked now.
[laughs]
Lose that ridiculous
beanie, will you?
Keeps my hair outta my face.
This shop is just through
this clearing.
We're kind of in the middle
of nowhere.
[rumbling, creaking]
Oh, ho!
There's George's shop!
Keep going!
God damn!
George!
Hey, George!
Get us a car.
I'll call the base.
George!
Hey! George!
Hey, it's Jimmy Lawson!
Got anything?
Yeah, it's working.
We gotta be close to
an hour ETA for impact.
Hour and 16 minutes 'til
it reaches the mesosphere.
Exhibition... this
is Operation Godfather.
Get me the Command Center.
Lawson, Admiral Keller here.
We lost you on radar.
I'm on the line with Colonel
Hauser at the Pentagon.
Jim and I need a rescue ASAP.
We lost your GPS on our
Colossus Dish minutes ago.
Keller, get Lawson to base
before these electromagnetic
pulses get worse.
We sent out rescue helicopters,
but their guidance systems
went out of control and crashed.
We sent out two more.
Both those transports
have since crashed.
Have your flight captain
take the XVision fleet
to your underground bunker
to shield them
from the electromagnetic pulses.
Yes, ma'am.
Is the antimatter engine
on the stranded drone
still sending a signal?
Affirmative.
What's the mission status?
I have word from the president
and the Joint Chiefs
that China and Russia
are synchronized
to launch their nuclear payload.
Once they detonate,
Jim will have a safe path
to reach the drone.
Jim and I are headed
to the base ASAP.
We gotta get Jim
here now, Paul.
Threat Response
reported electrical damage
to our Colossus Dish.
The longer we delay,
the less chance we have
to assist if our
guidance system fails.
I understand.
Hey, George!
You here?
Hey, George?
Come on, George.
And NASA's reporting such
a dense lunar asteroid field
that the pathway will
close roughly
one minute after the strike.
So Jim has to follow directly
behind the strike zone
to avoid destroying
the antimatter engine.
[rumbling]
Oh!
[Jim shouts]
Paul?
Paul, are you there?
Come in, Paul!
I'm here.
These earthquakes
are getting worse.
Get here now while
you still can!
Jim and I are headed
to the road ASAP.
Once we get on the road,
I need all defensive personnel
to maintain communication
on an open channel.
I have zero
digital communication,
repeat, zero digital
communication.
I need live updates.
Copy that.
You will have them.
Paul!
George!
[grunts]
Jimmy? Is that you?
Pull yourself out when I lift!
Now!
- [grunts]
- Come on!
Jimmy!
Jim?
Paul!
- Oh, shit!
- Come on, Paul.
Jim!
Come on, okay.
Jim, what the
hell are you doing?
Oh, yeah, yeah, ready?
One, two...
[grunts]
Okay, get underneath,
underneath. Go underneath!
All right. You ready?
- Go, go, go...
- You got it?
One, two, go!
[grunting]
Come on! Slide out!
Slide out! I got you!
Come on, come on.
Drop, drop, drop.
Are you good?
Got any breaks?
No, he's just gonna
be bruised for a long time.
I was just out back
turning off the gas
when I heard you guys yelling.
Hey, look, we need
a car right now.
We'll take you to the base.
All right,
I got you covered, man.
I got just the one.
Great.
Where are the keys?
Back there on the shelf,
number eight.
- On the board?
- Yeah. You can't miss it.
All right.
- You good?
- Your brother.
Oh, no.
A thank you would
have been nice, all right?
Shit, nothing changes
around here.
Before he went to the Air Force,
your dad had that
on his workbench.
Every day he'd look at it.
Man, I forgot all about it.
You know what? Take it.
I want you to have it, Jimmy.
For good luck.
Thanks.
Guys, I'm sorry I never made it
to your dad's funeral.
Hey, George, It's all right.
I was just...
What's our ETA to impact?
We got an hour and 12 minutes.
We gotta go.
All right, come on.
Let's go.
George.
Thanks, George.
Hey, man, she's is a
nitrous-burning monster!
Zero to 100 in a second!
[rumbling]
George!
- Come on.
- George!
Come on, Jim!
We gotta go!
Come on!
Go, go. Step on it.
Go, go, go.
You good?
Which way to the base?
Straight west.
Base, this is Lawson.
Do you copy?
Base! This is Lawson!
This is Admiral Keller,
Lawson, at XVision.
Go for base.
Jim and I are three minutes out.
Repeat, ETA is three minutes.
Do you copy?
Copy, three minutes.
We're currently tracking
your position
with the Xvision
surveillance drones,
so we'll have a more accurate
sense of your ETA.
We've sustained massive
damage here at the base
due to these earthquakes.
Some parts have
been completely decimated.
Most of our F-35s
and about 80% of all
aircraft are operational.
XVision craft is
ready to launch.
We're just waiting
for your arrival.
Copy that, base.
Maintain protocol
on Operation Godfather.
Copy that.
You should have
visual confirmation
of conventional weapons now
at 50,000 units and climbing.
Good. They launched early,
get ahead of
the earth's magnetic
poles reversing.
What's the ETA for the moon?
It's an hour
and eight minutes.
All right. See if you can find
something on the radio,
a newscast, anything.
[static]
...numbers of casualties,
and we're getting reports
of New York, Orlando...
coastal cities experiencing
unprecedented...
- Japan.
- There it is!
All of the
Canary islands, Alaska,
all in the states of...
I see it.
Just focus, brother.
We need to get to base.
Admiral, exterior damage
readings on the base
have overwhelmed our
damage-report live-stream.
Moving to the back-up feed.
Thank you, Major Romero.
Colonel Hauser...
China and Russia are chomping at
the bit to launch their nukes.
Is Lawson airborne?
Negative.
His helicopter crashed,
but we've regained
communication.
He's en route to the base
about one minute out.
We need him airborne
as of an hour ago.
We have Operation Godfather
on our threat screen.
We launched our missiles
to get ahead of
the reversal of
Earth's magnetic poles.
They're reaching
the mesosphere as we speak.
We will have Jim Lawson
airborne ASAP once he arrives.
Ma'am, an incoming meteor has
damaged above ground supports.
Below ground damage
is 20 yards at 5%.
Admiral, per the president
and the Joint Chiefs,
make it happen.
If Lawson doesn't tail
this strike,
every second decreases
our chance of success.
Yes, ma'am.
Our Colossus Dish is damaged.
Communication to the antimatter
engine is unstable.
Do you have steady contact?
Initializing communications
verification
with anti-matter engine now.
[signal sounds]
Signal still active.
The signal on the
antimatter engine
on the drone is active, yes.
How much life is left
in its power reserve?
Last reading was 72%.
Are you able to patch
this call over to Lawson?
I have a very unstable radio
signal, but it's all I've got.
[sighs]
Do it.
Yes, ma'am.
- Admiral?
- It's Hauser.
I can't hold Russia and
China back
from launching their nuclear
missiles much longer.
They seem to think that they can
solve this with a nuke strike.
A nuke strike
won't work, Colonel!
The only thing that'll stop it
is a major gravitational event.
We both know that, Jim.
But their physicists
seem to think
that our process isn't viable.
We need to convince them before
they take us all down with them.
Colonel, that antimatter
engine is a miniature version
of the large Hadron Collider.
That makes black
holes every single day.
So it is strong enough to create
a temporary black hole
the size of a football field
pulling the moon
back into orbit.
The Russians and Chinese
are saying that a black hole
will pull the moon and the earth
into it, destroying everything.
That's not true, Colonel!
They're going with the nuclear
option unless we can prove it.
Do we have proof?
Yes! It's something called
"Newton's Universal Law
of Gravitation".
Gravity decreases
in an inverse square
when moving away from
the center of a mass.
Colonel, the drone is
on the moon's far side.
So the earth is far enough away
from the event that
it'll only move a millimeter.
But that'll be enough to pull
the moon back into orbit
and back into equilibrium
with the earth. Copy.
Let's hope that
it's enough to ward them off.
Get it done.
[rumbling]
[alarm blares]
Ma'am, the Colossus Dish
has sustained heavy damage.
We've lost the distress signal
to the antimatter engine.
We're losing
its location, ma'am.
Threat Response,
this is Command.
Get above ground and repair
the Colossus Dish immediately.
If Lawson loses contact,
that dish is the only thing
powerful enough to communicate
the drone's coordinates.
Ma'am, radar indicates
Operation Godfather
clearing the mesosphere.
Lieutenant, when they strike,
get me a payload count.
[alarm sounds]
Colonel, we have
incoming meteors.
We have to find some
way to defend the dish.
Threat Response
is calling for artillery.
No.
If we use artillery, we
might as well be trying
to stop them with a pistol.
Diaz, get Threat Response
to set up
the LRAD sonic cannons
around the dish.
We'll launch a
sonic shield
to pulverize incoming
as it approaches.
Deploying sonic cannons, ma'am.
[rumbling]
Major Romero, how's the base's
earthquake stabilization?
Stabilizers are
still active, ma'am.
And the underground
line to the Pentagon?
Still active.
Ma'am, the missiles have reached
the leading edge of
the moon's debris field.
Field penetration at 18%,
30 degrees,
ordinance detonation at 31%.
Absolute carnage...
it is the end times...
I have reports of
satellites crashing...
Words cannot... Now we can see
whole structures...
around Paris...
our own station now...
Hey, the magnetic poles
are reversing.
Oh...
Hit the nitrous!
What?
In the console!
Oh, God! Oh!
Hit it!
Oh!
- Hang on!
- Here we go!
Hold on! Hold on!
Woo! Woo-hoo-hoo!
Ordinance detonation
at 38%, 50%,
60%...
80%.
We're still at 18% penetration
into the debris field
and holding...
Holding...
and 17%.
The missiles are prematurely
to detonating, ma'am.
The earth's magnetic fields
are reversing.
[alarm sounds]
Ma'am, I'm also getting
a heat sensor reading
from the stabilizers
underneath the base.
Rate of increase is
one degree per second.
All right, stand by.
Ma'am, we have to get our
spacecraft in the air now.
These earthquakes will
destroy our craft any minute!
What is Jim's ETA?
Captain Hayes, stand by until
I give you the order to launch!
Stand by, Captain Hayes.
The moon's weakening
the earth's magnetic field,
sending subatomic particles
shooting
through the upper atmosphere.
[crackling]
Ma'am, I'm getting a security
alert from the Pentagon.
The pole reversal is
activating the detonator,
destroying the missiles before
they can reach the debris field.
Stand by, Romero.
I'm getting an alert that
the Pentagon's Colossus Dish
is experiencing a power surge.
Do we still have
a line to Washington?
Still connected
to the Pentagon, ma'am.
All right. Put me through
to Colonel Hauser.
Ma'am, the cannons are down.
And the dish's
mainframe is overheating.
[cellphone rings]
It's Admiral Keller, ma'am.
I see zero confirmation
of his flight!
Get Lawson in the air now!
This is astronaut
Jim Lawson to base.
We are at XVision!
Start the engine on my craft.
I'll be airborne as soon
as I reach the cockpit.
He's here and about
to board, Colonel.
Copy that, Captain Lawson.
All spacecraft are prepped
and ready to launch.
You are at point position.
Repeat, you are at point.
Captain Hayes,
initiate launch sequence.
Jim Lawson is on his way
to fleet point position.
Hayes and Matthews,
you're running the edge.
Ready to launch.
Assuming left flank
to the point.
Ma'am, the temperature under the
base has increased 300 degrees.
Our pressure readings
are blowing out the sensors.
The building stabilizers
are melting.
[rumbling]
[ricochet]
Looks like it's
some type of geode.
Did this just come up
from under the base?
The last temperature
reading was 380 degrees.
The sensors are showing
a heat field at...
100 feet below ground!
Alert Lawson.
They might be driving right
into a volcanic eruption.
Ma'am, I'm getting an alert
from the power grid database.
All the power grids
in the U.S. are crashing
because the magnetic
poles are reversing.
This is Captain Hayes.
Ready to launch.
There's the fleet.
There's the fleet right there!
The engine's starting
to overheat.
The tarmac's heating up.
The tires are starting to smoke.
Yeah, the moon's pulling on
the earth's liquid core.
That's pushing magma
to the surface.
All right, we're gonna drive
right up to the craft,
get on the roof of the car, up
the ladder into the cockpit!
Copy.
Get those ships in the air!
Launch! Launch!
The channel's dead.
All right, we gotta get there
before another eruption!
Launch! Launch!
Break formation!
Go for launch!
Fleet, damage report.
We've lost 22 ships, Captain.
We're the only craft remaining.
They're gone!
Matthews and Hayes made it out.
They can't complete the mission.
Where's the AI craft?
What? The one untested?
The experimental craft!
Where is it?
Hangar 13!
We're going in.
What? To the cargo hold?
Hang on!
You can't drive into the ship!
Here we go!
Stop! Stop!
[screaming]
We gotta go!
Hello, Jim and Paul Lawson.
Preflight protocol
is initiated.
Jim, I see you are
the pilot today.
Go for launch!
Manual flight engaged.
Launch now!
Protocol discourages
launching from inside...
Launch now!
X.C., scan for imminent threats!
Imminent threat detected.
Launch at t-minus
three, two, one.
[Paul screaming]
- We got at least another mile.
- Okay.
So what brought you
to Camp Pendleton?
I was...
I started dating this guy,
a good guy, a Marine.
He had just started
his patrol on the base
when the earthquake struck.
Well, if everything goes
according to plan,
we'll get you reunited with him.
With who?
The Marine.
[rumbling]
[gasps]
What's our ETA to impact?
Hey, Paul?
Paul, focus on my voice, huh?
Deep breaths.
What's the ETA to impact?
43 minutes.
How far is the moon
from the earth?
NASA and the DOD's
database is down.
Hauser said the Colossus
satellite is disabled.
I'm not getting any updates.
All right...
X.C., how far is the moon
from our current position?
Calculating... there is no
GPS data available.
Communication satellite
shows fatal error.
Enabling laser distancing:
I detect a major disruption
of the Moon's orbit.
Current distance
from our location:
163,209 miles.
All right, so the moon's
a third of the way here.
We don't have an escort.
[beeping]
Jim, we are
receiving an alert.
Two XVision spacecraft are
approaching rapidly.
Sir?
We are guarding you the rest
of the way to the drone.
Thank you, Captain.
We owe you one.
Tell me, what's
your payload today?
We have
two stinger missiles each,
plus the two on your craft.
I am first point,
Lieutenant Matthews is second,
your craft is last.
Don't tell me Excalibur's never
fired its weapon system before.
You want me to lie to you?
Extremely hazardous conditions
detected in the troposphere.
Incoming meteors and
disabled satellites detected.
All ground contact is severed.
Advise safe landing
immediately.
X.C., shut up.
Incoming! 10:00!
It's maneuvering in the opposite
direction I want it to go!
It's following its program.
Well, turn it off!
I can't!
It's reacting...
Turn it off!
X. C., quiet mode!
Manual function!
Going quiet.
Manual function.
Thank you.
Incoming dead ahead!
Incoming!
Matthews!
[screams]
Sir, stay your course!
Staying the course.
We're almost out
of the mesosphere.
Be in orbit in 30 seconds.
Uh... Jim?
Incoming!
Fox One.
It's still coming!
Jim! What do we do?
Jim!
[screams]
- Hayes!
- No!
We lost them.
It's quiet.
Yeah, well...
We're in the middle
of the detonation zone
from the missile strike.
We're only gonna get
about a minute of this.
You all right?
Yeah.
I'm just not really used to
the physical impact of it.
[chuckles]
Well, we were pulling about
five Gs there,
so I don't blame you.
Yeah.
I hear this ship has
a cyclotron gyroscope
ballast here.
You don't know what that is?
It's artificial gravity.
[chuckles]
Wow!
Wow, this is what you
feel all day?
This is awesome!
I like this.
Try it on for size.
All right, focus up.
We need to find that drone.
[sighs]
X.C., find the distress signal
on our drone.
X.C. is back online.
Hello, Jim and Paul.
Locating drone.
Now Excalibur
can navigate us
straight to the drone.
I thought you
said it wasn't tested.
Yeah, it's untested,
but it has autopilot.
You know what that is.
Look, an AI component is a lot
different than an autopilot.
Yeah, I get that, but
this one's one of a kind.
You know, it's got
the robotic arm,
laser guidance system,
smart controls.
It'll save you from
doing a little moon walk
to get the antimatter engine.
Look, you were there
before we wanted to take off.
The ship wanted to delay
until we had to tell it
there was a threat.
Paul, look, human instinct
still has to be the baseline.
Okay, bro.
Diaz, the Damage
Response team
needs to reactivate
that satellite ASAP!
Run a fine-point signal to
capture any onboard functions.
We have no communication
with Lawson or the drone.
Their last alert was
10 minutes ago, correct?
These are distress signals.
The base was
completely destroyed.
Do we have confirmation of that?
Ma'am, some of the
distress signals
and security footage reached
our feed before it went black.
There's nothing left of it.
Looks like there was
some kind of explosion
that leveled at
a five-square mile radius.
What about our Air Force?
Are there any bases capable
of launching aircraft?
Ma'am, the communication
database feed
shows heavy damage
and destruction.
All of our assets
are inoperable.
Half of them went down
in the ocean
during the disruption
of the poles.
The loss of life is enormous.
[rumbles]
This craft looks familiar.
Yep. It ought to.
You designed it.
Really? So you just...
so you took my design?
No, I didn't take
your design, Jim.
I made the Defense Department
make sure that all the parts
and designs go under your LLC.
So anything they use,
you get paid for.
That was my way of trying
to make things right.
I love that picture
you got from George.
The one of us with
Mom at the beach?
- Yeah.
Dad must have lost that
when he worked for George
before he went in the Air Force.
Man, he was so mad.
He'd loved that picture.
It was his favorite.
I barely remember it.
Oh, you were only
about five years old.
All I can remember is him
laughing at something you said.
And then I tried
to say something.
And he... He just patted
me on the head.
[sighs]
Look, um...
It wasn't entirely your fault.
What wasn't?
Firing me.
Several years ago when you
were still in high school,
you hadn't even
started XVision yet,
I disobeyed a direct order
on my first lunar mission.
I was ordered back
to the lander,
but instead I went to recover
this metal sample
that we'd lost
when our rover failed.
I should have
gotten a reprimand,
but instead they said
I saved the mission.
I kind of developed a reputation
for doing stuff like that.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, well, everyone in
the Air Force loved Dad.
So they kind of loved
me by association.
I mean, the reports, they should
have said I was "reckless".
But they said
I was "quick thinking".
And then when I lost control
during last year's mission...
my reputation
went right out the window.
I mean, it didn't matter that
it was a gravitational anomaly
from 100 million miles out that
forced my craft into the moon.
It didn't matter.
I couldn't save my copilot.
No matter how thorough
my report was,
warning everyone about
an asteroid so massive
that it could affect
my spacecraft from that far out
and it was gonna strike the moon
in less than a year...
no one believed me.
Not even you.
What happened last year
wasn't your fault.
It wasn't your fault
at all, actually.
It was mine.
I was the one that
you discharged.
threw you under the bus.
Jim, your copilot's death
wasn't your fault.
None of this is.
It's mine.
But it could have been my fault.
That's why it's
not unreasonable for you
to strip me of my career
in order to save XVision.
Just like it wasn't unreasonable
for Stacey to leave me.
That's the dumbest
thing you've ever said.
If that's true, then why did
Dad have you drive him
to the hospital every single
day for his treatments?
Not once did he ask me.
You know why?
Because you're accountable.
You're accountable.
No cancellations,
nothing ever came up.
You were always there.
And me...
I'm selfish.
Always trying to
prove something.
You said Stacey's safe?
Yeah.
Yeah, Stacey's safe.
Good.
X.C., activate navigation.
Direct it towards
that distress signal.
Navigation engaged.
Distance to drone: 5,300 miles.
Current speed: nearing MACH 20.
15,208 miles per hour.
Homing beacon interface
visual and audio.
[gasping]
Malcolm...
Malcolm?
Ah... oh.
Communications dish in D.C.
might not have enough power
to get their message
through to our astronauts.
To get to the Comm 4, it's at
the top of the next ridge.
Plug the chip in that case
into the port inside
the box on the building.
Malcolm? Malcolm?
Hey...
Malcolm.
No.
No!
Wake up!
I'm so sorry.
[gasping]
I'm sorry, Malcolm.
Ow!
Laser distancing detects
a continuing disruption
to the Moon's orbit.
Hazardous flying
conditions ahead.
Debris field assessment:
100,000 cubic miles.
Incoming! Meteor approaching!
Evasive maneuvers!
All right, all right.
ETA to impact?
35 minutes.
Incoming!
Two meteors approaching!
First is upper left,
second is lower right.
Evasive maneuvers!
Hang on.
How fast can X.C. go?
MACH 30.
X.C., go to MACH 30!
Captain Lawson, given
the intensity
of the current meteor shower,
I cannot recommend...
X.C., the moon will crash
into the earth
if we don't reach that drone.
Calibrating.
This is an unprecedented event.
Risk assessment: both courses
of action will lead
to the destruction
of the spacecraft.
X.C., go at maximum speed now!
Increasing to maximum speed.
I am unable to advise further.
Good luck, Captain Lawson.
Good luck?
[gasping]
Pentagon, this is
Comm Four Southwest.
Pentagon, do you read?
Comm Four, this is
Colonel Hauser.
Do you have additional
bandwidth to redirect
the Colossus disc?
It's your last chance to
get that signal through.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
Okay, signal should be working.
Comm Four, we see no signal.
We're failing to
reach maximum capacity.
Uh, stand by.
Okay.
Okay, you should
have signal now.
Copy, Comm Four.
Transmission is live.
Ma'am, radar is picking
up an object
heading past the mesosphere
and into the debris field.
Is it a rogue missile?
No, ma'am.
It's a spacecraft.
That has to be Lawson.
Ma'am, our fine-point
signal has regained
contact with
the antimatter drive.
Try to make contact
with the spacecraft.
There's too much
interference, ma'am.
Amplify the signal to catch
any onboard functions.
We can build a
vectoring model
to send to Lawson in case
he loses the drone.
The Colossus can't sustain
the same stress levels
after its repairs, ma'am.
We have to get through to him
even just for a status update!
Ma'am, radar is picking up
a signal off the Chinese coast.
They sent out a global alert.
They've launched
their nuclear weapons.
We need to warn him
that a nuclear strike
in his vicinity is imminent.
Lieutenant, amplify
the signal to the dish
even if it risks destroying it.
Yes, ma'am.
X.C., prepare the robotic arm.
Running diagnostics
on the robotic arm.
All functions are optimal.
Lawson!
Colonel Hauser.
Are we actually getting
a signal from somewhere?
There's only a handful
of sites on earth
that have that type
of power of communication, so...
it's either the Pentagon
or some other G8 country.
See if I can get it.
[static]
Go for Jim Lawson.
[garbled speech]
Can't get it.
Ma'am, the missiles
from China are approaching
the upper atmosphere.
What's their time to impact?
Three minutes, 50 seconds.
Ma'am, we've rerouted additional
power sources to the Dish.
But it won't
hold up much longer.
I've got error
messages popping up
from the main control switches.
Are the electrical engineers
still at the mainframe?
Yes, ma'am.
Have them regulate the power
fluctuations manually.
Turn off the smaller systems.
Just keep the main circuit
from melting down.
Yes, ma'am.
We're about 8,000 yards
out now from the drone.
We should have a visual.
Lawson...
[static]
[garbled speech]
Go for Jim Lawson.
[static]
Did not stop...
Repeat, did not...
Oh, she's warning us
about something here.
X.C., can you break though the
static on the incoming message?
Clearing radio signal.
Paul, I apologize but I cannot
clear the incoming message.
Only discernible words are
"Repeat" and "Did not".
All right.
Keep monitoring the radio.
We're almost to the drone.
X.C., move the robotic
arm to port side.
Repositioning arm to port.
X.C., can you tell how
much battery power is left
in the antimatter engine?
Battery reserve on
the antimatter drive...
calculating 40%.
That battery's running out fast.
If it encounters a
problem in orbit,
it's programmed to send
the highest possible signal
and make sure it reaches earth.
Burns a lot of juice.
Ma'am, the nuclear missiles
are exiting the atmosphere.
Lawson, this is Hauser.
Come in, Lawson! Lawson!
X.C., extend the arm,
full extension.
Yes, Captain. Extending robot
arm to maximum extension.
Reverse thrust 12%.
Acceleration at... 88%...76%.
Target within 1,000 yards.
X.C., assume control
of the craft.
Bring us into
a stabilized position
on the port side
of the stalled drone.
Initiating guidance system
and assuming control
of the spacecraft.
All right, X.C.,
use the robotic arm
to remove the antimatter drive.
Are there any fine motor
fixtures which will require
use of the arm's toolkit?
X.C., there are 16 bolts
and a breakaway shield.
Make sure they're all removed.
Yeah, I know a thing or two.
Captain Lawson, now that
the bolts have been removed,
I will need to use the arm's
welding torch
to unseal the welded joints
on the engine's heat shield.
No, we can't risk
a welder damaging the engine
under the shield.
The drone's
too large to fit inside.
I may have to go out
and recover it manually.
- Let's suit up.
- Let's do it.
X.C., prepare for space walk.
Open cargo bay doors.
Yes, Captain.
Air containment in progress
and opening cargo bay doors.
- Good to go?
- Yeah.
What do you need me to do?
Well, when I tell the AI
to bring me back on the arm,
you monitor the controls.
Make sure it listens.
Copy that.
ETA?
We got 26 minutes!
Incoming! Nuclear missiles are
approaching the debris field!
Warning! Detonation within
the debris field is imminent!
Jim, we got a nuclear strike!
Don't touch anything!
Stand by!
Nuclear missiles are
approaching the debris field!
Jim, emergency
procedure requires
that astronauts outside...
Disregard emergency procedures!
X.C., do not listen
to that order!
I am bringing Jim inside!
Paul, I see you've engaged the
manual functions on the tether.
Jim, get your butt
back in here now!
Don't bring me in!
I've almost got it!
I don't give a shit, Jim!
Get back in here now!
Detonation in seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one...
Jim!
- Oh!
- Oh.
Closing cargo bay.
Severe damage reported.
- Fuel line has been breached.
- Go, go, go, go!
Fuel is leaking from
the exterior
and interior of
the spacecraft.
We need to shut off the fuel
before anything ignites it.
- Fuel remaining: 78%.
- It's no use.
All controls for the control
panel has been severed.
All right. We'll have to shut
down the engines.
- Shut down the engines?
- 65%.
Any electronic onboard
can ignite it!
I mean, we'd have to shut down
this entire ship!
Well, that's what
we're gonna do.
Maybe you forgot
we just lost the drone.
I mean, we'd be floating
dead in space, Jim!
Look, we don't have a choice!
If that explodes, we die
and every chance of saving
the earth goes with us.
X.C., cease all
onboard functions.
Power down the ship.
Captain, the craft is currently
spinning out of control.
Cease all engine and
onboard functions now.
Shut down the ship.
Ceasing all engine and
onboard functions.
You better be right.
We need an alternate means of
propulsion to reach the drone.
We can use the ship's
air evacuator valves.
What? So we use the onboard
air as propellant?
Exactly.
Come on.
We've lost them, ma'am.
No, not necessarily.
We lost their onboard stream
to our Cloud database.
Check the radar.
We still have a radar
reading on Excalibur, ma'am.
It looks like the majority of
their superstructure is intact.
Do we have any communication?
The systems are down, ma'am,
and thermal imaging suggests
that their engines are off, too.
[rumbling]
Ma'am, the structures
above us have collapsed.
Call engineering.
Have them devise a brace
for the structure.
Level Nine to engineers?
Code Grey!
The floor above us
is starting to collapse.
I repeat, Code Grey!
If Lawson's systems are offline,
he may need us to guide him
to the drone
using our radar coordinates.
Level Nine engineers?
Come in, Level Nine engineers.
Ma'am, the engineers
aren't responding!
Try to find them on
the server's location grid.
What are the orbital
coordinates of the drone?
29.09 north, 71.17 east,
209 million 200 miles
per hour at 94 degrees.
Threat Response team!
Give a full electrical surge
to the Dish's mainframe.
And Morse Code the following
coordinates, 29.09 north.
Look, I have a visual
on the drone.
But there's no accurate way
to judge distance
or coordinates, Jim.
Now what's the ETA
to atmospheric impact?
18 minutes.
All right, look,
we got four ducts
to evacuate air from the ship.
We got two here in the cockpit,
two back in the cargo hold.
But we're going to need the
exact location of the drone.
[beeping]
Is that Morse Code?
Well, it has to be the Pentagon!
It's a number.
It said 29.09 north.
Wait. That doesn't match our
coordinates.
That's 12,000 miles
from our starting point.
They're giving us the
coordinates for the drone.
Yeah, but we've lost access
to the ship's coordinates, Jim.
So we have no way
of tracking it.
The compass, the compass!
Compass?
What compass?
Jim, what compass?
Come on, come on, XC.
All right, look.
This is an old
World War II compass.
The needle's painted
with radium 66.
That's radioactive.
The engine has a
proton cyclotron booster
just like the Hadron Collider.
Now when that blast went off,
this was within 40 feet
of that engine.
So the subatomic particles
were affected?
Exactly.
Separated into ions
from the radium.
So now instead of magnetism
pulling the needle,
the ions in the dial are
mirroring the ions in the drone.
So it's overpowering
the magnetic forces?
Right. And if we could find
a horizontal plane relative
to the drone's orientation
and relative
to its vertical orientation,
we can measure
the angles on the dial,
triangulate the drone's
current heading
relative to our position.
Yeah, but what about its speed?
All right, we can trace our path
using the ship's database.
From when the nuke hit
us 'til now,
calculating for
distance over time.
That would work.
That could work.
Come on.
Okay, use those dials
to orient the horizontal
and vertical planes of
the Excalibur's vector map
based on the direction
of the compass' needle
relative to the drone.
Okay, the X and Y axis
are recalibrated.
XC, calculate a vector path
based on the new X and Y axis.
Aligning vectors now.
Vectors now synced.
Okay, let's get to
the cargo hold.
What?
Don't scrape anything.
All right,
pull at the same time.
This should bump us into
a clean trajectory.
Yeah, I got it.
On three.
Can you count that high?
Yeah!
All right, one, two...
- Three.
All right.
We should be on target now.
Yeah, hopefully.
All right, we're on course.
Let's slow our speed as
we approach the drone.
Okay.
You ready? We're gonna do this
together on three.
Yep.
One, two...
- Three!
What happened?
Nothing.
We must be getting out of air.
All right, again.
One, two...
- Three!
We're not slowing down, Jim!
All right. We're gonna have
to try to snag it
as we pass the drone.
Put on your helmet.
What?
Ma'am, look!
The Excalibur craft
has changed course!
It's steering towards the drone!
Is our fine-point signal able
to detect any communications?
No, ma'am, wait!
There's a vectoring
update in data Cloud.
It updated with
two parallel coordinates.
Good.
There must be something
onboard their ship
with an active database.
[rumbles]
Either their spacesuits
or the drone or both.
[crash]
Does the arm have a
dedicated power source?
Yes.
All right, we have
to turn it on.
But it could ignite the fuel!
We have to risk it.
- Okay.
- Give me a countdown!
Got it.
Making contact in 10, 9,
8, 7, 6...
Extending the arm.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
- We got it!
- Yes!
We got it!
Open the overhead doors!
What is our ETA
to the moon's impact?
Six minutes, ma'am.
Ma'am, the ceiling's not
gonna hold much longer
We have to hurry!
The moon's close enough
to the atmosphere
that it's causing "sprite"
electrical charges!
Jim, the power surges
are activating the ship.
The connection with
the anti-matter drone
has been lost.
- Warning, power surge detected.
- Oh, come on!
- Power surge detected.
- We just lost the drone!
We have to shut down
the system before...
[explosion]
Ma'am, there's been an explosion
onboard the Excalibur!
The spacecraft is headed
16 degrees, Vector 19
directly into
the sun's cosmic rays.
And the drone?
Do we have updates for the
fine-point reading on the Dish?
We did capture an active signal
to get it's last heading, ma'am.
Did you send a vectoring model
to the ship before it exploded?
I kept updating your
database every second, ma'am.
Then send a vectoring model
through the Dish, maximum hertz!
Do we have the engine?
No. It broke free in the arm!
Fatal error!
The hull has been breached!
Repeat, the hull
has been breached!
Failure of all
artificial gravity
and emergency systems
is imminent!
Catastrophic explosion!
X.C., where's the antimatter
engine now?
I am unable to locate
the antimatter drive.
The drive's distress
signal has stopped.
Battery power is depleted.
What's our ETA for the moon?
- Paul!
- What?
What's our ETA for the moon?
Three minutes and 20 seconds.
[explosions]
Disintegration of the
spacecraft's superstructure
is imminent.
Integrity of the spacecraft...
Warning, disinti...
The ship's breaking up!
Paul, the ship's breaking up!
Is there any other
propulsion onboard?
Paul, get it together!
Is there any other propulsion?
No, just us.
That's it.
I'm gonna get you outta here.
I need you.
Come on.
Wait!
My radio is picking up
a high-frequency pulse.
There's a waveform reading
in the display.
It's a sequence.
It's a vector model, Jim.
The drone's behind us!
Warning! Disintegration
of the spacecraft
superstrucutre is imminent!
Warning! Di...
Hey, we can't stay on the ship.
We can use the car
before the gravity dies!
What, Jim we can't use...
Zero to 100 in a second, baby.
Oh, yeah!
Thank you, George!
Let's get it.
X.C., open cargo doors!
Now! Go, go, go!
Oh!
Woo hoo hoo!
Hey, you got a hole!
Give me your arm!
What's the time?
A minute and 58 seconds!
Here, fix it.
All right.
It's okay.
Hey, brother,
look, you trust me?
Sure!
Oh!
Whoa!
What are you doing?
Paul, what's that light?
It's ionic particles
being pushed by the sun!
Our suits can handle it!
Are you sure?
I hope so.
All right, listen.
We've got the nitrous
in the trunk.
We can use that to shoot
ourselves toward the drive!
That's the plan?
You got a better one?
No.
All right, let's get
to the trunk!
Come on, come on, come on.
Take these.
Tape 'em to the side of the car.
Make sure the nozzles
are pointed backwards.
1:30,
we need to hurry!
Okay.
Now pop that nitrous when
I give the word!
- You got it?
- Got it!
All right.
Three, two, one...
Pop it!
[laughs]
All right, here we go.
It's working!
I'm gonna grab the drive.
You're only gonna get one shot!
Don't miss it, Jim!
Here it comes!
Grab it!
Yeah!
Woo!
Nice grab, Jumbo!
The battery's completely dead!
Time to impact?
Minute and five!
What's that light?
The Moon's reached the
earth's upper ionosphere.
The atmosphere is
about to catch on fire!
Take that in the back!
Hurry up, Paul!
Jim, what's that?
Paul!
- Paul!
- Ah!
Jim!
I got you, brother!
Pull me in!
I got you.
Come on, buddy.
Come on back.
[panting]
Where's the tape?
Got it!
Hold it still.
I'm gonna tape it down!
- We're almost out of tape!
- Use it all!
What are we doing?
All right, look.
The drive's battery has leads on
it just like any other battery.
All it needs is
a current to turn it back on!
I'll throw the switch,
the engine will start.
I'll rip the shield off
the side of the battery.
You can't!
It's screwed on!
Well, keep pulling!
Agh!
Come on!
Tear that thing off!
We need to get
the cadmium regulator!
[grunts]
I got it!
Great, let me
connect the battery.
Okay, the battery
is connected.
All right, great!
Here.
Attach these,
Just pull, man!
Can't! It's too short!
All right. We need something
metal, something...
We don't have anything metal!
Something that conducts
electricity.
Look in the glove box!
We don't have anything.
I got it, I got it, I got it!
Hurry! Hook it up!
All right, here we go.
- You ready?
- I'm ready!
Here we go!
- It's working!
All right, go!
[screaming]
[alarm sounds]
Ma'am, there's been an explosion
on the far side of the moon!
It's a black hole!
They did it!
[laughs]
Phew!
We're about
to re-enter the atmosphere!
Paul!
Paul, hang on, buddy!
Hang on, buddy!
I'm coming!
Need... to shield...
slow the fall...
All right, here we go.
All right.
Hang on, buddy.
Hold on.
Hold on!
Here we go!
Almost there.
All right, buddy.
We're going too fast.
We gotta find
a way to slow us down.
Let me secure us.
Here we go.
All right.
You know you cried when Mom made
us share a bed on vacation.
[chuckles]
Look at us now.
I'm gonna get you home
in one piece, brother.
Okay. Hold on.
Hold on!
[yelling]
Hang on, bro!
It's 50 below up here!
But you gotta breathe, brother!
Come on, man.
You gotta breathe.
This air's too thin for me,
but you breathe
that oxygen, brother!
Go on, breathe!
Breathe.
Come on, Jim.
Wake up!
Wake up, man!
Jim!
Jim Lawson, do you copy?
Jim Lawson, do you read this?
Wake up, Jim! Come on!
Jim!
[coughing]
Oh!
Oh, thank God!
Thank God! Come on.
Get you up. Come on
[laughs]
You did it!
You did it.
We both did it.
- I'm proud of you.
- I'm proud of you, man.
I bet Dad is too, man.
Yeah.
Gentlemen, congratulations.
Oh, Colonel Hauser!
We'll be sending a transport
to pick you up shortly.
D.C. just reopened our bunker
and there are a couple
of people down here
who want to say hello.
Paul? Are you there, Paul?
Juni! Juni, it's me.
We did it!
- I love you so much.
- We love you, Daddy.
- Come home!
- I love you, too.
Daddy's coming home!
Come in, Jim Lawson!
Jim?
Jim, it's Stacey!
Jim, please tell me
you're okay.
Stacey, is that you?
Jim, it's me.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Come home.
Come home, Jim.
I'm okay.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull