(gentle music)
- [Announcer] The following dramatization
is based on official documents,
personal interviews
and published accounts.
- [Radio Operator] Angel
Flight 8-6, Alpha Bravo,
you are clear to taxi
via Alpha for runway 2-6.
- [Rick] Tower, 8-6 Alpha Bravo,
ready for takeoff on 2-6.
Confirm my FR flight plan.
- [Radio Operator] Alpha Bravo.
Clear for takeoff on
2-6 (speaking faintly).
- Alpha Bravo, climbing on
runway heading for 7,000.
Good day, Sir.
I hope you're all tied down back there.
We got takeoff clearance.
- Brad, you can get that later.
- I got that, no problem.
(dramatic music)
I'll get to that later.
- All set, Chuck.
How 'bout you, you need a hand up there?
(engine revving)
(inspirational music)
- So, what are you doin' this weekend?
- (chuckles) My son, Travis
is learning how to cook.
I'll let him handle the kitchen,
I'll make a fire, curl up with Bob.
- Well, wake me up when we get there.
(music continues)
(engine whirring)
(wheels skidding)
(siren wailing)
- Okay, hon, one more cough.
- [Woman] I know I
should've looked after here.
(Sammy coughs)
- And again.
(Sammy coughing)
Just to be on the safe side,
I'd like to do an x-ray.
- [Man] Why, what's the matter?
- I'm not sure.
- Telephone call
for Dr. Johnson.
- I need a closer look.
- Telephone call
for Dr. Johnson.
- Let's go.
- Hey, come on, pumpkin.
Let's go see what you look
like on the inside, okay?
Come on (grunts).
Yeah.
- What's that?
- Pretty sure it's metal,
something she swallowed.
There's a non-surgical
procedure we can try
to get it outta there.
OR, please.
(monitor beeping)
(nurses speaking faintly)
- [Doctor] There we go.
Yeah.
Wait.
What's her blood pressure?
- [Nurse] 140/95.
(beeping increases)
- [Doctor] How's her heart rate?
- [Nurse] 99.
(beeping increases)
- [Doctor] What's her heart rate now?
- [Nurse] 125, 129, 131, 139.
She's tachy-ing.
140.
- [Doctor] She can't take it.
(monitor beeping rapidly)
- We did a bronchoscopy, but
we were unable to remove it.
We can't operate here, it's too risky.
There's an infection that could spread
to the heart or the lungs.
We have to fly her immediately
to Children's Hospital in Denver.
I can't overstate this, her
condition is extremely serious.
- My wife's terrified of flying.
- [Doctor] A seven hour
drive is too dangerous.
- I'll fly with Sammy.
- I'll make the arrangements.
- You go with Mom and I'll meet you
at the hospital in Denver.
(solemn music)
(Jack panting)
(phone ringing)
- I'll get it.
Bagshaw residence.
Okay, I'll be in in 20 minutes.
- [Travis] Who was that?
- Sorry, honey, I gotta go back to work.
Why don't you come with me?
You can ride back with dad.
- [Travis] But you just got home.
- I have to go, we're flying a little girl
to Denver for surgery.
- Mom, there's a big storm comin' in.
- I know, we'll get out before it hits.
Aw, Travis, what's the matter?
- I just wish you weren't
flyin' Angel Flights anymore.
I mean, look at it out there.
- Hey, it's my job.
I'll be back in time for your birthday.
(siren wailing)
- Hey, good lookin'.
- I gotta fly out to Denver,
a little girl is sick.
- Oh, terrific.
- Listen, take Travis home.
He's worried about me.
- He's worried about you and
he's not worried about me?
- (chuckles) He's worried about
you flying the chopper too,
but he won't admit it.
- Yeah, we'll talk about
this when you get back.
You gotta hurry.
- Okay.
- Love you.
(upbeat rock music playing)
(window whirring)
- You're a tough guy aren't you, buddy?
Ready to do it, killer?
Come on.
- Daddy, come with me, I'm scared.
- Just do it by yourself.
There you go.
(horn honking)
There you go, Justin,
that's it, bend your knees.
Piece of cake. Yeah!
Oh!
You okay there?
- Hey, you guys.
What in the world's goin' on, huh?
- You okay?
- I'm okay, Daddy.
- [Angie] You okay, sweetie?
- Gotta do it by himself.
That's the only way
he's gonna learn, right?
- Honey, we need to talk.
I think that we should just put Justin
in the church kindergarten.
- There's two things wrong with that.
It's at the church,
and it's at the church.
(phone ringing)
- Yeah, well, I know.
Well, all have Justin's friends go there.
I think that it would be good for him.
Brad?
- Angie,
I gotta get the phone, I'm on the call.
- Can we please finish this conversation?
- Yeah, Brown here.
- Brad, Teresa.
You gotta come in.
- [Brad] Well, do I have
time to take a shower?
I've been-
- [Teresa] No, the patient's
a two-year-old girl
with a fever of 105.
We're flyin' her to Denver.
- I'm on my way.
(phone beeps)
(pensive music)
I gotta go.
- (sighs) Great.
- Come here, buddy (grunts).
Your daddy's gotta go and take
a plane to Denver tonight.
- Don't go, Daddy.
- See, there's a little
kid like you who's sick,
and we gotta try to save her life.
- This is the way that it
always is, you know that?
- Angie, this is my job.
What do you expect?
- I expect you to give
Justin and I equal time.
Brad?
- I gotta go.
(Angie sighs)
(pensive music)
Hey, Maria.
- [Maria] Hey, Brad, have a good one.
See you tomorrow.
- [Teresa] We better move out.
- [Brad] How's she doin'?
- Not so good.
We didn't have time to
make introductions before.
I'm Teresa Bagshaw.
I'll be the flight nurse.
- I'm Jack Bahr.
- Brad Brown.
- My wife Patty and my mother Loretta.
- Just kiss me, Mommy.
- Oh, sweetheart!
- I want Bow.
- [Teresa] What's that?
- That's what she calls her bear.
- Hey there, Bow.
Gonna take good care of you too.
(phone ringing)
- Hey?
(Patty whimpers)
Hey, everything's gonna
be all right, okay?
I love you.
- Okay, we're all set.
Let's get a move on.
(man speaking faintly)
Heading for Denver.
I want you to keep an
eye on the stretcher.
Be careful.
Watch that IV.
- IV's fine.
- And here we go.
All right.
(siren wailing)
(EMTs chattering)
- I got the right.
- All right.
- [Teresa] Look her over.
- And one, two, three (grunts).
- [Teresa] Put her down.
How's the IV?
Good.
Put her down.
- Goin' down.
- Bring it down.
- One, two, three, go.
(somber music)
(engine whirring)
- Jack, let's go.
- Yo, Brad, how you doin'?
- How you doin', Rick?
Jack, this is Rick.
He's our pilot.
Rick, this is Jack Bahr,
he's the patient's father.
- Welcome aboard.
- Thanks.
- Jack, come over,
sit over here.
Hey, buddy.
- Hey, what'd you do, break your razor?
(Rick chuckles)
(engine whirring)
- [Teresa] I'm gonna do this real quick.
Gosh, you're good.
Is that bothering you?
I'll make it more comfy.
That okay now?
- Mrs. Bagshaw?
- Teresa.
- Shouldn't be in some sort
of infant seat or something?
- She's strapped in tight.
- Alpha, IFR flight to Denver.
I have information landing.
- [Tower Control] Air
ambulance 8-6, Delta Bravo.
You are clear to taxi on
IFR flight, gray junction.
- [Rick] Alpha Bravo, I'll
make sure, no problem.
- This is an air ambulance.
It's equipped for any
kind of medical emergency.
Got antibiotics, oxygen,
medical instruments, supplies.
(Jack exhales)
- [Jack] Thanks.
- Relax, Jack.
We'll be in Denver before you know it.
(engine whirring)
- What's that on the window?
- I'd say it's ice.
- Can the plane take off with ice on it?
- (chuckles) Look, you're
gonna have to chill out, okay?
It's no problem.
- [Rick] 8-6 Alpha Bravo,
ready for takeoff on 2-6.
Provide flight bearing.
- [Tower Control] Alpha Bravo,
cleared for takeoff (indistinct).
- Alpha Bravo,
climbing on runway
heading 2-6 to flight 101.
Here we go.
- [Brad] Yes, Sir.
(engine whirring)
(exciting music)
(monitor beeping)
(singer vocalizing)
(music continues)
- See?
Smooth as silk, huh?
Best job, Rick.
(monitor beeping)
(engine whirring)
- I'm just gonna check your heart.
Okay, honey?
(monitor beeping)
(engine whirring)
Hey Rick, do me a favor,
call ahead to the hospital,
give 'em our ETA.
- Sure, Teresa, I'll have
Jefferson Center relay the info.
- Jefferson Center, 8-6 Alpha Bravo.
- So, what do you do for a living?
- I'm the youth minister at my church.
- Great.
- What's a matter?
You got a problem with God?
- No, let's just say that him
and I have never been the best of friends.
- Well, I'm sure he won't
hold it against you.
- Well, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna get a couple
minutes of shut eye.
I've been skiing all day.
- Skiing?
Skiing, and a paramedic.
Thrills and spills.
- I'm a ski patrol and I save lives, okay?
(monitor beeping)
- [Teresa] Here, give me your hand.
I'm just gonna check on thing.
Do you know what this is?
This is gonna check and see...
(heart monitor beeping)
(alarm beeping)
- What's the matter?
What's wrong?
- The sound of the engine
lulls 'em to sleep every time.
Don't worry, it's good for her.
- Hey, its' my kid.
- You're right, I was outta line.
I'm sorry, Preacher Man.
- Don't call me Preacher Man.
(gentle music)
(engine whirring)
(pensive music)
(engine revs)
- Hessman Tower, paging Alpha Bravo.
- [Tower Control] Alpha Bravo, go ahead.
- Got a bit of an engine problem here.
Requesting a vector back
into Grand Junction.
- [Tower Control] Alpha
Bravo, paging in one 3,000.
(indistinct)
(pensive music)
- Hey, what's the matter?
- We've got a bit of engine trouble.
- Is it serious?
- Well, it's serious enough
to go back down and check it out.
(Brad sighs)
- It's pretty bad out there,
isn't it?
- Brad?
Don't bother him now.
(engine whirring)
(pensive music)
- What's goin' on?
- We gotta go back.
We got engine trouble.
We gotta go back to Grand Junction.
- Go back? We can't go back.
What about Sammy?
- Put her on another plane
as soon as they can get one prepped.
- [Jack] No, no, no, no,
there's not enough time!
- [Teresa] Jack, we can't
go on with only one engine.
We'll do what we can.
(engine whirring)
(dramatic music)
(engine chugging)
- [Tower Control] Alpha Bravo,
climb and maintain 1,400
for a minimum IFR altitude en route.
- Sir, I don't think we're gonna
be able to climb to 1,400 feet.
Can I make it through low?
- [Tower Control] Alpha Bravo, standby.
(indistinct)
- [Control] 11.
- [Tower Control] November 8/6 Alpha Bravo
has a situation developing
with his right engine.
He's unable to maintain
IFR minimum approach
for Grand Junction.
- Is he going to Grand Junction
or is he going to Rifle?
- [Tower Control] He's
going to Grand Junction.
- Copy that.
(air traffic controllers chattering)
(engine whirring)
(monitor beeping)
- I'm getting everything
tied down just in case.
- Everything?
- Yes, everything, right now.
Tell Rick to call ahead and make sure
another aircraft is ready
as soon as we're down.
- Rick, Rick, we got-
- Brad! Sit down.
(engine whirring)
- (sighs) I feel like the whole
world's against me tonight.
(Patty sighs)
I just wish I was with her.
- They should be in Denver
by the time we get to Glenwood Springs.
- Jack will call home as soon as he can.
- Come on, come on.
- Let's stop and get a cup of coffee,
make sure he has.
(Patty exhales)
- It's gonna be okay, sweetheart.
- Okay.
(pensive music)
(engine whirring)
(air traffic controllers chattering)
- What's Rifle got for weather?
(keyboard keys clacking)
(indistinct)
- They're reporting 10 tenths
cloud cover as of 0200 Zulu.
- They'll never make it
out on the one engine.
- What, think we should warn him off?
- Where to?
The guy's got zero options.
(pensive music)
(engine whirring)
- [Teresa] Sit down, Jack.
Jack, sit down.
- Sit down!
- Jack, you're gonna have to sit down.
Put your seatbelt on!
- Guys, sit down!
(engine whirring)
(dramatic music)
(alarm beeping)
(engine whirring)
(dramatic music)
- Oh man we're low!
(engine whirring)
(dramatic music)
- Come on!
Come on!
(dramatic music)
(engine whirring)
- Hessman Tower, mayday, mayday, mayday!
This is 8-6 Alpha Bravo,
8-6 Alpha Bravo, 8-6 Alpha Bravo!
(engine whirring)
- Rick, we're going into the storm!
- Stop it!
- What's happening?
(dramatic music)
(engine whirring)
Rick, we're losing speed.
Need more speed, Rick!
- Shut up, Brad.
He's flying it.
- [Tower Control] 8-6
Alpha Bravo, revisions.
6-8 Alpha Bravo?
(engine whirring)
(dramatic music)
- Well, folks, it looks like
I'm gonna have to set this thing down.
I want you to get everything
tied back down there, okay?
- Oh my God!
(engine whirring)
(dramatic music)
- A place, give me a place.
- Hey, her bed's loose.
Is she gonna be all right?
- Well, she's strapped
in, she's strapped in.
- [Jack] Sammy!
- A place, give me a
place, give me a place!
Give me a...
Got it!
Hessman Tower, I am going in
for an emergency landing in a hurry.
Do somethin'.
(suspenseful music)
- We're gonna crash!
Lean forward!
- You said chill out!
- Jack, lean forward!
(dramatic music)
(plane rattling)
(Rick yells)
(plane crashing)
(Teresa groans)
(Brad groaning)
(plane crashing)
- Sammy!
(singer vocalizing)
- 8-6 Alpha Bravo,
please state your position.
November 8-6 Alpha Bravo?
8-6 Alpha Bravo?
He's gone.
We've lost him.
- Advise Search & Rescue.
Angel Flight down.
(soft music)
(wind whistling)
(Brad coughing)
(pensive music)
- Teresa?
Teresa (coughing)?
Teresa?
(Teresa inhales sharply)
- What?
(Teresa groaning)
Anybody hurt (groans)?
Jack?
Rick?
- [Jack] Sammy?
Sammy?
Teresa, where's Sammy?
(Jack groaning)
(pensive music)
Sammy?
- Brad?
Brad, over here.
Brad, help me.
(Teresa groans)
- Sammy, Sammy.
(Teresa groaning)
(Brad groaning)
Sammy, Sammy?
How is she?
Is she all right?
Oh, baby (panting).
Tell me.
- She's breathing, she's got a pulse.
I think she's okay.
(Jack exhales)
- Oh, thank God.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, baby.
(Brad coughs)
- What about you, are you hurt?
- My head.
I'm...
I'm bleeding badly.
My head.
- [Teresa] Put your hand on it.
All right.
- Ow! Okay (groans).
(Brad coughing)
- Brad?
- My ribs hurt like hell but I'm here.
How you doin'?
Teresa (coughs)?
(Teresa gasps)
How 'bout you?
- I'm okay.
(eerie music)
I'm okay.
You gonna check on Rick?
- Yeah (panting).
- [Teresa] Watch the IV.
- Rick?
Rick?
(Jack grunts)
(pensive music)
Come on, buddy, talk to me.
I can't hear him.
I can't see him.
There's too much stuff blocking here.
We got a mess.
- What's that smell?
(Jack sniffs)
- We're drenched in aviation fuel.
We gotta get outside,
see if there's a fire.
(Teresa grunting)
It's jammed!
(pensive music)
(wind whistling)
- Rick?
Rick?
(Rick groaning)
Rick, talk to me.
(Rick coughing)
- [Rick] Help me outta here (coughing)!
- You okay?
(Rick coughing)
Okay, I'll only be one second.
- Oh, God.
Oh, God (groaning).
(Brad panting)
- Brad?
- [Brad] Yeah?
- [Teresa] Brad?
- [Brad] I'm checking the radio
to see if there's any power up here.
(Brad groaning)
- [Jack] Sammy!
- [Brad] The radio's dead.
Come on.
(Rick gasping)
How you doin'?
Okay.
I need your help, okay, buddy?
I'm gonna take you back.
All right.
(all grunting)
Okay.
(engine rumbling)
(radio playing)
- I'm gonna call Dad.
- Go ahead, I'll get some coffee.
Officer, is the pass clear up ahead?
- Yes, Ma'am, so far anyway.
Snow's accumulatin' up from the pass,
so we're advising anybody
who doesn't have to be
on the road to stay home.
- Hi, Dad, it's Patty.
We're in Glenwood Springs.
Has Jack called?
Are you sure?
Have you been home the whole time?
(pensive music)
Okay.
Okay, thanks, Dad.
(receiver clattering)
(music continues)
- What's the matter?
- Jack hasn't called.
Something's wrong, I can feel it.
- Well now, maybe he
hasn't had his chance.
- [Patty] I hope you're right.
(pensive music)
- All right.
- Back here.
- Okay.
(pensive music)
(Rick panting)
- Mayday, mayday, mayday, mayday!
- [Teresa] Rick, relax.
You're okay, relax.
- [Brad] He's disoriented.
- [Teresa] Try to keep him warm.
- [Brad] Okay.
- [Teresa] Jack, can you hold this?
- [Brad] I'm here, buddy.
How's she doin'?
- I took the IV out of her
to try to keep (indistinct).
- Let me see that head.
- It's bad isn't it?
- It's just a scratch.
Gauze.
- My shoulder, it's...
- Let me see.
- She's cold.
Sammy's cold.
(Brad groaning)
- All right, all right.
I think you may have a shoulder fracture.
You should try to keep it immobile
as much as possible.
Maybe Brad can make a sling for you later.
Can you hold onto Sammy
a little while longer?
- I can hold her no matter what.
- [Brad] How's she doin'?
- [Teresa] Rick?
Rick?
- She's cold.
- Can you hear me?
- I'm so sick.
- Okay.
- My stomach, I just feel
like I'm gonna throw up.
- It's all right.
Here you go.
- I'm gonna be sick.
- How's that ear?
- I don't know.
- Okay.
So what do you think?
- Not too good.
He has all the symbols
of a serious head injury.
And there's not much we can do about it.
If we don't get outta here quick,
he's not gonna make it.
And neither is she.
Jack?
Let's get Sammy to lay down.
I wanna check and see how she's doin'.
- [Jack] Okay.
- It's all right, Rick.
I got you.
- Is it bad?
Oh God.
(Rick's throat clearing)
(pensive music)
(wind whistling)
(Rick gasping)
Hot!
- [Jack] What's the matter with him?
- He's delirious, he doesn't
know what he's doing.
- Rick, take it easy.
Sit down.
(Rick gasping)
Relax, buddy.
Relax.
- Rick? Rick?
- Relax.
- [Teresa] Rick?
(Rick panting)
- Shh, it's all right, it's
all right, it's all right.
- Okay.
Okay.
(Rick coughing)
- It's serious isn't it?
- Hypothermia.
If we don't get him out
of here he's gonna freeze.
- Freeze?
Are we all gonna freeze to death?
- No, we're not.
- But he said that he was on
his way to freezing to death.
- If we work to stay warm we'll be fine.
- What about Sammy?
She'd be the first one to-
- She's not gonna die.
We're not gonna let her die.
I mean it.
- She's everything to me.
- Jack, I have a child and so does Brad.
He has a little boy.
Kids are everything.
We're not gonna let her die.
We can make a bed, use each
other's body heat to keep warm.
They know we're down.
There'll be a search plane looking for us.
- How long will that take?
- We had a 120 mile per hour collision
with a side of a mountain,
we're still here.
I won't let her die.
I promise.
- Yes, it's on hold.
- Hey, let's get movin'.
ATC just cleared us for night flight.
Why isn't my chopper warmin' up?
Come on guys, seconds are tickin' by.
Why isn't anybody up there?
- Bob, there is no emergency
locator signal comin'
from the wreck.
The transmitter's either
inoperable or destroyed.
(pensive music)
(radio chattering)
Without a radio beacon,
the only thing we can do is a
visual search at first light.
And it doesn't look very good.
I'm sorry, Bob.
(solemn music)
(radio chattering)
- At least we'll have something
between us and the cold floor.
Get Rick.
(Rick coughing)
Here you go.
There you go.
Jack?
(pensive music)
(Jack grunting)
Easy.
- Ow.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Okay.
Come on, over here.
That a girl (groans).
- [Teresa] Good girl.
There.
Try to keep her warm.
(Jack groaning)
That's it, that's it.
(Brad coughing)
(pensive music)
She's shivering, but she feels so hot.
- [Teresa] It's the chills from the fever.
- Oh, Sammy.
Oh, Sammy.
(wind whistling)
- Good news for the skiers.
- [Jack] What?
- Snow.
The damn storm climb's caught up to us.
(Jack panting)
- Well, how are they
gonna find us in that?
- I don't know.
(wind whistling)
- I checked Glenwood Springs,
the airport in Eagle, nothin'.
I mean, maybe he turned back in at Elm,
which is on the heading of 2-6
back in the prevailing wind.
- The only logical course after that
is an estimate landing at Aspen.
That puts him between Rifle and Aspen.
I'll meet you at the chopper.
- I'll call Civil Air Patrol.
And file a flight plan!
(pensive music)
(wind whistling)
(Brad grunting)
- There's snow coming in.
We're getting buried alive.
- They'll never see us.
- All right, we have to
(indistinct) cockpit.
I can feel the cold air coming
in from the front window.
- How are we gonna get outta here?
- Maybe we can dig our
way out when it quits.
- Wait a minute.
- [Teresa] What?
- Rick?
Wake up, Rick.
Wake up.
Rick, wake up.
Come on.
Where is the ELT?
- Good, Brad, the ELT.
- Where is the ELT?
Try to remember.
Come on, wake up, Rick.
Where is the ELT?
- What's an ELT?
- Come on.
- An emergency locator transmitter.
Goes off when there's a crash.
A search button and it hones
in on its transmission.
- Come on, think.
- Rick?
Rick?
- What?
- Try to remember.
The ELT.
- Come on.
- The ELT!
- We gotta make sure it works.
Where is the ELT, Rick?
Wake up.
Damn it, Rick!
- Easy.
- It's no use, his brain's a mess.
- Okay.
It's all right.
- I don't know.
(chopper whirring)
- Look, visibility's just about minimal.
We can't keep flyin' like this.
(indistinct)
No way.
- [Bob] There's a chance!
- Yeah, there's a chance
but if we keep goin' up
we're gonna take on too much ice to fly.
- It's Teresa, Robert.
- Look, I know.
But we gotta go back.
We can't keep flyin' like this.
Now you are no good to her dead, Bob.
(chopper whirring)
- [Jack] What are you doing?
- Taking her hydrate.
It'll help her fever.
Sammy, come on, honey.
Can you wake up?
Sammy?
- Hey, pumpkin, come on, wake up.
Come on, wake up.
Sammy?
Hey, wake up.
- [Teresa] Sammy?
(Patty sighs)
- Something's happened.
I know it.
- Sammy's probably in surgery right now.
She's gonna be fine, dear.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Everything's gonna be just fine.
(pensive music)
- [Jack] Hey, Sammy, wake up.
Sammy?
Hi, Sammy.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Hi.
- Here, open up, sweetie.
Want a lollipop, huh?
That a girl.
Open up.
Good girl.
- Hey.
Look what I found.
I found your Bow, huh?
I'm gonna put him right in here
so he can keep ya company, okay?
Here ya go.
I wanna say something.
I believe in God, and I
believe He will protect us
in this time if we pray to Him.
- Hey?
You can pray all you want, all right?
But leave me out of this.
I don't need you to preach to me.
- [Teresa] Brad.
- I wasn't going to preach.
I just wanted to say what I believed.
I thought it might help.
(sighs) My faith has
always gotten me through.
- I'm glad you told us, Jack.
I'm glad you have that to hold onto.
(somber music)
(wind whistling)
- [Bob] The plane went down.
- In the mountains?
- Yeah.
(Angie sobbing)
I've been out looking but
the weather closed in.
We'll blanket the area at dawn.
- Oh, God, we had this fight
right before he left (panting).
(Justin crying)
Justin!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
what are you cryin' about little guy?
Hey.
Hey, you should be sleepin'.
You should be under the
covers snug as a bug.
Don't you know it's snowin' out?
- I want my daddy, I want my daddy.
- Well, he can't be here right now.
I'm sorry.
How 'bout I take ya up to bed, huh?
Okay?
All right.
Come on there, buddy.
Yeah.
Hey, tell me, hey you ever really seen
a cow jump over the moon?
- [Justin] No.
(solemn music)
(wind whistling)
- [Teresa] You okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- Mm hm.
This cold is like a knife.
- Mm.
- You know, I was thinkin' about Angie
and when I was on the air rescue in Alaska
for the Air Force.
I used to describe the crashes to her.
I guess I needed her to think
that I was some kinda hero or somethin'.
And now she probably thinks
I'm one of the gory details.
I have done so many things that are wrong.
And if we ever get out of here, I swear...
I swear I'm gonna do things different.
Yeah.
(flashlight clicks)
(wind whistling)
- Yeah, we're flyin' out
on our own at first light.
How soon can they be here?
Thanks.
I got two more search planes
comin' in from Denver.
How are you doin, Robert?
- I got planes comin' in from
Aspen, Utah, the whole area.
Talk to Brad's wife yet?
- Yeah, it was hard on her.
- Yeah, well, she knows the odds.
(sighs) Jeez, I'm sorry, Bob.
- It's okay.
I know the odds, too.
(sighs) I think I'll go home.
Try to catch a couple hours.
(solemn music)
- Still gotta tell his kid.
(Bob chuckles)
- [Travis] What's the matter, Dad?
(Bob exhales)
- [Bob] Your mother's plane
ran into a little trouble.
- (stammers) Trouble?
(stammers) What kinda trouble?
- It went down in the mountains.
There's a chance that
she's still alive and...
- A chance?
- Travis.
- This is winter in the Rocky's.
- Travis, listen to me (chuckles).
If there's even the slightest chance,
you can bet your mother's
never gonna quit fighting, huh?
Hey, neither are we.
(pensive music)
(Bob sniffling)
(Teresa coughs)
- [Rick] Teresa?
Teresa, it's back there.
It's in the back (coughing).
In the compartment in the
back, in there, in there.
- [Brad] Rick, what are you talking about?
- (coughing) In the compartment.
In the back in there.
The ELT.
(dramatic music)
In the compartment.
(music continues)
(metal banging)
(Teresa groans)
- [Brad] Got it!
I got it.
- You know how to work it?
- Are you kidding me?
This is gonna bring a search
party right on top of us.
- What's the matter?
(dramatic music)
What's wrong?
- It's dead.
- What?
- The antenna's busted.
(pensive music)
Teresa, Teresa, this was our last chance.
(wind whistling)
(pensive music)
- Six wing aircraft
will be in the vicinity
of what we believe to be the
crash site at first light.
We'll follow in with choppers at daybreak.
Any questions?
- [Man In Plaid] Yeah,
yeah, can I say something?
- [Bob] Sure, who are you?
- I used to work for Mountain
Rescue over in Denver.
I came down to warn you.
- Yeah, well we know what we're doin'.
- You don't even have an ELT signal,
and without an ELT signal this search
is like trying to find
an icicle in a blizzard.
Now, if there was a 5%
chance I'd say go for it
but there is no chance,
and if you go up there today some of you
are very likely not to come back.
- Maybe we should put this to a vote.
- Oh!
- I don't want anyone to risk themselves
so much on my account.
- All right, fine!
Let's take a vote.
Everybody who thinks we better get up
off our butts and go
find these people say I!
- [All] I!
(all chattering)
(Teresa humming)
Don't you cry
Go to sleep
Little baby
(PA chattering)
(phone ringing)
- Can I help you?
- Hi, I'm Patty Bahr.
I'm here to see my daughter, Samantha.
She's here for surgery.
- Just a minute.
Someone wants to talk to you.
Mrs. Bahr is here.
(pensive music)
- Mrs. Bahr, I'm the chaplain here.
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
- [Teresa] Her fever's rising again.
I've given her a big dose of antibiotics
but we're gonna have to ration the rest.
- How long will they last?
(Teresa exhales)
- Maybe 24 hours if she
doesn't get any worse.
(pensive music)
- Why is this happening?
(wind whistling)
- All right, we search the
grid between Rifle here
and the northwest, south
towards Aspen and the southeast.
We've all got our sectors.
Keep a listening watch on
121.5 for that ELT signal.
- [All] All right.
- Maybe we'll get lucky.
- All right, guys, let's head out.
- All right.
- After this storm blows over,
there's worst forecast for the afternoon.
- [Man] Oh no.
- Let's go get 'em.
(all chattering)
(wind whistling)
- I got an idea.
Tomorrow morning we'll
set the forest on fire.
No search plane is gonna
miss a forest fire.
- Hold it.
You could set us on fire, too.
Remember, we're covered in aviation fuel.
- It's evaporated, Jack.
- [Teresa] It's too dangerous.
- Okay, fine.
I'll go and get some
fuel from the wing tank,
I'll go 50 yard from the
plane and I'll torch one tree.
- What about the wind?
- I'll go down wind.
- It might work.
- What if the wind turns?
- Then we won't freeze to death.
Come on, guys, I gotta try something.
- Okay, give it a try.
- All right.
I need some way to carry the fuel.
- What about a bed pan?
You can siphon the fuel out of
the wing tank with IV tubing.
- Okay, great.
Got any matches?
- I don't smoke.
- Big surprise.
You know, we're all gonna die
out here because we're
too health conscious.
Rick?
Rick, wake up, buddy.
Is there any matches anywhere?
- What?
- Wake up.
Where are the matches?
Matches?
Is there any matches anywhere?
- Back there, in there.
- Okay.
- The ELT's in there.
(Jack sighs)
- Wait.
You can use battery
powered defibrillators.
You strike 'em together
it'll make a spark.
- All right.
I'll try that in the morning.
(Angie sniffling)
(solemn music)
(wind whizzing)
(Teresa gasps)
- It's only the wind.
(music continues)
Brad?
- Huh?
- Jack?
Wake up.
Okay.
It's light out.
Sammy?
Sammy, honey, wake up.
- [Jack] What's the matter?
- Sammy?
- Teresa?
What's the matter with her?
- Call to her, Jack.
- What?
- Let her hear your voice.
- Sammy?
Sammy?
(suspenseful music)
Oh, Sammy!
Oh, pumpkin (panting).
- I got her.
- We've gotta get out of here.
Come on, let's go.
- Good girl.
(dramatic music)
- [Jack] You really
believe this will work?
- You're the one with all the beliefs.
(dramatic music)
(Jack groans)
(music continues)
(Brad groans)
(pensive music)
- We're in South Canyon.
- How do you know?
- I hauled enough oil drilling equipment
up this canyon to last a life time.
Servin' the Lord doesn't
always pay that well.
- I guess I've been kinda tough on ya
with that whole church thing haven't I?
- I've noticed.
- Well, I think man shouldn't
have to depend on a crutch.
- So, what do you depend on?
- Myself.
Let's go.
I gotta get fuel from the wing tank.
Got it?
Watch it, watch your step.
(Brad groaning)
(somber music)
- [Jack] You need some help?
- Got it.
(Brad grunting)
(Brad coughing)
- Brad!
(Brad yelling)
(dramatic music)
Brad?
(Jack groaning)
(Brad coughing)
Brad!
- [Brad] My ribs!
- Come on!
Come on.
(Brad groaning)
(suspenseful music)
(Jack groans)
(Brad grunting)
Brad?
- [Brad] I can do it!
- Stop.
Brad, Brad, stop.
Brad, Brad, Brad.
Brad, Brad, Brad, Brad!
- I can do it!
(solemn music)
(Brad grunting)
- [Jack] Teresa!
- Nothing works, nothing works.
(Jack grunting)
The snow's way too deep.
- We couldn't get anywhere (panting).
- They can't see us.
We trapped.
- We're not, Brad.
It's all right.
We'll try somethin' else.
We'll find another way.
- Don't you understand?
We're not gonna make it.
(solemn music)
We're not gonna make it (panting).
(wind whistling)
- Come on, Brad.
Come on.
You gotta keep moving.
- I'm tired of this.
I just wanna sleep.
- No, you can't sleep.
Hey, look at that little girl, huh?
She's growin' weaker by the hour
but she's fighting for light every minute.
Look at her.
Look at that little girl.
Think how'd you feel
if that were your kid.
- I just wanna sleep.
- You're scared.
- I'm not scared.
- Yeah, you're terrified.
You're afraid everyone
will know you're scared.
- I said I'm not scared.
- Oh, yeah!
Your whole life's based on
proving how brave you are.
You'd rather die than let
anyone know you're weak.
- Shut up!
- Prove me wrong, huh?
Prove me wrong.
I'll survive 'cause I'm
not a quitter like you.
(Teresa panting)
Listen, while you're up,
go check on Rick for me will ya?
(wind whistling)
(engine whirring)
- [Searcher] We're low enough.
- Nothing!
There's nothing!
It's too thick.
I'm goin' back up.
(engine whirring)
- Okay, that's better.
Come on, Rick.
Hey, Jack?
Hand Sammy to Brad for
a minute, help me here.
- Okay.
(Jack grunting)
(Jack shivering)
(gentle music)
- Hey, Sammy.
I got a little kid just like you.
- Hi.
- And I wanna see him again.
I wanna hold him in my arms and tell
him I love him more than
anything in this world.
- Don't cry.
- What?
- Nothing.
(Jack groans)
- I know how you feel.
Wanna hold her for awhile?
- Yeah.
- Here you go.
That a girl.
(gentle music)
(engine whirring)
- You guys get anything?
- Nah, there's no ELT.
It's all (indistinct).
Into the mountains up there
there's no visibility at all.
- Could you guys try again?
With the storm comin' in this afternoon,
we'll barely have a two
hour window to find 'em.
When that front hits it could shut
the area down for a week.
- Sure.
We'll go back up as soon as we re-fuel.
- Thanks.
I mean it, thanks, guys.
It...
- It's no sweat, Bob.
- That was the last of it.
- Let's get these choppers up.
(dramatic music)
(engine revving)
(buttons clicking)
- [Jack] Are you gettin' anywhere?
- Except for the antenna I can't see
anything else wrong with this.
One time in Alaska we had
this ELT signal in a crash.
And this guy kept turning it on and off.
He was trying to tell us
that he was still alive
so we'd go after him.
- How'd it end up?
- We saved his life.
(lever clicking)
(chopper whirring faintly)
- Maybe we're not in the area.
Maybe we're not even close.
(engine whirring)
(static crackling)
(signal whirring)
There!
There, did you hear it?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, it could be.
- That's it!
It's weak, but that's it!
See if we can lock in on it.
Mark?
Dearman?
Dearman? Where did he go?
(lever clicking)
- Maybe we could-
- No, you're right.
We'll clear the fuselage
so maybe they can see us.
- Okay.
(pensive music)
(Teresa coughing)
- Frozen solid.
We're trapped.
- What happened to it?
- We're way into our reserve tanks, Bob.
We gotta go back for fuel.
We can be back inside the hour.
(engine whirring)
(gentle music)
(objects clattering)
- [Brad] All right.
It's not that...
I think I can get through over there.
Grab this.
- No.
- Hold on.
You've been through enough.
I'll go.
(Brad grunting)
(Jack banging)
(Jack groans)
- You got it?
- [Jack] Yeah.
(Jack grunting)
(pensive music)
- Jack, you all right?
- [Jack] Yeah, I'm out.
I'm okay.
(wind whistling)
(Jack panting)
(Sammy coughing)
(explosion booming)
(Teresa gasping)
(eerie music)
- You're hurt, Teresa.
- No, I'm fine.
Ah!
- We need to deal with it.
- (gasps) There's no time for that.
This is the last of the antibiotics.
I think she's getting worse.
- It's white!
The plane's white!
The fuselage is white!
- Try the wing, Jack!
(Jack grunting)
(wind whistling)
Jack, be careful.
I'm on the nose.
(Jack gasping)
(suspenseful music)
I got an orange stripe on the nose!
(Jack grunting)
I can't get the...
There, I got it!
(Jack grunting)
- If he falls, I won't be
able to get him in time.
(dramatic music)
(wind whistling)
- I'm comin' in!
Open it.
(Jack grunting)
(Jack banging)
Come on, come on!
(Jack groaning)
I got it cleared.
- [Brad] I'm gonna go
outside for a signal.
- The wing's kinda small.
I don't know if they're
gonna be able to see us.
(wind whistling)
(Jack gasping)
Oh, my feet!
I can't feel my feet.
My legs, ow!
My legs, my legs are numb (gasping).
Oh, it's happening so fast.
I can't feel my legs!
- You're hypothermic, Jack.
Keep the blood going.
- Oh, God!
Oh, God, please!
I can't...
I can't feel my legs!
(Teresa speaking indistinctly)
We're dyin' out here!
- Come on, Jack.
Come on.
- You're not goin' outside anymore.
It's too cold.
- You did a good job.
They can see us now.
(solemn music)
- A steady stream of search aircraft
are coming and going from the space
in search of the Angel Flight
that went down somewhere between
here and Aspen last night.
And a new storm front is expected
to hit this area within a few hours.
The pilots in this desperate search said
they must find the
victims of the crash soon,
before the new storm makes
it virtually impossible.
The Civil Air Patrol is
working at full force.
This is Martine Singer reporting live
from Glenwood in Colorado.
- Please, God.
Please watch over my family.
- There's nothing like a sleeping child.
So innocent, so peaceful.
(gentle music)
Funny the things you think about
when you get in a fix like this.
I remember when my son, Travis,
was around two or...
I took him to a new playground
and I told him to stay off the slide.
So, naturally he had to sneak
over there and try it himself.
He nearly fell off.
He was hangin' there upside down.
I could tell he hated
having to be rescued,
but he was glad I was there.
I was actually thinking
about makin' this my
last flight (chuckles).
Maybe taking some nice,
safe work on the ground.
(engines whirring)
(rescue crew speaking indistinctly)
When I left yesterday,
I promised him I'd be
back for his birthday.
I'd hate it if the last thing
I ever did was lie to my son.
(gentle music)
(engines whirring faintly)
- That's a...
(Sammy coughing)
- [Jack and Teresa] That's a plane!
(soft music)
- Hey, let's split up.
I'll fly on with Frank.
Double our chances.
(Bob yelling indistinctly)
All right.
(engines whirring)
- Unidentified aircraft,
unidentified aircraft,
we are west of you, I
repeat, we are west of you.
(static crackling)
(engine whirring fades)
The damn plane didn't see us.
- Sammy, come on, wake up.
I can't wake her up.
I'm losing her.
She's dying.
- Sammy?
Give her to me.
- Sammy, wake up.
- Sammy?
- Pumpkin.
- [Teresa] Come on, Sammy.
She's unconscious.
Come on, Sammy.
(pensive music)
- "Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done on
earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread."
- [Teresa] Sammy?
(musical chiming)
Come on, Sammy.
(pensive music)
- Mom, the people searching Rifle say
that a signal has been heard
from the emergency transmitter.
Now, I'm not sure what that means.
(PA announcer chattering)
That's a good thing though, isn't it, Mom?
- Oh, I hope so, honey.
I hope so.
(gentle music)
(PA announcer chattering)
(pensive music)
(engine whirring)
- We're runnin' outta time.
They gotta be here somewhere.
Come on.
Where are you?
(pensive music)
- Hold hand, Daddy.
Hold hand, Daddy.
(gentle music)
(singer vocalizing)
- She's a fighter, she just won't quit.
(engine whirring)
(hopeful music)
- It's right on top of us.
(Brad panting)
(triumphant music)
Over here!
Come on, give us a sign!
They can't see the blanket!
- Here!
Brad, here.
Try this as a reflector.
- Come on.
- Where is it?
- There's no sun.
- The blanket, here.
Drench it in fuel.
We'll light it on fire.
- Okay.
(Brad panting)
(pensive music)
- Give it to me, the defibrillators.
It's the machine there.
- This?
- [Teresa] Yeah, the
whole handle, pick it up.
(pensive music)
(fuel sloshing)
- [Brad] Come on!
- [Teresa] I'm gonna set it on fire.
- Okay.
Just throw it as far as you can.
- Okay, go.
(air whooshing)
(somber music)
- I can't see 'em.
(triumphant music)
- [Brad] Yeah!
- We made it!
- Yeah!
(singer vocalizing)
(music continues)
- Come on, Sammy, sweetie.
Come on, hang in there.
Outta time, Bob.
We gotta get her off this mountain.
(singer vocalizing)
(engine whirring)
- Rick, come on.
- Civil Air Patrol has a plane waiting
to rush you to Denver.
- We gotta get Rick outta here
too, he's got head injuries.
- We'll all fit in my machine,
let's get him onboard.
- We're goin' home.
- [Bob] Easy.
- Got him?
- Yeah.
Listen, Rick, there's about one place
on this whole mountainside
you coulda set this
plane down in one piece.
You did one hell of a job of piloting.
I'd fly with you any day.
- We did it.
You know all that stuff
that you said about me?
About...
- No, I didn't mean that.
I was just-
- You were right.
I do put on a big show.
- Me too.
- You?
- Shakin' in my boots the whole time.
(gentle music)
- Come on, buddy, let's go home.
- Okay.
(Teresa groans)
(gentle music)
(triumphant music)
(engine whirring)
(all speaking faintly)
- [Justin] Daddy, Daddy!
- You okay?
(gentle music)
(rescuers chattering)
I've gotta tell you something.
- No, I have to tell you.
I am so sorry.
- You're sorry?
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
(Angie chuckles)
(Brad chuckles)
- I realized something out there.
I almost lost it out there, Angie.
- No, no, you didn't because you're here.
- But if I had been alone, I...
I wouldn't have made it.
- Baby, you're not alone, okay?
- I love you.
I love you.
- Daddy, daddy!
Can we go skiing when we get home?
There's lots of snow now.
(Angie laughs)
(Justin laughs)
(PA announcer chattering)
(gentle music)
- Jack!
Jack, you should be in bed.
(Patty sighs)
- Have you heard anything yet?
- No, not yet.
- You're a hero (chuckles).
I don't know how ya did it.
- It's funny, the
hardest part was thinking
about what you and Travis
were goin' through.
- Oh, it was an ordeal all right.
The kid's cookin's pretty awful.
Oh, Travis, hey buddy.
- Hey.
- You know the birthday we
promised to have together?
(gentle music)
- You bought that.
(Bob laughs)
- I got somethin' for ya.
(gentle music)
- (stammering) I'm so happy
that you're like, okay.
- I told ya I'd make it back.
Happy birthday, kid.
(gentle music)
(wind whistling)
People don't walk away from
mountain crashes like ours.
Maybe Jack was right.
Maybe it was a miracle.
Today, Jack continues to
inspire his congregation.
Brad still is a paramedic,
and Rick, our pilot fully
recovered from his injuries.
He was exonerated of any pilot error.
It was determined that a
mechanical error caused the crash.
Rick resumed his air charter business.
And me, I'm still flying
the Angel Flights,
though sometimes I ask myself why.
But you know, the little girl, Sammy,
we put it on the line for her.
Sammy's doing just fine.
(Sammy laughing)
- You ready for the fun stuff?
You ready?
Here it goes! Five!
(Sammy squeals)
(gentle music)
(triumphant music)