(music playing)
(music stops)
[woman] ♪ Are you really
♪ When you told me
♪ Did you want me to hear? ♪
♪ Do you really love me
♪ Are they just words
♪ And I hear it that way? ♪
♪ I'm not getting ready
♪ I just want to know if you're
♪ I don't want to hear ♪
♪ All the things
♪ I just want you near ♪
♪ So I can't misunderstand you
(music playing)
[Marci]
My best friend since preschool
What I'm about to tell you
in Cloverdale,
It happened to me and Summer
Here are some of them,
Rod and Tod --
Like,
just two guys
More about them later.
(music playing)
(rats squeaking)
Spike and Scooter.
A lot more
Summer's cousin Steve,
He's not in the story at all,
but some of his clothes are.
Herb Soric,
He comes to your house
like your garbage disposal
and there's a fork
and it, like, eats the fork
Anyway, he's in the story.
Mel Ching, the donut king
but not until way at the end --
[man] With two big locations.
Ahh, doorknobs.
I knew I had two more.
[Marci] Doris Trowbridge
People in town call her
Jewel Deluxe.
But me and Summer don't.
Manufactured by Higgins and Son,
Not that she isn't, weird I
These are little beauties.
She never finished high school
because she had to have
and couldn't be around germs.
Certainly will.
Now we have four crystal
How much does that make?
Have you had that in school yet?
What a lovely boy.
What a bright boy.
You're dressed like a bee today,
I think she might be weird
the total
like learning what's cool
I mean, you can just look
and tell she never got
You're funny looking.
[woman] Oh, Josh!
(chuckles)
[woman] Please don't...
make a game
Josh needs to understand
Josh, you hurt that woman's
Mommy's upset.
[Josh] She  is  funny looking.
[woman]
Not everyone is as fortunate
-[Josh] They're not?
Another person in the story
-[Marci] Regina Lee Savage.
what is it
Absolutely everything.
You are a loser, Charles.
You have the smell of defeat
[Marci] She doesn't live
She's on "Carlton Plaza,"
Charles.
Charles, who is Charles?
(music playing)
Jennifer Martin.
Jennifer has been eating
You know the type --
Hangs out with 11th graders
(scoffs)
It's just that girls like her
without ever having to
Beauty, talent, good hair,
Then,
(mechanical chair whirring)
Okay, Marci, just want you
Ow! Ow.
This is Summer.
(dental drill whirring
Okay, now open wide.
-[Marci] We do
Which includes getting
on the first and third Fridays
Now hold it right...
there.
Don't move.
Hur--
[Payne ] You've been drinking
Remember we discussed sodas?
-[Marci] It hurts ri' now.
Ah! Ah!
(telephone ringing)
Ooh. Just a sec.
Summer's dad is this,
And he helped invent
There was an article about it
Summer's still trying
Synthetic saliva doesn't have
except that if it starts
just remember -- anything
where people pay money
-(machine whirring)
-(Summer grunts)
-[Summer] Ah!
Sorry. That's my fault.
We were getting our bands
instead of afternoon
Spring vacation, which is when
You probably noticed
It's a major deal
There's a carnival
(music playing)
You have to be at least
to get into
So me and Summer started
because we generally don't like
until the last minute.
(music playing)
This is us waiting
the first year we went.
-[both] One, two --
Us the next year,
for all the good it did us.
(music playing)
Us last year,
And, like, probably us
(music playing)
Wait! Wait, wait, wait.
(video rewinding)
I forgot to tell you
(music playing)
The one thing Doris likes more
on TV even is yard sales.
She even bought her car
She goes to every single one
It's where most of the stuff
(indistinct conversations)
[man] That's really special.
That belonged to my wife's
or somebody.
Came from Europe.
Oh, it's very interesting.
-(box rattling)
It rattles.
$35.
Oh. Oh, no. I -- I mean
Oh, do you have the key?
$10.
Alright.
(chuckles)
This is a better view
that handyman guy
Now, watch this.
(music playing)
(muttering indistinctly)
I dreamed I went to Manderley
What?
You were showing some interest
in "Rebecca," Herb.
I never took you for a romantic.
You -- You know this one
Word for word, almost.
It's funny.
I can remember things like that,
but I can't remember
like where I put my car keys.
(chuckles)
Did you check the ignition?
Oh...No, I --
That was --
of the kinds of things
compared to the ki--
(chuckles)
You know what?
(music playing)
-[Herb] Well --
Oh, sor--
You know what?
They could probably go on like
So, let's take a look
It'll become important
I hope you find the keys.
Oh, okay.
Oh!
Told ya.
Anyway, you get the idea
Oh, and one last thing
me and Summer
It's like this job we got
Doris pays us $10 each
Her store smells
but not so bad
I guess.
Charles is Monica's
Monica has a brother-in-law?
"Popular daytime drama star
Regina Lee Savage,
comments on this week's
about Monica's brother-in-law
Details plus color
And why is Charles a loser?
I don't know.
[Doris] She said so yesterday.
She said he had the smell
Maybe he needs a bath.
[Marci] Good one, Summer.
Short-term memory loss.
It's the thing that bothers me
[Summer] Really?
Because, I think that
And, like, hair
And yellow toenails.
And, like, major saggies.
(cuckoo clock dings)
[Marci] Summer's right, Doris.
Forgetting stuff is pretty
Like, with all the other stuff,
That's my advice.
It made me and Summer
Doris up sometimes.
(telephone ringing)
Hello. Oh.
(telephone continues ringing,
Hello?
Yes.
Yes, this is Ms. Trowbridge.
I was calling you
in front of my shop
Hold?
What's this?
(giggles)
It's a knight light.
(laughs)
I don't get it.
Knight light.
(grandfather clock dinging)
Summer, are you getting enough
[Marci]
Yes? Yes, I'll hold.
-[Marci] You bought two rats?
Mary Cunningham's son James
so she put them up for sale.
Poor little things.
Oh, yeah.
Remember, James would come
and be all, like, "My rats ate
[Summer]
on account of rats
We had one in our garage
and it ate the fan belt
-[Marci] Yeah?
They got names or anything?
Oh, yes, perfectly
Um, Spike and, um...
and -- and Scooter.
But couldn't tell you
(sighs)
(music playing)
Now, back to me and Summer
and band tightening.
[Payne] Chew these, please.
Uh, I promise to brush better.
[Payne] And these will help you,
by turning your teeth black...
(dental drill whirring
...temporarily, to show you
You wanna know where your plaque
Seriously, I know where
And I brush everywhere they are.
[woman] Could someone come
Uh-huh.
Well, if you brush, floss,
adequately
then you have nothing
(man screaming, dental tools
But if you've not been truthful,
black teeth
-(man screams)
Okay, Marci.
Thank you.
The high school football team's
so I can always be sure of
just at the right moment.
(boys laughing)
(gasps)
Chew these, Summer.
The thing is, no matter
it can always get worse.
Oof!
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
Summer, do you ever find that
Like, even stranger
that happens every day.
Like what?
Like, already today you almost
I almost got
and we both got
and it's not even 10:00 yet.
Don't you find that strange?
-[Summer] Compared to what?
Marci. Summer.
I love it that we happened
Can I see you?
Guys, I'm trying to talk.
Move on.
God, they sound like dead cats.
As you know, tonight's
door prizes, exciting rides,
Like who?
Like me.
I'm being honored for winning
And some others being
They're listed at the bottom.
Unfortunately,
my neighbor needs someone
who just had this
And of course I can't do it
and because I have a date --
You probably don't know him
Jennifer?
-[Jennifer] Hmm?
I'm leaving in ten seconds even
Well, maybe you wouldn't mind
to help an unfortunate
You could order pizza
and probably have
Better even.
After all, it's better
and standing against the wall
which is all you'll ever do your
(music playing)
[announcer] And now the
"The Fairy Princess
Plus some mushrooms
without being noticed.
(laughter)
I forget the real name
but it was something
We'd love to help you out,
Jennifer, but, um,
Really? Who?
These guys.
That we know and you don't
(chuckles)
That's so great.
So I guess I'll you tonight.
Let's go.
You and your dates.
Oh...
you are so right about all those
happening to us, Marci.
Don't you think it's a little
Jennifer we have dates when she
and she is so gonna be telling
and everyone is gonna be
I'm not even gonna go!
Summer was right, of course.
I had set into motion the
to be our most serious
Little did I know
had been set
(woman singing opera music)
Years of yard sales
for Weird Doris
that no one could hardly
Hmm.
(sighs)
I wish my eyes were perfect.
(music playing)
Oh.
Oh, my.
I wish...
I wish I had different hair.
(Doris screams,
(boys grunting)
(bicycle bells ding)
I can't even believe
Summer, I said
And they're guys.
And -- And besides,
Tod calls you up.
Yeah, to burp the alphabet.
I am so sure I wanna be seen
burping the alphabet
Hey!
We wanna ask you guys something.
Yeah, you wanna see something
See? I told you
(burping)
[Rod] This is so cool.
Watch this!
Aah!
(laughs)
That's so cool.
He hit the trash cans.
Well, that's the --
(Rod continues laughing)
It looks like he's dead.
Well, that's the other
(laughs)
Anyway,
Skip it.
[Tod] Hey, what'd they want?
(chuckles) I don't know.
It's my fault, and I admit it.
I say we just
So we get laughed at a little.
There are worse things.
Yeah? Name one.
Shh!
Doris having
all of a sudden
What was surprising is the way
Not the way she said it,
I wished for it.
And I got it.
Isn't it the strangest thing?
Wanna touch it?
-[Marci] No, thanks.
You girls notice
unusual about me?
Come on, girls.
I'm sorry, Doris,
but it's really hard
I don't have to
Watch this.
"No user serviceable parts
(Doris chuckles)
"Opening case voids warranty."
(Doris giggles)
Look, start, stop, start, stop.
(laughs)
I have perfect vision
because I wished for it.
Smile, Marc.
Summer, hello!
(laughs)
I think it has to do
Too many years
Um, Doris, maybe you got
and then just forgot
Totally understandable.
Summer, remember the knight
Summer, think.
I turned him into a real knight.
He's in the back room.
Come on, girls.
Come on, I'll show you.
If this ever happens to me,
(giggling)
(music playing)
Ta-da!
(laughs)
Oh. Oh, no. He --
He must've gone out when --
Yes. See? The back door's open.
He's -- He's gone out.
Here, Summer, here, you try.
Make a wish, anything,
Okay.
Um...
I wish for a couple of cool guys
so we don't get laughed at.
Summer, I said I was sorry.
Okay?
Maybe there's cool guys
...open an artery over it?
No, I don't want you to open
You wouldn't do it anyways.
[Marci]
You are so obsessed
All those guys think...
I wish they had boys to...
whatever it was they wanted.
(Summer shouting indistinctly)
(opera music stops)
Um, Doris?
"Carlton Plaza" is on.
Uh, why don't you sit here
Sorry.
-[Marci] ...and watch it?
I'll turn it on.
And we can come back when
(gasps) Maybe...
three wishes.
I -- I made three wishes,
and that's all you usually get.
I wasted one on hair
and one on a knight
So, we're gonna go now.
Okay, Doris?
Okay?
Bye, Doris.
(music playing on television)
[man] The new big location.
...sale at Donut King's
on Front Street and East
coming soon
Take back the hair
[woman] And now,
(sighs)
This isn't you talking, Monica.
It's some stranger
You've tormented me
threatening to ruin me
Maybe I'm wishing the wrong way.
It's too late
Justin, how are you?
That's it.
(breathing heavily)
(gunshot fires)
(rats squeaking)
Ow.
Oh, stupid, stupid.
You think I'm a fool!
(gunshot fires)
Ow!
Oh, great, just what I need,
A lot of people wish
[Doris]
(gasps)
(grandfather clock dinging)
No!
Don't you think it's scary?
I mean, don't you ever worry
We are not gonna turn
That so won't happen.
How do you know?
I mean, I bet even Doris
she was gonna turn into Doris.
Summer, there are lots of
why we won't turn into Doris.
Name one.
Okay.
In 11 months for me,
we are gonna have totally
and correct jaw lines.
There's one right there.
Name another one.
We both got our own kidneys.
(tires screech,
[Doris] Yoo-hoo! Girls!
Woo! (laughs)
Girls!
I'm gonna get my mom, Marci,
-[Doris] Yoo-hoo,
That's not Doris.
Oh, my gosh.
That's popular daytime
Ta-dah!
Why are you in Doris's car?
[Doris] Because, I'm Doris.
I can explain.
You can try.
(music playing)
It wasn't the -- Oh.
It wasn't the three wishes thing
It was the Cinderella thing.
Did the fairy godmother
out of thin air?
No!
She had to make something
So she turned a pumpkin and mice
And you turned yourself
Well, not all at once,
First I got the legs.
And they came...
with heels and pantyhose.
And then, bit by bit,
I got the bow
(laughs)
You know, things like this,
once you start
And the clothes?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe it's like Barbie.
[Marci] That kinda made sense.
I mean Barbie always did come
(exhales sharply) If you're,
Well, who else
a semi-restored 1956
You could've stolen it.
Good one, Summer.
Tell us something
You two are desperate for dates
because you don't have any
Everyone  so  knows!
-[Summer] Oh!
I'm not finished.
No, but we are. Mom!
Swear to God, Marci, I am
Summer.
[Doris] Aren't they cute?
Isn't this what you wanted?
-[Judy] Summer!
Here's some crackers.
[Judy] Summer?
[Doris]
[Judy]
Ooh, athletic too.
Here, you're gonna need these.
Bye!
[Marci] Wait.
-[Judy] You sounded --
-[Summer] It was a mistake.
[Marci] What?!
Who are they?
Uh...
these guys.
Oh, do I know them?
Oh, probably not.
Summer, can I see you a sec?
Oh, would they like to come in?
I don't actually, like, know.
Summer!
You know we like
Ask them in.
Oh, I know what it's like
I'll be cool.
Summer!
(both chuckles nervously)
-[Marci] Whoa.
Really gotta tell you something.
-[Summer] Who are they?
-[Summer] Where did
She wasn't joking about
Hello, boys.
I'm Judy Weingarten,
They're rats?
Summer, that's not cute.
And who are you?
Oh, um, they -- they, you know,
um, they don't speak
Oh.
Are these the boys I read
Hmm? The foreign
Sweden?
Actually the exchange students
But...you know.
Sweden.
Sweden!
-(bird cawing)
Oh, that's right,
(laughs)
Names?
Sweden.
Yes, Sweden.
What are your names?
They really have to go.
Bye, guys.
[Judy] Summer Ann.
Uh, Mom, you don't understand.
(whispering) Go, please go.
[Judy]
It's hard enough
-[Judy] be in another culture...
...without people being rude.
Now, they learn about us from
It's a well-known fact
with her Electrolux
In my opinion, there are
So, I'll just be outside,
(birds chirping)
Summer, don't panic,
We have to do
(telephone ringing)
Pick up, Doris, please pick up,
She's not there.
Well, where is she?
Summer, how am
Like, she's got a hot bod,
anything could happen,
Summer, it's not polite
so you can talk on the phone.
-[Summer] We're not.
You have guests.
(clattering in distance)
(both gasp)
Personally, I never eat
on account of
I just can't get by it.
But it is so obvious that not
or anything would stop
who ate Jim Cunningham's
homework three different
(gasps)
(purring)
Bad. Bad rats!
Sweden!
Sweden.
Yeah, you stay back!
This cat's a killer.
Guard 'em.
You may remember him
Cats. Oh!
This is not what I need
Summer?
I don't feel right leaving 'em
Well, the rat that was in there
[Judy] Oh, Summer?
Ah-ha, yeah, listen
(Summer gasps)
Um...how's it goin' boys?
Listen,
and pick up some things and, uh,
then I should talk to them
No, no, no, no!
They ate my garage door!
Not all of it.
[Judy]
because I have to be
because I -- I really should
Oh, have the boys seen
I think that might be
(clattering in distance)
Now, it's easier
when you associate it
Minivan.
(tires screech in distance,
Mini-van.
[both] Minivan.
[Judy] Can you say airbag?
[both] Airbag.
-[both] Mini...mini-van...
[Judy]
[both] Airbag.
(music playing)
The plot thickens.
Now, Doris was used
But what she probably
is that getting
including designer outfit,
is way different
And going to the supermarket
[Doris] Yoo-hoo!
I bet you don't know who I am.
You've gotta expect that
is gonna be a total
I've lost a little weight
I also got straight teeth.
And big hair, although not
And perfect vision.
And I grew an inch and a half.
So, hey, what d'ya think?
Tenth grade English.
You sat right behind me.
You cheated off my test
Huh? Huh?
Come on.
Oh, my God!
Oh, I know I shouldn't have
taken the shopping cart
but you know what,
so I had to park over here
behind those
Oh, no, no. That is fine.
That is fine,
You can take the shopping cart
I can?
(music playing)
(siren chirps)
Excuse me. Excuse me, please.
Excuse me, please.
And I never miss an episode.
Hello. Excuse me.
What happened to Charles?
And welcome to Cloverdale,
birthplace of the legendary
and ancestral home
I'm Mayor Ed Feldman.
Just call me Mayor Ed.
And you are Regina Lee Savage?
Well, um...
What you've got
-[Doris] Yes? Yes, I'll hold.
the mayor won't even
When you're Regina Lee,
You are the popular
Anyone would be tempted under
Could I talk to you about
(chuckles) Anytime.
[man] ♪ Hey ♪
Well, then I  am  Regina Lee.
(cheers and applause)
Quiet down, everybody.
Please, everybody quiet down.
Uh, listen, uh --
Can I have your autograph?
[Ed] No, I'm sorry, darling,
Uh, Miss Savage, we have
over at the Kickapoo Expo Hall
a nondenominational
We'd love to have you
Me?
-[Ed] Yes.
[Ed] Please.
Oh, I'm sorry.
-[Ed] What?
What?
She's driving Doris's --
Let's don't --
Pay no attention to him.
I'm not even sure he lives here.
(indistinct shouting)
Hey, do you know Vicky Lawrence?
She was here, two years ago.
(music playing)
You were supposed to watch 'em
I'm absolutely sure they smelled
[Jennifer] See, I want to move
with like a bigger atmosphere.
I'm thinking Indianapolis.
[girl] Why? Why Indianapolis?
I don't know. The culture.
[boy] There you go.
[girls giggle]
Oh, my God.
Who are they?
[girl] They're gorgeous. Look.
[boy] Okay, will there
Yes, get out of the way.
[boy] Okay.
(music playing)
I always thought Jennifer might
I just never thought
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Come here.
Bad rats.
-[Summer] We gotta tie them up.
-[Marci] They'll
[Marci] And besides,
Don't be stupid.
Those guys with, like,
and Summer Spit Princess?
(scoffs)
Why do I seriously doubt it?
Girlfriends, why don't you come
Sit?
With you guys?
(chuckles) God, girlfriend.
She acts like
Oh, I'm Jennifer.
[Scooter] Minivan.
They're from Sweden.
[Jennifer] Sweden?
Sweden.
Minivan.
-[Spike] Minivan.
And you guys are showing them
What are your names?
I hope I can pronounce them.
Spike and Scooter.
(chuckles)
Would you like to join us?
You guys can take a break.
We'll show them around.
Spike and Scooter
This is Blair.
Airbag.
Huh?
Swedish.
-[Blair] Oh.
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
Logic told us that the rat boys
Okay, but, like, sorry,
with anything
[Jennifer] In this country
Oh.
I don't think there's
[Marci] Uh, that's okay.
We just wanted to make sure
understood that we were leaving.
It's not a difficult
Does my baby want a bite?
Yes, he does.
(chuckles nervously)
Well, we have places to be.
Spike, Scooter,
or come with us.
It's up to you.
Bye, girlfriends.
Bye.
[woman]
♪ I don't know nothing ♪
♪ Sock it to me, baby ♪
♪ I don't know
(both cheering)
-[Marci] Yes!
You did good, guys!
Did you see her face?
I know.
Of course.
They already heard I was dating
and didn't wanna cause any...
problems.
It's very thoughtful.
And also probably very Swedish.
Yeah, that explains you.
But what about us?
Yeah.
(music playing)
I don't know.
You guys should probably
Let's take 'em back to Doris.
We might as well take them
Yeah, we could take them
...you know...
...sometime.
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, sock it to me,
♪ I don't know nothing ♪
♪ Sock it to me, baby ♪
♪ I don't know
♪ Oh ♪
(music playing)
Oh! Oh, my God, is that Marci?
What do you mean keep them?
Not forever.
Just for tonight.
After the dance,
Summer, come on.
We would have guys way cooler
and for once, even Jennifer.
You are so obsessed
(gasps) I am so  not  obsessed
Look, I just wanna go
and not have to worry about
standing against
instead of dancing
Yeah, but, Marci, they're rats.
You liked the rats
Yeah, but I never wanted
I can so feel my face
and I just cleared up.
Look, all rats really wanna do
run on the treadmill,
What?!
Which -- Which,
Summer, doesn't make them
Most high school guys, anyway.
So we keep feeding them
and that'll keep their mind
off...the mating aspect
You better go get some nachos.
Yeah.
A double order.
[Summer] Okay.
(music playing)
(whines)
This is so unfair!
Everyone's gonna be
and I'm gonna be here
(music playing)
None of my other friends
I have the strictest parents
[Marci] Whining only really
And since obviously nobody was,
I had only ever sneaked out
But I only got caught once.
Aah!
Shh.
Herb, just take your evidence,
Hope you can get this
I'll have another talk with her,
I can't imagine that
Well, frankly I doubt
Whatever this is all about,
I'm sure it had nothing to do
-(loud thud)
Oh.
That's the second time today
I just saw you on TV.
Yeah, everyone thinks
Um, do you think that maybe
you're telling
Yeah, well,
Doris, look, okay, you're
pretending to be
Yeah, you're right.
I'm gonna turn everything
It's the best thing.
Go back to being myself.
Now you're making sense.
Turn those boys back into rats.
(sighs)
Don't overreact.
Um, your part of the deal
But Summer and me, our part
-(indistinct shouting)
Oh, um, Herb the handyman guy,
-[Doris] (gasps) Oh!
First we've got to go
We have to take a little ride,
Just go get in the car.
But I'm alive,
Looked in the mirror lately?
Oh, yeah.
Oh. (chuckles)
It's Doris they think is killed,
and Herb thinks that you did it.
Just use the ring,
and then show them.
Oh.
About the ring...
[Marci] Lost it!
(dog barking in distance)
Yes.
You have to help me find it.
I'm absolutely positive
or at the market, or --
or back at my store, or --
but, anyway,
and I'll take everything else.
But I -- I'm grounded.
And besides, I was just
[Doris] Marce, please.
Please?
(music playing)
Everybody's gonna be
I so can't believe it.
They're talking?
You look so good in pink.
I'm so not believing it.
(giggles)
Oh, my God, you guys.
Spike and Scooter had
that belonged
Steve, who joined the army.
[Summer] No!
(music playing)
The fact that they had
instead of eating
that things were now
Get back. Get back.
Yo, Ding Dongs.
I'm there.
[Judy]
Okay.
So that's Marci, so we're going
No talking.
(music playing)
I didn't know you two
(chuckles) Only since forever.
Girlfriend, hi.
[Judy] We are so proud of you
Junior Miss Indiana, Jennifer.
I know, everybody is.
-[Jennifer] Airbag.
Oh, the boys are back.
Me and Marci were
Oh, poor Marci.
She's been grounded.
At least, that's
so, I thought, why don't
and the boys too.
I mean if they were here.
Randy Frasier's
He's a junior
And, as he's my former
When did you break up?
Some time tonight.
Oh.
-[Scooter] No talking.
No. He's right.
Randy should be the first
He's been loyal,
But in the meantime,
I thought you guys might like
[Judy] Oh.
You're so obsessed
I so can't believe it.
I guess it's a yes.
Don't worry, Mrs. Weingarten,
I get that all the time.
Well, as long as Marci's
Come on, girlfriend.
I'm so not obsessed
You can be with Summer then.
(music playing)
[man] ♪ Hey ♪
(telephone ringing in distance)
(siren wailing in distance)
Okay, Herb, I want you
Just have a seat.
Yeah, it's Henderson.
Uh, I got that guy
He's waiting here in the lobby.
Just send somebody down,
pick him up and take him
Okay?
Just a second.
Somebody ripped off
I want justice.
Hello?
Hey. Hey, get out here.
Get off your coffee break.
It's time to deal with me.
Come on, I can't play my --
H-Have a seat right here.
Someone will be --
I'm bummed, man.
Understandable. Mm-hmm.
Come with me, please.
Yo. That was fast.
I got four months left
It's expensive.
(music playing)
(telephone ringing)
Hello?
Yes, yes, Rod, yes
Uh, no. No, I don't think
-[Rod] Tod.
-[Donna] Well, you're Rod.
[Rod] Marci came over
-[Donna] Excuse me?
-[Donna] The what?
I don't know anything
-[Rod] Ugh!
Do we know anything
-[Chuck] Rod?
Do we know a boy named Tod?
No.
I think we better talk
[Marci] (snoring, muttering)
Something about
I --
(snoring continues)
(snoring stops)
(sighs)
Marci.
(music playing)
You mean she's gone?
[Marci] I had so, like,
look for the ring on account
and I couldn't let her down
I was hoping that
left to go to the dance, too.
It's very important.
Did you happen to a --
-[boy] Nope.
It turned out that there was.
Man.
[Doris] Why can't you find
In movies, they're big
They show up
I got the new body.
I got the great shoes.
I got the hair.
Same ol' memory.
What have I done with this ring
and why did I buy
I don't care if they're on sale.
(music playing)
(engine starts)
-[Herb] Hands up!
Oh, look, okay, hands down,
Was that a gun in his pocket?
(indistinct conversations,
I was pretty out of breath
I figured I had
with Spike,
then figure out someplace
to store them
And then get back home
It all seemed pretty doable.
Until...
(music playing)
Betrayed!
Jennifer had won again.
She had the two coolest guys
eating right out
and my best friend
This was a wound so deep and --
I need to --
...that I...you know...
Okay, do you remember
Well -- Well, she --
..."Twilight Zone,"
-(Marci stammering)
Will you quit it?!
[Rod]
You remember Tod, right?
I don't know a guy named
This is what I'm trying
I so hope you are
Ugh!
Marci!
Jennifer said you were grounded.
Oh? And you were so quick
You weren't grounded?
Yes, I was so grounded,
I can't even believe you!
The point is that Tod --
-[Marci] The point is --
-[Rod] Tod! Tod!
and the  only  point is that --
[Ed] Excuse me, son.
Jennifer...
I need to speak to you
...my so-called friend --
[Ed] Can we go somewhere
(exhales sharply)
The point is, is that while you
Doris was in desperate
Desperate, okay?
And I, and only I, and I alone,
Summer, was the only
in a time of crisis
How bad do you feel now?
Doris is in trouble?
Don't try and change
(music playing on radio)
(music stops)
Oh, darn, high heels.
How does anybody walk
Ouch.
(metal creaking)
Oh.
Oh, boy.
-[Doris] You must
Okay, back away from the knight.
And no funny business.
You got me?
Mm-hmm.
You know what this is,
Well, um...
a-actually I do.
Oh, yeah?
It's a -- It's a --
Oh.
Don't make me use it, I will.
Oh, Herb.
This isn't like you.
(metal squeaks)
How come you know so much
And -- and the thing
even Doris didn't know
Oh, yes, she did.
She did, Herb, because she knew
in with your father
Alright, uh, inside.
Inside.
(telephone ringing)
Hello?
Oh, hi, Donna.
No.
No, she didn't come over here.
It's always bad news
what they think is going on.
[Donna]
I don't wanna upset you,
with Marci earlier.
In calling, around I heard
Marci and Summer were at
in the mall this afternoon,
Summer.
(record scratches)
And who was doing this?
[girls]
[Marci] Yes, you did.
[Summer] No I didn't.
Yes, you did.
No, I didn't.
[Marci] Yes, you did.
[Summer] No, I didn't.
-[Marci] Fine.
I'll just take Spike and Scooter
One belongs to me.
-[Marci] Fine.
(both gasp)
(music playing)
Hey!
Summer, we've been ripped off.
[Ed] Now, Jennifer,
(crying)
I know, dear, and we'll
But we have a real
[Marci] Something had happened.
For the first time in her life,
was not getting honored
Mel, Mel. Please.
Right after Regina Lee Savage,
I'll acknowledge Mel Ching of
(gasps)
Yeah, The Donut King supplied
all the refreshments
For that
My pleasure, Mayor Ed.
And my wife's nephew, Han Woo,
I'm after The Donut King's
Well, how often do we have a
Just put those boxes
Now, I'm sure you understand.
But she didn't understand.
And like, right then, you know,
was like this
that was not equipped
where your brain
or your nose broken or even
I, like, started hoping
Jennifer's side,
because she couldn't
(music playing)
Well,
Or Jennifer down either.
Hey, Ed, we got a problem.
Herb Soric is holding
[both] Uh-oh.
[Ed] What?!
(music playing)
I suggest we go on
Me first, you second, no nephew.
[man] ♪ Hey ♪
[Henderson] He phoned
that he was gonna hold her
until she told him what
-[Summer] Excuse me.
There you go, dear.
Like they never heard
(cheering in distance)
I tell you, Judy,
if we haven't been deceiving
I for one constantly feel
[Henderson] Ed, we can handle
I hope so.
Because if this ever hits
we're dead ducks.
(siren wailing)
(music playing, cheering)
Okay, wherever Herb is,
[both] Uh-oh.
We could tell them the truth.
I already tried that.
[Herb] Magic ring?
That's the stupidest thing
(sighs)
Well, is it any less farfetched
that some actress would come
and -- and --
What do you know about it?
Doris was kind and funny
she had a whole lot of what
somebody like you never notices
but somebody like me does.
Gee.
Somewhere in there is the nicest
Yeah, well...
I wasn't --
Only, I only just wish
Me too.
Why didn't you?
Yeah, well, I was working
For 22 years?
Then she gets bumped off by
Oh, oh.
Not the one about bumped off,
(sirens wailing,
Just a minute!
Don't get nervous.
Okay, okay.
(screaming in distance)
Excuse me!
Uh, okay. Okay.
Uh, Summer?
-[Marci] Faint.
Faint.
(music playing)
They can't yell at us
to the emergency room.
Summer!
Okay.
(exhales sharply)
(groans)
Good one, Summer.
Did she look in the mirror
-[Summer] I heard that.
[Summer] Ouch. Watch it!
Where do you think
Your  dates?
Well, your dates wanna go
in the parking lot, with us.
Heather, Blair, these guys,
They'll just tell you
You look so good
Summer, stay focused.
There's only one thing
that those guys
It's not food,
[both] Airbag.
She is so losing it.
Ugh!
You're gonna lose it,
Hey, I found Tod!
(Rod and Summer grunt)
What're you doing on the floor,
-[Summer] I fainted, okay?
Summer's fainted!
You have low blood sugar
I'm gonna try and find the ring.
-[Marci] Oh, right,
...'cause that's gonna be
He's like, "I wish
Well, I'm not fainting anymore,
-[Rod] And now he is
It's just 'cause
(thud)
What?!
(police radio chatter)
Ed, you might as well know
He tried to rob these people
Moses on the mountaintop.
Is there anything else
Come on, girls, you're gonna
Hey!
Don't lean against that.
You're gonna scratch up
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
Look, guys,
Brittany, please.
Hey, watch it.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
(music playing)
Let's go. Hurry up and ask.
-[Marci] Are you sure?
Excuse me.
Would you happen
Very sorry.
Han Woo speaks only Chinese.
Han Woo, I'm so sure.
Does he look Chinese to you?
-[Marci] Yeah.
(sighs)
Okay.
-[Doris] It's gotta
open the door
It's not a gun.
It's -- It's a bottle.
It's, uh -- wasn't a gun.
I know.
[Henderson]
(police radio chatter,
Bottle?
Alcohol is often a component
Break it down.
[man] Saddle up!
(men shouting indistinctly)
Maybe you could ask him.
(both speaking in Chinese)
This one?
[man] ♪ Ow ♪
Yes!
-[Summer] Thank you so much.
-[Marci] Thank you.
(music playing)
Marce -- Marci!
-[Marci] Aah!
[Blair] Oh, this is your car?
So, uh,
[both] Airbag.
[Blair]
(Spike and Scooter snicker,
Herb, help me look for it!
-(Pounding, Doris yelps)
A little ring you would think
[Henderson] We're gonna
Maybe I should've cleaned
(music playing)
Oh, hey, hey.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay. I wish that...
everything that got changed
turned exactly into the way
(magic warbling)
(music playing)
-[Doris] Aah! Listen!
Despite what I look like...
I actually am Doris Trowbridge.
Oh.
(music playing)
Alright, folks,
(electricity crackling,
[both] They're rats!
Aah! Aah!
[Marci] There's a lesson here
(both gasp)
You have got
Summer?
What's this I hear about
at the food court?
Oh, well, it was just the hand,
and I washed it
Marci Kornbalm, I hope you have
because I have got
Does that mean we have to go?
At least we got
(music playing)
[Judy] Just wait until
from that international
He's gonna have a few choice
Can you say grounded? Hmm?
Marci, call me when you finish
Oh, yeah, in about 20 years!
Oh, I am so never gonna
(rats squeaking)
Spike. Scooter.
[Donna] What're you doing?
Come on, Mom,
[Donna] Marci, when I said now,
No, really this will explain
(Donna screams)
[Herb] Well, obviously Doris
behind the counter there.
And then the, uh...
the actress jumped behind
Doris, uh, probably
when they were behind
Is it just me or what?
And then Doris came out.
-[Ed] Herb.
Look, the only thing
and she's -- she's --
That's the only thing
that -- that Doris is here
Like, sometimes I think
that if an asteroid
you know, and hit the Earth,
the first thing my mom
Marci Kornbalm,
that you are responsible
I'm not, Mom.
Um, I'm just gonna go there
Yeah.
[woman] We're in front of
where Herb Soric attempted
Marce, Marce...
Hey, Marci!
Marci! No. Hey.
[woman] Uh, wait, we have
-[woman] Uh, ma'am. Ma'am.
No, I don't wanna be on TV.
[Ed] Herb, you've always
And now you suddenly have
that two people were behind
You expect the voters
[Henderson] Well, nobody
'til this thing is solved.
That means mostly for you two.
[Doris] Herb.
(indistinct conversation)
Did you really mean that, Herb?
That I'm the most important
[Henderson] ...that Herb has
Herb, don't take
to say something, please.
[Ed] The most important thing,
is that we're missing
Now, you say all this happened
Where is it?
[Doris] I -- I don't have it.
I didn't know
even if she had the ring back.
As far as I could tell,
no matter
there was always gonna be
I just have to find it.
Doris, don't give me
short-term memory loss jazz.
I wish everyone
(cuckoo clocks dinging)
I don't remember.
What?
Anything since last November.
Oops.
Um, just about stuff
[Ed] Oh, yeah, now I remember.
Except, what are we doing here?
Well, I, uh, guess I need
-(Marci gasps)
[Marci] And not whatever
were talking about.
(magic warbling)
I could -- I could stay.
(clock chiming)
(opera music playing)
I was, like, so proud of myself
with the perfect solution
Mom had forgot all about
and Summer getting licked,
of I hate to see her worry
Mom, Mom,
We're going now?
No.
No, Marci, I'm trying
Yeah, Ma?
This morning when you asked
if you could have
what did we say?
Yes or no?
(music playing)
Well, Mom, as I recall
Of course Summer had forgotten
just like everybody else,
and it took me most of the next
She wanted her own
[Marci] Lost it?!
[both]
Girls, shh.
It's not lost,
I found a ring in the back room.
It isn't worth much.
I put it some place
I can't remember where.
You know, I forgot where I put
Well, we're all getting older.
Oh, Doris, please, please try
It'll turn up.
[Summer] Why didn't you wish
(box rattling,
Hello, Hidden Treasures.
Oh.
Hello.
Oh, dinner?
That would be lovely.
The end.
[Summer]
I so can't believe it.
What did she give you?
Ah, a D-plus.
She obviously doesn't like me.
What?
Let me see.
Well, she said the assignment
But it was true,
You have your own phone,
said you couldn't have,
And you have the rats
Plus, you wrote six pages when
And everybody knows
that really happened
I, like, also lost 20 points
And then she goes,
why Rod could remember
and that I could remember
And then I was all like,
Some things can't be explained."
That's why I put the part
Oh...sorry.
I know that's your great
That's life.
What can you do?
You are so right.
And that's what I told her.
So much of life is a mystery.
And nobody's there
Why do I gotta start
What did she say?
Started going on
What attitude?
Ugh! Exactly.
But then, she says if I rewrite
I can turn my D plus into a C.
And that's exactly
Watch this.
"So, it's, like, a year
I think there's a comma
You are such a good friend.
(music playing)
So it's, like, one year
I think the ring is still
on account of lots
has happened
(cheers and applause)
(music playing)
We both got our braces off,
earlier than expected,
And now we have retainers,
which are way more cool,
(music playing)
Jennifer doesn't
she did before the ring
Actually, I don't mind her
(music playing)
And now, when we wanna dance,
See, what Summer and me
is that we were
And if some people
it's their problem,
(music playing)
But the real magic
and, like, why i think the ring
has to do with Rod and Tod --
Like, all of a sudden
and they smell like shampoo.
How amazingly magical is that?
(music playing)
[man] ♪ So you wanna be
♪ While you're strumming
(music continues indistinctly)
As for Doris, well,
the high school experience
because of the transplant
Wanna dance?
It will be awkward for her,
but generally worth it.
I thought you'd never ask.
(music playing)
(exhales sharply)
[girl] ♪ Boys make
♪ But I think boys
♪ Tender like a baby ham ♪
♪ Sticky with pineapple jam ♪
♪ Sniff your heady new perfume ♪
♪ Clear your plate
(music playing)
♪ Boys are super crunchy treat ♪
♪ Make a cookie hard to beat ♪
♪ Butter up
♪ Like a chewy macaroon ♪
♪ Tease the palate
♪ Then the kettle
♪ I'm so hungry when I see ♪
♪ A juicy boy in front of me ♪
♪ Give me
♪ With boy as side dish
(music playing)
♪ Some are sweet
♪ Pour the milk
♪ Others simmer all day long ♪
♪ Bubble up
♪ Any way they're done
♪ Smack your lips
♪ I'm so hungry when I see ♪
♪ A dishy boy in front of me ♪
♪ Give me
♪ Of boy fondue
♪ I don't want a sirloin steak ♪
♪ Don't give me
♪ What my tummy needs the most ♪
♪ Creamy boy
♪ When he's nibbled
♪ Please, sir,
(music playing)
♪ Boys make
♪ But I think boys
♪ Tender like a baby ham ♪
♪ Sticky with pineapple jam ♪
♪ Sniff your heady new perfume ♪
♪ Clear your plate
(music playing)
♪ Boys are super crunchy treat ♪
♪ Make a cookie hard to beat ♪
♪ Butter up
♪ Like a chewy macaroon ♪
♪ Tease the palate
♪ Then the kettle
♪ I'm so hungry when I see ♪
♪ A juicy boy in front of me ♪
♪ Give me
♪ With boy as side dish
(music playing)
♪ Some are sweet
♪ Pour the milk
♪ Others simmer all day long ♪
♪ Bubble up
♪ Any way they're done
♪ Smack your lips
♪ I'm so hungry when I see ♪
♪ A dishy boy in front of me ♪
♪ Give me
♪ Of boy fondue
♪ I don't want a sirloin steak ♪
♪ Don't give me
♪ What my tummy needs the most ♪
♪ Creamy boy
♪ When he's nibbled
♪ Please, sir,
(music playing)
[END CREDITS]