Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[tense music]
[muffled whimper]
[tense music continues]
[grunt]
[muffled groan]
[Vin] Now,
looks like
a little cocksucker, all right.
[tense music]
Always a pleasure, Vin.
Worth every fuckin' penny, pal.
[muffled grunting]
- [thud]
- Shut the fuck up!
[muffled groaning]
You want in on any of this?
I'll pass.
Oh, yeah.
Retrieval only. I forgot.
[phone buzzing]
Your next gig?
[snaps fingers]
[muffled grunting]
[metal music]
[splintering crash]
♪ If you wanna shoot me down ♪
♪ Fire away ♪
♪ My final round ♪
♪ Won't be today ♪
♪ You wanna kill me, huh? ♪
♪ Go on, take your shot ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm goin' on ♪
♪ No plan to stop ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[subway rumbling]
♪ Come and take a mission ♪
♪ But it makes no difference ♪
♪ It may make you finally see ♪
♪ Gonna [unclear]
Your whisperin' ♪
♪ But the walls are listenin' ♪
♪ Maybe it all goes bad ♪
♪ Today, hey, hey ♪
[music continues]
[slam]
♪ You wanna shoot me down ♪
♪ Fire away ♪
♪ My final round ♪
♪ Won't be today ♪
♪ You wanna [unclear] ♪
♪ Go take your shot ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm goin' on ♪
♪ No plan to stop ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I will win ♪
♪ Fire away ♪
[song ends]
[muffled rhythmic dance music]
[click]
Hey. Gotta dance.
Get somebody else.
He asked for you.
I don't want to leave.
You're not going anywhere.
Listen to me.
Your numbers are low.
You owe the house.
You need to get out there.
[muffled dance music continues]
I always pay.
[announcer] All right.
Coming up next to the stage,
Waterfall!
[fast-paced rhythmic music]
[door slams]
You are a hard girl to find.
M-mm.
That was the idea.
What are you doing here?
Just business.
Thought I'd see my favorite
dancing girl on there.
You miss me?
[music continues]
No.
I don't miss you.
You know,
the boss wants to see you.
Which one?
I only work for Jefe,
you know that.
Yes.
Whatever you say.
Somebody's
been talkin' about me.
They around?
Someone's been sayin'
I'm workin' for myself.
It ain't true,
and it's got to stop.
- [snap]
- I heard it was you.
Rumors about me all the time.
But I'll make sure
to put out the word.
Angel is an honest man,
untouchable,
no more name calling.
[chuckles]
Always good to see you again.
Me, too, but,
I don't do that anymore.
Only dancing.
Oh, just one more time,
- like we used to.
- [ominous music]
No! I can't!
- [slap]
- No!
You get off...
- [grunt]
- Fuck off!
- Come here, you little...
- [thud]
- [grunt]
- [crash]
Hey!
- [thump]
- [grunt]
[rhythmic dance music]
- [thump]
- [grunt]
[music ends]
Hi, handsome!
Can give me a ride?
- Uh...
- Please?
Sure. Where we going?
Wherever you are.
- Please?
- Oh-okay.
- [engine rumbling]
- Let's go.
- Let's go! Go! Go!
- Okay, okay! I'm drivin'!
[muffled dance music]
[anticipatory music]
[cellphone ringing]
[voicemail] Please leave
a message for, Cully.
[beep]
[man] Cully.
Where the fuck are you?
You missed the drop.
Check in. Now.
- [click]
- [beep]
[voicemail] Message deleted.
- [click]
[man] His patience
is wearing thin, my friend.
You know how this goes.
Either you come to us,
or we come to you.
Don't make us
come find you, Cully.
[click]
- [beep]
- [voicemail] Message deleted.
[beep]
[Emma] Daddy,
pick up your phone.
I need to talk to you.
I really want you
to share in this with us,
so don't be mad, okay?
- Love you, Daddy. Call me.
- [click]
- [beep]
- [voicemail] Message saved.
[relaxing shop music]
[cough]
- [tense music]
- [shopping cart clattering]
[tense music building]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[gun clicks]
[tense music]
[anticipatory music]
[engine rumbling]
[engine cuts]
[tense music]
[shop music]
[crackle]
[tense music building]
[gunshots]
[shotgun cocks]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[thump]
[shop music]
- [gun clicks]
- Yo, Cully. Come out.
Okay. Okay.
[tense music]
- [gunshot]
- [grunt]
[thump]
[exhales]
[ominous music]
[fast-paced music]
[door slams]
[engine starts]
[tires squealing]
[engine roaring]
[gun clicks]
[music fades]
[soft tense music]
[safety belt clicks]
Get out of the car.
[door clicks]
I can get you money.
No.
Put these on.
Oh, come on.
Let me take the car south
and I can get you real money.
How am I supposed to
get my next job
if I sell out on this one?
Come on, man,
you don't have to do this.
I know.
I just love it so much.
Damn.
Really?
[gun clicks]
[cellphone rings]
Yeah.
[Turk] What?
I've been trippin'
over bounty hunters
all the way down the coast.
Well...
somebody sent them.
The car.
Yeah, it's here.
The deal was for the driver.
Fine.
The car'll cost him extra.
Change of plans.
[quirky music]
Where we goin'?
Disneyland? [chuckles]
Get in.
[door clicks]
Hey, look,
I like your car better.
Yeah. Well, come on.
This car is empty, dog.
You got a gas card?
[quirky music continues]
I said no.
Lot of trouble
for a piece of shit car.
Oh, man, that's not heavy.
I'm gonna have to
pay that shit back.
[engine starts]
[engine cuts]
Hey, baby.
I wanna listen to music.
Can you leave
the keys in the car, please?
You're so cute.
Hey, okay. But after this,
can we go to
the hotel up the street.
I know a good one,
it's a hourly rate.
We can save money...
I know exactly what you want,
looking forward to it.
- Go, go!
- Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hey! Come back soon! [kiss]
[quirky music continues]
Hey, baby. Get me a lemonade!
A lemonade? Okay!
[engine rumbling]
Oh! What the fuck?
Get out my way!
Shit!
Fuck. Fuck.
[engine starts]
Asshole!
Where you goin'?
[engine fades]
Wait!
Hey, what are you
gonna do with me?
Take you back.
Today?
Right now.
They're gonna kill me
once they get their hands on me!
Jefe's a powerful man.
You should have
thought about that
before you stole his car.
Oh, really?
Thanks a lot, jackass.
Hindsight's twenty-twenty,
all right?
Motherfucker.
You know, I gotta make a stop.
Hey!
[safety belt clicks]
You hear me?
[Cully] I gotta make one stop.
Yeah.
Said I gotta make a...
One stop.
[door slams]
- This ain't a taxi, man.
- I got a kid.
- You got a kid?
- Yeah.
Good for you.
Hey, look. Come on.
She's young,
I haven't seen her in years.
Please.
She's gettin' married tomorrow.
That ain't my problem.
Oh, come on, man!
I'm beggin' you, man!
Please.
- Come on, man!
- Do you ever shut up?
One more word out of you
and you're goin' in the trunk.
[Cully] Please?
Is that a word?
Yeah.
Come on. Please!
[unclear]
[ominous music]
[clatter]
Where is he?
I don't know.
[gasping]
Please don't kill me.
I won't say anything.
I know.
[gunshot]
- [car ambiance]
- [lighter clicks]
[scrape]
[engine roaring]
- [crash]
- [squealing tires]
- [gunshot]
- [grunt]
- [grunts]
[dramatic music]
[gunshot]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[slam]
Oi, Turk. Fancy seeing you here.
Five million ride, man.
Go! Go! Go!
I'm goin'! Jesus!
Maybe we find some place
to ditch the car.
Can't ditch the car.
We can't ditch the car.
We're standin' out, Cully!
We've been made.
No! We can't lose the car!
All right?
[dog barking]
[door rumbling]
-[click]
[chuckling]
Oh, man, there's nothing
wrong with this car.
This car is fine, dude.
Bro.
Oh, you can trust me, you know?
Yeah.
[quirky music]
[slam]
[clatter]
Oh, shit.
[groaning]
[tense music]
[dog barking]
[music fades]
It's a money car.
Oh. Yeah.
From over the border.
Oh.
- Originally, yeah.
- Why?
Why would they smuggle
so much drug money at once
and take the risk?
They bought on an inspector,
they had an in...
Who knows?
Shit happens. You know?
Explains why everyone
in Baja has been after us.
That's like 500,000 dollars,
and you just decided
to take a joyride to
your daughter's wedding, today.
Look...
Kill me, man.
See it like
an opportunity, all right?
But, I know they're gonna
wanna have it back, so...
- I get it.
- Yeah? Yeah.
Look.
Hey.
Unless,
we make a run with it, or...
You make a run with it.
You know what it's like
to have guys
like this after you?
I do.
Too well. But...
just change cars.
That'll take time.
And then we'll actually
be in a stolen car,
that was reported.
So what's the idea, then, champ?
Drive the car down the coast
and take it straight to Jefe.
And give the money back?
It's the shortest distance
between here
and not getting killed.
I get it. Let's go.
[quirky music]
- [gun cocks]
- Cully!
[slam]
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry.
You wanna ride in the front,
or in the trunk?
I'll ride wherever
you want me to
as long as you don't kill me.
Get in the front.
- [tense music]
- [breathing heavily]
- Lalo!
- [grunts]
- What happened?
- Lalo!
They got away.
- Where's Paco?
- They...
Where's my brother?
They shot him
on the street, ese.
Lalo?
They shot Emma and got away.
They still have the money car.
[groaning]
Call the boys.
Call everyone!
[cellphone beeps]
[fast-paced music]
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
♪ Candy was the kind
You never never knew ♪
♪ Where she had
A switchblade temper ♪
♪ A shotgun mouth ♪
♪ She were all bad
And never once was good ♪
♪ But you didn't
Mess with Candy ♪
♪ 'Less you were [unclear] ♪
♪ Stand left ♪
♪ Meet the hotel bar ♪
♪ Neon lights
Make the face look hot ♪
♪ Cigarette ♪
♪ Between red lips ♪
♪ Faded dress shaking
From those hips ♪
♪ I was rolling in ♪
♪ She was standing out ♪
[engine revving]
[gasps]
♪ Well, you are walking away ♪
♪ And I've been walking by ♪
- [engine cuts]
- [song cuts]
Hey. What luck.
[chuckles]
What, you got
a little car trouble?
Yeah.
Actually, my, uh...
my friend's
gonna be here soon, he...
He knows exactly where I am.
- And right now, he, uh...
- [snorts]
- He should be here...-
- Relax.
I'm sorry about that back there.
No hard feelings, huh?
No. No hard feelings.
No hard feelings.
Been lookin' for this car.
We weren't sure if maybe
you had somethin' to do with it.
A car?
Money car.
Loaded down with eight bills.
I, uh...
Guy named Culpeper stole it.
You know him?
[ominous music]
Who?
[sighs]
Why don't you just hop in?
Come on.
Well, I should
wait for my friend.
- He's gonna be here.
- Oh, that could be hours.
Come on.
Well...
I'm not in a hurry
to go anywhere, so I...-
Don't be stupid, Crystal!
Come on.
Tell you what.
Why don't you and I
take out this Culpeper guy,
I'll take you back to Jefe,
we'll clear the air.
It'll be fine.
Come on.
Shit.
[exhales]
Okay.
Good girl.
[engine starts]
♪ ...I was rollin' in ♪
♪ She was standing 'round ♪
What the hell?
Goddamn traffic. [sighs]
Must be a accident.
Shit.
- [upbeat Spanish song]
- [engine hissing]
Where am I gonna go?
Nowhere.
That's the point.
Aren't we a little exposed here?
- Huh?
- Yep.
You should take
the three-oh-seven.
One-eighty is safer.
It feels sort of faster.
If there's no traffic.
But they're
gonna be expecting us
to take the three-oh-seven.
One-eighty,
with two-ninety-five.
What?
Back to three-oh-seven.
Dude, that adds an hour!
We stay out of view,
and nobody gets hurt.
Hey, gimme two hot dogs.
[horn honking]
[muffled tense music]
- [cellphone beeps]
- [ring tone]
Hey, homie. Check it, man.
Blue car, two cars back.
[fast-paced Spanish rap song]
Oh, I know a place where
we can stop to eat in Rosarito,
if we take the three-oh-seven,
just gotta turn...
turned off right here.
Is that where
your daughter's mother lives?
What? Oh, no. Of course not.
♪ Between red lips ♪
♪ Faded dress shaking
From those hips ♪
♪ I was rollin' in ♪
- Get down.
- What?
Don't turn around.
We got company.
Shit.
[distorted music]
- [gun cocks]
- Cut me out of these right now
before they kill me.
Come on.
- [snick]
- [grunt]
Shit.
Just. Stay. Cool.
[tense anticipatory music]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
- [door slams]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[horn honking]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[tires squealing]
[rapid gunfire]
[rapid gunfire stops]
Shit!
[soft tense music]
Put it down.
- Get in.
- [gunshots]
[gunshot]
- [engine roaring]
- [tires squealing]
[horn honking]
Get out of the car!
I didn't do nothing. Hey!
What the fuck, man!
[engine roaring]
Fuck.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
[exhales]
[lighter clicking]
Shit.
What's your name?
Turk.
[engine rumbling]
[sighs]
Crystal.
Who was that guy?
Who?
The bald guy with the Beretta.
You mean Angel.
He, uh...
He's a hit man,
work for a mob boss. Jefe.
- [exhales]
- Jefe.
I know Jefe.
Who were the other dudes?
Just locals.
Must know about the money.
You know this guy Cully?
He used to work for, Jefe.
He was a...
driver.
Driver, like smuggler.
Like bodyguard?
Like a guy, with a funny hat.
[smooth music]
So...
He just decided to steal
a car full of money one day.
He saw the chance, I guess.
Where do you think he's goin'?
His daughter.
Somethin' about
his daughter gettin' married.
[music fades]
What do you mean,
they got the car?
He took it.
Who?
That Cully guy.
He took it and headed south.
- Fuck them!
- [clatter]
[soft clatter]
[speaking Spanish]
There were others.
- Who else?
- A crazy dude.
Bald.
Shot the whole place up.
There's a gringo
and a woman, too.
All right.
I think I know
where they are going.
Luis?
Get my cousin on a clean phone.
Go.
Go!
[tense music]
Gracias, mamacita!
[fast-paced tense music]
[door rumbling]
[music fades]
[door clicks]
[rattle]
[tense music]
[thump]
[tense music continues]
[door clicks]
[grunting]
[rumble]
[thump]
[music fades]
[rustle]
[soft tense music]
Hi.
Don't worry.
Are you okay?
- Where's Emma?
- She's fine.
Um, we don't have her?
Now won't you shut up, man?
Huh?
I'm sure you know
my cousin Marcos.
- Huh?
- Marcos.
Oh.
Yeah, well, he sent us out to
go look for your daughter, but...
your wife will do.
Why?
Well, you're gonna do
a little job for us, man.
We got a proposition for you.
Like what?
You're gonna whack Jefe.
You gonna kill him by tomorrow.
[chuckles]
Me? [laughs]
You want me to kill
the biggest drug lord in Baja?
Really? [chuckles]
[laughs]
- Hilarious, right?
- Yeah, I think so.
[laughs]
Yeah. That's exactly
what you gonna do.
And then you gonna deliver
the car with the money in it.
Either that...
or you never see her again.
Oh.
Mm. [scoffs]
Hey?
Are you a sick man?
You telling me that
you would orphan your daughter?
Why, hang on, no.
Oh, I mean...
Yeah, I know. I know.
No-I mean, of course.
Huh? You would
make your daughter motherless,
- is that what you're sayin'?
- Maybe.
I mean, have you
spent any time with her?
Fuck you, Cully, you prick!
Get me out of here!
I'm workin' on it, okay?
But I gotta like you, okay?
Help me, okay?
You gotta help me out here.
Hey, shut up, man!
Where's the car?
What car?
The car with the money in it!
Um, I don't believe I know
what you're talking about, sir.
Just give them the car already.
I can't give them, I don't
have...
I don't have the car, Maria!
I can't give it to 'em!
Liar!
Because you steal everything!
Of course he has it!
He stole my mother's earrings
and sold them.
One time-You burned my clothes!
You screwed that
cheap waitress at the bar!
She wasn't, she was
a thousand dollars an hour!
- And we were separated!
- Shut the hell up!
Enough already, man.
I get it, man.
The both of you guys
don't like each other, right?
Look, man, what...
Where's-where's your daughter?
- Out.
- Out where?
I don't know.
She's out with friends.
Wait, wait, wait, back up, man.
You guys mean to tell me
you don't even know
where your own daughter's at?
- Huh?
- She's a grown woman!
She's 18, man!
You know what, man?
The both of you guys
are terrible parents.
Check yourself.
Terrible parents, my ass!
I gave that girl everything!
I mean... I mean,
we gave her everything.
- I mean...
- What?
- I mean, more Maria.
More Maria, gave her everything.
Why don't you give me
my damn child support?
Oh, god. Child support!
I'm so tired of child support!
I'm workin' on it, all right!
I...
Oh, you've been
working on it for years!
Shut up!
All right. Listen, man.
May-maybe this was
a mistake. You know what?
I tell you what.
The boys are gonna
go looking for your daughter.
You're gonna whack Jefe,
and then you're gonna
hand over the money in the car.
And the girls,
oh, let's just say,
they're gonna walk free,
all right?
But before that, Lewis,
dumb shit here,
he's gonna take you to the car,
and you know
where the keys are at.
Oh. What keys?
- [click]
- [gun cocks]
I remember something.
I'm sorry. You mean the...
You must mean the...
these keys right here.
Yeah. All of a sudden
your memory's back, huh?
Well, the shotgun helped me out.
It jogged my memory.
Yeah, it does that sometimes.
Man, shut him the hell up!
Sorry.
- Shut him up!
- I'm sorry.
[car ambiance]
You work for Jefe, too?
No.
Just a freelance contract.
Retrieval.
The guy Cully?
More his car, it seems.
But yeah.
Look.
I can help you.
I don't need the liability.
The daughter's
getting married tomorrow.
Yeah?
You know what brides go,
before their weddings?
[techno song]
Whoo!
[engine cuts]
Okay.
Do you know a lot of background
in bachelorette
hangouts, do you?
What do you want?
A cut.
No.
A small cut.
Couple of [unclear].
No.
What you gonna tell Jefe?
When you come up dry.
Is he gonna believe you,
or he's gonna think,
maybe, you took the money?
Let's call it, sub-contract.
A kickback.
Whatever.
I know the town.
I know how to find the daughter.
And then we can
trace her back to Cully.
Sounds good?
All right.
[chuckles]
- Let's go!
- Shup up, already.
[engine starts]
[door rumbles]
[engine turns over]
Hey, man.
Aren't you gonna flood it?
Oh, no, it's fine.
Fine, it's all right.
[engine turning over]
Damn!
Maybe you're right.
I gotta have a look. Yeah.
Real quick.
Hey, pop...
pop the trunk, will you?
Yeah, right there.
- [click]
- Great.
Come here, gimme a hand, man.
Come on.
You want the car or not?
Come on. Give me a hand.
Right there,
right there, right there.
[rattle]
Oh, shit.
Put your hand right there.
Yeah.
Yeah, both hands, man.
You want the car or not?
- Here?
- Yeah, right.
- Now, don't move.
- Okay.
- Don't move.
- [tense music]
- [clang]
- Ready?
- [slam]
- [grunt]
[slam]
[thump]
I flooded it, man.
You were right.
[upbeat music]
♪ Yo. Yo ♪
♪ Snapshot, yo ♪
♪ With your hands, yo ♪
♪ Get it ♪
♪ Come on... ♪
♪ Come on, dog ♪
♪ The party crackdown ♪
♪ Yeah, come on ♪
♪ Snapshot, yo ♪
♪ With your hands, yo ♪
I would have
loved to take you out...
You still can!
I can't. You're already taken.
I'm still single
for a few more hours, you know?
Honey, guess who?
Daddy?
It's me! Let's go.
We gotta go. Time to go.
Hey, dude.
Take your hand off me
or I'll cut your arm off!
- Daddy!
- No-Honey, I'm just joking.
How are you?
It's so good to see you.
[muffled music]
[music fades]
[tense music]
- [thuds]
- [grunt]
- [thud]
[music fades]
Look.
You are entirely too young to be
drinking at a place like this.
- I am a grown woman!
- You are a little girl.
- I'm getting married tomorrow.
- And who's that guy?
I don't know, some guy.
Okay, where's the other guy,
the fiancé?
I don't know.
Okay, how long ago
did you meet him?
Three years.
How old is he?
Twenty-one.
Okay. You were 15 years old?
What kinda guy
dates a fifteen-year old girl?
We didn't-I just liked him.
We dated later.
Come here.
It's okay, too.
Whatever the answer is.
- Are you pregnant?
- No!
[ominous music]
Um...
When this is over... [chuckles]
- I wanna meet him, okay?
- Okay?
Let's... let's go.
We gotta go, really fast, okay.
- When what is over?
- Don't worry about it.
[tense music]
[gun clicks]
[fast-paced tense music]
- [gun clicks]
- Down!
- [gunshots]
- [screaming]
[gunshot]
Go! Go! Go!
[gunshots]
[gunshot]
- [gunshots]
- [scream]
- [gunshot]
- Emma!
I'm with your father,
you'll see. Come!
Come with me!
[gunshots]
[Emma gasping]
- [gunshots]
- [Emma gasping]
- [screaming]
[gunshot]
- [gunshots]
- [screaming]
[gunshots]
[gunshot]
[thump]
- [gunshot]
- [grunt]
[gunshot]
[screaming]
[gunshots]
[gunshot]
[tense music]
[shotgun clicking]
[gun clicking]
[tense music]
[shotgun cocked]
- [gunshots]
- [scream]
[gunshot]
[crying]
- [gunshots]
- [screaming]
[gunshot]
Freeze!
[gun clicks]
- [gunshots]
- [screams]
Oh my god, he's shooting at us!
[crying]
[gunshots]
[gunshot]
[whoosh]
[thump]
- [high-pitched hum]
- [tense music]
- [grunt]
What are you doing here?
- Put it down.
- Hey, Turk.
It-it's empty.
Cully?
Daddy!
- Don't...
- My daughter!
- Don't do it.
- My daughter, man. I gotta...-
- I gotta go, man.
[gunshot]
- Go!
- [gunshot]
[gunshots]
[thump]
[ominous music]
[whimpering]
- [tires squealing]
- [whimpering]
Okay. Okay.
[ominous music]
[groaning]
Oh, shit.
Come on.
[groan]
- [thump]
- [grunt]
Daddy! Daddy!
[splutters] It's okay, honey.
It's okay. It's okay. [chuckles]
No, it's not okay.
Where's the car!
Um, I don't know, man.
Where'd you park it, dude?
Cully, just tell them.
- What?
- Just tell them!
You know what,
you're never on my side!
Never on my side. Ever!
Why are you never on my team?
What are you talking about?
Like when
we were to get married,
your father said
I'd never amount to anything
but like a punk and a...
you know,
hoodlum and a crook, you know?
So, you're not.
That's true. It's a bad example.
Daddy, just give them the car!
Um-How could you
let her marry this guy?
What, like it's
not her decision?
Uh-he's not
good enough for her!
You don't even know him!
I know him. I know the type.
God, I know him.
He's always hustlin',
looking for the angle,
bullshittin'...
- Oh. Well, you mean like you.
- No, like him.
- [thump]
- [grunt]
- Damn.
- Where's the goddamn car, man?
Enough of this bullshit
already, all right?
I'm done playing
with your ass, man!
- [groaning]
- Where's the car?
And she's too young!
She's the same age we were!
Exactly! Look at you,
you're a wreck!
- You've proved my point!
- Daddy, stop!
Just give them the car.
Young lady,
listen to your father.
Relax.
For your mother and father
are trying to have a talk.
What's she
supposed to do, Cully?
You're never around.
You've never been
here to support her.
[gun cocked]
[tense music]
Here's the deal.
No more playin', all right?
You tell me
where the car is, man,
or it's your last day today.
Um, hang on.
No [grunts]
Okay.
She goes first, you get it?
- [whimpers]
- She goes first!
Where's the car?
You gotta listen to me, man.
Everything,
that I value, and have,
in the world, is in this room.
Now you pull that trigger,
and I ain't got
nothin' to lose, brother.
Nothin'.
And you, and no one, ever,
see that money.
You a funny guy, huh?
- I ain't funny at all.
- Huh, you're crackin' jokes.
You actually do
got a valid point, though, man.
I never gave anything, Maria,
until now.
And now I'm
doin' somethin' for you.
Where would they go?
I don't know. I don't know.
A safe house,
maybe a drop point.
They're not exactly
in the fuckin' phone book.
Come on. Think.
[exhales]
I'll kill Jefe for you
like you want.
All right?
You get all his shit.
All his trafficking rounds,
infrastructure, everything,
it's all yours.
Yeah, you take his spot,
and you step up,
and you're a major player.
All right?
All I want,
is you let my girls go.
[exhales]
Jefe has some properties
in this area.
Real estate,
condos,
and garages.
Could be anywhere.
Oh, shit.
Road block.
Shit.
[engine rumbling]
[engine cuts]
What I don't get is,
why are you so into all this?
You know some of these guys.
Don't you wanna stay out of it?
Yes, I do.
I wish I could.
But it's not what you think.
It's not that simple.
Look.
You're a dancer.
You can make that
kind of money in a weekend.
And you won't have to
deal with all this shit.
You'd be free.
You don't know me. We just met.
You don't know my story.
You don't know
what I'm running from.
Don't call me dancer!
[soft tense music]
Let's put this way.
It's better than being, alone.
I will make sure,
that nothin',
nothin' at all,
will ever touch you.
No idea, no one got an idea,
that I whacked Jefe, for you.
Okay?
Now you kill me,
no one's gettin' nothin'.
Right?
So, take the deal.
'Cause most likely
I'm not gonna make it out alive.
Either way...
your next birthday,
you're really rich.
Really rich.
You got my attention.
He's a dead man walkin',
he just doesn't know it yet.
He's a dead man.
Hang tight.
I'm gonna move the pins.
[door clicks]
[door slams]
- [tense music]
- [footsteps]
[engine starts]
Asshole!
[engine revving]
We're workin' together.
[exhales]
[reflective music]
♪ Love, but not for love ♪
♪ [unclear] not at all ♪
♪ One more round ♪
♪ And then I'll heed The song ♪
♪ Another round
For the day I met you ♪
♪ A round for the day you cry ♪
♪ Another round
Since the day I left you ♪
[siren wailing]
[crash]
- [tires screeching]
- [crash]
♪ Round inside ♪
♪ One last gasp of mercy ♪
♪ Another round, another mercy
♪ Some stay lost
While others... ♪
♪ A round
For the day I met you ♪
♪ A round on the day you cry ♪
♪ A round
Since the day I left you ♪
♪ A round inside ♪
[thump]
[elevator dings]
[rhythmic beeping]
[music fades]
[grunt]
[groan]
[coughing]
Too many Cubans.
They give you these tanks
to keep you alive.
But all they really mean is
you're dying
a slow, painful death.
Thank you for coming.
I lost the car.
But I can get it back.
I need some information,
on your driver Cully.
[coughing]
[retching cough]
Jefe?
She must have been screwing him.
Hell, she was probably
fucking half my men.
I saw how he looked at her.
And I saw how
she looked at all of them.
But, I understand
what it must be like
to be married
to someone half dead,
twice your age.
Married?
I've reason to believe
her life is in danger
from a madman.
Yeah.
I think we met.
- Why did you send him?
- I didn't.
Angel was my best wet worker.
Twenty years,
and now he's gone off the map.
It's not your problem any more.
I'll take it from here.
[labored breathing]
You want me off the job?
He has her.
[rip]
And there's only one place
that sick bastard
works someone over.
[ominous music]
[scream] No!
Get off of me!
That goddamn fetishist,
it's not Christian.
I'm done being delicate.
I'm sending my own people.
They'll bring her back
where she belongs,
with me.
What about the money car?
She'll tell me where it is.
She's just not thinking clearly.
She really
does love me.
I bet.
Don't judge me, Turk.
When you're counting down
your final hours,
you realize
how all you really have
is your family and your legacy.
Do not judge.
You'll get paid on your way out.
Turk.
Don't judge.
[game music on phone]
[door clicks]
[slap]
[tense music]
- [rustle]
- [groan]
- [thud]
- [thump]
[whetting knife]
[muffled cry]
[fast-paced tense music]
[gun clicks]
[click]
- Oh, shit.
- Come here often?
[tense music]
[door rumbling]
- [gunshot]
- [grunt]
[muffled grunt]
[knife clatters]
You!
Shit.
Missed me?
[door rumbling]
Where's the money?
What do you mean?
Where's the dancer, man?
Huh?
One of two things has happened.
Either Jefe's operators
got to her in time
and she's back at the casino,
or,
they knocked on the door
and found her cut to pieces.
No.
Angel likes to take his time,
the sick bastard that he is.
He's a goddamn fetishist
or some shit, you know?
Yeah.
I've heard.
You're going back for the girl.
Yeah.
We gotta get movin'. Let's go.
There's no 'we.'
I need your help, man.
Why? Because
I can't do it alone.
It's the only way
to keep my family safe.
Because I owe her.
And because that asthmatic
motherfucker stiffed you.
And I can get you
your cut of the money back,
okay? So what do you
think about that, huh?
What do you say?
Half.
Oh, come on.
Standard cut, we're not...
- Fifty percent.
- Fine. Good.
And I'm drivin'.
No, no, but...
I'm drivin'.
Okay, asshole. There you go.
So, uh, you don't strike me
as someone who has
gone out of the way
that often to help many people.
So tell me, uh...
which part of
my speech was it that,
- you know, convinced you?
- Get in the car.
[anticipatory music]
[coughing]
[gasps]
- [grunting]
- [clinking]
It's okay.
You're home.
[whimpering]
I'm done with you.
I'm done.
[panting]
Fuck.
[grunting]
I don't want your fucking ring!
Bastard!
[grunting]
I fell in love with you
for your passion.
But you've never known
what's best for you.
[electronic club music]
[tense music]
[indistinct speaking]
[club music]
[tense music]
Hey.
What are you doin'?
What are you doin' now?
Just tryin' to
remember where I am.
What?
You...
I thought you said
you knew this place.
I've only been here once.
Cut me some slack.
[gunshots]
[screaming]
- [muffled gunshots]
- Angel.
- [muffled gunshot]
- Shit.
- Oh, shit.
[muffled gunshots]
[tense music]
You got your hands full,
don't you?
[gunshots]
[screaming]
[tense music]
- [rustle]
- [grunt]
[gasping]
[music fades]
[thump]
[breathing deeply]
Cully?
Yeah?
Come on.
Oh. Yeah.
[tense music]
They're coming for you.
He's coming for both of us.
- Huh? Go, go, go.
- Hey!
[rapid gunfire]
Right there.
[gunshots]
- Over there.
- Get to cover!
- What?
- There!
- Move!
- Go!
- [gunshots]
[gunshot]
[rapid gunfire]
Oh my god. How...
- [speaking Spanish]
- [gunshot]
What's he sayin'?
Oh, it's not good.
Not good at all.
[tense music]
- [gunshots]
- [thump]
- Follow me. Over my head.
- [gun clicks]
[gunshots]
[rapid gunfire]
[tense music continues]
[mouthing]
Asshole!
- [scuffling]
- [grunt]
- [thud]
- [crack]
Now that...
was a giant pain in the neck.
Obviously.
[gun clicks]
- Really?
- Yeah.
Let's get 'em.
[tense music]
- Fuck!
- [grunt]
[gunshots]
- [gunshots]
- Move!
[gunshots]
- [gunshot]
- [groaning]
[rapid gunfire]
[tense music continues]
Come on.
[ominous music]
[gun clicking]
I forgive you
for leaving.
[Crystal] I did not ask.
[gun clicks]
I gave you everything.
[sobs] Everything.
You tried to buy me,
like a trick.
Like a goddamn [unclear].
And I let you believe you could.
[sobs]
You can't buy me.
You're a bitter, sad, sad man.
[click]
You used me.
Because you know
I was afraid to be alone.
[gun cocks]
What you gonna do?
I'm not gonna
let anybody hurt you.
Or me.
We are gonna be
together for ever.
Is this really the only way up?
- Jefe's a paranoid man.
- [elevator dings]
[smooth elevator music]
[elevator dings]
[gunshot]
[thump]
[tense music]
- [thump]
- Hey.
On my mark.
- Go, go.
- [door clicks]
[ominous music]
[Crystal panting]
Put it down.
I'm dead anyway.
And I'm takin' her with me.
No.
No, you're not.
Don't do it.
Go, clear!
[gunshots]
- You bastard!
- [gunshots]
That's what you deserve.
- [chain clinking]
- You okay?
[sobs] Yeah.
- Huh?
- [chain clattering]
[Turk] We gotta go.
We gotta go, guys. Now!
- He's right.
- Come on.
Come.
[door clicks]
[elevator dings]
Watch.
[tense music]
[gunshot]
- [gunshot]
- [grunt]
[gunshots]
Oh. Hey.
Hey, wait. Wait.
I have to hit the car.
Why?
Give me the keys. I'll do it.
Hey, Turk, man.
Come on, come on, man.
It's my thing, you know?
It's my thing. Yeah.
But Angel's out there.
I'll do the car.
You just stay here.
All right. You're right.
Sorry, sorry, I-Here you go.
Let's go.
[slap]
[unsettling music]
Stay here.
I mean it.
[Crystal] We will.
You-be careful, okay?
[Turk] Wait here.
[unsettling music continues]
[gunshots]
- [gunshot]
- [grunts]
[gunshots]
[rapid gunfire]
[music continues]
[tense music]
[gunshots]
[tense music continues]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[music fades]
[gunshot]
[thump]
[tense music]
[thud]
[gunshots]
[tense music]
[door creaks]
[door slams]
[tense music]
Hey, white boy!
What you think you're doing
with your hands on our car, huh?
Drop it.
Now!
[gun clatters]
Let's go. Open it up.
[latch clicks] [creaking]
- [beeping]
- [explosion]
[fire crackling]
[tense music]
Cully!
[thump]
Shit!
[door clicks]
- [grunt]
- [slam]
[music fades]
[parking brake ratchet]
[quirky music]
[knocking]
[exhales]
[door clicks]
[tender music]
You look lovely. [chuckles]
So, where's the kid?
Calm down, Daddy.
I wanna meet him, come on.
Okay. Okay.
Just stop.
Be nice.
I'm calm.
You have to promise me,
you'll stay calm.
I'm calm. If I were
any more calm, I'd be asleep.
All right?
Lido?
Daddy,
Lido.
Hm.
The boy.
Sir?
- Real quick.
- [grunts]
[thump]
Are you gonna
treat this perfect angel,
like the princess
and queen that she his?
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah?
I mean,
everything she says is right?
Everything.
Yes, Ma'am. No, Ma'am.
How much money
can I get you, Ma'am?
All that.
Yes.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Okay. You got my blessing. Yeah.
[mouthing]
Okay, honey. Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Emma. What are you doing?
You can't see the groom
before the wedding!
Mama, don't be so superstitious.
I am not being superstitious.
Now come on, go get ready.
Did he hit you?
- Not yet.
- Good.
Do me a favor
and go get the groceries for me?
Yes, Ma'am.
[chair scrapes]
[door clicks]
[Maria] So how are you?
Huh?
How are you?
Uh...
You know-[sniffs]
I'm fine. I'm fine. Why?
Mom, should I put the dress on
now or at the church?
Hey. Maria?
- [tender music]
- Um...
You-Maria?
You're a really good child
but this family...
you're a good family.
Really good.
We're all right.
Come here.
Listen to me. Um...
I am so sorry.
Honey, I...
I missed your whole life,
and I'm your dad
and I shouldn't have missed it,
but I did, and I'm sorry.
It's okay, Daddy.
- You did the best you could.
- [sniffs]
- I love you.
- You do?
I love you, too.
[sniffs] Oh, shit.
[sniffs] Sorry.
[sobs]
- Dad?
- Yeah?
- [sniffs]
- You stink.
What?
You need to get cleaned up
if you're gonna
walk me down the aisle.
I'll walk you down the aisle?
Oh. [chuckles]
Really?
[sobs]
[music fades]
[tense music]
[door rumbling]
[quirky music]
[Cully] I got somethin' for you.
[Maria] Is this dirty money?
[Cully] It was.
But now that
it's in your pristine hands,
it's not.
[clatter]
[door rumbling]
- Hey.
- They'll be looking for this.
We won't be safe.
They're not gonna
do anything anymore, you know.
Looking, not looking,
sleeping, you know.
[chuckles]
Look.
We're free and clear, finally.
[quirky music]
[door clicks]
[slam]
Hey, look. I should go.
Um, I have to find a...
suit, somewhere.
You have a suit.
Really?
Where?
Upstairs. In the closet.
Sure it's mine?
I thought
you've burned everything.
I guess I missed one.
Maria, really,
in all seriousness,
do you want me to stay?
Do you?
I haven't asked you to leave.
[tender music]
[soft clatter]
[thump]
[dull thump]
[anticipatory music]
[clatter]
Jackpot.
Hey.
You could have
just asked for these.
[tinkle]
- Is this your money?
- No.
I already have mine.
I went shopping.
Do you like my new dress?
[upbeat music]
Yeah.
That's all your money.
You comin'?
Which way you heading next?
I don't know.
Maybe south.
South?
I was hoping you would say that.
Let's go!
- [laughs]
- [engine starts]
Hey!
Hey! What the fuck?
[quirky music]
[laughs]
Asshole! [chuckles]
- [door slams]
- Bad boy.
Doesn't feel so good, does it?
I've never felt this good,
my entire life.
- [kiss]
- Just drive, will you?
[engine rumbling]
[Crystal whooping]
Yeah! Come on!
[upbeat music]
[music ends]
[metal music]
♪ Let's all pretend
We're the same ♪
♪ Stand up and watch them go ♪
♪ Lost all the [unclear]
For the strange ♪
♪ You're left alone
And you know ♪
♪ You are ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Let's all pretend
We're the same ♪
♪ Stand up and watch them go ♪
♪ Lost smiles and [unclear] ♪
♪ You're left and you know ♪
[metal music]
♪ For you ♪
♪ Watch them take you ♪
♪ Feel them break you ♪
♪ Let's all pretend
We're the same ♪
♪ Stand up and watch them go ♪
♪ Watch [unclear] strange ♪
♪ You're left alone
And you know ♪
♪ Will have to follow you ♪
[music fades]