Dad, yeah, I just
gotta turn in this paper,
and I will meet you
guys at the ferry.
Yes, of course I
brought the champagne.
Oh, sorry.
Listen, I gotta go, okay?
Bye.
Oh!
Are you okay?
Yeah, fine.
You...
Um, um, your teeth.
Well, I am English.
No, they're covered in blood.
Oh.
I think I might need
to go to the doctor.
Hey, I'm at the clinic.
No, no, I'm okay.
I just ran into
someone on my way
to turn in my assignment.
Like, literally
ran into someone.
He's asleep or passed
out or something.
Yeah, he's cute.
Stop it.
Okay, have fun in Greenwich,
and I'll try to meet
you when I can, okay?
Bye.
Oh, sorry.
Did I scare you?
No, I was just surprised.
Yeah.
Me too.
You have a little...
Oh, oh.
All right, let's get this out.
How's it feel?
Yeah.
Ooh.
Well, it looks pretty good.
I should probably get going.
You two took knocks to the head.
- Really?
- Mm, yeah.
One too many in
your case, it seems.
You likely have
minor concussions,
and I'd like you to do
neurological checks every 4 hours.
I have some pamphlets
that'll walk you through it.
Wait, even me?
That's a good
question, actually.
Because evidently you have
a particularly thick skull,
so it might not be necessary.
But you know what?
Let's be safe and just
do what I tell you, okay?
All right, well...
Oh, that lip actually.
It's gonna be tender
for a few days,
so go easy on him?
Oh, no-
- Paracetamol for the pain
and I'll be right back
with your pamphlets.
Thank you!
So, um...
Do you really think I'm cute?
You heard that?
Yeah.
Can I get your number?
Yeah, sure.
Would you mind passing
me my phone, it's-
- Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
I'm late.
- Oh, no-
- I'm sorry!
But you...
You haven't learned how to
do your neurological check...
Yet.
Where on Earth are you going?
Sorry, thank you!
Why, hello, Miss Master of Art.
We haven't graduated yet.
Wait, what are you doing here?
Oh, I didn't get his number.
What?
I know.
I lost track of time and-
- Ugh!
I had to get my assignment in,
so I just had to leave
there in a hurry.
Well, easy come, easy go.
Oh...
Is that all I get?
Well, that's why
I'm glad you came.
The champagne!
Oh, I totally forgot.
The others-
- Here.
Oh, thanks.
They went somewhere to
find a liquor store.
Wait, where is it?
I don't know,
across the commons?
No, no, where is my journal?
It's not here, I must've
left it at the clinic.
It's got my whole year in there!
Well, it'll still be there.
We'll go back, I'll go with you.
After my champagne.
Okay.
Be careful!
Where have you been?
Having a jolly time, I hope?
Yeah, I was at the
university doctors.
Oh.
Here's the-
- If I'd known you were
gonna take that long,
I'd of just brought it
after my class finished.
This is your diary.
Hm?
Oh, sorry.
Here it is.
I made a few notes,
nothing too major,
but just take a look and
let me know what you think.
Where's Richard?
Richard?
He's still in
Prague, 'til Saturday.
Oh, of course he is.
I forgot.
What's this?
What was I coming over here for?
A cup of tea?
Oh, yes, please, Harry.
Thank you.
James, what were you
doing at the hospital?
Oh, that is really sweet.
I ran into someone.
Head first, I presume.
Yeah.
Why?
Oh, dear.
Oh...
We clean it after every
visit, there's nothing here.
Except that.
Look, are you ready to learn
how to do a neurological check?
Sure.
Good.
Hello?
Is anybody there?
I'll sort it.
Um, James?
I think you should wait.
Did you get your assignment in?
Yeah.
I found this.
I've got this.
Should we get a drink?
I have to learn my
neurological check.
Oh.
How about a walk in
the park, tomorrow?
A walk in the
park would be great.
Oh.
Why are you here?
I forgot something important.
Oh, gross.
Go on, out you go.
No, no, I need to get-
- Please, please!
- Out, out!
- Out!
- What are you doing?
You're supposed to be a doctor.
Meet me tomorrow at
the cafe Tea Darling.
I don't want tea with you!
Sorry about that.
Tea Darling?
You look better.
No, I don't.
But thank you for trying.
I'm a little bit hungover.
You know, we had our
finals yesterday, so.
Oh, there's a doctor
on campus who specializes
in people with your condition.
I think the treatment
might be worse than the cure.
Come on, I know
what will fix ya.
Oh, it's the other
way around, actually.
Now that is the best
hangover cure in the world.
Trust me.
A bit of salt, carbs, grease.
You'll be good as
gold in no time.
I am supremely
jealous right now.
So, you come here often?
Mm, all the time.
I love it.
Here?
It's just so adorable.
Yeah.
It's Tea Darling.
Yeah, so I'm not
technically a student.
By which I mean, I'm not
actually a student at all.
I work at this
startup ad agency,
and we have this graphic
design grad student
interning with us,
so he prints things for me.
Isn't that stealing?
Nana says stealing is wrong.
Will, they're on a date!
Sorry.
Will, that was rude.
Get off me, Sophie!
So, is this J your signature?
Yeah.
Yeah, I Photoshop it
into all the campaigns.
Oh.
Oh, I love this one.
Have it.
I think I have...
Oh, yeah.
I can't take this.
No, please.
I would like you to.
I don't particularly want it.
Yeah, but, you've
been hiding something
behind your back for
about a minute now,
which I can only
presume is a gift,
and if you accept that,
then I get to to take credit
for giving you the first gift,
even though I didn't
actually get you anything.
Here.
Thank you.
Oh.
This is beautiful.
Puts mine to shame,
I'm embarrassed.
Well, I love your
picture of another woman.
Oh, there it is,
a J on her hand.
Why do you put that in?
For fun, I suppose.
Not to keep things stimulating?
What do you mean?
Well, doesn't it get
creatively stifling
working on drill bit campaigns?
No.
No, the creativity
is in making a sale.
The art is defined
by the outcome,
and this is literally art that
moves something, I love it.
Beauty is in the
eye of the beholder,
but art is art in itself.
Is that what that note
that you wrote on my work means?
You think we see too much?
Well, your whole message is that
this company is not
just selling drill bits,
but a way through
obstacles, right?
This image is awful.
There's nothing
aspirational about it.
Punch in with a macro lens
and show the spiral thingies...
Thread.
Show the thread in a way
that suggests something more.
Like a spiral staircase.
Yeah, but no, because it's
not always as, you know,
neat as art for art's sake.
The what and the why
can't be separated.
For instance, your
picture, right?
Now, that's obviously
incredibly special to me.
To anyone else, that's just a
picture of a building corner.
Is that so?
A lovely picture.
You're darn right.
Look.
You're the
uncompromising artist,
I'm the compromising artist.
You're the starving artist,
I'm the well-fed artist.
No offense.
You're right, maybe
I'm clinging to an ideal.
Maybe I won't make
a bunch of money,
but I believe in what
I do, I'm proud of it.
And you're brilliant at it.
I mean, you'll probably
end up proving me wrong
and become the next
famous photographer.
You can't think of any, can you?
I don't think they exist.
Oh, that is spicy.
Seems like we've run out
of things to talk about.
Shut up.
That's another way to put it.
- Aw!
- Oh!
- Ow.
- I'm sorry.
Please, believe me.
There is nothing
I would like more
than to kiss you right now.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
It's fine, honestly.
I mean, if you hadn't,
we'd of never of met,
so I'll take it.
Um...
Can I see you again?
After your pitch?
I'd love that.
Well, do you want
to just meet here
and see where the
night takes us?
Sure.
Do you want my number?
No.
No, let's do it the
old-fashioned way.
It's more romantic.
But what if we
miss each other?
Well, if it's meant to
work, we'll make it work.
James, I'm going back
to the States in two days.
If it's meant to work,
we'll make it work.
We love it!
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you.
How about we
celebrate with a pint?
Oh, actually, I-
- We'll take it from here.
We'd love to.
Congratulations.
We're selling a means to an end.
Another?
Thank you.
Let me just put
this one over here.
You know, I nearly laughed
when you first said that.
But at the end of the day,
they're just drill bits.
But boy, you're onto something.
James is certainly
very competent.
He's a wizard.
Don't let go of that one.
Don't worry.
I don't intend to.
All right.
I'm going to the loo.
How many pints
are we gonna have?
You have somewhere to be, mate?
Did you change your shirt?
Oh, yeah.
I wanted to be comfy.
Right, yeah.
Well, as a matter of
fact, I've got a date.
Do you?
Mhm.
And she goes home
tomorrow, overseas.
This might be my last
chance to see her.
Who's going overseas?
Did you change your shirt?
I wanted to be comfy.
So, what?
Are you gonna leave England?
I don't know, maybe.
We haven't figured
any of that out,
that's why I need to go tonight.
Wow, you're not kidding.
Where's she from?
You might need
to cancel, darling.
I can't.
But we're celebrating!
No, I mean, I
literally can't cancel.
I don't have her number.
James, blow her off.
You're about to close on a
multi-million dollar campaign,
and you want to go off
chasing some foreign floozy.
All right, Morgan.
Firstly, she's not a floozy.
And secondly, we've
already closed.
As I was just
explaining to Henry here-
- It's uh, Harry.
- You can't go...
What?
You called me Henry,
but my name is Harry.
As I was just explaining
to lowly, meaningless intern,
you can never take a
person at her word.
Until the ink is drawn,
you've got nothing.
Trust anyone.
This is really
important to me, Morgan.
Sorry, James, you're staying.
How about we order
something to eat?
Oh, sounds marvelous.
Um, all right.
Harry, mate, can you
do me a massive favor?
Yes, of course.
Okay, you know the
bridge over the duck pond
in the common?
Yup.
I need you to go
there, find the girl.
She's got dark hair,
might be holding a camera,
answers to Edie.
I need you to find her,
tell her I'm really sorry
I can't make our date tonight,
but I will swing by her dorm
first thing in the morning.
You want me to skip dinner?
Well, yeah.
I will buy you dinner if
it means that much to you.
James, what are you eating?
One minute.
Three courses.
What?
You'll buy me a
three course dinner,
and I get to pick
the restaurant.
Yeah, whatever.
I'm just kidding James, relax.
You shouldn't seen your
face, two courses is fine.
Harry, hurry!
You're gonna be late.
I got it, mate.
Trust me.
Excuse me!
Edie!
Are you Edie?
Yes.
My goodness.
I tried the Tube,
but it was late.
I ended up getting a taxi.
I thought I might've missed you,
but it doesn't matter.
James wanted me to tell
you he can't come tonight,
but he'll stop by your dorm
first thing in the morning.
Okay, yes.
Yes.
Okay, great.
It's nice to meet you.
One minute, I just
need to send a text.
Are you on social media at all?
Cape Town, right?
And there's place
called Shark Bank.
500 foot cliffs, straight down.
And the actor's gonna jump...
I just need to make
a stop on the way.
Okay.
What is it?
Hi, I'm looking for James.
Oh.
You're American.
Yes, and I'm on my
way to the airport.
I just wanted to make
sure he got this.
Is he here?
Give it to me, darling.
I'll make sure he gets it.
Which, I thank you
so much, I just...
Hurry up, love!
Meter's running, and you've
got a plane to catch.
Who is it?
A girl scout.
Thank you, Mr. Parker.
Have a nice day.
Oh, it'll be delivered
by Wednesday.
How much was that piece?
17.
$17,000?
Yup.
Can you believe it?
It looks like the
artist just threw
a bunch of paint on a canvas.
Well, that's an awesome
commission for you.
It is.
And I would be making
an awesome commission
off of your stuff.
I can't afford to be a
starving artist anymore.
Why?
It's too unreliable.
Product and portrait shots
just pay so much more.
Yeah, about that.
How's your mom doing?
She'll be fine once
the divorce is settled.
Is it nice living back home?
It's not the word
I'd use to describe it,
but now we're just trying
to move to this house.
Yeah, I get it.
Have you called Noah back?
No.
And don't make me sorry
I told you about that.
What?
It's a big job!
And it'd give you
breathing room.
Jess, it's literally
shooting poop.
Whoa.
It's fertilizer, okay?
Calm down.
And it'd give you freedom
to do other things.
You know I'm right!
What does your mom say?
She says I should marry him.
Well, I'm sure he'd
be along for the ride.
No, no.
See, when the
conversation switches
to getting romantically
involved with Noah Pepper,
that's my cue to leave.
Oh, you mean that's
all I have to do
to get you to stop
loitering around here?
Shut up!
Call him, Edie!
Honey, just call him.
It will help to talk.
Okay.
I hear you, universe.
I guess I'm calling Noah Pepper.
Pepper Poop.
This is Penny.
Hi, this is Edie Stevens
returning Noah Pepper's call.
Edie Stevens!
Yes.
Can I put you on a...
Can I put you on a brief hold?
Uh, sure.
Okay, thank you.
Noah?
Noah, hi.
Edie Stevens is on the phone.
Edie's on the phone?
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh boy.
Um...
This is really good.
Okay, I'll talk
her off hold then.
No, I'll do it.
Um, excuse me.
Uh, which button do I press?
This one right here.
No, no, no, don't touch it!
I just need a moment to prepare.
Sure, sure, sure.
Okay.
Can we practice, is that okay?
Yeah.
Can we...
You'll be Edie, I'll be Noah.
Okay.
Edie, hi.
How are you?
Good.
She doesn't sound like that.
Sorry.
Can you just sound a
little more like her?
Sound like you're trying...
Can you just...
Just work with me here.
Edie, hi.
Hi, Noah.
Oh, that's pretty good.
Edie, I've been following
you since high school.
Been following your
work since high school.
Yeah.
Um...
Been following your
work since high school.
I noticed you'd take
pictures really well,
and, that's stupid,
I need a mint.
Do you have a mint?
Do we have any mints?
Let me check.
We had a candy drawer
here for years, Penny.
And I told you you could
rearrange the office,
but it's a big deal to me
that we keep up
with consistency.
It's fine, it's fine,
it's fine, I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't of, I
know, you know...
Edie.
I was wondering if we
could grab food to eat?
I like it.
I don't know, sometimes
I feel like maybe
that's a little too flashy.
Okay.
Yeah, maybe not.
Well, now you got me in my head.
Is it not too flashy
or is it too...
I like it.
Okay, well I know
Antonio's is fine.
I need to, um...
I need the blood on my...
I didn't do any of my
cardio today, excuse me.
Could I just have a little
bit of space, please?
- Yeah, definitely.
- I'm so sorry.
You're doing a great job.
- Definitely.
- You're doing a great job.
Thanks.
Is this too tight?
It's too tight.
I can't do it in
your office, Penny.
Okay, um...
Dinner, do we want
to have dinner?
I want to offer you a job.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Mm.
Okay.
I'm ready.
This one, right?
There.
It's the one on the left.
This one, right here.
Right.
Oh my gosh, Noah.
You're killing me!
So, when this
campaign launched...
Geez, I was 17.
So, 12 years ago?
Yeah.
It has that vibe.
I remember your M&amp;M
phase in school.
Phase?
I'm joshin' ya.
Gosh, it's so good to see you.
How are you?
How's Susan?
Mom sends her love, of course.
I mean, she's thrilled
we're working together.
Mom's great, thanks.
Yeah, and it has been a while.
It has, hasn't it?
You know, I keep on passing
your studio in town,
and I think to myself,
"I should go in and say hi."
But I know you're so busy
running the business
and everything,
I mean your life is insane.
Certainly is.
So...
So, what should we do?
With the campaign?
Uh, I'm used to working
with smaller business,
like much smaller.
And you're turning around, what?
330 million and change.
Wow, yeah.
That's a lot more...
You're a much bigger company
than I'm used to working with.
Have you thought about bringing
an ad company on board?
Like, people who do
this for a living?
Oh, I have one already,
I went with a British company.
Kind of glam up our
image a bit, you know?
Great.
So, what am I doing?
Well, you're gonna shoot it.
Look, I know you're
not an advertiser,
but I remember our
senior year art class.
Oh, Noah.
You've got a darn good eye!
And I want you on my team.
You don't need me-
- I need someone I trust
looking out for me.
You know, truth be told, Edie.
I'm scared of you
creative types.
I mean, you're so cool
with your crazy hair
and old-school fashion.
I don't have either
of those things.
But you know people who
do, and you understand them.
Should I put that on my resume?
Why?
It was a joke.
See?
I didn't even get that, but
you speak their language.
I believe it's called English?
That...
That's funny.
English.
That's good.
Edie, I need you to keep
an eye on these guys.
Be my woman on the
inside, so to speak.
We can't have another
campaign like the last one.
I mean, it was terrible.
All right.
Welcome to the
Pepper Poop family.
Maybe we could go out
to dinner this Friday.
Celebrate.
Sure.
Edie.
Edie!
Do you really have
to do that right now
while we're trying
to eat breakfast?
No, Mom, I'm eating breakfast.
You're still on one of
your intermittent fasts.
I mean, it's the best
way to lose weight.
Until you read about the
next one in a magazine.
Hey, if I could lose weight,
I could be a cougar.
Yeah.
Hold that thought.
Mm!
Look what you made me do.
Edie?
Honey?
Are you okay?
Holy-
- Poop.
Tons and tons of poop.
You know, people really
underestimate it.
But I always say that
if you want to go green,
you gotta go brown first!
Oh, you know, I could get
you a salad if you'd like.
Oh, no, that's okay.
Are you sure?
Okay.
And I said "Careful
mate, that's my face!"
Do you believe that?
He nearly took my
face off, he did.
Edie's here.
Edie!
Hi.
Thank you, Penny.
Help yourself to some
coffee and breakfast.
Oh, no thank you, I'm fine.
I already had plenty.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You mean Edie.
I can get you
something right now.
Oh, I'm okay, thank you.
Harry was just telling
me this funny incident
that happened during
a commercial shoot.
I've got loads of
stories, my friend.
I want to hear all of them.
Don't bother, half
of them aren't true,
and the rest sadly are.
Good morning, I'm Morgan.
Gutt Morgan.
Edie.
Actually, I think I am
gonna get that coffee.
Noah.
I've been thinking about
it, and I have to agree.
You should feature
prominently in the campaign.
Good morning, everyone!
James!
Noah.
Nice to finally meet you, mate.
Oh, buddy, I've
heard wonderful things.
Oh, no, not from Harry, I hope.
If they are, you probably
shouldn't trust them.
Nah, I only told
him the bad ones.
Oh, no, no, they've all been
really good, I assure you.
Oh, James.
This is our photographer,
Edie Stevens.
Nice to meet you, Edie.
You too, James.
Now that we're all
acquainted, shall we begin?
Right.
So, we need a new ad
campaign, obviously.
So, the broad plan
is for you guys
to come up with the idea,
and work with Edie
to produce it.
What's the time frame again?
I'd like this out by fall.
Well, that's doable.
Do you do many commercial
productions, Edie?
A few.
She's being modest.
I mean, she's done tons.
Everyone knows if you want a
commercial shot in Charleston,
you want Edie.
That is a wonderful reputation.
I mean, she does portraits,
she even does animal portraits.
Moving on...
You're looking for exposure
across multiple
platforms, I'm sure.
Have you had any
thought as to where?
I trust you guys to come up with
the best go-to-market strategy.
Mhm.
And how would you
define your customers
if you had to place them, say.
Mm.
Well, our largest clients by
far are industrial farmers,
but we don't really see
much growth in that sector.
May I...
Go for it.
We think there's a high
margin of retail potential
for urban agriculture.
You know, people
who grow vegetables
on top of balconies
and rooftops.
Farmers and the millennials,
they're two very
different demographics.
Yeah.
We do quite a bit of
business with city parks,
suburban gardeners, and
believe it or not, cemeteries.
So you're literally
targeting everyone,
the living and the dead?
Those are great, aren't they?
Oh, yeah.
These are very evenly lit.
Yeah.
Totally.
I don't see a
single shadow on them.
You can see
everything perfectly.
And they're in focus too.
They sold the product.
Isn't that what art is,
defined by the outcome?
Well, I mean...
Beauty might be in the
eye of the beholder,
but surely art is
in the art itself.
I think somebody
told me that once.
Do you believe that or
are you just spinning words?
Spinning words?
Well, that's what you do, right?
As an ad man?
I believe in what I do.
Can you say the same?
In my experience, clever
words aren't enough.
A successful campaign
needs follow through.
You don't just launch
something and then abandon it.
Unless it always supposed to be
a limited campaign, of course.
What is this?
Is this a tote bag?
No.
I know what this is,
this is a compromise.
Unlimited compromise,
I know I recognized it.
Oh, come on, I...
I was just playing.
Edie!
Well, that was a good start.
Edie, Edie, where are you going?
I was only joking.
I haven't seen you
in 5, maybe 6 years,
and that's how you speak to me?
I really don't see
what the problem is here.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Noah, I'm sorry, mate.
I didn't mean to offend anyone.
Oh, okay.
Thanks, James.
I got this.
Okay.
What happened?
Was it something he said?
No.
Did I do something?
What?
Noah, no, I...
I can't do this.
Oh, right.
Fresh with cream.
I got this for you.
Is that tomato poop?
Root poop.
That's our top
product right there.
You put it on your root
vegetables, it's a miracle.
Cool.
Noah, listen, I
don't think it's a-
- Look, I get it.
You do?
You're a free spirit, you
don't want to be tied down.
Kinda.
You're doing the same
job over and over again.
Oh, no, I meant I-
- Look, I know it's gonna
take some time to adjust,
so why don't you go
take the rest of the day
and we'll talk
about it at dinner.
Thanks.
That would be great.
Edie!
Babe!
How'd the meeting go?
It was a disaster.
Why?
Because I've betrayed every
artistic ideal I've ever had
and I'm living a lie.
Are they gonna pay you?
Yeah, Mom, they're gonna pay me.
Yay, that's
great, congratulations.
Let's go out to
dinner to celebrate!
I can't.
I have a date.
Don't bother, I'm
not telling you.
More.
Keep going.
Yup.
There we go.
What's the story here?
He's here.
Who?
James.
James?
English James.
Wait, English James?
Flaky English James.
Flaky, but cute English James.
Infuriating, arrogant,
and rude English James!
You're going to dinner with him?
I'm going to dinner with, uh...
What?
Wait, how?
Why?
It's not what you think.
I think it's a work
dinner or something?
Some sort of welcome
to the company dinner.
When I walked out of the
meeting earlier today,
he chased after me.
And I wanted to call it
all off, but then he just-
- Wait, wait, wait.
One thing at a time.
You walked out on
a meeting because-
- James!
James and his stupid
uppity ad agency
are the ones producing
Noah's campaign.
Oh!
That's why he
looked so familiar.
Who?
Well, an English guy
came in here this afternoon
asking about holding
a launch party here,
Noah sent him.
When you went back to
the university clinic,
he was with me in
the waiting room.
Wait, they want to have
the launch party here?
Yeah, I guess it could work.
Of course it will.
I can't have too much.
I'm having dinner
with Noah Pepper.
You're right.
You can't have too much.
What am I doing?
I don't know.
To us.
Finally getting
to work together.
You know, you probably
don't know this,
but I guess I've never
told anyone before,
but back in high school
I kinda had a crush on you.
Oh.
Yeah, secret's out.
You know, but don't
worry though, please.
I almost didn't even
invite you out to dinner,
'cause I don't want
to send mixed messages
or act at all in any
way inappropriately,
because more than
anything, Edie,
I want to work with you.
You know, I wasn't
kidding the other day,
I really meant it.
I need someone who can
handle these creatives,
tell me what's going on.
Like today.
It seemed like that
guy was being a jerk,
but I honestly have no
idea what was being said.
James was...
Look, okay, yeah,
he was being a jerk.
I'll just fire them then.
Get a new agency.
I mean, you're more important
to me than they are,
in every way.
No, no, don't fire them.
So...
Are you in or out?
Out!
In!
It was out.
I'm pretty sure it was in.
Whatever.
40-15, my serve.
Noah's gold digger is
back on the campaign.
Gold digger?
I know her type.
Morgan, you think that every
American's a gold digger.
You still haven't gotten
over Wallace Simpson.
Look, you can't blame Edie.
I upset her.
A stiff breeze would upset
that delicate snowflake, James.
Look, creative differences
are a part of the job.
I mean, have you
seen her pictures?
They're awful.
A trained monkey
could do a better job.
Anyway, do you fancy
a gin and tonic?
It's about 10 in the morning.
Not in England, darling.
You've got a problem, you know.
I know.
I'm parched.
So where would the bar be?
Good morning, gentlemen.
James, this is Jess.
The gallery owner.
Oh, nice to meet you, Jess.
Nice to meet you as well.
I was actually in
London with Edie,
so I guess we have
a mutual friend.
Well, I hope so, but
I'm not quite sure.
Oh, I wouldn't worry too much.
You know, when I
came in the other day,
I thought you looked familiar.
She was on Jersey Shore.
No?
Survivor.
Am I close?
Morning.
Okay.
When we were sent from London
to open our North
American agency branch,
we did it with Pepper
Poop on our minds.
How are the acoustics?
Yeah, they're fine, Morgan.
You're not gonna say
that though, are you?
Well, I don't know
what I'm going to say.
Do we need a mic?
I think we need a mic.
Harry, Harry?
Are you writing this down?
Writing what down?
I agree with Morgan.
With a lot of people here,
a microphone will really
help cut across the noise.
Then we'll get a mic.
James.
Seeing as Edie missed
much of Friday,
perhaps you could
bring her up to speed.
Of course, Morgan.
All right.
Let's see.
After you left, well,
I came to your dorm,
I went to Heathrow, and
then the proceeding 6 years
were pretty dull and dreary.
But, you know, that's
England for you.
After the meeting, James.
Oh, not much really.
We decided we'd do
billboards, print, TV, radio.
In terms of the creative vision,
we're gonna emphasize
what fertilizer does
rather than what it is,
for obvious reasons.
And...
Yeah.
Noah wants to be featured
in the campaign personally.
Again?
You saw that?
It was a different time,
and it worked back then.
Right, yeah.
Although I suppose the
outcome made it art.
What do you mean?
Just, you know...
Beauty's in the eye
of the beholder.
Seriously?
Oh, come on, Edie!
We're both compromised
artists now.
The only difference is, I
don't see any shame in that.
Whereas you clearly haven't
come to terms with it.
Do you think
that's why I'm angry?
Isn't it?
No!
Well, yes, but I'm mostly
angry that you never showed up.
Well, excuse me?
I waited for you.
And then when you
didn't show up,
I even went to your office.
I gave Morgan my number.
I want the spotlight on me.
I think I'm gonna head out.
I have enough to get
started on some test shoots.
It's simple.
Sell the function, not
the product, feature you.
I have some ideas.
It'll be easier to
show you than tell you.
You won't stick around today?
No, I think this is a much
more productive use of my time.
How can they call it football?
Only one man on the field
ever touches it with his foot.
Harry.
Do you remember
about 6 years ago
when I asked you to meet
a girl in a park for me?
Of course I do.
You still owe me
dinner for that.
Did you actually
speak to the girl?
Yes.
Ide.
Nice girl.
We're still friends online.
Show me?
I always wondered what
happened between you two.
I always figured
it ended naturally
when she moved back to Japan-
- Oh, no.
Have you seen her
animated cat videos?
Aren't those incredible?
Harry, what have you done?
What?
Edie.
Harry, I said Edie, not Ide.
You said a foreign
girl with a camera
who answered to Edie.
This was the only
one in the park.
Edie!
Edie?
Oh, God, it's Edie.
Wait, that's where
I've seen Jess before.
She was at the clinic.
Where are you going?
To beg forgiveness!
But you have chips
coming, do you...
Do you want your chips?
You still owe me for dinner!
Noah, how did you get
it under your collar?
I don't know, it just
kind of dripped down.
It looks good to me.
Come on, we've got work to do.
Thank you.
Famous photographers?
They exist.
How did you find me?
Harry told me.
Did you really go to Heathrow?
Yeah, I did.
I didn't get very far.
Apparently they frown
upon young lovers
trying to storm security.
Mio Ide, huh?
I see he's told
you a few things.
Yeah, he's a nice guy.
Unlike me?
Pretty much.
Okay.
I am sorry, Edie.
For the way that I spoke
to you in that meeting.
You should be.
But I'm not sorry
for what I said.
You're insufferable.
And I'll admit that.
If you admit that you're
above shooting tote bags.
I needed the money.
Since when did you
care about money?
Yes.
I compromised.
I betrayed a younger, more
pure version of myself
because I needed the
money to help someone.
Are you happy now?
Well, obviously not, now
you've put it like that.
But...
It was a joke, Edie.
One of life's little ironies.
But you took it to
this whole other level,
which I understand
now that I know about
Harry and that tourist.
But, no...
No, I am not doing this.
Doing what?
Arguing with you.
I bought you that
book to say sorry.
Why didn't you say it?
'Cause, you had company,
and I didn't want to intrude.
Well, I'm here now.
And I'm saying sorry.
For the way that I spoke to you.
But not for what you said.
No.
No, because what I saw in
there was not inspiring, Edie.
And I don't mind
saying that to you
because I also know
that it's not you.
You don't know me.
I don't know you?
This is you.
You still have this?
Of course.
And you carry it with you?
Mhm.
That's a little weird.
Newsflash!
I am a little weird.
And I didn't keep it because
I never moved on from
whatever it was that we had,
I kept it because I was
wrong, and you were right.
It's not just a picture
of a building corner
or a drill bit, or fertilizer.
It's a story, that
was our story.
And tote bags do
not tell stories.
Yes.
Enough about the
tote bags, I get it.
But do you?
Because I want to
work with this Edie.
I am dying to work
with this Edie.
You know, our drill bit
campaign won us loads of awards.
Practically put the
agency on the map.
And you know what
the centerpiece was?
What?
A macro photographer
of a drill bit,
low angle, with the spiral
thingies pointing up.
They're called threads.
That was you, Edie.
You put us on the map, in a way.
Also, it was me, because
my copy was amazing.
Hey.
I just thought I'd bring...
Oh, wow.
What is that smell?
Chicken poop or something.
Fertilizer of some sort.
Why is that smell?
You get used to it.
Hey, come check these out.
You'll be fine, come on.
Oh, Edie, these look great.
This is fertilizer?
Yeah.
Wow, I haven't seen you
do anything like this in years.
Hey!
Dating Noah is clearly
working out for you.
We're not dating.
How many times have
you been out to dinner?
Twice.
But we were doing a
work thing last night-
- And when are you going
out to dinner again?
Tomorrow.
Well, if it looks like poop-
- And smells like
poop, yeah, I get it.
But this isn't Noah.
I had a good conversation
with James yesterday.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, yes!
Oh, these are brilliant.
I love this one!
That's amazing.
Was that in the studio?
Yeah.
Good morning, Penny.
Good morning, Noah.
How was your night?
Good.
The dog wet the bed
again, but it's okay.
Just had...
Yeah, it was.
I feel like we should
maybe figure out
a way to incorporate Noah.
Maybe like behind over here.
Yeah, behind everything maybe.
Just somewhere small.
Hidden in the dirt.
Just like, way off
in the distance.
Basically not in it.
That would be more ideal for me.
Oh, no, these are great.
These are great.
Well, we can get some
more of these then?
Yeah.
I have a couple more extra.
Okay, before our lucky talk
about fertile fields
and productive farming,
we have to at least
acknowledge the fact
that what we're
selling is feces.
So, we double down.
We make a joke out of it.
But not out of the campaign.
No, we can't undermine it.
And Noah needs to be in it.
Right.
Okay, let's get him in it.
I think he's gonna like this.
Noah?
Sorry.
I have no idea how late it is.
Well, we've been on a roll.
Getting it done.
That's it.
"Getting it done."
That's the tagline.
I love it.
Yes!
Come on, put it there.
Mm.
All right.
Should we call it a day there?
Heck no.
Do you want to do
some test shoots?
I mean, I'm up
for it if you are.
Let's go.
Let's go!
To the studio, baby.
Can I have a couple
more minutes, please?
"Things in life should be
simple rather than complex."
I've been saying
this for a long time.
I don't know what else
to say at this point.
I don't think any of
them make any sense.
Also, how do you use chopsticks?
Are you supposed to have two?
I only have one.
Here, you want my other one?
Not really.
Excuse me.
Can I have another
double on the rocks?
Would you like any food, sir?
No, just whisky.
And the check, please.
Off the plane, you'll be greeted
by a tropical breeze.
Imagine your toes in the sand.
Oh.
Hey, Noah.
This.
Do you like the lean?
Do I look like the face of poop?
I don't think that's gonna-
- That's what I'm
really going for here.
That's not gonna work for Noah.
I'm not opening the bag.
Come on, we have to show him
what we're thinking, right?
I'm not showering
myself in poop.
I don't even want to
know what's going on.
Harry, Jess.
What are you two-
- There's no time for that!
Edie, your mom and I guess
now Noah is looking for you.
What...
Oh, no, I forgot dinner.
What?
I need my phone.
Can someone call my phone?
On it.
You need to hide him, now.
Oh, no, we were just working.
Yeah, Harry, mate, we
have an awesome campaign.
Nice one.
Think about what
this looks like!
Your mom is worried about you,
she's looking for you.
She and Noah are
going to come here.
Shoot, you're right, yeah.
You gotta go.
What?
No, this is absurd.
I'll just explain to
Noah we were working,
show him the shots.
You had a date with him?
No, it's...
Can we just not complicate
things right now?
Too late.
I see Noah and an
angry looking woman
that parked across the across.
That's Susan.
Who's Susan?
My mom.
Yeah, I'm gonna hide.
Yeah, go to the bathroom.
Shh.
Why are you in here?
Because the mom looks
really angry, I got scared.
Edie?
Why aren't you
answering your phone?
Mom, I'm not a child,
I don't have to
explain myself to you.
Uh, maybe not to me,
but you definitely have to
explain yourself to Noah.
He called and you
missed your date?
It was just dinner.
Oh, no, no, don't
sell yourself short.
You're wonderful.
Do you think I don't
have better things to do
than to drive all over town?
Mom, if you would just
stop talking for two seconds,
I could explain.
I've been-
- Yeah?
I've been, uh-
- Here, with me.
Yeah, Edie and I
had dinner together,
and she just totally
forgot about your date.
It's my fault.
I'm so sorry, Noah.
It's okay.
Is that the Evergreen
Pro-Poop-Lactic?
What?
That fertilizer.
It's a proprietary
disease resilient blend.
Oh, that's wonderful.
It's Pepper Poop.
I was working earlier,
and I got caught up,
I completely forgot.
Telephone?
You coulda called.
- It's fine, Mrs.
- Stevens, it's really-
- Okay.
It's fine.
I just didn't know where
you were, and I got worried.
Well, I mean if
you're okay, Noah,
I guess we could go.
And I'll see you at home.
But I just gotta go to
the bathroom real quick.
- No!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's going on here, girls?
Just go at home.
Uh, Edie, I have to
go to the bathroom now.
Not later.
There is a bar down
the block that is open.
Okay, you guys are being
really weird right now.
What is going on, okay?
I have to go to the
bathroom, excuse me-
- Nope.
There's someone in there.
My date.
Okay.
So you have a
boyfriend now, Jess?
No, not my boyfriend.
This is our first date.
You brought your new
date to dinner with Edie?
We're having it after dinner,
he just needed to
use the bathroom.
Well, do you like him, dear?
- Yeah.
- Your date?
Yeah.
He's...
Accidentally offensive
and persistent,
but there's something
really adorable about him.
Oh, that's wonderful, hun.
Hey.
Can you focus?
He has been in there
for quite a while though.
You sure he's okay?
Yeah, he's been in
there for a minute.
Oh, he's not feeling well.
Okay.
What was that?
Huh.
Good evening, everyone.
How are you feeling?
Much better, thank you.
Great, in fact.
Jess, are you
ready for our date?
Yup, yup.
Excellent.
- Okay.
Um, okay.
Can I use the bathroom now?
Okay.
Noah?
Noah!
Edie, there's no toilet paper!
Okay.
Sweetie, what's going on?
Is it that Englishman?
Noah told me about him.
I really worry about you.
I hate to see you get hurt,
and I don't think
it's a good thing
to be chasing after this guy.
I mean, he's the
one who left you.
I'm afraid he's
gonna do that again.
You really need somebody
stable, dependable,
and Noah's a good man,
and he would be
financially stable as well.
I just really worry.
And, you know,
when your dad left,
I promised I'd never let
something like that happen to you.
I'm afraid this guy's
gonna break your heart,
and you're gonna lose your
opportunity to be with Noah.
You know I love you, and I
just want the best for you.
I'm really glad
we had this chat.
And thank you for
listening for once.
Well, now I gotta go
to my kickboxing class.
See you later!
We need to focus
on the campaign.
What are we selling?
Poop.
No.
No, we're not selling
that, we're selling...
Cultivation.
Growth.
Life itself!
I'll go for coffee,
while we wait for them.
I'll help you.
Where are they?
They're not together.
I know that much, I
saw James this morning
and he was definitely
on his own.
A raspberry frappuccino.
You got it.
Morgan?
Black.
Good luck.
Oh.
Nice of you to join us.
How was your lie in?
I wasn't aware we had
a meeting scheduled.
Oh, you must've forgotten.
No, Morgan, you must've
forgotten to actually tell me.
Don't you dare
speak to me like that!
Especially in front of a client.
I expect an apology.
For what?
For insubordination, tardiness,
and inappropriate relations
with a team member!
Oh, Harry and I are
just good friends.
With the American girl.
Edie and I were working.
And the campaign's good.
It's really, really good.
If you can grow up for one
minute, you'll see that.
She's his girlfriend, James.
I didn't know that!
Look-
- Haven't you done
enough damage?
Yeah, all right, Morgan, just...
Look, Noah.
Noah.
I understand you're upset
that Edie missed
your date last night,
but we have your campaign,
and it's beautiful.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Can you promise
me you have nothing
but professional
interest in Edie?
Excuse me?
Can you promise
me you have nothing
but professional
interests in Edie?
The campaign.
Noah, it's everything.
I...
Need to go to the factory
and check on production.
Noah!
Noah.
Do you want us to continue
working in your absence?
I can assure you, we are the
right fit for your company.
Look, please.
Just don't do
anything rash, okay?
We will do whatever is
necessary to keep your business.
Let's just talk about it
when you're back from
the factory, okay?
Noah?
Noah, I know you can hear me.
Noah!
Richard, darling!
I don't understand
why they have to be
so juvenile about this.
Are they wrong?
What?
You hesitated when Noah
asked you that question.
Is your interest in me
purely professional?
Um...
Yes, yeah.
You're lying.
Edie...
You are dating Noah.
No, I'm not.
Well, that's not what
everyone else seems to think.
That's not what
Noah seems to think.
I mean, you have
literally been going
on dates with him, Edie.
So, are you leading him on
or are you leading me on?
It's just dinner.
Apparently not to him.
And frankly, not to me.
I'm not that guy, okay?
And you seem to
be having trouble
with committing to either of us.
If you can't admit to Noah
that you have feelings for me,
then we can't be anything more
than just work colleagues.
Can we?
Bravo, darling.
You know, you might've
just single-handedly
ruined our North
American expansion.
You know...
Labor laws are a funny thing.
I wish I could fire you.
But alas, all I can
do is promote you.
You know, I've just got
off the phone to Richard.
I've been telling him all about
the sterling work
you've been doing here.
Did you know he's looking
for a new creative director?
For the whole agency?
Oh, yes.
And you've got the job.
Congratulations.
Well, you can't make me take it.
But why wouldn't you?
Surely such a
promotion is within
your professional interest.
Yeah.
Well, you'd better
book a flight, darling.
Who's gonna replace me here?
Noah, they didn't
have raspberry,
so I got you blueberry.
Where's Noah?
Why's everyone staring at me?
Don't laugh!
It's launching in your
gallery in less than a week.
Yeah, but they know
that I don't have
anything to do with it.
Don't they?
Meanwhile, my
name is all over it.
I'm kidding!
Edie, it's, um...
Well, it's pretty terrible.
But in a goofy,
Noah kind of way.
Have you told him yet?
About the campaign?
What else do you
have to tell him?
I try, but he's just so
darn happy all the time,
I don't have the heart.
It's like kicking a puppy.
Besides, he hired me to
handle the creatives,
and I've been
completely steamrolled.
I can't work with Morgan,
she's got awful ideas,
and Harry, he's...
Oh, it's okay, you can
trash talk Harry to me.
I don't mean to.
Harry's really sweet,
but we spend three full
days shooting Noah.
Thousands of images.
At some point, you just
need to make a decision.
That is the smartest
thing you've said all day.
So, what is your decision?
Are you dating Noah or not?
Why do people
keep asking me that?
Because you keep going
out on dates with him.
Am I dating Noah?
Not very well.
Room 418.
Enjoy your stay
with us, thank you.
Thank you.
Excuse me?
Yes.
I'm looking for Harry Masters.
Nevermind, I think I found him.
I've been meaning to ask
about the campaign, Morgan.
Out with it!
Well, it's sort of similar
to the last one, isn't it?
I know, darling.
Look, Noah doesn't
care about it,
and quite frankly, we don't
want to overwhelm his customers.
They're American, remember.
They've got less culture
than a cup of yogurt.
Well, I don't think-
- Good.
You're not cut out for it.
Your service.
Right.
What was that?
My points, I believe.
It's just a
freaking game, Harry!
Harry!
Edie, what are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
Yeah, so why are you here?
This is the men's room.
I can't let Morgan see us.
Oh.
She does seem rather
omnipresent, doesn't she?
The campaign is a train wreck.
I know.
It's awful.
We need to do something.
I've tried.
Believe me, but
Morgan won't listen.
She's like a tank.
The only person she'd
ever listen to is James.
So, we go over her head.
To Richard?
Well, we can try, but
he won't get involved.
There's got to
be someone else.
I mean, technically the creative
director's more superior.
James.
Yup.
You already knew that.
- Yeah.
- Oh my god.
Does your team look up to you?
Come on, sit down.
You know, I wanted to offer
you this job when it opened up,
but I didn't know you
wanted to leave America
just after you arrived.
So...
Tell me what you're thinking.
Uh, well, I think that the teams
are working pretty
well individually,
they're just reluctant
to collaborate-
- Yeah, yeah, yeah,
not about work.
There's something else
going on, isn't there?
Have you ever been in love?
Ah!
Um, three times, married four.
Yeah.
So, tell me about her.
How long you got?
40, 45 minutes.
Come on.
I want to hear it all.
I'm having a
hard time deciding between
the fish and the steak.
Oh, the fish is great.
It's so rich and so soft.
Yeah, it looks rich.
Yeah, it's so rich.
And that butter sauce
is super mellow,
I mean, it's a safe choice.
Well, how about the steak?
Mm, I don't know.
Do you like hot English mustard?
I mean, yeah, I
like a bit of heat.
I just can't do it,
it gives me hiccups.
But you know, you get
whatever you want.
Don't let me sway you.
Are you ready to choose, ma'am?
Yeah, I think I am.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
She told me girl guide.
No.
No, no, girl scout.
American.
Oh, that Morgan,
she's a piece of work.
Yeah, we need another bottle
to get through all that.
Oh, I have one actually.
No, no, please.
My head's already spinning.
Oh!
Ah, I'm gonna be sorry
to see you leave.
Excuse me?
Well, you're going
back, of course.
What, to America?
Mhm.
No.
No, I don't want
to muck things up
more than I already have.
Well, perhaps you
could help rescue them.
What do you mean?
Well, you see...
Your love life was
not the only thing
that Morgan was
sabotaging, it seems.
Hm?
Yeah, the Pepper Poop
campaign is a total disaster.
Oh, yeah, I know.
But what do you want me to do?
It's about to launch.
Mhm.
What if I told you there's
a way you could save it.
There is?
Mhm.
You see, James...
Sometimes in order
to see forwards,
you have to look backwards.
To the past?
You think there's something
I could've done differently?
Probably.
Just look back.
What, I mean, me
and Edie came up with-
- Oh, for goodness sake,
you're as thick as
two short planks.
Just look behind you!
Edie!
Edie...
Developed the concept
you both came up with
and made it work.
Harry is printing
and swapping it now.
So, what do you need from me?
Authorization.
As creative director,
it's your responsibility
to maintain
the company's
reputation worldwide.
Morgan's not gonna like this.
James, James.
I believe in you.
You're scared of
her, aren't you?
Terrified.
Are you ready for
your speech, Morgan?
There are few things
that I detest more
than public speaking.
I can do it.
That idea is one of them.
To be honest, I don't
even know what to expect.
I saw one mock-up early on,
but these guys have been making
all sorts of changes since then.
Real creative types.
They've got me in-
- Wow.
Noah, is that...
Penny?
Um, Noah?
Can I talk to you?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Mrs. Stevens, will you
excuse us for a second?
Sure, of course, of course.
Your mom doesn't know yet, huh?
I think she's gonna take
it harder than anyone else.
I enrolled in a painting class.
Cool!
Noah, there's something-
- It just kinda helps me
take my mind off of things,
which is good.
Right.
But about the-
- Just stop.
It's fine.
I'm fine.
I get it.
You don't feel about me the
same way I feel about you.
It's not the first
time this has happened.
Noah, I do care about you.
You're a kind,
sweet, sensitive guy,
and you're gonna
make the right woman
very happy someday.
But I'm not her.
I know.
But...
That's not what I
needed to tell you.
The campaign is terrible.
Oh gosh, yeah.
I can't stand any of it.
Why didn't you say something?
I felt bad for letting
Morgan send James back.
I didn't want to admit
that we needed him,
that I needed him.
And more importantly,
Edie, you needed him.
Well, about that...
We've made some changes
to the campaign.
I gotta talk to him.
Everyone's attention.
Right, well...
First off, please join me
in showing our appreciation
to Jess Hammond
here for hosting us
in her amazing gallery.
Jess Hammond, everybody!
You came back.
I love her, Noah.
Yeah.
Me too.
I'm sorry, mate.
I didn't want to
ruin everything.
No, it's not
about what you want,
it's not about what I want.
It's about what Edie
wants, isn't it?
She lights up whenever
she's around you, James.
Even when she's angry.
Mm.
Especially when she's angry.
Let's grab a drink.
It is a privilege, of course,
for any agency new to these
shores, or well established,
to work with...
Poop.
Noah Poop.
Sorry, Noah Pepper.
Um, I hope you all enjoy
watching the campaign
as much as we've
enjoyed giving it life,
and please, don't
forget to promote us.
So, without further ado,
we give to you Pepper Poop
like you have never
seen it before.
Surprise!
I know it's not what
you're expecting,
but we did it!
Eh...
You did something, but
you didn't do that.
I'm just happy
these two were here.
And Harry.
If you hadn't make me
take thousands of photos,
we wouldn't of had
what we needed.
I always say, you could
never take too many photos.
I've heard all about
your games, Morgan.
And unfortunately,
I can't promote you.
But I can fire you.
We'll take it from here.
You presumptuous little toad.
I am the agency in America.
Actually, Morgan, you're not.
Excuse me, Mor-
- Oh, shut up, Harry!
What do you think you're doing?
Pulling rank.
Richard would like
a word with you.
Richard, darling.
Yeah, no...
You can't...
Hang on, you can't-
- Wait a minute,
that's my phone.
Just a second.
Richard, please.
Well, I'm gonna go make
sure the bar's stocked.
Shall we go somewhere quieter?
It seems like we've run
out of things to talk about.
Shut up.
That's another way to put it.
That's better.
- Can I have your number-
- Do you want my number now?
That went great, Noah.
Thanks.
You look amazing, by the way.
Really?
Yeah.
I was like...
Wow.
Thank you.
Um...
I'm sorry about Edie.
It's okay.
Have you ever loved
someone so much that
you feel like they
don't even see you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know exactly
how that feels.
I mean, maybe I don't love Edie.
Maybe I just love
the idea of her.
And she's a creative.
Exactly!
I should find somebody
in the industry.
Somebody who knows
how to support you.
Someone who loves fertilizer.
And would do literally anything
to be noticed by you.
Oh, I would definitely notice.
Yeah?
Yeah.
And I would never let her go.
Well, goodnight.
Okay, goodnight.