("MORE" BY THE SISTERS
OF MERCY PLAYING)
(VOCALIZING)
♪ Some people get by ♪
♪ With a little understanding ♪
(THUNDER CRASHING LOUDLY)
♪ With a whole lot more ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ Why you gotta be
So undemanding... ♪
(THUNDER CRASHING)
Whoa! (KIDS LAUGHING)
(LIVELY CHATTER) (SONG FADES)
Storm gonna get you!
Whoo!
(KIDS LAUGHING)
Wow, they are
easily entertained.
BEN: You come all this way,
and the thing they're most
excited about is the storm.
I'm surprised they're
not disappointed
about not having s'mores.
THOMAS: Oh, no, they're
gonna want some s'mores.
Trust me, that's a
battle for later.
(CHUCKLES) Thank you, babe.
Yeah, cheers.
Hey, where's my couch service?
Oh. The bottle's
right over there.
(LAUGHS) Well, okay, then.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, what, uh, what's
going on with the forecast?
BEN: It'll clear up
by morning, which is
good news 'cause I got a big
hike planned for us tomorrow.
Mm-mm. MARGARET:
Of course, you do.
BEN: Yeah, I do.
Can we just do some relaxing
while we're relaxing, you know?
Some fun indoor activities?
Yeah, like, uh, drinking.
BEN: That's what
we're doing right now.
(THUNDER RUMBLING) Hey, I'm
gonna... (CLICKS TONGUE)
I'm gonna take down
the, uh, patio umbrella
before the storm gets it.
Oh, do you want a
hand? No, I got it.
(INDISTINCT KIDS CHATTER)
You know, actually, we should
probably call it a night.
(EXHALES) I... No.
Come on, it's early.
We can still have some fun.
You know what? Let them go.
We... We have all weekend.
ELLIE: Yeah, it's
just been a long day
with the drive and
the kids, which...
Where did they... In there.
Oh, uh, kids, we're gonna
go back to our cabin.
Say good night to Auntie
Margo and Uncle Ben.
KIDS: Bye. Bye.
Bye, you little munchkin.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Okay, let's go. SPENCER:
See you tomorrow.
Mm-hmm. Tomorrow.
(MOUTHING)
(KIDS CHATTERING,
LAUGHING) Yeah.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CLICKS TONGUE)
That was fun. Yeah.
You know, it's early.
Just 'cause they're going to
bed doesn't mean we have to.
(CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(SONG RESUMES)
(VOCALIZING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
♪ I want more ♪
LUCY: This one's the Squire.
Mm.
And this one's the Chaos Spell.
And this one is the
Serpentine Lord.
He's my favorite card.
He does two times damage
for every attack
counter you have.
See? BEN: Yeah, yeah.
Uh, careful. You're
gonna walk into a tree.
Here you go. Remind
me not to invite
the Serpent Lord
over for taco night.
(BEN AND MARGARET LAUGHING)
He eats souls, Margaret,
not tacos.
Yeah, he eats souls, Margaret.
(MARGARET AND BEN LAUGHING)
You guys need a break?
BEN: You serious?
Already? ELLIE: I mean
from motormouth over
here. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Mom! (CHUCKLES)
(PLAYFULLY) Lucy. Oh, my God.
Tell me about your
cards. LUCY: Okay.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Mm.
No, I'm good. (CLICKS TONGUE)
It's gin and tonic.
What is wrong with you? (LAUGHS)
So, how's Ben doing?
You guys okay?
Ellie, he's fine now.
Just asking, as your friend
who wants you to be happy.
No, we're good. We're
good, I promise.
We just went on that
trip to Yosemite.
I saw that. It was awesome.
ELLIE: Those photos you posted
online looked like so much fun.
MARGARET: Mm.
(MUSIC FADES)
ELLIE: (SIGHS) Okay.
Is this still even a trail?
Knowing Ben, probably
not. (CHUCKLES)
Uh... (BLADE CHOPPING FOLIAGE)
(GRUNTS, SIGHS)
Pretty sure the, uh, path
picks up just over here.
(ELLIE STAMMERS)
Just careful with
that around the kids.
MARGARET: It's okay, Ellie.
He's just clearing a path.
You want to try, Thomas?
Kids? Mm. SPENCER: Vamos.
ELLIE: Uh, Spence, easy.
(BLADE CHOPPING FOLIAGE)
BEN: Yeah. You
shared your machete.
BEN: Yeah. Like
to pass it around.
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(KIDS CHATTERING)
ELLIE: Whoa.
Oh, my God. (CHUCKLES)
Careful. (MARGARET LAUGHING)
Oh. MARGARET: Whew.
Oh. Wow.
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
THOMAS: What is this place?
I feel like it should be
on a map or something.
LUCY: Hello?
BEN: Looks like it really
winds around back there.
Wonder how far back
it actually goes.
MARGARET: Oh, gosh, Ben.
There's only one
way to find out.
(GRUNTS)
All right, I got you, buddy.
Ready? Watch your head.
(GRUNTS)
BEN: Easy does
it. You need help?
LUCY: I got this.
THOMAS: Okay.
BEN: Watch out
for spiders. Okay.
Oh. LUCY: Spiders?
(MARGARET GROANS)
First step is a doozy.
MARGARET: (CHUCKLES)
It is. Come on.
Are you crazy? I'm
not going in there.
Come on.
Aren't we being
adventurous these days?
(CRICKETS CHIRPING) Seriously?
ELLIE: Okay.
MARGARET: You coming?
ELLIE: Apparently.
MARGARET: You good?
ELLIE: Ooh, yeah.
LUCY: This is so cool.
BEN: Yeah, it is cool, right?
THOMAS: Hey, don't go too far.
Stay where we can see you.
LUCY: Okay. MARGARET:
So what do you think
this place was used for?
Yeah, there's actually
a lot of these old ruins
around the countryside out here.
Could be anything,
decommissioned military fort,
fur trading company,
abandoned miner camp.
I really just asked 'cause
I knew he wanted to tell us.
ELLIE: Oh. (ELLIE AND
MARGARET LAUGHING)
Where did the kids go?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Kids?
(LUCY SCREAMS IN
DISTANCE) Oh, my God.
ELLIE: Lucy? Lucy!
THOMAS: Spencer!
THOMAS: Spencer,
where are you guys?
Say something. Say something!
LUCY: We're in here!
LUCY: Ew, gross.
ELLIE: What happened?
(LUCY GRUNTS)
ELLIE: Are you hurt?
We're fine. MARGARET:
Are they okay?
THOMAS: Yeah, false
alarm. (CLICKS TONGUE
You can't scare your
mother like that, you two.
Oh.
Look how all this stuff
just grew in through here.
Look, babies.
Oh. Uh, okay.
Spencer, put it back.
THOMAS: You know that
if they smell like you,
mama bird won't keep them.
SPENCER: But they're dead.
Mama's dead, too.
Just put it back, bud.
Okay? ELLIE: Whoa.
(LUCY KICKING)
ELLIE: Luce, what are
you kicking over there?
Luce, stop kicking dead things.
MARGARET: Hey, guys, Come
here. You got to see this.
What?
THOMAS: What's going on?
ELLIE: What'd you find?
(KIDS LAUGHING)
(THOMAS SPEAKS SPANISH)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
BEN: Whoa. MARGARET:
I know, right?
BEN: Wonder what busted these
holes through the walls.
MARGARET: And why make a
staircase up to a wall?
That's weird, right?
Oh, wow.
Bigger question is, why wall
off a huge hole in the ground?
Whoa. This is so cool.
SPENCER: Echo! (BEN CHUCKLES)
(ECHOING) Echo! SPENCER: Echo!
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(KIDS) Whoa. ELLIE:
Okay, guys, come on.
Let's get back from the edge.
ELLIE: Thomas, can you...
THOMAS: Yeah. Guys, come on.
How far down do you
think that goes?
BEN: I don't know. Huh. (GRUNTS)
(ROCK CLATTERING)
Oh, that's pretty deep.
Yeah, which is why I want
the kids to come back.
Come on, guys. You're
making me nervous.
This place gives me the
creeps. I'm going now.
El lugar que brilla.
"The place that shines?"
What do you mean, bud?
What are you talking about?
Es brillante.
Guys, it could not be more
dark down there. (CHUCKLES)
All right, guys. Let's, uh...
(PANTS) THOMAS:
Whoa. You okay?
Thomas? THOMAS: It's
okay, it's okay.
THOMAS: It's all right.
Just a little nosebleed.
Come on. Let's take care of you.
ELLIE: Come here. Y... You
okay? I got some tissue.
THOMAS: It's okay. Here.
Tilt your head back.
Can you tilt your head back?
There you go. Hold
that there. Hold it.
All right. All right,
little man. Let's go.
Bloody... bloody
nose? ELLIE: Yeah.
BEN: I used to get those as
a kid. They're the worst.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
Spencer! BEN: Oh, my God.
(MUSIC FADES) BEN: Whoa, dude.
THOMAS: (SPEAKING SPANISH)
Spencer, you have to be careful!
(SIGHS)
Are you listening?
(SIGHS) Oh, my God.
(BEN SIGHS) LUCY: Is he okay?
THOMAS: He's fine.
THOMAS: It's okay, it's okay.
MARGARET: I think it's, uh...
THOMAS: I got you. Time to go.
MARGARET: I'm so
glad you were there.
BEN: Oh, yeah, thanks, babe.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(MUSIC FADES)
THOMAS: Cabrón, technically,
the actual term is, uh,
"Macho cabrío,"
like the male goat.
MARGARET: (LAUGHING)
Really? (LAUGHS) Yeah.
Oh, no. (LAUGHS) THOMAS:
That, um, that...
(LAUGHS) THOMAS: That
doesn't translate literally.
The kids are zonked.
That hike really
took it out of them.
ELLIE: They're sleeping like
the dead in there. (CHUCKLES)
Did you give Spencer that
gift you brought him?
Oh, no, I was gonna do
it after dinner. Hmm.
I got him devil sticks.
Hmm. I saw them at a
shop on our last trip,
and I... I had some
when I was a kid.
I loved them. I
thought he'd like them.
They're harmless hippie toys.
Uh, yeah. (LAUGHS)
They kind of are.
Harmless as that
souvenir slingshot
he almost took my eye out with
last summer? Mm-hmm.
That was maybe
not the best gift.
Thought that
counts. (CHUCKLES)
Babe, can you pass
me a beer? Yeah.
(BEERS CLATTERING) You guys
should look into, like,
the Badlands. BEN: Dude.
How'd you do that?
It's easy. You want
to try? Yeah, I do.
Just, uh, just put the cap
against the table.
Cap goes there.
Firm grip on the neck.
BEN: Yeah. Mm-hmm.
So, you guys going
on any other trips?
THOMAS: Hold it really tight.
MARGARET: Yeah. Going to Florida.
You got to hold it really
tight. And then slam on it.
BEN: Ow. (GROANS) Damn
it. All right. Try again.
MARGARET: Next year, maybe
you can join us for that.
Oh, nice. THOMAS: Try again.
The kids could stay with your
parents. BEN: I'm gonna get this.
You almost got it.
BEN: Jesus Christ.
It's all right. I can do it.
No, I can open my own beer. THOMAS:
I'm just... I'm just saying.
THOMAS: Try again.
BEN: Super tight.
Very tight.
Ow! But I did it.
THOMAS: There you go.
You did it. MARGARET:
(LAUGHING) Oh, wow.
You did it in, uh,
in your own way.
That's fantastic. (BEN
AND MARGARET LAUGHING)
Yay? (LAUGHS) BEN: I guess
you just got to do it harder.
THOMAS: You got to do it
harder. There you go, man.
Oh, cheers. ELLIE: College.
ELLIE: Babe, come on.
Do you really have
to keep doing that
on someone else's furniture?
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
No, yeah, you're right.
Uh, that would be...
so inappropriate.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(MOUTHING)
(SMACKS LIPS) Hey,
you want to go,
um, toss some horseshoes? Yep.
(THOMAS SIGHS) Uh, wh... okay.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Ellie, would you like
to help me make a salad?
Sure. (MUSIC FADES)
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING
IN BACKGROUND)
MARGARET: Okay, I
chop, you spill.
It's... honestly, it's nothing.
He's been acting so weird
since we got here.
(REFRIGERATOR CLOSES)
You, too. So out with it.
I really, really shouldn't.
"Oh, I really shouldn't."
You want to tell me
so bad. Look at you.
Plus, you know, it might...
might make you feel better.
(GRUNTS PLAYFULLY)
Okay, we're gonna need
some drinks. (LAUGHS)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
Wine. Yeah.
THOMAS: Hey, about this
morning, can't thank you enough.
Ah, dude, it was nothing.
Um, so Spencer...
he's a little crazy.
Oh, he's a lunatic. Absolutely.
But you're great
with him. Uncle Ben.
Eh.
So?
When are you, uh,
when are you guys
gonna have your own?
Uh, I... you know.
I don't know that we're really
quite ready for that yet, so...
Bro, nobody's ever ready.
Like, I think of our parents,
and I'm surprised we even
made it to adulthood.
(CHUCKLES) No, you just
got to, you got to jump in.
Headfirst. De cabeza.
So, Kyle... Mm-hmm.
And Katie? (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Mm-hmm.
How exactly did that work?
(CLICKS TONGUE)
A lot of alcohol.
And the kids were
at my parents'.
I can't believe
Katie. Kyle maybe.
Oh, Kyle definitely.
But, I mean, you know, they
got married after college
just like Thomas and me.
W... Was it just,
like, all of you
in one big, like...
blob or...
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I want details.
(GULPS) I need another
sip. (BOTH LAUGHING)
So you and Kyle are on the bed.
And where are Thomas and
Katie during all this?
Uh, on the chair in
the corner. Mm-hmm.
That little blue one?
Okay.
And so, she's, like,
sitting in Thomas's lap...
Mm-hmm. Her back to me
clothes still on,
mind you. Mm-hmm.
And Thomas, you know,
starts kissing her neck,
and then looks over
her shoulder at me,
and it just felt like,
"This is it. Let's... let's go."
(BOTH LAUGHING)
BEN: I'm not opposed
to it in theory.
It's more... in practice
I'm not so sure about.
THOMAS: Uh-huh.
You do know you still have
fun when you have kids, right?
(SCOFFS)
It's just slightly
different fun.
I like kids. We both
like kids. It's just...
It's kind of like the
high-end Airbnb, you know?
It's great for the
weekend, just...
not so sure it's
really our lifestyle.
Yeah, you'd be surprised how
your lifestyle can change.
Is it hard?
Sometimes, sure, but
it's the best thing, man.
Mm.
Sometimes it feels like
it's the only thing.
So things... progress
between Kyle and me.
Okay, like, you took
your clothes off or...
Mm-hmm.
Ellie. Did you guys actually...
Oh, we fucked.
(SQUEALS)
(LAUGHING)
(INHALES) And?
(CUP THUDS ON TABLE)
And it was great.
Until I look over
at Thomas and Katie,
and they're just
watching us, sort of...
I don't know, like,
half-heartedly canoodling.
Canoodling?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, it
was weird, Margo.
But did you finish?
So, I told Thomas
that I faked it.
Off the fucking charts.
(LAUGHS) Okay, Kyle.
Yes. (BOTH LAUGHING)
(INHALES) And so it's
been weird ever since.
Mm-hmm. I mean,
you saw. I just...
I don't know. I... I feel like
I cheated on him or something.
He'll get over it. Mm.
Like, he hasn't
touched me since.
To be fair, you know, it's just
been busy with work... Hmm.
And the kids and my parents.
We haven't really had
any time to ourselves.
Well, why don't the kids
just stay here tonight?
Could they?
I mean, I don't see why not.
Ben actually seems
to kind of like
having them around.
(POURING DRINK)
Yes, he does, doesn't
he? (GLASSES CLATTER)
Don't get any ideas.
We're still not having any
of our own. (POURING DRINK)
Mm. (THUD ON TABLE)
You know, we're focusing
on our careers right now,
and we're not kid people
at the end of the day.
We like to go out
on a whim and travel
and, you know, all the
stuff you and I used to do
before you...
Before I had kids.
(SIGHS) You know what I mean.
Well, maybe it's for
the best, you know?
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELECTRICITY ZAPPING)
MARGARET: A double Cancer?
ELLIE: Yep, the other
one's a Cancer, too.
MARGARET: It's just... it's
not common when you're, like,
a triple of one sign.
THOMAS: Is it a bad sign?
Yes. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
BEN: Uh, focus. Oh! Hey.
All right. Whoa, whoa,
whoa. Careful, dude.
You're gonna whack
yourself in the head, okay?
Look, took me a while
to figure it out,
but you'll get the hang of
it. (CHUCKLES) Just practice.
You're doing great. Um, just...
(CLEARS THROAT) (MUSIC FADES)
BEN: Ah, you... I know.
It's just frustrating.
Great. No. Ooh, watch
your face. Ooh, sh...
(CLICKS TONGUE) BEN:
All right, go get them.
I was thinking maybe the kids
could stay with us tonight.
Say what?
(GULPS, CLICKS TONGUE)
That's a great idea.
Yeah. Sure. That should be fun.
Won't that be fun, guys?
A little sleepover?
You guys can stay...
(SPEAKING SPANISH) Okay?
Can I get some
verbal confirmation?
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
No, that's all right. You
don't have to turn around.
Uh, yeah, I think we've
already been replaced.
ELLIE: Mm-hmm. BEN: That's it.
Okay. Okay, okay.
Okay. Hand them over.
Hold my beer.
Devil sticks. See?
Just finesse, finesse.
You just got to
feel them sticks.
Give it a flippity flip.
Okay? You want to
see the helicopter?
(MAKING WHOOSHING SOUNDS)
How about them hot moves?
Yeah? Yeah? See how easy?
Remember the balance?
(SLURPS, GULPS) BEN: Just keep practicing,
and you will get the hang of it.
Promise. (SIGHS) Well,
I'm about ready to go.
Right now? Mm-hmm.
THOMAS: Okay? Yeah? Yeah.
ELLIE: All right, kids,
we're gonna go, so be good.
BEN: So, this is
the simple stuff.
It's for babies, okay?
(MOUTHING) BEN:
Once you get good,
you start doing the flips, okay?
BEN: Oh! MARGARET: Ooh.
LUCY: Nice. Demon Sword. BEN:
Wait, I have a Demon Sword.
MARGARET: Uh, wait, so can I
play now... (GLASS THUD ON TABLE)
that he's put his card down
or do we have to wait...
You can't do that. MARGARET:
You had two Demon Swords?
BEN: I'm gonna referee.
You can't do that.
There's no order.
This isn't Uno.
LUCY: Guys, it's... it's not that
complicated. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Unless you get the Rabid
Queen. That changes everything.
Ooh, what happens if
you get the Rabid Queen?
Yeah, what happens?
You don't want to know.
We just asked. Here.
Moving on. I'm playing this one.
Normally, you put
the thing there.
MARGARET: Here? LUCY:
No. Let me... (SIGHS)
Quiero volver.
(LUCY AND MARGARET
CHATTERING) What's up?
Quiero volver. I don't
know. What's that mean?
He wants to go back.
(THUD ON TABLE)
Back where? LUCY:
The bright place.
The place that
shines. In the woods.
Oh, that old fort?
Nah, dude, I don't think
we're gonna go back there.
Ah, we got lots of fun
things we can do here,
like teach you some new
tricks with your sticks.
See if you can pick those up.
(LUCY AND MARGARET CHATTERING)
I got a lot of cool
stuff... (HISSES)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING) (CHATTERING STOPS)
Sounds great, Ben.
MARGARET: I'm gonna pull.
I feel like... Okay.
MARGARET: Oh, shit! Good.
I got the Serpentine
Lord. BEN: Mm.
MARGARET: That's bad,
right? You swore.
Um...
if I give you 20 bucks,
will you not tell your mom?
You're bribing children now?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Guys, let's just play this game.
Yeah, sorry. I win.
MARGARET: We'll
be right out here
if you need anything, okay?
Do you want the
door open or closed?
LUCY AND SPENCER:
Closed. Okay. Good night.
(LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS)
They're out like a light.
That wasn't so
bad. (BEN SCOFFS)
Kids are fine.
It's what it does to the
parents that I don't like.
You talking about Thomas?
No, I'm talking
about both of them.
They were at each
other's throats all day.
Well, that is not
the kids' fault.
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you know?
What aren't you telling me?
Why don't we enjoy
the night air?
Okay. (DOOR OPENING)
(SIGHS)
BEN: Wow. Just wow.
(LAUGHING) I know.
Kyle I can see, but...
Right? (BEN CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(LAUGHING) Makes
me wonder about
all those date nights my
parents had when I was a kid.
(GROANS) (CHUCKLES)
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
What?
Do you want kids?
(LAUGHS SOFTLY) What?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
I...
I mean...
well, you kind of
decided this for us.
See, that.
That there. I made
the decision, not us.
You know, I see how great you
are with Lucy and Spencer,
and I just...
I wonder if it's something
I'm keeping you from.
You know? Like, I just...
I want to make sure
that we're still
on the same page.
Look, we don't have to
decide tonight, all right?
We've got time.
I mean, you got time. I
have an expiration date.
Fair enough. Okay.
(SIGHS) Okay.
You want to talk about
it? Let's talk about it.
I mean, yes. I don't...
I don't know. I...
I just don't want to feel like
I'm the only person that
has to figure it out.
What do you mean by that?
Never mind.
Okay. (SIGHS)
Oh, I just feel
so real right now.
What do you mean?
Like... connected.
That's the word.
I feel connected.
Connected to what?
This. This... fire.
These trees, these bugs.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
Um, I want to feel
this way all the time.
I just feel like I'm
a part of everything,
like everything is connected
and it's bigger
than me, you know?
And you think about the city
and how disjointed it is,
and... I don't know.
When I think about it sometimes,
it just makes me... (MAKES
GAGGING NOISE) (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Love... you are very high.
(LAUGHS)
No. Oh, no, I... I promise.
You got to trust me on this one.
I'm a little high. (LAUGHING)
You're high as hell.
Come here. (LAUGHS) Okay.
(GRUNTS) Let's feel connected.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
I'll take that. I'm
a one-hit wonder.
You took like six hits.
(MARGARET LAUGHING)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHIMES CLANGING)
(CHIMES CONTINUE CLANGING)
(ELECTRICITY ZAPPING)
(ZAPPING INTENSIFIES)
(MUSIC FADES)
Oh, good morning.
(FEIGNS LAUGHING) Here you go.
Mm, thank you. BEN: Yeah.
You look incredible
this morning.
You're a liar.
(GROANS) Do we have Advil?
Yeah. We do.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) You're
a saint, you know that?
(PILLS RATTLE)
(BEN EXHALES)
(PLATES CLATTER)
(PHONE CHIMES)
(CUTLERY CLATTERS)
Yes. Get it, girl.
(PHONE CHIMES)
MARGARET: The kids awake?
No, they're, uh, still
sleeping, I think.
Lucky they sleep
so late. (CHUCKLES)
Rise and shine, sleepyheads.
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Lucy? Spencer?
I think I can convince Ben
to make us some pancakes.
Luce? Spencer?
I'm gonna open the door, okay?
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
They're not in there.
Did you check the
bathroom? Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Uh, maybe they're just
playing outside or something.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
I don't see them out there.
Really?
Maybe they're, um...
Go check and see
if they're playing
over by the pond.
(SIGHS) (DOOR OPENING)
(POURING) (THUD ON TABLE)
(BEATING EGGS) (DOOR CLOSING)
BEN: You don't see them?
Huh. (DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSING) Okay,
I'm freaking out.
No, no. You know what?
Remember they were playing
hide-and-seek yesterday?
Probably just hiding
and want us to...
Right, well... Lucy, we're not
playing right now! find them.
Spencer? Hey, guys?
Hey. Breakfast.
(SIGHS)
Lucy?
They're not in any
of the closets.
Okay, wait.
Look, hey, they probably
just went back over
to Thomas and Ellie's
place. She just texted me.
There's no way
they're over there.
The kids' shoes
are gone. What?
They took their shoes.
No, they wouldn't have.
They wouldn't have what,
Ben? Ben, where you gonna go?
They wouldn't have what?
I'm just gonna check the path.
They can't have gone far.
Okay, well, I'll go with you.
No, no, no, stay at the house in
case they come back. (DOOR CLOSING)
Were they even in the cabin
when we came back in last night?
They didn't sneak
out, all right?
The sun came up, they
thought they'd go for a walk.
They probably just went
back down this path.
They can't have gone far.
They're fine. Everything's
gonna be fine.
(MUSIC FADES) We're
gonna find them.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(PANTS) Lucy.
BEN: (IN DISTANCE)
Lucy! Spencer!
(GROANS SOFTLY, PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
Guys?
Jesus Christ, there you are.
What are you guys doing in here?
Hey! You know you can't
be here without an adult.
Guys.
Es brilliante.
Okay, I need you to come
down here right now.
No, I'm... I'm
serious. Right now.
No, no, no. Stop! No!
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(WHISPERS) Oh, God.
(STIFLED RETCHING)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(PANTS)
(CELL PHONE CONTINUES VIBRATING)
Why aren't you
answering your phone?
(SIGHS) Fuck.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Margaret. MARGARET:
Where are you?
Have you found them? Please
tell me you found them.
(SNIFFLES) I went up
to the lookout, and...
Ben? I followed the flowers.
No, Ben, you're breaking
up. I followed...
I followed the flowers. Ben?
I'm alm... I'm almost home.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey.
MARGARET: (SIGHS) Thank God.
(KIDS SHOUTING PLAYFULLY)
Thank God. No, Ben,
they're here. They're here.
I was so sure I was gonna see
their little bodies
floating in the lake.
Could you even imagine? (SIGHS)
I... I see you.
(MUSIC FADES) No, I
can't. I can't imagine.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)
MARGARET: You know how much he
loves to hike... (KIDS LAUGHING)
so he had to fit one in.
ELLIE: Damn, Ben,
you look like hell.
I was just telling Ellie
how quickly the kids
petered out this morning.
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And how you took them out
for a hike, brought them back
and then went out on your own.
BEN: Right.
(KIDS CHATTERING PLAYFULLY)
(DOOR SLAMS LOUDLY)
You good, man?
Uh, yeah. Th...
They're... they're okay?
Yeah, except they're bouncing
off the freaking walls.
What'd you guys give them for breakfast,
pure sugar? (KIDS SCREAMING PLAYFULLY)
LUCY: Wait for
me. ELLIE: No...
(THOMAS SPEAKING SPANISH)
I'm busy. I'm... Stop. No.
Okay.
(LAUGHS) I'm coming to get you!
MARGARET: Well, it looks like
you two enjoyed your night off.
(LUCY SCREAMS PLAYFULLY)
(THOMAS AND ELLIE TALKING
QUIETLY, LAUGHING)
MARGARET: Okay. We're
still standing here.
Mom, why is Ben staring at me?
(MUSIC FADES)
I saw them.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
I know I saw them.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MARGARET LAUGHING)
BEN: Hey, guys.
Did, uh... you sleep
all right last night?
Of course we did,
silly. Dead bugs.
Those aren't dead.
(LUCY CHUCKLES)
Like I said.
Uh... L... let me
ask you something.
Did you two go for a
little walk this morning?
(HUSHED CHITTERING)
What was that all about?
It's our secret language.
You want to know
what he said to me?
Stop messing around.
I need to know
where you went this morning.
Hold this under your chin.
If your chin glows yellow...
Okay, did you go back
to the fort, all right?
If you did, it's okay.
I just need to know.
Do the thing first, then
I'll tell you. Promise.
Está brillando.
Means you have a secret, too.
Okay, well?
LUCY: Yes, we went there.
But you won't tell
on us, will you?
Wait, what did you do there?
Careful, Ben.
Or we'll run off
and join the circus.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey. Little man.
Careful with those, all
right? They're heavy.
If you hit yourself in
the head, it'll hurt.
Hey, just don't go so high.
Stop.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(LUCY SPEAKS SPANISH)
Is it glowing?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAUGHS)
(THOMAS AND ELLIE
CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
I'm starving. THOMAS: Mm-hmm.
ELLIE: Yeah, you think
that I'd leave this?
THOMAS: No. ELLIE:
That's not how it works.
But this is why, like,
I live in a house.
(THOMAS SPEAKS
INDISTINCTLY) Oh. I'm full.
(THOMAS AND ELLIE
CONTINUE INDISTINCTLY)
(THOMAS AND ELLIE LAUGHING)
(MUSIC FADES)
You all right?
Ben? Ben.
Um... what... what
were they doing?
The kids when you found them.
Oh, I didn't.
Ellie said that they
came into the cabin
right before they saw us.
She thought we sent them over
to get them up in the morning.
They must have been
in the backwoods
behind the cabin
or something and we
just missed them.
They... they went...
they went back there.
Where? T... To that
old fort, the pit.
"The place that shines."
They told me that.
That's a really strenuous hike
for two little kids to make.
They're probably
just putting you on.
Wait, you haven't
noticed? What?
The way they look at you now?
The... the... the nosebleeds?
And... and Spencer
with the sticks.
He couldn't fucking keep
those things in the air
for two seconds yesterday,
and now he's a
goddamn majorette.
That's not possible.
I was really scared
this morning, too,
but they're here now and
they're safe and it's fine.
No. I... I need you
to just listen to me
'cause what I'm gonna tell
you is gonna sound impossible.
Just please hear me.
I saw them jump into that pit.
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
I saw them just tip right
into it like they were in
some sort of a trance.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
I don't think that's
them out there anymore.
Margo.
What?
How you been feeling lately?
Are you serious right now?
I'm just asking.
Look, you've seen that.
That is not this.
This is not that.
I don't know what this is.
Yeah, but you don't believe me.
I think you were in
an agitated state,
and you maybe saw something
that you can't quite explain
or process in some
rational way just yet.
"Rationally." Yeah, no. Uh,
way to parse words, Margo.
Look, we're both really... a
little overtired right now.
You know, why
don't you lie down?
Have a nap.
(SIGHS) Yeah. No, you're right.
I should probably
just get some rest.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(MUSIC FADES)
Jesus Christ.
You shouldn't swear.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
What are you doing in here?
Just wanted to see
what you were up to.
Okay, well, I'm not in
the mood, so just get out.
But we want to play
a game with you.
What game?
(SHARP THUD) (GASPS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)
MARGARET: Did you ever
play, like, powder-puff?
Why'd they call
it "Powder-puff?"
I don't know. 'Cause
they have to call it,
like, a little bitchy name 'cause
you're a girl. (ELLIE LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS) I don't know. That's what I
was thinking. Like, why isn't it just
"Girls football?" It's called "girlie
girl girl football." (LAUGHING)
"Do you play football or
do you play powder-puff?"
(MARGARET AND ELLIE LAUGHING)
I don't even remember
what was on the back
of my jersey, like...
(ELLIE SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY) MARGARET: Hey.
I thought you were
gonna lie down.
Uh, I didn't want
to miss all the fun.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SMACKS LIPS) So, I
think that would be good.
Hey. They ever, uh...
(BOX CLOSING)
They ever scare
you? Those two?
Yeah. Absolutely. All the time.
No, not them. Kids. Your...
your kids. (BEER UNCAPS)
What, you mean like...
I don't know, just,
like... Oh, geez!
THOMAS: (LAUGHING) Okay.
(CHUCKLES) Good timing, Spence.
I'm hungry. THOMAS:
All right, just...
Just have some chips,
but don't overdo it.
Dinner's almost ready.
LUCY: Hey, Ben!
(MARGARET AND ELLIE LAUGHING)
Just like a super, like, tiny...
Look at me.
Whoa, hey! Hey!
What?
Um...
Do you want a beer?
Uh, no, we're drinking wine.
Cool.
You want some?
They're my favorite.
Jesus Christ. No. But
aren't you hungry, Ben?
Hey. Not everybody wants
to spoil their dinner, bud.
You feeling all right?
Yeah, no. I'm...
(MUSIC FADES) just tired.
Excuse me, young lady. What
do you think you're doing?
Oh, my God.
What... Lucy. That
was inappropriate.
And amazing. (LAUGHS)
Thank you.
That's a really
good pour. Too good.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SPENCER TAPPING)
For you, Daddy.
No, no, no. Oh, my God.
What the hell, dude?
Whoa. THOMAS: The
hell's your problem?
Uh, hey, wait. Wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Just show, um, show them.
Show them! Hey,
don't yell at my son.
Ben, what are you doing?
Give me the bottle.
Give me the goddamn...
Hey, Ben! Hey!
Hands off him! BEN: Give
me the goddamn bottle.
Ow! All right, hey, look.
MARGARET: Hey, Ben! What?
You're on mood
stabilizers. So what?
(PILLS RATTLE)
Wait, th... these...
these were empty.
He... You showed me... She
was gonna put the, um...
them into... SPENCER:
(CRYING) My hand.
He hurt my hand.
Jesus Christ, Ben.
What's wrong with
you? Are you okay?
I thought they were candy.
No, they're fucking with me.
Ben, he's nine. No.
Wh... Whatever he is,
he's fucking with me.
He showed me this bottle.
It was empty, all right?
And she was gonna put them
in... into your drink,
and somehow he got the pills...
you got the pills back in here.
Somehow he put them back in
here to make me look like...
To what? To make me overdose?
Is that what you're saying,
that my kids were
gonna make me overdose?
I... I don't, I
don't, I don't...
Just breathe. Okay?
Take a breath.
They went out on their
own this morning.
MARGARET: Ben. What?
BEN: Yeah, they...
they went out.
What are you talking
about? BEN: No, no, they...
they snuck out, and...
and I went after them
to the... to the ruins.
And you know what I saw?
No. Yes.
I saw them jump into
the pit. And then I saw
your broken little bodies at
the bottom of that fucking pit!
ELLIE: Ben, shut the
fuck up! That's what...
Shut up. Shut up.
(QUIETLY) Okay. Uh...
Kids, go... go play.
But I want to listen. THOMAS:
Lucy. (SPEAKING SPANISH STERNLY)
Vamos.
You let them go out alone?
No. We didn't let them
go out. They just went.
They just... What do
you mean they just went?
Well, when we woke
up, they were gone.
Hold... hold on a s...
I'm... I'm missing something.
When I texted you this morning,
why didn't you mention that?
Well, I didn't know then,
and we just didn't
tell you afterward.
We just didn't want to worry you
if there was nothing
to worry about.
Margaret, what the fuck? I'm
still trying to understand
how you let them out of
your sight like that.
They were sleeping.
What, are we supposed
to tie them in a tree to
protect them from bears?
No, Ben, we wanted you
to be responsible adults,
but clearly we made
a bad judgment call
on you and your
goddamn mental health.
Okay, Thomas, that's enough.
Those are our
children, Margaret.
Okay, maybe you don't
know what that feels like,
but it would be really
fucking nice if you'd try.
Okay, so because I
haven't experienced
the miracle of childbirth,
I don't know what it takes
to babysit your kids?
You don't understand
the responsibility.
What? You say that you
guys aren't kid people
because your jet-setting
life is so full,
you're so focused
on your career.
Give me a fucking break, okay?
You're not fooling anyone.
Are you serious?
Like you two are the
paragons of responsibility?
Okay, you need to
stop right now.
Oh, oh, Mr. Moral
Authority speaks.
I'm not fucking around,
Ben. BEN: Oh, great.
I'm glad you're serious.
Then we can all talk
about the fact that we're
only in this situation
because the two of you
pawned your creepy-ass kids
off on the two of us... What?
To save your
shitty-ass marriage.
MARGARET: Okay, Ben.
Oh, wait, right.
You guys live, like, a mile
away from your parents, right?
That's super convenient.
So then you can just
pawn your creepy kids
off on them, too,
whenever you guys want
to go have a foursome.
(MUSIC FADES) Ben.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I know.
It was more of a...
two-and-a-half-some,
right? MARGARET: Ben!
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Are you fucking kidding
me? ELLIE: No. (SIGHS)
I... THOMAS: You...
ELLIE: Babe, I'm
sorry. This is fucked.
I'm sorry. You're all fucked.
THOMAS: You're all fucked! Mm.
Ellie, I'm sorry.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Well, I see everything's
all out on the table.
What?
Come on, Ben.
You think we don't tell
each other everything?
About your little
manic episodes?
Ellie, shut up.
How you went off the deep
end and lost another job?
MARGARET: Ellie. ELLIE: You
know, maybe it's not that
Margaret doesn't
want to have kids.
(MUSIC FADES) Maybe she just
doesn't want to have them with you.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
Fucking nice.
MARGARET: Ben.
(BEN SIGHS)
(HINGES CREAKING) (SIGHS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
LUCY: What's wrong?
(GASPS) Stop doing that.
I didn't mean to scare you.
SPENCER: Fuck.
Shit, fuck, shit, fuck.
S... Stop. Okay?
Get out of here.
Guys, look. Hey,
I'm... I'm done.
All right, go play
with your parents.
I don't care anymore.
But don't you want to know
what happened this morning?
I'll tell you.
If you can keep it a secret.
Yeah. No, no, no, I won't
tell anyone. What happened?
SPENCER: Insectos muertos.
BEN: What did he just say?
Dead bugs.
BEN: Hey, Lucy,
I was responsible
for the two of you,
so I need to know
that you're both okay.
I need to know that I'm okay.
Do you understand
that? Of course I do.
And I promise... we're
better than ever.
(GROANS) Jesus Christ.
(MOCKINGLY) "Jesus Christ."
All right, give me the shovel.
Make me.
Make you? Just give it to me.
BEN: (GRUNTING) Come on,
give it to me. (LAUGHS)
Spencer!
(CHOKES) (LUCY LAUGHING)
Spencer?
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
Hey. Wh... Spence, hey, hey.
All right, just cough.
Try and cough it up.
(CHOKING) (LUCY
CONTINUES LAUGHING)
Spence. Spencer.
Spence, hey, hey, hey.
Come on. Breathe. You
got to breathe, buddy.
Come on. Come on.
(SLAPPING LIGHTLY)
(GRUNTS)
Come on! Come on!
(BEN SLAPPING)
Come on, Spencer.
Spencer, come on.
Just breathe. Breathe.
Please. Come on. Wake up. Come
on, don't... don't do this.
Don't do this. You're
messing with me.
Come on. Come
on! Wake up. Ben?
Oh, my God. BEN:
He's not breathing.
I... I can't find a pulse.
Margo, I can't find a pulse!
Ellie! Ellie! Move, move,
move. (STAMMERS) What do we do?
What do we do? I don't know.
(GRUNTING) BEN: I don't know.
He's not... he's
not, um... Ellie!
I don't know what
we're supposed to do.
ELLIE: (STAMMERING)
What... what? BEN: He's...
What? No, no, no, no!
No, Spencer. (PANTS)
BEN: Is he going to be okay?
ELLIE: (GRUNTS) Come
on. No, Spencer.
Come on. Come on,
Spencer. MARGARET: Thomas!
(CRYING) Come on,
What happened?
ELLIE: Come on. No.
No. Come on. Daddy.
Oh, no. Oh, my God.
No. No. No. No. THOMAS:
Lucy, look at me.
(ELLIE CRYING) THOMAS: It's
gonna be fine. It's okay.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING) (SOBBING)
(ELLIE SOBBING LOUDLY)
No. No.
(ELLIE CONTINUES SOBBING)
What happened?
What did you do?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
No, no, no. I... I didn't,
I didn't do anything.
This wasn't me.
This... this isn't...
this isn't my fault.
What are you talking
about? BEN: They did this.
This is... this is their fault!
This is your fault!
ELLIE: Get out!
BEN: No, I... I...
Shut up and get the
fuck out of here!
I told you, ever
since they went out...
I just need you to listen.
No, get the fuck out!
Okay, okay. Get the
fuck out of here!
Get out!
Just listen to me
for one second.
ELLIE: Get the fuck
out! Get the fuck out!
(SOBBING)
(MUSIC FADES)
(SOBBING LOUDLY)
Oh, my God, no!
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
MARGARET: I need to
report a... Oh, God.
I need to report...
I... I need to report a death.
Hello? This is Thomas Huerta.
(INHALES) Ben Winslow
has just murdered my son.
End of Churchill Road.
The Far Syde Cabins.
A few hours?
Yeah, we can wait.
We'll be here.
(THOMAS CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
(MARGARET RETCHING, COUGHING)
(INHALES, COUGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(TOILET FLUSHING)
(SOBBING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(SNIFFLES, SIGHS)
(BREATHING SLOWLY)
(MUSIC FADES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Margo.
Hey. No, no. It's not
me. Hey. Hey. Hey.
You got to believe me.
I don't know what to say to you.
This all started when we...
when we went to the ruins.
Th... Think about it.
The kids have been obsessed
with going back there.
"The place that shines."
They jumped in, and something
down there took their place.
Their bodies must
still be there.
MARGARET: Oh, Ben. No, no,
I'm not crazy. I'm not.
You know, if you come
with me, you'll see.
Come on, come on.
Ben, let go of me.
No, you just need to
see. Let go of my arm.
No, come on. Ben!
You're just making things
worse. What will this prove?
I need you to believe me. I
need you to be on my side.
Fine. Fine, let's go.
And when there's nothing there,
what then? What do we do then?
(MUSIC FADES)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
BEN: They were there.
Margaret, they were
just right there.
Margaret, please.
Do not look at me like that.
There's nothing there, Ben.
No, I know what I saw.
They were right there,
okay? (STAMMERS)
Just right... just
right fucking there!
All right, all right, okay.
I'll j... I'll... I
can climb down and I...
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
What the fuck? Okay. Okay, okay.
I bet an animal dragged
them away or something.
Some... Something
happened! Some...
Th... There's something I
just don't understand yet...
Ben. Ben. But I will.
Okay, no, no, no!
I'm gonna understand,
and then you'll see
it. Ben! Just stop!
Even with all of the evidence
just staring right at you,
you can't admit, you can't even
acknowledge just for one moment
that you might be wrong!
Everything that's happening...
it's just in your head!
I know what I saw.
You need to listen to me.
Ben, Spencer is dead.
He is dead. And
it's not because of
some old building or
a hole in the ground.
It's because your actions,
they have consequences.
Your ac... You. You
did this. Just you.
That's how it is?
Yeah, that's how it is.
(SCOFFS) Ben.
We have to go back
and... sort it out.
But... when we're there...
we can keep talking.
Ben, for me, please. Let's
just go back together.
(MUSIC FADES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(LUCY SNAPPING) (GASPS)
Oh.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(MARGARET SIGHS)
(CLICKS TONGUE) You should
be with your parents.
It's okay. He's just playing.
Lucy, honey... Can
I show you a trick?
Sure.
Oh. Lucy, I think we should stay
by the cabin with your parents.
I'll get them soon.
What?
I want to play with you now.
Honey...
I want to show you
what's in the woods.
Lucy.
I want to show you
what's in the woods.
Please? (SNIFFLING)
(CRYING) Oh, honey.
THOMAS: Are you
okay for a minute?
I'll... I'll be just
a minute, okay, hon?
I'll be right back.
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES) Hey.
Get the hell away
from her, Margaret.
Lucy, come here right now.
But... She just wanted to...
Don't tell me what she wants.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
I'm gonna go check
on your mother.
You stay strong, okay?
LUCY: Daddy?
Are you okay?
Can I show you
something in the woods?
Ellie?
(DOOR CLOSING)
Thomas?
(CELL PHONE RINGTONE
PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
Thomas?
(RINGTONE CONTINUES)
(THOMAS GASPING IN PAIN)
MARGARET: (IN DISTANCE) Hello?
(CHITTERING IN DISTANCE)
(RINGTONE STOPS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHITTERING CONTINUES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(PANTS)
(LINE RINGING) Fuck.
Oh, come on, Ben.
(PANTS) Pick up, Ben.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(VIBRATION STOPS)
(LINE RINGING, STOPS)
(CLICKS TONGUE)
(GASPING)
(CHITTERING NEARBY)
(MUSIC FADES) (RAPID
CLICKING NEARBY)
(RAPID CLICKING CONTINUES)
(ELLIE COUGHING, PAINED GASPING)
(CHITTERING) (SUSPENSEFUL
MUSIC PLAYING)
Ellie?
What the fuck?
(CHITTERING) (GASPS, PANTING)
(RAPID CLICKING)
(FLOORBOARDS CREAKING)
(GASPS, SCREAMS)
(ELLIE COUGHING, GASPING)
Oh, m... Oh, my God!
Ellie! Ellie! (SOBS)
Ellie! Ellie, what...
(GRUNTING) (ELLIE GROANS)
Oh, my God, what happened?
(GASPING, COUGHING)
What happened? (SOBBING)
(PAINED GRUNTING, GASPING)
MARGARET: (SOBS) Oh, my God.
(BREATHING DEEPLY, STOPS)
(MARGARET CRYING SOFTLY)
(HISSING, RAPID CLICKING)
(SPENCER LAUGHING) Spencer?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
What did you do to
your mom, Spencer?
(RAPID CLICKING)
(MARGARET SCREAMS)
(SPENCER GRUNTS)
(HISSING, RAPID CLICKING)
(POUNDING ON DOOR) (SCREAMS)
(PANTS)
(POUNDING ON DOOR CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
(SPENCER SNARLING)
(POUNDING ON DOOR CONTINUES)
(WHIMPERING)
(SNARLING, HISSING)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
(POUNDING AND SNARLING CONTINUE)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(RASPY GROWLING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(FLOORBOARDS CREAKING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(PANTS SOFTLY)
Want to play a game,
Margaret? It's fun, I promise.
You play the Rabid Queen.
And I'll even give
you a head start.
You want to know what happens
when we catch the Rabid Queen?
I never got to tell you.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
(RAPID CLICKING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(RAPID CLICKING, CHITTERING)
(SPENCER LAUGHING)
SPENCER AND LUCY: Ten.
Nine.
(CHITTERING)
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
(HINGES CREAKING)
Three.
Two.
(CHITTERING)
One.
(SINGSONGY) Ready or
not, here we come.
(GASPS)
(HISSES)
(DOOR OPENING, CLOSING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(RAPID CLICKING)
(FLOORBOARDS CREAKING)
(CLICKING)
(WHISPERS) Off with her head.
(SCREAMS, WHIMPERING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(KEYS RATTLING)
She's dead. They killed her.
PARK RANGER: Whoa, whoa.
Slow down. Slow down.
Are you Ms. Huerta?
No. She's dead. They killed her.
You're not listening
to me. Okay, I received
a call about a dead boy.
It's Ms. Huerta who's dead?
No, he's not dead. He came
back and he killed her.
(MARGARET PANTING) Listen, I need
you to take a deep breath, okay?
Just breathe.
It's them. It's the
fucking children.
We... we need to get into
your truck right now.
All... all right, ma'am.
Why don't we go inside
and you can just show
me what happened, okay?
Everything's gonna be all
right. We'll work this out.
I don't want to go in
there. She's in there.
Ms. Huerta? No,
it's... it's her kids.
She's dead in the bedroom.
Okay, okay. And now her...
Actually, why don't you
stay out here instead, okay?
I'll just go in and
check things out,
see what's what and...
Stay right there. Do not move.
Don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENING, CLOSING)
(RAPID CLICKING IN DISTANCE)
Fuck this.
All right. Stop right
there, ma'am. Stop. Okay?
There's a lot of blood in
there. You're right about that.
But there's no dead boy
and there's no dead
lady in there either.
That's not possible. I...
Listen, I'm gonna need you to
come down with me to... to...
(SQUELCHING)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SCREAMS) (GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
(OBJECTS CRASHING)
(PAINED SCREAMING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(BODY THUDS)
(MUSIC FADES)
(CLICKING NEARBY)
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING) (FOOTSTEPS STOP)
(GRUNTS QUIETLY)
(PANTS)
LUCY: (SINGSONGY)
Margaret. Where are you?
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
(HISSING)
(BREATH TREMBLES)
(HISSING, CLICKING)
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(PANTING SOFTLY)
(VEHICLE THUMPS)
(VEHICLE THUMPING)
(RAPID CLICKING)
(SINGSONGY) Olly olly oxen free.
(HIGH-PITCHED WHISTLING)
(SNARLS)
(LUCY AND SPENCER CHITTERING)
(CHITTERING CONTINUES)
(RINGTONE PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
(HIGH-PITCHED
WHISTLING) (HISSING)
(SNARLING)
(GRUNTS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
MARGARET: Ben?
Ben?
(ENGINE STOPS)
Ben, where are you?
(DOOR CLATTERING) (GASPS)
Margaret.
Oh, my God. (SOBS)
Okay. (PANTING)
Okay, we need to go.
What? We need to go.
I'm so sorry that I
didn't listen to you,
but everything you said was
true so we have to go now.
No, no, no. Why
would we do that?
Because they're
trying to kill us.
No, it's beautiful.
I didn't understand
why the kids were
so drawn to it before,
but now... now I do.
I know why they
followed it down.
Hey, I... I don't know
what you're talking about,
but we need to, we need
to, we need to go now.
The place that shines.
And you can see it, too.
I don't... I don't
want to see it.
I want to... I want
to go, Ben. (GRUNTS)
There's nowhere else to go.
I think we should settle down.
(GASPING) (SNARLING
IN DISTANCE)
We should start a family.
(HISSING AND SNARLING OUTSIDE)
You decided for us before,
but now... I'm weighing in.
Those fucking things are
trying to fucking kill us!
We don't even know
where Thomas is.
Those things, they killed Ellie.
They're young. They'll learn.
And we can be
together. All of us.
That feeling of connection you've
been searching for. (PANTS)
It's being part of
something bigger.
I've found that. I can show you.
I don't know what you
are, but you're not Ben.
(SIGHS)
(NECK CRACKING)
You'll see.
And you'll make more of them.
We'll make more. We'll
make them together.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(BEN GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS) (SCREAMS, SOBS)
(GRUNTING)
(MARGARET SHOUTS) (BEN GRUNTS)
(SOBBING)
(GROANS)
(WHIMPERING)
(PAINED GASP)
(CRYING)
(WHIMPERING)
(PANTS)
(YELLS) (MUSIC FADES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(PAINED COUGHING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(FOOTSTEPS) (BODY DRAGGING)
(RAPID CLICKING)
(MARGARET EXHALES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHIMPERING QUIETLY)
(RAPID CLICKING NEARBY)
(PANTING SOFTLY)
(LUCY AND SPENCER CHITTERING)
(GULPS)
(BODY CONTINUES DRAGGING)
(HISSING)
(CHITTERING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS QUIETLY)
(SHARP HISS)
(HISSING)
(PANTING SOFTLY)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(HISSING)
(SHARP HISSING)
(MARGARET GRUNTS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(RAGGED PANTING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
BEN: Margaret.
No. (PANTS)
No.
(GRUNTS)
Just... just let
me go. Let me go.
(MARGARET GASPS)
(THOMAS GRUNTING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC
PLAYING) (BOTH GRUNTING)
Go!
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
BEN: Margaret!
(MARGARET PANTING)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(MUSIC FADES)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(SOBBING, SCREAMING)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(SNIFFLES, PANTS)
(PANTING SOFTLY)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCOFFS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(SCREAMING)
("INFERNO REBELS" BY
FOTOCRIME PLAYING)
♪ Inferno rebels
All in a trance ♪
♪ Stand guard Over
armies of cats ♪
♪ Eternal children Peek
through the cracks ♪
♪ Old scars Confessional
rats all fade ♪
♪ Fade ♪
♪ Pleather angels
Writhe in a dance ♪
♪ Fed on fungus Were
born and were dead ♪
♪ Crush the bones of the
priests Who were left ♪
♪ Nuclear mystics Ethereal
theft can't escape ♪
♪ Escape ♪
♪ Another tiny apocalypse ♪
(SONG FADES)