(dramatic music)
(radio chattering)
(metal clanging)
(dramatic music)
(yelling)
(whacking)
(dramatic music)
(yelling)
(razor tapping)
(dramatic music)
- 40 dollars, 70 cents.
Coming right up.
(register clattering)
Here, count it, then sign.
- [Radio] Sometime, probably in the last decade,
this guy came in with all the fanfare,
and really has done
nothing for the Wolverines.
(dramatic music)
Relax kid, you'll be all right.
Maybe.
(man chuckles)
(dramatic music)
(door clangs)
(engines rumbling)
(dramatic music)
♪ Flying blind and it feels like falling ♪
♪ We're the cannon balls
that clear the way ♪
♪ I'm in camouflage but I am lucid ♪
♪ With the way that I was yesterday ♪
♪ I have no enemies ♪
♪ All the places where I find you now ♪
♪ Swirl in my head way into the day ♪
(dramatic music)
♪ There are reasons
coming back to save me ♪
♪ There were leaders calling from rain ♪
♪ There were teachers with
their headlines breaking ♪
♪ Saying look again the other way ♪
♪ I have no enemies ♪
♪ Only places where I find you know ♪
♪ Swirl in my head ♪
(man knocks)
♪ Swirl In my head ♪
- Yeah, what do you want?
- Excuse me.
Looking for Tommy Larabito,
he used to live here.
- Who are you?
- I'm his brother.
- You're Tommy's brother?
- Yeah.
- Ain't you supposed to be in jail?
- Got out.
- Legally?
- I believe so.
- Wait here.
(door bangs)
- Jesus fucking Christ.
What the hell are you doing here?
When did you get out?
- This morning, about ten o'clock.
- Why didn't you call me?
I would have picked you up.
- I tried, the phone's been disconnected.
- Didn't I give you the new number
when I wrote you last time?
- Tommy, I'm sure I would
have wrote it down if you did.
- At least you remembered the address.
- Tommy, I lived here for 20 years.
- I can't believe it, you look great.
Got a little bulk, huh?
So what do you think of my wife?
- She's your wife?
The blonde?
- Yeah.
- Shit, you never told me you got married.
- Hey, we all gotta go sometime.
Lorraine, where are ya?
(dramatic music)
(dog barks)
Joey.
Lorraine, this is my kid brother.
- Glad to meet you.
Congratulations on being married.
- What, is there one beer left?
You didn't buy any beer?
- Not enough money for beer.
- Not enough money?
What did you buy?
- Food.
- [Tommy] You bought food instead of beer?
- Yeah.
- Here, kid.
- No Tommy, its your
last one, you have it.
- Come on, when's the
last time you had a beer?
- [Joey] Six years, I guess.
- [Tommy] Six years?
Come on, Take it.
- Tommy, may I speak to you for a minute?
Out here, please.
- I can't believe you're here.
- [Lorraine] What's he doing here?
- [Tommy] What are you talking
about, he's my brother.
- [Lorraine] I know that,
but what is he doing here?
- [Tommy] He's my brother,
what do you want me to do?
- [Lorraine] I think he wants to stay.
You know?
Find out what he wants.
(kids chattering)
(bird tings)
- This place has really changed.
- Yeah, the house ain't
the same since mommy died.
- I'm sorry about that.
They wouldn't let me out for the funeral.
There was this mix up, by the
time it got straightened out...
- Oh, she went quick, you
know, she didn't have any pain.
- You tell her what happened?
- You know, she never really asked.
- Hey, let's go down to Cropsey's
and get some beers, huh?
- [Joey] Cropsey's still open?
- [Tommy] We're going out
hun, we'll be back later.
(door bangs)
So where are you going to stay?
- I wanna talk to you about that.
Think I could stay at the
house for a little while?
At least till I get a
job, settle in somewhere?
- Jesus kid, I don't know about that.
I mean if it was up to me I wouldn't mind,
but you know, Lorraine is
really weird about her privacy.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah sure, I understand.
I'll find a place.
Is my stuff still in my room?
- Yeah, me and mommy put it in boxes.
Now, we didn't know when you got out
whether or not you were
going to come back or not.
- I'll come for it as soon
as I find a place to stay.
- You know what, fuck it.
I'm gonna have Lorraine fix something up
for you in the basement, all right?
I mean, this way you got your privacy,
she's got hers, and you know...
I mean till you find a place.
- Sure I won't cause any problems?
- Don't worry about it.
- You sure about that, Tommy?
- Hey, blood is thicker than water, no?
- I don't know, I haven't
drank any in a while.
- You haven't changed a bit, you fuck.
(upbeat music)
Believe that?
So he's standing there staring at me,
says, "What's your problem?"
Well my problem is you're
a thief and a crook,
and you look like a fucking rat.
(crowd laughs)
So he grabs a pipe from behind the bar,
he's walking towards me,
and I grab a chair, I smash it
over his fucking head.
He falls down cold on the floor, right?
His brother runs into the
phone booth to call the cops.
I go out to the car,
Lorraine's sitting there.
I start the car, ready to go.
She holds it up, she goes, "Oh
God, look, I had it all along."
(crowd laughs)
Can you believe this, I
wanted to strangle her.
Gary, two more over here.
- You're all tapped out, Tommy.
- [Tommy] What?
- Harry says you're at the limit.
- You gotta be kidding,
you're gonna break my balls
with all the money I spend
in this fucking joint?
- Hey look, I'm only doing what Harry
tells me to do, all right Tom?
- I got it Tommy, no problem.
- [Radio] In the neighborhood.
And he's someone I've known
since he was a little boy.
(cupboard creaks)
Well the things is, my husband,
he doesn't really like this kid,
and he's telling my daughter
that she can't see him anymore.
I think its just a harmless
teenage relationship,
but my husband has suddenly
gotten so protective.
I mean like, he's just
watching every move she makes,
and when I try to talk to him about it,
he just says she's too young to be dating,
or he just refuses to
talk about it at all.
It's created like...
- Joey, I'll pay you back
when we get back to the house.
- Don't worry about it.
This is really great, Lorraine.
I haven't had a meal
like this in a long time.
- Thanks.
- She's a good cook, huh?
- So what are your plans
now that you're out?
- Huh?
- Now that you're out?
Where are you staying,
you know, stuff like that.
- He's staying with some friends,
but they're out of town right now
so I said he could stay
in the basement till he finds something.
- Oh.
Where do your friends live?
- [Tommy] In the neighborhood.
- How many days they say they'd be gone?
- A few days, right?
- Can he answer for himself?
- He could if there weren't
so many goddamn questions.
- I'm sorry if I offended
you with my questions, Joey.
It's really none of my business.
- I'm not offended at all.
- Speaking of business,
shouldn't you be getting ready?
- For what?
- Don't you have a job tonight?
- Told you, it was canceled.
- You didn't tell me that.
- I did tell you, this morning
in the hallway, remember?
- No.
- What do you do, Lorraine?
(phone rings)
Yeah?
Look, Camille call back,
I'm waiting for a call.
(phone bangs)
- How did you know I
didn't want to talk to her?
- She'll call back, she always call back.
- He thinks the world's supposed to end
just cause he's expecting
a call, you know?
- Why don't you stop?
You know these calls are business.
- Yeah, monkey business.
- [Tommy] Why are you getting
so bent out of shape for?
- [Lorraine] Because maybe I
wanted to talk to her, ya know?
- Think I'll look for a job tomorrow.
- She'll call back.
- That's not the point.
- Remember we used to work
at the supermarket, Tommy?
- Give me a fucking break here.
- The old AMP on Decker.
I was in charge of the frozen foods.
- Why don't you give me a break?
- He was in charge of the produce.
- What?
What are you, a fucking imbecile?
- [Lorraine] Don't pick on him.
He didn't do nothing, did he?
(phone rings)
- Yeah?
Hey, how's it going?
Yeah.
- You finished with that?
- Yeah, I am.
(phone bangs)
- I'm going out. If anybody
calls, I'll be back.
And don't tie up that phone.
Joey, come on, take a ride with me.
- You sure I can't help
you with the dishes?
- No, I'm fine.
Just take the ride with Tommy.
(engine rumbling)
- [Joey] Where we going?
- I got to see someone.
(dramatic music)
What's wrong?
- Cops was just here.
- What did you expect?
We're in the fucking projects.
(dramatic music)
- What's in the bag, Tommy?
- What?
- I could get sent back
another eight years
for what you got in that bag.
- What are you talking about?
- Come on Tommy, I'm not an imbecile.
- Nobody said you were.
It's weed, all right?
(dramatic music)
There, all right, you happy now?
Make believe like it's not even there.
(dramatic music)
Got you a pillow and some sheets.
It's a little musty, but it's clean.
- Thanks.
- You going to be all right down here?
- Yeah.
- Look kid, I'm sorry I snapped
at you in the car before.
I just wanna say I'm glad you're back.
And I meant what I said before.
- What?
- You are an imbecile.
Goodnight, kid.
- Goodnight, Tommy.
(cricket chirping)
(dramatic music)
(whacking)
(rain spattering)
- You think Mike Tyson's
finished for the evening?
- Will you stop it, he's my brother.
- I know who he is.
(rain spattering)
(thunder crashes)
- [Radio] We've been,
you know really close,
we're really good friends...
He's being a little mysterious lately.
(garbage crinkles)
(bag rustling)
- [Radio] I don't really know where he's going,
and I've never really been
to his apartment or anything.
(phone rings)
- Yeah?
Look, you know not to call
before noon, call back later.
Idiot.
- Sorry Lorraine, I didn't
mean to wake you up.
- Don't apologize, you didn't.
I've been up.
I'm a very light sleeper.
- You got any more trash bags?
There's a lot of stuff I
could throw out back there.
- You don't have to do that, you know.
Actually I think Tommy likes
things cluttered up like that.
- Mind if I sit down?
- No.
- Where is he?
- He doesn't get up before
noon, if he can help it.
- I'm like you, I'm a light sleeper.
In the joint we had to be up by sunrise.
- If you want to wash up,
the bathrooms up on the...
You should know where it is.
- I washed up down here,
I hope that was all right.
- You can wash up wherever you want.
- You don't have to worry, Lorraine.
I'm not going to be here long.
Just had nowhere else to go.
- I didn't say you couldn't stay.
- No, you're absolutely
right, I don't belong here.
My story about friends from out of town...
I ain't got any friends.
They're not out of town.
I'm sorry to lie to you like that.
- You didn't lie to me, your brother did.
- As soon as I can, I'll be moving on.
- [Lorraine] Where you gonna go?
- I don't know.
How long you and Tommy been married?
- Going on four years.
- He never mentioned it.
I guess he was too busy,
didn't have time to write.
- Did you write him?
- No, I didn't.
- Jesus Christ, you two are up early.
Who called before?
- Conrad.
I told him not to call before noon.
- So how'd you sleep your first night out?
- Fine.
It was strange though, without the bars.
- Good morning, beautiful.
- Morning, asshole.
(dramatic music)
- Tommy.
This is the second notice
we got from the bank.
- What?
- Mortgage.
- Let me see.
I sent them a check last week.
- Yeah, I know.
- They must be on glue down
there, I'll call them later.
- Alright.
Oh, some guy Louis
called, he's coming over.
- That's another hundred bucks.
- Word spreads fast around here.
- What?
- Nothing.
He doesn't really seem how you described.
- What do you mean?
- Your brother.
He doesn't really seem capable
of the things you said.
- He doesn't, huh?
- He's got a parole officer, right?
- So?
- What happens if he should come over?
- Why don't you let me worry about that.
- [Boy] Yo Candy, what
do you say we go behind
the quarry and I'll show you my pet snake?
- Yeah, no thanks, I don't like snakes.
- Come on, it doesn't bite.
- Yeah, but I do.
Give it back. What the fuck?
Jesus Christ.
Why don't you all grow up?
- Candy Riedel.
- Who are you?
- Joey Larabito, remember?
I used to hang out with your brother.
- Get out of here. Joey Larabito?
Oh my God.
- [Boy] Yo candy, who's your
boyfriend, Freddy Krueger?
- He looks old enough to be your old man.
Twice as ugly.
- You guys should treat
a girl with respect.
- Why don't you mind your
own business, Freddy?
- Maybe you want to take
a step and say that.
- Joey, it's all right.
They're just little boys.
Come on, come on.
- You going home?
- Yeah.
- I'll walk ya.
- See you tomorrow in school, Candy.
Freddy Krueger.
- [Joey] So who are those guys?
- Just some jerks from school.
The short one, he likes me.
- Likes you?
He's got a funny way of showing it.
- No, he's only like that
when he's with his friends.
He's actually really shy
when he's by himself.
- Still, that's no way to behave.
So how's Carl doing?
- Oh he's fine, yeah.
He lives in California now.
He's married, he's got two
kids, a boy and a girl.
- Get outta here.
- Yeah.
- Never pictured Carl married with kids.
So what happened, did you get left back?
(dramatic music)
This place hasn't changed at all.
- Yeah.
- How's your mother and your father?
- They're doing good, yeah.
I'd ask you to come in, but you know.
- Yeah.
- Tell him I was asking for him, okay?
- Yeah, I will.
Thanks.
Oh, and thanks for walking me home.
- Anytime.
- All right.
Hey, sweetie.
(dramatic music)
Hey, mom.
- [Lorraine] Dinner's ready.
(dramatic music)
- I put in an application
at AMP today, Tommy.
- Again with the AMP.
- Did you know Mr.
Fritz still works there?
He don't remember me, but
he took my application.
(door knocks)
- [Tommy] 70 a quarter.
- [Man] 70? Last time it was 60.
- [Tommy] Well its 70 now, you
want the fucking pot or not?
- [Man] All right, give it to me.
- [Tommy] Hurry up, my
dinner's getting cold.
(door bangs)
- Who was that?
I never saw him before.
- That's Frankie Hamm, he's
friends with Joe Bologna.
- Frankie Hamm and Joe Bologna?
What are they, meat products?
Just be careful who you got coming here.
- Don't worry about it.
- Just be careful, all right?
- You made your point, all right?
- Hey, Tommy.
You got a pail and some
rags I could borrow?
- For what?
- When I was out today, I thought up
a fast way to make some quick cash.
- Oh yeah, doing what?
- Well, the stores on main street,
they got plate windows, right?
And they're dirty, some
are filthy, I checked.
So I figured I could clean windows,
make some quick cash, what do you think?
- I think that's a great idea, no?
- Yeah, yeah.
- I mean you could make 50,
a 100, maybe 200, 300 dollars a day.
- Will you stop it. Maybe he
wants to earn some honest money
for a change. Who are you
to be putting him down?
- Why don't you mind your own business?
He's not talking to you, is he?
- So what do you think I could charge
for that, cleaning windows?
- Jesus, kid.
You know there's a lot of things
to consider here with this.
You got to consider
the size of the window,
the width, how thick it is,
if it's tinted,
if there's lettering on it.
You know, if there's lettering on it,
you got to charge more, no?
(door knocks)
(indistinct muttering)
(door bangs)
- Look, if it's a normal size window,
like the candy store or something,
charge five bucks for the
whole job, inside and out.
But if it's one of those plate
glass windows, like the
laundromat or the supermarket,
charge five bucks for like each side.
- Think that's a fair price?
- Yeah.
I'll get you the bucket and rags.
- [Joey] Great.
- [Radio] Good, its just that
she just wants to move out
and I don't understand why.
- Your hands are really soft, Lorraine.
- Skin cream, thanks.
(glass shatters)
- Sorry.
- It's all right.
Its just a plate.
- Don't move, its everywhere.
(door bangs)
- What the hell's going on here?
- Dropped a dish.
- Why do you have him doing housework?
- He actually offered to help,
and I let him. What's the big deal?
- The big deal is I turn
my back for one minute
and you're feeling up my wife's feet.
- You don't feel up my
feet anymore, do you?
- [Tommy] You touch her toes?
- Might've touched the big one.
- That's it, its over!
Nobody touches my wife's toes!
- Maybe I should leave you two alone.
- Where are you going?
- Hey.
- Come on, we're gonna go out.
- Where you taking him?
- The Garter.
- Oh.
- When's the last time
you saw a naked girl,
and not in a magazine?
- I don't know.
- You're going to see some tonight.
If you're lucky, you might even get laid.
- They got toes down at the Garter?
(Tommy laughs)
- How the hell'd you go six
years without having sex?
Huh?
- I don't know. Try not
to think about it, I guess.
- What was it like in there?
- It was rough.
- Did you get into fights?
- Yeah, some.
I was on the boxing team.
- Boxing team?
- Yeah, we had a boxing team.
We had a team for everything.
Even had a chess team, which somehow
turned into the boxing team.
- Did you get into any
fights outside of the ring?
You know, people trying to fuck with you?
- I had my share.
- Did you get raped?
- Tommy, what kind of
question is that to ask?
- Hey kid, I didn't mean anything
by it. I'm just curious.
- Some things are better not talked about.
- Me and you used to talk
about everything, remember?
- Yeah, I remember.
- [Woman] Hey, baby.
- [Woman] There's more to see.
- Hey, forget about it, all right?
Let's just have a good time tonight.
All right?
♪ I'll meet you in the moonlight ♪
♪ Where the fast tracks dwell ♪
♪ Make sure your fires running hot ♪
♪ While I gaze at your spell ♪
♪ Did I imagine... ♪
- Hey, you.
- [Woman] Hey, baby.
About time I see you.
How you doing?
- What do you think, huh?
♪ And scratch me at will ♪
♪ It was under this moonless sky ♪
♪ When baby burned slow ♪
♪ Was under the spell I'm told ♪
♪ It was under this moonless sky ♪
- Tommy, what's up?
♪ I was under the spell I'm told ♪
♪ How was I to know ♪
(men chuckling)
- You laugh, I'm telling
you he's a tough bastard,
I wouldn't fuck with him.
- What do you think, it makes
you Superman cause you're inside?
- How do you know he didn't get
his ass kicked everyday he was in there?
- I bet he was probably married
to some six foot spade named Tyrone.
(men laughing)
- Bet you're right.
♪ You ripped my heart in two ♪
♪ While I was down on my knees ♪
♪ It was under the moonless
sky when baby burned slow ♪
♪ I was under the spell I'm told ♪
♪ It was under this moonless
sky when baby burned slow ♪
♪ I was under the spell I'm told ♪
♪ How was I to know ♪
- So to what do I owe this special honor?
Where have you been for
the past six months?
- You know where I've been.
- Then why are you here now?
- Well, what are you saying?
- I don't know, I think Tommy
might get fucking pissed.
- Why?
If he's right, there's no harm done.
♪ Moonless sky, baby burned slow ♪
- [Man] I'll set it
up, you tell everybody.
- Come on, Ronnie, huh?
Give the guy a break, he's
been away for six years.
- No, you give me a break.
- Come on baby, do this for me?
I mean it's not like he's a
stranger, he's my brother.
- What do you think I am?
- I think you're the most
beautiful creature in the world.
- You could charm a snake
out of a tree, you know that?
Okay.
But I have my price.
- Ronnie, what are you doing?
What are you... What are you doing?
- I know what I'm doing.
- Ronnie, Ronnie.
Ronnie.
(belt buckle jingles)
Jesus Christ.
♪ I want you to move,
I want you to groove ♪
♪ I'm growing a need ♪
♪ And I don't care ♪
(boxes thudding)
(dramatic music)
(door bangs)
(Tommy thuds)
(dramatic music)
- Tommy?
- Look at this, he's
calling for his mommy.
(men laughing)
(dramatic music)
- I don't want no trouble.
- Yeah, well that's what
you're getting, motherfucker.
(dramatic music)
(Joey thuds)
(men laughing)
- You fat fuck.
Where you going?
(dramatic music)
(men yelling)
(Ronnie moaning)
(whacking)
- So what's your brothers name?
- [Man] That was unbelievable.
(men yelling)
- [Woman] Hey Tommy, your
brother did all right.
- [Man] Hey, Tommy.
- You all right?
What happened?
- Take me home Tommy, I'm gonna be sick.
- Did you do this?
- [Joey] Yeah, he wouldn't leave me alone.
(man laughing)
- You think its funny?
I should kick your fucking ass.
- What are you, fucking nuts?
You're the one who said he was so tough.
- Not bad for a retard.
(whacks)
Fuck.
- Give me that.
You all right?
- Yeah.
- Where the hell did you
learn how to fight like that?
That was one big motherfucker
you just fucked up.
- Where the fuck were you, Tommy?
- Shit.
- What the hell happened?
- He had an accident.
- What do you mean an accident?
Tommy.
- [Tommy] Sit down.
- What happened to him?
- Some asshole started some shit.
- [Lorraine] And where were
you when this happened?
- [Tommy] What?
- [Lorraine] Where were
you when this happened?
- [Tommy] I was in the bathroom
taking a piss, all right?
- All this took place when
you were in the bathroom?
- [Tommy] Yeah.
- Why didn't you just leave?
- Lorraine, the guy was
an asshole, all right?
We had no choice, we had to fight.
- What do you mean we?
I thought you were taking a piss,
I don't see a scratch on you.
- Were you there?
Were you there?
- No.
I was just trying to find out, all right?
- Just fix his face.
- You all right, you wanna go
to the hospital or something?
- He's fine.
- You shouldn't have taken
him there in the first place.
It's sleazy and dangerous.
(dishes clatters)
- So are you.
- He didn't mean that.
- Don't stick up for him.
- Sorry Lorraine, I hate to bring
this kind of trouble into your house.
- You're the one that
had your face punched in.
I don't understand you.
You're an enigma.
- What?
- Enigma, puzzle.
- Why?
- It doesn't add up.
I mean you're supposed to come out
worse than you went in, right?
But in your case you...
I don't know, whatever.
- It's not so hard to figure.
I don't want to go back there.
Even if I gotta clean toilets
at the depot, I'm not going back.
I'd rather die than go back there.
- I got that pail and rags
for you, they're on the porch.
- Thanks.
I should get started
while it's still early.
What was that word you said before?
- Oh, enigma.
- Yeah.
It's a good one, I got to remember that.
(dramatic music)
- [Woman] Joey?
- Denise.
- When did you get home?
- A few days.
How you doing?
- Fine, I guess.
How about you?
- Fine too.
I'm staying with Tommy.
You know he's married now?
- Yeah, I see his wife
sometimes, she's very pretty.
Guess you didn't hear, I'm married now too.
- Really?
That's great.
I'm happy for you.
Any kids?
- Two boys, two and four years old.
Actually the four year old
is my husband's from a previous marriage.
- Who'd you marry?
- It's nobody you would know.
He's older than us, friend of the family.
- Well, that's great.
- I gotta go, cause I gotta pick
up my kids from my mother's.
- Sure.
- It's good to see you.
I'm glad you're home.
- Thanks.
It's good to see you too.
So where you living now?
- We're... I'm over on Porter.
You remember the Beeler house?
- Dead man Beeler's
house, the haunted house?
- Yeah, that's the one.
- You're living there?
- It's all fixed up now.
- Remember when we was kids,
we was always seeing
ghosts and monsters inside.
- Yeah, well you know,
when you're a kid,
you think a lot of things are true.
You almost convince yourself of them.
You grow up, you see things in
a completely different light.
- Yeah, it's like an enigma.
- Well, anyway, that's
where I'm living now so...
I gotta go.
Take care, Joey.
- You too, Denise.
(dramatic music)
Enigma, shit.
- [Man] Hey Burke, where's Scalero?
- [Burke] Out by the trailer.
(dramatic music)
- [Man] You want the part?
What the fuck am I running here?
- [Man] Seem on edge today.
- Hey Bobby, don't be a comedian.
- Thanks, Ralph.
- Oh Christ, you show up two days early,
it can only mean bad things.
- Why do you say that?
- Why?
Because I know you.
You got something for me?
It's a little light here, Tommy.
It feels about 200 light.
- Look, I wanted to talk to you about that.
The last few weeks have
been really rough for me.
- Now look, I've been giving
you a break as it is, huh?
And what about the pound of
weed you got from my nephew?
How are you going to pay for that?
- I didn't pay for that
shit, he fronted me.
- What are you going to do
when Jackie wants his money?
He ain't as nice as me.
- Look, what am I going to do, run away?
You know I'm good for it.
I'm being straight with you, Ralph.
- I know that.
I appreciate it.
That better not be long distance.
Remember what I told you about that?
- Hey, I gotta go.
- Fucking guy, he calls
his mother everyday,
upstate, on my phone.
Like I'm responsible for
his personal fucking life.
- It was a local call, honest Ralphie.
- Yeah?
We'll see when we get the bill.
You guys have been here all day, can't ya...
(metal clanging)
Fucking tidy up, or something?
I mean what the fuck, this place
looks like a fucking pig sty.
Too fucking proud to pick
up a fucking broom, huh?
Not now, ya fuck.
I mean when you're just hanging out
in here with nothing to do.
Tommy, look, I appreciate
what you're saying here,
but we gotta do something
about settling this account.
You got to start paying a principal.
I can't carry the weight anymore.
My fucking back is breaking.
- I told you, you know I'm good for it.
- I don't know nothing, Tommy.
All I know is you're two bills short.
I hear your brother's out of jail.
- Yeah.
- I hear he kicked the shit out
of Gas Tank the other night.
You're just causing problems
all over the neighborhood, ain't you?
- His brother beat the
shit out of Gas Tank?
I thought he was a retard.
(man chuckles)
- He's not retarded, asshole.
- I saw your wife at a
party the other night.
Sucking cock, ten bucks a head.
Was pretty good too.
(man laughs)
- Oh yeah, I saw your mother
at the racetrack sucking a horses dick.
- All right, all right, you
two, that's enough, okay?
What am I running here,
a fucking day camp?
Look Tommy, this has gone on
as far as it can, all right?
I can't do you any more favors.
People think I'm a fucking charity.
It's not the money, you know that.
It's about respect.
Responsibility.
- Yeah, I know.
- No, I don't think you do.
That's the fucking problem.
I want a thousand on Monday.
- I'll give you something on Friday.
(dramatic music)
(Tommy thuds)
- I want all of the money on Friday.
You got that?
I thought I told you
guys to clean up in here.
(Tommy thuds)
- Oh, I know.
Shouldn't be up here.
- That's okay.
What you looking at?
- Some old pictures.
Saw an old friend
yesterday, got me thinking.
- Is that her?
- Yeah, her name's Denise.
- [Lorraine] Close friend?
- You could say that.
We was gonna be married, me and her.
Long time ago.
- Oh.
- [Joey] Yeah, she's
married and got a kid.
- I'm sorry.
- Its funny, you think
something's over, you know,
after a certain amount of time passes.
And then you see them, it's like
a rubber band snaps you back.
And you realize, maybe
it's not over after all,
at least not for you.
That ever happen to you?
- No, not really.
- Thing of it is, I think
we could have had a good life together.
I mean, I really loved her.
(dramatic music)
- What's this?
Who drew these?
- [Joey] Used to be
able to draw real good.
- You drew these?
- Hard to believe, right?
- I didn't mean it to sound like that.
- No, you're right, I find
it pretty amazing myself.
- If you drew these, it's not like
you're going to forget how to draw.
- Haven't you noticed, I'm
a little slow upstairs.
It wasn't always like this.
I was pretty smart as a kid.
That all changed after the accident.
- What accident?
- Tommy never told you?
- No.
- I was a kid.
We was playing out in the backyard.
I fell.
Cracked my head on cement
stairs by the kitchen.
I was in the hospital for a long time.
They didn't think I was going to live.
Anyway, I did.
But ever since I've been
like this, you know.
Slow.
- I don't think you're slow at all.
- Well anyway, I can't draw anymore.
- Yeah.
Well, when was the last time you tried?
Oh, I was going to say,
maybe you should sleep in here
from now on. You know, it
was your room to begin with,
and your stuff's here.
It'd just be easier.
I'll get you some clean sheets.
(dramatic music)
Tommy?
Who are these people you owe money to?
Honey, who are these
people you owe money to?
- Scalero.
- Ralphie Scalero.
You promised me, you swore to me
you were finished with that.
- Lorraine please, please.
- So you haven't been paying
the mortgage, have you?
And all the money I've been making?
- It's the only way I
can get them off my ass.
- Oh fuck, Tommy.
It's like a bad fucking dream.
What are we gonna do?
We can't get another loan on the house.
There's nothing left to sell.
- I did this for us.
- You didn't do this for us.
You don't give a fuck about us.
You did this for you.
I want this garbage out of my life.
I'm sick of this shit.
(dramatic music)
What are they going to
do when you can't pay?
- What do you think they're gonna do?
- [Man] And you're living there
with your brother and his wife?
- Yeah.
- Okay, 'cause I'm going
to have to come by soon,
and it's my duty to inform you
that I could come by at any time.
I don't need a warrant.
I don't need a reason.
And I work around the clock, okay?
- Okay.
- How are you doing with work?
No steady employment yet?
- I put in an application at the
AMP and three other places.
- All right.
Try and get something soon,
'cause this cleaning windows stuff...
Well, it's nothing to put in your file.
- [Joey] Okay.
- You're not taking any drugs are you?
- No.
- Not hanging out with
any of the old crowd?
- No, it's pretty much me by myself.
- Good.
'Cause if you hang out
with the wrong people,
you'll wind up right
back where you came from.
You know that, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
You're off to a good start.
But if you still haven't found
work by next week, let me know,
and I'll see if there's something
I can point you towards.
- Okay.
- That's it.
- I'm outta here?
- Yep.
Pretty painless, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'll see you next week.
- Aren't people going to smell that?
- They won't know the fucking difference.
- [Lorraine] You still won't
have the money by tomorrow.
- Are you working tonight?
- They haven't called back yet.
- You know if you did, it would help.
- Then what? What about next week?
What happens then?
What about the guy you got this from?
He's going to want his money
eventually, don't you think?
- Enough of the questions, all right?
- One more question.
Your brother, he's on parole, right?
They're going to send him right back.
- What do you want me to do,
kick him out of the house?
(phone rings)
Answer that, it might be the agency.
(phone ringing)
(oregano thuds)
(dramatic music)
(Joey knocks)
- Joey, what are you doing here?
- Just dropped by to say hello.
- You shouldn't have done that.
What if my husband was home?
- What, you can't see an old friend?
- He doesn't know
anything about you, or us.
- I wanna talk to ya.
- I can't.
I got my kids inside, I gotta fix dinner.
- Just five minutes.
Five minutes, I'm out of here.
Hey.
- Come on.
Come on, hun.
- The place has been fixed up nice
since the last time I saw it.
No ghosts, either.
- So?
You said you wanted to talk.
- When's your husband coming home?
- He works late on Thursdays.
- Oh, what's he do?
- He's a bookkeeper at McReynolds.
- The department store?
- Yeah.
- That's great.
- Yeah, it's okay.
So?
- Well, it was really good
to see you the other day, Denise.
And... Look, you're right,
this was a terrible idea. I better go.
- Well, you must've had something
on your mind, or you wouldn't have come.
What is it, Joey?
- You really want to know?
- I'm waiting.
- It's just that I felt I deserved
a little better than what I got from you.
I felt I deserved something more.
A goodbye, an apology, an excuse.
Anything other than what I got.
- You do? That's pretty funny.
- [Joey] Why is that so funny?
- Because I feel like
I deserved better too.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about Joey Larabito,
the neighborhood patsy.
Everybody's door mat.
- I was nobody's door mat, except yours.
- You were the biggest joke around.
- How could you say
that? You of all people.
- Because it's true, everybody knows it.
Just pat you on the back
and throw you to the wolves.
You went with a smile on your face.
- Well, Denise what's true
is that once I was inside,
once you didn't have to be there anymore,
you left me to rot like
a piece of garbage.
All that shit you said
to me, how you love me,
how you would wait for me.
How could you lie to me like that?
- I never lied to you.
- What do you call saying those things?
Why did you make all those promises?
- I promised you nothing.
- You promised me everything!
(baby cries out)
- Don't yell at me, and
don't upset my kids.
You can get the fuck out, right now.
Its okay, mommy's right here.
Don't cry, everything's fine.
Watch your brother.
- I'm sorry I yelled at you.
But Denise, if you wanted to fall in love
and get married, fine.
I know you deserve those things.
But why did you say that you love me?
- I did love you.
I would have waited forever for you.
But the more I thought about it,
day after day, the more mad I got.
I was young, and I wanted
a life together sure,
but I wasn't prepared to
throw 10 years of it away
because of your brother.
- Tommy has nothing to do with this.
- God, you can't tell me
the truth even now, can ya?
You know you are so fucking dense, Joey.
- Denise.
- Stop it.
It wasn't you.
I know it wasn't you.
You never hurt nobody in your life.
You wouldn't harm a fly.
Let me ask you a question.
Did he ever once even say thank you?
- Denise, you're wrong.
- I have never been more right in my life.
He took six years of your life,
and you know what, I don't even blame him.
I blame you.
'Cause if you had really loved me,
you wouldn't have given him those years.
- You don't understand, he's my brother.
- No, you don't understand, Joey.
That's the problem.
- You love this guy you're married to?
- What does that have to do with anything?
- Because I want to know.
Denise, I loved you more than I ever loved
anything in my life.
- No Joey, you never loved me.
I gotta fix dinner.
Well, I guess there was some
ghosts in here after all.
- No, no.
[Tommy] No, that's not what I'm saying.
I know, but that's not what I saying.
You said I had till Friday,
I don't know what the problem is.
I'm doing the best I can here.
I mean you're... Hello?
(phone clicks)
Joey.
What are you doing?
- Just fooling around.
- Let me see.
That's not bad, kid. You still got it, huh?
Look, I want you to do me
a favor tonight, all right?
I want you to drive Lorraine to a job
and wait there till she's finished, okay?
- Yeah, no problem.
- She's got to be there by nine.
- Hey Tommy, what does she do?
So he wasn't kidding, was he?
- Who?
- Tommy said you strip.
It's what you really do.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ Which nobody can deny ♪
- [Woman] Happy birthday.
(dramatic music)
(audience cheering)
(bullets clinking)
(dramatic music)
(audience applauding)
- Here's a little something extra for you.
You really made his night, thank you.
- I'm glad.
- I just hope he's not
going to be spoiled now.
- It was fun. Thank you.
- Drive safely going home, okay?
(door knocking)
- What do you want?
- Who the fuck do you think
you, you fucking bastard?
- Whoa, whoa, what's your problem?
- What's my problem?
- Come on in, we'll talk about it.
- Do I look like a
fucking pizza guy to you?
- Who's this?
- Don't worry about who that is, man.
Do I look like a pizza man to you?
- What's your problem?
- You wanna know what my problem is?
This is my problem, man.
(car doors banging)
- What are you going to do with that?
- If I don't get my shit, you'll find out.
- What you take from me,
you take from Scalero, remember that.
- [Man] I'm afraid he's right.
- Jack.
Look, I don't want no trouble, all right?
But this fucking guy ripped me off.
- [Jack] What'd you cop from him?
- [Man] A quarter ounce
of oregano man, smell it.
(Jack inhales)
- You know, you're a real asshole, Tommy.
- Does Scalero know you're
working with this little prick?
- I thought Jack oughta
know what's going down with you.
(whacks)
(Tommy thuds)
- Here, this settle things for you?
- Yeah, I just want what I paid for.
- Good, we're settled then.
Next time you cop from
Peter Louise, understand?
- Got it.
- [Jack] Now get outta here.
- Thanks, Jack.
- Where are you going with that?
This is mine. Get outta here, you too, go.
(whacks)
(Tommy thuds)
Now where's my money, fucker?
How the fuck you paying my uncle,
when I ain't seen jack shit?
Huh?
What's with the oregano?
What are you, fucking stupid, Tommy?
Huh?
I want my money now, Tommy.
- I ain't got it.
- Where's the rest?
- Come back later, I'll
give you something.
- Come back later. Hey
fuck you, come back later.
- My wife's got it, all right?
- Your wife, what is she, the
fucking bank of New England?
Tommy.
- Hey, fuck you, all right.
- Fuck me?
- [Man] Gonna let him
talk to you like that?
- Gut him.
(Tommy thuds)
- Check the house, whatever
you can find upstairs.
- This little piggy went to market,
this little piggy stayed home,
this little piggy got roast beef,
this little piggy, fuck this little piggy.
(finger cracks)
- Do you mind if we just
drove around for a bit?
I don't feel like going home just yet.
- Okay, where do you want to go?
- I don't know, nowhere.
Just drive.
- Wake up, fuck face. Come on, get up.
Have a little breakfast.
- What do we got?
- This is all there is.
Some of it's good, most of it's shit.
- Throw it in the garbage. This
fuck never learns, you know?
- Look, if his wife really has the money
we should stick around for her.
- Maybe we should stick
around and stick his wife.
- Now you're talking.
- She got a tight little ass, eh Tommy?
So how do these look, huh?
- [Jack] They look good.
(drawer bangs)
- Yo, fuck, get down.
- Tommy, put it down, Tommy.
- On the floor!
Get down!
- Fuck you.
- Fuck me?
Fuck.
(man cries out)
Don't you two move!
Go, get up.
Get up, motherfucker, get up!
Let's show your friends
how you suck a cock.
- I was just doing what they tell me.
- [Tommy] Put it in your mouth!
- Son of a bitch.
- You better fucking
kill him, motherfucker,
cause your life ain't worth
jack shit if you don't.
- I'll show you what my life is worth.
(glass shatters)
You, get down on the floor.
Get down!
- Okay, okay!
(whacks)
- [Jack] Calm down, Tommy.
- Your pockets.
- Let's talk about this, Tommy.
(gun clicks)
- I'll blow your fucking head off.
- Cool it man, he's fucking crazy.
- All right Tommy, take it easy, all right?
It's all right, Tommy.
You know my uncle ain't gonna
be too happy about this, Tommy.
Yeah, this is everything, all right.
Here, can I go?
Come on, Tommy.
Can I go, Tommy? Please?
- Get the fuck out of here,
and take that piece of shit with you.
(dramatic music)
- Come on.
- It's you and Tommy, huh?
- It's everything.
- Hope you guys can work it out.
It's important to stay together.
- It is obvious you've never been married.
- I'm sure it's not easy,
but it's gotta have its good points too.
- Yeah?
Name one.
- To have somebody in your
life, that's a good thing.
To find somebody you
love who loves you back.
That doesn't happen too often.
- Happens everyday, people fall in
and out of love all the time.
I'm sorry.
Don't listen to me, I
don't know what I'm saying.
- Are you going to stay with him?
- I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Tommy's my second husband so...
I was one of those 18, straight
out of high schoolers, you know.
Wasn't even pregnant, either,
I wanted to get married.
He did too, so...
We thought we were in love,
and all the bullshit that goes with it.
- [Joey] So you kind of know
what you're talking about, huh?
- Not really, no.
- What happened with your first husband?
- He was an animal.
Didn't hate myself enough
to be with an animal.
Tommy never laid a hand on me.
It's funny.
All the shit we've been through,
never came down to that.
- Tommy was always a lover, not a fighter.
- What about you?
- Me, I'm neither.
- Maybe you're a little bit of both.
(door knocks)
(suspenseful music)
(door knocking)
- Come on, I know somebody's in there.
Open the door.
(suspenseful music)
(door knocks)
(whacks)
(dramatic music)
- Shit.
Christ.
(dramatic music)
- [Lorraine] When you killed that guy,
was it really an accident?
- Didn't Tommy tell you about that?
- Yeah, but he didn't tell me much,
I mean, he said he only
knew what you told him.
- Yeah?
What was that?
- That you broke into the TV store,
and you were cornered, and killed
the owner trying to escape.
- That's what he said?
- Basically, yeah.
- Then that's what happened.
- [Lorraine] Why'd you
break in in the first place?
- [Joey] Seemed like a
good idea at the time.
It was too easy to pass up.
So I snuck in, see what I could find.
(dramatic music)
- [Lorraine] Why didn't you
just punch him and get away?
- [Joey] It was either him or me.
I wasn't thinking at the time.
(dramatic music)
(metal clatters)
Broke my mother's heart.
I don't think she ever forgave me.
- Your mother never spoke bad of you.
- Yeah?
What did she say?
- She loved you, of course.
She never let any of us even touch
your room while you were away.
I guess she just thought
of it as a mistake.
We all make mistakes.
- Well, I think I'm going to
try and go back to school.
Learn a trade or something.
Can't wash windows for a living.
- I think you should.
- You think so, huh?
- Yeah.
- Maybe we should head back.
- Right.
- No, I know she's on a job,
I need the phone number where she's at!
I need the number where she's at!
(phone bangs)
- Why are the lights out?
Tommy?
Oh my God, you're
bleeding. What did you do?
- We're getting out of here tonight,
I packed some of your stuff.
You got gas in the car?
- What the fuck is going on?
- Those motherfuckers came here tonight
looking for their money.
- [Lorraine] I'm calling the police.
- To hell with the police,
we gotta go now.
You coming or you staying?
- I'm coming with you.
I'll get some clothes.
- No, no, you got no time for that.
We gotta go.
- I got a bag down here then.
- Wait a minute, we got no time.
(dramatic music)
- Aw, Christ.
Tommy, what the fuck did you do?
- What is down there?
Tommy?
Who is down there?
- [Joey] Great, he's dead, Tommy.
- I thought it was one of them,
he came right in the house.
- Who is down there?
- It's my fucking parole officer.
Can't take the blame for this one, Tommy.
I'm just not doing it again.
Can't fucking believe you did this to me.
- Fuck this, let's get out of here.
- I'm not going with you.
- [Tommy] What'd you say?
- I am not going with you.
I didn't do anything, why should I run?
- [Tommy] Because they're going
to come back here and kill me.
- That's why you should
go. Why should I go?
- Oh, this is bullshit.
Give me those car keys.
- [Lorraine] I am not going.
- You're coming with me.
- Tommy, I'm sorry.
I've had enough.
- [Tommy] You're going,
you're coming with me.
- I am not going.
- [Tommy] You're going.
- [Lorraine] No.
- [Tommy] I said let's go.
- She's not going with you, Tommy.
- Mind your own business, and
give me those fucking keys.
(keys jingling)
- Now let's go.
- You go ahead, Tommy.
Won't call the cops for a half hour.
- What?
- Just leave while you can.
- Shut up, this is between me and my wife.
- Yeah, and she's telling you no.
- This is because of you, isn't it?
- Just stop it.
- Why is it that everything
you touch turns to poison?
- Fuck you, Tommy.
You didn't even tell her you
was in the store that night.
I wouldn't have been there
if it wasn't for you.
I'm through paying your debts.
- Paying my debts?
I got a fucking lifetime
of debt because of you.
I was the bib every time
you spit up your food.
I got into a fight every time
some kid in the neighborhood
called you a retard.
- What are you talking about?
The accident?
- The accident, no.
Wasn't it called the incident?
- I never called it that.
Is that what this is?
You're digging up shit from 20 years ago?
You are a sick man, Tommy.
You need help.
- No, you're the one that needs help.
- Gonna help me with that gun on me?
(dramatic music)
- You better get to the hospital.
- Are you coming or not?
- Fucker!
(Tommy thuds)
- Going somewhere, motherfucker?
(whacking)
- Tell me I suck cock,
I got your fucking cock
right here, you motherfucker.
(whacks)
(gun fires)
(dramatic music)
(groaning)
(whacking)
(crying out)
Motherfucker!
- [Lorraine] Joey.
(whacking)
(crying out)
(windows shatters)
(gun fires)
(dramatic music)
(dog barking)
- Tommy?
We gotta get out of here.
- We didn't do anything, Joey.
- [Joey] I'm on parole.
- I'll tell them what happened.
- [Joey] They ain't gonna believe it.
- I'll make them.
- [Joey] We can't take that chance.
Get up. You dead?
(dramatic music)
Tommy?
(engine rumbling)
(phone clicking)
(dramatic music)
- Get me the police.
Someone's been shot.
- What are you doing?
What, are you calling the cops?
- I shot someone, Tommy.
- What?
- I shot somebody.
Tommy, you're hurt.
Let me call the hospital.
- You're calling the hospital?
(phone bangs)
Where's my brother?
- I don't know.
- Where did he go?
- I don't know, Tommy. He took the car,
I don't know where he went.
- He took the car, where did he go?
(dramatic music)
What are you two up to?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- You're gonna blame me for this?
You're gonna tell the
police that I did it?
When they get here, you're gonna
tell them that Joey did it.
You understand me?
He did it.
He killed Scalero, he
killed his parole officer.
- Tommy.
- Do you understand me?
Do you understand me?
- [Lorraine] He did it. He did it.
- [Tommy] He did it. Joey did it.
Joey did it all.
- I did an awful lot of
things, didn't I, Tommy?
- I thought you left.
- You'd like that, huh?
Think I'll stick around.
- Well that's good, because the police
are going to be here any minute.
- Yeah, that's what I'm counting on.
- How are you going to explain
your fingerprints on the gun?
- With the truth.
- With the truth, huh?
- Yeah.
(sirens blaring)
Here, Tommy.
I'll turn around.
Get your favorite angle.
(sirens blaring)
- [Man] Everybody get into position.
This is a dangerous situation,
everybody clear off the
streets and go home.
- [Man] You two move, get
the hell out of here, now.
- What's up, Danny?
- We got a possible hostage situation.
We got one Caucasian male,
possibly armed and dangerous.
This is the police, throw your weapons out
and come out with your
hands over your head!
- Don't shoot, I'm coming out!
- Keep your hands over your
head and in plain sight.
- All right, just don't shoot.
- Keep your hands above your head.
Stop right there, don't move.
In the house, throw out your weapons,
come out with your hands up.
- [Tommy] Get away from there.
- [Danny] The house is
surrounded, you cannot get away.
Give yourselves up.
- How could you do this to him, Tommy?
- [Danny] The house is
surrounded, you cannot escape.
- [Lorraine] He's your brother.
- [Danny] Throw your
weapons out and come out.
- [Tommy] Wait here.
- Nobody wants to hurt anybody here.
You on the porch, raise your
hands above your head now!
- Tommy, do it.
- Don't hurt him, he didn't do nothing.
You hear me, he didn't do nothing!
- Raise your hands now!
- I'm the one you want.
- Tommy, don't!
- Drop the gun.
(gun fires)
(guns firing)
(dramatic music)
- Down, down, down. Down on the ground.
On the ground, on the ground.
Arms out. Get 'em around, get 'em around.
Come on, come on. Relax now, relax.
- [Medic] You're gonna be just fine.
Easy now.
All right, watch the curb.
- Where they taking her?
- Relax, they're taking
her to the hospital.
She's not hurt too bad.
- What about me?
- You, we're not sure about that.
We're gonna straighten
that out at the station.
(chattering)
- I don't care where the hell you're from.
(sirens blaring)
(dramatic music)
- [Radio] Okay, let's
go with our next caller,
I believe it is Janet Forstily.
Hi Janet, you're on the air.
- [Janet] Hi, hi, this is Janet.
- [Radio] Yes Janet, you're on, welcome.
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music)
♪ Behind the doors in
the secret passages ♪
♪ Are the haunted hearts in all of us ♪
♪ Where we search to find the windows ♪
♪ Of our soul ♪
♪ Chase the beast away, undo the past ♪
♪ You take away the phantoms mask ♪
♪ When there's no disguise
I'm not afraid to be alone ♪
♪ There's still a sky up
there that turns blue ♪
- Don't stare.
♪ There's still an innocence in me too ♪
♪ There'll be a brand new day ♪
♪ On the other side of
where I'm going to ♪
♪ I will hear the same wind blow ♪
♪ There'll be a piece of me I let go ♪
♪ As I close those doors, I
say a prayer for the ghost ♪
♪ In the heart ♪
♪ When the truth is in somebody's eyes ♪
♪ There is nothing you have to justify ♪
♪ It's where you find the open window ♪
♪ Of their soul ♪
♪ Keeps that sky up there so blue ♪
♪ Keeps that innocence in me too ♪
♪ Makes for a brand new day ♪
♪ On the other side of
where we're going to ♪
♪ I will hear the same wind blow ♪
♪ There'll be a piece of me I let go ♪
♪ As I close those doors ♪
♪ I say a prayer for the ghost ♪
♪ In my heart ♪
(dramatic music)
♪ When the truth is in somebody's eyes ♪
♪ There is nothing you have to justify ♪
♪ It's where you find the
open window of their soul ♪
♪ Keeps that sky up there so blue ♪
♪ Keeps that innocence in me too ♪
♪ Makes for a brand new
day on the other side ♪
♪ Of where we're going to ♪
♪ I will hear the same wind blow ♪
♪ There'll be a piece of me I let go ♪
♪ As I close those doors I'll
say a prayer for the ghost ♪
♪ I will hear the same wind blow ♪
♪ There'll be a piece of me I let go ♪
♪ As I close these doors ♪
♪ I'll say a prayer for the ghost ♪
♪ Behind the doors in
the secret passages ♪
♪ Are the haunted hearts in all of us ♪
♪ Still we search to find
the windows of our soul ♪
(dramatic music)