(dramatic music)
(thundering)
- [Skeeter] There's this game
called Virtual Combat right?
It's really cool.
- [Josh] Really?
- Yeah, it's rad.
So what games have you seen?
- Oh I saw this game
called Mortal Ninjas
or something like that.
- Oh really was that cool?
- Yeah, the guys like
jump around chopping
each other with big old swords--
- Hey there's Debbie Morrow.
- [Debbie] Hi Josh.
- Hi Debbie.
- Hi.
- How are you coming with
your science assignment?
If you want I can help
you with your homework.
- Come on Josh.
- [Debbie] Well maybe.
- You know science
runs in our family.
My dad works at
the government lab.
- Hey, how's it going
today boys, huh?
Mmm, who is this
your girlfriend huh?
This your girlfriend!
Your girlfriend!
- I don't have a girlfriend.
- Yeah, never had
one, never will huh.
So what's your old
man been up to?
Build any monsters lately
in the basement huh?
(groaning)
He's gonna build a big ship
that's gonna go to Mars,
well that's where
he belongs huh.
- [Josh] Ow!
- Leave him alone Charlie.
- Huh, what was that?
Huy, what you say?
Say it again.
- Get lost!
- Hey go back to
Arkansas, lizard boy!
Hey forget these guys
come with me Debbie,
I'll buy you a milkshake.
- Bye Debbie.
- [Skeeter] You
in trouble again?
- [Josh] Kinda, I
didn't clean my room
and I didn't make my bed.
- So what's your
dad working on now?
A death ray.
- Yeah, I wish I could
use it on Johnny Thomas.
- You wanna come over
and play Virtual Combat?
It's 32-bit.
- No, I don't think
my mom will let me.
One more mistake
and I'm grounded.
- Okay, but if you want to
come over, give me a call.
- Okay.
See you later.
Mom, I'm home!
- What are you doing?
- Getting a cookie.
- One!
What happened to your face?
- Nothing.
(telephone ringing)
- [Mom] Hello.
(dog barking)
- Hey, come here.
Hey, hey Cosmo,
how was your day?
Yeah, you got it made.
No mom to boss you around,
no school, no homework.
No Johnny Thomas.
- Josh your backpack's
on the counter.
- See what I mean.
- Cosmo, get down! Get down!
(dog whining)
Why don't you tell me
what happened today?
Okay, but you can't let those
guys push you around Josh.
You gotta stand up to 'em.
- But he's bigger than I am.
- Yeah, well,
bullies usually are.
They want a fair fight
so they pick on kids
they can win against.
But you can't let 'em win.
- But what if I get hurt?
- Well this hurts doesn't it?
Sweetie, if you don't
stand up for yourself,
you're gonna hurt more
inside than you do outside.
Look, if you're wrong admit it.
Everybody's wrong sometimes
and that's when you back down.
But if you're right, got to
stand up for yourself okay?
Feel better?
(doorbell rings)
- Somebody at the door Mom.
- Young man, is
your mother at home?
- Well--
- Thank you!
Oh, there you are.
- Mrs. Pringle, what
can I do for you today?
- It's about that
thing in your backyard.
- What were you doing
in our backyard?
- Oh, I was on a ladder
cleaning out the rain gutters,
I couldn't help but see.
- (laughing) Of course not.
Well I'm really sorry that
that device offends you.
Next time why don't
you have your husband
clean out the rain gutters.
- I will take this up with
the Homeowners Association.
Hmmmph!
- Hmmmph.
- What a fruitcake.
- Josh, remember to
respect your elders,
even if they are
fruitcakes (laughs).
(light music)
- Earth to Griffin.
Just what are we wasting
our time on today Griffin?
- Well, I uh.
I have this formula that
perfectly replicates
the cellular code
of any solid matter
with a negative polarity.
Um, well, here, watch.
Now the fluid will
act as a magnet.
Right.
There we go.
See.
- Interesting Griffin.
- Very interesting Dr. Woorter.
- Thank you sir.
And I'm sure you can see
the military applications
of my inventions.
(clearing throat)
- Yes, Professor Griffin?
- Did you have
something to add Karl?
- No, um, no, just something
stuck in my throat.
- Well, Doctor, this has been
a very valuable presentation.
- Thank you Colonel Cutter.
- Jerry, call me Jerry.
- Jerry.
- [Mom] Then what happened?
- Then he called him Jerry,
like they were all
friends or something.
- When the colonel was gone
did you give him a wedgie?
- [Mom] Joshua.
- It's your invention you
ought to fight and get it back.
- Josh, adults don't fight.
Fighting only creates chaos.
- Josh has a point honey.
I mean you can't just let Dr.
Woorter walk all over you.
You've got to stand
up for yourself.
- What and lose my job!
Honey, honey you
just don't understand
office politics do you?
What I invent at the lab
is the lab's property.
They own it, they
make the profits.
- Well then invent
something at home.
I mean you have your own lab
down in the basement, use it.
- Well I still think you
should have given him a wedgie.
- Cosmo, you eat your own food
and we'll eat our own food okay?
- Hmmph, I can't believe
the neighborhood association
allows people like that
to live around here.
- [Mr. Pringle] Mmm hmmm.
- No telling what that crackpot
is doing in his basement.
Maybe making a bomb.
- Mmmm hmm.
- If he blew up a
bomb, can you imagine
what that would do to
property values around here.
- Mmm hmmm.
- Hmmmph, well if the Homeowners
Association isn't going
to do anything about him,
we should go to City Hall.
- Yes dear.
- He's back down in
that basement again.
Probably doing
something immoral.
- Honey!
Honey!
- Mmm mmm.
(light music)
- Well Griffin.
What are we wasting
our time on today?
- Nothing sir.
- Nothing, that's nice.
You know that automatic
shaver you designed.
- Yes sir.
- Well it doesn't work!
If you need me for
anything, I'll be at lunch.
(chuckling)
- Honey, dinner's ready.
- I'll just eat down here okay.
- More sweet potatoes Josh?
- Oh no Mom, I gotta go.
- (sighing) Yes, and what
a nice family dinner.
Here you go.
- Oh hi!
I'll just eat that later.
- Yeah, okay.
- Yes!
Looks good huh Cosmo?
Cosmo, science dog (laughing).
You wanna help daddy
with an invention?
Works by changing the
cellular density of the,
ah, you wouldn't
understand would you?
You're a dog!
Are you a thirsty dog?
It's non-toxic, biodegradable.
Won't hurt you a bit, yeah.
There you go,
that's right Cosmo.
Tastes good, huh.
Yeah, yeah.
Alright, flop number one.
Science.
- Herbert, that Griffin's going
to blow up the neighborhood.
- Mmm, anything you say dear.
- Alright, that might do it.
Here you go, want another drink?
Yeah, you do, don't ya.
Uh huh, yeah, ooh
that tastes good.
Hmmm.
Nothing.
(dog whining)
Oh wow! Wow!
(dog barking)
No, stay! Stay!
Cosmo!
You are there aren't you Cosmo?
Stay, stay.
Don't! Stay! Stay!
(dog whining)
It's okay, come on
now, it's alright.
Good, good, good.
There you go good girl.
Now, Cosmo! Cosmo!
We can't tell anyone
about this yet.
Oh no, no, no, no!
Now you just don't go blabbing
this around town okay!
(dog barking)
You're gonna have to be
invisible for a few days
and then I can patent
the formula in my name
and then I can use the lab
at work to find the antidote.
Till then, this is our
little secret okay?
(dog barking)
Good girl! Yeah!
- Cosmo! Cosmo!
Hey Mom have you seen Cosmo?
- Uh, no.
- Well she's not
in the back yard.
- Maybe she's hiding.
- I can't find her anywhere!
- Well, wouldn't
get upset about it.
She didn't just
up and disappear,
she's around here somewhere.
- Cosmo! Cosmo!
- My mom is no one.
Sometimes it feels that way.
(dog panting)
- I think Cosmo ran away.
- Oh she's probably
just out exploring.
- Why would she leave?
I was always nice to her.
- Josh, she's around somewhere.
- 'Cause I didn't play
with her enough, isn't it.
She was always bringing me
her ball wanting me to play.
But I didn't have time for her.
I didn't make time for her
and now she's gone.
- She'll be back honey.
Tired, smiling from
her adventures,
waiting for us to look
the other way so she can
snatch some food off the table.
- I hope so.
- (sighing) I hope so too.
(music playing on TV)
- [TV Character] How are they
gonna protect themselves?
- Handguns and rifles,
that's all they'll have.
(ominous music) (gunshots)
- Is your room clean?
- Mmm hmm.
- Have you made your bed?
- Great, thanks.
Don't forget to take
the garbage out tonight.
(gunshot)
(lighthearted music)
(dog whining)
- Joshua!
Josh!
- Yes Mom.
- Joshua Griffin, you
are grounded for a week.
- But Mom, there's a
sci-fi double feature
at the Elray theater
this weekend.
- Well I'm really sorry,
but your room isn't clean.
Your bed isn't made.
- But, but I made my bed.
- Josh!
I'm sorry, but there
will be no movie-going
for you this weekend.
And turn this TV off.
When you finished that, can
you set the table for me?
- Yes Mom.
(Mom gasping)
(Dad laughing)
- Oh my!
Oh did we have a good day?
- Yes, yes, my ship has come in.
- Oh, it's not
the Titanic is it?
- What does your ship do?
- Makes objects invisible.
- Oh that's nice honey.
- Imagine, imagine,
invisible eye glasses.
Invisible braces.
Invisible bandages,
invisible anything!
Honey, honey we
are gonna be rich.
We're gonna get rid of the
old station wagon of yours.
We're gonna maybe move
to a bigger house.
Maybe take a vacation in Hawaii.
- Oooh! (laughing)
- What kind of vacation
would it be without Cosmo.
- Cosmo!
The reason is that you haven't
seen her for the last Week
is because of my experiment.
You see I tested the formula
on her son and Cosmo is uh.
I'll just show
you, just show you.
Cosmo, come here girl!
(dog barking)
Come on, come on.
There she is.
Formula works on dogs too.
- Oh!
Oh! (shrieking)
Oh my goddess, honey,
you're a genius.
- You gave me the idea.
- Well, can you bring her back.
- Oh yeah, yeah sure,
with an antidote.
- Way to go dad.
Hey I'll do the dishes later.
Come on Cosmo!
(screaming and laughing)
(telephone ringing)
- Morning Al.
- So let me get this straight.
Everyone in your family
is totally jazzed
'cause your dad invented
this invisibility stuff.
- Right.
- Cosmo's back but you
still can't see her.
- Right.
- And you're still grounded!
- Right!
- Man, what I wouldn't
give to be invisible.
For just one day.
- Well, well, well lookie here.
It's lizard boy and
his good friend Dweebo.
Hey guess what Dweebo,
your girlfriend,
she's a little bent out of shape
'cause you didn't take her to
the movie Saturday you know.
- So?
- So, I think I'm
gonna have to take her.
Maybe I'll give here a
little kissing, ha, ha, ha.
- This place is spooky.
- Well here let me
turn on the light.
(Skeeter screams)
- Geez, Skeeter,
it's just a skeleton.
I'm not too sure
this is a good idea.
- Come on Josh, it's the only
way to sneak past your parents
and save Debbie Morrow
from that Thomas creep.
- What if it hurts?
- Did it hurt Cosmo?
- Well, maybe we
should try it on Ben.
- No, not a good idea.
- Well then, I'm
not gonna drink it.
- Fine, okay.
(ominous music)
- [Mom] Josh is that you?
- My mom.
- [Skeeter] Ben! Ben!
Where'd he go?
Where'd he go!
- What are you doing down here?
- I'm just showing
Skeeter Dad's lab.
- Well you know you're not
supposed to be down here
without your
father's permission.
- Yes Mom.
- You know you're not
supposed to have company over
when you're grounded.
- Yes Mom.
- Sorry to run you off Skeeter.
- It's okay Mrs. Griffin, I
have lots of homework to do.
- [Mom] What am I
gonna do with you Josh?
- Sorry Mom.
- Go upstairs and
do your homework.
Thank you.
(slow dramatic music)
- I'm gonna be grounded
for the rest of my life.
(gasping)
- What!
Oh my gosh!
Josh! Josh you get in
here right this minute!
I don't believe this.
What is going on.
Stay calm.
Just wait till your father
hears about this young man.
Josh, what happened to me?
- Uh, well.
Uh Skeeter and I
had this plan and--
- Josh, look at me!
- I'm trying, but
you're not there.
- Okay, let's start with
breaking into your father's lab.
- Okay, I broke into the lab
and borrowed some of dad's
invisibility formula.
- Joshua!
- Okay, I stole some of the
invisibility formula so that...
and I put in the RC bottle
and I guess you drank it.
- Why?
- Because you were thirsty.
- Why did you steal the formula?
- So, so I could sneak
out of the house.
See, 'cause this, 'cause
this guy named Johnny Thomas
he was gonna--
- Oh young man you wait
till your father gets home!
- Sorry mom.
- Hi honey, I'm home.
Honey?
(Mom sobbing)
What's wrong?
- Look at me Karl,
just look at me!
- Hey, hey there's
no reason to cry.
I mean underneath all that
stuff you're beautiful.
- Underneath all this stuff
I'm invisible! (sobbing)
- What!
- Josh broke into your lab
and stole some of the formula
and I drank it by mistake
and now I'm invisible.
- Oh my god!
It works on people too.
I mean this is so much
more than I ever imagined.
Tell me, how does it feel?
Tingly?
Is your vision blurred
or is it darkened at all?
- Karl!
Am I gonna look
like this forever?
- Now did you say
that Josh did this.
- Yes and as soon as
you give me the antidote
I'm gonna kill him.
- Honey, I don't
know how to say this.
- Say what!
- There is no antidote.
- What!
- Not yet at least.
- So?
- So, so, I didn't have time
to develop an antidote yet.
- Yet!
- Honey now you may
have to remain invisible
until I sell them the formula.
- Hah!
Forget it!
- That's not gonna
work for you is it?
- Oh, this is ridiculous.
Karl, you've got to
find an antidote.
If you have to sneak around
to do it, sneak around.
- Okay, okay, I'll just have
to smuggle the formula in,
make the antidote
and hope that Dr.
Woorter doesn't catch me.
- Well that'll be easy.
- It would be easier
if I had a test subject
so that I could make
sure the antidote works.
- What about Cosmo?
(dog barking)
- Cosmo's too big.
I'm gonna have enough trouble
getting the formula
past Woorter without--
- Ben!
Ben, Skeeter's lizard,
he's invisible too.
- Well, what have we
got going here Griffin?
- Oh, um, this is the a,
my kinetic energy experiment
that I have been working on.
You know.
- Oh well, now that
you've brought it here,
it's our property right?
- Oh, of course.
You know, but I need the
computer to run a few equations
then you can have the
wheel for analysis.
- Certainly, certainly.
- Right.
Okay, come on, come on.
Yes, alright now,
formulate the antidote.
- The antidote to what Griffin?
- My formula.
- And just what does this
new formula of ours do?
Invisibility, hmmm.
I feel a promotion coming
on, for myself naturally.
- Dr. Woorter,
this is my formula.
Now I developed this
myself on my own time.
- On your own time,
but in our laboratory
with our computer.
- Well, not exactly.
- You know that's
grounds for dismissal.
- No, Dr. Woorter,
you don't understand.
- Oh yes, I understand.
And I think that I'm
going to confiscate this
for the good of mankind.
And I don't think that
sending this off right now
is such a good idea.
- You realize what would happen
if this falls into
the wrong... hands.
Oh my god.
- Get me security, fast.
- Dr. Woorter! Dr. Woorter!
You can't do this.
- Sorry Griffin, but as
of 3.07 this afternoon,
you are barred from
this lab for life.
- You don't understand, my wife!
- Oh yes, your wife.
Well, looks like
she's gonna have to
find another job now huh?
So will you for that matter.
Can you say, would you like
fries with your burger?
- Dr. Woorter, please, I
must have access to the lab.
- Bye bye.
- No! No!
- Oh great, it's in code.
It's alright, I can
break it, I think.
My new formula.
- And just what do
you think it does.
- Well sir, imagine if
you can, an invisible army
capable of crossing enemy
lines and attacking at will.
Past guards, past surveillance
cameras, without being seen.
- Science fiction Doctor.
- Science fact.
- Empty cage, or is it?
- Seems like some
kind of trick to me.
Empty cage with a
motorized wheel.
- It's no trick sir.
It's an invisible lab specimen.
I'm telling you, inside of
this cage is an invisible...
Something or other.
- Something or other?
- Sir, whoever
owns this formula,
is going to rule the world.
- If you can prove this Doctor,
you're gonna be a
very, very rich man.
Now as soon as you can get
me a valid lab specimen,
I'll show it to the boys in D.C.
- What are you? A rat?
(light music)
- Mom, you home?
Aaargh!
- [Mom] Not until after dinner.
- Mom, don't sneak
up on me like that!
- [Mom] Well don't
sneak cookies like that.
- Mom, you don't
have any clothes on!
Or at least I
don't think you do.
- [Mom] Is your bed made?
- Mom, where are you?
- [Mom] Watching
your every move.
(knocking)
- Hiya doing Griff?
Go get your mommy, I'm
collecting for the Tribune.
- How much?
- 12 bucks, plus a generous
tip you little twerp.
- Mom, it's the paper boy
and he needs 12 dollars.
- [Mom] My purse is
on the coffee table.
- Wait here.
Mom, you've only got 10 dollars.
- I'll take a check.
Hey Griff, by the way, I'm
taking that girl you like
out to the movies
Saturday night.
Too bad you can't
make it huh? (laughs)
- She already had one
filled out for you.
- What and no tip.
Hey that nose of yours is
looking pretty good there huh.
Ready for another pop! (laughs)
Ow!
Man, what is that?
- Didn't I tell you
I was telekinetic?
- Huh?
- I can move things
with my mind.
- Ow!
What are you talking about?
- It's one of my
dad's experiments.
You lay one hand on Debbie and
I'll make your head explode.
I can do it!
- [Mom] Look at that boy run!
- Thanks Mom!
- [Mom] No sweat kiddo.
Hi honey, did you get it?
Did you find the answer?
What's the matter?
- I got fired.
- [Mom] (gasps) You what?
- Fired from the lab.
No chemicals, no super computer.
- No antidote.
- Dr. Woorter
confiscated the formula
and barred me from the lab.
- Karl, I can't stay
invisible forever!
- I don't know what to do.
- Oh.
- Something is wrong Herbert.
- Yes dear.
- I haven't seen
Laura Griffin all day
and goodness knows
I've been looking.
It's as though she's
just up and disappeared.
(sad music)
- Dad, you can't let those
guys push you around.
You've got to stand
up for yourself.
- He's my boss Josh.
He's more important than I am.
- But he didn't invent
the formula, you did.
You're the genius dad.
He may be your boss but
you're smarter than he is.
You can't let him win.
- He fired me!
It's over!
I lost!
- You can't give up just
because you're hurt.
You've got to keep going.
If you don't stand up for
yourself, you'll be hurt
on the inside as well
as on the outside.
It's your formula Dad.
You have the right to break
into the lab and get it back.
If you find out the
antidote in the process
it's even better.
- You make it sound easy.
- It will be.
We've got to take the chance.
- I've still got my keys.
They're closed on Saturday.
If I can get past the
guard at the desk.
- We can do it.
We've got to get
Mom back to normal.
- [Security Guard] Dr. Griffin,
what are you doing back?
- We're here to
clean out my desk.
- Mmm hmm.
- Just be cool.
Right here.
(tense music)
Alright, here we go.
- This is a pretty
cool place Dad.
- Thanks.
We got to hurry though.
(telephone ringing)
- Woorter here.
No I didn't give
Griffin permission to
collect his things.
How long has he been there?
No, no, no, don't
call the police.
I'll take care of this myself.
- Alright, alright,
this better work.
Now this I believe is the
ingredient that we were missing.
Yeah, yeah.
Huh.
- Let's try that on Ben.
- Let's try.
Here you go Ben.
There you go.
I've learned a
valuable lesson son.
I should have thought
before I acted.
Once Mom's back I'm gonna
destroy the formula.
Shred every trace, it's
just too dangerous.
The world's not ready yet.
Look what it's done to us.
- It's okay, you
didn't know Dad.
- Maybe I should have.
(dreamy music)
Yes, yes!
It works! It works!
- Mom's gonna be okay.
- [Dr. Woorter] I'm
so happy to hear that.
- Run! Run!
(fast paced music)
- Restrain him will you, he
just ruined my experiment.
- Dr. Woorter, Dr.
Woorter, I can explain.
My wife has disappeared.
I have to get her back.
- Your wife disappeared?
- [Dad] Yes.
- And so that made
you break into my lab.
- Yes! I needed certain
chemicals to make an antidote
to bring her back.
She's invisible.
- Invisible!
Did you hear that?
I believe he said
that she's invisible.
I think that you'd better
call the state mental hospital
and have them come
and get Prof. Griffin.
- My god, didn't
you just hear me?
My wife is at home, she's
there waiting for me.
She's invisible.
You can't do this.
- So, you decided to try
this experiment on your wife?
- Look, just let me go.
Let me go Woorter and I'll
split the formula with you.
- Oh, there's no
reason to do that.
You see Griffin, once
the competency hearing
finds you mentally unstable.
Well, they're gonna
lock you up for life.
Then the formula will
be mine, all mine.
Take him away.
So, that's who you are.
- Listen, you've got
to let me out of here.
My dad isn't crazy, my
mom really is invisible.
It's my fault really.
I'm the one who gave
her my dad's formula.
Look, my dad isn't crazy.
You believe me don't you.
- Aha, you got him huh?
Well dementia seems
to run in the family.
Better get a child
custody officer here
to take care of little Joshua.
Put him in a home for
disturbed little children.
As for you Griffin, I see
basket-weaving in your future.
Lots and lots of basket-weaving.
- Didn't you hear what I said.
YOu've got to believe
me I'm not crazy.
My wife is really
invisible, really.
Let me out.
Help!
Somebody help! No! No!
You don't understand.
I'm the only one who
knows how to help her.
(yelling)
Help!
Help me!
- Rats.
The only proof that the
formula really works, ruined.
Thanks a lot pal.
All I need now is just
another invisible specimen.
Yeah, something that would
sway the joint chiefs
to pay me twice what I want.
What?
Wait a minute.
The mother, Mrs. Griffin.
Of course!
(ominous music)
There, she'll never
know the difference.
Perfect.
- [Mom] Gosh you guys
it's after five o'clock.
Where are you?
You said you wouldn't
be this late.
- [Josh] Well don't I at
least get a phone call.
- [Woman] Alright
but make it quick.
(telephone ringing)
- [Mom] Oh finally,
this has got to be them.
Hello.
- Mom.
- [Mom] Where are
you, are you okay?
- Well we ran into a
little trouble at the lab.
Dr. Woorter caught us.
They put me in this orphanage.
- [Mom] Orphanage!
- Yeah, until the hearing.
- [Mom] What hearing?
- Dad's sanity hearing.
They've got him
in the loony bin.
- [Mom] What!
- Dr. Woorter convinced
them that he's crazy
because he thinks
that you're invisible.
- [Mom] Well, where
is this hearing.
- No Mom, you can't go there.
Dad thinks the formula
is too dangerous.
You can't let anybody know
that the invisibility works.
- [Mom] What else can I do?
- Well Dad's hearing's on Monday
morning nine o'clock sharp.
You gotta think of something.
- [Mom] I will.
- That's enough.
- Just a minute.
- [Mom] Josh! Josh!
- Mom.
- [Mom] Yeah?
- I love you.
- [Mom] I love you too.
- Alright, come with me.
- [Mom] Alright,
Laura, stay calm.
Stay calm and you can get
everything straightened out.
(mumbling)
Poor Karl, he must be so upset.
What could be keeping that cab.
I have to get to the lab before
Prof. Woorter gets there.
If I can just get to Karl's lab,
I can find the antidote
for this somewhere.
I can't believe it's
taking that cab so long.
Oh, my gosh I'm gonna
die in this outfit.
Must be 100 degrees.
Josh, I never wanted
this to happen to him.
Don't worry family,
Mom will pull through.
(lighthearted music)
(taxi hooting)
At last.
- Where to lady?
- Applied Technologies lab.
- [Driver] Want
me to step on it?
- Here's a twenty, it should
cover the fare and your tip.
- You feeling okay lady?
- Just get going.
- Okay.
Here you go lady,
safe and sound.
- Thank goodness, I
could not have stayed
inside these clothes
one more minute.
It's pretty hot in
here, you know that.
Just got to get
these things off.
Then I got to get in, I've
got to get past the guards
without being seen.
When I find that Dr.
Woorter, what he did to me
I'm gonna give him
one swift kick in the.
I don't believe I'm taking
my clothes off in public.
Broad daylight.
Excuse me, what are
you looking at buddy!
Thanks for the ride.
- Have a nice day.
- [Mom] You too.
- Before we make a presentation
to the joint chiefs
I need proof
Woorter, solid proof.
- Oh you'll have your proof sir.
Just as soon as I
can secure a specimen
for my show and
tell presentation.
- And just how long do
you think it will take you
to secure this specimen?
- [Mom] Excuse me.
- I think that I'll have one
very soon sir, very soon.
- [Mom] I know the antidote
must be around here somewhere.
Oh, hi Ben.
Where could it be?
What does it look like?
Oh! That's not it.
Maybe over here.
Wait a minute, that's it!
(shrieking) Help! Help!
Let me out of here!
Let me out!
- Well, good evening
Mrs. Griffin.
Nice to see you, or not to
see you as the case may be.
- [Mom] Let me go!
- I wish you'd stop
struggling so much though.
I'm afraid you
might hurt yourself.
- [Mom] Let me go!
- Oh, I'm afraid
I can't do that.
You see Mrs. Griffin.
Well you are dramatic proof
that the invisible formula
really works on humans.
Now, after your poor husband
is found mentally unstable
and committed to an asylum.
I will use you as part of my
presentation in Washington.
You will help me
to sell the formula
to the government for millions.
- [Mom] I won't
help you Woorter.
- Oh yes, I think you
will Mrs. Griffin.
You see, well if you co-operate,
well then I will supply you
with the antidote, which
you came so close to.
And also your husband and
your son will be released.
Now if you choose
not to co-operate.
Oh dear, I sure hate to
see families separated
but I'm sure that you understand
that business is business.
- [Mom] You promise you'll
release my husband and son.
- Scout's honor.
Just stay quiet until we
get to Washington, alright.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I will go and prepare
your room for the trip.
Well, I hope you'll like
your room Mrs. Griffin.
- [Mom] Oh it's
swell, real swell.
Just, remember to
keep your mouth shut
until we get to
Washington D.C. huh.
- [Mom] I heard
you the first time.
- Anything you
say can jeopardize
the future well-being
of your family.
- [Mom] I know that.
- Oh, here's something
to think about.
- [Mom] Ow!
You're not gonna get
away with this Woorter.
(lightning crashes)
- What are you thinking about?
- My mom.
- I used to think
that having a mom
was the worst thing
in the whole world.
Even worse than head-lice.
But then my mom went
away, never came back.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
What happened to your mom?
- I don't know.
- You should get some sleep.
(sad music)
(lightning crashes)
- [Mom] Hey guys, I'm
sorry I let you down.
I promise we'll be a
family again really soon.
I love you. (crying)
- I can't sleep.
I'm worried about
my wife and my son.
Funny, I haven't worried
about them in a long time.
I'm usually busy doing
unimportant things.
Now it may be too late.
(crying)
- [Mom] Oh I don't want
to go to Washington.
- Well Lenny, this is the one.
Come on let's get
it on the truck.
It's almost nine a.m.
- [Mom] Nine a.m!
- I heard you the first time.
- I didn't say anything.
I gotta get some sleep.
Come on.
- Geez, this thing's heavy.
- It must weigh a ton.
- [Mom] Excuse me, I don't
weigh an ounce over 112.
- Did you hear that?
- Nothing in there,
but a picture.
- [Mom] Hey, no peeking.
- Smitty!
- [Mom] Sleep tight.
Sorry guys, but
sometimes a mom's
got to play a little tough.
- Morning, sleep well?
- Listen, you have no
reason to keep me here.
I am not insane.
- Ah, that's what they all say.
- [Dad] But I'm not like the
others, I really am sane.
- That's what the hearing's for.
- To prove I'm sane.
- No, to prove that
you belong here.
Come on, haven't got all day.
- Oh sir, sir, I think
that in the interests
of national security
that we shouldn't mention
the invisibility
formula at this hearing.
- Well at this point, I'm not
sure there is such a thing.
- Oh yeah, there is, there is!
Wait till you see the
new specimen I have.
- The board acknowledges
Colonel Cutter.
- Well Professor Griffin
was always a strange bird.
Not exactly the kind of man
you would expect to find
in the army.
Men like me, strong, courageous,
with a love for
dressing up in uniform.
A love for living
with other men.
In other words, he was not what
you would call a man's man.
- Like yourself Colonel.
- Well thank you ma'am.
Yes exactly.
He was always cowering in
the corner during briefings.
Strange bird.
- I see, is that all?
- I think that about covers
the situation ma'am yes.
- Thank you.
- Is there a Mrs.
Pringle present.
- Oh, yes I'm right
here your honor.
- I'm not a judge,
I am a doctor.
I understand you have some
information to share with us.
- Yes, your honor.
- Mrs. Pringle please
take the stand.
- Professor Griffin and
his wife and son have lived
across the street
from me for 11 years.
If you ask me, he
was never quite sane.
And then, suddenly last
week, his wife disappeared.
Hmmph, just up and vanished.
I think he killed her
and cut her up in pieces
and buried them all
over the back yard.
I bet if you would get
some men with shovels
they could dig her up.
- Thank you, that
will be enough.
- Hey son.
- Don't worry, you're
gonna get out of this.
- I know, I know.
- Hey buddy, keep your distance.
This guy's a psycho.
- He's my dad!
- Just keep your distance.
- [Doctor] Professor
Griffin please.
- Good luck.
- My name is Karl
Jackson Griffin
and there has been
a mistake made.
As a research scientist for
Applied Technologies Laboratory
I created an
invisibility formula.
Then, due to a
mistake, my wife Laura,
drank some of the formula
and she became invisible.
And then Dr. Woorter stole
the invisibility formula
and he fired me.
When I attempted to break into
the lab to create an antidote
so that my wife
could be seen again,
Dr. Woorter had me arrested.
Here I am now.
Dr. Woorter is the one
who should be on trial
for stealing my formula.
- This is not a trial,
it is a hearing.
- Okay, then hear this.
I love my wife
and I love my son.
I love my family and
I also love my job.
And I won't go on working
with disreputable people
like Dr. Woorter, who
steal the work of others
and claim it as their own.
That's enough to drive
anybody a little crazy.
For years, I did nothing.
I let him steal from me,
afraid that he would fire me.
Well I, I can't do that anymore.
I am not gonna let bullies like
Dr. Woorter push me around,
claim that he invented my
formula and say that I am crazy.
Dr. Woorter is a thief.
He's the one who should
be on trial, not me.
- This is not a trial.
It's a hearing.
Thank you Dr. Griffin,
you may take a seat.
So let's hear what Dr.
Woorter has to say.
- Well first of all, let me
assure you that I'm no thief.
Now, I'm sorry to have
to be the one to say this
but Professor Griffin has
clearly lost his mind.
I mean invisibility, come on.
We all know that
there's no such thing
as an invisibility formula.
And as for his wife
being invisible.
She disappeared all
right, she took off!
I mean otherwise
she would be here.
And as you can plainly
see-- (slapping)
She's not.
- Glad you could
make it sweetheart.
- Oh it's a little warm in here.
Now, seems to me that
Professor Griffin should not
be allowed to interact with
fellow human beings like myself.
(grunting)
Stop that!
Stop that immediately.
Excuse me.
Furthermore, I believe
that Professor Griffin
should be committed to the
state mental health facility
because-- (giggling)
Stop that tickling!
Stop that!
- Do you see anybody?
- No, of course not.
Do you?
- Man's obviously crazy.
- That's not true,
I'm not crazy.
It's her, don't you understand.
Can't you see?
Of course you can't see.
That's because she's invisible.
But believe me she's there.
She's the one that made me
pick my nose, she slapped me.
She's been tickling-- (yelling)
She's trying to
make me look crazy.
I'm not, I'm not crazy.
- That's what they all say.
(Woorter yelling)
- Everybody wave
your arms around.
You'll hit her, you'll hit her.
I'm telling you I'm not crazy.
- I'd say that this
hearing is over.
Professor Griffin,
you're free to go.
And I'd like to see a
full report on Dr. Woorter
tomorrow morning.
See that he doesn't
hurt himself.
- Honey! Honey?
- Professor Griffin.
It looks like we're gonna have
a vacancy at Applied
Technologies.
- You want me to take my
old job back after this?
- No I wouldn't think of
giving you your old job back.
How would you like
Dr. Woorter's job?
- What?
- What we're looking
for is a leader.
A man who isn't afraid
to stand up for himself.
So do you want the job?
- Yeah.
I mean, yes sir.
And there are gonna be some
big changes around here
and I have got plenty
of ideas Colonel.
- Jerry, call me Jerry.
And if I were you I'd take
that wife of yours out
and celebrate tonight.
I don't think you would've
gotten out of this without her.
- Oh you're right.
You know if it's not
too much trouble,
have the invisibility antidote
sent over from the lab.
- I'll do that right away sir.
- Well, congratulations
neighbors.
Oh!
Why I never.
Hmmph.
- [Mom] Oh, I've wanted
to do that for so long.
- There you are.
So, where to now?
- [Mom] Home!
- You are some woman.
- [Mom] You wouldn't
believe what happened to me.
I got locked in a cage
and had to beat up
two guys to get here.
- Oh I wish I could see the
expression on your face.
- [Mom] I wish I could
just see my face.
- Hey Dad, this just
came by messenger.
- The antidote.
- [Mom] Oh thank God.
- I can't wait to see you.
How I have missed you.
Okay honey.
- I've missed me too.
- Here we go.
Don't spill any.
- [Mom] Did I get the right one?
It tastes like water.
- Nothing happened, I?
- You mean it doesn't work.
(mom groans)
- We're gonna figure
out something son.
If I have to get the team
at the lab to work on it,
they're gonna work
on it night and day
until we find an antidote.
Sorry Laura, I'm so sorry.
(mom moaning)
(dog panting)
- Hey Cosmo, what are you doing?
Sit, sit.
Oh hey, I used to
think you had it made.
No mom to boss you around,
no chores, no homework.
What am I gonna do Cosmo?
Hey? C--
Mom, Dad, come quick.
Cosmo, Cosmo I can see you.
- [Mom] What is it?
- Look.
- [Mom] She's visible.
- How did it happen,
what did you do to her?
- Nothing, she was like
this whenever she came in.
- [Mom] Karl, does this mean
that the formula just wears off?
- No I don't think so.
It has to be a chemical reaction
to something that
she ate or drank.
- Something in the house.
- [Mom] Like what?
- Let's look.
- [Mom] Hurry Karl.
- Let's just go
through everything.
- [Mom] What are we
supposed to be looking for.
Nothing out of order here.
There's nothing in here.
What?
- Honey.
- [Mom] Yeah?
- The dog food.
- [Mom] You want
me to eat dog food.
- Yes, yes, Cosmo did.
Maybe there's something in
it, some chemical additive
or preservative.
You know, we won't
know unless you try.
(Mom sighing)
- [Mom] Blech!
How can you eat this
stuff Cosmo, ech.
Well, is anything happening.
- No, I guess it's
not the dog food.
Keep searching.
- [Mom] Great.
(slurping)
Anything?
- Guess it's not the water.
- [Mom] I'm not going to
drink out of the toilet.
I don't care if it
will make me visible.
- Course not.
- [Mom] And I'm not
gonna bite fleas.
- Oh no, no, I wouldn't
have you do that.
But what else does Cosmo eat?
- [Mom] Besides dog food.
Table scraps when
no-one's looking.
- Table scraps!
I'll be right back.
- [Mom] Wait, Karl,
where are you going?
- Dad what's the hurry?
- I've got it.
- Oh yeah.
- Now go get your mother,
she's over by the refrigerator
tell her to lay
down by the sofa.
You ate this, you
drank this didn't you?
- [Mom] Josh, what is your
father doing down in the lab?
- Don't worry Mom,
Dad's got an idea.
- [Mom] I hope it's a good one.
- Okay, I've found it.
It's a version of the
formula that didn't work.
My equation was off by 2%.
- [Mom] So?
- So, that 2% is the
difference between the formula
and the antidote.
See, I put the beaker next
to my dinner in the basement.
When Cosmo tried to get
the food, she knocked over
the beaker, drank some of the
liquid, now she's visible.
- Is there enough left for Mom?
- Gosh I hope so.
Well, let's go.
(gulping)
Okay, now we wait.
- [Mom] I feel
funny, all tingly.
(dreamy music)
- Gross.
- Look at that, amazing!
- How do I look without makeup?
- Simply beautiful.
- Mom, I can see you.
Don't ever disappear again okay?
- Okay.
- (laughing) That
goes for me too.
- Okay, but no more
nutty experiments.
- Oh, but I was working on this
experimental growth formula
that you can do on a baby chick,
makes them grow to
the size of a house.
- Karl!
- I threw it out in the
trash, don't worry about it.
(strange barking)
- [All] Cosmo?
(lively music)