(Arrows whooshing)
(♪♪♪)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
(Comets whooshing)
(♪♪♪)
(Indistinct whispering)
- (Woman whimpering)
- (Indistinct whispering)
- (Woman grunts)
(Indistinct whispering
continues)
(Whimpering)
(Woman screams)
MAC: No one seems to care
about anything lately.
Good or bad.
I think people are finally
wakin' up.
Don't start that with me.
I'm not talkin' politics
with you.
I'm not.
This is far more important.
You see, that's it.
You're Mr. PC. Then, bam.
People are actin' different.
At work, where I take lunch.
Everywhere.
S... something's not right.
It feels dangerous.
Don't you feel it?
Come on, man.
What are you doin'?
Are you messing with me
right now?
There's nothing
to be afraid of, Mac.
You'll see.
You know, when people
suspect a conspiracy,
but don't have any proof,
that's paranoia.
Yeah, just because
you're paranoid.
You know
what Winston Churchill said?
What did Winston Churchill say?
Those who never change
their minds,
will never change anything.
What the hell does that
have to do with anything?
Well, as always,
thanks for the morning coffee.
- Yeah.
- (Sighs) I'm off to work.
I'm done with your power saw.
I'll bring it by tonight.
Have a nice day, Mac.
(♪♪♪)
(Indistinct speech)
JANE: I just don't think
I'm being paranoid.
There's something goin' on.
MAC:
Relax, relax.
WEATHERMAN:
(Indistinct speech)
Everything is...
everything's gonna be fine.
WEATHERMAN:
(Indistinct speech)
- We're just imagining it.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
We're just being paranoid.
Yep.
Do you still love me?
I guess. Most of the time.
(♪♪♪)
(Schoolbell ringing)
Hey, Laurie, Emily.
I don't even know
why she tries to talk to us.
Ew.
Don't hold it against them,
Kim.
They're just insecure.
I bet deep down,
they're better than that.
(Sighs) Right.
You know, you don't have to be
like that anymore.
Like what?
Defensive. Insecure.
Comparing yourself to others.
Whatever, Skye. I gotta go.
(indistinct chatter
in background)
MAC: I'm not sure where you're
going with this, Marlowe.
MARLOWE:
I know how you can be.
I won't get mad.
MARLOWE: That is precisely it.
Your anger, Mac.
(Clears throat)
So you agree?
I'm your top earner
for a reason.
Sometimes I need to be
a little intense.
MARLOWE:
Anger is a poison.
What are you asking me?
MARLOWE: Could you be convinced
that you don't have to be angry
ever again.
I'm not an angry person.
I just don't feel the need
to agree with everyone
all the time.
MARLOWE:
And that's what you believe.
That's the truth.
MARLOWE:
That's your truth.
What else is there?
Oh, well.
There's everything.
There is everything else.
Why don't you just
take the rest of the day off
and you can think about
what we discussed.
(♪♪♪)
HYSTERICAL WOMAN 1: Don't
tell me to fucking calm down!
HYSTERICAL WOMAN 2:
You calm down!
HYSTERICAL WOMAN 1:
My husband is not my husband.
(Indistinct argument
in distance)
(Door squeaks, closes)
Am I in trouble?
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
ETHAN:
No.
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
Patel told me
you asked to go home.
Yeah.
It's a zoo.
One of the worst I've ever seen.
We need your help, Jane.
Not you hiding in here.
Well, Ethan,
until our phones start working,
I'm gonna go home.
That's all there is to it.
I'm sure Mac's fine.
- Everything's gonna be fine.
- Yeah.
Everything that's going on
out there, that is not normal.
I have a really bad feeling
about this.
Look, I know I'm gonna get...
- You know what I heard?
- What?
I heard the governor is gonna
declare a state of emergency.
- I don't know.
- From who?
From what? Are ERs filling up?
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
How would you even know that?
Our phones aren't working.
Jane, there's nothing
to be afraid of.
What are you doing?
ETHAN:
Wait. Jane.
JANE: What the
fuck are you doing?
Stop it!
(Grunts) Help!
Help!
(♪♪♪)
Get inside.
Get inside!
Marc!
Fuck!
- Did you see that?
- Hi, neighbor.
- I live around the corner.
- You know my dad, Blake, right?
I don't think so.
Oh, well, I'm Sara.
- I saw you this morning.
- Yeah?
I work out a few times a day.
MAC: What were you
talkin' to Bill about?
Don't you think I'm pretty?
MAC:
What?
Invite me inside.
Now, I know your wife
won't be home for a while.
It's Jane, right?
It's Jane?
Hi, Kim!
Hey.
Later.
- MAC: You saw that, right?
- KIM: Yep, I saw that.
- Do you know that girl?
- Sara Polaski.
No, I guess I don't.
You notice that people
are acting...
- Really strange.
Yes, my friends, too.
Most of them.
Something's wrong. Really wrong.
- It's not just my imagination.
- No, it's not your imagination.
(Siren blaring in distance)
You stayin'
at your Uncle Kurt's?
KIM:
Mom's tracking the night shift.
She still makes me.
I'll call my mom.
Maybe she knows
where Uncle Kurt hid the key
this time.
(Static)
- No signal.
- Really?
- Did you change your Wi-Fi?
- No.
No cellular either.
Come on. I'll be right back.
(♪♪♪)
(Alarm beeping)
- BROADCASTER: This is a Connecticut...
- MAC: Kim!
BROADCASTER:
Emergency Action Notification.
The Office of the Governor
has declared
a state of emergency.
Previous notifications
have encouraged residents
to seek shelter at home
and await further instructions.
- Private residences...
- Previous notifications?
- Are no longer considered safe.
- It's the first I've heard.
BROADCASTER: All citizens and their
families are now required to proceed
to the nearest public school
or emergency shelter
where you will receive
further instructions
from police
or military personnel.
Repeat,
the Office of the Governor
has declared
a state of emergency.
Citizens failing to comply
will be subject
to criminal indictment.
MAC:
We're not doin' that!
BROADCASTER: This is a Connecticut
Emergency Action Notification.
- ...tion. Private residences...
- KIM: Mac?
BROADCASTER:
Are no longer considered safe.
Jane should be home by now.
She was only supposed to work
a half day for Aliya.
BROADCASTER: To proceed to
the nearest public school
- or emergency shelter...
- You think we should go?
BROADCASTER: Where you will
receive further instructions
- Not without Jane.
- Or military personnel.
Repeat, the Office of the Gov...
(Static)
You think this is the end
of the world?
Uh, I'm gonna say "no".
I kinda think it might be.
Okay.
I've lived through my share
of prophesized doomsdays.
Always uneventful.
This time tomorrow,
we'll be lookin' at this thing
like it's Y2K or 2012.
What's a Y2K?
Exactly. Yeah.
Everything's gonna be all right.
I'm sure your mom and Kurt
are fine, too.
Well, you seem pretty worried.
No, just...
just a different situation.
I give you that.
I have this strange feeling
that nothing's ever gonna be
the same again.
Yeah.
Like you woke up
in a different world.
Like that exactly.
(Static)
CAPTAIN GREGORY:
They are running the show.
Again, to anyone listening,
this is US Naval Captain
Gregory Schneider broadcasting.
I don't have a lot of time,
so listen closely.
This is a real threat,
not a mass hysteria event
or rampant paranoia.
People around you,
people everywhere
are not themselves anymore.
They've changed somehow.
They're organizing, taking over.
Avoid contact
with anyone you don't know
and even then only engage
with extreme caution.
Trust no one. Not completely.
They've infiltrated
the military, government,
all civil services.
The scales have tipped, people.
(Indistinct yelling)
CAPTAIN GREGORY:
I'm armed. Stay back!
(♪♪♪)
BROADCASTER: The Office of
the Governor has declared
a state of emergency.
Previous notifications
have encouraged residents
to seek shelter at home
and await further instructions.
Private residences
are no longer considered safe.
- (Static)
- It's everywhere.
BROADCASTER: Are now required to
proceed to the nearest public school
or emergency shelter
where you will receive
further instructions from
police or military personnel.
Oh, no.
BROADCASTER: ...has declared
a state of emergency.
Citizens failing to comply
will be subject
to criminal indictment.
That wasn't helping.
Where the fuck is Jane?
Do you think anybody else heard
that Navy Captain?
I don't know. Maybe.
(Siren blaring in distance)
What do you think that siren is?
Can you just give me some space?
Jesus.
(Siren blaring in distance)
(♪♪♪)
Who's back there?
(Siren blaring in distance)
(♪♪♪)
I know you're back there!
I just saw people
in the backyard.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- MAC: Oh, thank Christ.
- KIM: Jane?
MAC:
Yeah.
Where've you been?
JANE:
Give me a minute.
- What's wrong?
- Give me a fuckin' minute.
KIM:
Jane, are you okay?
JANE:
Fuckin' unbelievable.
MAC:
What's goin' on?
JANE:
Oh my God.
- He fuckin'...it's Ethan.
- MAC: What?
JANE:
Ethan fuckin' attacked me!
- MAC: Ethan?
- JANE: Yeah, I know.
I mean, he's always been
comin' on to me,
but this time he just
fuckin' went at it.
- MAC: Hey, are you hurt?
- Yeah.
Yes, I'm fuckin' hurt!
Oh, God, he was so strong.
Oh!
Come here, come here,
come here, come here. It's okay.
- Please, don't touch. Stop.
- (overlapping speech)
Mac, please,
I don't wanna be touched.
All right.
I'm gonna fucking kill him!
He kept... he kept like
tryin' to kiss me.
He just kept sayin',
over and over again,
"There's nothin'
to be afraid of.
There's nothin'
to be afraid of."
- I'm sorry, Jane.
- JANE: I'll be fine.
I've been dealing with it
for hours.
First, the security report,
and then HR.
Everyone was half zoned out
like they don't even care.
So I told 'em I was leavin'.
They can fuckin' fire me.
KIM: They expected you to
stay and work after that?
MAC: Normal people
do not act that way.
Do not... they can't know about
this.
The navy captain came on
the emergency broadcast.
- He said...
- Uh, the signal cut out.
- People are changed.
- And people aren't themselves.
- They...
- Trust no one.
They're organized.
They're takin' over
the military and the government.
And then he's like,
"Stay back, I have a gun."
- It's happening.
- JANE: Are you fuckin' kiddin'?
It's not paranoia,
it's happening.
JANE:
Oh my God!
I mean, so many people like us.
Patients, their families.
Everyone's convinced
that people aren't themselves.
Whatever this is...
it's contagious.
- Something in the air?
- JANE: No.
No, no, I doubt.
I... I mean, I... seriously,
I wasn't at the hospital
for five minutes before
they called us down to the ER.
And we still couldn't keep up.
I mean, it was... I've never
seen anything like it.
There was car accidents,
suicide attempts, assaults,
- shootings.
- KIM: There were shootings?
- Yeah! Yeah.
- This is bad, right?
- Okay, d... don't panic.
- JANE: (overlapping speech)
Look, we... we're here,
we're okay.
I'll help, I'll take care of us.
Just don't drink the tap water.
I don't trust it. Okay?
There's bottles of water
in the fridge, Kim, okay?
Hey, Kim.
- You okay?
- Not really.
I don't know where
my Uncle Kurt is.
And my mom,
I can't call her.
I know. I'm worried
about my mom, too.
KIM: Landline's down, too.
I can't reach anybody.
What about your sister?
MAC: I can't worry
about her right now.
Oh God.
- I can't believe...
- MAC: Bill's coming.
- Mac, I don't want him in here.
- MAC: I know.
JANE: I mean, seriously,
don't trust anyone.
- MAC: I know, just...
- JANE: Mac!
- MAC: I will handle it!
- (overlapping speech)
Hey, Bill.
Hey, Mac. I got your power saw.
Jane, Kim, what's going on?
Jane had a rough day
at the hospital.
With everything that's goin' on,
we can't be too careful.
BILL:
What do you mean?
We spoke about this morning.
People aren't right.
She thinks it might be
contagious.
Hmm.
MAC:
You haven't turned on the radio?
No.
Apparently, if we don't
report to an emergency shelter,
we're breakin' the law.
- BILL: Oh?
- Shut the door.
- Shut it.
- Wait.
You haven't turned on
your phone, huh?
- Or the TV?
- No.
I think we could all use
a little less technology
- every now and then.
- Shut the door.
Have you seriously not noticed
the way people are acting?
No.
Actually, I find it to be
quite peaceful and all.
Peaceful? Are you kidding me?
Jane, Mac,
there's nothing to be afraid of.
Get off him!
Kim, help me!
Oh, Jane!
Jane, where are you going?
Stop it. Stop it.
Get the fuck off of him. Now.
(♪♪♪)
MAC:
What was that, huh?
JANE:
Just tell us.
MAC:
Why did you attack me?
JANE:
Just give us some answers here.
MAC: He knows what's goin'
on, clearly.
He's part of it.
- Say something, Bill!
- Wait!
Whatever this is,
it's physical.
Some sort of infection or virus.
Rabies. That causes confusion
and aggression.
Not feeling like yourself today,
Mr. Costello?
I'm a changed man, Kim.
Changed?
That's right.
JANE:
But you're still Bill Costello.
Well, who else would I be?
Then tell me about
last Christmas.
BILL:
You were here with us.
Another Jane and Mac
Christmas extravaganza
that your mother skipped
to be with her latest boyfriend.
Tayden even let you
sip some champagne
when your uncle wasn't lookin'.
When Kurt found out,
he was angry at you both.
MAC:
Okay. You're you.
Why're you acting so weird?
I've been perfected. Changed.
MAC:
Changed, how?
I was kissed yesterday
by a wonderful red-haired woman.
It was perfection. Bliss.
MAC: Wait, so you were tryin'
to kiss me this morning?
- Wait, he tried to kiss you?
- I thought he was kidding.
That's it.
That's why Ethan
tried to kiss you.
- That...
- Yeah.
That's how they're doing it.
That's how they're
changing people.
JANE:
Tell us.
- MAC: What the fuck?
- KIM: Now what?
- MAC: Shut up, shut up.
- Shh, shh!
- Maybe it's Uncle Kurt.
- MAC: Shh! Kim, be quiet.
JANE:
Stay still.
- KIM: But...
- MAC: Shh. Don't... don't move.
- KIM: But what if it's him?
- JANE: Kim, quiet.
- That's his knock!
- MAC: Kim, stop!
BILL:
None of this is necessary, Jane.
Why don't you just
surrender to me?
Quiet.
(Banging on door)
KURT:
Kim, you here?
(Banging on door)
KURT:
Mac, Jane, you in here?
What? Your car's
in the driveway,
but you're not home? Come on.
KIM:
He sounds fine to me.
Yeah.
KURT: Can you tell me what is this
saw doin' out here on the ground?
- Right. Total asshole.
- KURT: Kim?
(♪♪♪)
KURT:
Kim?
MAC:
Yeah, Kurt, she's in here.
KURT: Well,
you're gonna open the door or what?
MAC:
How're you doin'?
I'm tired.
How do you think I'm doin'?
MAC:
Everything okay with you?
Mac, I'm beat. Long day.
I wanna get Kim home, eat,
and fall asleep in my chair.
Where is she?
Everything okay with you?
MAC: You notice anything
strange goin' on out there?
Like what?
MAC:
Like people acting different?
Yeah. You.
MAC: You haven't noticed
people acting different?
What people?
MAC:
Most people.
You know me.
I mind my own business,
get the same in return.
Look, is Kim in there or not?
(♪♪♪)
Let's go, huh?
I don't wanna have to
make dinner twice.
Did you see anyone
outside the house?
KURT:
No. What's wrong with you two?
You haven't turned on
your radio?
The radio? No.
How about you stop
asking me questions?
Just tell me
what the problem is.
MAC:
We're not sure.
There's a situation
and it's growing.
- People are acting...
- Strange.
Different. They're changed.
They're themselves,
but they're not.
You're saying
you haven't noticed
anything about anyone out there.
You know I'm by myself all day
drivin' state to state
for the dealership.
MAC: You haven't heard
emergency broadcasts.
You haven't seen anything.
I listen to my music,
not the radio.
You're acting like a lunatic,
Mac.
Jane thinks
it's some sort of sickness
that's going around.
KURT: Okay, I don't care if
people are acting different
or strange
or if everybody in town
is infected
with the bubonic plague.
You know, I put in
over 600 miles
of 95 North today.
So, Kim, let's go. Now.
Something's really,
really wrong, Uncle Kurt.
We've got Mr. Costello
in the basement.
Whatever it is, he's got it.
- Bill?
- MAC: Yeah.
KIM:
Yes, Bill.
What's he got now?
KIM: You need to come
see for yourself.
Are you kidding me?
This... this is a joke, right?
MAC:
Are you not listening?
What the hell did they do
to you, Bill?
- They tied me to this chair.
- Yeah, pretty shitty job.
MAC:
He's not going anywhere.
- Look, she's 16.
- KIM: 17.
I... I'm gonna kill you, guys.
JANE: Stop bein' so
bull-headed and just listen!
No! This is a goddamn felony.
- We had no choice!
- He attacked me!
It's true, Uncle Kurt!
- Get off!
- KIM: Ask him a question.
Look, they are holding a man
prisoner, Kim.
I'm not gonna be a part of this.
You are not gonna be
a part of this!
Tell us how you've changed.
What would you like to know?
KIM:
What if we let you go?
I'd change all of you.
KURT: You'd change us. What...
what's that supposed to mean?
KIM: It means if you untie him,
he'll try to make out with you.
It's a means to an end, Kim.
To serenity.
Whatever this is,
my best guess is
that it's transmitted
through saliva.
Something about that compels
to change
- to propagate it willingly.
- KURT: Oh my God.
MAC: He attacked me,
he tried to kiss me.
That's why we tied him
to the chair!
Oh. Oh, he tried to kiss
you. So how does that work?
Like a cold
that makes you different
but not really?
MAC: I don't know. I don't know.
He's from outer space.
What do you want from me?
Ask him!
W... what's the deal, Bill?
- You into guys now?
- You wouldn't believe me.
- KURT: Maybe I will.
- We're trying to help you.
KURT: We? Who's we? What?
Like little green men?
No, not exactly.
- I'm gonna put a stop to this.
- (Overlapping conversation)
Hey! Look, obviously,
he's got a screw loose.
- This can't be helping.
- KIM: Just listen!
You have no idea
what the fuck is goin' on.
- Stop!
- JANE: Oh my God!
KURT: I know. I know that you
and your loony wife put us
into this fucked-up situation.
MAC: He attacked me,
I didn't do anything!
KURT:
No, no, you attacked him.
(♪♪♪)
- KURT: You attacked him.
- MAC: That's not what happened.
KURT: Yeah, what do you drag
a 16-year-old into this mess?
MAC:
Oh, you give a shit about her.
Get off him!
Holy fuck, Jane. What the fuck?
I was attacked
by my supervisor.
And I've known him
for five years!
Then Bill attacks Mac.
We have to deal with whatever's
going on here, not you!
So fucking listen!
What does it mean to be changed?
What do you wanna
change us into?
I want to perfect you.
JANE:
How?
We have the power
to usher in the next incarnation
of your existence
on this plane.
JANE:
You're still not convinced?
KURT:
He's gotta be on drugs.
He's not the only person
acting that way.
That's what we're tryin'
to tell you.
All my friends, Uncle Kurt.
What would that be like
if we let you change us?
Perfect order.
Perfect satisfaction predicated
by perfect productivity.
We're gonna penetrate
each and every one of you
to reveal the face
that you failed to recognize.
Halcyon, days and nights,
and so on forever.
Perfect harmony,
perfect balance.
A peaceful coexistence
with every living creature
on this incredible,
organic machine.
Inside of each of you,
I can unlock the true potential
of humanity.
JANE: Okay,
so if you're not Bill anymore...
why shouldn't I put you down
like a rabid dog?
I am Bill.
Changed.
KURT: Look, um,
you put that gun down, Jane,
- or I'm gonna take it from you.
- Oh, Jane, Jane, Jane, Jane.
Come on.
I'm just tryin' to make a point.
Are you getting it?
MAC:
Back off. Settle down!
I'm settled.
(Bill clears throat)
Excuse me, but can I have
a glass of water, please?
Huh. Yeah, sure. Why not?
I'll get you some water.
- You got this?
- I got it.
Thank you.
(Sara vocalizing)
Hi.
MAC:
What do you want?
Why don't you come outside
so you can see me better?
MAC:
I can see you right now.
Look, I just hope I didn't
make you uncomfortable before.
MAC:
Nope, I'm fine.
You like what you saw?
MAC:
I didn't say that.
You can fuck me if you want to.
I don't mind.
And it'll change your life.
MAC:
Please, leave. Okay?
Just please, leave.
(Siren blaring in distance)
I said, "Go. Leave!"
(♪♪♪)
Mac, come on!
- Wait.
- They're gonna kill each other.
- Wait, what? What?
- Let's go!
(Overlapping conversation)
- Back up.
- Oh, you don't get it.
This is bullshit.
Shut the fuck up.
Really I'm warning you
I'm gonna show you how I shoot!
No, and there is no fucking
magic space virus!
JANE:
You want me to shoot you?
- Oh my God!
- You're a nurse, not a fucking...
You don't even know
what the fuck is going on!
- You're a nurse, not a doctor!
- Let go of me!
MAC:
Back off. Just stop!
There are people out there
right now,
definitely watching us.
What?
JANE:
See, something's happening.
MAC: It was that girl
from this morning.
Tried to get me to come outside.
JANE:
Sara.
MAC: Yeah, Kim saw her.
She tried to seduce me.
She's pulled the same stunt.
- JANE: Wait, just now?
- MAC: Just now.
I swear I saw people
hiding in the backyard.
Just before Jane got home.
- I'm gonna look for myself.
- MAC: Just wait!
They're gonna know
that we're onto them.
Uh, they're gonna see you.
Please, trust me.
They're sitting there
perfectly still
watching us for God knows what.
He knows.
(♪♪♪)
Tell us what's goin' on.
BILL: You promised
me a drink of water.
Who are you people?
We're changed.
And you can be, too.
Listen to me my neighbors...
Everything that
your friend Bill was, I am.
Only better.
Every detail,
every human experience
absorbed in perfect unity.
You have nothing to lose.
Everything to gain.
Come on! This is bullshit.
BILL: Mac,
how many times have you told me
that all you want
is the freedom to do
what you want,
when you want.
And I've watched you.
I've watched you pursue it.
Money, status, dreams.
And deep down, you know
it's all a damn lie.
There is no happiness
or freedom to be had.
Species as selfish
and aggressive as yours
will never find peace.
But if you join us,
you will have the answer
to every question that
you'll never care to ask again.
No more confusion or worry.
Desires gone.
No fear or doubt!
You will know certainty.
Tranquility.
Bliss.
You're gonna save us, huh?
Save us from ourselves?
BILL: The world as
you know it is over.
Be a part of this.
Be with us.
Mmhmm.
See, the way I see it,
you murdered my best friend.
KURT:
Mac, don't. No, come on.
You don't know what's
really goin' on out there.
I got a pretty goddamn
good idea.
Yeah, well, maybe
what you think is happening,
- it's... it's... it's all a hoax.
- MAC: Come on, Kurt.
KURT: Yeah, maybe...
maybe Bill's gone crazy.
No.
Whatever this soulless
piece of shit is, he's not Bill.
- Not anymore.
- Yeah, but what if you're wrong?
Okay, you cannot go around
just blowin' people's heads off.
If he's right, it's the end
of the world, right?
The rapture? Right, Bill?
- Right? Right, Bill?
- KURT: Mac!
Stop, Mac, stop it!
It isn't right!
I know you.
I know the peace you seek.
- Please.
- BILL: Be with us.
- Mac.
- Be a part of this.
(♪♪♪)
I need time out.
JANE:
Mac!
Okay, okay look, Kim.
I'm... I'm the one in charge now.
Whatever.
(Inhales, exhales)
BILL:
Kurt, can you kindly untie me?
Look you just..just keep
your fucking mouth shut.
Oh my God.
(♪♪♪♪)
(Breathing heavily)
You fuckin' know me?
Huh? You know what I want?
Huh? You think
you fuckin' know me, huh?
What are you gonna do, Mac?
What are you gonna do?
Fucking do?
I'll blow
your fuckin' head off! Fuck!
Oh my God, think, think, think,
think, think, think,
think, think.
Fuck.
Come on, Mac, figure it out.
Jesus. Fuck!
Everything's fine up here!
Everything's fine!
Okay. You got this.
Come on. You got this.
All right. You got this.
You got this.
(Breathing heavily)
What am I gonna do?
(♪♪♪)
There is no good reason
not to untie me.
I told you to shut up.
I'm thinking.
BILL: The energy in this
house has gotten still.
Don't you think so?
I mean, we could all use some...
Look, would you just
shut your mouth
for five goddamn seconds,
so I can figure out
- what to do?
- Both of you, shut up.
BILL: You and I are in
similar circumstances, Kurt.
Oh, you think so?
I'm not tied to a chair,
I haven't gone schizo.
Mac and Jane's position of power
and authority is limited
to this house.
- Do you understand that?
- No.
Divide and conquer.
- That's your plan?
- Oh my God.
Zen masters aren't above
that sort of thing?
Okay, none of this makes sense.
I... I need you to explain to me.
Explain to me
what's wrong with you.
I'm a changed man.
Yup, changed. That much I got.
(♪♪♪)
Please!
Tell me what you want.
(♪♪♪♪)
Have you come to join us, Kim?
(♪♪♪)
You guys are playin'
a prank on me, right?
Kim put you up to this?
Are you acting in accordance
with what you think is right?
Listen, I don't like
what's happening at all.
Any of it.
But there is definitely
something wrong with you.
Can you both stop talking?
What if your actions here
today, right now,
were placed under the scrutiny
of judgment?
If this isn't a prank,
I'm not responsible
for any of it.
I'm a victim, just like you.
Always suffering
for the deeds of others,
aren't you, Kurt?
Sleep is blindness.
You know the truth,
but you resent it.
You'll always be alone.
Loveless.
Loveless?
So, if I drink the Kool-Aid,
- all that's gonna change?
- BILL: Yes.
One kiss?
Yes.
Okay.
You are batshit crazy.
BILL: If you think that
my mental clarity is gone,
why don't you take me
to a doctor?
That would be
the right thing to do.
She won't let me.
The other loony's got the gun,
in case you missed that.
BILL:
That's all right, Kurt.
I know you're not the man
in charge here.
Hmm.
Are you changed?
Are you ready?
I don't know.
It feels like giving up.
It's not weakness.
It's strength to accept change.
Life is change.
Are you all connected?
The same mind?
No. We remain self-contained,
united in the pursuit
of absolute truth.
KIM:
I don't know, Sara.
What we offer is clarity
in the deepest sense,
unburdened by concepts
of good and evil.
The changed don't see
moral categories
as a force to resist
but as opaqueness.
You remain yourself,
yet like a lens wiped clean,
the light can shine through.
So all that I am remains?
SARA:
Yes.
I need you to promise me
that I'll still be me.
Why would you want that?
Your desire to stay what you are
is what limits you.
But you are different.
You are.
You're brave,
that's why you're here now.
The others?
What I am,
what you'll become,
would be incomprehensible
to them, except as gods.
(Breathing heavily)
(♪♪♪)
All right.
JANE:
Mac, get the fuck down here!
Mac!
You're making
the right decision, Kim.
(ECHOING)
Kiss me, Kim.
And it'll happen.
I can't.
(♪♪♪)
Kim.
Don't fight it when it comes.
(♪♪♪)
Soon.
MAC:
Just listen.
Can you fuckin' listen for once?
KURT:
No!
(Indistinct conversation)
MAC: How many times do we
need to go through this?
- Guys, just settle down!
- (Overlapping conversation)
KURT:
Who the fuck put you in charge?
Calm down, huh?
KURT: Oh, well, no,
easy for you to say.
You're the one with a shotgun!
Everybody gets a gun
but Kurt, right?
We shoot skeet,
we're not a gun show!
- KIM: Stop fighting!
- We have two guns!
KIM: Did any of you
even notice I was gone?
KURT:
You know what? Fuck this.
You're on your own.
And when you're done
torturing him,
you better find a good lawyer,
because I'm gonna
throw the book at you two.
This one's gone wackadoo
and she's a fuckin' minor.
MAC: Are you talkin'
about lawyers right now?
- You can't be this dense.
- KURT: Come on, Kim.
This isn't our problem.
Not anymore.
KIM:
It's not safe out there.
KURT:
I'm goin', with or without you.
MAC: Are you serious?
JANE: Really?
You're gonna leave your
niece. That's your solution.
KURT: If the world is
ending, and it's not,
it's gonna end for me
in the comfort
of my own home.
MAC:
Are you kidding?
With everything
you've seen and heard?
KIM:
Listen!
All of you just shut up
and listen!
I went out there.
I talked to Sara.
One of my friends from school
was there, too.
Sara asked to change me
and I thought about it.
- I really thought about it.
- MAC: Why?
Why wouldn't I?
Look at the alternative!
- MAC: Are you serious?
- JANE: Kim.
- Hey, I didn't, did I?
- BILL: You will.
It's only natural to fear
what you don't understand.
But you want to understand, Kim.
KURT:
Jesus Christ.
We do not know for sure
what is really goin' on
out there, if anything.
I just told you what's going on!
They know we're in here
and they're coming in after us!
I told you they were out there.
Wait, she just said
they're coming in after us?
- Basically.
- JANE: When?
Soon.
JANE: Are your people
going to attack?
There is a timeline.
KURT: Oh, Kim.
Kim, you need to mind me, okay?
So let's go now.
KIM: Uncle Kurt, even if you
don't, the rest of us know
this has been building up
for at least a month.
For whatever reason,
you're still you
and I'm still me,
but we're in the minority now.
We need to stick together.
MAC:
Kurt.
JANE:
Come on.
KURT:
I'm done.
Stay here. Come with me.
I don't give a shit.
KIM:
Uncle Kurt!
JANE:
Go ahead, I'm right behind you.
(♪♪♪♪)
Go ahead, Judas.
Say somethin' smart.
You do anything while I'm gone,
I'll be the one
to blow your head off.
Behave.
MAC:
Don't go out there, Kurt! Stop.
They're out there, hiding.
They're not just gonna
let you walk home.
- Don't be an idiot.
- I'm the idiot?
This is all an elaborate hoax,
- you'll see.
- It's not a hoax.
KURT: Tomorrow, you'll see!
Or else you're all prankin' me!
Why don't you just admit
you're scared, Uncle Kurt?
I'm scared, too.
We all are!
MAC: Don't go out there.
Don't do this.
KIM:
What's wrong with you?
You're the only one
who doesn't get it.
What, you wanna go home
and sit on your ass?
Who do you think
you're talkin' to?
Just like your useless
bitch of a mother slut,
gets herself knocked up
and for the rest of my life
that makes you my problem!
I'm goin' home now
to sit on my ass!
MAC:
Hey, hey!
JANE:
No, Mac.
KURT:
Hey, what...
Hey, you, stop, stop,
stop right there, okay?
Just stop. Just back off!
All of you, just...
just back off!
What do you want?
You... you want people?
There's people right...
right there in that house.
Get them.
Right there, get them!
Those people in that house!
I didn't do anything.
- We need to do something.
- No. No.
No, Mac.
- KURT: Oh, let go!
- He asked for this.
KURT:
Oh!
You asked for this.
(♪♪♪)
- I should have helped him.
- No.
There's nothing
we could have done.
I don't know how to feel.
He seems okay.
He's not dead.
Looks like it was painless.
Maybe I should have done it,
too.
- Sara made it sound pretty cool.
- No.
You're better than that, Kim.
Gee, thanks dad.
I don't know why you
wanna change who you are.
We think you're pretty awesome.
Thanks, but my life sucks.
Not like Sara.
She graduated
when I was a freshman.
Different crowd. Popular.
We hardly knew each other.
Now, she was nice to me.
Being a teenager sucks.
Yeah, Kim. You can be right.
They... they seem to have it
better than us.
Peaceful.
But rewinding
the last few weeks in my head,
knowing who's who,
who's changed,
and pretty much when...
it's like they have no souls.
They're missing that spark.
You know,
they're livin' life
right alongside you.
But you're not in it alone.
Just like Bill.
Empty.
I'm not ready to give up.
Life's hard.
And whatever they are,
they may change
every single last one of us.
They're gonna find that out
soon enough.
Good news, Bill.
We're walkin' you out of here.
JANE: It'd be wise if
you keep your mouth shut.
Don't give us any trouble.
And tell your friends
the next one of you clones
comes to the door,
try something funny,
I'll start shooting.
Consider it self-defense.
Nah. No,
you're not gonna shoot me.
JANE: You're not
gonna take my soul.
Fear clouds the mind
and the spirit,
binds the concept
of the soul to the body.
The ego.
JANE:
Who says I'm afraid?
(Sighs)
You all are afraid.
Every one of you.
Every day of your life.
- MAC: Jane!
- (Gun blares)
- Jesus, Jane.
- Stay away.
(Grunts)
MAC:
Are you changed?
Yes.
You, motherfucker.
- KIM: Mac, wait.
- (Gun blares)
(♪♪♪♪)
- Jane.
- (Takes a deep breath)
Everything's gonna be fine, Mac.
Are you in pain?
I feel pain.
But pain no longer controls me.
I control it.
Jane, what am I supposed to do?
What I wanna
help you understand
is pain.
The pain I feel right now.
Fear.
Confusion.
Doubt.
No longer cover my actions.
Jane, what do I do?
Join us.
Kiss me.
If I do?
Cellular organisms...
are passed through saliva.
We inhabit our hosts...
(Groans)
...become one.
(Takes a deep breath)
Is this what you want?
All this chaos?
Bill was telling us the truth.
I've been given
an enlightenment.
An understanding.
Where are you things from?
(Whimpers)
You know I don't wanna
be changed.
Change is inevitable.
Kiss me.
I can't. I won't.
I'm losing a lot of blood, Mac.
(Takes a deep breath)
I wanna live.
That much about us
remains the same.
No. No, we're not the same.
Join us.
Or die.
Oh.
Just realize I am dying now.
Jane.
You're gonna help me save Jane.
Come here.
- Mac.
- Come here.
- I don't wanna kill anybody.
Break it open.
Shove a shell in.
Close it.
Pull back the trigger.
Shoot.
You do it again.
You understand?
You've been brave
since I've known you.
Strong.
I need you to be
that girl for me now.
She needs help, she's been shot!
What are you waiting for?
We'll get her medical attention.
MAC:
You better.
Give me a reason
to bash your fuckin' head in.
I wanna apologize to you,
Kimberly.
I know I've always
treated you poorly.
KIM: Would have been nice
if you realized that sooner.
I know.
I've changed.
Join us.
KIM:
I don't wanna be some clone.
I wanna be me.
MAC: You heard her?
Now fuck off!
You fuckers.
(♪♪♪)
You okay?
Yeah.
(♪♪♪)
(Loud banging in distance)
(Sobbing)
(Banging)
(♪♪♪)
When they start comin' in...
I shoot first.
And you go while I reload,
okay?
Not much.
It's us or them.
(♪♪♪♪)
What if I can't?
Well, then we're dead.
Or you lose everything
that you are.
I don't know what to tell you.
Nothing in life
that's worthwhile is easy.
It is the struggle and the fight
that makes us who we are.
They wanna exist through us.
And you're exhausted, I see it.
So am I.
And they're gonna use that,
so that we disappear into them.
Life doesn't make any sense.
But neither does that.
(♪♪♪♪)
MAC:
Kurt's one of them.
They took Jane from us.
Those fuckers
changed everything.
This is it, Kim.
Us or them.
(♪♪♪)
I'll fight with you.
What else can I do?
(♪♪♪)
(Cellphone rings)
I'm Katie Walters,
a face you know and trust.
Now changed, for the better.
I'm asking for your trust now.
If you're watching
this broadcast,
you represent
the small percentage
of those still unaffected
by the historical
and metaphysical change
your species is experiencing
across the globe.
By this time tomorrow,
there will be no one like you
left anywhere.
I'm sure this confuses
and frightens you.
I'm here to quiet your mind.
Those you know and love,
those who have already
crossed over
have experienced no pain,
no discomfort.
They are alive and well,
just as they were before.
And now each of them
reborn with fearless purpose
and moral certainty.
For you,
a kiss is never free of desire.
We simply desire
to give you more.
One kiss awakens belonging.
No sorrow, no questions,
no fear.
We ask that you
open your hearts and homes
to those who will initiate
your transition.
Please open your doors
to them now.
Discover your deepest clarity.
The alternative?
Those who continue to resist
will be taken by force
at sunrise.
Individuality
and the interest of self
will not be tolerated.
We admire your species.
Your utilitarian physical form,
your adaptive nature,
your inquisitive minds.
We know you will make
the right choice to join us.
I'm Katie Walters.
Thank you and good night.
Hello, viewers.
I'm K...
What are we gonna do?
Kill 'em all.
- (Sniffles)
- Tell me again how I'm strong.
I've never seen you
cry before tonight.
Big girls don't cry.
That's what mom always says.
I hope she's okay.
Maybe.
I'm with you, Mac.
I'm sorry this happened to you.
You got your whole life
ahead of you.
Not anymore.
Yeah, well, maybe you should
go out there
and do it like you said.
Don't be a jerk.
I had a moment of weakness.
That's all.
Fair enough.
(Siren blaring in distance)
Let me see you reload.
Good. Do it again.
Good. Don't forget
to pull the hammer back.
Not right now.
Do it again.
All right, shoulder it. Aim it.
Aim it like you mean it.
You ready to do it?
All right. Good.
Good.
(♪♪♪)
Maybe we should play a game.
It might make us feel better.
A game?
A list.
Things that
make life worth living.
Whatever you can think of.
No rules.
All right, fine.
I'll start.
(Chuckles)
Meat ball grinder.
The smell of Jane's hair.
Winning the IM.
(Chuckles)
Getting drunk
on a Sunday afternoon.
Junior prom.
Drivin' fast.
Really fast.
Sleeping all day.
Punk rock.
Summer vacation.
Livin' life.
Just livin'.
That's what I was gonna say.
(♪♪♪)
(Sirens blaring in distance)
This is it.
You know what?
Just go out the back.
I got this.
But they're back there, too.
Hiding.
Probably have us surrounded.
MAC:
Yeah, right.
I didn't want you to go.
(♪♪♪)
No point waiting.
God hates a coward.
I go out first. I shoot first.
Get behind me.
Let's go.
Guess what?
(Gun blares)
(♪♪♪)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ God reached his hand
down from the sky ♪
♪ He flooded the land
and he set it afire ♪
♪ He said, fear me again,
know I'm your father ♪
♪ Remember that no one
can breathe underwater ♪
(♪♪♪♪)
♪ So bend your knees
and bow your heads ♪
♪ Save your babies,
here's your future ♪
♪ Yeah, here's your future ♪
♪ God reached his hand
down from the sky ♪
♪ God asked Noah
if he wanted to die ♪
♪ He said, no sir,
oh, no sir ♪
♪ God said,
here's your future ♪
♪ It's gonna rain ♪
♪ So we're packing our things,
we're buildin' a boat ♪
♪ We're gonna create
the new master race ♪
♪ 'Cause we're so pure ♪
♪ Oh lord, we're so pure ♪
♪ So here's your future ♪
♪ God told his son,
it's time to come home ♪
♪ I promise you won't have
to die all alone ♪
♪ I need you to pay
for the sins I create ♪
♪ The son said, I will,
but dad, I'm afraid ♪
(♪♪♪♪)
♪ Yeah, so here's your future ♪
♪ So here's your future ♪
♪ Yeah, here's your future ♪