♪♪ [ P.A.: Instrumental, Faint ]
[ Chattering, Faint ]
[ Chattering Continues ]
[ Man ] I'M SERIOUS.
SORRY.SORRY.
WOW, THIS IS REALLY COOL.
YOU HAVE A CAR ?
UH, YEAH,
I-- I HAVE A CAR.
SURFER GAS PEDAL.
YOU A SURFER ?
WELL, I USED TO LIVE
IN OSAKA IN-IN JAPAN,
AND I USED TO SURF THERE,
BUT-- BUT NOT HERE THOUGH.
WELL, THERE'S NOT REALLY
ANYWHERE TO SURF
AROUND HERE, SO--
WELL, I DON'T MIND,
REALLY.WHY ?
'CAUSE I CAN HAVE A CAR HERE.
I COULDN'T HAVE A CAR IN JAPAN.
THEY DON'T LET YOU
LEARN HOW TO DRIVE TILL
YOU'RE 18,
SO I COULDN'T HAVE
A CAR THERE.YOU MISS SURFING ?
NO, I MEAN, THAT'S-THAT'S
NOT WHY I GOT THAT.
I JUST THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE FUNNY BECAUSE MY CAR'S
NOT A SURFER CAR AT ALL.
IT'S NOT LIKE
A VOLKSWAGEN.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S A PLYMOUTH.
A GRAN FURY.
OH. HOW LONG
HAVE YOU HAD IT ?
IT'S RIGHT HERE.
CAN WE PUT IN
THE SURFER GAS PEDAL ?YEAH, SURE.
DO YOU THINK IT'LL LOOK COOL
OR JUST STUPID ?
WHY WOULD IT LOOK STUPID ?
YOU HAVE A SCREWDRIVER ?YEAH.
WHY DON'T YOU GET ONE ?OKAY.
[ Horns Honking ]
DUMB TRUNK,
TRUNK, TRUNK.
CAN I KEEP THIS ?
YEAH, SURE.
ACTUALLY,
I'D BE REALLY HAPPY
IF-IF YOU TOOK IT.
CAN I GIVE YOU
A RIDE SOMEWHERE ?
YEAH, YOU CAN
BRING ME TO WORK.OKAY.
[ Man ]
SO, THIS IS IT ?
DEPARTMENT OF SANITATION ?
MY UNCLE'S
HEAD OF THE DEPARTMENT.
MY DAD MAKES ME WORK WEEKENDS.
SUCKS ASS.
WOW.
MY NAME'S SETH.I'M MARCY.
OH, THAT'S COOL.
UH--
SON OF A BITCH !
SORRY.
SORRY. SORRY.
[ Man On Television ] THE MALE COCKROACH CAN LIVE OFF ITS MATE'S HUSK FOR SIX MONTHS,
UNTIL THE LARVAE HATCH AND THE MALE MOVES TO ITS OFFSPRING'S FLESH FOR WINTER.
SETH ! TURN OFF
THE GODDAMN DOOR !
[ Glass Clinking ]
WHERE THE FUCK
HAVE YOU BEEN ?
I'M HUNGRY. HUH ?
I WAS
JUST DRIVING AROUND.YEAH ?
WHAT'S THIS ?
HUH ?
YOU'VE BEEN AT THE STORE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AT THE STORE
FOR THREE GODDAMN HOURS ?
HUH ?YOU HUNGRY ?
YOU WANT ME TO MAKE--
DON'T GET WISE WITH ME.
YOU GOTTA GIVE ME
A RIDE TO NICK'S.
MY TRANSMISSION'S BROKE.
WELL, THEN YOU
OUGHT TO GET RID OF
THAT PIECE OF SHIT.
YOU GOTTA GIVE ME
A RIDE TO NICK'S.
I SAID, YOU GOTTA GIVE ME
THEN CALL ME A CAB.
CALL ME A CAB ! [ Door Locks ]
THEN I'LL CALL A CAB MYSELF.
I'VE GOT DIALING PRIVILEGES, YOU SON OF A BITCH !
HELLO, OPERATOR, I'VE GOT DIALING PRIVILEGES.
I WANT YOU TO CALL ME A CAB.
SUNRISE TAXI. I'VE GOT DIALING-- I WANT YOU TO DIAL IT !
[ Rattling Phone ]
♪ WHY DOES PAIN FAIL
♪ WHERE DOES IT GO
♪ IT'S LESS PERILOUS
♪ THAN SOUTHERN SNOW
♪ WHY DO I WAIT
♪ ONCE A YEAR
♪ BRING YOUR SORROW
♪ OVER HERE ♪
[ Chattering ] ♪♪ [ P.A.: Instrumental ]
HI.
IT REALLY PISSES ME OFF THAT THEY DON'T HAVE ANY BLACK BOBBIE HEADS IN THIS PLACE.
NOBODY CARRIES THEM
AROUND HERE.
YOU JUST WANT THE HEAD ?YEAH, YOU KNOW,
JUST THE HEAD ON THE STAND.
YOU CAN DO THEIR HAIR
AND MAKEUP AND STUFF.
JUST THE BUST.
THEY HAVE THE WHITE ONE,
WHICH I ALREADY HAVE,
BUT NO BLACK ONE.
MAYBE THEY'LL ORDER ONE.I WANT THE STORE TO HAVE IT.
THEY SHOULD HAVE IT.
THEY PROBABLY DON'T THINK
ANYONE WOULD WANT ONE.
THERE'S NOT THAT MANY
BLACK PEOPLE AROUND HERE.
THERE ARE BLACK PEOPLE
EVERYWHERE AROUND HERE.
THEY'RE JUST TOO FUCKING STUPID
AND RACIST TO ORDER THEM.
YEAH, THEY ARE RACIST.
THEY ALSO PROBABLY THINK
THAT IF THEY DID HAVE
BLACK BOBBIE HEADS,
THEY'D REALLY STAND OUT
AND LOOK REALLY RACIST...
BECAUSE THEY'D BE
THE ONLY BLACK THINGS
IN THE STORE.
WHATEVER. COME WITH ME.
I HAVE A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
I LIKE YOUR CAR.
IT LOOKS LIKE AN UNDERCOVER
POLICE CAR, I THINK.
WELL, YEAH, YOU KNOW,
IT USED TO BE A REGULAR
POLICE CAR,
BUT I GUESS IT IS LIKE
AN UNDERCOVER ONE NOW.
IT'S LIKE THE ONES
YOU SEE WAITING AT THE LIGHT.
THEY GET IMPATIENT,
FLIP THE SIREN,
THEN DRIVE RIGHT THROUGH,
WHICH TOTALLY BLOWS
THEIR COVER.
IT'S NOT LIKE THEIR COVER
ISN'T BLOWN AWAY.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT COPS
ALWAYS DRIVE GRAN FURYS
NO MATTER WHAT.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS THEY DRIVE
OTHER KINDS OF CARS TOO.
PARK OVER THERE IN THE MIDDLE
OF ALL THOSE TRUCKS.
IS YOUR WHOLE FAMILY
IN THE GARBAGE BUSINESS ?
IT'S REALLY SMART...
SEEING THAT EVERYBODY'S
GOT GARBAGE.
DEPARTMENT OF SANITATION
OFFICIAL VEHICLE NUMBER 5309.
YOU CAN KEEP THE STICKER
AND PARK HERE WHENEVER
YOU WANT NOW.
THANK YOU.
I CAN GET YOU ANOTHER ONE,
IF YOU WANT ONE.
NO, I MEAN,
I ONLY HAVE ONE CAR.
IT'S THE NICEST PRESENT
ANYONE'S EVER GIVEN ME.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES,
WHEN I'M SAYING SOMETHING,
AND IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT,
I CAN'T LOOK AT THE PERSON
THAT I'M TALKING TO.
I JUST THINK IT'S REALLY GREAT
THAT YOU CAN'T DO THAT EITHER.
I REALLY WANT YOU TO HAVE
THAT BLACK BOBBIE HEAD.
THEN LET'S GO GET ONE.
LET'S GO TO TORONTO. IN CANADA ?
WE HAVE TO GO TO A BIG CITY,
AND ALL THE NEAREST
BIG CITIES ARE IN CANADA.
I CAN'T GO TO MONTREAL BECAUSE I CAN'T SPEAK FRENCH.
PLEASE, TELL ME
YOU CAN'T SPEAK FRENCH.
NO, NO,
I-I CAN'T SPEAK FRENCH.
I NEVER WANTED TO GO TO CANADA
WITH ANYONE BEFORE IN MY LIFE.
YEAH, ME NEITHER.I'LL PAY FOR GAS.
SO, WE'RE JUST GONNA GO ?YEP.
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Glass Shattering ]
CAN WE STOP BY MY HOUSE BEFORE WE GO TO CANADA SO WE CAN GET SOME CLOTHES ?
YEAH, SURE.
PROBABLY BE A GOOD IDEA
TO BRING SOME CLOTHES.
WE WON'T HAVE TO STOP
BY YOUR HOUSE. I WANT YOU
TO WEAR MY CLOTHES.
IS THAT OKAY ?
YEAH. YEAH, SURE.
WOW. OH,
THIS IS YOUR HOUSE ?
YEAH.
WHERE SHOULD I PARK ?
HELLO ?
[ Grunts ]
I THINK MY DAD'S UPSTAIRS
TAKING A NAP.
MOM'S PROBABLY
AT THE DENTIST.
DOES YOUR MOM GO
TO THE DENTIST A LOT ?
YEAH, SHE THINKS
SHE HAS REALLY BAD TEETH.
YOU HAVE
REALLY NICE TEETH.
I MEAN, I-I JUST THINK
THAT Y-YOUR TEETH ARE NICE.
I LIKE YOUR TEETH.
I LIKE HOW THE BOTTOM ONE
IS CROOKED. IT'S COOL.
THANKS. I THINK YOURS
ARE MUCH NICER THOUGH.
ARE YOU HUNGRY ?
FUCK.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY DONUTS.
YOU WANT A DRINK ?
UH, NO, THANKS.
WE'VE GOT A LONG DRIVE.
WH-- OH, THAT ONE--
THAT ONE HAS A HOLE IN IT.
YOU LIKE CHEESE ?SURE.
ALL RIGHTY.
OH, PUT THAT IN HERE.SURE.
WELL, WHERE
ARE WE GOING ?MY ROOM.
WOW, THIS IS YOURS ?YEP.
YOU KNOW, I WISH WE HAD
ONE OF THOSE FUZZ BUSTER
THINGS,
SO WE COULD DRIVE
REALLY FAST THE WHOLE WAY.
YEAH.
YOU'VE GOT THIS WHOLE
HORSE THEME GOING ON HERE.
YEAH, I REALLY LIKE 'EM. I USED TO HAVE A HORSE.
COULD YOU TRY ON
MY CLOTHES NOW, PLEASE ?
SURE.
COULD YOU PULL OVER
AT THE NEXT LIQUOR STORE ?
I NEED TO GET SOME WHISKEY.
REALLY ?YEAH, I'M THIRSTY.
[ Chattering ]
[ Man ]
YEAH, SHE WAS
ALL OVER THAT SHIT.
YEAH. I TOLD YOU IT WAS
GONNA HAPPEN, MAN.
WHAT I REALLY WANNA KNOW IS
WHAT IS UP WITH THAT GUY ?FUCKING RAINCOAT.
NICE RAINCOAT !
HI, HOW YA DOING ?
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE ME
ONE OF THOSE POCKET COMBS;
TWO OF THOSE HERBAL UPS,
THE GREEN ONES;
A ZIPPO,
THIRD ONE FROM THE LEFT,
AND A PACK OF PHILLYS.
WHAT ABOUT LOTTERY TICKETS ?
YOU HAVE ANY LOTTERY TICKETS ?
NO ? OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, I HAVE TO SEE
SOME SORT OF I.D. NOW.
OKAY, WE'VE GOT
FOUR BOTTLES HERE.
I'LL PUT TWO OVER HERE.
WE'RE EVEN.
I'LL GIVE YOU, UH,
18 BUCKS, ALL RIGHT ?
[ Stammering ] N-NO.TWENTY BUCKS ?
TWENTY BUCKS.
THAT DOESN'T DO ANYTHING.
YOU UNDERSTAND ?
I NEED TO SEE VALID I.D.
REAL I.D.
I HAVE A REAL I.D. I'VE GOT A DRIVER'S LICENSE.
THIS IS MY HUSBAND.
WE'VE GOT OUR KIDS
IN THE CAR. HURRY.
YOU GOTTA BE 21 TO BUY WHISKEY.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND, 21 ? OKAY.
YOU'RE NOT 21.
I CANNOT SELL YOU WHISKEY.
WELL, CAN I HAVE THAT BACK ?I THINK YOU BETTER GO
BEFORE I CALL THE POLICE.
OKAY, BUT THAT'S
MY REAL LICENSE.
I NEED THAT TO DRIVE WITH.
I DON'T THINK SO.OKAY.
HEY, MARCY !
HEY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE GOT IT BACK.
I'VE NEVER BEEN CARDED
IN THAT PLACE BEFORE,
ALL RIGHT ?
UH-OH, GUYS,
IT'S RAINING OUTSIDE.
EXCUSE ME,
YOU FUCKING ASSHOLE.
HUH ?
W-WHAT'D YOU SAY ?
[ Grunts ]WHOA.
WHAT IS THAT,
LIKE, PUNK ROCK ?FUCK OFF, SHITHEAD.
WHOA-OA-OA. WHOA, MAN,
THERE WILL BE NO CUSSING
IN FRONT OF THE LADIES.
YEAH, WATCH YOUR LANGUAGE.
YOU'VE GOT A FILTHY MOUTH.
NOT AS FILTHY
AS YOUR PUSSY, CUNT.
FUCKING CUNT.
- [ Seth ] MARCY.
- LOOK BUSY.
I'M FINE, I'M FINE,
I'M FINE.
WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING AT, BITCH ?
I'M FINE.GET IN.
[ Marcy ] AT THIS TIME, NOBODY REALLY KNEW WHAT IT WAS YET.
I COULDN'T EVEN GO TO SCHOOL WITHOUT CAUSING A TOTAL RIOT.
I'D SPEND MOST OF THE DAY
INCREDIBLY-- NOISILY--
MAKING SURE MY CHAIR WAS
EXACTLY IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE ROOM...
FROM EVERY ANGLE
AND PERSPECTIVE POSSIBLE.
WHAT ?IT IS OKAY THAT I USED
YOUR TOOTHBRUSH, ISN'T IT ?
MM-HMM.THANKS.
WHEN I GOT THE CHAIR THERE,
IT WOULDN'T COUNT...
UNLESS I TAPPED THIS AMAZING
DRUMROLL ON THE BACK OF
THE GIRL-IN-FRONT-OF-ME'S HEAD.
WHICH, OF COURSE,
WOULD MAKE HER CONSTANTLY
FREAK OUT AND COMPLAIN.
HM, HM, HM, HM,
HM, HM, HM, HM.
ALL THE KIDS I WENT
TO GRAMMAR SCHOOL WITH HAD THESE
FUCKED-UP NICKNAMES FOR ME.
CALLED ME "MENTAL MARCY"
AND "SPAZZY" AND "TWITCHY."
SO, FINALLY, MY DAD TOOK ME
TO THIS DOCTOR IN SYRACUSE...
WHO SAID I WAS
A BIOPSYCHOSOCIOPATH...
AND THAT I HAD
TOURETTE'S SYNDROME.
SOUNDS AWFUL.
SOUNDS LIKE A REAL DRAG. [ Bottles Clinking ]
IT'S NOT, REALLY.
I MEAN--
NOW IT'S JUST
KIND OF PART OF WHO I AM.
I'M USED TO IT.
ALL THE TOUCHING AND SHOUTING
AND ALL THAT STUFF.
IT SCARES THE SHIT OUT OF PEOPLE
'CAUSE EVERYBODY WHO HAS
TOURETTE DOES DIFFERENT THINGS.
I HAVE, UH, LIKE, THE--
I HAVE THESE MUSCLE TICS.
LIKE TENSING UP
AND MY HEAD GOES BACK.
I ALSO HAVE THIS THING
CALLED ECHOLALIA,
WHICH IS WHEN YOU HAVE
TO REPEAT THE SAME WORD
OVER AND OVER...
UNTIL YOU FEEL LIKE,
IN YOUR THROAT, THAT--
ACTUALLY, IT'S LIKE I HAVE THIS ITCH INSIDE OF ME, AND IF I DON'T TIC...
OR SAY THE WORD EXACTLY
THE WAY I NEED TO SAY IT,
I JUST FEEL LIKE
I'M GONNA FUCKING EXPLODE. REALLY ?
YEAH, IT'S NOT LIKE
I WANNA DO THIS STUFF.
I-- I HAVE TO.
SO, MOST OF THE TIME,
I JUST DRINK A LOT BECAUSE
THAT'S WHAT HELPS THE MOST.
WELL, DOESN'T
ANYTHING ELSE HELP ?
SEX HELPS.
FOR SOME REASON,
UM, SO THAT WAS--
THAT WAS, LIKE,
AN ATTACK,
WHAT HAPPENED BACK THERE
WITH THOSE GUYS
IN THE PARKING LOT ?
WE WERE HANGING OUT TOGETHER
ALL DAY LONG,
AND I WAS TRYING TO HOLD IN
MY TICS 'CAUSE I DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO SEE ME DO IT.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO SCARE YOU
OR ANYTHING.
AND SO, I-- I HELD THEM IN
FOR A REALLY LONG TIME,
AND WHEN THOSE GUYS
STARTED FUCKING WITH YOU,
I JUST KIND OF FLIPPED OUT.
I'M SORRY.
THAT STUFF'S CALLED
AGGRESSIVE EXPLOSIVE BEHAVIOR.
I DO THAT SHIT ALL THE TIME.
NOT ALL THE TIME,
BUT SOMETIMES I DO IT.
RARELY, I DO IT.
ARE-- ARE YOU OKAY
AND EVERYTHING ?
DO YOU WANT ME TO GO GET YOU
A SOUP OR SOMETHING ?
I CAN'T HELP IT.
THAT'S ALL.
I HAVEN'T NOTICED
ANYTHING AT ALL.
THAT'S JUST 'CAUSE
I'M REALLY GOOD AT MAKING IT
LOOK NORMAL.
LIKE, I INCORPORATE MY TICS
INTO SOMETHING NATURAL.
LIKE, I'LL--
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT I DO.
OR I'LL GO LIKE THAT
AND I'LL FIX MY HAIR.
I DID THAT TO YOU, RIGHT ?
YEAH.
ALSO, HALDOL.
THAT'S THE MEDICATION
THAT I TAKE FOR IT. THAT HELPS.
IT DIDN'T MAKE MY TICS
GO AWAY.
IT MADE ME HAVE THEM LESS
THAN I USUALLY WOULD.
SO, DOES IT FREAK YOU OUT ?
NO, NOT AT ALL.GOOD.
[ Grunts ]
SO, UH, WHAT WAS THAT
THAT YOU TOOK BACK
AT THE LIQUOR STORE ?
I DIDN'T TAKE ANYTHING.OH, YOU DIDN'T ?
[ Chuckling ]
YES, YOU DID.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU ACTUALLY SAW THAT. WELL.
[ Chuckling ]WHAT IS IT ?
I'M NOT AS SMOOTH
AS I USED TO BE.
YOU'RE GETTING SLOPPY
IN YOUR OLD AGE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
THERE YOU GO.THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
♪ TWO UP ON THE CROSS
♪ THEIR PAINS, THEIR LIVES  THEIR HURTS ♪
SORRY.NO, NO.
♪ CHANCE ONE TURNS AWAY
♪ ARE THEY FOREVER LOST
♪ YES, I BELIEVE  THAT THERE'S A POINT ♪
♪ TO WHAT WE DO
♪ BUT I ASK MYSELF
♪ IS THIS SOMETHING MORE  BESIDE YOU ♪♪
IF WE HAVE A BABY,
WE HAVE TO NAME HIM
SETH, JUNIOR.
OKAY, BUT IF WE HAVE
A LITTLE GIRL, WE HAVE TO
NAME HER MARCY, JUNIOR.
IT'S NOT
GONNA BE A GIRL.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
HANG ON.
IS THAT EVERYTHING ?YEAH.
GOOD.
♪ YOU'RE THE ONE  YOU'RE MY SHINING STAR ♪
♪ YOU'RE THE ONE  I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR ♪
♪ LET'S FLY AWAY
♪ TO SOME FOREIGN COUNTRY
♪ WHERE NOBODY KNOWS  WHO WE ARE ♪ [ Dinging ]
♪ I WISH I HAD A SHIP  TO SAIL THE WATERS ♪
♪ I WISH I HAD ABOUT  A HUNDRED DOLLARS ♪
♪ BUT I JUST STAND  WITH THIS-- ♪♪
[ Both Laughing ]
IF YOU'RE EVER GONNA FIND
THOSE PILLS, YOU'LL PROBABLY
FIND THEM HERE.
WHY ?'CAUSE IT'S DOUG'S DRUGS.
CAN YOU IMAGINE ?
WHAT IF HE HAD A RUG STORE ?
"DOUG'S RUGS."
DOUG'S RUGS.
[ Laughing, Groans ]
I'M SORRY.IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT HAPPENS
ALL THE TIME.
[ Pharmacist ]
YES. THERE'S REALLY NOTHING
THAT I CAN DO.
HI, I WOULD LIKE
100 HALOPERIDAL
AND 50 COGENTIN.
DO YOU TAKE VISA ?YES.
ALL RIGHTY.[ Sighs ]
OH, UH, CAN I SEE
YOUR PRESCRIPTION, PLEASE ?
OH, YEAH, SURE.
THIS IS A PRESCRIPTION
FOR MOTRIN.
OH, IS IT ?YEAH.
I MUST'VE LEFT THE OTHER ONE
IN MY OTHER PURSE.
I CAN'T DISPENSE HALOPERIDAL WITHOUT A PRESCRIPTION.
IT'S A CLASS ONE,
NEUROLEPTIC.
I THINK YOU'RE MAKING
A BIG MISTAKE.
THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO.
CAN I SPEAK TO DOUG,
PLEASE ?
I AM DOUG.
WELL, LISTEN, DOUG,
I HAVE A NEUROLOGICAL DISORDER
CALLED TOURETTE'S SYNDROME,
AND I'VE BEEN TAKING
THIS MEDICATION SINCE I WAS
A LITTLE KID.
I DON'T LIVE AROUND HERE,
SO COULD YOU, PLEASE,
JUST FILL IT FOR ME ?
I REALLY NEED IT,
DOUG.
COULD YOU HAVE YOUR DOCTOR
GIVE ME A CALL ?
THANKS.
[ Marcy ]
JUST BLOW IT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST GET
A DOCTOR TO DO THAT.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW DIFFICULT IT WOULD BE...
TO FIND A DOCTOR TO DIAGNOSE ME IN "COW MANEUVERS," NEW YORK.
IT WOULD BE LIKE DOUG.
DOUG. DOUG'S A DICK.
SORRY, I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY TO THAT GUY.
WELL, YOU JUST--
YOU WALK UP WITH A COMPLETELY
STRAIGHT LOOK ON YOUR FACE,
AND YOU SAY, "HERE.
HERE'S MY FUCKING PRESCRIPTION."
CAN YOU, PLEASE,
FUCKING FILL IT FOR ME ?
YOU CAN'T SAY "FUCK."[ Gasps ]
SURE YOU DO.
YOU-- YOU SAY, "FUCK."
FUCK, FUCK.
FUCK !FUCK.
EXCUSE ME, DOUG. FUCK.
GIVE ME SOME DRUGS.
FUCK. GIVE ME MY
FUCKING DRUGS, DOUG.JUST STOP !
DOUG.
OOH.
♪ I WAS DRUNK  BUT I'M SO SOBER NOW ♪
♪ HE WAS THERE  AND HE WAS HERE ♪
♪ IT WAS FATE  THAT MADE US SPEAK ♪
[ Chattering ] ♪ I REMEMBER
♪ BUT I'M SO MUCH OLDER NOW ♪
THANK YOU, GIRLY.
WHOO, YOU'RE REALLY SUCKING
THAT DOWN. YOU WANT ANOTHER ?MM-HMM. THANK YOU.
MONEY'S ON THE TABLE,
SALLY. SEE YOU, TOM !
THANKS AGAIN, SAL.
HEY, THE BACK OF YOUR HEAD
IS SHOWING.
[ Laughing ]
UH, DIDN'T YOUR MOM WANT US
TO GO TO THE LIQUOR STORE
AND PICK UP BOURBON FOR HER ?
SHE DID, DIDN'T SHE ?
SHE'S REALLY SICK.
SHE REALLY NEEDS IT.
WE SHOULD GO.YEAH, WELL, I THINK
EVERYTHING'S CLOSED,
SO I GUESS YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO GET THAT BOTTLE FROM ME.
HERE YOU GO.
YOU TELL YOUR MAMA YOU GOT
FRIENDS IN HIGH PLACES, OKAY ?
DIDN'T YOUR MOM SAY THAT SHE NEEDED TWO OF THEM ?
[ Marcy Grunts ]
♪♪ [ Car Radio ]
AH.
I FEEL AWFUL.
YOU LOOK BETTER THOUGH,
MUCH BETTER.
I THINK I NEED
SOME WATER OR SOMETHING.
HERE.NO.
WE'LL STOP OFF
AND GET YOU SOME.
WE SHOULD STOP BY A PHARMACY
AND GET YOU SOME OF THOSE PILLS.
YEAH, WE'LL GET YOU
SOME WATER.
DEFINITELY NEED
♪ WE GO WALKING SOMETIMES  WHERE SHE CAN FOLLOW ♪
♪ WHEN WE TURN  IT'S HER DRINK WE SWALLOW ♪
♪ AND EVERY TIME  WE FEEL SO HOLLOW ♪
♪ WE WONDER IF  WE SEE TOMORROW ♪
♪ AND IT ISN'T EASY  AND IT ISN'T PLAIN ♪
♪ TRYING TO LOSE HER
♪ SHE REMAINS
♪ AND SO MAYBE  WE WOULD ALL GO INSANE ♪
♪ OH, WE'D LOSE OUR MARY
♪ YEAH, JUST LIKE MARY  WELL, JUST LIKE MARY ♪
♪ YEAH, JUST LIKE MARY  OH, OH ♪
♪ WHAT WE GONNA DO  ABOUT MARY ♪
♪ I WISH THAT WE COULD SELL
♪♪ [ Indistinct ]
HM.
STOP !
I CAN'T HELP IT, OKAY ?
YOU KNOW I'VE HAD EXPERIENCE
WITH DRUG ADDICT KIDS BEFORE.
WELL, THIS IS KIND OF
AN EMERGENCY.
I'LL JUST BET IT IS.
GO ON. GET THE HELL
OUT OF MY STORE.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.OH, OH, REALLY ?
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HM.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET ANY DRUGS.
GO ON. GET OUT.HEY, I'M UP !
WHAT ?
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.WHAT DON'T I UNDERSTAND ?
[ Yells ]
YOU DO.I DO WHAT ?
YOU DO.
FUCK, FUCK.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW
BEFORE I CALL THE SHERIFF.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE LEAVING,
BUT FUCK YOU, FUCK YOU.GO !
JUST GET THE HELL
OUT OF MY STORE.
OKAY. OKAY !
OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY, OKAY. FUCK.DO YOU KNOW WHERE THERE'S
A LIQUOR STORE AROUND HERE ?
JUST GET THE FOULMOUTHED BITCH
OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW. GO ON.
OH !DON'T YOU EVER
TALK TO HIM LIKE THAT !
- GET OUT OF MY STORE !
- DON'T FUCKING TOUCH HER.
DON'T YOU EVER TOUCH HER.OH, WHAT HAVE WE TURNED INTO,
MR. FUCKING TOUGH GUY HERE ?
HOW ABOUT THIS,
MR. TOUGH GUY ?
HEY !
GIVE ME
THE FUCKING PILLS !JESUS.
OH, MARCY.JUST HURRY THE FUCK UP,
ALL RIGHT ?
PLEASE, DON'T PLAY
WITH THE GUN. STOP.
I'LL GIVE YOU
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
JUST CALM DOWN.
MARCY ?
YOU SHOULD CONSIDER YOURSELF ONE LUCKY MOTHERFUCKER !
SHUT UP.
[ Sniffling ]
LET'S JUST GO, OKAY ?
NO, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
[ Alarm Beeping ]
MOMMY'S LITTLE HELPER.
[ Marcy ] OH, JEEZ, YOU GOTTA KEEP ON YOUR TOES.
[ Seth ] I KNOW. I'M SORRY.
HELLO.
COME TO MOMMY.
IT'S LARADOPA.
YOU EVER HEAR OF IT ?UH-UH.
OH, MAN, IT HYPES YOU UP
LIKE YOU HAVE TOURETTE'S.
I FIGURE IF I TAKE
SOME OF THIS WITH HALDOL,
I WON'T FEEL LIKE A ZOMBIE.
THEY'LL BALANCE EACH OTHER.WOW. REALLY ?
SURE.
OOH, LOOK AT THIS.
DO YOU WANT THIS STUFF ? YEAH.
YOU ALMOST DONE ?YEAH, JUST A SEC.
MAYBE THE HALDOL'S BACK
WITH THE TRANQUILIZERS.
I REMEMBER YOU,
MR. DRUG ADDICT KID.WOW, NO, WE--
SO WHERE'S YOUR
FOULMOUTHED LITTLE FRIEND ?[ Screams ]
[ Marcy Screams ]
SETH.HANDS UP, MISSY.
I GET YA ?
YOU BETTER COME ON OUT.
I'M GONNA TEACH YOU A LESSON.[ Gasps ]
[ Marcy Panting ]
SHIT. SHIT.
[ Grunting ]
COME ON, SETH.
OH, SHIT.
GO, SETH ! GO !
MARCY, COME ON !
HEY, COME BACK HERE !
HEY, THAT'S MY CAR,
YOU LITTLE TURDS.
COME BACK HERE !
STOP, ASS-FACE !
STOP !
[ Yells ]
I'M GONNA CALL THE COPS.
[ Seth ] IT REALLY HURTS BAD. MAYBE WE SHOULD GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
I CAN'T TAKE YOU
TO THE HOSPITAL, SETH.
WE JUST KNOCKED OVER A PHARMACY.
YEAH.ALL RIGHT. HERE.
YOU GOTTA TAKE THESE,
ALL RIGHT ?
I-I-IT SAYS TO TAKE TWO
EVERY FOUR HOURS AS NEEDED,
ALL RIGHT ?
WELL, I REALLY NEED THEM.
THEN TAKE FOUR.
HERE.
OKAY, OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
I HAVE TO LIFT IT UP, OKAY ?
IT'S GONNA HURT.
[ Screaming ]SHH.
AH !IT'S ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, IT'S OVER. IT'S OVER.
IT'S OVER, IT'S OVER.
IT'S OKAY.
YOU OKAY ?YEAH. YEAH.
OKAY.
ARE YOU OKAY ?YEAH, I'M OKAY.
JUST RELAX, ALL RIGHT ?
OKAY ?
YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE, OKAY ?
WE-WE GOTTA GET OUTTA HERE.
[ Dispatcher Chattering  On Police Radio ]
FOR SOME REASON,
MY DAD DOESN'T HAVE ANY TEETH.
IT'S BECAUSE, WHEN HE WAS
IN JAIL IN MIAMI THAT TIME,
THE COPS,
THEY USED TO TAKE HIM
IN THIS LITTLE CELL,
AND THEY USED TO BEAT THE SHIT
OUT OF HIM ALL THE TIME.
THEY KNOCKED OUT
A LOT OF HIS TEETH.
ALL OF THEM ?NO, NO.
NOT ALL OF THEM.
YOU KNOW, THE ONES THAT HE HAS LEFT, THEY AREN'T ANY GOOD EITHER.
ALL HE EVER EATS... ARE CORN FLAKES.
YOU KNOW, I'VE TRIED TO MAKE HIM, LIKE,
MASHED POTATOES AND STEAK-- YOU KNOW, LIKE CHOPPED STEAK.
ALL HE EVER WANTS
ARE CORN FLAKES.
♪ I GET UP AT SEVEN  AND BEFORE I GO TO WORK ♪
♪ I EAT A BOWL OF CORN FLAKES
♪ AND I GOBBLE UP THEM FLAKES
♪ OH, I'LL CHEW IF I HAVE TO
♪ BUT I'D RATHER SUCK
THEM SOGGY FLAKES ♪
♪ THEY RUN AMUCK IN MY BOWL  THEM TASTY FLAKES ♪
UM, OH, YEAH.
THIS IS THE CHORUS, OKAY ?
OKAY.
♪ BUT IF THE COOK
DON'T COME TODAY ♪
♪ THEM OLD CORN FLAKES  WILL HAVE TO DO ♪♪
THAT'S IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I ACTUALLY SANG YOU THE CORN FLAKES SONG.
FUCKING GREAT SONG,
BUT I COULDN'T HEAR
ALL THE WORDS...
'CAUSE YOU MUMBLEDA LOT.
I NEED YOU TO SING IT AGAIN
FOR ME, AND I DON'T WANT YOU
TO MUMBLESO MUCH THIS TIME.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
I FORGOT MOST OF THEM.
SING IT AGAIN !
WHAT IS IT ?NOTHING.
AGAIN. AGAIN.
WHAT IS THIS, SOME KIND
OF FUCKED-UP HALDOL THING ?
NO, I DIDN'T TAKE ANY HALDOL.
DO YOU WANT ANOTHER ONE ? WHERE ARE THEY ?
I DIDN'T TAKEANY HALDOL.
OH, SHIT !
NO, I DIDN'T TAKE ANY
ON PURPOSE.
I JUST TOOK LARADOPA, LARADOPA.
WHAT ?
I DIDN'T WANNA...
FEELTHE EFFECTS AGAIN.
I DIDN'T TAKE IT ON PURPOSE. I REALLY WANNA BE THERE WHEN WE GET THERE.
BESIDES, THE LARADOPA IS REALLY MAKING ME FEEL FUCKED-UP.
WHAT WAS THAT ? WHAT THE FUCK WAS THAT ?
- NO ! NO ! TO THE RIGHT !
TO THE RIGHT !
- [ Marcy Screaming ]
- STRAIGHTEN IT OUT !
- OH, FUCK !
[ Screams ]
I DON'T KNOW
IF I SHOULD TAKE
THIS MANY.
WE HAVE, LIKE,
THOUSANDS OF THEM.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
[ Coughing ]
GOD, WE NEED TO GET
SOME WATER.YEAH.
WHAT'S THAT ?MM, IT'S A TRUCK.
OH, MAYBE HE HAS
SOME WATER.
JUST ACT NORMAL,
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. HERE, LET ME
HELP YOU UP.
ALL RIGHT. YOU OKAY ?
YEAH. OKAY.
OH, GOD, HE'S STOPPING.
HE'S STOPPING. FUCK.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
[ Groans ] OH.
OH, WOW.
HI. COULD YOU NOT POINT
THAT GUN AT US ?
PLEASE ?
YOU WANT A DRINK ?
THERE YOU GO.J.W. BOOZE.
OOH.
PRESIDENTIAL BLEND.
ONE SHOT HITS THE SPOT.
GODDAMN.
WELL, WE HAVE TO GET RID
OF THAT CAR.
[ Man ]
AIN'T AS BAD AS IT LOOKS.
WHAT'S THAT MEAN ?IT MEANS I CAN
FIX YOUR BOY UP.
[ Groans ]AH.
- AH !
- GODDAMN IT.
HOLD STILL, FOR CHRIST'S SAKE.
[ Metal Clanging ]
IF WE HADN'T FOUND OIL FOR THEM SON OF A BITCHES, THOSE FUCKIN' RAG-HEADS,
YOU'D STILL BE SITTIN' AROUND
PICKIN' FLEAS OFF ONE ANOTHER.
YOU GOT THAT, EARL ?
[ Man Chattering, Faint ]
TELL YOU WHAT YOU DO.
READ SOMETHING, READ UP ON IT.
A BOOK, MAGAZINE, NEWSPAPER,
ANY GODDAMN THING.
PICK UP
A FUCKING PHONE BOOK.
OVER AND OUT.
DAMN, BOY,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YA ?
IT'S MARCY.WHAT ?
SHE JUST WANTS
TO SLEEP ALL THE TIME.
WELL, JESUS CHRIST, SETH,
LET HER SLEEP.
SHE'S PROBABLY TIRED.
THAT'S ALL. YOU COLD ?YEAH.
JESUS CHRIST.
DO YOU HAVE
ANY CORN FLAKES ?
NO, I DON'T HAVE
ANY GODDAMN CORN FLAKES.
I DON'T LIKE CORN FLAKES.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH
FUCKING OATMEAL ?
NO, IT'S FINE.
I JUST--
JESUS H. CHRIST
AND GENERAL JACKSON.
I'LL EAT THIS SHIT.
WANT SOME EGGS ?
I GOT SOME EGGS.
A LOT OF GODDAMN EGGS
IN THE ICE BOX.
REALLY ?NO.
FUCKING WITH YOU.
YEAH ?YEAH.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE FISH.
WE'RE NOT GOING FISHING,
ARE WE ?
BITCH.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT LIKE
I THINK THEY'RE GROSS
OR ANYTHING.
I MEAN, THEY'RE FINE.
I'M JUST--
I'M JUST SCARED OF THEM.
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
MAN'S SCARED OF WORMS,
SCARED OF WORMS.
YOU GOT EVERY
GODDAMN RIGHT TO BE.
WILL YOU THROW IT IN
FOR ME ?NO SHIT.
TAKE THE FUCKING THING,
THROW IT IN LIKE I TOLD YOU.
JUST TAKE THE THING
LIKE I TOLD YOU.
I WISH YOU WOULD DO IT.PUT YOUR RIGHT HAND
AND THROW THE FUCKING THING.
THESE ARE
REALLY COOL BOOTS.YEAH.
WOW, THEY'RE ALL THERMAL
AND EVERYTHING.YEAH.
IT'S NICE.YEAH.
WHOA !
AH.
NOW YOU'RE TALKIN'.
FUCK THIS FISH !
MOBY DICK, MOBY DICK.
IT'S YOUR FISH, SETH.
YOU CAUGHT THE SON OF A BITCH.
YOU BLEW ITS HEAD OFF.
IT'S YOUR FISH, SETH.
WELL, I KNOW, BUT I'D--
I'D RATHER THAT YOU HAD IT.
I MEAN, YOU DESERVE IT
A LOT MORE THAN I DO.
ANYWAY, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
WANTED FISH FOR BREAKFAST.
I'LL JUST HAVE THE EGGS.
WHEN I FIRST SAW YOU
OUT THERE FISHING,
I THOUGHT, JESUS CHRIST,
HE'LL NEVER MAKE
A GOOD FISHERMAN.
THEN I SAW THE WAY
YOU LANDED THE FISH,
FINALLY HELD HIM.
AND I THOUGHT, WELL,
HE MIGHT BE SCARED OF WORMS,
BUT SHIT, YOU DON'T NEED
A GODDAMN WORM TO CATCH
A FUCKING FISH.
BUT NOW YOU TELL ME
YOU'RE SCARED OF FISH ?
I'M NOT SCARED OF THE FISH.
I'M SCARED OF YOU HITTING ME
WITH THE FISH.
JESUS CHRIST.
WHY WOULD I WANT TO HIT YOU
WITH THIS GODDAMN FISH FOR ? I DON'T KNOW.
OH.
THAT'S GROSS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I HIT YOU WITH THE FISH, SETH,
AND YOU'RE A BETTER MAN
FOR IT.
I FEEL LIKE A BETTER MAN,
ACTUALLY.
HOW MANY EGGS YOU WANT ?
COUPLE.
I LIKE 'EM FRIED.
OKAY, YOU'RE GONNA GET 'EM FRIED.
IT'S THE POWER OF SUGGESTION, SETH.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT FUCKS US UP.
IT FUCKS ME UP.
I ACTUALLY CAUGHT ONE,
AND THEN WE PUT IT UP
ON THE BANK.
WALTER LET ME BLOW
ITS HEAD OFF WITH HIS GUN.
IT'S THIS BIG SILVER AUTOMATIC
AND HAS WOOD HANDLES.
IT'S REALLY LOUD.
REALLY ?
YEAH, AND THEN WE WENT UP
TO THE PLACE WHERE HE KEEPS
ALL THE CARS.
HE TOOK THE GRAN FURY,
AND HE CRUSHED IT...
IN THIS COMPACTOR,
WHATEVER YOU CALL IT.
WHY DIDN'T YOU WAIT
FOR ME ?I-I'M SORRY.
DON'T YOU THINK THAT
MAYBE THAT'S SOMETHING
I'D LIKE TO WATCH TOO ?
TOO. TOO !
I'M-- I'M SORRY, MARCY.
MAYBE HE'LL DO
ANOTHER ONE LATER.
HE'S GOT A LOT OF STUFF
UP THERE.
CARS AND STUFF.
[ Clucking ]
[ Clucking Loudly ]
YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW.
I KNOW, ESTHER.
IT IS A HARD GODDAMN ROAD
TO WALK, THAT STRAIGHT
AND NARROW ROAD.
I'VE SURE MADE
SOME OF MY MISTAKES GOOD.
YEAH, WISH I COULD'VE,
WOULD'VE, SHOULD'VE
IF I COULD'VE, WOULD'VE.
OHH.
THEY JUST A COUPLE OF KIDS.
I HAVEN'T GOT A GODDAMN
CHINAMAN'S CHANCE.
OH, ESTHER.
I KNOW, ESTHER.
OH !
OH, ESTHER.
YOU'RE A PRETTY GIRL.
WELL, YOUR FEATHERS ARE.
YOUR FACE'D STOP
A BAG OF SHIT IN MIDAIR,
ESTHER.
SHH.
[ Radio Static Hissing ]
[ Dog Barking ]
THERE YOU GO.
COME HERE.
COME ON.
DROP IT RIGHT HERE.
NAW, GODDAMN IT,
GO LAY DOWN.
GET OUTTA THE WAY.
PAY ATTENTION.
WELL, LOOK WHO'S BACK
FROM THE DEAD.
YEAH. ARE YOU GOING TO TEACH US HOW TO PLAY GOLF ?
WHY,
HELL YEAH, MARSHY.IT'S MARCY.
YOU JUST PUT THAT LITTLE
BASTARD RIGHT THERE.
KEEP YOUR EYE
ON THE SUCKER.
GO RIGHT FOR THE--
GODDAMN. I NEVER
HIT IT BETTER.
IF YOU'RE GOING
FOR A LONG ONE,
REMEMBER, YOU GO
RIGHT FOR THE FLAG.
THE RED FLAG IS
OLD ARNOLD PALMER'S HAT.
- FUCKING SON OF A BITCH.
- [ Gunshot ]
GODDAMN,
SON OF A BITCH.
IT'S A NICE GUN.YEAH, GIVE ME
THAT GODDAMN THING.
♪ I'M AN ORPHAN
♪ ON GOD'S HIGHWAY
♪ GONNA SHARE MY JOURNALS
♪ YOU GO MY WAY
♪ I HAVE NO MOTHER
♪ NO FATHER
♪ NO SISTER
♪ NO-O BROTHER
[ Car Horn Honking ]
♪ I AM AN ORPHAN ♪
YOU GUYS GO IN THERE.WHERE ?
GO ON AROUND OVER THERE.
GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
[ Coughs, Clears Throat ]
LET'S JUST GET UP
IN HERE.
HOW YA DOIN', ALBERT ?
HEY, WALTER,
HOW YA DOIN' ?OH, I CAN'T COMPLAIN.
LITTLE TARGET PRACTICE ?YEAH, YEAH, I GUESS
YOU HEARD ME.
- YEAH, SOUNDS GOOD.
- SHIT !
OH, HEY, DON'T WORRY.
WALTER WILL FULLY DEAL
WITH THIS COP.
YOU THINK HE'S SO FUCKING GOOD
AT EVERYTHING, JUST 'CAUSE HE
TAUGHT YOU HOW TO FISH.
NO, HE'S GOOD AT THESE
SORT OF SITUATIONS.
YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
HE TAUGHT YA HOW TO FISH.
I'M LOOKIN' FOR A COUPLE
OF KIDS, A COUPLE OF PERPS.
SUSPECTS: MALE, FEMALE;
18, 24; DRIVING A PLYMOUTH.
'78, '79 GRAN FURY.
YOU SEEN 'EM AROUND ?
SHIT. THERE AIN'T NOTHIN'
BUT ME AND THE FUCKIN' CHICKENS.YEAH.
LOOK, I-I LIKE THE GUY,
ALL RIGHT ?
YEAH,
I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW.
HE TAUGHT YA HOW TO FISH.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO ?RIGHT NOW, I JUST NEED YOU
TO HOLD ME, OKAY ?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.ALL RIGHT ?
I JUST NEED YOU TO LOVE ME
RIGHT NOW, OKAY ? PLEASE.OKAY.
OKAY, OKAY.
WHAT ARE THEY DOIN' ?COME ON, I--
NO, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.COME ON !
KISS MY ASS.
WAIT, WAIT, HOLD ON. [ Zipper Unzipping ]
[ Moaning ]
ISRAELI-MADE.YEAH.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
PLEASE, PLEASE.NO, NO, NO,
I WANNA SEE--
I WANNA SEE IF YOU GRADUATED
FROM THE FUCKING ACADEMY.
[ Moaning Continues ]
OKAY, YOU LOOKIN' ?YEAH, I'M LOOKIN'.
[ Gunshots ] [ Moaning Continues ]
[ Gunshots Continue ]
HEY, MARSHY, I GOT RID OF THAT COP.
SHH !
HE'S SLEEPING.
I GOT RID OF THAT COP.GOOD.
WHY ARE YOU BEING
SO NICE TO US, WALTER ?
WELL, I HATE THEM BASTARDS
AS MUCH AS YOU DO.
WELL, THANKS A LOT.
WANT YOUR GUN BACK ?YEAH.
THERE YOU GO.OKEYDOKE.
LISTEN.
WHILE HE'S TAKING A NAP,
YOU WANNA FEED THE CHICKENS ?
OKAY.ALL RIGHT.
ONE. OKAY.
TWO.
SPREAD IT ALL AROUND THERE, MARSHY.
THERE YOU GO.
WHAT'S UP WITH HER ?
OH, THAT'S ESTHER.
DON'T PAY ANY ATTENTION
TO ESTHER.
ESTHER'S OUT OF HER GODDAMNED MIND.
WHY IS HER NAME ESTHER ?
IT'S A PRETTY FUCKING STUPID
NAME FOR A CHICKEN, ISN'T IT ?
WELL, I NAMED HER AFTER MY WIFE.
SORRY.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER ?
OH, SHE DIED.
ABOUT TWO YEARS AGO.
PNEUMONIA.
GODDAMNED DOCTORS
SAID IT WAS...
A VIRAL INFECTION OR SOMETHING OF THAT SHIT.
THAT'S AWFUL. I MEAN, THAT'S
KIND OF JUST LIKE SAYING...
"THANK YOU FOR PAYING ME
AND CALLING ME NAMES,"
AND LETTING YOU DIE.
DIE ! DIE.
DEAD.
THAT'S WHY I DON'T BELIEVE
IN THE GODDAMNED DOCTORS.
I DON'T TRUST 'EM.
I DON'T TRUST THE GODDAMNED COPS.
[ Grunts ]
TELL ME ABOUT ESTHER.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU, MARSHY ?
IT'S MARCY !
O-O-OKAY, MARCY.
SORRY. SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO
SCREAM AT YOU, OKAY ?
YEAH.
JUST TELL ME
ABOUT YOUR WIFE.
WELL--
I GUESS THERE ISN'T
ANYTHING TO TELL, MARCY.
JUST TWO OLD PEOPLE
THAT WERE CRAZY
ABOUT EACH OTHER.
FUCKING SLUT !
I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T, UM--
I DIDN'T MEAN TO TALK
ABOUT YOUR WIFE LIKE THAT.
[ Shouts ]
WHAT DID SHE LOOK LIKE ?
I JUST WANNA KNOW
WHAT SHE LOOKED LIKE,
THAT'S ALL.
WELL, SHE HAD...
BLUE EYES.
SHE HAD THE BLUEST EYES
THIS SIDE OF... SYRACUSE.
WHAT ELSE ?SHE HAD THE BLUEST EYES
THIS SIDE OF POUGHKEEPSIE.
[ Grunts ]
SKIP THE SHIT AND TELL ME
ABOUT THE BITCH ! BITCH !
WHOA.WALTER, I'M FUCKING
SORRY, MAN.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I
KEEP ON DOING THAT.
UM--
[ Sighs ]
JUST TELL ME--
TELL ME SOMETHING
ELSE ABOUT HER.
WILL YOU TELL ME ?YEAH.
SHE USED THIS SOAP.
HER HAIR WAS REALLY SWEET.[ Low Growl ]
IT HAD THIS SWEET--FUCKING
SENTIMENTAL BITCH !
IT WAS A FUNNY THING TO SAY.
IT WAS A FUNNY SENTIMENTAL
THING TO SAY.
WELL, I'M A FUNNY,
SENTIMENTAL SON OF A BITCH.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, ESTHER ?
I'M A SON OF A BITCH
AND I'M SENTIMENTAL.
AND I DON'T KNOW MY ASS
FROM SIX BITS.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT ?
[ Cooing ]
I'M ON TARGET !
[ Exhales ]
I JUST NEED YOU
TO TALK TO ME, OKAY ?
WELL, I'M TALKING TO ESTHER.
WHO ARE YOU ?
WHAT THE FUCK
IS GOING ON WITH YOU AND
THE GODDAMNED CHICKEN ?
WELL, YOUR HONOR,
WHO IN THE FUCK ASKED YOU ?
I'M SORRY. I JUST--
I THINK IT'S NICE
THAT YOU'RE CLOSE.
GODDAMN RIGHT !
WHAT THE FUCK
ARE YOU ALL ABOUT ?
COME HERE.
COME ON, BABY. [ Chicken Clucking ]
THIS LITTLE CHICKEN...
BRINGS ME COMFORT.
COMFORT.
YEAH.CHICKEN. CHICKEN IS
NICE CHICKEN, RIGHT ?
IT'S A NICE CHICKEN.
SEE, HERE'S THE CHICKEN.
HERE'S THE CHICKEN.
EASY, EASY, EASY.YEAH, YOU WANNA KISS
THE FUCKER, HUH ?
ARE YOU A CHICKEN FUCKER,
HUH ? CHICKEN FUCKER !GODDAMN YOU !
CHICKEN LICKING BITCH !
GIMME THAT GODDAMN THING !
OW, YOU--
THERE YOU GO !
CHICKEN LICKER !
THAT'S IT ! THAT'S IT !
[ Grunts ]WHAT'D YOU DO TO ME ?
CHICKEN LICKER
MOTHERFUCKER !
- [ Groans ]
- CHICKEN LICKER !
[ Groaning ]
[ Panting ]
WALTER ?
ESTHER ? ESTHER,
COME TO WALTER.
FUCK.
SORRY, SORRY, SORRY.
WHERE ARE
MY GLASSES ?
[ Groans ]
GET IN THE TRUCK.
YOU GET IN THE
FUCKING TRUCK NOW !
SORRY.
WE'RE GONNA SEND HIM
SOME MONEY RIGHT AFTER
WE KNOCK OVER THE FIRST BANK.
OKAY, BUT THAT'S NOT--NO, NO, WE'RE GONNA
SEND HIM LIKE TWO GRAND.
I'M A REALLY BAD PERSON.
NO, DON'T. IT'S--
YOU'RE NOT A BAD PERSON.
IT'S JUST THAT--
IT'S JUST THAT YOU
JUST BEAT THE SHIT
OUT OF WALTER...
AND HE WAS
REALLY NICE TO US.
AND I KNOW YOU DIDN'T
MEAN TO AND THAT
DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S JUST THAT--
I JUST NEED A MINUTE TO--
YOU KNOW ?
ARE YOU TIRED OF ME ?
I MEAN, I AM REALLY AFRAID
THAT YOU'RE GONNA GET
TIRED OF ME.
AND YOU'RE--
I MEAN--NO, NO.
I'M NEVER GONNA
GET TIRED OF YOU.
IT'S JUST THAT I'M SUCH
A PAIN IN THE ASS.
I HAVE ALL THESE FUCKING TICS
AND I'M ALWAYS HITTING YOU.
IT'S SO FUCKING UGLY.
I-- I LOVE THEM.
IT'S PATHETIC.NO, IT ISN'T.
IT'S ALL PART OF YOU.
IT'S-- IT'S ALL YOU.
AND-- AND--
DON'T SAY THAT RIGHT NOW.
WHY NOT ?
'CAUSE WE'RE RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF A FUCKING INTERSECTION.
[ Clicking Hammer  On Gun ]
MARCY.
I'M SORRY. I--YOU JUST THINK
I'M A FUCKING IDIOT, RIGHT ?
NO.
YOU CAN DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
OKAY.
THEN GIVE ME THE GUN BACK.
WHAT'S WRONG ?
WELL, IT'S LIKE
YOU SAID.
WE'RE AT AN INTERSECTION.AND ?
WELL, SO WHAT ARE WE GOING
TO DO ? ARE WE STILL
GOING TO TORONTO ?
IS THAT WHAT
WE'RE GONNA DO ?
ARE WE GONNA GO HOME ?
NO, WE ARE NEVER GOING HOME,
ALL RIGHT ? WE'RE NOT
FUCKING GOING BACK.
I REALLY WANT THAT
BLACK BOBBIE HEAD.
WE NEED MORE GAS.
♪♪ [ Humming
"Charlie's AngelsTheme" ]
I FEEL LIKE FUCKING FARRAH.
SHE'S MY FAVORITE ANGEL.
YOU KNOW,
MAYBE IT'S NOT
SUCH A GOOD IDEA
YOU HOLDING THE GUN.
OH.
HERE.
YOU CAN HAVE ONE TOO.
♪♪ [ Radio: Punk Rock ]
HI. CAN I HAVE 30 BUCKS
WORTH OF DIESEL ON PUMP SEVEN ?
LIKE RIGHT FUCKING NOW !
YOU KNOW, SINCE I'M GONNA BE
HERE FOR A WHILE, COULD YOU
GET ME MY CIGARETTES ?
WHAT KIND DO YOU SMOKE ?SPINNERS.
SURE.
THIS IS REALLY GONNA
FUCK UP YOUR CLOTHES.THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU THE GUY
THAT ROBBED THE PHARMACY ?
YEAH.
DO YOU WANNA GIVE HER
A LICENSE PLATE NUMBER
OR ANYTHING ELSE, SETH ?
THAT'S OKAY. I'M NOT
GONNA TELL ANYBODY.
I PROMISE.
HERE.
TAKE A FEW OF THOSE.
THEY'RE REALLY GOOD.
THANKS.
TAKE IT EASY.YEAH, YOU TOO.
SMOKE THIS.
[ Grunts ]
GOOD MORNING.
UH ! YOU KNOW, I THINK
YOU'RE A REALLY GREAT ROBBER.
YOU WERE EXCELLENT
BACK THERE.
YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
BEEN THINKIN' A LOT,
AND I THINK YOU SHOULD
REALLY QUIT SHOPLIFTING,
SINCE WE'RE REAL
CRIMINALS NOW, YOU KNOW.REALLY ?
YEAH. IT'S JUST
NOT VERY CLASSY,
YOU KNOW.
I THINK WE SHOULD STICK
TO CLASSY CRIMES ONLY.
I DON'T WANNA BE SOME KIND
OF LIKE SLEAZY CROOK LIKE
MY DAD AND MY UNCLE CARMINE.
YOUR DAD'S A CROOK ?HE'S A TOTAL FUCKIN' CROOK.
PROMISE ME WE'RE NEVER
GONNA DO BUSINESS
WITH THEM, ALL RIGHT ?
YOU NEVER DO BUSINESS
WITH YOUR PARENTS.
I AM REALLY
GONNA MISS THIS TRUCK.
[ Explosion ]
WE'LL GET A NEW ONE
WHEN WE GET TO CANADA.
YEAH.
WE'RE GONNA SEND HIM
A CHECK.
YEAH, I KNOW.
ARE WE NEAR CANADA YET ?
[ Seth ] WE HAVE TO WALK A LITTLE WAYS.
♪ NEVER THOUGHT I'D EVER
♪ CONQUER MY WEAKNESS
♪ 'CAUSE EVERYBODY KNOWS
♪ MY WEAKNESS IS YOU
♪ THE ANSWER CAME  THIS MORNING ♪
♪ AND YOU SHOULD BE  THE FIRST TO HEAR ♪
♪ WHAT A SIMPLE  LITTLE THING ♪
♪ I HAVE TO DO
♪ THINK I FOUND A WAY
♪ TO LIVE WITHOUT YOU
♪ I CAN GET BY
♪ THINK I FOUND A WAY
♪ THAT CAN HELP ME OUT ♪
[ Pills Rattling ]
HEY.HEY.
WHY ARE YOU WATCHIN' ?
SURE YOU WANT
TO DO THIS ?
YEAH. WE'RE NOT GOING TO
GET THROUGH CUSTOMS
IF WE DON'T.
I SAVED YOU A BUNCH
OF DEMEROL FOR THE
VERY LAST MINUTE, THOUGH.
I THINK WE SHOULD TAKE
A BUNCH NOW, THOUGH.
HERE.
ONE,
TWO,
THREE,
FOUR ?
[ Marcy ] NIAGARA.
NIAGARA, NIAGARA,
MARCY.NIAGARA, NIAGARA, NIAGARA,
NIAGARA, NIAGARA, NIAGARA,
HEY.NIAGARA, NIAGARA.
NIAGARA.
[ Barking ]
♪ IT'S A CURSE
♪ LIKE A BLACK THUMB
♪ EVERYTHING I TOUCH
♪ AND I AM SURE  YOU ARE SURE ♪
♪ YOU COULD HELP SO MUCH
♪ BUT IT'S A CURSE
♪ LIKE A BLACK THUMB
♪ EVERYTHING I TOUCH
♪ RUNS OUT WITH THE PRESSURE
♪ BECOMES A PILE OF DUST
♪ OOH, THEN THE WIND GETS IT
♪ EVERYTHING I TOUCH
♪ RUNS WILD ♪
[ Seth ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I DIDN'T THINK THEY WERE
ACTUALLY GONNA HAVE IT.
TOLD YOU THEY
WERE GONNA HAVE IT.
OH, NO.
ALL THEY HAVE
ARE WHITE ONES.WE'LL JUST GET HER.
UP THERE.
JUST GET HER.
[ Seth ] ALL RIGHT. NO, IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO CLIMB. YEAH.
WE'LL JUST TAKE THIS ONE.
OH, SHIT.
IT'S ALL LOCKED UP.
EH, WHAT ARE YOU DOIN' ?
YOU CAN'T CLIMB UP THERE.
YOU CAN'T TOUCH THE DISPLAY.
IT'S NOT LIKE THERE'S
SOME BIG SIGN THAT SAYS,
"DON'T TOUCH THIS." EH ?
WELL, I GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO
PUT A BIG SIGN UP THERE,
WON'T WE, EH ?
[ Seth ] ACTUALLY, WE WANTED THIS BLACK BOBBIE STYLING HEAD.
DO YOU HAVE ANY MORE
IN THE STORE OR MAYBE
SOME IN THE BACK ?
[ Grunts ]
MANAGER.HOW 'BOUT THE MANAGER ?
DO YOU HAVE A MANAGER ?
YEAH, HE'S AROUND HERE.
I GOTTA DO SOMETHING FIRST.
THEN I'LL GO GET HIM, OKAY ?
SURE.OKAY, NOW DON'T BE
CLIMBING AROUND NO MORE.
I WON'T CLIMB.ALL RIGHT.
WHAT I'M TRYING TO UNDERSTAND IS
WHAT IS THIS WHOLE FASCINATION
WITH A BLACK BOBBIE HEAD ?
WE HAVE THREE VERY PRETTY
WHITE BOBBIE HEADS
ON THE SHELVES.
I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW.
WHAT I'M TRYING TO
TELL YOUIS THAT...
WE DON'T CARE ABOUT THE BOX.
JOIES CANADIENNES
DOES NOT DEAL IN USED
OR DAMAGED MERCHANDISE.
- THAT DISPLAY, SIR--
- HEY, BIRDIE, BIRDIE !
EXCUSE ME.
NO, SHE--
SHE DOESN'T MEAN THAT. EXCUSE ME !
I THINK YOU TWO
SHOULD LEAVE. MAURICE !
- NO, NO, NO, NO.
- MAURICE ! MAURICE !
I'M SORRY. HEY, MARCY.PLEASE SHOW THESE TWO
TO THE DOOR.
ALL RIGHT ! WE'RE--
WE'RE LEAVING. OKAY. THANK YOU.
[ Seth ]
JUST A MINUTE.
STOP IT.
[ Bangs Shelf ]
I WANT TO TRY TO GET IT
ONE MORE TIME, OKAY ?
SEE ? THIS IS WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT. THIS IS
EXACTLY WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT !
- EXCUSE ME !
- OH, SHIT.
EXCUSE ME !SHIT !
SIR, PLEASE GET DOWN
FROM THERE.
WHOA !
GO GET THE COPS.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
HE'S ALL RIGHT !
IT'S ALL RIGHT !
IT'S ALL RIGHT ! HEY ! IT'S ALL RIGHT !
HE'S ALL RIGHT !
[ Marcy Continues Shouting,  Indistinctly ]
I'M SORRY. NO. NEXT WEEK.JEN, YOU GOTTA GET OFF
THE PHONE. JEN ?
HE'S ALL RIGHT !
BLACK BOBBIE'S IN CHAINS !
CHAINS !
CHAINED BLACK BOBBIE !
TAKE THE GODDAMN BOBBIE, MAN !
CHAINED HER UP !
YOU CHAINED UP BOBBIE !
CHAINS !
SHE'S IN CHAINS !
CHAINS ! CHAINS !
WE GOT A COUPLE OF ROWDIES
CAUSING A BIG DISTURBANCE.
DON'T EAT THAT.
NO, NOT YOU.
CHAINED BOBBIE !
CHAINS !
ALL THE BLACK BOBBIES
ARE IN CHAINS !
CHAINS ! CHAINS !
CHAINS !
[ Marcy Continues Shouting ]
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE COULD BE ON DRUGS
OR SOMETHING.
CHAINS !PLEASE, LEAVE THE STORE !
[ Shouting Indistinctly ]
STOP LAUGHING !
GET UP ! JUST CALM DOWN.
JUST CALM DOWN, ALL RIGHT ?I'M OKAY.
- OKAY ? ALL RIGHT ?
- I'M OKAY.
WE'RE GONNA
LEAVE THE STORE.[ Shouting ]
[ Marcy ] LET GO OF ME ! LET GO OF ME !
CHAINS ! SHE'S IN CHAINS ! MAURICE,
HELP ME HOLD HER !
BLACK BOBBIE'S IN CHAINS !
BLACK BOBBIE'S IN--
[ Gasps ]JESUS.
IT'S OKAY.
SHE HAS A DISORDER. SHE'LL BE OKAY. SHE JUST HAS TO WORK IT OUT.
JUST PLEASE DON'T CALL THE COPS.
WE'LL PAY FOR ALL THE DAMAGES. PLEASE ?
[ Manager ] NO, RIGHT NOW ! I'M TELLING YOU THE COPS ARE COMING HERE !
I WANT YOU OUT OF THIS STORE RIGHT NOW, MISTER !
WE'RE LEAVING. I JUST--
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
WE'LL PAY FOR EVERYTHING.
OKAY, THEN STAY HERE.NO, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
[ Cop #1 ] WHAT'S GOING ON ? [ Manager ] STAY RIGHT THERE.
HEY, "OSSIFER."
- DROP IT !
- [ Customers Screaming ]
NO-O-O-O !
MARCY ?
SORRY.
[ Whispering ]
I'M SORRY.
[ Seth, Reading ] "DEAR WALTER, I KNOW IT MIGHT SEEM DUMB...
"THAT I'M WRITING YOU AFTER WHAT HAPPENED,
"BUT I THOUGHT ENOUGH TIME HAS PASSED NOW TO GIVE EACH
OF US SOME PERSPECTIVE...
"ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED WITH YOU AND MARCY AND ALL.
"I'M SURE YOU KNOW HOW REALLY SORRY SHE IS FOR WHAT HAPPENED.
"SHE DIDN'T MEAN IT, AND IS ON HER MEDICATION NOW.
"I'M SENDING YOU $20 RIGHT NOW TO PUT TOWARDS A NEW TRUCK
FOR THE ONE WE BORROWED.
"OBVIOUSLY, IT'S NOT ENOUGH FOR EVEN A DOWN PAYMENT,
"BUT I THOUGHT THAT A FINANCIAL GESTURE
WAS IN ORDER.
"MONEY IS A LITTLE TIGHT RIGHT NOW,
"EVEN THOUGH I'M WORKING DOWN ON WALL STREET
IN A REALLY GOOD JOB.
"I'M GLAD TO SAY THAT EVERYTHING TURNED OUT FOR THE BEST
AFTER ALL.
"AND GUESS WHAT. WE GOT MARRIED.
"CAN YOU BELIEVE IT ?
"WE THOUGHT ABOUT INVITING YOU, BUT I FIGURED YOU WEREN'T MUCH
FOR WEDDINGS AND STUFF, SO--
"MARCY'S SETTING UP THE HOUSE I BOUGHT FOR US.
"IT'S A GREAT BIG PLACE AND I CAN'T WAIT FOR YOU
TO SEE IT.
"WE'RE GONNA FIX UP A ROOM JUST FOR YOU WHEN YOU COME
AND VISIT.
"I JUST WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW HOW MUCH IT MEANT TO US
TO STAY WITH YOU.
"YOU WERE THE NICEST PERSON I THINK I EVER MET.
"MARCY SAYS SHE THINKS SO TOO.
"ANYWAY, I'LL WRITE TO YOU SOON TO GIVE YOU ALL THE DETAILS.
"MAYBE EVEN AN INVITE TO A BABY SHOWER.
HINT, HINT.
TAKE CARE. SETH."
♪ SHE SEES HIM LAYING
♪ IN THE BED ALONE TONIGHT
♪ THE ONLY THING  A TOUCHING HIM ♪
♪ IS A CRACK OF LIGHT
♪ PIECES OF HER HAIR  ARE WRAPPED AROUND ♪
♪ AND 'ROUND HIS FINGERS
♪ AND HE REACHES  FOR HER SIDE ♪
♪ FOR ANY SIGN OF HER  THAT LINGERS ♪
♪ AND SHE SAYS  YOU ARE NOT ALONE ♪
♪ LAYING IN THE LIGHT
♪ PUT OUT THE FIRE  IN YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ AND LAY WITH ME TONIGHT
♪ ONE OF THEM BULLETS  WENT STRAIGHT FOR ♪
♪ THE JUGULAR VEIN
♪ THERE WERE PEOPLE RUNNING  A FLASH OF LIGHT ♪
♪ THEN EVERYTHING CHANGED
♪ NOTHING REALLY MATTERS  IN THE END, YOU KNOW ♪
♪ ALL THE WORRIES SEVER
♪ DON'T BE AFRAID FOR ME  MY FRIEND ♪
♪ ONE DAY WE ALL  FALL DOWN FOREVER ♪
♪ AND YOU ARE NOT ALONE
♪ LAYING IN THE LIGHT
♪ PUT OUT THE FIRE  IN YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ AND LAY WITH ME TONIGHT
CLOSED-CAPTIONED BY
CAPTIONS, INC. LOS ANGELES
♪ THE WEDDING DATE WAS JUNE
♪ JUST LIKE ANY OTHER BRIDE
♪ SHE LOVED HIM LIKE  NO ONE BEFORE ♪
♪ IT WAS GOOD TO BE ALIVE
♪ BUT SOMETIMES THAT CAN  SLIP AWAY AS FAST ♪
♪ AS ANY FINGERS  THROUGH YOUR HANDS ♪
♪ SO YOU LET TIME  FORGIVE THE PAST ♪
♪ AND GO AND MAKE  SOME OTHER PLANS ♪
♪ AND YOU ARE NOT ALONE
♪ LAYING IN THE LIGHT
♪ PUT OUT THE FIRE  IN YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ AND LAY WITH ME TONIGHT
♪ YOU ARE NOT ALONE
♪ LAYING IN THE LIGHT
♪ PUT OUT THE FIRE  IN YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ AND LAY WITH ME TONIGHT ♪
♪ SITTIN' IN THIS LONELY TOWN
♪ I WONDER WHEN THINGS  ARE GONNA CHANGE ♪
♪ DREAMING MY LIFE AWAY
♪ AND IT SEEMS THEM DREAMS  THEY TURNED INTO A BUNCH
OF DUST CLOUDS ♪
♪ GETTIN' MY NERVE UP
♪ BUT MY PAST  IS PULLIN' ME DOWN ♪
♪ WONDERIN' HOW LONG  THIS BLACK SHEEP HERE ♪
♪ CAN STICK AROUND
♪ SOMEBODY TOLD ME ONCE BEFORE
♪ HE SAID THAT YOU CAN  NEVER GO HOME AGAIN ♪
♪ ONCE YOU LEAVE
♪ IT'D TAKE ANYTHING  JUST TO SCARE ME AWAY ♪
♪ FROM THE TRUTH OF WHO I AM  AND WHAT I BELIEVE ♪
♪ SO I THANKED HIM  FOR HIS TWO CENTS ♪
♪ WITH A SHAKE  AND SOME SYMPATHY ♪
♪ AND I PACKED UP  MY BLUE JEANS ♪
♪ AND I HEADED FOR  THE BIG PRIZE ♪
♪ OF MY FREEDOM
♪ SO BYE-BYE
♪ BLACK SHEEP OF THE FAMILY
♪ BYE-BYE
♪ BLACK SHEEP OH, THAT MEANS SO MUCH TO ME ♪
♪ TO MY FRIENDS  AND MY FAMILY ♪♪