[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHILDREN PLAYING STICK-BALL]
Hey, batter, batter, batter, batter.
Swing, batter, batter, batter, batter.
Come on, Mark, knock it far, rock it far.
Give 'em in the heater, Mark.
Let her fly!
Come on, throw the stupid ball, Mark, I gotta go!
My mom thinks I'm raking the backyard.
[LOUD WHACK]
Whoops!
Jerk!
That's my rake handle.
My mom's gonna kill me! - Sorry!
Sorry, nothing.
What am I gonna tell my mom?
Tell her to start buying thicker rakes.
[LAUGHING] - That's not funny!
Really not funny.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
[KISSING)
Hi.
[CHUCKLING] Hi!
So--
Mm?
You feel maternal?
What?
[LAUGHING] I don't know.
Yeah, maybe, maybe.
Good.
Got to be positive.
Attitude, remember that, attitude.
Getting pregnant iis a little more
complicated than that, Bill
Mm-- attitude.
Hey, guys, what's up?
Wanna play?
[OVERLAPPING SOUNDS OF CHILDREN  PLAYING]
[WISTFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BUS TOOTS HORN]
So the Norris's say they'll donate $50,000
to the school's general fund.
Oh, that's great.
If the school will name a building after them.
Do they have any particular building in mind?
No, they're flexible.
We'll have to see how flexible.
What else you got?
Class of '55 reunion.
Sorry to interrupt, Hilton Burberry's here to see you.
I'll call the Norrises.
Would you?
Tell them we appreciate their generosity
but fortunately, we don't have any unnamed buildings
available.
Hi!
I don't know if you remember me but I run the baseball program
your son used to play in.
Of course I remember.
C'mon in.
Yeah, it's a great program, he really loved it.
Look, now, we don't really know each other
and I know it's been awhile since your son passed on.
And I've always felt bad about not offering my condolences.
He was truly one of a kind.
I mean that.
Thank you.
That's very nice of you to say.
You and your wife doing OK?
Oh, yeah, fine, just fine.
Great as a matter of fact.
Can we talk for a minute?
Sure.
I've got to run over to administration, why
don't you walk me over?
All right.
You a big baseball fan, Bill?
Oh, I wouldn't say a big one.
I read the occasional box score, take in a game now and then.
Baseball will be starting up again pretty soon.
You're kidding.
It seems like it just ended.
I know what you mean.
I feel like I get about one week's
vacation between handing out trophies
and finding new coaches.
Wait a minute.
Is that why you stopped by to see me?
You want me to coach?
Well, I had hoped to ease into a little more gracefully,
but yes, the thought had crossed my mind.
You'd be surprised how much fun it can be.
Oh, I'm sure it is.
But, um-- I'm kind of busy at work,
I wouldn't have the time to put it.
Now listen, listen, I'll shoot straight with you.
You've had a tough year and I imagine it's
not going to get much easier.
Keeping busy, being around kids, it might help.
They're good kids, Bill.
You probably know most of them, your son
was a pretty popular boy.
Yes, he was.
Think about it.
BILL: How's the book?
It's OK.
You finish the puzzle? BILL: Almost.
I think I'm going to go to bed.
So soon?
It's early.
I'm tired.
Don't stay up to late, OK?
OK.
Hey, um, guess who stopped by to see me today?
Who?
Hilton Burberry.
What did he want?
Just to say he was sorry about Nathaniel.
Oh.
That's sweet.
He, um-- also asked if I'd be interested in coaching
a baseball team this year?
Why you?
I don't know.
He said, he thought I might want to.
Do you?
I'm thinking about it.
Why?
Might be fun.
He's gone, Bill.
This is not about Nathaniel.
OK, whatever you say.
If you really want to do it, I think you should do it.
Well, I do.
And don't worry, it will be fine.
It'll be a lot of fun.
Do we have any ice cream?
OK, now, here are your rosters.
You have 15 kids on a team.
And you'll each have an assistant
to help you corral them all.
Bill, you're the new guy here so we don't
have an assistant for you yet.
I'll keep looking, but if you find somebody who is willing,
grab him.
Now Fred White is going to be umpiring for us again this year
and I don't want you to give him a hard time.
The job is hard enough without you guys
screaming down his throat all the time.
And besides, if we lose him, then I'm stuck doing it.
And believe me, none of us wants that to happen.
[CHUCKLING]
I see Hilton talked you into this, too, huh?
HILTON: Our season starts in two short days--
Yeah, Hilton has a way of doing that, doesn't he?
Yes, he does.
He is relentless. I--
HILTON: -- a lot of work you--
--tell you he just keeps coming at you.
HILTON: --refurbishing this year.
We've received bats, a new dugout.
In fact, we have a lot--
How are you and Harper doing?
Fine, just fine.
Great.
Good. That's good to hear.
HILTON: Hell, I know it takes a lot of--
Is there anything Laura and I can do?
No, we're OK.
Good.
That's good.
Hey!
Hey you!
Me?
Yeah, you.
Come here!
OK.
What can I do for you, sir?
Last night they told me I couldn't eat pizza.
Who told you that?
That quack, teenage doctor of mine.
He wrote on my chart that I couldn't have spicy food.
Oh, they brought me a tuna casserole.
Tuna casserole!
Well, tuna's good.
Sure, lightly grilled with a nice Dijon mustard sauce,
but not in a casserole with potato chips
sprinkled all over the top of it.
Trust me, it's terrible.
What did you do?
I told them that no teenage, quack doctor
was going to tell me whether I could
or could not eat spicy food.
So I went into the kitchen and got myself a bottle
of Tabasco sauce and I sprinkled it
all over that blasted casserole.
Well, you certainly made your point, then.
Yes, I did.
Unfortunately, it gave me the runs.
I thought for sure I was going to die in my sleep.
Point is, I'm still a man.
If I want to eat spicy food and get the runs,
that's my business.
I agree.
Darn straight!
I'm alive and I'm all here.
At least on most days.
You-- you run by here every day, don't you?
Yes, sir, I do.
Well, if you ever get bored and you want to talk,
why just wander up here.
Ask for Mr. Godfrey.
Mr. Godfrey.
I'll do that.
And, uh-- bring me a pizza or something, will you?
I'll see what I can do.
Harper?
Up here.
Hi.
What are you doing?
Field Library's having a book drive.
I was going to donate some of Nathaniel's books.
Is that OK?
Yeah, sure.
He didn't have that many, but for some reason
this seems to have taken most of the day.
It's OK.
We should have bought him more books, Bill.
I just-- I keep thinking a little boy
should have a lot of books.
If I ever get pregnant again we'll fill the house--
[SAD, LILTING MUSIC PLAYING]
I promise.
We'll have books everywhere.
Why'd we wait so long?
Why didn't we have another baby when
Nathaniel was a little boy?
I don't know.
I guess we just always felt complete.
You know, I'd forgotten how much he loved Custer He must
have had five books on Custer.
"Custer and the Battle of the Little Bighorn."
"George Armstrong Custer, Man Of Courage."
He loved Custer.
I have no idea why.
I should have asked him why.
I'll bring these books to the library tomorrow.
Hopefully, they can give them to another little boy.
[SIGHS]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[SAD, LILTING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ELECTRIC TRAINS HUMMING]
[TOY TRAIN WHISTLE]
You haven't been out here in a long time.
No, I guess I haven't.
You and Nathaniel used to come out here all the time.
So secretive, the door always closed.
What did you talk about?
I don't know.
Guy stuff.
Secret guy stuff.
Oh, I see.
Honey, uh-- there's this kid on my team.
His name is Diamond.
You ever heard of him?
No, no, doesn't go to our school.
I could ask some of the other teachers, if you like.
Yeah.
You taking this baseball team pretty seriously, aren't you?
No, just doing my homework.
OK, OK.
I just don't want it to make you unhappy.
It won't.
OK.
[TOY TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
You know, every once in a while
it would be nice to be a part of that secret guy stuff.
[TOY TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING]
Hi!
You from around here?
Oh.
Where do you live?
Off the logging road.
Really?
What's your name?
Lucky.
Lucky what?
Lucky Diamond.
He said he lived off the old logging road.
So?
So nobody lives up there.
Nathaniel and I used to hike up there all the time,
there aren't any houses.
Look, isn't it possible that in all your extensive hiking,
you missed one house?
Harper, there's not even a power line leading up there.
Why would he lie about that?
I don't know.
But there is something weird about this kid.
I don't believe you.
You meet a mute boy who won't give you an exact address
and you're ready to call in the grand jury.
OK, forget it.
I just hope he can play baseball.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Aw, it's gonna be a good year.
Oh, yeah, it's going to be a very good year.
You all right, Josh?
Yeah.
All right, let's pair up.
Throw the ball around and see what kind of arms we got.
Dickie you want to throw with Lucky?
I always throw with David.
OK.
Josh, how about you?
I promised I'd help Melissa.
Lucky?
[CHUCKLING]
Aw, burn out!
Ow!
All right, I quit.
I quit!
All right, Dickie, get one.
Melissa!
OK.
Josh!
Jill!
Atta girl!
Melissa!
OK, Melissa, um, look, get in the ready position.
Get your hands on your knees, crouch down, just like this.
Go ahead.
That's it.
All right, we got a man on first, ground ball at third,
let's get two.
Melissa, you ready?
Ready.
OK.
Hello, Melissa.
What?
Well, I said get to.
Get to what?
We'll come back to this tomorrow.
Come on in.
Huddle up.
Hustle, let's go!
Are there any questions before we knock off practice today?
Yes, Charlie?
Did you bring any snacks?
Oh, snacks.
No, I didn't.
[CHILDREN MOANING AND WHINING]
The coach always bring snacks.
He does?
Sometimes cool snacks, like ice cream.
Yeah, don't you know anything about baseball?
You babies.
We're not here to eat snacks, we're here to play ball.
Win some games.
Right?
No, I'm just here for the snacks.
[CHILDREN ALL LAUGH]
All right, I'll see what I can do about snacks for next time,
OK?
See you Wednesday. Get out of here.
When does the baseball season start?
Tomorrow afternoon.
Hilton Burberry still heading that up?
Yes, sir, he is.
He used to be a general manager of the Red Sox,
you know. - Is that right?
Yeah.
Well, it was a long time ago.
He doesn't talk much about it.
It ended very badly.
A ballplayer got drunk at a party at his house one night
and wrapped his car around a tree.
Ended very badly, indeed.
Those kids of yours ready to play ball?
Not at all.
Well, you got your hands full.
But enjoy every minute of it, Bill, every minute of it.
Because you may wind up where I did,
sitting on a porch watching other people living life.
And dreaming about the good old days
when you could eat all the pepperoni you wanted to.
How'd you like to be my assistant coach?
What?
Practice every day, games twice a week.
What do you say?
I don't know whether you've been paying attention, Bill,
but I am old.
That shouldn't stop you from coaching baseball.
Come on, I could use the help.
You sure about this?
First game's tomorrow afternoon.
Coaching baseball, huh?
Yep.
You're all right, Bill Parish.
Yes, sir, you're all right.
[ACADEMIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Ladies and gentlemen, Spring is here.
And once again it's time for baseball.
[FANS CHEERING]
As the commissioner of this league,
I want this to be our best season ever.
I don't want there to be any arguments, no harsh language,
and fighting will absolutely not be tolerated.
Now I also have a few words I'd like to say to the players.
Play hard.
Play well.
And play fair.
Enough speeches.
Let's play ball.
OK, come on.
Let's huddle up!
You heard the man, gather in here.
Panthers, I want you all to meet our new assistant coach.
His name is Mr. Godfrey.
He's going to be with us from now on.
You look old.
So?
You look stupid.
Charlie?
You all right there?
Sure, coach.
OK, now.
Let's all remember what we talked about in practice.
What is the most important thing to remember?
When someone throws you the ball, don't duck.
That's very good but that was more of a personal message
to you, Melissa.
Everybody stay alert, always be thinking
what you would do with the ball if it was hit to you.
And outfielders, remember--
Don't do cartwheels between pitches.
Well, I think that about covers it.
Hands in a circle.
What are we?
ALL: A team!
What's it going to take to win?
A lot of runs.
Yeah, and teamwork.
ALL: Teamwork!
All right, let's get out there and play some--
[CHEERING]
--baseball!
Yeah, I think that went pretty well, don't you?
Uh, Bill--
You know, I got to admit I was a little bit
nervous about our first game, but I
think we're going to do OK.
Uh, Bill--
Yeah.
You sent the team out on the field.
You see, we're batting first.
Ah!
Come on back in guys, we're up first.
Thanks.
No problem.
Come on, hustle up.
Let's go!
Anybody got an extra belt?
UMPIRE: Strike three, he's out.
ANNOUNCER: Next batter for the Panthers, number nine,
Melissa Jones.
Come on, now, Melissa, don't be afraid of it.
Be a hitter.
What?
UMPIRE: Strike!
I wasn't ready!
UMPIRE: Strike one!
He was talking to me, weren't you?
I was just yelling.
Well, why were you yelling at me?
I didn't get the strike until after you yelled.
UMPIRE: Can we get on with this game now, please?
I just said be a hitter.
Come on, Melissa, good eye, good eye.
What?
UMPIRE: Strike two!
He keeps on talking to me!
Melissa, it's just baseball chatter.
- Well, it's very distracting. - Well, I'll stop.
Thank you.
Oh yeah, it's going great.
UMPIRE: He's out!
Nice play.
Get fired up here, now.
Charlie, you're up.
Josh, on deck, Lucky, in the hole.
So last at bats, we need runs.
Get on base, Charlie.
I can't get a hit, send somebody else in.
Charlie, you got to stop worrying so much.
Just go out there and do the best you can.
That's all we're asking.
PANTHER: Go, Charlie!
ANNOUNCER: Now batting for the Panthers, number two,
Charlie Gray.
We need base runners, Charlie.
We need base runners, let's go.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BELL DINGS]
UMPIRE: Time!
Charlie, you OK?
Sure, coach.
Way to shake it off.
Hey Coach, what do I do now?
I've never actually been on base before.
Well, Mr. Godfrey's coaching first, you just listen to him.
Gotcha.
ANNOUNCER: Now coming to bat, number one, Josh Connolly.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BELL DINGS]
UMPIRE: Time!
Hey guys, it didn't hurt at all!
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
No wonder you guys talk like idiots.
You're always getting hit on the head.
Hey, I don't want to see anybody else let the ball him
them.
Next person does, sits out a whole game.
We understand each other?
Huh?
CHILDREN: Yes, sir.
Man!
Hey!
Two on, nobody out.
Nervous?
Great!
ANNOUNCER: Next up for the Panthers,
number three, Lucky Diamond.
UMPIRE: Play ball!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRACK OF BAT]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh yeah!
Yes!
Man, he nailed it!
[CROWD CHEERING]
Good game, guys.
Hey Lucky.
Your folks come to the game today?
Listen, if you don't have to be home any time soon,
why don't you come over and have dinner with my wife and me.
I can take you home afterward.
Yeah?
Come on.
Good game, by the way.
Lucky, I really wish you'd let us call your folks.
I don't want them to worry about you.
All right.
I'll just take you home after dinner, then, all right?
So Lucky, what do your folks do?
What do they do?
Maybe he doesn't want to talk about it.
Well, it's just a question.
I'm curious.
Do they work around here?
We might know them?
[SAD MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry.
[SAD MUSIC CONTINUES]
Listen, why don't I walk you in and meet your dad?
I really should, you know.
[SAD MUSIC CONTINUES]
Take out the trash.
You mad at me?
Why did you have to grill him like that?
I didn't grill him.
He obviously didn't want to answer the question.
Oh come on, Harper, he's hiding something.
There's something going on with that kid.
Maybe there is, and then again maybe
he's just a lonely little boy.
[HUM OF ELECTRIC TRAIN]
[TOY TRAIN WHISTLE]
Look, I'm sorry.
I don't want to fight about this.
You want to talk about it?
No, I'm all right.
You're obviously mad.
No, I'm not.
OK.
Maybe we ought to take this track apart and put it away.
Just like Nathaniel's room?
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, you couldn't wait to turn that into a guest room.
We agreed on that.
Both our parents were coming to visit for Christmas
and we needed the space.
We needed the space.
Harper, you want to take a look around?
Our lives are filled with nothing but space.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
(WHISPERING) Bill?
I-- I thought I heard him down here.
He was uh-- he was playing that baseball
game we made up with dice, do you remember that?
I remember.
I saw him.
Yeah-- I saw him.
I saw him, he was right here.
Yeah.
Hey Charlie, let's try grabbing on that ball
a little harder, all right?
Hey Charlie, you sure you want to be a pitcher?
Well, I can't play the outfield
and I can't play the infield and I'm too scared to catch.
Mm, then you're gonna be a fine pitcher.
But I need a catcher!
What you need is an arm.
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
[CHILDREN LAUGH MOCKINGLY]
All right, all right, that's not bad.
Pros do that all the time, right Mr. Godfrey?
No sober pro I've ever seen.
I can keep throwing.
I'll get better.
Yes, you will, Charlie.
But let's get better on another day, wha'dya say, huh?
All right, that's practice.
Come on in.
Game Thursday.
You're not going to let him pitch, are you?
Well, maybe he will get better, you never know.
Maybe he'll spout horns and give milk.
I don't expect that to happen either.
What's the matter?
What, your glove?
Where is it?
It's gotta be around here somewhere, don't worry,
we'll find it.
You driving that slow because of me or
are you just a lousy driver.
Careful, next time you'll walk.
I'd get hit quicker than if I was riding with you.
My wife, Ruby, was a demon behind the wheel.
That woman scared me to death.
Took my life in my hands every time I slid into the seat next
to her.
Stop signs, red lights, intersections,
meant nothing to her.
She just kept on driving and talking,
hands waving everywhere.
I miss all that.
I ever tell you about the day she died?
No, sir.
Well, she died of a stroke.
She laid down on the couch to take a nap
and she never woke up.
I'm sorry.
I came back from playing golf and there she was.
I just held her, I didn't cry.
I just rocked her back and forth in my arms for about a half
an hour.
Then the doorbell rang, I went to answer it.
It was this little Girl Scout.
It seems that Ruby had ordered some cookies
and she came around to collect.
Well, I went into the kitchen to find Ruby's purse.
And in her wallet was a picture of her
and my three grandchildren taken at the county fair.
There they were all looking up at me, smiling.
Laughing in the sun.
And Ruby had on this God awful hat.
It was made out of balloon animals, all
twisted to look like a crown.
I just burst out laughing.
There I was, my wife dead on the couch,
me laughing my head off in the kitchen.
You know, Bill, God inhabits the bitter and the sweet in life.
Ruby was always saying that.
And I never knew what it meant until that day.
She sounds like a very special woman.
That she was.
You ever see a 69-year-old woman
wearing a balloon animal hat?
I can't say as I have.
It's a beautiful sight.
Yeah, it's a beautiful sight.
Hi.
How are you doing?
You went to the doctor today, didn't you?
No, why would I go to the doctor?
You thought I was pregnant?
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
It's just, you know, you called and said
to come over right away, so-- - I didn't think.
I should have said it wasn't that.
I'm sorry.
No, it's all right.
So what's up?
It's Lucky.
I've been making some calls.
Wha'dya find out?
Well, I was right.
There is no special school in Groundhill,
there's just a public school, and they don't even have
any special education classes.
There are no special schools in this county.
Then he is lying.
He's never been registered in any public school
in this whole state.
There's no record of his father, nobody's talked to him,
it's like the two of them don't exist.
UMPIRE: Strike three, he's out.
It's nice that you're giving Charlie a start at third base.
Well, he hasn't played much this season and, uh--
his grandmother's in the stands.
Oh?
Is she a looker?
I'll introduce you.
It's good he's playing.
Course I've never actually seen him field a grounder.
Come to think of it, I've never actually
seen them catch a ball.
The truth is I wanted to bench Dickie Pratt.
How come?
I think he stole Lucky's glove.
Really?
You sure he just didn't lose it?
No, I'm pretty sure Dickie stole it.
C'mon coach, we need a better in here.
What's your hurry, Ump, you got a date?
Josh, you're up.
Lucky, on deck.
Let's go, come on, guys.
Let's go-- go!
ANNOUNCER: Next up for the Panthers,
number one, Josh Connolly.
Hey Lucky, your dad coming to the game today?
UMPIRE: Out!
Come on, Josh, look for your pitch.
Be looking for it.
Think I could meet him someday?
That's all right, Josh.
Good cut, good cut.
When can I meet him, Lucky?
UMPIRE: Play ball!
DICKIE: That kid doesn't know where anything is.
First his glove, now his dad.
That's enough, Dickie.
Got a hit, Lucky.
We need runners.
ANNOUNCER: Now batting, number three, Lucky Diamond.
UMPIRE: Foul ball!
Baseball is a dangerous game.
Lucky get his glove back yet?
Must be hard to play without a glove.
I lent him my old one.
They're pretty expensive, aren't they?
Yeah.
A good won can set you back--
--about eight lawns.
Remember?
That's right, he did, didn't he?
Nathaniel mowed every lawn on this street.
There aren't a lot of lawns up on that logging trail.
You want me to give him Nathaniel's glove?
Boy needs a glove, Bill.
I can't.
I just can't.
OK.
I think I'm gonna turn in, I'm pretty tired.
It's kind of early, isn't it?
Get used to it.
First three months are a killer.
What?
Wait a minute.
What are you saying to me?
Let's just say I feel very maternal.
Yeah?
[BOTH GIGGLING EXCITEDLY]
UMPIRE: Ball one!
Bases loaded, nobody out.
She's a tough kid.
She can finish the game.
UMPIRE: Ball two!
You need a pitcher, coach?
What do you think?
I think I'd rather have Melissa pitch.
UMPIRE: Ball three. - Yeah, I know.
It's just-- I feel so sorry for him.
He's so--
Dorky.
Yeah.
UMPIRE: Ball four, take your base.
Time.
UMPIRE: Time.
Loosen up, Charlie, you're going in.
I was born loose!
Oh, save us all.
You pitched a good game, Jill.
Why don't you go out play center field, have Lucky take a break.
Go on, you pitched a good game.
I've been working on a special pitch, coach.
It's sort of a knuckle change spitball.
Charlie, no special pitches.
Just throw the ball in the general direction
of the catcher and we'll hope for the best.
OK?
Gotcha.
MR. GODFREY: Good game, Lucky.
All right, Charlie, you're a pitcher now,
you gotta throw strikes.
It's nice what you did.
What's that?
Oh, well, the boy needed a glove,
it's no big deal, really.
UMPIRE: Play ball!
Charlie, the mound is fine. Quit digging!
Kid's digging a moat out there.
ANNOUNCER: Now batting the left fielder, Ronnie Jackson.
MR. GODFREY: Here we go.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Get the ball, Charlie!
Run!
UMPIRE: He's out!
Third, Charlie, third!
Third base, throw it to third base!
UMPIRE: You're out!
He's out!
ANNOUNCER: Holy cow!
That was a triple play!
[CHILDREN AND AUDIENCE YELLING  AND APPLAUDING]
Oh, man!
See, I told him I could pitch.
ANNOUNCER: Congratulations!
Boy, these kids were playing some ball.
Drive safely and we'll see you next week.
Well, that's too bad.
I was sure Lucky's father would stick around.
Mr. Godfrey?
Where am I?
You're at the ball field, remember?
Oh-- oh, Bill, yeah.
Yeah.
Listen, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm-- just very tired.
Why don't I take you home.
Yeah, good.
Did we win?
Yes, sir, we did.
I really hate to lose.
So do I.
Well, Hilton, this is a surprise.
You know, a family used to live here before the school
bought this place.
Furman, I think was their name.
This was the little girl's bedroom.
Loud girl, always yelling about something.
Hilton, is there anything you don't know about?
I try to know just enough about everything and everybody,
you never know when it might come in handy.
Bill, there was an accident today up at the notch.
Oh, what happened?
It seems a couple of loggers were loading up a skidder out
past the Goshen trail, and apparently something snapped,
and the logs came pouring off the skidder like a tidal wave.
One of the loggers was killed instantly.
Jeff Grout.
What happened to the other guy?
He ran away.
The state police believe this means
it was something more than an accident
but I prefer not to think that way.
Hilton, why are you telling me this?
The logger who ran away was Lucky's father.
They have a warrant out for him.
Oh, no.
Does Lucky know about it?
My wife went to get him, he's with the state police now .
I appreciate you telling me.
Well, I thought you should know.
Even if his father comes back, the state
will never let him keep custody of the boy now, not after this.
They will probably put him in some state foster home.
Too bad, he's a good kid.
You know, maybe you and I can put our heads together and come
up with something better.
What do you say?
You're hurting, Bill.
Everybody can see it.
Who knows, maybe this could help it get better.
Don't put me in this position.
Sounds like a good idea.
I can't do it!
The boy thinks the world of you.
No!
I'll stop by your place and see how he's doing.
That would mean a lot to him.
Just remember, nothing in this world happened by accident.
There's a reason for everything.
You just have to look deep enough to find it.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hi, Eunice.
I just stopped by to see how Lucky is doing.
Come on in.
He's in the den watching some baseball.
Where's Hilton?
I send him out to the store.
Sometimes I think it's best just to get him out from under foot.
[SOUND OF BASEBALL GAME ON TV]
Hey, buddy.
I can't stay.
I just wanted to--
just wanted to stop by.
Maybe I could sit with you for a minute
and watch some of the game.
That all right?
How is he?
He'll be OK.
Hilton thinks the boy's father will lose custody of Lucky,
if they ever find the guy.
From what we saw, he didn't appear to be much of a father
anyway.
That's true.
You know, Hilton came up with this crazy idea
that maybe you and I should consider taking Lucky in.
What did you say?
I said, no, of course.
There's all kinds of reasons why we can't.
I mean, we're still adjusting and, well, we just can't.
Shouldn't we at least have talked about it?
Why, you think I should have said yes?
No, no, I just thought--
What?
I just-- I just--
I just-- I can't believe what kind of a day it's been,
I just can't believe it.
Do not tell me they make you wash your own patrol car.
Nah, they give me a little cleaning
allowance in my check each week but if I
choose to do it myself--
Every little bit helps.
Exactly.
Listen, Jamie, I hear there was quite an accident up on Hilton
Burberry's property yesterday.
Yes, I was.
Mind if I ask you a couple of questions about that?
Sure.
I don't know that I'll answer them, but shoot.
You were the first trooper there, right?
Yeah, I was pretty close when the call came in.
Pretty bad, was it?
I've seen worse.
Logging is a pretty dangerous business.
Jamie, was he alone up there?
Well, of course he was.
You know, Jeff always worked alone.
Why?
You're sure there was nobody with him?
Like who?
Lucky Diamond's father.
Don't know him.
Well, he's a logger.
Really?
Never heard of him.
BILL: Let's go!
Everybody in.
Come on, let's move!
Why aren't you sweating?
All right, now it's extremely important
to anticipate what you would do if a ball were hit to you.
Melissa?
You with me on this?
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh, OK.
We'll be starting with the infield.
Charlie, man on first and third, one out, ball
hit to third, what do you do?
Hope I wasn't playing third base.
BILL: Let's say you were.
What would you do?
Well, I'd miss it.
But the ball would probably hit me in the chest.
Keeping the ball in front of you, that's good.
And then I'd see if the guy on third was going home.
That's very good.
That's excellent.
Hey, coach?
Yeah.
Why did Nathaniel have to die?
Why do you ask that now, Charlie?
I don't know, I just thought of it.
MELISSA: Why did he?
Yeah, why?
Well-- I can't tell you why.
But he got really sick.
And sometimes when people get really sick, they die.
Even kids?
Yeah, even kids.
I miss him.
So do I.
Me, too.
I miss him, too.
He was pretty funny.
Yeah, he did that thing where he'd
turn his eyelids inside out.
[CHILDREN ALL LAUGH]
And he could make real loud armpit noises.
He was cool.
Yes, he was.
He was very cool.
OK, game Thursday, don't forget.
Get outta here, go on.
Hit the showers.
Hey!
Hi!
What are you doing here?
Oh, I thought I'd like to watch you in action.
Where's Mr. Godfrey?
I don't know, he didn't show up today.
Did Hilton call?
No, you didn't talk to him today?
No, he never returned my calls.
Listen, honey, I ought to find out what's going on.
Why did he lie about the accident?
I don't know, but I don't want you to talk to Lucky about it.
I mean, maybe his father was unemployed, he was embarrassed.
He's going through a lot right now.
OK.
Wanna go get some ice cream?
Yeah, sure.
Want to take Lucky?
I said take him for some ice cream, not adopt him.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC, SUBDUED  CONVERSATION]
Bill!
Hilton?
You're suddenly a very hard man to get a hold of.
Been busy.
Why don't you stop by the house tonight and we'll talk.
No, I think we'll talk now.
I'm afraid this young man has a lot on his mind.
No problem, I was finished anyway.
I'll see you later.
Have you had lunch?
No.
Want some?
The shrimp and strawberry soup sounds horrible
but it was surprisingly good.
I didn't come here to eat lunch or talk about soup,
Hilton, you know that. - I know.
You came because I'm not as sharp as I used to be.
I came because you lied to me.
Same thing.
Why did you tell me Lucky's father was with Jeff Grout
when he died?
Oh, now that wasn't the question I expected.
I was sure you were going to ask me why I didn't tell Jamie
Sterman or any of his patrol buddies
that Lucky's old man was there.
He wasn't there.
I talked to Jamie yesterday.
And there was no police bulletin out for him
and Lucky was not waiting at the police station.
That's true.
He was with my wife.
Right after I heard about the accident,
I went out to the trailer and picked him up.
Then where was Lucky's father, because he
sure wasn't with Jeff Grout?
Bill, you have every right to doubt me.
But when Jeff Grout died, Lucky's old man disappeared.
That's a fact.
A fact, you want to explain to me why you
hid that fact from the police?
Because I hadn't figured out yet what to do with the boy.
No.
I don't believe you.
Lucky's father was never there.
Bill, you're a very smart man, and you've
obviously done your homework.
But you're just going to have to trust that I know
what I'm doing, because I do.
Now, how about that soup.
UMPIRE: Strike one.
C'mon, we need you on base, walk, single, double, anything.
UMPIRE: In there, strike two.
C'mon Dickie, take your cuts, don't be afraid of it.
It can't hurt you.
Are you kidding?
You can be killed!
[LUCKY TAPPING TWO BATS  TOGETHER]
[CHILDREN CHEERING]
All right, yes.
All right, that's it!
That's a rally start!
Let's go, Lucky!
No pitcher, no pitcher!
Little foot, move 'em out!
Little bingo, baby! Good for the punch!
Punch it through!
Hit a screamer, Texas leaguer, out of the yard!
Take 'em deep!
Brown tripper, tater-tot, bat, bat, bat!
Gone, holy cow!
ANNOUNCER: Now stepping out, number three, Lucky Diamond.
Good job, Lucky.
[CHILDREN CHEERING]
Hello?
Hi.
Um, could you tell me where Mr. Godfrey is,
he didn't show up at our game today.
He's dead.
What?
Dead.
Died yesterday.
Oh.
OK.
Thank you.
Mr. Godfrey?
(SHOUTING) Mr. Godfrey!
What?
Can't you be quiet.
Some very old people living around here,
don't you know that?
Well, I'm sorry, but the lady in the lobby
said you were dead.
Oh, that's Tilda.
She always pulls that on visitors.
Sick sense of humor on that woman, but a darn good kisser.
Come on.
C'mon, I want to talk to you anyway.
Wow, nice TV.
Did you see the TV in the lobby?
Nineteen inches and no remote.
It's ridiculous.
You want to-- you want to stay for supper?
It's Thursday.
Actually, I think we have solid food tonight.
No, actually, I just stopped by to make sure you were OK.
Maybe some other night.
Hopefully, another solid food night.
OK, well, go on.
I'll see you later. - All right.
Uh, no, Bill.
They're making me leave.
They're sending me to someplace in New Hampshire.
A place with more hands-on care.
I've been blanking out lately.
You know, like I did at the game last week.
Oh well, why don't you let me talk to them?
Oh no, no, please don't do that.
It's all right the way it is, really it is.
Well, when are you leaving?
Tomorrow.
I-- we-- we've still got a couple of games left,
I mean the kids need you.
Maybe they can put this off for a while.
No, no, it's OK, really.
I just wanted to say goodbye.
I just wanted to take that and don't
open it until you get home.
Bill, you've been a good friend.
Asking me to help with the kids has made me feel useful.
I haven't had many chances to feel like that lately.
You should at least say goodbye to them.
At my age, you kinda want to limit your goodbyes.
You do it for me, will you?
OK.
And Bill, it's good that you care for those kids.
But you take care of you.
Me?
I'm fine, just fine.
I'm great.
Just great.
Mr. Godfrey, I'm falling apart here,
and I don't know what to do about it.
Pain is everywhere, Bill.
It's surrounds us all.
It hangs in the air waiting for us
and one day it decides to stick.
You can't avoid it.
You can't shake it.
You can only make your peace with it.
Now, why don't you go home to that wife of yours.
I don't even know your first name.
Ed.
Thanks for everything, Ed.
My pleasure.
You know, one of the regrets of my life,
it's not something I said, something I did,
just that I worried too much, took things too seriously.
Ruby knew that and she tried to tell me, but I never got it.
I'd sit in the front seat and cringe and let her run
all the red lights.
Don't forget that, Bill.
You think of me once in a while and floor it!
I will.
[HORN BEEPING ON COP CAR]
Hey, Bill.
Jamie.
I was just headed out to your house to come talk to you.
Something wrong?
No, no, no, no, no, everything's fine.
I just need you to tell me everything
you know about Lucky's father.
Oh, well, I don't know much.
He's a logger.
Drives a blue truck.
Doesn't seem to take much interest and his kid.
I've never met him.
I was afraid of that.
I did some nosing around yesterday.
Put out an APB for the truck and I made some calls.
Yeah, what did you find out?
Well, Lucky Diamond was born in Boston.
And his mother was a 15-year-old runaway.
Other than that, we don't know anything.
And that truck you were talking about?
Yeah.
That truck belongs to Hilton.
Harper?
In here.
Oh my, I was about to send out a search party.
Ooh!
I just saw Jamie.
That blue and white truck Lucky's father drives
belongs to Hilton.
You're kidding?
So he's logging Hilton's land, he's driving Hilton's truck.
I'm going over there to get some answers.
Who's here?
Lucky.
Eunice dropped him by.
He's out back.
You should have seen his eyes when I showed him the trains.
Come on, say hello.
You're out here running the trains?
It took me a half hour to figure out how to turn them on.
We derailed them three times before we
finally got the hang of it.
Oh!
Lucky came up with this great idea
to add a mountain with a trestle.
Now, it'll probably cost a fortune
but I think we ought to try it.
I thought you, um--
I thought you wanted to tear all that stuff out of there.
Well, yeah, but that was--
why are you getting upset?
I'm not upset.
Just you've never shown any interest in those trains
before, that's all.
I was always interested, you just never thought to notice.
Look, why don't you come join us,
you can talk to Hilton tomorrow.
No.
I've got to talk to him tonight.
OK, fine, fine!
I just thought it might be more fun for us to do this together.
But I guess that room always has been a little too
small for three people.
What does that mean?
There's a reason that door was always closed, Bill,
and it wasn't because you wanted to talk about secret guy stuff,
it was because you didn't want to share him with anybody,
not even me.
That's not true.
It is, Bill, you liked to keep him to yourself.
Baseball, trains, hiking, camping,
you cultivated interests with just the two of you,
I was always the outsider.
You even invented your own board games that just the two of you
knew how to play!
We would have included you, if you'd asked.
Included me!
Bill, we're talking about a family
here, not choosing sides for kickball.
Come on, Lucky.
You know why Nathaniel was an only child?
Why we waited so long to have another baby?
It's because it would have made Nathaniel
seem not quite so special.
[CRYING] And I don't think you would have
been able to deal with that.
Well, the trains are all yours, Bill.
Hello, Bill.
I love to come out here at night.
I look at the lake, watch the fish jump.
The mosquitoes eat me alive sometimes,
but I guess it's worth it.
Who's Lucky's father?
(CHUCKLING) You're a man who likes to get right to it,
aren't you?
Did you know his mother?
Suzy?
No, not really.
She was a child.
She had no idea what she was getting herself into.
And just what was she getting herself into?
HILTON: [SIGHS]
Come on, Hilton.
Where's Lucky's father?
And how were you involved in all this?
You know, a person can make a lot of mistakes
in the course of one lifetime.
Baseball players are no different.
They drink too much, they gamble,
they spend too much time at work, not enough time
with their families.
In short, they're just rotten Joe's just like the rest of us.
They just have a lot further to fall than most of us do.
Lucky's father is a baseball player?
Lucky's father was a baseball player.
Ben Slaughter, rookie of the year in 1982.
Sweetest swing I ever saw.
He the guy--
--who wrapped his car around a tree after
leaving a party in my house.
His blood alcohol was twice the legal limit.
They said he was doing 92 when he hit the tree.
Ninety-two miles an hour on a quiet suburban street.
Suzy Diamond came forward at the funeral
and told me that she was three months pregnant.
She was 15 years old.
I got her a job in Boston.
She never got married.
She worked.
She poured everything she had into that boy, Lucky.
And she died about a year ago--
cancer.
Lucky stayed with various relatives but none of them
had any room for him.
So I brought him here and I paid Jeff Grout to watch him for me
until I could find him a home.
Meaning Harper and me.
You lost a boy.
Everyone in town could see the pain you were in.
You set us up.
I told you nothing happens in this world without a reason.
So getting me to coach baseball,
putting Lucky on my team, that was
all part of a big ploy to manipulate Harper
and me into adopting him?
Just who do you think you are?
You can't go around controlling people's lives like that!
Bill, when Lucky's mother died, that boy was lost.
I swore to him that I would find him a home.
I felt I owed him that much.
No!
You're playing God with people's lives.
This is not the Red Sox.
We're not players you can just trade around.
If I had come to you four months ago
and asked you to take him in, would you have done it?
Of course not.
You needed time.
You both needed time.
Coaching those kids gave you that time.
You had no right.
Maybe not, but I did it, and I can't change it now.
Redemption, Bill.
We all want redemption.
A chance to set things right.
To restore some semblance of order.
We both have a chance to do that now.
Don't we?
[GENTLE, LILTING MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, Bill, God inhabits the bitter
and the sweet in life.
Ruby was always saying that and I never knew
what it meant until that day.
[QUIET, LILTING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on.