[fireworks exploding]
[calming music]
[film reel rolling]
[whoosh]
[slam]
[sparkle fade]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[ominous music]
[electric crackling sounds]
[sports buzzer]
[sports whistle blowing]
[ball bouncing]
[crowd cheering]
[upbeat classical music]
Dominoes, the greatest game
ever invented mother fuckers.
Good evening, ladies
and gentlemen,
Wannabe domino players,
fans, groupies,
and niggas sick
and tired of losing
all the motherfucking time.
Welcome to my Masterclass.
I am the Pimpfesser
Dr. DMF, AKA Big Dub.
Look, I'm here to
explain this shit,
so sit down and
shut the fuck up.
See dominoes was
started by the Chinese.
Down in the Compton
part of China.
[laughs loudly]
[gun shots ring]
- Back in the war.
- [Man] What war?
Would you shut the fuck up?
I told you I'm on TV.
It don't matter what war.
Nigga we got so many, who cares?
Yeah, shut the fuck up.
Like I was saying before
I was rudely interrupted.
[cart speeds off]
My great-great-great-
great-grandfather
learned the game
from the Chinese.
He snatched the big six.
We wrote the whole damn game.
Then he smuggled
it back to America.
Where it spread like
mudbutt on ribs.
You dig?
Mother fuckers from all parts
of the world took to it.
'Cause see, that's
the magic of dominoes.
It brings people together.
Even the saltiest motherfucker
will pull that stick
out of their ass when they
sit down and throw them bones.
28 bones to be exact.
Yeah, yeah I know, real bones
are white and so are dominoes,
but they wouldn't mean shit
if it wasn't for them
black dots, you feel me?
[laughs]
Can I get a witness?
[Man] Black power, alright.
Ah fuck you.
Big six is the highest number.
Match the numbers in
your hand to seven
with the bones on the table.
If you can't play,
that's when you draw from
the boneyard until you can.
Score in multiples of five,
and play until you
have your last domino.
And when that's gone,
you yell "Domino!"
Or as we say in the hood,
"Domino motherfucker!"
To let them know you run shit.
[sighs]
And that's all there is to it.
Buy my app, if you're too slow
to figure the rest
of this shit out.
Now, for real, shut the fuck up
while I watch the wildest,
ratchetest domino tournament
ever played.
[laughs loudly]
I know y'all ain't ready.
[hip-hop music]
♪ 50 on my waist
fuck out my face ♪
♪ We can not relate can't ♪
relate bitch I'm way too paid ♪
♪ I just hit a bank hit ♪
a bank feel like 50K ♪
♪ Watch me run it
up I run it up ♪
♪ All up in your face ♪
♪ Watch me run it up hey ♪
I can't get enough damn ♪
♪ She gon give me top yeah ♪
let's go hit the cook now ♪
♪ Stick stuff in they cup aye ♪
♪ We don't give no fucks aye ♪
♪ Keep a shooter with me ♪
♪ Since you think you
can't get touched ♪
♪ Drop top purple walk hey ♪
♪ Yeah I lean a lot she ♪
just want to fuck me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm thumbing
through this knot ♪
♪ We is not the same 'cause ♪
you be fucking with the cops ♪
♪ Keep her right up on me I ♪
ain't fucking with the ops ♪
♪ 50 on my waist
fuck out my face ♪
♪ We cannot relate
bitch I'm way to paid ♪
♪ I just hit a bank
feel like 50K ♪
♪ Watch me run it up run it up ♪
♪ All up in your face ♪
♪ Watch me run it up hey ♪
♪ Watch me run it
up I run it up hey ♪
♪ Watch me run it up hey ♪
♪ Watch me run it up I run ♪
it up all up in your face ♪
♪ Pull pull pull
up to the scene ♪
♪ Phantom ice and beams ♪
♪ Clutching heavy on this ♪
thing about to let it sing ♪
♪ And we taking everything ♪
that's on everything ♪
[birds chirping]
[water running]
Another mother fucking day.
[gargles and spits]
[smooth hip hop music]
You have to get up to get down.
♪ These haters wanna
bring me down ♪
♪ That's why I
don't come around ♪
Aah, I hate that nasty ass shit.
Let's do this.
[smooth hip hop music]
♪ 'Cause niggas
be weird as shit ♪
♪ If I don't never do no ♪
favors I ain't owe you shit ♪
♪ I don't be coming round to ♪
much you be on bogus shit ♪
♪ Trying to oversell me ♪
OJ get promoted shit ♪
♪ But I be over shit and ♪
what the fuck is it ♪
♪ I'ma do some shitty
strictly of the ♪
[indistinct chattering]
[smooth hip hop music]
[Man] It's all
good, what's going on?
We got dominoes, we
got food going man.
[Man] Now look
at this shit man,
they crazier than
a motherfucker.
♪ 'Cause I don't want
to hear that shit ♪
What you gon' do?
Tension on the compound,
tension on the compound,
What you got to say
about that baby?
Chinese man say same thing.
[sighs loudly]
[laughs softly]
[Man] All right, all
right, all right, all right.
[Gerald] Alright.
There you go, what
you gon' do now?
The rate is switching bitches
Damn you be cheating
Gerald, you ain't shit.
Let me see if these
motherfuckers won.
My daddy always said,
"If you can rock these
bones, you can start a cult."
I breaks champions over
these tables every day.
That's the real juice of
being a true dominologist.
A domi what?
Dominologist, I
psychologically abuse
and dominate a man's soul
and spirit across any table.
Gerald, shut
the fuck up. Okay?
[harp chord chime]
[optimistic peaceful music]
- [Woman] We did it.
- [Man] We did it.
This is love, this
is what I call love.
- I know.
- You understand me?
We are gonna have
so much fun in Cabo.
Cabo!
[laughs]
You know what?
I'm so happy that Andy's gonna
be staying with your pops.
Listen, I can't wait
for Andy to meet my pop.
Trust me, it's gonna be great.
My father is a father, father,
he gon' take care of him.
I know, you're so lucky baby.
Because my father, he was shit.
And your pop seems so
hype on the FaceTime.
And Compton
[sighs]
The art, and
culture and museums.
Why are you going to Cabo
and I'm going to Compton?
Where's Compton?
I heard that Compton's
become so hentrified
in the last couple of months.
Hentrified?
Yeah, hentrified and
like, all cleaned up.
Yeah, I'm with you.
- [Woman] Cabo.
- [Man] We on the way.
Can I come to Cabo?
- We're on the way
- Ooh
Fiesta, fiesta.
We can't get
there quick enough.
I hope you got nine lives,
'cause I'm finna eat
the cat from the back.
Who are you?
How are you even my dad?
Meow, blow me a kiss baby.
[blows kiss]
Oh, ooh ooh ooh, it's so strong.
[slaps herself]
Right where I like it.
Come ride this tally whacker.
Jeez.
Stick it in my pocket.
- Love, love.
- Cabo.
Cabo.
[car door bangs]
Listen we finna get it in!
We finna get it in!
Hey, quit stalling nigga,
'cause you've been
talking shit all morning
trying to avoid
this ass whooping.
- Stalling?
- Let's do it.
Do you think
I'm scared of you?
Yeah.
I ain't scared of
nothing but dying.
You've been dying
for me all day.
[laughs loudly]
Let's run it, let's
run it back then.
Let's run it back.
[phone rings]
Hold, hold, hold up.
Junior, why you calling
me this time of the AM?
Yeah, yeah, I know about
the boy and everything.
Listen I told you,
that girl was just
having the jungle fever.
Jungle fever?
You were supposed
to get rid of her.
Now you done married her,
now I got this obligation.
You know, I got big shit popping
around here this weekend.
I'm over here rehearsing
for this domino tournament.
- You ain't gon' win shit.
- That I'm gon' win.
Come on now, what?
Listen, you know white
kids is a problem.
They bad luck. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, I'll be there,
giving me orders like I
work for the government.
What's this shit?
I'll be there in a minute.
Tell him to look for
a elderly Denzel,
and a classic Ella Ryder.
Yeah, yeah, I'll be
there in a minute.
Bye.
Denzel, really?
Watch them bones.
[airplane engine roars]
[door slams]
[birds chirping]
[Gerald grunts]
Rufus.
Hurry up and finish my ride
so you can come on in here
and let me whoop
that ass for you.
Didn't I whoop your old
last night in those dominoes?
You was dreaming.
[quirky instrumental music]
[phone beeps]
Domino motherfucker.
[sighs]
Domino.
[airplane engine roars]
[car engine roars]
[old school hip hop music]
Hey little boy,
your name Andy?
- [airplane engine roars]
- [Andy] Yeah.
Come on over here, I've
been waiting on you for hours.
Running up all my gas.
[door slams]
[old school hip hop music]
[cars revving]
You know you're eating
in my practice time
showing up late boy.
I got to get ready
for this tournament.
The World Domino Championship!
[explosion]
It's cracking y'all!
Bones are gonna break, and
the world's gonna shake.
As the greatest dominoes master
in the whole damn universe,
universe, universe
is crowned!
We're talking a grand
prize of 10,000 big ones.
So bring your baby mama
and the whole damn fam.
'Cause it's going
down, down, down.
Where?
This luxurious
Compton rent-a-space.
So act like you know, and be
there or be a punk ass bitch.
[fire explodes]
West side.
Huh? You like that, huh?
Oh, that is fly stuff, man.
Fly stuff. This
is gonna go viral.
- Yeah?
- [Walter] I know it.
[phone rings]
Oh, sorry.
Can you just give me a second?
- [Camera man] Yeah, sure.
- Oh, thank you.
Hey Shauna,
did you see the graphics
of the bouncing low riders?
[Shauna] No, I don't give a
damn about low riders, Walter.
Yeah, it's pretty
fly stuff right?
Yeah, we're getting
dozens of responses.
[Shauna] Where's
the damn money?
What, no?
[Shauna] That's why our
credit's in the damn toilet.
What do you mean our
credits in the toilet?
In fact, it depends on
how your defining toilet.
[Shauna] That's
money for the kids.
No.
[Shauna] I'm gonna take them.
You can't take the
boys away from me.
[Shauna] I'm leaving and
they're coming with me.
Oh my God, just.
I really got a good feeling
about this, this is the big one.
[Shauna] That's it,
it's the last straw.
Just stick with
me, honey, honey!
[Camera man] Everything okay?
Ah yeah, yeah, yeah, if you
could, just give me a sec.
[Camera man] Yeah.
[Walter sobs loudly]
[chill hip hop music]
This is my kitchen.
Where I cook things I like.
I don't know what
white folks like.
That's the living room.
That's where I play dominoes.
Hey, hey, don't touch that!
Still got a game going.
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
Who's she?
That's Ella May.
Sweetest most faithful
woman to ever live.
[harp fading in]
Ella, I wanna
give you something.
I wanna give you this ring.
Gerald, Where'd you
get this ring from?
I know you didn't buy me no
ring with no gambling money.
I don't want no gambling ring.
I told you I ain't
gambling no more.
I got this ring with
my hard earned money,
and I want you to have it.
I ain't lying.
Then I'll wear it,
and cherish it forever!
Shit, you better cherish
that damn ring forever.
You with me for the long haul.
Till death, do us part.
Okay.
[mosquito buzzing]
Goddam mosquito.
Where the waiter at? Goddamn.
Been waiting for our
damn food for 30 minutes.
All they brought us
is some damn wine.
I'm hungry!
[harp fading out]
That's your room on the left.
Wait a minute.
Slow your roll son.
Everything in here
is important to me.
I don't want you to forget that.
Neat, I definitely
will, Granddad.
And I'm not your granddad!
Do we look related?
My good for nothing,
all the time, son
ditched you on me.
And that's what this
is, social service.
So since we gotta be
trapped in here together,
I got some rules and shit.
Don't touch nothing
that ain't yours.
Wash your ass, keep
my house clean,
and make yourself useful.
White privilege is a foreign
term in Compton, boy.
If you didn't
know, now you know.
And that's my room on the right.
Whoa, that's a lot of pills.
Hey, don't touch those.
They're for my heart.
I forget them sometimes.
So you see them lying
around, leave them be.
And you must be Ms. Jeffries.
Mr. McDonough.
Yes, Walter McDonough,
so nice to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you.
Please, let me show
you around the venue.
Now, Pastor recently
bought this place.
So it's still a
work in progress.
Oh, don't mind the mess.
As long as you don't
mind my camera crew here!
You're so gorgeous!
You should be in the movies!
Oh, I wish I was.
I mean, this crib could
use some renovations.
I mean, wasn't
Jesus a carpenter?
Yes, and a divine one.
Oh, all right.
Well, hopefully
he'll come back soon.
We could really use him, huh?
You know, I'm just,
I'm like a chameleon.
I'm always rebuilding
myself, rebranding.
After 34 years of
award-winning service,
they just revoked my
retirement fund, huh?
I guess you don't send a
little old mimis around
with the lady showing her-
But, uh, you know,
so I had to dabble in a
lot of different things.
And some of them were just
right before their time.
[chuckles softly]
You know, they say
you miss a 100%
of the shots you don't take.
So I'm glad I took those swings.
It's just unfortunate that
they ricocheted right back
and hit me in the nuts.
Oh, this way to
the pastor's office.
He should be in there now.
Give you a hand there.
Thank you, Mr. McDonough.
There you go.
Follow me.
[pastor praying quietly]
Goddamn, Ms. Jeffries.
Even the Devil knocked twice.
I was just spreading some...
[Ms. Jeffries] God comes
in a thief in the night.
[Pastor] Yeah, He do.
Okay, we brought a
guest, a visitor.
Pastor Steele, this
is Mr. Walter McDonough.
He's the gentleman who's
going to rent the venue
tomorrow afternoon.
His crew is loading
in right now.
Okay, you got my check, right?
Yeah, yeah, I sure do.
It's right here.
Yeah, there you go.
All right, all right.
Thank you, Jesus.
All right, Ms. Jeffries,
You go and run that
money down to the bank.
You know, take care of,
and I'll put you on
[indistinct] later, all right?
Be marching with you, okay?
Shit, for an old lady,
Ms. Jeffries got ass.
But anyway, you know, this
was a Mexican restaurant.
And they was selling
some nasty tacos.
That's why it shut
down, but you know,
and then I decided to
get ordained by the Lord
and we went into
business together.
So we got a lot to do, man.
A lot to catch up on.
So I'm going to
take y'all around
in the spirit of the Lord.
[chill hip hop music
playing softly]
Granp...
Mr. Edges, your food is ready.
Hot damn Rufus,
it's been your play
for the last five
fucking minutes.
Mr....
Not now, boy!
Can't you see I'm busy?
[Andy sighs]
What, boy? You're
breaking my concentration.
Well, your food's ready.
My mom says the body needs
three square meals a day
to be happy and healthy.
You sure she stopped at three?
What I need is to play somebody
who ain't just sold their fridge
to get that China Brown.
[Rufus snoring]
What I need is somebody
I can talk shit to.
You can talk shit to me.
Watch your fucking
mouth in my house.
What you know about them bones?
It's basic
probability, really.
It all comes down to
how many variations
of numbers you can play
based on the factors of
the hand you've drawn.
And then you calculate the
most efficient statistical one,
until you're down
to a single tile.
You mean you know
how to play this shit?
Well, I, uh, yeah.
Hell, Andy!
Shit!
Hell!
Damn!
Shit!
Why didn't you say so?
Rufus.
Rufus!
Take your ass home!
No, no way down
to the damn floor.
Go on home, you
ain't no good here!
I'm gonna call your mama
and tell you on your way.
You know I ain't got no car.
You calling me an Uber?
Uber?
The fuck is a Uber?
I got some Goobers.
You want some peanuts?
Bye, Rufus.
Let's see what you got.
Watch them.
[mellow hip hop music]
That's all you got?
[dominoes clacking on table]
That a bitch!
Your mama do voodoo or
something like that?
Damn!
Is white privilege in Compton?
Domino?
[vinyl record squeaking
to a sudden stop]
The fuck just happen?
What kind of Twilight Zone
have I just slipped into?
Is this what a
stroke feels like?
Sorry, well, my mom
says I don't make friends
because they're intimidated
by my intellect.
And that I should be
proud of my gifts.
I try to listen to her.
But it's hard to see your inner
light, or much light at all,
when you're stuffed
inside your locker.
Yeah.
Well how the fuck did your
little albino sausage fingers
learn to throw bones like that?
Oh, from this app.
App?
The fuck is a app?
It's a way you can
play people on the phone.
It was actually
beating the AI system
that got me so proficient
at it and the...
Fuck, wait a goddamn minute!
You're telling me you ain't
playing against people
just your damn phone?
Well, there are other
opponents on their phones, too.
The fuck is the
world coming to!
Dear God, Jesus, you oughta
just come back and kill us all.
Oh, bring the rapture, Lord.
Look.
You can't play bones
with a screen, boy.
Dominoes, real dominoes is
all about the mental game
just as much as
it is the numbers.
You hear me?
We got a lot of training to do...
We?
I'm sorry, I just, I
can't cheat for you.
My mom would...
It ain't cheating actually.
Niggas do bones with a spotter.
You do wanna be a
real nigga, don't you?
Ah, don't you answer that shit.
I see that shit eating
grin on your face.
Look, I need a spotter.
You wanna be a real nigga.
Everybody wins.
So come on.
Let's practice.
What's you got in your hand?
Double six.
No, no, elephant ass, no.
It's called Big Six!
Look, I don't want you
getting laughed off the table
with your Oxford English
motherfucking speaking ass.
All right?
Lord, help me, he
got a ways to go.
You know, you sure talk a lot
but I'm beating you 75 to 25.
Are you?
You think you're winning, huh?
What I see across from me
is a neglected little boy.
You know my son is
[chair squeaking]
pumping your momma right now.
Putting an integrated
baby in her with my DNA.
That's going to be
stronger, faster,
and a million times more
mocha latte lovelier than you.
And when that baby comes,
it ain't gonna take no time
forgetting your pasty, two
tons of fun ass ever existed.
[slams domino onto table]
Domino.
See.
You don't win at bones unless
you get in the folks head.
The game is all mental.
I'm tired of this game.
Why don't you me about
that scary devil guy
you were talking about?
Never mentioned that
guy's name in my house.
And if there is a God,
he'll give me my revenge
at this tournament
I'm training for.
I want the whole
world to see me whoop
that tweaking bully's ass!
[funky music]
See, usually ladies,
I don't mingle amongst
them gangster thug
sober motherfuckers.
Who in the fuck gonna
gang bang if you're sober?
That's silly, I
don't trust them.
See, if I want to win this
tournament and get my crown,
I had to call in the
baddest gangster bitches
security guards I know.
And it was you and you.
You gotta understand
this is about me.
I am the greatest
motherfucker that ever lived.
There's God.
And then,
there is me!
[laughing loudly]
[snorting cocaine loudly]
[high pitched excited yelling]
[funky music]
You know the Lord
laid his hand down
in this one right here.
You know, this is the room.
You know, this is the one
for all my entrepreneurs.
You know, the big wigs.
- Yeah man, what a blessing.
- So, but this is the lobby?
Oh yeah, yeah, what a
blessing, what a blessing.
Well it just seemed like the
pictures made it look bigger
in the pamphlet.
Yeah, we do that.
Namita, hold off one second.
Is this ceiling load-bearing?
Uh, partially.
Hey, God bless you.
Well, let's just
hold off for a second.
Till I get this figured out.
I got a lot of run
running on this
and I can't have any lawsuits
'cause I've technically
maxed out my credit cards
and put a lien on my house.
But it's all good.
It's all good.
Whoa!
Oh, I gotta sit down.
Woo, who knew?
But yeah, it's good.
You know, I haven't
seen my kids in a while.
Ever since my wife threw me out.
She said, and I quote,
"I'm an abject failure and
a complete joke of man."
But I think this tournament's
gonna turn everything
around, right?
[claps]
Yeah!
We can do this, right?
Namita, give me, give it up.
All right, yeah.
My name is Namita Sodhi.
I am the event coordinator
and general task master
for the WDC.
I'd like to say, for the record,
that I'm here to serve my
client's personal needs
and tastes.
And that if I were
running things,
my decisions would have been,
different.
But considering the I'm
the only, even marginally,
competent person here,
I think things could have
turned out a lot worse.
And by that, I mean we've
yet to have anyone seriously,
injured.
[ladder clacking]
[Man] Oh, shit.
This is fucking heavy.
Oh shit, shit, shit!
[glass and metal crashing]
And this is my
prize back here.
'Cause the Lord said,
"Let there be light!"
[electricity zapping]
There it is.
Oh, yeah.
Does that happen a lot?
Oh, when you got
Jesus on the main line,
anything is possible.
Okay.
And I call this my incubator.
These are the companies
and the brands that I own.
It's not for you.
I got some big stuff for you.
I got the big room for you.
This is just
collaborations of brands
I wanted to introduce
you to, you know,
like I can partner with you.
Well, it's nice.
It's not exactly
what I envisioned
but what's that saying?
"A shoddy craftsman
blames his tools."
[Pastor laughing]
I don't know what the
fuck you talking about
but do you wanna
partner with Mac Woo?
Macaroni and sushi?
Bomb.
Oh, sure we're always
looking for sponsors.
Yeah, I'm just really
excited to get going here.
It's gonna be a great show.
Me too.
And so when Ms.
Jeffries' cash that check
and it go "cha-ching",
then we can go.
Until then, you don't want
me and the Lord on your ass.
No, no I don't.
Don't don't make
me pray for you, boy.
Okay.
[sighing exasperatedly]
[electricity buzzing]
Oh, come on! Namita!
Can you please do
something about this light?
Hey, Walter, it's cool.
I got this.
[sighs loudly]
I'm sorry.
We just got such a
big show planned.
People are gonna be asking
you what are you doing here?
They'll be all up in your grill.
But fact of the matter is,
once we have our winner,
we'll be able to edit this
together in a nice tight promo.
And sell it to a
couple of investors
I got coming out
on tournament day.
So, everything goes as planned,
we're gonna be in business.
[Cameraman] You really
think you can get this off
without a hitch?
Well, you know what?
I've pretty much
lost everything.
So what's the worst
that could happen, huh?
His dumbass got no idea.
Follow me, ladies.
I'm trying to tell y'all
and then when we do
what we gotta do.
What the fuck?
Do you know who
the fuck that is?
No, cuz.
Well kick the
motherfucker in the ass!
Get him!
[women yelling]
[man grunting and yelling]
[laughing loudly]
This is my brother!
Ain't these some bad
motherfuckers, aint they?
You better tell them who I am!
Okay, calm down,
calm down, calm down.
We don't need to
kill my brother.
Boy, y'all are some bad
motherfuckers though.
Now y'all get back over there.
Take my keys, what we doing
[whispers softly]
This ain't WWF motherfucker!
I'm gonna take your ass-
[yelling and arguing]
Hold on, killas!
Calm down.
There's plenty of ass to kick.
It's cool, shit, hold up.
This is important to me.
Excuse me, she's calling me.
[snorting loudly]
Ain't nothing more beautiful
than breaking a
motherfucking domino.
When you break a
motherfucker in dominoes
it's like breaking their
motherfucking soul!
Let me show you
motherfuckers something.
See this shit here?
[locks clicking]
[mimicking angels singing]
Y'all do this shit?
No.
No, thanks.
You wanna start?
[trippy music]
It's like 37
orgasms at one time.
Now, what we're gonna do,
is this right here.
Follow me.
[roller skates screeching]
[funky psychedelic music]
Look at it!
Look around.
Don't touch nothing!
This right here, ladies,
my greatest prized possession!
[laughing]
[upbeat funky music]
Domino D.
This motherfucker was
undefeated, never lost a game!
I tore his ass up just when
he thought he had it made!
[short quick yelps]
And the nigga passed out.
I went to his funeral.
Best funeral I ever been to.
Boy, I enjoyed it.
[sighs loudly]
Gerald Edges.
I've been beating this
motherfucker his whole life.
Even with his wife dying.
I just don't give a fuck.
I got his ring.
I love beating
this motherfucker.
And when I beat this dude again,
my book will be complete!
Domino OG, I hate to do
it to you but I had to.
Ah, man.
Man, Calvin, I'll
catch you little later.
I'ma get you.
[Calvin] All right, my man.
[indistinct]
What's up, buzzard?
What's happening, man?
Let's [indistinct] blood,
what's happening, man?
What you been doing?
Uh, nothing, nothing.
I ain't seen you in
a good minute, bruh.
I had probably thought
you were up and relocated
or something.
Ah, shit, nah man. It just
happened like that, man.
You know what I'm saying?
I've been in the
wind, you feel me?
I had to get relocated a little
bit, you what I'm saying?
I'm out to play my priorities,
blood, you feel me?
Prison, nigga.
Okay, right, right.
I understand every word
you just said, man.
Shit, I see you're
still representing
for the Swetto, blood.
That's what's up.
Oh, for sure. For sure.
I rep every day.
I wake up in the morning saying
Sewoo-nothing but the blood!
I even do them when I go to bed.
Sewoo, I pray. [snoring loudly]
All right, what's up.
I'd be happy to be free,
you know what I'm saying.
'Cause like with
the Lord on my side,
I can go down a righteous
path, you feel me?
And put all that shit behind me.
I'm tryna win this domino
tournament, you feel me?
and get all the bread from that.
And get my own spot.
So right now, I'm
at the point where
every time I think about beating
the shit out of somebody,
I just rub my thumbs
against my earlobes
and shit like this, right?
And I just be like
"On bloods, nigga.
Don't break this
nigga's chin on bloods."
That shit be working
every time though.
Not every time.
Sometimes I still fuck a nigga
up but other than that nigga,
I'm basically out here
living a zen life-
- Oh shit.
Who the fuck threw
the ball at me?
I don't know, OG.
Throw me a shot.
[yelling excitedly]
[fist smacking face]
Oh, hell no, shit!
[low tempo hip hop music]
[speaks Spanish]
Oh, why don't you
stay out of my business
and off of the tables, kiddo.
Because Dominica has
been embarrassing
the whole family lately.
Who's Dominica?
My alter ego.
Get out of my room.
[yells in Spanish]
[speaks Spanish]
I'm a grown ass woman!
Sure doesn't look like it.
We just wanna know where
you're going [speaks Spanish]
To practice for the
domino tournament tomorrow.
What?
Is that allowed?
What do you think, Mom?
[speaks Spanish]
So why don't you follow your
mother's example for once?
Respect the men of
the house, you know?
How about you find your balls
or get my dad's out
of your fucking mouth!
[speaks Spanish]
Do I look okay, papa, huh?
I don't know how
to answer that.
Why do you have to be this way?
It's unnatural!
You know, after a long
day's work, men come home.
They like to unwind
over a game of bones.
We should have
that right as men!
Women, they have
their own sports even.
Like volleyball.
Ribbon dancing.
Basket weaving.
Basket weaving, ha!
For real?
You guys can talk all the
misogynist shit you want
but when I come back
holding this trophy,
my seat at the table
will be undeniable!
I'll be the best domino
player to carry the Ines name.
[upbeat music]
[pounding on wall]
Andy!
Come on, boy, wake up!
It's time to go.
We got a tournament to win.
♪ Watch me run it up ♪
♪ All up in your face ♪
♪ I can't get enough ♪
♪ She gon' give me top yeah ♪
♪ Let's go hit the cook now ♪
♪ Stick stuff in they cup aye ♪
All right, boy, we got to
get there early and register.
Then go over a few things.
We're not taking the car?
Why would we take a car when
it's just a couple of blocks?
Gas is as high as a
giraffe's coochie.
- Granddad.
- You better hurry up.
Wait up.
Unless you got
navigation on that phone.
And I ain't your damn granddad.
[Andy panting out of breath]
Hurry up boy!
I'm on a mission.
I'm gonna take this bitch down.
And this is gonna be it.
Me and Tenspeed.
I'm coming for you!
Worst day of my fucking
life, you feel me?
Worst.
You know you're still white
even though you
wear Nike's, right?
Man, pay attention
what I'm saying!
My bad, nigga, my bad.
What I'm saying is, before
I even could do anything
she walked in on me
with her sister, man.
Fucked up.
Ah, man, what'd you say?
Man, I said I was trying
to get to know her family
a little better, you
know what I'm saying?
Get a little relations
with the relatives,
you know what I'm saying?
Shit, nigga, did it work?
No, it didn't work!
I can't take my advice from
Shaggy songs, my nigga.
That only works for
light skinned niggas
with their shirts off.
Hey, did you just
see this Rastafari
with this check right here?
You know how many
Nike's and tattoos
that he can buy
with that, nigga?
That's 10 thou-wow!
Oh we about to get it, nigga.
[Gerald panting]
What kind of ghetto
ass operation is this,
not having a ramp
for my wheelchair?
Y'all trying to kill the king
before I get a chance
to sit in my throne?
So who do I need to
make wild passionate
chittlin grease love to to
get some water up in here?
[Andy coughing loudly]
[Namita] Oh my god!
[Gerald] Just let his
body completely shut down
and reboot itself stronger.
That's the way real
black slaves did it.
And you're welcome for
the history lesson.
You poor thing.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I love you.
Okay.
I mean, I'm Andy.
Have some water.
Hi, I'm Andy.
Get out of my
fucking way, kid!
Look, you can't be going around
with my name in your mouth
acting softer than baby shit.
You got to take
pride in yourself.
You wanna be a Edges?
You don't take nothing
off of nobody, ever.
[funky, psychedelic music]
Shit.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Tenspeed is in the building.
[laughs loudly]
Drop it [screams]
[indistinct]
You wanna get this [indistinct]
Ha, if it ain't the S.N.I.C!
You know what that means,
little white fella?
No.
[laughing]
Well, let me tell you.
If it ain't the saddest
nigga in Compton,
Gerald motherfucking Edges.
Tenspeed.
I see that rehab
went terribly bad.
The judge must've
been on drugs.
He shouldn't have been trying
to stop me from doing cocaine.
I love cocaine, nigga.
That's not what this is about.
This is about if you think
you finna come to Compton
and take my victory from me.
See, let me explain something
to you about winning.
Only a loser would lose
something so precious.
You're a loser, Gerald.
You can't fool a nigga like me.
You lost the most precious
thing that God gave to man.
That you vowed that
you could keep it
and you lost it!
When you get your ass
played at dominoes,
you think about this.
It's 2020.
You run around
here like it's 1974
with all that goddam chest
hair on your goddam chest.
You look ridiculous!
You need to get a tattoo
that says "Flammable".
[laughing]
I love this shit.
[roller blades screeching]
Come on, Andy.
Don't worry, Grandad.
No matter what it takes,
if it means bending
the rules a little,
I'm gonna help you
bury his second rate
Scooby Doo villain looking ass.
Because Edges stand up
for themselves, right?
You damn skippy, my
little soda cracker.
[roller blades skidding]
Look at all this sweet shit!
Hell, look at all
these goddam brownies.
Trying to fuck up
my blood pressure.
All this sweet shit.
Let me add a little,
a little flavor to this.
Tenspeed flavor.
Don't want to put too much...
Just balance my blood sugar.
[snorting]
[deep bass hip hop music]
Name please.
Slams. S-L-A-M-S.
Oh, sorry, your
birth name, sir?
Oh, that's
Rutherford Wrinkleton.
[laughing]
Really?
Yeah, it's on my parole
bar, you know what I mean?
I just got out.
You know, I did like a quick 10.
I don't even know what's
bracking these days.
What you like to do?
You like going to the binema?
Sorry, what?
The movies, you like
going to the movies?
Oh, mm-hmm.
Okay, bull, bull.
So maybe after this, we can
go catch like a [indistinct]
matinee or something?
I'm more of a Netflix
& chill girl, honestly.
All right, Netflix is bull.
I could do that, what's that?
That's the new shit?
Okay, I'm with that.
My name right there though.
[chuckles softly]
Excuse me, miss!
I'm gonna need you
to hold on a second.
I'm gonna need you to step
over here for a second,
big fella.
Random search!
I really don't think
that's necessary.
I rolled a dice and
his number came up!
I want you to know I'm extremely
proficient with a taser.
And I have a certificate.
I'm gonna need you to
assume the position
I'm sure you're familiar.
Please spread them!
Oh my god this is ridiculous!
What's going on here!
Is this a weapon?
Are you moving suddenly?
Do not move suddenly, sir!
[Namita] Calm down!
I got this under
control ma'am!
It's a spork, blood.
I don't do forks no more, man.
They too sharp.
And spoons are too dull.
That's a hybrid utensil, blood.
A spork.
All right, I'm gonna need to
take this one to the back.
Why?
[Security Guard]
Ma'am, let me do my job!
I have an online degree!
No!
All right, full cavity search.
The fuck you say?
Stand down!
Don't you know who this is?
This is legendary
Bonesmith Big Slams.
From the D Block.
Come on, G.
I am so sorry, Mr. Slams.
It's bull.
It is not bull,
it is not bull.
We're gonna treat you like
the pampered prince you are.
We're gonna make sure
you get all the L'Croix
and hand sanitizer your
massive heart can handle.
All right?
And some cocoa butter so
your elbows don't get ashy.
I know, 'cause I
get ashy elbows.
Little known fact,
white guys get ashy too!
Yeah, it's true, it's true.
All right, come on Namita,
let's get him his name tag.
What are you doing?
Give me that.
What's wrong with you?
How would you like it?
Jeez-ah!
[taser zapping]
Put that away!
Walter!
Harold.
How's it going?
You must be Quinton?
Yeah, it Quilton, actually.
Quilton?
Yeah, like a quilt.
Oh, and your parents
named you that?
Family names.
Very artistic!
You know what, Namita?
why don't get these guys
the VIP pizza rolls,
that little area?
And give them triple pepperoni!
On the house.
Enjoy. Here we go, there it is.
Hey, and everyone,
I want y'all to know
that black lives
absolutely matter!
Probably more than ours!
Definitely more than ours!
I mean, haven't we
screwed it up enough?
[crowd mumbling in agreement]
So, black lives matter at
this tournament especially.
[exhales sharply]
Big Slams is coming up fired up.
[grunts loudly]
[sighs sharply]
Man, I get mad about that.
Am I the only one
that misses Obama?
Am I right here?
Jeez!
[sighs sharply]
That guy had it going on.
And Michelle, can we
talk about Michelle?
[upbeat music]
This is the most beautiful
shit I've ever seen.
[speaks Spanish]
I'ma get you.
[upbeat hip hop music]
[roller blades screeching]
[laughs loudly]
You good?
Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
I'm just looking for
somebody for registration,
you know what I'm saying?
This is the Domino
Tournament, right?
Absolutely, this is
the Domino Tournament.
I'm a domino tournament.
You know, I'm a child prodigy.
Look, I'm a long line
of domino champion.
You know what I'm saying?
You're a prodigy?
Yeah. I ain't lost
since I was three.
I'm just here brother,
I'm just here to help you.
Matter fact, since
you're a prodigy,
I got something for you.
I wanna welcome you.
Take one of these
bralettes, man.
Registration right there.
And make yourself at home.
This is what this is about.
All right man,
thank you, brother.
A prodigy.
Well, I appreciate that, man.
Matter of fact, you
take two, take two.
Oh man, thank you, man.
I ain't know it was
gonna be like this man.
You know I got your back man.
Oh man, thank you.
Yes.
- What's up buddy.
- Hi.
I need to holler at you.
You got an appointment with
one of Jesus' disciples.
Let's go.
It's starting to pick up.
It's getting hot.
I'm excited.
Oh thank you.
[laughs loudly]
Do you love the Lord?
Oh yes, I love the
Lord, hallelujah.
Praise the Lord.
You know, because the
Lord says, don't be cruel,
'cause I will never
be that cruel to you.
You know.
[indistinct] said
it's my prerogative.
You know?
Didn't Bobby...
[objects clanking]
You're coming up in
here with bounced checks,
playing with me.
You thinks this is a game?
No, no, no.
It's not a game.
Listen, about that,
my wife, she must've put
a block on my account,
but good news,
I've got the gate money.
[chuckles softly]
You can take that.
You can have it.
Gate money?
[indistinct] Oh, you're
giving me permission
to have my own fucking money?
I will cut a mother fucking
pie hole out of you.
Hold on.
You know what I mean,
you scared of this?
[gasps sharply]
Yeah, yeah.
Guess what, guess what?
I got three, 50
pound cockroaches.
The size of pit bulls right
[metal clanking]
You hear me?
Cockroaches?
Yeah, yeah.
God, no.
Hey, what?
Oh, you're gonna use
the Lord's name in vain?
- No.
- Huh?
I didn't.
In my fucking establishment?
Do you know I'm a man of God?
Clearly.
You got till 4:00
PM to come up with
my mother fucking scratch.
Okay.
Or I'ma have these
these cockroaches
bite the shit out of you.
You hear me?
[chains rattling]
Oh Lord, forgive me.
Cockroach, cockroaches?
[upbeat hip hop music]
[laughs loudly]
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for coming out.
Oh, hi there.
So we're getting about to
get started in a minute.
Oh look, we got some
hotties coming in.
Just want y'all to know
we're gonna get this show
on the road.
So just sit back.
Yeah, sit back.
Time to party.
All right, let's hear
from DJ Dominoes.
Oh yeah.
Y'all know what time it is.
It's your girl DJ Dominoes.
[imitating horn sounds]
I'm here to drop knowledge
and drop some dope sport beat.
Not trying to hate, but I
taught her everything she knows.
Facts.
Let's take a look at
our strongest contenders
as we enter the first round.
On table one, we have Tenspeed.
The highest ranked player
according to Liberty Parks,
top 10 winners.
He's most famously
here for his ability
to mind fuck opponents,
hard and deep
with no lubrication, y'all.
Somebody move all your asses.
Then there's big
slams on table two.
Who've been locked up
for the last 14 years
and it has shit else
to do but play bones
for 23 hours in his cell.
And on table three,
got Camilla Ines.
Known for her lewd and
downright nasty trash talk.
Oh, Ines is getting personal.
It looks like a family
rivalry is a brew
as her cousin Fredrico,
a big time champ himself
sits at table four.
On table five, we've
got Pimpdaddy fresh,
a retired pimp whose fashion
sense is a mix of mace,
bargain, late 2000s.
We don't really know.
But it doesn't seem like
Pimpdaddy has his opponent yet
as we wonder where the
great veteran Gerald Edges
has disappeared to?
Somebody find me a man.
Where are you at? [indistinct]
Are you hanging out
with aunt Jemimah?
What's you doing?
All right.
So you have a flip
phone, so texting is out.
Okay, this is three, five.
This is four, six.
And if you have any doubles,
it can be, oh, Lord,
it's hot in here.
All right?
Get it?
Yeah, I got it, I'm
black and I see now,
and it ain't that
damn difficult.
Yeah, it's not like
talking with girls
or anything like that, right?
Hell you're talking about?
Well, I was just wondering
if I help you with dominoes,
maybe you can help
me learn about women?
Oh, shucks.
Hormones raging, huh?
Okay, ain't nothing
more beautiful in life
than finding the
love of a good woman
'cause you'll never
be able to find one
half as good as mine
'cause my Ella May
was the greatest woman
that ever graced
this green earth.
Having love is like pure magic.
There's no greater feeling.
Losing it is like a
repeated kick in the ass
with a steel toed boot.
That damn Tenspeed got her ring.
That's the only memory
of her I got left.
I don't wanna lose it for life.
Not while I'm still half alive.
He beat him in the losing
in last tournament.
We got to win it back.
All right, let's get it back.
But what you were
talking about with girls,
I think I found my Ella May.
Look, we don't have
a lot of time left,
so we're gonna have to do
a crash course, all right?
Two things I'ma give you.
A, [indistinct whispering]
[chuckles]
And lastly, about you
random motherfuckers
who are definitely gonna lose.
[exclaims loudly]
It looks like Gerald
Edges has finally decided
to come on through and play.
[sighs]
[chuckles softly]
Uncle Ben.
Did you just climb
out of your rice box?
Man. I want all these
beautiful people
to watch me whoop your ass.
And there ain't gon' be no
sympathy here Papa Bones.
Although, I would like
to formally thank you
for the invention
of peanut butter.
That shit is good as fuck.
Especially with jelly, goddam.
George
Washington[indistinct]looking ass.
Lemme tell you what.
What?
Get on up, so we can get down.
Oh man. What was
that from the 50s?
Goddam, get on up
so we can get down.
There were no cars
when you was born, sir.
All right, all
right, all right.
About to play some dominoes.
And no sore losers up in here.
Y'all got it?
Let's keep it cute, Compton.
Let's get it.
[sighs softly]
I'm about to tear your ass up.
Come on with
the big six again.
Is this sponsored by ARP?
Got you right there.
[sighs softly]
Come on.
What you got?
Nickel.
Alfred Lord Tennyson.
What the fuck that is.
How does that feel, Gerald?
Painful?
Do you got your
arthritis acting up?
Oh, a dumb ass mistake
from Gerald Edges.
He must be getting old
or is it that
dementia kicking in?
What's wrong pops?
Come on man.
Ah, that's right.
Circle of life Mufasa, the old
clearing out for the young.
Your time is up.
[humming]
[laughs loudly]
Go get this ass whooping boy.
Yeah, legendary Tenspeed.
Yeah, I heard about
your motherfucking ass.
Guess what?
What's that?
I ain't scared
of your bitch ass.
My momma told me all about you.
You ain't nothing but a
motherfucking crack head.
All this time I've been
fucking your mama nigga
it's the first time she
telling you about me bitch?
And it should have been your
daddy that told you about me
motherfucker.
And just don't disrespect me
with an unlit cigarette
and you taught me to cocaine?
What the fuck crack head
cocaine do many things.
I do cocaine motherfucker.
I do the finest shit
in the Peruvian.
Come on, I defeat
everything I do.
And next time I fuck your mama,
I'ma tell her to keep
your ass in the house.
10.
15.
First of all, I didn't
hear shit you said.
Is your mustache too big?
And I will suck your bitch ass
but you ain't gonna feel it.
Oh you're a genius, huh?
You real slick with your
motherfucking mouth.
Let me tell you something
you little irrelevant
motherfucker.
20.
It ain't never too
late for an abortion.
So you should shut
your goddam mouth.
You see what I'm saying?
What?
Dominoes, that's
what motherfucker.
[screams loudly]
I'm about to tear your ass up.
46, 46 trombones
in the big parade.
It looks like
I spoke too soon.
Gerald is racking up points.
The fuck he is.
Very white.
The fu...
Two four, three five.
Hey.
Sorry, I have Tourette's.
Tickle that teat.
Security, security.
Oysters.
Some kind of commotion
going on in the crowd.
We're gonna have the
monitors take a look.
25 big booty bitches bouncing.
[domino bangs]
Shocker, shocker, doing
the pink, what a stink.
Dominoes.
Stop.
Tell your
grandmamma I said hey.
She'll remember me.
And a huge come from behind
victory from Gerald Edges.
Congratulations.
You must start taking your
fish oil halfway through
I see that.
[chuckles softly]
Ooh, Camilla Ines is looking
surprisingly shaky out there.
You know, I've been meaning
to ask you this all game.
Aside from the fact
that you are dressed
like Cleo from "Set It Off,"
how does it work when
you're in the bathroom?
Like are you standing up?
Are you sitting down?
Are you on there backwards?
What are you doing?
Well, I'll be
standing only when
it's in your momma's mouth.
[giggles loudly]
Nasty.
You should make
sure you hold onto her
before you lose her.
Call her and shit.
All right?
What?
Are you good?
Are you okay?
Are you having a mental
breakdown right now?
Are you suffering
from identity crisis?
You wanna write your
feelings in your diary?
Huh?
Go ahead, you got time.
You can have a
whole lot of time.
I'm just be over here,
spanking that ass.
Who the hell invited Mr. old
town road to this tournament?
See, this is gentrification
at its finest.
I'm telling you.
Miguel, right?
Vandersloot, right?
Good to see you.
You too, man.
You build that wall yet?
Working on it.
Let it rip.
Boom.
There you go, Willie Nelson.
Come on, let me see
what you on there.
Well, it's anything
like last time.
You know exactly how this goes.
Mmh okay, that means I'm
gonna leave out of here a winner
and you get to go
back to your cousins.
That's exactly what that means.
[chuckles softly]
Boom, there we go.
Okay.
15, put a lasso around
your ass for that one, huh?
Hey, well, sorry to
disappoint you 'cause,
domino bitch.
[crowd cheering]
That's right.
Oh, you're gonna
cry now, aren't you?
Look, I know it hurts.
[cheering loudly]
Willie Nelson
looking motherfucker.
Come on, get out of here.
♪ I'm gonna take my horse ♪
to the hell out of here ♪
Get yo ass up out
the damn chair.
That's right.
Seems like it's officially
national douche bag day
as Fredrico wins his
first game, advancing on.
[grunts loudly]
Camilla still struggling.
You know, I hope
you learn from this.
I truly, truly hope
you learn from this
and find out what
happened when you fuck
with the superior sex.
Look at this goddam shirt.
I look like a African pill.
Kick his cheat ass.
I have, I learned that
having a dick means,
if you try hard enough, you
can always go fuck yourself.
Dominoes.
Get the fuck out
of here Bernie Mac.
[cheers loudly]
Man, wait a minute.
Where did this even come from?
Somebody check her.
[speaks foreign language]
Lets swing the
action onto table two.
Look like big Slam is coming
for blood on them bones.
You remember that bitch
you wasted at the park blood?
Bitchuation? What the
hell is a bitchuation?
[exclaims loudly]
Oh, you talking
about the situation
when you beat the
black off old dude
for hitting you
with a basketball
and I might have ran away?
Kinda, yeah. I know what
you're talking about.
Yeah, word on the street
is bloody got knocked out,
and he ain't wake up yet.
He taken a nap?
He had to be in the hospital.
In the boma, blood.
You mean a coma?
I mean a boma?
Police are looking everywhere
for the nigga that did it.
I wonder who did it.
They checking for witnesses too.
Hold up, witnesses?
You bee anything Balvin?
Did I see anything?
I mean, did I bee anything?
Hell no, I ain't bee anything.
Do it look like I can bee
any damn thing right now?
If I find out somebody's
snitching a bump
on their gums about me.
Well, I ain't got
to worry about,
you know what I'm saying?
'Cause you got my back, right?
Technically you
got a big ass back.
So I got partial of it.
I'm just saying if I find
a nigga snitching on me
in my proximity again,
I'ma changed man blood,
but on the set, I'll kill blood.
Hold on.
You said you're gonna kill him?
Absolutely nigga, I
don't fuck with witnesses.
Did you hear that?
My phone going off.
Hold on real quick.
Hey ma, you said what?
You in the hospital?
What the doctor say?
Your heart?
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
I'll be there in a minute.
That's auntie?
That's mom's man.
The doctor says she got
seven minutes to live,
so I gotta go.
Oh that's auntie
man, that's family,
fuck this tournament,
man, I'm going too, blood.
No, no, no, no, no.
You stay here, all right?
Take care of the cash and
I'ma take care of mom's,
all right?
We in this together.
Word, all right, blood.
I'ma say a prayer
for her, blood.
Big slam didn't even
have to lay one bone
to win this round.
His opponent took off
like somebody told him
to split the check.
Who next?
I do this.
Oh you do this, huh?
Get some intels on
your motherfucking ass.
What a showdown y'all.
This is crazy.
And that's it for
round one folks
But y'all know what that means.
Soowoop.
It's the best part
of the whole damn show.
We grabbing.
Now save me a plate.
It's all the info I need.
[upbeat music]
Hey, how are you Dominic?
Oh, look at this.
It's gorgeous.
Guys, got something
to eat there?
Yeah, enjoy yourselves,
thanks for coming out.
Hey, big slams.
Leave a little for
the rest of us.
Oh, sorry.
Thanks for coming out here.
Hey.
Oh gosh, this is great.
Something ain't right.
Okay?
Now Gerald with
that little white kid.
That wippy kid?
Yes, the little chunky one.
The one who fails to do sit ups.
What's up?
That one.
That motherfucker
is up to something.
What, what is it?
Ain't no way a white kid
hang out with a black man
if they're not being kidnapping.
Ain't no ransom involved
if you don't hang out
with a little white kid.
That's what I told ya
I'll to get to my fault.
I'm going undercover and
tryna find out what's wrong.
Did you get the mics?
We got it, we got it.
I got you, I got
it right here, look.
Bitch, do we look
like we're doing
a motherfucking concert?
What you gonna do?
Well we put the
mic on, go with it.
I'm a go around.
And when I go...
Bitch, have you ever
heard of [indistinct]
Yeah.
Me too, bitch.
She don't catch a case.
[clears throat]
So, our fish was
pretty great, right?
Yeah, sushi gives me gas.
I'll regret it later,
as will your mother.
Our marriage will
be tested tonight.
Papa, come on, please.
Leaving without me now?
This has gone far
enough, Camilla.
You need to stop now.
You need to quit the tournament
before you do even more
damage to this family.
No, no.
You're making a laughing
stock of all of us.
- I'm not.
- Yes.
Look, I know we
have our difference.
But how can you
treat me like this?
I'm still your daughter.
[speaks Spanish]
[indistinct]
You're working with
the area motherfuckers?
I just wanted a Fresco.
My fault homie.
Old habits die hard you
know what I'm saying, blood?
You can't run up on me
like that from the back.
You know where I'm from
you get shanked homie.
Cool.
[upbeat hip hop music]
[laughs loudly]
I like you, Gerald.
I liked your
motherfucking old ass.
And the way you
slapped them bones,
you damn motherfucker.
Dude you slapped the
fuck out them bones.
And the next batch
is gonna come to us.
So why don't you
just go on ahead
and drown yourself and
all that upcoming hand.
You know what, Gerald,
let me tell you something, man.
I like you.
If a old motherfucker
did a lot for me,
and you made a way for
a young fighter player
motherfucker like
myself to do what I do.
I'm telling you something,
that little fat white boy,
he's a little
chucky motherfucker
you're running around with
playing up Mr. Rogers with.
That motherfucker
is up to something.
And up to nothing.
That's my son's new
stepson, all right?
Yeah.
Him and his mom have been
living this white privilege life
living off their hard work.
Fuck you doing?
I'm just checking man.
Just say what you gotta say.
But he's a little fat
roly polis son of a gun.
I got arrested of
their life, you know?
But they just left them on me.
I don't know what he does.
I don't know where
he goes to school.
I don't even know his last name.
You know. How the fuck
white people will come
to hood just yelling.
Six, four.
Everybody know six
four on domino.
That's some bullshit, Gerald.
So goddam bullshit, Gerald.
So why don't you just
forget about this little
Cheddar Bay biscuits eating boy
and focus on the one who's
gonna fuck your life up
better than a
NyQuil [indistinct]
I like that, Gerald.
I like that.
There you go.
That's some bullshit like daddy.
Take this guy down,
fuck that bullshit.
Sup Slams?
You look like they
revoke you bro.
Competition here is
tough as hell man.
And I need that,
my girl dumped me.
Well that sucks.
What happened?
What do you do?
I ain't do nothing.
Do you try talking to her?
I tried talking to her but
she ain't trying
to hear that shit.
Now she's scared of
me all of a sudden.
I feel you, man.
How long have you
two been together?
About two and a half hours.
I know it ain't a long time,
but it was real, you know?
[upbeat music]
If it isn't popping fresh,
you get your shit together?
Oh, you gonna try to
fool me like you did,
when y'all was yelling
out all that slick shit.
How can I help you Mr. Speed?
Actually is me who
wanna help you to see
there's a rumor going around
that your little
chunky ass is more
than the cocktail spectator.
Some say you're the
greatest ever did this shit.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I don't know
what to talk about.
Yeah, and you and Gerald
trying to fool me,
running around here
like y'all best of kins
and this little
interracial family shit.
But I'ma tell you
something you don't know
little chunky fella.
Guess what?
Gerald don't even like your ass.
You don't believe me?
Listen to this.
That's my son's new stepson,
they just left him on me.
I don't know what he does.
I don't know where
he goes to school.
I don't even know his last name.
See, you goddam step kid.
He been using your ass
and he been using me too.
You don't even like it?
He don't give a fuck about you.
Listen to this little fat boy.
But he is a little fat growing
son of a gun [indistinct].
Yeah kid, go on crying.
She used to cry [indistinct]
What's going on?
What's wrong with you?
Game's about to
start in a minute.
Hey, where the
hell are you going?
Home, I'm ordering an Uber.
Maybe look it up.
What?
We're about to win the
whole damn thing kid.
I don't wanna play anymore
and I definitely
don't wanna be related
to you anymore either.
[door creaking]
What the hell just happened?
[hip-hop music]
We're back bitch.
And it's time for some lip
smacking, bone slapping fellas.
Is y'all ready?
All right everybody,
take your seats.
We're about to start
the final round of WDC.
[Crowd cheering and clapping]
Come on DJ Dominoes
hit it with the beat!
Guys we got some
investors in the house.
Big up to the
bankers in the back.
You know what's
great about bankers?
They always have money.
Y'all watch busy bagels.
Is this organic chorizo or...
Oh yeah.
No, I'm good.
[dominoes rattling]
I'm not feeling too
well, it's my angina.
I'm gonna take a minute.
It's a vibe.
Vibes.
- Mm.
- With a Z.
Great.
That guy's got a knife.
Anybody seen Andy?
Andy?
Hell is that boy?
Goddam.
Andy?
All right, I'ma need
ya all shut the hell up
and let me orchestrate.
'Cause this here is the big one.
We've got Ines vs Ines,
for control of the
familia [indistinct]
and it's pretty
clear from over here
where the fans loyalty lies.
Well, well what's
going on Luda Chris?
You ready to go down
[speaks foreign language]
I mean, I would
think you'd be used
to it by now [speaks Spanish]
[chuckles softly]
15 mommy [laughs].
I swear this isn't
even fun anymore.
Hey, hey you promised me
a fight not a massacre.
[speaks in Spanish]
Thea, she's got five.
Is that seriously
the best you got?
Oh sweetheart you're frazzled.
[sniffs loudly]
What's that smell?
Did you get your period?
Oh okay no, no, no it
must be your hair braided
too tight.
Either way I think
you worked out
on me beating you
bloody [speaks Spanish]
Thank God for the red table.
This is starting to look
pretty bad for the one
and only Dominica.
Oh, you're gonna cry, right?
No don't do it right here.
Fuck this bullshit.
If I'm going down, I'll be
sure to bite your dick off
when I'm there.
[speaks in Spanish]
Thea.
But I'm your nephew.
[speaks Spanish]
Bro get your wife,
who are you smiling at?
Camilla
[crowd cheering]
You boys may think dominoes
is machismo game huh!
The thing you boys
forget about dominoes
is that the bones might
be hard and loud and cold
but the only thing anyone
actually gives a fuck
about out of those
little periods
laying enough together
on every side.
[speaks Spanish] motherfucker.
[laughs loudly]
What the fuck?
You gotta be...
Come on, man.
[crowd cheering]
Got the holy spirit here.
Got the holy spirit, something
magical's happening here.
[crowd cheering]
Fuck that, Camilla Ines
just dominated your ass.
[crowd applauding]
And the party don't stop
as two of our
heaviest hitters go
[speaks foreign language]
[upbeat hip hop music]
I got that
activated [indistinct]
Man, come on man.
What about this?
No, you gotta go home, bro.
You've got to like that.
Tenspeed, what did
you do to that boy?
When the fuck you
start giving a fuck about
a motherfucker you don't give
a fuck about motherfucker?
Who's a motherfucker?
You are a motherfucker.
Oh, so little squirty
you wanna fight dirty, huh?
Why don't we just cut the
games and throw down clown?
1974 style a box,
I don't give a fuck.
Put them up.
I'll knock your old ass out.
I'm about to knock the
wrinkles out of your grandma.
Swing bitch, that's right.
Die right now motherfucker.
You deserve it,
you deserve to die.
It's my heart.
Fuck your heart, nigga.
My Angina.
Fuck your aunt vagina and
the rest of them bitches.
You cool O.G?
It's like your grandmamma
is sitting on my chest.
Fuck your chest.
Die, why are you
still standing up?
It's the big one Ella May.
God, why are you still
taking so goddam long
the devil wouldn't
have been [indistinct]
I'm coming.
Don't you come over
here [indistinct]
Mr. Edges.
Fuck this nigga.
We should get you
to the hospital.
- No, no, no, no.
- Fucker.
I just need to get
the blood pumping again.
I ain't quitting.
Okay, let me get
you a chair, okay?
Let him die.
You okay?
[breathing laboriously]
Well everything seems normal
but you have to take it easy.
No more fighting. Promise?
Promise.
You promise to do
something for me?
But that is the
saddest I've ever seen.
We're in front of white
people in bow ties.
Can't take y'all niggas nowhere.
The footage is great.
I mean, twists and turns,
drama around every corner.
This is gonna be good,
real good, you know?
But I'm a hustler.
I get it done.
What's up buddy?
Though I'd pray for you.
Come on man, come to
my office, you know.
Prayer changes.
Okay.
And I realize, you know,
you're on my property,
I haven't prayed for you.
Okay.
Put your hand on the Bible.
Now look motherfucker,
it's 4:00 PM.
The bank is closed.
Now, somebody about to lose
some motherfucking fingers
if I don't get my cash.
Okay, listen.
I can't, I tried, I
don't have the money.
Don't please, wait, wait, wait.
I don't even have
the prize money yet.
I'm hoping that this
film blows up, you know.
That's why I invited
the investors down
but I am 20 grand
in the hole myself.
- Oh, for real?
- Yeah.
That's some shit.
I'm desperate,
I'll do anything,
just give me a few
more hours, please.
So you want me to
give a few more hours?
Well, you, my friend are in luck
because the Lord has anointed
me to get my certification
to be a same day lender.
Oh, that's convenient.
So you can sign right there
and I can loan you money
for the next 45 minutes.
Okay.
- Isn't it beautiful?
- Yeah.
God is good.
Where's my money?
Oh, white Jesus.
That's your credit.
That's right, that's the savior,
He saved your ass today.
All right.
It's gonna be good.
It's gonna be real good.
[sniffs loudly]
Big, big [indistinct]
[laughs loudly]
[indistinct]
Big wink wink [laughs]
Look, wink, wink.
I want to have your
big homies know
that the first time you caught
a case at nine years old,
you got caught stealing
some goddam twinkies.
You was a motherfucking
twinky gangster.
[laughs]
Nigga with the cream filling.
Then give me 15 while you
sitting there thinking.
Who the fuck
told you that shit?
Your grandmother.
She's a sweet lady.
Grandma always talking shit.
Running her fucking mouth.
Hating ass bitch.
Still in that halfway house?
So tell me, when
did you get out?
I spend 175 days in the hole.
Nothing but darkness and the
sound of my own heartbeat,
blood sweeping through
my veins, homie.
Hey shit you can do
that can break me.
I been through
everything, blood.
Give me that 20.
[laughs loudly]
You like that, huh?
Congratulations on
your new relationship.
How the fuck you
know about Sherry?
Sherry?
EBP?
What the fuck is EBP, blood?
Nigga, that's
everybody person.
And don't even get mad.
I fucked twice.
The pussy barely decent, you
shouldn't be getting that mad.
Uh Oh!
I can't hear what they're saying
but it looks like Tenspeed
found his opening.
Fuck you, nigga.
Oh, you wanna fuck me now?
Prison must have really
clean the best of you.
Listen nigga, get
off your feelings.
Calm down.
Everybody's neighborhood
say good things about her.
Here, see, hold on, look
at that pretty smile,
ain't she gorgeous?
What the fuck is this?
That was her in
church with her grandma.
She sending you
pictures, nigga?
That was just at church.
Ain't that smile pretty?
Oh, this one you might like.
Don't that smile look pretty?
With my dick in her mouth?
Oh shit, slam is
about to lose it y'all.
Everybody get down.
This negro finna blow.
Everybody hit the deck.
[indistinct]
[objects rumbling]
[dominoes crashing]
[indistinct mumbling]
[taser buzzing]
[muffled screaming]
[phone ringing]
[Andy] Hello?
Hey Andy, it's Namita.
[Andy] Yeah?
Hey, I don't know
where you are right now
but can I talk to
you real quick?
[Andy] Yeah, sure.
I'm outside on the steps.
Okay, cool, I'll
be right there.
There you are.
Everyone's worried about you.
I really doubt that.
Oh Andy, of course
they're worried about you.
You've become quite
the talk around here.
Damn!
A tragic loss for one of
the best to bang the bone.
Everybody get the fuck down.
[indistinct]
[wailing loudly]
Anybody wanna try some
shit I'll put your ass down
just like him.
Damn, I need a better agent.
- Oh, hell no cuz.
- Fuck this shit.
Hey, get your
big ass over there.
Hurry up.
Yeah, nigga, make a move and
I promise I started bursting.
Yeah, all right.
Put your hands in
the air fat wink wink.
Do some.
Get your tiny
ass on the ground.
Please, I have several
adult rescue cats.
Hand cuff yourself.
Everybody is scared except me.
I ain't scared of shit.
Hurry the fuck up.
Ah, I'm trying.
Yeah, that figures.
Sad, lonely white kid
that nobody loves.
I'm sure they're all laughing.
You know I'm different too.
When I first came here, it
was hard for me to fit in.
People judge me by my outside.
But you know, you can't
judge a book by its cover.
You just can't
always see through
the rough exterior sometimes.
My parents don't
even care about me.
They're too busy focusing
on their own lives
and Cabo or whatever.
I'm sure that's
not true, not really.
Like your granddad, they
may be distracted sometimes,
but people tend to come
around when the dust settles.
You think so?
I do, family's
for life after all.
[indistinct]
[upbeat music]
Move it here.
Fill the fucking
bag [indistinct]
Fuck you're looking at.
Trick or treat mother fucker.
This is [indistinct]
I think you might be the
first real friend I've ever had.
Well, I doubt that, but I
am definitely your friend now.
So what do you say we
get back in there...
Namita, can I
ask you a question?
Do you have a boyfriend?
And what's reverse cow girl?
Is it like a
time-traveling lady cowboy?
I'm going to time travel
and pretend that last three
seconds never happened.
Right now, we need to get
back to check on your grandad.
He had an accident trying
to defend your honor
against Tenspeed.
Where is he?
Is he okay?
Tenspeed better
not have hurt him.
Let's go.
Anybody else got
something to say?
And who the fuck is you?
Get the fuck in here.
Huh?
And get the fuck over there,
you hear the fuck I'm saying?
There's a fucking gun,
man, put that shit down.
Grab the fucking hook.
You're ruining everything.
Okay, yeah, pass the
bag around[indistinct]
[speaks Spanish]
[yells in Spanish]
[crowd screaming]
My blood pressure is too much.
[speaks Spanish]
[crowd screaming]
Motherfucker.
Bitch get the fuck off.
What's wrong with you?
Tenspeed, bitch.
[crowd screaming]
Oh hell yeah.
Where y'all going,
the motherfucker's dead?
[indistinct] what's
wrong with you?
No, no, no, no, no, stay.
Everybody stay in here.
Not in my house, they're
not gonna stop my dreams.
Look, what just happened
was a horrible experience.
And I'm sure it's gonna
cost me thousands more
in medication, therapy,
which I absolutely do not have.
But just stop for a second
and think about it, okay?
Listen, some of you paid
a perfectly reasonable,
but not minuscule price
to be in this tournament.
And some of you spent
your hard-earned money
to come out here and see the
world's best dominoes players
go for the grand prize.
$10,000, $10,000
that has still not been claimed.
I have it right here.
Now, are you seriously
willing to walk away
from what we've started?
What we're part of?
History.
Just because a couple of
trick ass gangsters choose
to disrupt our championship?
Fuck those guys.
Now, who are the
winners in this place?
Huh?
Is it us or is it them?
'Cause I went on a search all
through South Los Angeles,
terrifying journey to
find the best of the best.
And those are the winners
that stand before you today.
And for one of you,
the title, the
respect, the glory
is still yours for the taking.
[crowd cheers]
As long as you don't
let those losers win,
we just keep fighting
for our dreams.
[crowd cheering]
Now, who's with me?
I mean, come on.
[crowd cheering]
Yeah, yeah.
It's party time, let's
get this started.
[crowd cheering]
[Police Officer] LAPD.
Hello officer.
There's just been
an armed robbery.
[Police Officer] All right.
How quickly can you be here?
[Police Officer]
What's your location?
We're in Compton.
[Police Officer]
Oh, I don't think
- we can make it out there.
- There's white people here.
[Police Officer]
Oh, in that case,
we'll be there in two minutes.
Okay, great, thank you.
Papa we should get
you to the hospital.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
[speaks Spanish] I'm fine.
Are you okay?
I don't know what
I would have done.
If they'd hurt you.
I'm fine Papa.
Listen.
Dominoes was never
about pretending
to be something I'm not.
It's actually the only time
I've been able to
be who I really am.
But maybe this is a sign that
maybe this is not for me.
No [speaks Spanish]
No, no, no, no,
no, no stop Camilla.
Listen.
- I was wrong too.
- No.
No, you [speaks Spanish]
are strong.
You have got more balls than
that punk cousin of yours.
[speaks Spanish]
[laughs loudly]
You can be whoever you wanna be.
You're still my baby girl.
Papa, that's
all I ever wanted.
[sobs loudly]
I gotta say, Walter, what
we've seen here today has been-
- Real, right?
Quite the experience.
Yeah a bit too
real for my blood,
but, hey, thank you for
an unforgettable ride.
So unreal.
I guess suddenly will
start their work then.
What work, sir?
Well, you guys as
producers must know
that the real in
reality television
isn't really what it seems.
That security guard you think
he's a real security guard?
[sobbing]
Actor!
What?
- Oh, hell yeah.
- No, no way.
Genius.
No, no.
Those dudes that
came in, actors.
Wardrobe, acting, all
of it guys, come on.
Why are you gonna do
one cheap promo piece,
when you can get hours
of ad sponsored footage
for a reality television show?
I see it.
You see it?
I mean it's it's yeah, it's-
- What about this
one right here?
- Yeah, actor.
- No.
[laughs loudly]
- So real.
- Yeah?
You don't know man I almost
shit my pants I was crowning.
- Oh yeah?
- Prairie dogging it.
- Oh yeah, me too.
- Am so thankful.
Me too I was into it.
- Yeah.
I mean that
speech you felt wow.
- I felt it.
- Well, now I'm in it.
Like now we are in.
You're in it?
- We are in.
- Yeah, yeah.
Do you guys want
some of the Forty?
- Yeah, what is that?
- What is that?
Mr. Edges, I heard
you're sick, are you okay?
You just took down a
crazy ass bitch with a gun
and you worried about me?
Only white folks.
Well, yeah, I saw you
forgot this at home.
So I grabbed them just in case.
They are for your heart, right?
Yeah.
But ain't nothing wrong
with my heart boy.
This is nothing this little
pills can take care of.
I ain't got it no more.
I've been weak out there.
I was faking just to buy time
and now I realized that,
ain't no more time
in this game for me.
Time for some new blood.
You're the one that got us here.
You the man now Andy.
I want you to go over
there, take my place.
I want you to show
the world what we got.
Me against Tenspeed?
Against the world
starting with Tenspeed.
He's gonna roll over
and crush me though.
He ain't crushing you boy.
You smarter than
all these people.
You've proven it to me
now prove it to yourself.
You're ready.
- All right?
- Okay.
Now I want you to
go on over there,
when you sit down, I
want you to represent us.
Okay.
Him for me.
[upbeat hip hop music]
It's been a wild
night tonight guys,
but let's get back into it.
We have a last minute change
for our championship round.
We got Gerald Pablo Bones,
he's passing his seat seat
onto his grandson, Andy Edges.
Get him youngster.
Go on.
And this is it.
Andy Edges is growing up fast
as he sits in for
his ailing grandad.
Is good versus evil.
Purity and innocence,
versus a heart
of the blackest midnight.
Hey, bitch, what you doing
that old racist shit for?
Fuck you calling midnight bitch?
Hey fuck you Tenspeed.
I hope a Lego falling
your skate boots,
how about that?
Now let's fucking domino.
[crowd applauding]
Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy,
Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy.
What the fuck
[indistinct] adorable shit?
[upbeat hiphop music]
Let's go, shake em.
♪ Activated, all ma ♪
niggas fully activated ♪
♪ Activated push your button ♪
watch me activate it ♪
Hit six.
Bam!
15 like that.
You know one thing
going on about dominoes?
It ain't about no
goddamn app [indistinct]
It's not about that shit.
It's mental.
This is all about psychology,
and to win the mental game,
you gotta know people Andy.
You gotta know their strengths,
[bangs table loudly]
you gotta know their weaknesses,
but most of all,
you gotta know what makes them
[bangs table loudly]
buckle, under pressure.
See, you don't know people.
Just a loser.
You just a little
chunky, obese little boy
you have no love [bangs table
loudly] in Tenspeed house.
Now,
you're all alone.
[bangs table loudly]
Tenspeed officially revealing
he was raised by wolves,
is going in on Andy,
damn, mind, body and soul.
Can we please contact
child protective services
[bangs table
loudly] on the line?
[bangs table loudly]
Give me 10.
Like to count Andy?
[bangs table loudly]
Give me 25.
Think about everything
you're doing.
Yeah.
In the hood when you fuck up,
some time you got to get out
[bangs table loudly]
other times you gotta
go to the ball yard.
Oh Tenspeed with the blocks
as Andy keeps the digging.
But goddamn, I know he
is a human skid mark,
but the nigga can show domino.
Another one.
Oh, try again
and again.
Look Andy Edges,
digging his own grave.
Don't follow the light Andy,
don't follow the light.
You better call on Jesus.
Don't follow the light.
Shut the fuck up, can't
you see he is trying
to concentrate?
Oh, ungrateful ass nigga.
You don't win at bones unless
you get in the folks head,
the game is all mental.
[bangs table loudly]
That's 10 bitch.
[crowd cheers loudly]
Mr. Tenspeed Sir.
That's me there,
that's my grandson.
[crowd cheers loudly]
Wow, Andy Edges noting
the comeback is essential.
15 Sir.
Looking not so little man, go.
You think we having fun?
Get in Andy.
Winning ain't fun
until it is won.
Won is fun.
He's moments away
from taking it home.
That's 10 looks
like five to go.
Oh, looks like it's
all over for Tenspeed.
There is a God.
Is he heading for the boneyard?
Fucking brilliant.
[solemn classical music]
You only need five to go, jeez.
But not that jeez, domino!
Little mother fucker,
you can't beat me.
Talking about the
mind, psychology.
Go on over there you goddamn
loser, that's the game.
[domino crashing]
[cheers loudly]
Damn, what kind
of bullshit is that?
Well, I guess that means
Tenspeed wins, yippee.
Now let me take my
ass and get a drink.
And the winner is Tenspeed.
[wails loudly]
[indistinct]
[laughs loudly]
Focus on the money,
let's focus on the money.
Oh, oh, oh.
Yeah, focus on the
honey lady there.
And I wanna give a big shout out
to drugs.
Because they try to
make you think drugs
ain't good for you,
they're lying to you man.
Some of the greatest ever
did, it was on drugs.
I wanna thank Nino Brown
from New Jack city.
I wanna thank Rollo
for a good time.
Johnny Cash, 'cause like
he said, I did it my way.
You are my first interracial
friendship and without you,
I mean shit it still be the same
but I'm really
emotional at this point.
Only the world know
that I deserve this.
The American dream ladies
and gentlemen, you saw it here.
The World Dominoes Championship.
Keep your head up.
It's not you.
Your grandfather ain't
shit, never been shit.
I been kicking his
ass his whole life.
And guess what?
If I'm number one, that
make you number two.
And guess I got
something for you.
You keep that little
chunky [indistinct]
[somber music]
You done good.
I'm proud of you anyway.
But I didn't get your ring.
No, no, no.
I'm proud of you because in
spite of all this trash talk
you stood up to a bully
and earned everyone's
respect, especially mine.
You stood firm when
someone was trying
to put fear in you.
That's the very first thing
every black man learns
in this society.
So maybe you coming around,
grandson.
Look Andy, he can have it.
I'm good.
Mr. Tenspeed wanted
me to have this.
What?
Boy don't be taking
that from that guy?
Could be anything.
What's in there?
Is this Ella May's ring?
Yeah, I don't give a damn
about no ring no more son,
I got you.
Thanks granddad.
Hey, I still got her
panties though nigga.
[yells loudly]
[door bangs loudly]
[shouts loudly]
And where are you going?
You know what?
You were clearly a pimp at
some point, am I correct?
But now I'm
pimping for the Lord
and don't nobody take
the Lord's money.
'Cause that's my money.
You understand what I'm saying?
Now where the fuck
is my money at?
Good news, good news.
I got an advance on
the reality show and
[laughs loudly]
- Hey man, that's bad.
- Yeah
That's bad, Sam.
Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Jesus.
Now about that inches.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
White Jesus?
Oh white Jesus,
Holy Lord white Jesus.
All right, we're good now.
No, no, no, like the
paperwork you signed
this is...
- Interest.
- The collateral, white Jesus.
Okay, well what could the
interest be on a 45 minute?
Let's see, 45, 58%.
What?
See, see, see.
You know what your
problem is, Walter?
You shouldn't sign shit
under duress, right?
Ah shit.
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit.
Now I got to cut
the shit out of you?
No.
Yeah, I gotta cut
you, I gotta cut it.
You don't have to cut me.
I have to because
you know why?
Why?
People think I'm
old school, see?
They think I preach
out the Old Testament.
Old Testament preaching, dude.
I'm more like a New Testament.
Oh shit, I'm ordained,
I'm an ordained Minister.
[grunts loudly]
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
I'm anointed.
How many fathers smite him?
I don't believe in the
effectiveness of your
[indistinct] punishment blood.
Come on come on big
guy. Come on big guy.
Save me God.
We've got enough
of that for today.
You get the fuck
out of here man.
That was really good.
Proud of you fool.
Matthew 21:12 He who
lies can [indistinct]
You said it.
Don't say it.
So what you like to
Netflix and bill too?
No, what if I'm matinee girl?
Matinee, I likes
that, that's old school.
You my type of woman, Bamilla.
All right, Camilla.
Yes.
You hungry, you
want something to eat?
Let's get a fat burger?
Big Slams, I wanna make you
the head of the WDC security.
What do you say?
The fuck?
Get the fuck out of my face
man, before I pack you out.
Okay.
All right.
We did it.
[laughs loudly]
And I survived with
all my fingers.
You know what Namita,
I could not have done
this without you.
Why don't we make
this permanent?
I'm gonna make you
vice president of WDC.
That's right.
You're the new vice president.
You know how real is that?
I don't know what to say.
Good.
Because I got a lot of
thoughts going through my head
and I don't want you
to stop the train.
We're going worldwide.
You hear me?
London, Paris, Africa,
Afghanistan, Kazakhstan.
Forget it, all the stans.
And we're going
wherever you're from.
Cool.
You want some help there?
Yeah, thanks.
All right. It's gonna be good.
It's a wrap y'all, it's a wrap.
That's it y'all. It's
a wrap, we're done.
Y'all gonna get on out here.
But guess what?
I got one more tune
to take us all home.
Young Bugatti, run it up.
[deep hip hop music]
[Man] You lost, bitch.
- 15.
- Domino motherfucker.
Domino.
What's up y'all?
This is my family y'all, no cap.
We're back at it in
Compton, California
for the World Domino
Championship Deluxe.
It's on.
We got new jerseys
from the swap meet.
This is my family y'all.
No Cap.
You'll see the best Dominoes
players in the world.
Win that big money.
We got international players.
All the way from China
town and Fullerton.
We got some Rastafari
from the Bahamas
coming with that sweet ganja.
Come on down to the Word
Dominoes Championship
in Compton, California.
It's gonna be to be pumped
and we'll see you next time.
Yeah.
We're out
Fridah, are you really out?
Boy, you got a new look.
Yeah granddad, this
is my Compton swag.
Compton swag, get on here boy.
Let's ride.
[door bangs]
[hip hop music]
[car engine revs]
[upbeat hip hop music]
Beefing with that fool.
Think about this
look, what is that?
In God's will is the holy jeans.
You know I even draw characters.
You so fugly, you see
this crack head one day,
he had talent, I was like,
"Man, what you doing?"
He was like "Man, I'm over
here making these balloons."
And he was making these
sexy balloons and I said,
"Why don't you come on down
here to the church work center
and be an entrepreneur?"
So now we've got
the erotic balloons.
Brownie is so fuck delicious,
you know what I'm saying,
I thinking of starting
my own brownie business,
you know what I'm
saying, with Joe Jackson.
Joe Jackson.
Oh yeah.
Smack 'em brownies.
You know what I'm talking about?
Oh, yeah, that's
what we go'n do?
Joe Jackson brownies.
I can't even play dominoes
but I don't really even
know exactly what happened.
I got to put the
urge to run a 58.
58 miles, man I thought
the tournament was over,
which is crazy.
'Cause I'm ready to go.
I'm ready to rock.
I've never lost
since I was three.
So I just got a lot
of energy right now.
That's the only one to
stand to stay apart.
Anybody wanna build it.
Build a house.
[Man] So you didn't play?
Nah, I didn't get to play.
Right now, I feel like if you
put dominoes in front of me,
I could build an
origami out of dominoes.
You ain't never seen
that shit like that.
Thirsty on parts?
[indistinct]
You don't just sit down and
just cordially play dominoes.
What a motherfucker.
Hey, nice hands.
Great, shut the fuck up.
Bitch, domino.
20 motherfucker.
Shut up, get in the
bone yard, nigga.
[indistinct]
[laughs loudly]
Domino motherfucker.
♪ Tryna stay rich ♪
♪ Y'all tryna be saints ♪
♪ But that's your thing ♪
Walter.
West side.
This is my son.
I hate you.
It's all love down here
at the World Dominoes
Championship.
[upbeat hip hop music]
Where did everybody go?
Hey, my cuffs.
Boss!
Somebody help me.
Y'all still here?
Ain't nothing else to learn.
Y'all need to get a damn life
but I can't teach you that shit.
Unless you sign up for
my other master class.
How to stop being
a little bitch.
Order now.
Especially you.
Or you can buy my sequel,
"Secrets Of Dominology,
Straight Out Of Compton, China,"
for just $999.99 cents.
Coming soon.
Be there or I swear
I'ma find you.
Peace and love.
You dig?
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull