(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(OBJECTS RUSTLING)
I have a double,
so you're on your own tonight.
You're my hero.
Where's yours?
In my bag.
EVER'S MOM: Okay.
Just making sure.
Okay. Have fun
on your field trip.
Fun? (SCOFFS)
What's wrong?
Nothing. You're doing
that withdrawn teen thing.
What am I missing?
No, Mom. No, I'm not.
You completely are.
Mom. I'm not.
Still in that thing with Tamra?
It's nothing.
EVER'S MOM: You're being
pulled in so many directions
in high school. Ever...
...your body is changing.
Oh, my God, Mom.
It's normal
and it's okay...
Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom, tr... Stop.
I'm fine. Trust, please.
Stop.
You know that I'm here for you.
I've been you. I am you.
I'm here to help.
High school.
The drugs and the booze
and the sex.
Jesus.
It's like chemical warfare.
Okay.
Please, try to have some fun.
But make good choices.
Mom.
Okay.
All right. Well, okay, good,
'cause I've seen some shit.
All right, Mom.
Okay. I love you, Ever.
EVER: Love you, too. (SIGHS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(HORN HONKING)
(MID-TEMPO SONG PLAYING)
♪ How can it be? ♪
♪ Blue eyes woman, don't cry ♪
♪ You know that goodbye ♪
♪ Is only
We'll see ♪
♪ Sometime soon
You'll fall into a swoon ♪
♪ Best believe... ♪
Ever. Wh... what is this?
Come on.
What? TAMRA: We're
going on a field trip,
not to pinochle. (CHUCKLES)
EVER: Is it too much?
(CHUCKLES) Too much?
It's nothing, Ev.
Sh... should I change?
TAMRA: No, we're late.
And changing would take
forever ever, Ever.
Just get in, Grandpa. (CHUCKLES)
("YOU'RE SOMETHING NEW" PLAYING)
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh... ♪
Whoo! Field trip!
Oh, my God. TAMRA:
Let's get that extra credit!
Okay, you just, like,
need less layers.
Like, show a little
skin or something.
I mean, take this off,
first of all.
Oh, my God. Tamra!
What? You don't need a jacket.
It's so hot out.
Stop. I'll unzip it.
TAMRA: You're super cute, okay?
You're just hiding
under all this clothing.
EVER: (CLICKS TONGUE) Shut up.
(CHUCKLES) What?
Yeah, easy for you to say.
Easy for everyone to say.
"Super cute."
It's two words.
Wow. (CHUCKLES)
TAMRA: It's two words. Yeah.
You have to let people
see it, you know?
I mean, you just have
to let Steven see it.
Shut up.
(CHUCKLES) You know.
EVER: I wish I never told you.
Oh! Oh, you know, Jacey taught
me this really cool trick.
Oh, my God, I don't want
to hear about your new friends.
They're not my new friends.
We just have class together.
Ever's now pissed. Dude!
What do you expect me
to do, like,
be antisocial
the rest of my life?
How's that working out for you?
Tamra, please. Stop.
Tamra, stop. I mean it.
We can try every once...
Tamra, stop! Stop!
TAMRA: Oh, my God!
(BOTH SCREAM)
(RANDALL GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
He's dead.
Is he dead?
No.
But let's make sure.
Are you okay?
(RANDALL EXHALES HEAVILY)
Guys almost took me out!
Randall? There goes
my "good driver" discount.
(SOBS)
I... I... I'm... I know.
I'm sorry.
We were just, um... I'm so sorry.
I totally didn't see you.
Yeah, I get that a lot.
RANDALL: Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Um...
TAMRA: Whoa.
Oh, it's okay, Tamra.
I just, uh...
Uh, I... I'm totally okay.
(SIGHS) Are you sure?
You're, um...
Um, you're...
Randall.
Randall, right?
You sure you're... you're good?
Yeah.
Couldn't be better.
Oh, okay.
Sorry.
EVER: Oh, hey, let me help you.
Oh, don't. I... I got it.
I got it. Sorry.
Oh.
It's just, uh, fragile. Sorry.
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
Yeah, no worries.
Uh, hey, maybe sometime...
(TIRES SCREECH)
("SUMMER'S GONNA BE MY GIRL"
PLAYING)
(BOTH GASP)
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, fucking bulls eye!
Yes, bro.
HUNT: Hey, what's up, Tammy?
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah... ♪
Hey.
JACEY: Oh, my God.
Such a cute fit, babe.
Right? Thanks.
What the fuck?
DANNY: Oh, I'm sorry, man.
Hey, I didn't mean
to hit you right there.
What were you aiming at?
I was aiming for your head.
(CHUCKLES)
What? It's, like, funny.
You got to admit it.
Fucking assholes.
Are you okay?
Do you want a ride?
Ever.
There's no room.
Sorry. We have to go for the...
Ever. Come on.
I'm s... I'm sorry.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
CHAD: All right,
principal's watching, guys.
Phones in the bag.
We're gonna live
inside the IRL, you know?
Communicate with each other.
Thank you. Grazie.
If I say, "Grazie,"
you say, "Prego."
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Wow. That is a death stare.
Grazie.
You say, "Prego."
EVER: Hi.
Give it.
I don't have one.
CHAD: Really? Still?
Yes.
Well, give my regards to 2006.
(CHUCKLES) Go ahead.
(CYMBAL CRASHES)
CHAD: Right this way,
children. Whoa. (TUBA PLAYING)
Give it.
I know you got that flip.
(MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING)
CHAD: Phones in the bag, people.
Last call. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You, too, Wayne.
Come on, get...
Let's get the phone.
(CHUCKLES)
You should see your face.
I'm just kidding, man.
Okay, go ahead.
Captain on the bridge!
"You're Randall?"
Really? Like we haven't known
him since sixth grade?
Whoa, what happened to you?
You don't want to know.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're right. Give it.
EVER: I know he's weird,
but he's...
CHAD: Last call!
Damn, now that is nice tie-dye,
Deadhead.
TAMRA: Speaking of sixth grade,
you know the first time I ever
got tongue was on a field trip?
Yeah, because you tell me
every time we go
on a field trip.
TAMRA: Yeah,
but have I shown you?
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
Stop! Stop.
(DISTORTED RINGTONE PLAYS
OVER CELL PHONE)
Dude, you gotta stop
sending nudes to this phone.
It's a work phone.
I just want to make sure
you know how it works.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
I mean, who knows?
It could be your day.
Oh, come on, Ever.
Dude, dick pics are nudes.
That's my truth.
(SIGHS)
JACEY: You should
try black lipstick.
It would really bring out
your bright, gleaming smile.
You think?
JACEY: Yeah.
Always happy to do charity work.
(WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Are we okay?
Yeah. Sure.
Thanks for asking.
Yeah, you got it.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
See?
Stop.
Super cute.
Don't.
(CHAD CLAPPING)
This could really be your day.
Eyes front, children.
Something's wrong with you.
(CHUCKLES)
We are going to have
some 4-H fun today...
Ryno! Rynomite! All right,
let me have that phone.
And if you... Okay, no,
there's not, uh...
Just, can you just take a...
Oh, God. Dude. Dude.
Okay. No fat shaming.
It's frowned upon.
Just, uh, beach yourself
anywhere, quickly.
Yeah We'll wait.
It's time to earn
that extra credit.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
That's right. We're going to be
immersed in nature.
We're going to see
some wildlife.
We're going to show some
of you wallflowers
the perks of real flowers.
And maybe, just maybe,
we'll plant the seeds
of friendship
and bond like braces.
You know what I'm talking about,
don't you, Candace?
So shy. Are you transmitting?
(CHUCKLES)
Try to keep it down
to a thunderous roar,
and we'll get through
this together.
The PTA requires it.
Hit it, Wayne!
("WATERFALL" PLAYING)
♪ Tell me what to do
Tell me what to say ♪
♪ I can do this anyway
You're making me crazy ♪
♪ I can tell you something
I can tell you anything ♪
♪ I can tell
You're making me lazy ♪
♪ Tell me what you love
Tell me what you find ♪
♪ I can do this anyway ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Like a waterfall
Like a waterfall ♪
♪ And I can do this anyway ♪
♪ Like a waterfall ♪
(SNORES)
♪ And I can do this anyway ♪
♪ Like a waterfall
Like a waterfall ♪
♪ I can do this anyway ♪
(GROANS, SNIFFS)
♪ Tell me what you want
Tell me what you need ♪
♪ I can do this for you
Baby, today ♪
♪ Tell me what you need
Tell me everything you need ♪
♪ I can feel it in your legs ♪
♪ Tell me what you want
Tell me what you need ♪
♪ I can do anything
That you want to ♪
♪ Tell me what you want
Tell me what you need ♪
♪ I can do anything
That you want to ♪
(GROANS, SNEEZES)
♪ Like a waterfall
Like a waterfall ♪
Wait, I thought you
weren't eating anything
with a face.
Okay, you eat the face
and give me the rest.
(CHUCKLES) No, stupid.
Gummies are made of gelatin.
So?
You know, gelatin's made
of bones.
Like, pig bones and cow bones
and horse hooves.
(WRAPPER CRUMPLING)
Thank you.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Ew.
Dude, just eat the faces.
What?
(CHUCKLES)
♪ Like a waterfall ♪
♪ Like a waterfall
Like a waterfall ♪
♪ Like a waterfall ♪
♪ And I can do this anyway ♪
♪ Like a waterfall
Like a waterfall ♪
(GROANS)
♪ And I can do this anyway... ♪
Uh, what route
are you taking, Wayne?
♪ And I can do this anyway
Like a waterfall... ♪
Wayne, you're going
the wrong way.
Will you just get off my back
and let me fucking drive!
Geez, Wayne. Language.
Oh, I'd hate to have
to fucking write you up again.
You want to go?
'Cause we can go right now!
What the fucking... Jesus!
(SCREAMING, CLAMORING)
WAYNE: Hang on!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Hit the brakes, Wayne!
We're going down!
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPING, COUGHING)
CHAD: Wayne, you half-wit!
Can you do anything right?
WAYNE: Something hit
the windshield.
No. You hit something!
(RADIO STATIC)
CHAD: It was clearly a tragedy,
but let's just hope
he was a racist,
so we don't have to feel bad.
Okay. Is anyone hurt?
Um, I... I think she is.
CHAD: Oh, gross.
(SOBS)
Okay. Jacey, uh,
take a... a towel or a...
Or a jacket or something,
and... and... and cover that up.
No... nobody needs to see that.
Aren't you a doctor?
Well, I mean, I'm a doctor
of physical education.
It's not... (THUDDING)
(ALL SCREAM) MALE
VOICE: What the fuck is that?
There's somebody out there.
CHAD: Oh, well,
good news, Wayne.
It looks like you're not
a murderer after all. Mazel tov.
EVER: Here, Jacey, um,
for your... for your nose.
It's all I have.
(GROANS)
Ew.
(WHIMPERS) How bad is it?
It's...
not that bad.
(THUDDING)
(ALL GASP)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(PANTS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(METALLIC CREAKING)
(LOUD BUZZING)
(EVER GROANS)
WOMAN OVER RADIO: This message
is transmitted at the request
of the United States Office
of Civil Defense.
Take a battery-powered radio
and essential supplies with you
to the nearest fallout shelter
and seal the doors.
Stay on this broadcast
for further information...
Turn that...
Turn that down, Wayne.
WAYNE: I think
this is important.
Just turn it down!
WOMAN OVER RADIO: We are
under siege by a chemical attack.
Avoid affected areas
at all costs.
(SCREAMS)
(ALL GASPING)
TAMRA: What was that?
EVER: I... I... I don't know.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
I think he wants to come inside.
Open the door.
You want me to open the door?
Are you nuts?
Please don't open the door.
Open the door.
I'm with the kids.
You should be with the kids!
He's clearly hurt,
and at least one of us needs
to take some responsibility.
Maybe that's the difference
between you and me, Wayne.
That and 70 to 75 pounds.
Watch and learn.
Are you all right, friend?
Maybe we should...
Go.
Do you have insurance?
(SNARLS)
(SCREAMS)
Go! Go!
TAMRA: Go where?
(ALL SCREAMING)
Shit, shit, shit. Go. Come on.
JACEY: Go, go, go, go, go!
(YELLS)
Go, go!
(SCREAMS)
(CLAMORING)
DANNY: Move it! Come on!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(COUGHS)
BOY: Go, go, go!
(ALL SCREAMING)
JACEY: Danny, wait!
HUNT: Danny Go! Come on!
(GRUNTS)
HUNT: Come on, Candace! Come on!
(SCREAMS)
JACEY: Danny, wait!
Candace!
(GROWLS)
Shit!
(PANTS) Candace, grab my hand!
(SCREAMS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
JACEY: Come on!
DANNY: I don't need your help.
JACEY: Take it anyway.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMS)
(PANTS)
Tamra? Tamra!
(GROANS) I just got these.
Come on, man.
Tamra! (COUGHS)
(LAUGHS)
What was that back there?
I don't know. Satan shit.
Where are we?
(EVER WHIMPERS, GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
EVER: Tamra!
(GASPS)
RANDALL: Ever! Come on!
(SCREAMS)
RANDALL: This way!
(SHRIEKING)
Ever!
EVER: Thank God.
Hey, we... we need
to find help. (GASPS)
Hey, we gotta keep going.
That guy was not normal.
DANNY: Yeah, no damn duh,
Factoid.
That alert message on the radio?
We have to find cover.
Where?
We're in the fucking Shire.
RANDALL: There.
There's a building or something.
I don't see anything.
STEVEN: Yeah, right there.
Guys, it's right... I see it.
(ZOMBIE SNARLING)
RANDALL: Shit! Go! Come on!
JACEY: Let's go!
TAMRA: Come on!
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
RANDALL: Oh, this way! Turn!
DANNY: Follow the hero,
not the zero, dipshit.
HUNT: Hey, keep up! Keep up!
W... wait for us!
(YELPS)
Fuck! Fuck! Oh, my God!
(RETCHES) Help me!
Take my hand, man.
Help me fuck...
(HUNTER GROANS)
Will you fucking help me!
I'm gonna fucking throw up!
You got this, bro.
(RETCHES)
HUNT: You got this.
Don't leave me!
(RETCHES)
(GROANS)
DANNY: Oh, babe.
Fuck! Ah, you fucking pussy!
(DANNY GAGGING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DANNY GRUNTS)
Hey, be quiet.
You be quiet.
HUNT: Oh, that was a dead end.
Where do we go now?
(SHUSHES)
Go this way. Come on.
RANDALL: (SHUSHES)
Stop shushing me.
You want to go?
EVER: Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
What's wrong with you? I
wouldn't be here right now
if I didn't need
the fucking extra credit.
Okay, well, cheat off
someone smarter next time.
I copied off of you.
Ugh!
Fuck.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(INSECTS BUZZING)
(SNARLING IN DISTANCE)
(ALL GASP)
(SNARLING)
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
(ALL GASP)
Guys, maybe we should go left.
Wait, why left?
RANDALL: B... because
it's the only direction
not making scary sounds, okay?
TAMRA: What is this place?
DANNY: Oh, this is where
the tweakers and thespians go
to huff paint and have
existential crises.
(SNARLING IN DISTANCE)
RANDALL: We hit him with a bus,
and it didn't slow him
down at all.
STEVEN: No, and it sounds like
there are more out there.
I know it's crazy,
but given what we've seen...
Yeah, no, that emergency
broadcast warning was national.
I mean, that's-that's
everywhere, everyone.
What'd they say? Seal the doors
and windows and shit?
What does that mean for everyone
back in town? Our families?
Okay, we don't even need
to worry about that.
Okay, you know why? We're not in
a goddamned comic book.
Okay? So, wet dreamers,
wake the fuck up.
We all saw what we saw.
Yeah, we saw a crackhead
looking to molest us,
not a real-life
Fortnite invasion.
STEVEN: Danny, what are you
talk... That guy looked like
he was trying to eat
Mr. Lorenzo.
DANNY: Right, right.
Can you explain something to me?
'Cause I just don't get this,
right?
What is it with you shut-ins
and your zombie fantasies?
Okay, I think
Randall's right, Danny.
Something is very wrong here.
Oh, you think something's
really wrong here? No fucking...
(SNARLING IN DISTANCE)
(GASPS)
DANNY: Let's pick it up,
Blandall.
STEVEN: Hey. Hey.
(DISTANT MOANING)
STEVEN: Come on, almost there.
All right?
(SNARLING, GROWLING CONTINUES)
This should do.
Get out of the door.
(GRUNTS)
Well, I can't believe it,
but I actually agree
with the dweeb.
I can't believe I agree
with the guy
who smells like horse shit.
There's a lot of stuff
everywhere.
Maybe we should just fan out
and grab what we can and...
Batten down the hatches.
Secure the structure.
HUNT: Hey. We need
to find weapons.
Yeah, you know what?
He's right.
Real men should do that.
JACEY: Hey.
DANNY: Lock it down.
Nothing in or out.
Except maybe you nimrods.
JACEY: Come on, Tamra.
Oh, Ever.
Uh, no.
I think we should
stick together.
Yeah, so come on.
Everyone's going
in different directions.
Let's go, Tamra.
TAMRA: I'll bring her back.
Hey, Ever! Would you want to...
(EVER GASPS)
Oh, sorry. Uh, would you
just want to, like,
check some stuff out
upstairs or...
EVER: Uh, Wh... why
not? (CHUCKLES) If... Oh
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
Is this a weapon?
Can you swing it?
Come on, you even lifting, bro?
(GRUNTS) Come on, man.
It was supposed to be leg day.
(GRUNTS)
JACEY: Hey.
Hey.
Whoa! Watch the Dolces.
(EVER GRUNTS)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(CANDACE SCREAMING IN DISTANCE)
(CLATTERING)
(GASPS)
Oh, fuck.
(SIGHS)
Sorry. My bad.
That's gross.
Yeah.
HUNT: Is someone out there?
TAMRA: I thought
I saw Ryan, but...
Huh. What
about the other Randos?
What? Who are you talking about?
The other Randos.
Zits, Slenderman,
Hairy, Brace Face.
You mean Candace?
Sure.
You know they have
a nickname for you, too.
What?
Jump Street.
Why?
I'll let you figure it out.
Danny: Incoming!
Out my way.
Go, go, go.
STEVEN: Okay.
Hey.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(GROANS)
Are you okay?
DANNY: Yeah, I'm all right.
Let me look at that. Oh.
DANNY: Okay.
Thanks, babe.
JACEY: Yeah.
Yeah, you know I just want
to keep you safe, right?
No, I get that.
Danny, why are you
only sweet to me
when no one else is around?
Well, look who's talking.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
This place is so creepy.
(CHUCKLES) I know.
It's like some crazy
serial killer's secret lair.
Oh. No, I... I was just kidding.
This is... this is just, like,
some hunter's hangout for,
like...
(CHUCKLES)
...hunting and stuff, like...
You know, for...
(CHUCKLES)
But if a serial killer were
to pop out and try to get us,
I'd protect us.
(EVER CHUCKLES)
Fuck him up big-time.
(SCOFFS) Now you sound like
one of those meat heads.
Oh, come on, Ever.
I'm a D&D level 20 RAW wizard.
I've been fucking shit up
since before they were trying
to fill out
their Little League cups.
(CHUCKLES)
I wasn't sure
if I sold that line.
You sold it, Steven.
STEVEN: They just go...
Every single day,
it's the same, like,
"What's up, Big Head?"
EVER: I know.
"How's your big head?"
(CHUCKLES)
They're so mean.
STEVEN: At this point, like,
I just hear their insults
as just, like, beeping noises.
(CHUCKLES) You know,
like, they're not...
They're just, like, robots.
They're not even humans.
They're just, like,
a bunch of robots
programmed to make my life suck.
Yeah, but that kind of gives
them a pass, don't you think?
(STEVEN SIGHS)
I mean, there are way worse
coping mechanisms, right?
I'm sorry. (CHUCKLES)
I know it's tough.
STEVEN: You know, maybe
they're onto something.
Being a good person
is highly overrated.
Have we even tried bullying?
(CHUCKLES) It might be awesome.
EVER: Hey,
it's just high school.
No, it's... it's more than that.
It's a microcosm for life.
People don't change, ever.
You don't know that.
Randall: Oh, yeah?
Where's your bestie?
High school doesn't end.
It spreads.
JACEY: Sorry about earlier.
It's just, like,
things got all, like...
Like, murder-y and stuff,
you know? Ooh.
(CHUCKLES) Right.
Since your car
is a piece of shit...
(TAMRA COUGHING)
...you should just ride with us.
Oh. Well, I drive Ever.
We only have room for one.
But you can sit with Hunt.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Whoo! Good find, Randy. Damn.
Well, all right.
It ain't up to code,
but it works.
Bravo, baby.
(WHIMPERING IN DISTANCE)
EVER: Did anyone else hear that?
(CANDACE IN DISTANCE)
Someone help me, please!
I think it's Candace.
It's who?
CANDACE: Someone,
please, help me!
(EVER GRUNTS)
CANDACE: Help me!
(EVER PANTING)
It is Candace.
CANDACE: Someone please help me!
HUNT: Oh, shit, it's Braces.
Let's get her.
(SNARLING IN DISTANCE)
EVER: Let me go.
(RANDALL SHUSHES)
Hey.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(FIGURE GROWLS)
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
(GASPS) He's gone.
No. No, he's not.
CANDACE: Somebody, please!
CANDACE: Help me! Somebody!
We can save her.
The fuck we will.
TAMRA: (GASPS) There he is.
(CANDACE SOBBING, WHIMPERING)
CANDACE: Somebody
please help me!
TAMRA: What's he doing?
EVER: He's just watching her.
(CANDACE WHIMPERING)
Guys, we gotta do something.
No, we don't.
Slow gotta go. Hard truth, okay?
Ever, what if he follows her
and gets in?
If you get us killed,
I'm gonna be so pissed.
Come on, Tamra.
Please.
I'm sorry. I... I... I'm sorry.
(DISTANT SNARLING)
CANDACE: Somebody, please!
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMS)
JACEY: I can't watch this.
CANDACE: Someone, please!
Please help me!
Help me, please!
Someone please help me!
(CANDACE SCREAMS)
Candace! Run this way!
Candace!
Run!
DANNY: What the fuck did you just
do! CANDACE: Somebody help me!
JACEY: Stop her! Hey!
(EVER PANTS)
EVER: Come on, Candace!
JACEY: Ever!
(EVER GRUNTS)
Look out, Candace!
(GROWLS)
CANDACE: Help me! (SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
Help me!
(GROWLS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CANDACE SCREAMING)
EVER: Candace!
(ROARS)
DANNY: Get away from the door!
(GASPS)
(SNARLS)
Holy fucking shit! Oh, my God!
(GASPS)
RANDALL: Fall back! Back!
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMS)
STEVEN: Oh, my God!
(GASPS)
RANDALL: Come on, come on! Go!
(SCREAMS)
(ALL SCREAM)
RANDALL: Come on!
STEVEN: Okay, close the door!
(GROWLS)
(ALL SCREAM)
JACEY: Here. Here.
Here, here! Hold it! Careful!
(SNARLS)
(SIGHS) Oh, fuck yes.
I think he's leaving.
STEVEN: No, no, I don't like
when you try to think, Never.
That's when people get attacked.
EVER: At least
it gave her a chance.
HUNT: Did Braces even make it?
RANDALL: We have to get away
from this door
in case it doesn't hold.
Feel around. There might be,
like, a light or...
Got it.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
This is some layaway rave shit.
(SNARLING IN DISTANCE)
(JACEY SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
I got you.
Zombie!
Shit!
Dude! Oh, fuck! Shit!
Wait, Ryan. You're okay.
Yeah. I... I... I think so.
Really, dude? The fuck?
Are... are you all right?
I mean... No.
EVER: How did you...
How the hell did you survive?
I don't know, Daniel.
What did you say?
Okay, you don't call me that.
All right?
You don't fucking know me.
No, I don't know you anymore.
HUNT: What does that mean?
BOTH: Nothing.
Oh, please, please.
Ryan, what did you see
out there?
Before I... before I left
the bus,
I saw that thing.
It was thrashing everybody.
It got Juniper, Karlak,
Wagoner, Matt.
(SNIFFS)
I think that Candace
might have made it.
Sh...
She didn't get away.
I... I thought I saw that...
I thought I saw Wagoner
out in the woods,
but he was just...
He was different.
He was just... just
thrashing around,
and his arm was twisted
and... and broken, and...
It was like he didn't even care.
And I... I tr...
I... I tried to help,
and there was...
There was too many of them.
It's spreading.
RYAN: Fucking zombies.
All right, can you shut up?
There's no such fucking thing.
STEVEN: Well, then how else
would you explain that?
EVER: Ryan.
Did you see
where the others went?
I... I'm pretty sure
that we lost 'em.
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
(ALL SCREAM)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
RANDALL: There's gotta be
another way out!
Come on! Hurry! Let's go!
(GROWLS)
(SNARLS)
STEVEN: Ever, go! This way!
(GROWLS)
This way.
There's gotta be
another way out. Come on.
HUNT: Danny? Danny?
They're getting closer.
We gotta do something. Come on!
Danny!
Come on.
HUNT: Danny!
Danny, help! Come on!
(GRUNTS)
I gotta go.
Danny, what are you doing?
JACEY: Danny!
DANNY: I gotta help him!
(GRUNTS)
HUNT: Aah! Get off!
STEVEN: Ever, come on!
You go. All right, uh,
y... you first.
Go! Ryan, go!
No, I'll be right behind. Go!
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(YELLING)
(GROWLING)
HUNT: Danny! Help!
(DANNY GRUNTS)
Danny!
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTS)
Okay.
(GRUNTS)
(HUNT SCREAMS)
Danny!
Hunt!
(GROWLS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(SNARLS)
(DANNY GRUNTS)
DANNY: Go.
RANDALL: Go, go, go, go, go!
(ALL PANT)
(BREATHES HEAVILY) Okay.
Hey. Where's Hunt?
I could've helped him.
Where...
(SOBS) I didn't.
That thing was there.
There was too many
of the others.
And they took him.
They took him from right
fucking in front of me.
I could've helped him.
I could've...
I didn't save my friend!
Danny.
You stay away!
Just stay the fuck away.
You're bad fucking luck.
I am so sorry about Hunt. I am.
You know, if there was any way...
I said stay away!
(SOBS) You don't give a shit!
And he fought for you!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
And we did nothing for him!
We did fucking nothing!
(SOBS)
We deserve this.
JACEY: Danny, stop.
DANNY: Look around.
This isn't random.
They chose us.
(DISTORTED, EERIE LAUGHTER)
You don't scare me.
You don't scare...
(SNARLS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
(JACEY GRUNTS)
JACEY: Leave us alone!
(WHIMPERS)
(BROODING MUSIC PLAYING)
(THUDDING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(PANTS)
Randall?
Randall.
Hey, that was...
That was awesome.
TAMRA: Randall.
That was fucking amazing.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
You saved us.
I... I just reacted. I...
Anyone else
would have done the same.
I'm just, um,
I'm glad you're safe.
Holy shit.
Guys, look at all this stuff.
Wayne was on everything.
TAMRA: I can't believe they let
this guy drive a school bus.
Our district blows.
Hey, we should keep moving.
RANDALL: Yes.
Okay? Right?
(COUGHS)
You okay, babe?
It's fucking cold in here.
(DANNY GROANS)
JACEY: Babe?
(DANNY GRUNTS) Did
anyone scratch or bite you?
Fucking junkie stabbed me
with something.
Inspect it yourself,
you fucking larper.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(DANNY SIGHING)
Danny?
Look at that.
Are you feeling okay?
Danny?
(GROANS)
DANNY: I gotta go.
EVER: I think
you just need to breathe.
RANDALL: Where you going?
I'm gonna save my friend.
That's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna go save my friend.
JACEY: Danny, don't go
up there alone.
DANNY: (GROANING) Shut up.
STEVEN: Hey, Danny.
Hey, Danny.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS)
Danny. Jesus Christ.
DANNY: What we need is fire.
We gotta...
We gotta burn 'em all.
JACEY: Babe...
TAMRA: Jacey, don't.
DANNY: What we need is fire.
Ryan.
JACEY: Babe.
TAMRA: Jacey, don't.
Hey. Do you...
Do you want some water or...
Or something?
Do you have water?
No.
Fucking Christ!
I'm just... I'm just...
Just trying to help.
Just trying to help, right?
Just trying to help me.
Trying to help me
feel guilty, yeah?
Daniel. Daniel's been
gone since camp, Ryan.
So what, you just trying to make
everybody know now?
Danny.
You want everybody to know?
No!
I lost it all, Ryan!
Now I got a fat fucking reminder
every fucking day!
Danny, let him go!
You're hurting him!
DANNY: No!
No!
JACEY: Danny.
I changed fucking
everything about myself.
I changed fucking everything
so I didn't fucking vomit
every time I look
in the fucking mirror.
(PANTS)
EVER: Danny.
DANNY: Don't fucking look at me!
(DANNY SCREAMS)
EVER: We're here with you,
Danny.
Please.
(SCREAMS)
We just want to help you.
DANNY: Fuck you!
(GROWLS)
(ALL SCREAM)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMS)
JACEY: Oh, my God.
RYAN: Is... is he dead?
Of course he's dead, Ryan.
He just fell off
the frickin' roof!
EVER: Steven.
(SOBS)
I'm...
I'm sorry.
(SNIFFLES)
Ryan.
He wa... he wasn't always
such an asshole.
I just wish everybody else
could've known that.
(SNIFFLES)
W... wait.
(GASPS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROWLS)
(GASPS)
What in the uppercase
fuck was that?
STEVEN: How did he survive that?
(SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE)
(ALL GASP)
If that doesn't convince you,
I don't know what will.
(PANTS)
If he just turns like that...
There was a whole bus
full of kids.
This is happening.
(SOBS) Is Danny gonna be okay?
Are any of us? (PANTS)
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know, but I promise you
I will do everything I can
to make sure that we are.
Okay? Okay?
I won't let anything
happen to you, Tamra.
Okay?
Um...
We can't go out there.
It's not safe.
So we barricade the doors
and let's just stay in here.
Come on. No. Then
we'll just trap ourselves.
Guys, we have no food, no water.
We need help, and I think
there is help out there.
There has to be.
What, but you just...
You just want to stay here
and do nothing?
Whoa. Calm... calm down, Ever.
I'm just trying to protect us.
Yeah. That's all, I'm sure.
Well, what do you suggest
we do, then?
Those things,
I say we draw them
to one side of the building
and then slip through the other.
Go get your phones.
Maybe the bus starts.
No, no, absolutely not.
Absolutely fucking not.
It's dangerous.
Guys, c... come on,
help me with the door.
Wait, who put you
in charge, exactly?
Ever.
What?
I am sick of no one listening
to common fucking sense.
Absolutely not! I forbid it! No!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
You know what?
The great thing about this plan
is that I don't need
your permission, Randall.
If you fuck this up,
we can all die.
We have listened to you
this whole day.
You've somehow always
had the answers,
so everyone went along with it.
But how's that working
out for us?
Danny was right.
What we need is fire.
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Wayne was good for one thing.
(YELLS)
Oh, fuck!
(SCOFFS)
There is no back way out.
EVER: I'll make one.
TAMRA: Ever!
("CELIA" PLAYING)
(GROWLING)
♪ Celia ♪
♪ I'm sorry for the way
I treat ya ♪
♪ Celia ♪
Ever! Ever! Stop!
What are you doing?
Randall's right.
You can't go out there.
Oh, so now you think
we should stick together.
What? What are you talking...
Wait.
Wait, no, that... that's not...
That... that's not
how it was at all.
Oh, you really don't get it.
Look, I'm just...
I'm trying, okay?
Trying to do what?
Be one of them?
Sorry, I don't fit in that box.
Ever, wh... wh... whoa, whoa.
That's not what happened. I...
Tamra!
This is not the time.
We don't know what's going on,
we are cut off
from the rest of the world,
and the one thing we should have
is each other's backs.
Ever, come on.
No, just leave me alone.
You're good at that.
Wait! Ever, don't leave me.
Ever. (PANTS)
(SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE)
STEVEN: Ever, wait! Hold up!
Hey, wait!
Just hold up! We gotta talk
about this! Ever.
Ever, wait. Hey, hold up,
hold up, hold up, hold up.
Seriously, we have to think
this through.
I've been thinking it through
all day.
I should've said
something sooner.
But Randall said...
I don't care what Randall said,
and you shouldn't, either.
But, just please don't go
out there, okay?
Wh... what if there's more...
Everything is a what if.
I know, but... but just if...
What if I'm right?
Fine.
But I'm coming with you.
(BOTH GRUNT)
EVER: Okay.
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
EVER: Thanks for coming with me.
I was kind of scared shit less.
STEVEN: Yeah, I still am.
EVER: Oh. Sweet.
Okay, come on.
EVER: Let's go.
STEVEN: Okay.
(EVER GRUNTS)
STEVEN: Here, I got you.
EVER: Thanks. Okay.
STEVEN: (SIGHS) Okay?
EVER: Yeah. Here.
STEVEN: Thank you.
STEVEN: It's fine.
EVER: Let's get you up here.
EVER: That's it. Oh, yeah.
(STEVEN GRUNTS)
EVER: Okay.
(CREAKING)
(EVER SCREAMS)
STEVEN: Oh, shit!
STEVEN: Oh, my God. Oh, God.
EVER: (SHUSHES) Inside voices.
Inside voices. Okay.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, I am so sorry.
(WHIMPERS) Okay.
Gotta find the phones.
Oh, my God. Okay.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
EVER: Fuck.
STEVEN: What?
EVER: No. No, no, no.
EVER: They're...
They're all broken.
Fucking great!
STEVEN: Ever, I'm so sorry.
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
STEVEN: This was a really
good idea.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
You say that now.
This is why I should just
shut up and let...
Let other people...
STEVEN: What?
Oh, my God, no.
No, no, no, no.
Don't say that.
Oh, my God.
Why not?
What have I ever done
to justify anyone
listening to me?
Clearly nothing.
I'm just nothing.
Look at me. My...
My hair, my... my clothes, my...
Even my best friend
thinks I'm nothing.
I tried to save Candace twice.
Nothing.
My entire existence is just...
nothing.
I mean, it could be worse.
EVER: How?
I don't know.
I was... I was just trying
to make you feel better.
Now who's good
for nothing? (CHUCKLES)
Ever, I get what you're saying.
In your head, you think
you're one thing...
and you try hard
to be that thing.
I mean, like, you try really...
really, really hard to be that,
and then you're just not.
And then all the insults,
and the insecurities
and the names rush in
when you try
to be that way in public
and you can't. I... I...
(SIGHS) ...I get it.
I, like... I really,
really get it.
I do. I know.
I know.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
I know you.
Is this when you kiss me?
W... wait. Um, uh...
EVER: What?
What?
STEVEN: No, no, it just, um,
it's just been such a long day,
and, um...
EVER: And?
I... I lost my gum, and I, like,
I ate a ton of dirt
and mud earlier,
and I'm just...
I'm really stinky right now.
Steven.
What?
I might have puked
a bit earlier.
That's great.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
That's really great, 'cause...
then we're... we're basically
in the same boat.
Pretty much.
Do you still want to...
Yeah.
...even though...
EVER: Wait.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry. You're...
No, no, no.
Look. The radio. The radio.
STEVEN: What? What?
Come on.
EVER: Come on.
MAN ON RADIO:
...these are combustible villas.
I feel like I need a doggone...
I was right.
FEMALE VOICE:
...tensions in the DMZ
are finally beginning to calm,
as a once-torn nation...
This isn't everywhere.
(CHUCKLES)
(RADIO BROADCAST STOPS)
(BUZZING)
FEMALE VOICE:
This message is transmitted
at the request
of the United States...
EVER: I was fucking right.
It's a tape.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
Someone set this up.
(GROANS)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
Steven?
You weren't supposed to
find out about any of this.
None of this
was supposed to happen.
You...
STEVEN: I'm so, so sorry.
(GASPS)
STEVEN: Please believe me.
You're gonna be okay.
You'll be okay.
It's just a little bit.
Okay? Just a half dose,
and you're gonna
wake up, and it's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be fine.
You... you'll forget
about all this,
and we can start over.
It's okay... (VOICE FADES)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Good job, Steven.
Good job. You had to.
COACH: (SHOUTING)
That's no hustle! That's a nap!
RANDALL: I'm not talking
about changing the whole world.
I'm talking about changing
a few people for the better.
You know who? People who
make our lives a living hell.
What if we gave it back in a way
that actually made a difference?
What kind of difference?
Remember the Scared Straight
program?
Convicts and drill sergeants
yelling at kids,
showing them prison life,
awful shit, you know,
until they cry and promise
they won't grow up
to be assholes?
Yeah, but Danny, Hunt
and all those guys are popular.
They're not considered
at risk, dude. We are.
Exactly.
Nothing ever happens to them.
We can fix that.
They'll be our perfect audience.
We'll look like heroes
for a day.
We'll save the day.
The assholes will respect us
for once.
Scared Straight.
STEVEN: Randall,
this is the biggest place ever.
How are we gonna
wrangle all this?
RANDALL: Exactly. That's why
we have a ringer, Chip Landsness.
Chip Landsness?
Isn't that guy a dealer?
We'll get to that.
(GROANS) Holy shit, Chip.
Holy fucking shit.
I said subdue, Mr. Lorenzo,
not bite his fucking face off.
CHIP: It looks worse than it is.
He's fucking dead!
What are you, a doctor now?
Fucking look, Chip!
Does he look alive to you?
What the hell, man?
CHIP: How do you know?
(PANTS)
CHIP: Hey.
They needed to believe it,
and I delivered, okay?
Full commitment.
I'm fucking method, dude.
Did he deserve it?
Fucking A, he did. Fucking A.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
CHAD: He looks familiar...
doesn't he?
STEVEN: Okay,
I get everything else,
but what are we doing here?
What's this part of the plan?
Well, zombies can only
do so much.
They scare them inside,
we scare them up here.
STEVEN: So, what
should I put on mine?
RANDALL: How do they see you?
STEVEN: Okay, wait.
But we're still counting
on tricking the bus driver.
WAYNE: There's no need
to trick the bus driver.
Chad Lorenzo has been shitting
on me since I was a freshman.
He got me there. I loved being
a high school bully so much,
I never left.
Became a teacher.
I'm all the way in.
CHIP: Jesus, Wayne,
hitting a little hard, bud.
You gonna be able to function?
Function?
Chip, I've been waiting
20 years for this,
20 years to unleash.
I'm putting the "fun" back
in "function."
CHIP: Oh, he will be humbled.
Believe me.
Ever, I read somewhere
that 99 percent of all teens
wouldn't be bullied
if they simply believed
they didn't deserve it.
Do you deserve it?
(SHOUTING, SCREAMING)
RANDALL: We let Chip
do his thing,
and they all start running,
and we lead them
to here, and we wait
for the zombies.
CHIP: Which will be
your drugged-out
Rando classmates,
herded by Wayne and yours truly,
because...
Check this out.
What's in that stuff?
CHIP: Control.
This is your Manson Family
desert drug.
You tell 'em to dance,
they will dance.
You tell 'em to follow,
they will follow.
Where did it come from?
Burning Van.
Burning Man? CHIP:
No. That shit's for hippies.
Burning Van.
Happens in Pensacola
about once a month.
You can get all kinds
of shit there.
Had my guy mixology
this special cocktail for us.
This is your zombie juice.
See, we got it all planned out,
Stevie.
STEVEN: Okay, sure,
that's the plan,
but what's the plan
after the plan?
RANDALL: The plan after the plan
is exactly what they testify.
We just say
what they say they saw.
We get attacked by someone
who doesn't exist.
We all heard the tape
that's been burned
in some barrel.
And we say exactly
what they say they saw.
STEVEN: Except,
what if somebody catches on?
RANDALL: If we keep 'em
confused and scared,
then they won't figure it out.
How much did you fucking
inject them with, Chip?
That shit back there,
that was fucking crazy!
I didn't know it was
gonna be like that!
I thought it was just gonna be,
like,
shuffling Night of the Living
Dead zombies.
That shit back there was like...
Was like World War Z
on fucking bath salts, man!
CHIP: It's an imperfect
science, Steven.
Chip, you said that they
wouldn't feel anything.
You said that they wouldn't
get hurt.
You said...
CHIP: Look, dude, do I need...
I need to explain drugs to you?
It will wear off.
They won't remember a thing.
They will wake up
and not feel a thing.
STEVEN: They're not gonna
forget, 'cause they know, Chip.
They know. They know.
They all know. I heard them.
(SNARLS)
(SCREAMS)
Help us. (SCREAMS)
What do you even know
about anything?
You don't even know
what the fuck
you put in those things!
We had a plan, man.
Focus on the positive.
Everyone bought it.
We did our job.
I mean, so what
if there are a few hiccups?
I... Hiccups?
Wayne almost got everybody
killed, including me.
And now he's dead.
No one was supposed to die, man!
It's a mulligan.
We did our job.
(HOWLS)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Whoo!
CHIP: I don't know what you guys
are shitting your pants about.
You knew this would be
a possibility.
Why else would you have
a bag full of real weapons?
I got you your prize, assholes.
They're all in the cage.
Now go do what you gotta do.
What are you fucking talk...
What are you talking? What cage?
What weapons? What... what?
CHIP: Come on, Stevie.
You really think plans like this
don't have backup plans?
STEVEN: What the fuck
is that for?
CHIP: This is the contingency
plan.
This negates any
and all human error,
of which there's been
a real fucking lot of!
You two, uh...
you gave me hope.
I saw a chance to take back
all the years
that were stolen from me
because of the... the judgment
they put upon me,
because of the labels
they gave me,
because of the resentment
inside of me.
All that shit
that happens in high school,
that doesn't stay
in high school.
That shit gets branded in here,
and it festers in here.
I still carry
all that fucking anger,
all that sadness,
all that... that worry
and anxiety.
I'm so fucking mad!
It's different faces
but the same fucking dudes.
The same fucking teachers,
the same fucking cops.
Now, I hoped that we could
cure something tonight.
I really did.
We just exposed it
for what it is.
A fucking plague.
Now, I'm going to do
what I can to clean it up.
Maybe that'll help with
some of the years of misery.
I don't fucking know. (CHUCKLES)
But that could kill them.
If it need be, Stevie.
And that need...
be.
RANDALL: All right,
Tamra's gonna wonder
where I went.
I gotta get back. (SIGHS)
It's a shame I was only able
to save you, Steven.
What are you talking about?
What the...
Wh... what are you saying?
Anyone who's onto us
has to go, for real,
or we go to prison forever.
I ain't going back.
You were in fucking jail?
Only twice. Chill.
I rehabilitated.
STEVEN: Oh, my God, we're so...
fucked! Fuck!
Oh, no, no. Hey, hey.
(SOBS)
We just rewrite the ending.
We work with the girls.
We kill the assholes.
If anything happens,
anything goes down,
they are just as guilty as us.
Okay? Win-win.
I'm sorry.
Ever was just too smart
for her own good.
Maybe Jacey's more your speed.
Come on.
(WHIMPERS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey. There's no turning
back now, Stevie.
(WHIMPERS)
CHAD: That man is going
to murder you tonight, Ever,
unless you do something
to stop him.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
RANDALL: I wanted
to be the hero.
Guess I was always destined
to be the villain.
What now? What now?
What's the plan?
This is the grand finale,
Steven.
But we won't lose.
("LUCKY ONE" PLAYING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
♪ It's so dark in here ♪
(GRUNTS, YELLS)
♪ I can barely hear my voice ♪
♪ In excruciating pain ♪
♪ It's excruciating ♪
♪ I'm the lucky one ♪
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
It's time to put everyone
out of their misery.
♪ The bridge is flooded ♪
(GROANS)
♪ I can't ♪
♪ Get across it ♪
I want you to know
I wasn't planning
for things to go this way,
but since they are,
I also want you to know
that you deserve it.
♪ Down here... ♪
Let's have some fun.
♪ What do I do with this? ♪
(GROANS)
♪ What do I do, do, do ♪
♪ But call... ♪
Dose him. Don't worry
about being gentle,
especially with that one.
♪ The bridge is flooded ♪
(HOWLS)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
Leave him alone.
Why? He didn't leave me alone.
♪ I know... ♪
(GROANS)
Ever wonder where you'd be
without Danny?
Probably just another Rando.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SCREAMS)
Got you!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
RANDALL: It's time. Them or us.
You understand?
♪ Hey, hey ♪
(GRUNTS)
(EVER GRUNTING, GROANING)
♪ Hey, hey... ♪
(GRUNTS)
If you stop fighting,
I'll be sweet.
(PANTS)
Whoa.
CHAD: Ever.
Remember what your mother said.
♪ Hey, hey... ♪
Make good choices!
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
♪ Hey, hey... ♪
(GRUNTS)
(WHIMPERS)
♪ Hey, hey... ♪
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(EVER GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS, YELLS)
DANNY: Fuck.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Okay, when I slide
this door open,
you remove the latch
and get out of the way.
Okay?
Okay. Okay.
TAMRA: Randall?
Jesus, there you are.
I thought I heard something
up here.
Thank God. Where...
Where have you been?
Tamra, I'm... I'm so sorry.
Ever's gone.
Those things got her.
No, but...
We can get through this.
(SOBS)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
RANDALL: Tamra,
I need you to be strong.
I know how to save us.
We gotta get everybody up here.
Can you help me?
(SOBS)
RANDALL: It's what Ever
would've wanted.
(PANTS)
(GASPS)
I need your help, okay?
(SOBS)
DANNY: Steven? Hey, just
let us go, man.
Hey, you know,
you don't want to be here, man.
I'm with you.
STEVEN: Stop talking.
HUNT: Steven!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
What the hell are you doing?
You do this, bro,
there is no coming back!
Hey, shut up!
(YELLS)
STEVEN: Shut up right now!
Shut up! Shut up!
There's no coming back.
(HUNT YELLS)
Shut the fuck up right now!
(ALL YELLING, SHOUTING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROWLING IN DISTANCE)
RANDALL: Do you hear that?
It's them.
They killed our friends.
Well, now we got 'em cornered.
Now it's time to end it
before they take anything
else away from us.
JACEY: Let's get out of here.
No!
Look at what happened to Danny!
We can't keep running.
If we do,
they're just gonna
keep chasing us,
and that's how they win.
But not tonight.
We're gonna kill as one,
right here, right now.
Where'd you get these?
Ask me later. Use 'em now.
I don't think I can.
RANDALL: I know.
But they aren't us anymore.
(ALL SHRIEK)
RANDALL: Eyes front! Get ready!
All right, you're strong enough.
You don't need anyone else.
None of us do.
On three, you put them down.
On three.
(ALL SNARL)
One.
Two.
Three! Now!
(BOTH YELL)
No!
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
EVER: No!
No! Stop!
(GASPS) Ever?
Oh, God! She's one of them!
(GRUNTS) No, I'm not.
They drugged us! (GRUNTS)
Hey! She's infected!
She's trying to trick us!
Attack her!
Steven and Randall,
they set this whole thing up!
She's gonna kill me! Don't
worry, Steven! We're coming!
(GRUNTS, PANTS)
They tricked us, drugged us,
want to screw us,
but they fucked up,
and now they have to kill us
to get away with it!
She's telling the truth!
Danny?
Daniel?
Don't listen to her!
This is what they want!
If you want to live,
fight right now!
EVER: Tamra.
You're my best friend,
so have my back
and clock that fuck!
(GRUNTS)
Randall, no!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
You've gotta be
fucking kidding me.
DANNY: Look out!
(EVER GASPS)
(YELLS)
Ever! Ever!
(GRUNTS)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yes, Steven, you are.
STEVEN: No!
(ALL SNARL)
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
Go!
No, no! No! Oh, my God!
(STEVEN SCREAMING)
We got this.
STEVEN: Help me!
(GROWLS)
STEVEN: (SCREAMS) Oh, my God!
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
RYAN: Hey.
TAMRA: You okay?
(GASPS) Ever, look out!
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS) Jacey!
(WHIMPERS) Oh, God.
EVER: Jacey!
Oh, God. Oh, God.
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(SCREAMS)
Hey, fucker!
(BOTH PANT)
We could've been everything.
(CHUCKLES)
I would never be
with someone like you.
Fine.
(GASPS)
Tamra!
Goodbye, Tamra.
(YELLS)
No!
Daniel!
Jacey.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
TAMRA: Ever!
(GASPS)
Are...
Are you okay?
No.
Not at all.
Pretty sure I just went
through withdrawal.
(PANTS) How about you?
No, pretty... pretty messed-up.
Yeah.
(GASPS)
We're good.
JACEY: Are you okay?
(GASPS)
I'm so sorry. I was such
a fucking asshole to you.
And you, too.
Yes. You have been,
but I'm not letting you die
until we figure it out. Get it?
(SNIFFLES)
Okay.
Good talk.
(DANNY GRUNTS)
(RANDALL GROWLS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROWLING)
(SNARLS)
(GROWLS)
(PANTS)
You can't stop me!
No, Randall.
I can't.
But they can.
("FLESH WORLD" PLAYING)
♪ All the bones grew strong ♪
♪ Before they broke ♪
♪ All the blood runs hot
Before it's cold ♪
♪ All the bones grew strong
Before they broke ♪
(GROWLS)
(PULSING DANCE BEAT PLAYING)
Fuck it.
(ALL GRUNT)
(GROANS)
♪ We die ♪
♪ All the bones ♪
♪ Grew strong
Before they broke ♪
♪ So what? ♪
♪ All the blood ♪
♪ Runs hot before it's cold ♪
♪ We're here ♪
♪ All the bones ♪
♪ Grew strong
Before they broke ♪
♪ We die ♪
♪ All the bones ♪
♪ Grew strong
Before they broke ♪
♪ So what? ♪
♪ All the blood ♪
♪ Runs hot before it's cold ♪
♪ We're here ♪
♪ All the bones ♪
♪ Grew strong
Before they broke ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
(GROANS)
Jacey!
I... I got it.
(BOTH GRUNT)
Son of a bitch!
That was awesome.
(RYAN GRUNTS)
(EVER GRUNTING)
(RANDALL PANTING)
You... you are nothing.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
Shit.
Should I have said
something cool?
You nailed it.
Sweet.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
EVER: And so, the PTA set up
a field trip for extra credit
with the goal of teaching teens
to become one with nature,
respect each other...
My life sucks.
EVER: ...and maybe, just maybe,
plant the seeds of friendship.
But instead, two boys,
desperate to be lords
of high school
and two adults
who never grew up past it
hatched a plan
involving reckless driving,
drinking, drugs,
violence and horror
to teach a teacher a lesson,
bully the bullies
into submission,
humble those with hubris,
and have unprotected apocalypse
sex with their crushes.
This plan was an epic fail.
However, as the sun rose,
something else about that night
dawned upon us,
an unintended side effect
of what we'd all been through.
A bully had become a protector.
Who would've thought that we'd
be friends again, huh, Danny?
(CHUCKLES) It's Daniel.
EVER: The estranged
had come back together.
If I may ask,
what happened between you two?
It's a long story.
No, man, it's not.
We were best friends
at fat camp.
Yeah, and then
I lost all the weight,
but I became a bit of a dick
until this morning, so...
(CHUCKLES) Guess
it's a short story.
Onward. (CHUCKLES)
More like a sonnet.
EVER: A beauty queen
realized the inside
is just as important
as the outside.
Strangers were
no longer strangers.
Not to be rude, but...
who are you?
I got on the wrong bus.
Thanks.
EVER: And there it was.
This unlikely group
had bonded, like braces,
during the most combustible,
formative years of teen life
to become a loyal tribe.
Matt, Juniper...
Candace, Wagoner.
I hear Karlak can help us
get the bus started.
How can I help? Who says
we want your help, Jump Street?
I'm kidding.
Let's go, Hunter.
It is amazing how much
you can learn about somebody
after you've been
held captive together.
Ain't that right, Fat Camp?
DANNY: I guess so, Jump Street.
EVER: And then, there were
the two old friends.
And...
then there's us.
(CHUCKLES)
What did we learn, you and I?
You first.
Um,
I... I guess this is all about
getting out of your own way.
(TAMRA CHUCKLES)
I got stuck.
Sorry.
Well, I mean...
I was seriously close
to killing you back there,
so... sorry.
Yeah. What was up with that?
You know, in the moment, I...
Uh-huh.
...didn't recognize you.
But then...
I saw my friend.
But she wasn't the same anymore.
Is it that bad?
Uh, more like badass.
What?
Yeah.
Really?
Yes.
You think so?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
It's totally you.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
that was crazy back there.
Like, you got a total
mayhem makeover.
But...
yeah, all of a sudden,
there you were,
standing there, like...
complete.
And that was the scariest
part of the whole night.
'Cause I thought...
"She doesn't need me anymore."
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
No one said
high school was easy.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You know,
my mom said it's when
you get out of high school
that you learn
who you really are.
That's when you figure out
where you belong.
But maybe...
this completely
fucked-up night...
proved that we don't have
to wonder
which groups are gonna
accept us or define us,
because any group
would be fucking lucky
to have us consider them.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHUCKLES)
You know, I think
we needed that.
(ALL SCREAM)
What the fuck?
("TOO MUCH" PLAYING)
♪ Keep distance
Just don't let 'em get close ♪
♪ Seems like you're
Doing the most ♪
♪ Humanitarian boast ♪
♪ Well, keep
The brainwash going ♪
♪ It's a system untouched ♪
♪ Am I saying
Too much, too much? ♪
♪ Keep distance
Just don't let 'em get close ♪
♪ Seems like you're
Doing the most ♪
♪ Humanitarian boast ♪
♪ Well, keep
The brainwash going ♪
♪ It's a system untouched ♪
♪ Am I saying
Too much, too much? ♪
♪ Too much ♪
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
So, in an attempt to triumph
over your targets,
you two troubled teens
tricked, terrorized
and tragically tried
to take out your own classmates.
But all the besties, bullies
and babes
not only didn't bite it.
They emerged, humbled,
brave, balanced young adults.
Does that sound about right?
What are you, CIA?
FEMALE VOICE: No.
PTA.
The Parent Teachers Association
is bringing back
the Scared Straight program.
And the question we have
for you boys is...
can you do it again?
("WATERFALL" PLAYING)
♪ Like a waterfall ♪
♪ Like a waterfall
Like a waterfall ♪
And I can do this anyway ♪
♪ Like a waterfall
Like a waterfall ♪
♪ And I can do this anyway ♪
♪ Like a waterfall
Like a waterfall ♪
♪ Hey, you in the crowd
Looking south ♪
♪ Tell me what you found
I can do this anyway ♪
♪ Hey, you in the crowd
Looking south ♪
♪ Tell me what you found
I can do this anyway ♪