[music]
[wind]
[rumble]
[speaking in egyptian]
-Not now, Silvio.
Go away.
[reading in egyptian]
-"We call upon black
powers to restore life."
No.
I won't do it.
[screaming]
-C'mon, you know
this one, Robert.
-Canopic jar.
-What dynasty?
-Nineteenth.
Eighteenth.
-That'll work.
Boy, you are hot today.
There's nothing more
I can teach you.
-You know, Brice,
I'd like to review
the second and third dynasties.
-What's up?
You know, I thought you were
like the Renaissance art man.
Or was that Gina's influence?
-No, her influence is over.
-Then why the interest?
What's her name?
-Margaret.
Now
-I thought so.
I'd like to have
a drink with her.
-Oh, good.
Maybe you two will
have a good time,
because she never
wants to see me again.
-Oh, well then, why
are you studying this?
-Because I'm an art historian.
This week anyway.
Get over here.
All right, buddy, start talking.
Who are you?
-Relax, sir.
I though it was
just a hallway door.
-Listen, who are you?
And why are you
breaking into my place.
-Mrs. Trelawny.
She sent me.
She said she called.
-Hey, where you are is fine.
MARGARET (ON ANSWERING
MACHINE: Robert, it's Margaret.
I know we haven't spoken in a
while, but I need your help.
Something terrible has
happened to my father.
I'm sending his driver for you.
I'll understand if you
don't want to come,
but I hope you will.
-Cheeky bastard.
-All right, so what exactly
happened at the house.
-I really don't know.
I'm not too involved in
the goings on at the house.
All I know is there
was a lot of blood.
I haven't seen you before.
Do you work for Mr. Trelawny?
-No, I'm an art historian.
-Friend of Mrs. Trelawny, then.
-Yeah, we met at her show.
-Oh, yeah, the photographs.
-Good evening, sir, Mr. Wyatt.
-WYATT: Yes.
-Won't you come in?
I believe Miss Margaret will
be down in a few moments.
-Thank you.
-If I could take your bag, sir.
And your coat, perhaps.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, sir.
-Robert, you came.
-Margaret.
-What happened?
-He's upstairs.
-How is he?
-Terrible.
He's unconscious.
-Have you call the doctor?
-He's with him now.
Father was alone in his study.
I heard a scream.
I walked in to the room.
His arm was all torn up.
There was blood everywhere.
-Ah, Margaret, I
just about finished.
Seems to have lost a
great deal of blood.
I think he could do
with a couple of units.
And I do have some
of his own plasma.
-Why don't you take
him to a hospital?
-No, my father hates hospitals.
-I don't think I've ever
seen a coma quite like this.
-(UK ACCENT) No one entered
through these doors.
Who are you?
-Robert Wyatt,
friend of Margaret's.
And you?
-Daw, head of security for
all Trelawny industries.
-How do you know no one
came from the balcony?
-Or I should say no one forced
their way through those doors.
I've seen enough forced doors
in my time at the Yard to know.
Came in through this door.
Unless he did it to himself.
-I think we can rule that out.
He has too much
respect for life.
-Well, there it is.
And where were you again
when this happened?
-I was in my dark room.
I hadn't seen my father all day.
-No?
The housekeeper
Mrs. Grant said she
heard Mr.Trelawny
talking to you.
Called you by name.
-She must be mistaken.
-Maybe he was dictating.
-Uh, Mr. Wyatt, if
you please, could
you give us a moment alone?
-I want him to stay.
I've asked him to be here.
MR. TRELAWNY (RECORDED
VOICE); Margaret, I'm
on the verge of a
discovery, if all goes well.
If not, and I am
suddenly stricken down
by accident or attack,
you must follow
my directions to the letter.
If I'm not already in my
study, I am to be taken there.
Once there, you I
must never be left
alone, not for a single instant.
Day and night, at
least two persons
must remain in the room.
And none of the Egyptian
artifacts can be moved.
There's a special purpose in
the placing of each piece.
Also, the small key
must remain on my wrist.
My life will be in your hands.
DAW: Does anyone know
what this key opens?
-Uh, no I don't.
-MR. TRELAWNY (RECORDED):
Not now, Silvio, go away.
I won't do it.
(SCREAMING)
-He sent me away
when I was seven.
It's taken me all this time
to be with, and now this.
-He knew someone was
after him, and it
was probably someone
in the house.
-MARGARET: I really don't
know any of the people here.
ROBERT: You know, he really
should be moved to a hospital.
MARGARET: My father
has his reasons
for staying in the house.
I don't know what they are, but
I don't want to second guess
him.
Wyatt, I need your help.
-OK, I'm not leaving.
[[squeaks]
[eating sounds]
-(BRITISH ACCENT) If you need
anything, just call, sir.
-Oh, hey, you can
call me Robert.
What's your name?
-Lily Mrs. Grant's daughter.
You live in SoMa?
I hear there are a
lot of clubs there.
-Yeah, a lot of clubs.
-Do you think you could--
I mean, if there were
some clubs where
you could get me in.
-Little lonely for
you in this house?
-Gives me the jitters.
Sounds a bit odd, but the
house has its own personality.
It makes strange noises,
especially that study.
Late one night, the
door was open a crack,
the lights began
to dim, and I heard
a banging coming
from behind the door.
I knew Mr. Trelawny was
already asleep in his bedroom,
so I started to
peek my head in--
-(CAT HISSING) I
have my chores, sir.
-Well, wait, wait
what did you see?
-It's supposed to rain tonight.
You might want to
close your window
before you put your head down.
-Hearing this noise
from down the hill.
What's down there?
-The stables.
-Horses.
-There are no horses anymore.
Mr. Trelawny gave them
away a few months back.
-Hmm
-Oh, um, can we get the
heat turned up a bit?
I'll get you a space heater
from the basement, sir.
-Thanks.
[angry cat meow]
-Can you believe this rot?
Can't be moved.
Two people watching him.
I mean, why is
this being treated
like some sort of
a mystic thing?
-I don't know.
-You and Margaret
seem quite familiar.
Wonder why I've never
heard your name before.
-(SIGHING) We, uh, barely
got to know each other
before we had a
little falling out.
You know hot it is.
Listen, have you talked
to the driver yet?
-Jimmy?
-Yeah, I saw him
with a silver flask.
I think it belonged
to Mr. Trelawny.
-Hmm.
I spoke with him briefly.
But he's still on my list.
-Robert?
Would you mind taking the
late shift with my father?
We're tired, and I
remember you get up late.
-Yeah.
Fuck.
-(FROM UPSTAIRS) Lily,
where did you go off to?
-Mum, I'm just down
in the basement
getting a space
heater for Mr. Wyatt.
What's that?
I'm not cleaning that mess up.
-[laughing]
[phone ringing]
-What?
Robert, do you have any
idea what time it is?
-Yeah, it's after midnight.
I knew you wouldn't be
doing anything important.
-Yeah, and I was having a
damn good time doing it.
ROBERT (ON THE PHONE):
Listen, I got something here.
It's a small hand
rake, except it's
shaped like a snake with fangs.
-Uh.
How many?
-Uh, seven.
-RICHARD: Oh, boy.
Yeah, you know, that sounds
like a mouth-opening staff
used during mummification.
One hundred grand, easy.
-That explains why it's
bashed in the head,
but not why someone's
digging in the dirt with it.
-No, don't go yet.
-I should be going anyway.
-Robert, can we talk
about this in the morning?
-Yeah, one more thing,
stone tablet in two pieces,
one big symbol, a man
with a dog's head.
-Nibba, whoa, master
of the mysteries.
It's very important for
mummification and resurrection.
Boy, I just hope none of that
stuff is stolen, you know,
the curse.
-Don't give me that
King Tut bullshit.
-No.
Although, I'll tell you, years
ago workers on the Aswan Dam
stumbled upon an undiscovered
tomb full of treasure.
Two diggers took sapphire eyes
out of a Pharaoh's statue.
The next day, they were
found burnt to a crisp.
-C'mon, you don't believe that.
-Well, I don't, but my old
professor does, though.
And get this, he lost
an eye that same night
in a freak accident.
Yeah.
Girls love that story, yeah.
It scares the hell out of them.
I'm, I'm, I'm almost-- Oh, man.
ROBERT (ON PHONE):
Gotta go, Brice.
-Changing of the guard.
-It's about time.
It's a ridiculous exercise,
two people when one will do.
-Hi, I am Robert.
-Hello.
-Oh, yes.
Mrs. Grant was out
when you arrived.
You were at church, wasn't it?
Confessing you said?
-I said I was praying
for Mr. Trelawny.
-Yes, well, I'm off to the city.
I'll be back tomorrow.
-He's right.
I can take care of him myself.
-Oh, that's OK.
I promised Margaret I'd do it.
What is that smell?
I keep getting a strong
whiff of a pungent--
-Oh, the rich aroma
of ancient Egypt.
It's these artifacts.
They reek of it.
I can't imagine it's
good for Mr. Trelawny.
-No!
Margaret!
-What have you got there?
-So, have you worked for
Mr. Trelawny very long?
-Going on 30 years.
Do you believe what that
pompous ass implied?
Doesn't know the difference
between confession
and saying the rosary.
This man means the
world to me, and he
should be in hospital right now.
-Is there something I should do?
Should I go get the doctor?
-He seems all right now.
But that's the third time he's
done that since I've been here.
I'm going to insist very
strenuously that he be moved.
-I'm gonna go get
some fresh air.
-Hutchins?
-Yes, Miss.
-Where are you going?
-We're leaving, Miss.
I told Gwen, after what's just
happned to her, I think she
and Lily should leave, too.
Strange things have happened
here over the last few years.
This was just too much.
-Mrs. Grant told me that you're
a very superstitious man.
But my father needs you now.
Please, don't go.
-Keeping the police
from getting involved
is becoming
increasingly difficult.
Someone is obviously
trying to kill your father.
-And Mrs. Grant obviously
gone in their way.
-Have there been any
strange by, unusual
phone calls, so on and so forth?
-Not that I remember.
-What about the
prints from the study?
-Keene is processing them.
-There was someone
he was expecting,
but he never showed up.
-Someone?
-He was very upset, and
then a package came,
and he was calm again.
-A name?
-What was his name?
It was Cor-- Corbin--
-Corbeck?
-That's it.
John Corbeck.
-A dreadful man, a liar,
a thief, a grave robber.
-C'mon, tell us what
you really think.
-You listen to me.
I know about him from
my days at the Yard.
Let's just say we're
fortunate this man
has not set foot in this house.
-Seems like you hit a nerve.
-I need a break.
And a kiss.
[snoring]
-J. Corbeck.
-That tape was fantastic.
Do you really think any
of that stuff was stolen?
-Man, I hope not.
-OK.
OK, from 1967, it seems
everything in Trelawny's study
is from this tomb, the tomb
of Queen Tera, very powerful
5,000 years ago.
OK, it's a;; been
recorded in the expedition
logs, but none of it
has been seen since.
I was actually at this
tomb myself 10 years ago.
Some of the items haven't
even been touched.
-Why not?
-Well, you know, Queen Tera
was killed by her priests,
because of her popularity
with the masses.
Her dying breath was a
curse for touching anything.
I mean, you're cursed even
if you talk about what you've
seen, which I never
have, until now.
-Brice, you really believe
these curses, don't you?
-Nah, when you get down to it,
curses aren't that interesting.
-Wyatt.
-I'll print off hard
copies of this stuff.
-Yeah.
OK, look, you gotta
move faster for me.
-Hold on a sec.
Please.
OK, what are you saying?
You don't have a number for him?
All right, look, I gotta go.
Brice!
OK, this is a hell of a curse.
-Girls get a big
kick when I do that.
OK.
-Yes?
-Hello, I'm looking
for John Corbeck.
Does he live here?
-No.
-But he did live
here, didn't he?
-No.
-Can I see that?
His favorite cigars.
-I'm Robert Wyatt, I'm a
friend of Abel Trelawny's.
-Trelawny.
John hasn't been
here in a while.
-Well, do you know
where he is now?
It's important.
-John did live here on and
off, um, for a few years.
But he left suddenly.
-Why?
-I don't know.
-Do you know what his business
was with Mr. Trelawny?
-No.
He sent me-- he
sent me an old lamp,
and he said it was important I
take it to Trelawny personally,
that it competed a set.
And when John got back
from his last trip,
he was consumed with
finishing an assignment.
He sat outside a
lot, after dark.
He said he was
studying the night sky.
And with every day that went
past, he grew more distant.
Look, if you are a friend,
maybe you can help him.
-What's this?
-He's been there about a month.
If you do see him, be careful.
He's strong, and
he can be violent.
-Ah.
Here's-- the journals
of Abel Trelawny.
Yeah, should pay
for my retirement.
-[bumping]
-Playground down here.
"Today is the saddest
day of my life.
I had to send Margaret away.
I will not have her involved.
I cried when I saw her go.
I will cry every day.
Yep, that's the start of it.
And that's the end.
-[growling]
-Silvia?
Is that you?
Come back to say
goodbye, did you?
-John Corbeck?
My name is Robert Wyatt.
-I'm not interested, son.
-I'm here for Abel Trelawny.
-And I'm here because
of Abel Trelawny.
-What do you mean?
-Enough.
-Look, Margaret said you were
supposed to come to the house.
-Margaret is at the house?
-Yeah, for about six weeks now.
-Done.
I'm done.
Enough.
-Look, you sent a package he
was waiting for, didn't you?
-I sent many packages to Abel
Trelawny through the years.
-Look, something's
happened at the house.
-Something has happened to me.
-Yeah, what did
happen to you anyway?
-All right, I had just returned
from one of my many expeditions
finding artifacts
for Abel Trelawny.
And I had to arrange the
artifacts around the floor
to examine them,
when suddenly I got
the acute sense
of being watched.
I grew hot and weak.
My vision was blurred.
It's not the normal situation
when I drink, I assure you.
The lights went out.
And all of a sudden
in the air a sort of
must of ancient
tombs and a colors.
The senses-- sacred
the hell out of me.
I haven't been that
scared since I was a boy.
I found myself standing up on
a ledge to a window stark naked
with nothing but a headdress,
screaming, "My God help me.
God help me."
And I don't even believe in God.
Someone called the
police, as if it
was unusual behavior
for San Francisco.
Well, you go back
and tell him that.
-Abel's in a coma.
-What?
-He was attacked, and we
don't know who did it.
-Is there any marks on him,
on his wrists, on his neck,
like seven scratches
side-by-side?
-How did you know that?
-You must take me to the house.
Everyone in the house is in
danger, especially Margaret.
-Well, I can't.
-Look I know how to stop it.
We must complete the
task that it asks for us,
but I must be there.
-There's the little
matter of this door.
Someone feels that
you should stay here.
-It is not that they
think that I'm crazy.
It is that I think
that I'm crazy.
Now, will you take me there?
-I want you to find
out all you can
about the latest
whereabouts of John Corbeck.
There's a file in my
office, start with that.
And don't come here
anymore, don't call me.
I'll contact you.
The reason I put you on this
case in the first place--
-(JAMAICAN ACCENT): Is
because I am the best.
And where will you be staying?
-Here, for the time
being at least.
-You can have this house.
It has the same feeling
as the woods back home.
It gives me them creeps.
Well, I'm out of here.
-It really does have some
extraordinary pieces here,
doesn't he?
-I suppose so.
I prefer the Impressionists.
-Really?
You've been estranged from your
father for quite some time,
haven't you?
Sent away to school at seven,
lived in Switzerland, France,
and here in the United States.
-That's right.
-Really haven't had much of a
relationship for, what is it,
two decades?
And suddenly you develop this
keen interest to visit him.
-I've been trying to
come here for years.
My father has always
turned me down.
-Really?
Yet, here you are.
-One day I showed up
at the front gate,
uninvited and unannounced.
I was drawn here
for some reason.
I knew it was time to be home.
Have you found anything new?
-We're still checking
a few things.
-Such as?
-What exactly was your
location during the attack
on Mrs. Grant?
-I was in my room.
-Mr. Wyatt says you
were the first person
to enter the study.
-And?
-He said he could only see
shadows through the curtains.
He couldn't make
out the attacker.
It's odd that both your
father and Mrs. Grant
seem to have had
their worst luck
when you were nearest to them.
-Where was I when Mrs.
Grant was attacked?
Your father seem
to have his worse
luck when you're nearest to him?
-I'm conducting an
investigation, no more.
It's my job.
-Not anymore
-I work for your
father, not you.
If that's a problem for
you, well, there it is.
I should've have thought
you'd want me to be thorough.
-Find whoever did
this to him, Mr. Daw.
-I certainly will
do just that, Miss.
ABEL TRELAWNY
(VOICEOVER): School
in Paris will be
best for you now.
It's only a few hours away.
-Daddy, don't send me away.
I need you.
-ABEL TRELAWNY: Oh, my
darling, it'll be best for you.
-Margaret, I think
you should see this.
There's snaps of your mother.
-I don't understand.
Father said all
the pictures of her
were burned during the fire.
-Not these.
-She was so pretty.
-I'll let you look
at them by yourself.
-All right now, let's see what
you've been up to, Mr. Corbeck.
I can do astrology,
alignment of the stars,
um-- That's tomorrow night.
Daw's gonna love this.
Gonna throw me a party
at the Trelawny estate.
Dancing girls, beautiful
women, in Jamaican--
Just paid the bill--
What do you want!
It's true.
-Margaret.
-John Corbeck?
-I've often wondered
how you'd look.
And how you would speak.
-You had business
with my father?
-Much more personal than that.
Is he in the study?
-What exactly was it?
-I must see him now.
-Mr. Corbeck, my father
is seriously ill,
and I know nothing about you.
-That could be a blessing.
I, however, know a
great deal about you.
Your father and I, we
go back a long way.
This bracelet he
found at a previously
undisturbed grave
site near Tiba, 1961.
This sculpture here,
Giza, 1966, I believe.
We had a deuce of a
time trying to convince
the locals to let
us near that site.
Your father was so excited
he fell off a steep hill.
Damn near broke his neck.
But it was on the next
expedition that matters most.
You were born on that
dig, as far as I remember.
I know what's wrong
with your father.
-The doctor thinks--
-Uh-uh, doctors cannot help him.
I must see him alone.
-He said there are to be two
people in the room with him
at all times.
-Oh, there will be.
Your father still
counts, doesn't he?
You old fool, translated
it, didn't you?
(GROANING)
-These are the
instructions to the dead.
We've got to find
the other half.
-(EGYPTIAN SPEAKING)
-He says it won't be here.
This tablet was broken
for a good reason.
And the other half was sent
to the end of the Earth.
Look!
The gods will not
come at any summons.
The nameless one has insulted
them, and is forever alone.
Do not enter or--
-Or what?
-Their vengeance
will wither you away.
--Don't worry.
Don't worry.
-I've been here before, but I
thought it was just a dream.
Or a nightmare.
A nightmare still have.
-Hey, come here.
-Queen of the Egypts.
Daughter of Antiff.
Monarch of the North and South.
Daughter of the sun.
Tera.
-John, over here.
This is it.
C'mon.
The jewel, it is Queen Tera.
Pack it up.
Pack everything.
-Look at her hand.
Do you really think we
can get out of here alive,
or without being thrown
in chains for eternity?
-I think we are one
step closer to finding
out what eternity really is.
Pack it up.
-We both agreed
that we wouldn't try
it unless we were here together.
Well, I'm here now.
On that last
expedition with Abel,
we traveled to the Valley of
the Sorcerer, which is where we
discovered the tomb for the
most powerful woman in all
of Egypt, Queen Tera herself.
-She was too powerful.
The priests were going
to have her killed
because she was usurping
their authority.
-Well, that is the
official story.
The truth is somewhat different.
She heard of the plot, and she
came up with an intricate plan.
She would have
herself mummified.
-Weren't all royalty
mummified back then?
-Yes, but she had her own
doctors and her own tomb.
That, and along with
other incantations
and other white magic,
she said that she
would one day soon return.
And she always
kept her promises.
-Wonderful, Corbeck.
A simply wonderful
performance from a very
accomplished conman.
Sargent
-Still smuggling, are you?
Or have you moved up to
out-and-out theft of private--
Sargent John is a
guest in this house.
-That's all right, Margaret.
Sargent Daw and I
go back a few years.
We have a every
equitable relationship.
He hates me.
And I have other things
to do rather than think
of him, like saving Abel's life.
I knew her very well.
Your father loved her very much.
-Then why did he leave her
alone when she was pregnant?
-He didn't want to
go, but she insisted.
-What was so important
about this expedition
that it couldn't wait?
-We had found Queen Tera's tomb.
As far as we could tell, when we
opened the tomb, you were born.
Two days later, we heard
of your mother's death.
Abel was never the same.
Never spoke to
anyone for a year.
Couldn't work.
He hated it, but he
had to send you away.
-I thought just wasn't
important to him.
-Oh, far from it.
We talked for many hours.
He kept tabs on you.
He was very, very proud.
You have your mother's heart.
The sarcophagus in the study,
she's inside, Queen Tera.
-Margaret, hey, I saw
Corbeck reading this.
It's amazing.
It's all here.
There's, um, Queen
Tera, Valium Sorcerer.
-Where's the special jewel?
I don't think he's
telling the truth.
MARGARET: Make love to me.
[thunder]
BRICE (WHISPERING): Robert.
-Brice?
What the hell you doing here?
-You're not going
to believe this.
Whoa.
A sudden Egyptian interest?
Not bad.
-Hey, hey, hey, Brice, what
the hell you doing here?
-I came to warn you.
Boy, you aren't kidding.
This place is great.
-Hey, c'mon, warn me about what?
-Ok, I talked to a colleague of
mine about this tomb business,
then I mentioned Corbeck.
Swear to God, Robert, the
man went white as a ghost.
-So, is Corbeck some
kind of a conman?
-No, no, no, he
used to be some kind
of like respected
expedition leader,
until he found the tomb of Queen
Tera, then he went like nuts.
I mean, he started
mummifying people.
-What are you,
high or something?
-I'm honest.
He's trying to
mummify real people.
I'm not joking.
[scraping]
-What is that?
Brice!
-Robert!
No!
-Brice!
When he was at Scotland Yard he
had a protege, Terry Branigan,
23 years old, six
months in the force.
So I assigned him
to follow Corbeck.
Seems Corbeck does have
a history of smuggling.
Anyway, late one night
Branigan was following him,
and during the course
of a high speed chase,
Corbeck beat a
train at a crossing.
Branigan didn't.
-Dangerous business.
Being up here reminds me of
the first time you and I met.
-You know, I loved your
pictures at that show of yours.
Hey, I wanna propose a
toast to your next show.
-Robert, you know I
can't stand champagne.
I'm just going to us some water.
-OK.
-Whoa.
The sudden Egyptian
interest, not bad.
-What the hell you doing here?
-You're not going
to believe this.
Oh, great.
I am starved.
All right, now, I found out
because Trelawny has found
so many treasures, and
he gave so much money,
he has this special arrangement
with the Egyptian Minisitry
of Antiquities to study
the artifacts here.
And well, of course
like when he dies,
all the research and all the
antiquities go back to Egypt.
-So he's got permission.
Man, that's the best news
you could've told me.
-This is great.
Oh, I was taking a look at
that videotape you sent over.
I'm telling you, there
are some things on there
that have never
even been cataloged.
-Look, you gotta go, man.
MARGARET: Hi.
-Hi.
Brice Renard.
-This is Margaret.
Brice is a, uh, colleague.
-Colleague?
I believe I taught him
everything he knows.
-Yeah, Brice is the janitor--
-Curator.
-Curator of Egyptian exhibit
at the De Young Museum.
-I, uh-- You know, I heard
that Robert was staying over
at your place, and I
would give my first born
to be able to come over and
take a look at all that.
-Any time
-Great, you know, actually,
take a look at this.
Look at the mill work on that.
-Wow, it looks
like Third Dynasty.
Isn't that a little pricey to
carry around in your pocket?
-Nah, I do it all the time.
-It's beautiful.
How old is it?
-Well, technically
speaking, very old.
But we won't know for sure
until we get the test back.
-ROBERT: Brice?
Hey, Brice, man you OK?
Brice?
Brice!
-I just, I-- need to
get some fresh air.
-Ow!
-What happened?
-I cut me on this bloody knife.
-Oh!
Doctor better take
a look at that.
-Maybe you could
bring him up here.
-You sit tight.
I'll be right back.
-Well, Abel, you didn't know I
knew about your secret place,
did you?
Oh, what's this?
A copy of you special key.
Now, let's see what
you got in here.
Beautiful.
Beautiful, gov, my compliments.
-Last night, I
was reading a book
by a Dutch explorer,
named Van Huene.
He mentioned a seven-sided ruby.
-Strange reading for bedtime.
-There's also a
drawing of the jewel,
reflecting the light
of seven stars.
-Ah, is that so?
-Perhaps the jewel is the
reason you're here now.
-I heard Abel talk of
the jewel quite recently.
-I'm here to help my friend.
-Is that right?
-That's right.
-You know. it's extraordinary,
but I can find you
in my hair every time someone
close to me gets hurt.
Tell you something, the
next one hurt will be you.
-Is that a threat?
-Game of darts anyone?
OPERATOR (ON PHONE):
May I help you?
-I need to talk to someone
at Abel Trelawny estate.
Uh, my friend Robert is there.
I need to warn him.
OPERATOR: Sir, would
you like me to connect
you to directory assistance?
-Uh, Abel Trelawny's estate.
It's the curse.
They're all going to die.
-OPERATOR: I'll connect you
to the Sheriff's Department.
-This scarab--
-SHERIFF (ON PHONE): Marin
County Sheriff's Department--
-I was looking at her
face, she was looking--
SHERIFF: Just calm down, sir.
Are you still there, sir?
-Excuse me, Jimmy's
injured himself.
-Oh, dear.
-Wonder where Margaret is.
I think I'll have a
little check outside.
-Ah!
Lily!
-What's above this room?
-Who's watching Abel?
-My god, he's alone.
-What the hell?
-No!
-He's in here.
-Hold on to something.
-What's happening, John?
-Father!
Something's happening in there.
-Lily, stay there.
All right, everyone
just hold on.
-MARGARET: Please, do something.
-All right, get out of the way.
Step back.
-Wait!
Let me go first.
MARGARET: Father?
CORBECK: Good god.
MARGARET: He needs me.
ROBERT: No, no, let
the doctor help him.
-Gwen, he my bag.
-Why did you love
the bloody doors?
Jesus Christ.
-It's all right to be afraid.
Tera will not
release your father.
She'll hold him for ransom
until she gets what she wants.
-What does she want?
-For her spirit to breath again.
-I don't care if you believe
in this bollocks you talk.
But it's over.
It's finished!
If your queen is inside
here, she's dust.
She's no more alive that
the dust my housekeeper
sweeps off the bloody floor.
CORBECK: You're more
the fool than I thought.
Tera, he doesn't know
what he's talking about.
He's got no soul.
-Please, this is
very delicate work.
-All right, let's
just take it easy.
Margaret, we should get
out of here, all of us.
Your father needs
to be hospitalized.
-Tera will not let him leave.
-You didn't tell me.
What does she want?
-We'll have to ask her.
-He wants a bloody
seance now, is it?
-Not a seance, you idiot!
-Or channeling or whatever
the hell you call it.
-No, no.
Not in this house.
Please, miss, I'll leave.
I don't want to leave him.
And I will.
I'm a God fearing woman, and I
believe it when the church says
that it's a sin to
contact the dead.
-You know what you are?
Pathetic.
Pathetic!
Filling this young girl's
head up with rubbish.
Leading her on while
her father lies there--
ROBERT: Knock it off!
Knock it off!
MARGARET: Stop!
ROBERT: Philip!
-That's quite enough.
-Don't do anything
you're going to regret.
-My only regret is I didn't do
this a bloody long time ago.
-Stop!
You two fighting your private
battle will not help my father.
John, I really don't
believe in any of that.
-In this house, guns
will not help you.
-Wait, Silvio, wait.
[meow]
So
-Wait, wait, wait.
I don't think you have enough
lives to go down there, baby.
[door opening]
-God help me.
[singing in egyptian]
ROBERT: Margaret!
Margaret!
[speaking in egyptian]
ROBERT: Margaret!
Margaret, what are you doing?
DOCTOR: Come, pull yourself
together, Margaret.
-Is that still she?
DOCTOR: We need to take
her back to the house.
ROBERT: We need to wait
for the storm to pass.
-We've been at this a
long time, my friend.
Now, let's see if
it's all been nothing.
[speaking in egyptian]
-What sort of language
is that, then?
-It's ancient Egyptian.
-Ah, listen to this, Abel.
She's telling us that she's
Tera, Queen of the Egypts,
Daughter of Ateff,
Monarch of the North
and the South,
Daughter of the Sun.
She's introducing herself in
the most customary manner.
-I've seen some cons,
but this takes the cake.
Queen Tera, my girl?
You're no more a
bloody queen than I am.
ROBERT: Margaret!
-I know where the jewel is.
I know where the lamps are.
I know about Abel's plan.
And I know what you want, Tera.
And I promise you,
you shall have it.
-Christ!
-Trust John.
Do what he says.
-Abel's been planning
this for years.
The great experiment
he called it.
Bringing Tera what
she wanted to see
if the legacy
could be fulfilled.
So, for years, we
collected everything.
Amulets, canopic jars, lamps--
-And the mummy.
-Yes, even Tera herself.
We dismantled her, her
tomb, piece-by-piece
and brought it
here to the house.
-What?
-Yes.
We will capture the changes
in stars over 5,000 years,
and pick this as the perfect
location for this experiment.
What we're looking for is the
key to the tomb, the obelisk.
It was accidentally returned
to the museum in Egypt.
I had to retrieve it, and
then I had to hide it.
I was about to deliver
it to Abel, when
I spotted Daw
entering the house.
Not wanting to renew our
acquaintance at the time,
and not wanting to
keep it to myself--
-Why is that?
-Well, I didn't quite
have all the right permits
when I left Cairo.
Didn't know it was the bloody
key to the bloody door.
Ah, shine the light.
-Ah, John.
What are you doing, man?
-It's here.
I know, I put it here.
It's got to be here.
I put it here.
-John, let's stop.
Let's go back.
-Hey, don't fuck with me, man!
It is here.
-John, there's nothing in here.
OK!
Ah, it's a head.
-Oh, god!
-Tera was not the
only mummy Abel
and I brought back
through the years.
Abel hid the mummies
for many years,
preparing for his experiment.
He learned that Tera
planned to come back alone,
she's being back
a court as well.
Abel gathered the other
mummies from her court,
and destroyed them, then buried
them in unsanctified ground.
-OK, look, I'm getting
Margaret out of here tonight.
-No, we must find this
key, and complete the--
-No, no, John we should
all get out of here.
We'll get Abel--
-No!
We must find the key.
-It's not here!
Look there's nothing
here but dead things.
Look!
Man, what am I doing here?
This is crazy.
Look, nothing.
It's empty, just like
Abel's fantasies.
Ow!
John, John, give me a hand here.
Ah!
-You think you're going to
take Margaret away, do you?
There are forces
here far greater
than you could ever understand.
-It's ripping my
fucking arm off.
Get back here, you bastard.
You shoulda stayed in
that damn institution,
you crazy old-- No!
-There it is.
The key to the
tomb, the obelisk.
-Oh, John, I don't know what
the hell's going on here.
Whatever it is--
-She's not going
to go to let us go
until she gets what she wants.
-There's not much
hope left here.
-We can't give up.
-The key's not there.
It hasn't been since
his last attack.
-Do you have the key?
-No, I don't have the key.
-We need it.
We need to get the jewel,
and the jewel is in the safe.
Without the jewel, he will die.
We've got to find that key!
-When I was at the Yard, I met
a very interesting gentleman,
a very talented
burglar And he could
make short work of any lock.
He was also very willing to
share his talents with me.
-We're gonna have
to move everything
down to the tomb, including
the queen herself.
-That's it.
-Good.
There's a secret
compartment in the back.
Yes.
There it is.
Look at it.
Look at the life
in it, look at--
-Incredible.
That is why Abel was attacked,
because of this jewel.
Thank you very much, Phillip.
Abel.
Abel, we're moving
everything down to the tomb.
[tribal drums]
CORBECK: We're here.
You really did it.
Let's bring in the artifacts.
-No.
Turn her around.
Have her facing home.
CORBECK: Now, when the
seven stars on the plough
are finally aligned tonight,
the precisely set prism
will split the light
in to each lamp.
Then, we'll see
if Abel was right.
But first, we must wait.
Since you're the most trained,
and have a steady hand,
Doctor I'll let
you do the honors,
sir, at the right moment.
-Well, you do only live once.
-Maybe.
-Margaret?
-She was my secret.
I would talk to her for hours.
And one day, father saw me
trying to pry the lid open.
That's why he sent me away.
Wyatt, I need for him to live.
DAW (OFF SCREEN): Robert, it's
very important I speak to you,
please.
-Go on.
We have time.
DOCTOR: -My god, seven fingers.
-Doctor, you look tired.
You should go home
and get some sleep.
-Home?
This is too fantastic
to leave now.
-Doctor, (SPEAKING IN EGYPTIAN)
-Quite right.
I should go.
-I don't know what I'm doing.
Carrying around mummies.
Setting up artifacts as some
sort of a cult ceremony.
I'm a man of reason.
I believe in God,
but I sure as hell
don't believe in
that Queen Tera.
I'm leaving.
-So, why have you been helping
us the last three hours?
-Because I had to.
See, when Margaret
was choking me,
I had a sensation, not just
the choking, more hypnotic
than that, more
like a loss of will.
-I don't understand.
Oh my god.
-I can't explain it.
I can't think straight anymore.
I simply don't want to
think anymore at all.
I, um, I need to get some sleep.
Please tell Margaret that I'll
contact her in a few days.
-Hey, Phillip, take
care of yourself, man.
-Where are you going, Sargent?
John says it's almost time.
-Um, I have some work to do.
I shall be back in a few days.
-Well, if we don't
see each other soon,
the best of luck to you.
-Goodbye, Robert.
-[phone ringing]
-Daw.
KEENE: Where have you been?
I've been trying to reach you.
Listen, the Marin sheriff
found our man fried
like an egg in a phone
booth down the hill
from you, poor bastard.
-Relevance Keene?
KEENE: He has Trelawny's
address in his pocket.
And the butler, Hutchins,
his friends called the police
and said he was missing, said
he went back to the house
to collect his things.
And what happened to me?
Man, you ain't paying me
to go through that again.
That house is cursed!
Get them out of there.
-Those bastards!
Mr. Trelawny?
Oh, Jimmy.
Damn!
Mr. Trelawny, sir?
Good, it's you.
I could do with a hand.
I seem to be stuck,
sinking, you know.
Damn you!
I need some help!
Help!
Something's pulling me down.
What the hell?
I gotta get out of here!
Oh, no!
-That's it.
It's started.
Set the lamps, quickly.
Quickly, man.
Stars don't stand still,
Not even for the queen.
Now, we'll see.
Look.
Tera did it.
-It's unbelievable.
-Look at her skin,
untouched by time.
-The blood is fresh.
-Uh.
-She needs her jewel.
Stand back.
-John, what's going on here?
-She's moving.
ROBERT: I don't believe it.
[thunder]
ROBERT: Margaret, get back.
-All my father every wanted
to do was to help you.
Would you please,
please release him.
ROBERT: Margaret!
-Corbeck, we gotta
stop this now.
Knock that lamp over.
Corbeck!
-No.
-Get the hell out of--
-It's too late to stop it now.
-Are you crazy?
What's wrong with you?
-You never did understand.
This is the way it was
always supposed to be.
This was Abel's desire.
The resurrection of Queen Tera.
The only thing he
did not know when
he put the two pieces of
tablet together was that she
was going to come back through--
--Through me.
-Will not stop it.
You can't stop this.
But tonight, you are
to witness a miracle,
something that has
never happened before.
Resurrection of Queen Tera!
And you know where she
would be without me?
Huh?
Answer me!
-Dust
-That's right.
She would be dust.
Tonight, I hold power.
Tonight, it will be my destiny
to bring her back to life.
-So, she's be
nothing without you.
-That's right.
ROBERT: Yeah,
John, that's right.
It's all about you, you
stupid son of a bitch.
-You need me, don't you?
Huh?
Tonight, I own the power.
You cannot do without me.
-[knife thrust]
[ECSTATIC MOANING
-You really must stop
worrying about me so much.
I'll be fine.
If I weren't fine,
I wouldn't say so.
-How are you feeling, sir?
-Very well.
Thanks to you.
There are a few
reminders, however.
Margaret told me everything.
I'll never forget what
you've done for us.
-Well, I love your
daughter very much, sir.
-And we may have a
little surprise for you
when we get back.
-Goodbye, father.
We'll be back in a week.
-Well, goodbye, sir.
-Bye Robert.
-You ready?
-Wait.
I forgot something.
I love you very much.
-I love you, darling.
[woman moaning]
-I want more champagne.
-Yes, Mrs. Wyatt.
-It's been a long time since
I've been this happy, Wyatt.
Just think, fourteen hours
from now we'll be in Paris.
The second most romantic
place in the world.
-The second?
What's the first?
-Cairo.