[singers vocalizing]
- [both] ♪ I got a feeling ♪
- [man] ♪ Everything's about to change ♪
♪ No, I'll never be the same ♪
- ♪ And it's a week away
- [both] ♪ I got a feeling ♪
[woman] ♪ Everything has led to this
And the way it is ♪
- ♪ So we'll never forget ♪
- [both] ♪ So if you hear it, you hear it ♪
♪ You hear it too
The music, the music ♪
♪ It's calling to you ♪
- [man] ♪Turn it up, dive in ♪
- [woman] ♪ Dive in ♪
[both] ♪ Let it play like a song
From your heart to your skin ♪
♪ Feel the love, soak it in
Soak it in ♪
♪ This is where you belong
This is where it begins ♪
♪ While we're young
Take a chance with me ♪
- ♪ Come on, come on ♪
- [woman] ♪ Let's go make a memory ♪
[singers vocalizing]
[both] ♪ I got a feeling
That a wave's about to crash ♪
- [man] ♪ I'm about to make a splash ♪
- [woman] ♪ We're gonna have a blast ♪
- [both] ♪ I got a feeling ♪
- [man] ♪ That a star's about to rise ♪
♪ Like a fire in the sky
Gonna light up the night ♪
♪ Light up the night ♪
[woman] ♪ Turn it up dive in
Dive in ♪
♪ Let it play like a song
From your heart to your skin ♪
[man] ♪ Feel the love, soak it in
Soak it in ♪
♪ This is where you belong
This is where it begins ♪
[both] ♪ While we're young
Take a chance with me ♪
- ♪ Come on, come on ♪
- [man] ♪ Let's turn it up, dive in ♪
[woman] ♪ Let it play like a song
From your heart to your skin ♪
[man] ♪ Feel the love
Soak it in ♪
♪ This is where you belong
This is where it begins ♪
♪ While we're young
So alive and free ♪
- [both] ♪ Come on, come on ♪
- [man] ♪ Let's go make a memory ♪
[police siren wailing]
[cop] Stop, kid!
Stop right there!
It's just a stupid car.
You're gonna make it worse on yourself.
Freeze! Stop! Freeze!
Stop right there!
[puffing]
[straining] Now, bud, come on.
We're going over to the wall.
[grunts]
Get this hand behind your back!
There you go.
- What are the odds we call this a warning?
- Not good.
Let's go! We're going!
Will.
[sighs]
You stole a cop car.
Six years. Seven schools.
- Twenty-two homes.
- [scoffing]
That's gotta be a record,
and not one to be proud of.
[chuckling] It's hard not to see it
as an accomplishment.
I'm glad you think it's funny.
This time it's serious, Will.
That leaves me no choice
but to remand you to a state facility.
Juvie?
Mark, come on, you can't be serious.
- You've been through a lot.
- I'll do better.
You're smart.
- Talented.
- Hey, I'll change.
For real this time.
- There's gotta be something else!
- There's not.
I'm sorry, Will.
That group home was the last option.
I know it's been hard since you lost
your parents, but you're a great kid.
I just hope for your own sake,
you figure that out
sooner rather than later.
[knocking on door]
[woman] Hey Mark,
Kristin's here to see you.
[door closes]
[Mark] Wait here.
I'll be right back.
- Hey, Kristin, how are you?
- [Kristin] I'm fine. Thanks.
Kristin.
[evocative music playing]
[woman] One, two, three, make a wish!
Well, today's your lucky day.
Good news. This is Kristin.
She's one of our foster parents
and her son.
George. I'm George.
Umm...
- Hi.
- Nice to meet ya.
- You too.
- Will, I was discussing it with Mark,
and we would be excited
if you would join us this year.
Where?
You are going to summer camp.
Mark, I'm not really camp material.
All right then, uh, juvie it is.
- Sorry, guys, thanks for trying.
- Wait, juvie?
[Kristin] George, he doesn't want to go.
No, hey, wait.
Uh...
- Summer camp sounds perfect.
- You're gonna love it.
You are gonna love it.
I'm so totally excited. You play guitar.
We're gonna rock the talent show.
Plus, there's swimming
in the lake, a zip line.
It's gonna be epic.
I'll show you the ropes.
[rock music playing]
♪ Started out this morning
In the usual way ♪
♪ Chasing thoughts inside my head ♪
♪ Of all that I had to do today ♪
♪ Another time around the circle
Try to make it better than the last ♪
[Kristin] Let's go.
♪ I opened up the Bible
And I read about me ♪
- And you.
- Me?
♪ Said I've been a prisoner
And God's grace has set me free ♪
♪ Somewhere between the pages ♪
♪ It hit me like a lightning bolt ♪
♪ I saw a big frontier in front of me ♪
♪ And I heard somebody say, "Let's go" ♪
♪ Saddle up your horses ♪
♪ We've got a trail to blaze ♪
[all vocalizing]
♪ Through the wild blue yonder ♪
♪ Of God's amazing grace ♪
♪ Let's follow our leader
Into the glorious unknown ♪
♪ Into the glorious unknown ♪
♪ This is a life like no other ♪
[all vocalizing]
♪ This is the great adventure! ♪
[all cheering]
This is weird.
It's gonna be great!
[George] ♪ So, come on, get ready
For the ride of your life ♪
- Nope.
- Come on.
♪ Gonna leave long-faced religion
In a cloud of dust behind ♪
♪ And discover all the new horizons ♪
♪ Just waiting to be explored ♪
♪ This is what we were created for ♪
[all] ♪ Saddle up your horses ♪
♪ We got a trail to blaze ♪
[all vocalizing]
♪ Through the wild blue yonder
Of God's amazing grace ♪
♪ Let's follow our leader
Into the glorious unknown ♪
♪ Glorious unknown! ♪
♪ This is a life like no other ♪
[all vocalizing]
♪ This is the great adventure! ♪
Hi.
I'm...
Um, Avery.
Nice to meet you, um, Avery.
- I'm...
- [Sean] ♪ It's team week! ♪
♪ And we're gonna kill it this year! ♪
We're gonna kill it, baby.
- I'm sure you will.
- Will!
- Oh, Will, there you are.
- So, I'm guessing it's Will?
Yeah, Avery, Sean,
and Sean's squad. This is Will.
New kid. Nice to meet you.
You too.
- So, how do you two know each other?
- [George] Um, Will is my...
We're family, cousins.
I'm visiting from Philly for the summer.
[George] Yes.
- [stammering] Family.
- Mm-hmm.
What about you? Where are you from?
I just got back from the Arctic,
helping to save the narwhals.
- Narwhals?
- Yes.
I didn't think those were real.
I thought they were like unicorns.
Majestic unicorns of the sea.
Ah.
I'm just doing my part, you know?
- Taking this one next year.
- What?
- Right?
- Taking her?
- Yeah.
- I actually never said that.
- All right, fellas.
[squad harmonizing]
♪ We'll travel over
All the mountains so high ♪
♪ We'll go through valleys below ♪
♪ Still through it all
We'll find that ♪
♪ This is the greatest journey ♪
♪ The human heart will ever see ♪
♪ The love of God will take us far ♪
♪ Beyond our wildest dreams ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[vocalizing]
- Yes sir.
- [stammering]
- [squad laughing]
- That's what I do.
Wow. Is he for real?
He is very, very real. Anyway...
♪ Saddle up your horses ♪
- What?
- ♪ We've got a trail to blaze ♪
[all vocalizing]
♪ Through the wild blue yonder ♪
♪ Of God's amazing grace ♪
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ Let's follow our leader
Into the glorious unknown ♪
♪ To the glorious unknown ♪
♪ This is a life like no other ♪
[all vocalizing]
♪ This is the great adventure! ♪
- [all cheering]
- Hi, George.
[campers chattering]
[George] Come on.
[Will] You didn't tell me
this was church camp.
- Hey, David.
- Hey!
It's the last week of summer.
Are you ready?
Five hundred percent.
Leaves and hearts will be a-changing.
Yes! So what do you
have planned for the tribunal?
It's pretty exciting. Two words.
[in Scottish accent]
Braveheart!
Well, that's actually one word.
Oh.
Oh! Look, here's Will Hawkins' file.
- Oh, right.
- Social Services put everything in there.
What's this? Is this real?
He tried to sell his high school
on Craigslist?
- Mm-hmm! That boy got three offers.
- [chuckles] Okay.
Uh, is this kid something
I gotta be worried about?
I seem to remember
a certain bad boy back in the day.
Yeah, back when I had
a glorious head of man-hair.
[laughs] Relax, Fabio. Will will be fine.
George is showing him the ropes.
It's actually kinda cute.
- You got him staying in the...
- Yeah, the legit cabin.
- Yeah, it's, um...
- It's...
- Yeah.
- It is.
[tense music playing]
Mmm. She's a classic.
That's a word for it.
[sighs]
Hello, old friend.
You actually chose this cabin?
Yeah, I mean, who wouldn't?
The toilet backs up, when it works.
There's no AC... Oh, and the spiders.
Spiders?
Huh.
I guess they haven't
come out yet. Anyway.
Oh well.
Oh, by the way, what was that back there?
The whole family slash cousins thing?
[stammering]
I don't mean to be a prude,
but lying's up there on the top ten
"Thou shalt nots."
I wasn't ready.
It made me kinda uncomfortable.
- It doesn't really fly...
- Yeah, I totally get it.
- Oh, you get it?
- [Will] Yeah, I do.
[chuckles] Great.
That's a relief 'cause
I'm not trying to be uncool.
You like the view.
What?
The view.
- No, that's not it at all.
- Careful. Lies are up there.
What's her name?
[dreamy music plays]
[George] Presley Elizabeth Borsky.
Dean's list four years straight.
Loves all things cute and cuddly,
specifically anything pug-related.
[chuckles] She wears the perfect
little shoe size.
Seven and a half, narrow.
We're gonna have to work on
this stalker vibe you got going on.
What about Avery? What's her story?
[chuckles] Way out of your league.
Trust me.
Really? Ouch.
Yeah, how should I say this?
I don't know if she'd be into the whole
"stealing a cop car" kinda guy.
First of all, borrowed a cop car.
Second of all, how did you even know that?
Oh. Georgie's got ears everywhere.
[sighs] Well, then,
what would she be into?
Like, what's her deal?
Uh, this camp, honestly.
She practically lives here.
Her dad owns the place.
What about her mom?
Let me guess, she's off
saving the world like Mother Teresa.
No. She's...
Doesn't really talk about it.
She spends most of the summer
as a counselor and, uh,
this is the only time
she gets to be a normal camper like us.
And watch out, she's crazy competitive.
[chuckles] That makes two of us.
[George chuckles]
George, you said that telling
the truth wasn't an option.
No. I'm just not super sure
Avery would be into it.
That kinda sounds
like the same thing, dude.
[chuckles]
I have to make this camp thing work. Okay?
If I'm going to fit here,
I have to be something I'm not.
That's where you come in.
- Right, Georgie?
- Um...
How about this? If you help me,
then I'll help you
with Miss Presley Elizabeth Borscht.
- Borscht? Barber?
- [George] Borsky.
[Will] Borksy! Right.
All you gotta do is keep our secret,
show me the ropes.
That's it.
So I guess I'd be like...
[imitating Yoda]
Your Yoda, I will be.
- Yes. Sure. My Yoda.
- [continues in Yoda voice] Mmm.
- Lesson one, my young Padawan.
- You can stop talking like that.
Shorts, wear them, you must.
[chuckles]
[in normal voice] You're welcome.
Got plenty. Welcome to camp.
You're a really weird dude.
Thank you.
[upbeat music playing]
Why are they so itchy?
Polyester blend. Or as I like to call it,
God's gift to fashion.
I smell like old people.
This is my super real cousin Will,
just visiting from out of town.
- We're related.
- Easy, tiger.
- [Will] What's the plan, Rain Man?
- [George] Take your pick.
- Archery, baking club...
- Oh, what about that?
[Will] Nope. Don't do heights.
Okay, we are definitely
signing up for that.
Uh, no paintball, I never do paintball,
I wasn't really built for that.
- Today's the day.
- No, stop, don't go over there.
- I don't want to. Don't invalidate me.
- Hey, guys, how's it going?
Hey! It's, um, it's Will, right?
- Ah! Good memory, um, Avery.
- Thanks. Funny.
- Let me guess, you're on the red team?
- Yeah, Crimson Angels.
Did you come up with that name?
Why?
I'm just trying to decide
how honest to be in my opinion.
Oh! That's funny.
I, uh, was thinking the same thing
about your shorts.
- [chuckling] Touché.
- [Avery laughs]
And you must be Presley.
- Yeah, hi, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Hey, George.
[chuckles bashfully]
George was actually just telling me
all about you earlier.
- Really?
- No, no, no...
- Nothing weird or anything.
- Right.
- I... We're cousins for the summer.
- I love the summer.
- He's my cousin and we're here.
- Cool.
- The summer.
- It's okay.
I was just showing him around. No biggie.
That's awesome, George. [chuckles]
[George] Y-yeah.
- This'll be fun to do it together.
- [George clears throat]
- Where do I sign?
- Here.
- [George] Don't write my name. Forgery.
- I'm signing your name.
- [Avery] You'll be great.
- Excited, because...
- There we go.
- - [George clears throat]
[Avery] Thanks.
Good luck, Will...
Hawkins.
You're gonna need it.
- Luck?
- [Avery] Yeah.
- Okay.
- [Avery] Okay.
- See you there.
- See you around, George.
Mm-hmm.
[chuckles]
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
[muttering]
That was good. You looked good.
That time.
- Dude, what was that?
- I know. [groans]
I can talk to anybody
but Presley. It sucks.
So, it looks like George
still has a thing for you.
Come on, he can't even look at me.
Presley could have any guy she wants.
Trust me, all right? I tried last year.
I wrote her a letter every single day.
I didn't ever send them.
Maybe you should invest in some stamps.
I'm telling you,
if the two of you just would talk.
You just gotta talk to her.
Yeah.
[girls talking indistinctly]
Dude, come on.
♪ I don't even know
What I would sa y if I wanted to ♪
♪ Not exactly what the kids
These days are calling cool ♪
♪ Don't overthink it, man
Just do you ♪
♪ If I were you
Maybe that would be true ♪
♪ What if I try to talk all smart
And only dumb comes out? ♪
♪ Just a pretty face
Like, that's the only thing I'm about ♪
♪ There's way more to you ♪
- ♪ Oh, I hope that's true ♪
- Well, it is.
♪ Can't help but wonder
If I'm good enough ♪
♪ I just don't think
That I am good enough ♪
♪ She don't even see me ♪
- ♪ He's way out of my league ♪
- What are you talking about?
♪ So stop talking crazy ♪
♪ There's just no way
That you're not good enough ♪
♪ Don't let them tell you
You're not good enough ♪
♪ A little weird is a good thing ♪
[both]
♪ God made you just how you should be ♪
♪ Good enough
More than good enough ♪
♪ I wish you could see
How amazing you are ♪
♪ You just gotta be you
Don't break yourself apart ♪
♪ I wanna see myself like you do ♪
♪ Just gotta own it, girl
It's so true ♪
♪ The only way you could go wrong
Is if you doubt yourself ♪
♪ Confidence is everything
No need to be someone else ♪
♪ It's so easy for you ♪
- Eh. That's true.
- Come on.
♪ Can't help but wonder
If I'm good enough ♪
♪ I just don't think that
I am good enough ♪
♪ He don't even see me ♪
♪ She's way out of my league ♪
[both] ♪ So stop talking crazy ♪
♪ There's just no way
That you're not good enough ♪
♪ Don't let them tell you
You're not good enough ♪
♪ A little weird is a good thing ♪
[both]
♪ You know you're just how you should be ♪
♪ Good enough
More than good enough ♪
Okay.
- [boys and girls vocalizing]
- Mm.
♪ Trust me, I know you're afraid ♪
♪ Be who you are, man
Who cares what they say? ♪
♪ And you'll be all right
Just show 'em your light ♪
♪ Get out of your own way ♪
♪ You've got no reason to doubt
You are so beautiful inside and out ♪
♪ You'll be all right
Just show 'em your light ♪
♪ Can't help but wonder
If I'm good enough ♪
♪ I just don't think that
I am good enough ♪
♪ She don't even see me ♪
♪ He's way out of my league ♪
♪ Stop talking crazy ♪
♪ There's just no way
You're not good enough ♪
♪ Do you really think that
I am good enough? ♪
♪ If you're having trouble believing ♪
♪ God made you just how you should be ♪
♪ Good enough
More than good enough ♪
- [George] Lay of the land.
- [Will] Hit me.
Camp's divided into three teams.
I'm Verdes Maximus.
- [Sean] Georgie boy and new kid!
- Looking good, Stuart.
- Excuse me? Did you call me Stuart?
- He's turning around.
Oh my gosh.
Why did you do that?
- [George] Hey, hey, hey.
- Hey man, it's Sean. My name is Sean.
- That's what I said, right?
- That's what I heard.
- Right?
- Whatever.
Georgie, we're gonna
destroy you this year.
- Mmm-hmm.
- [Sean] Because what?
We haven't lost in how long?
Oh yeah, that's right.
♪ Never ♪
- Yeah. Mmm.
- Wow.
- Good ear.
- A long time.
Maybe you'll be one of my Apostles, Will.
- Really?
- Yeah.
If you have Apostles,
doesn't that make you...
- Winners! Yes!
- [Will] Okay, got it.
So, you're a team of Apostles. Got it.
For a second there I thought you might
have an over inflated sense of self.
[snorting, coughing]
The thing is,
I'm not sure I'm brave enough
to pull off one of those t-shirts
in public, I'll have to pass.
Oh. That's a shame
because I sell these t-shirts
to raise money
for a cause close to my heart.
- I think that's him on there.
- On that narwhal.
Anyways, your team's not a choice.
We'll see what happens
tonight at the tribunal.
Can't wait.
Great. Awesome.
I'll see you gentlemen tonight.
- See you tonight.
- You will.
- Apostles out.
- See you there.
Great!
- [Azures whooping]
- [Sean] Hoo-rah!
Oh.
- Okay, let's be on our way.
- Will.
[Will] What is this tribunal thing?
We're gathered here tonight
on this hallowed ground
beneath the great moon and stars,
to honor an age old tradition.
Welcome to the tribunal!
[campers cheering]
[whooping]
[David] Newbies! Rise!
From this day forth,
you'll be part of your tribe,
and your tribe will be part of you.
And you forever
will be part of us all.
Come forth!
Crimson Angel!
[Crimsons cheering]
Azure Apostle!
[Azures whooping]
Whoo!
Hmm...
Crimson Angel!
[Crimsons cheering]
Good to meet you, Will.
You too.
[David] All right.
Verdes Maximus!
[campers cheering]
I pulled some strings.
Pretty cool, huh?
[chuckles] You're one of us now.
[David] Azure Apostle!
[Azures cheering]
[rhythmic beat playing]
♪ We are Apostles
And we're gonna win ♪
♪ We beat you last year
And we'll beat you again ♪
[Azures] ♪ We are Apostles
And we're gonna win ♪
♪ We beat you last year
And we'll beat you again ♪
No!
We're gonna have a lot of fun this week.
♪ We're not rude, we're not mean ♪
♪ We're just money honey
We're the green machine ♪
[Verdes] ♪ We're not rude
We're not mean ♪
♪ We're just money honey
We're the green machine ♪
[cheering]
♪ Stronger than steel
Hotter than the sun ♪
♪ Red won't stop
Till we get the job done ♪
[Crimsons] ♪ Stronger than steel
Hotter than the sun ♪
♪ Red won't stop
Till we get the job done ♪
All right!
Boo!
♪ I'm sure you're fine
I'm sure you're sweet ♪
[Azures] ♪ I'm sure you're fine
And oh so sweet ♪
♪ I got bad news
We can't be beat ♪
- You wish!
- ♪ I got bad news ♪
♪ We can't be beat ♪
- [cheering]
- Awesome!
Greatest week ever, right?
Well, you'll get there.
♪ You like our style?
You like the way we rock? ♪
[Verdes] ♪ You like our style?
♪ Green is the team
That can't be stopped ♪
[cheering]
All right, let's go!
♪ Red's gonna beat you
Red's gonna score ♪
[Crimsons] ♪ Red's gonna beat you
♪ Red's gonna win
God loves us more ♪
[Crimsons] ♪ Red's gonna win
- [Crimsons cheering]
- Yes, God loves us all equally.
[Kristin] Let the games begin!
[campers cheering]
[Sean whooping]
[bugle reveille playing over PA]
[David] Good morning, campers.
It's a beautiful sunny day.
Everybody up. Everybody moving.
It's time to get this party grooving.
As you know, another year
of Warrior Games is at hand.
Will the Apostles hold onto their lead?
Or will another team rise
from the ashes and claim their throne?
Good morning, campers.
It is a beautiful sunny day.
Everybody up. Everybody moving.
It's time to get this party grooving.
[Will] Just make it stop.
[clicks tongue]
- Hello. Earth to Will.
- Go away.
We get to kick total butt today.
Finally show Sean
and his mini-me's how Jedis get it done.
[imitating lightsaber]
- It's gonna be epic.
- No, it's not going to be epic.
I'm 17.6 miles from civilization
and surrounded by Jesus freaks.
Wow. I feel like I should be offended
but I'm actually just impressed
with your geographical skills. Like,
did you just know that?
Rule number one:
always have an exit plan.
- That's rule number one?
- Yes, it is.
Problem is,
all roads lead to juvie this time.
Yeah, but this time you got a George.
He's not going to let you leave.
Right? I need you for the talent show.
You're what I need
to bring the performance over the top.
- And it's gonna be epic.
- Please stop saying that.
Well, it's true.
I'll quit if you quit with the "boo-hoo,
I'd rather be anywhere than this place
because I'm so broody and cool."
It's not a good look, even I know that.
Look, you have a chance to do
something really solid this week.
Help me win for the first time in my life.
Bonus, hang with Avery.
And, who knows,
maybe you'll have a little bit of fun.
Like, by accident?
So, stop whining.
Suck it up.
And help me kick some
[singing] ♪ Apostle behind ♪
Hmm?
[sighs]
- That was a pretty solid pep talk, George.
- Thank you.
Did you practice that?
I did. Was the singing too much?
I couldn't decide.
- No, that's what got me.
- The singing?
- Mm-hmm.
- Nice.
Want some Ovaltine? Apple Jacks?
- No, I'm good. I got Twizzlers.
- Nice.
[upbeat rock music plays]
Why would you get more of this?
I like it. It's camp.
- It's gross, is what it is.
- You're supposed to get a bun.
- Ugh!
- All right.
[Sean] All right!
Five minutes!
[all] Five minutes!
[all chanting] Five minutes!
- What's going on?
- You're not gonna like it.
All right! The people have spoken.
- Will Hawkins!
- There it is.
- Oh!
- It's time for your five minutes of fame.
- Five minutes?
- Get there.
[Avery] Five minutes!
[all chanting] Five minutes!
Five minutes!
- Get up there.
- Okay, I'll do it.
- [Sean] Let's give it up for the new kid!
- Wish me luck.
[campers cheering]
[George] I believe in you!
[Sean] The name is William Hawkins.
The game is five minutes of fame.
And the name of the game is to find out
who the mysterious new kid really is.
Mysterious? Huh.
[campers cheering]
- [whooping]
- Okay, all right.
Bring it on.
Favorite color?
Green, of course.
[Verde team cheering]
- Profession?
- Teenager.
- Favorite movie?
- Twilight.
- [applause]
- You good at sports?
If awesome is good then yeah.
[campers laughing]
- Celebrity crush?
- [Will] Bella Swan.
Real crush?
- I'm still going with Bella.
- [campers laughing]
- [girl] Biggest regret?
- Sitting here.
Favorite book of the Bible?
Uh...
Ah, man, you know,
I-I couldn't pick just one.
Oh, I totally get that.
[scattered laughter]
Who's your hero?
My dad.
Your favorite person?
My mom.
[campers] Aww.
[chuckles] Okay, all right!
Let's give it up for the new kid, huh?
- Huh?
- [campers cheering]
[Sean] All right, who's next?
How about Georgie boy?
I believe in you, cuz.
- I don't know!
- Come on! Come on up here.
George! George! George!
- Okay, okay.
- [campers chanting] George! George!
All right! Okay.
- You're welcome.
- [David] Will.
Thanks a lot.
- Whatever happened, I swear it wasn't me.
- Oh, you can relax.
I don't believe for a second
you're a Twilight fan.
You don't seem the type.
- Don't judge a book by its cover.
- I never do.
I just wanna say
I'm glad you're here, Will.
That's it. So I called you out here.
Glad you're here.
Well, thanks.
Hey, by the way, what's with the name?
Aweegaway?
Yeah, no, it's Aweegaway.
You guys are taking a week away
to hang out with us.
Oh, yeah, that makes more sense.
And bonus, every once in a while,
somebody finds out they're a week away
from an experience
that changed everything for them.
My favorite part.
[chuckles]
Here I was thinking you were a funny guy
who was a little too into Braveheart.
You're right, I am a funny guy
and I do love Braveheart.
- But don't judge a book by its cover.
- Touché.
One last thing.
Don't put my camp on Craigslist.
- I won't.
- Okay, thank you. Well, it's time.
- For what?
- [siren blares]
Warrior Games, baby!
[siren blaring]
- Wow.
- [David] Warrior Games!
- Hear ya.
- Man, is that Will Hawkins, the new kid?
Thanks a lot.
You set the bar high in there.
- I'm sure you were great.
- If awesome is good then yeah.
- [Will chuckles]
- Oh my gosh.
Everyone's talking about you
and Sean hates it.
- Will!
- Tragic.
- That was so impressive.
- Oh, thank you.
Yeah, I mean, anyone can answer
questions, but it is about to get real.
- [George chuckles]
- [Sean] Whoo!
Warrior Games, baby!
What he said.
- Whoo!
- [Avery] That's right.
- You're gonna beat the blob this year.
- That's because I love the blob.
- This girl loves the blob.
- I do love the blob.
- That's why I do it, Sean.
- I love the blob too.
- Really?
- I do.
- You love the blob? I thought you...
- George, you know me. I love that thing.
- Great.
- My friends call me "blobtastic."
- That's cool.
- Really? You like can't get them to stop?
I've tried, but they just seem
too overwhelmed by my skills.
Of course.
Ah, well, look,
don't feel bad because when I beat you
I won't think any less of you.
Okay.
Mr. Blobtastic.
You can call me Will.
Uh, eh... Bye. Bye, George. [chuckles]
I didn't know you blobbed.
If we go now we could get
practice jumps before anyone else.
You wanna? Come on!
Wait, back up, jumps? You didn't say
there were gonna be jumps.
George!
[rock music playing]
[George] Time to fly.
Can you give me
something extra on the jump?
The further I go, the higher we score.
- Hello?
- Huh?
Dude, that's pretty tall.
Yeah, it's the blob.
Wait, have you never...
No.
Yeah, great. Well, Blobtastic,
today's the day.
[rock music continues]
♪ The long awaited rains
Have fallen hard on the thirsty ground ♪
♪ And carved their way to where ♪
♪ The wild and rushing river
Can be found ♪
♪ And like the rains I'm here
Where the river flows ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[tower creaking]
♪ My heart is racing ♪
♪ My feet are weak as I walk to the edge ♪
♪ I know there is no turning back ♪
♪ Once my feet have left the ledge ♪
♪ And in the rush I hear a voice ♪
♪ It's telling me
It's time to take a leap of faith ♪
♪ So here I go ♪
♪ I'm diving in
I'm going deep ♪
♪ In over my head I want to be ♪
♪ Caught in the rush
Lost in the flow ♪
♪ In over my head I want to go ♪
♪ The river's deep
The river's wide ♪
- ♪ The river's water is alive ♪
- You got this!
♪ So sink or swim
I'm diving in ♪
[George screaming and laughing]
♪ There is a supernatural power
In this mighty river's flow ♪
♪ It can bring the dead to life
And it can fill an empty soul ♪
♪ And give a heart
The only thing worth living ♪
♪ And worth dying for ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ We will never know
The awesome power of the grace of God ♪
♪ Until we let ourselves
Get swept away into this holy flood ♪
♪ If you take my hand ♪
♪ We'll close our eyes
And count to three ♪
♪ And take a leap of faith ♪
♪ Come on, let's go! ♪
♪ I'm diving in, I'm going deep ♪
♪ In over my head I wanna be ♪
[all] ♪ Caught in the rush
Lost in the flow ♪
[Will] ♪ In over my head I wanna go ♪
♪ The river's deep
The river's wide ♪
♪ The river's water is alive ♪
♪ So sink or swim I'm diving in! ♪
[all cheering]
[Will] ♪ Oh, yeah ♪
[vocalizing]
[blows whistle]
[screaming]
[both laughing]
[Avery] ♪ Let's go ♪
[all] ♪ I'm diving in
I'm going deep ♪
[Will] ♪ I'm going deep ♪
[all] ♪ Caught in the rush
Lost in the flow ♪
[Will] ♪ In over my head, I wanna go ♪
♪ The river's deep
The river's wide ♪
♪ The river's water is alive ♪
♪ So sink or swim
I'm diving in ♪
- [all] ♪ I'm diving in, I'm going deep ♪
- [Will] ♪ In over my head, I wanna be ♪
♪ Caught in the rush
Lost in the flow ♪
[Will] ♪ In over my head, I wanna go ♪
♪ The river's deep
The river's wide ♪
♪ The river's water is alive ♪
♪ So sink or swim I'm diving in! ♪
[all] ♪ I'm diving in, I'm going deep ♪
[Will] ♪ In over my head I wanna be ♪
♪ Caught in the rush
Lost in the flow ♪
[Will] ♪ In over my head I wanna go ♪
♪ The river's deep
The river's wide ♪
[Will] ♪The river's wide, oh! ♪
[all] ♪ So sink or swim I'm diving in! ♪
[David on PA] Get ready,
next up is an epic dodgeball face off.
[campers cheering]
Come on, Presley!
[cheering]
- [grunts]
- Hey! Oh, not cool.
Oh! Sorry. Didn't see you.
[upbeat rock music playing]
We can do this!
- Ow!
- [campers] Oh!
It's okay. You're fine.
Hey, good work.
Eye on the prize!
[indistinct]
[inaudible]
[tense music playing]
[in slow motion] Presley!
No!
Oh!
- I'll be right back.
- Wow!
[whimpering]
Oh, poor baby.
- Try this.
- Thank you so much.
- Hmm?
- Oh.
It's cold.
- Let me know if you need anything else.
- You're an angel.
Thank you.
Ah!
She's right there. Just go check on her.
- Come on, you can do this.
- No.
George.
It's really not that bad, you know. Sorry.
I have a bag of peas on my face, Avery.
Yeah, but your hair...
it's never looked better.
Really?
No, it's actually really frizzy
and it's a little flat.
[both laughing]
- George, what are you doing?
- I can't go out there, forget it.
- Stop pacing. Please.
- [groans]
Stop!
You just don't understand.
I'll never be the guy who gets the girl.
I'm Duckie. What can I say?
What? You are the cool guy, George.
- You're kinda the coolest.
- I'm a sucker.
You gotta go out there and get her.
This is your moment.
- Like one of those Jeff Hughes movies.
- John Hughes.
- That's it! You have to John Hughes me.
What?
John Hughes me. The makeover montage.
We go to the mall, you get me
a leather jacket, jeans with rips in 'em,
and killer shades. It works every time.
- Come on, just do it.
- [sighs]
All right, I'll see what I can do.
Uh...
Now go get the girl.
That was a really quick montage.
[clicking fingers]
♪ Oh! ♪
♪ Uh! ♪
♪ Baby, baby
I'm taken with the notion ♪
♪ To love you
With the sweetest of devotion ♪
♪ Baby, baby
My tender love will flow from ♪
♪ The bluest sky to the deepest ocean ♪
♪ Stop for a minute ♪
♪ Baby, I'm so glad you're mine ♪
♪ Yeah, ooh ♪
♪ You're mine ♪
♪ Baby, baby
The stars are shining for you ♪
♪ And just like me
I'm sure they adore you ♪
♪ Baby, baby
Go walking through the forest ♪
♪ The birds above
Are singing you a chorus ♪
♪ Stop for a minute ♪
♪ Baby, I'm so glad you're mine
Yeah ♪
♪ Ever since the day
You put my heart in motion ♪
♪ Baby, I realize
There's just no getting over you ♪
[audio playing in reverse]
[sighs]
Super nope.
[bugle reveille playing over PA]
[David] Good morning, campers.
It's a beautiful sunny day.
Everybody up. Everybody moving.
It's time to get this party grooving.
Afternoon water sports
have been postpone d due to umm...
uh... but we're cleaning up.
Side note: Chef Lisa's spicy chili
is off the lunch menu
for the remainder of the week.
[Will] ♪ I've spent... ♪
♪ So long ♪
♪ Hurting ♪
♪ Lying came so naturally ♪
That's beautiful.
Oh.
Oh, sorry, I...
I was just walking.
- I didn't mean to...
- No, it's cool.
[sighs]
I thought I'd come here,
watch the sunrise.
Mh.
And George is a little perky for me
in the morning.
- So...
- [chuckles]
[Avery] Yeah.
Is that, um...
something that you wrote?
Uh, just a little something
I've been working on.
So he's Mr. Blobtastic
and he plays the guitar.
That is pretty impressive.
[both chuckling]
All right, I'm up here
writing moody sunrise songs.
What's your excuse?
You know, it's kind of a personal thing,
but if you wanted to, you could come.
Pass up a mystery outing?
Let's do it.
[chuckles]
[gentle music playing]
[Avery] Just over here.
Are you taking me to some secret hideout?
[chuckles] Sort of.
- Should I be alarmed?
- No!
Okay, just checking basics.
Y'know, I'm kinda a big deal at camp,
so if I go missing,
people will come looking.
- Will they?
- Mmm-hmm.
Really?
[talking indistinctly]
[gentle music swelling]
[Will] Wow.
[Avery] Pretty amazing, huh?
I come here every year.
It is pretty much
my favorite place on the planet.
- I can see why.
- [chuckles]
When I was little my, um...
my mom, she got sick.
And so my dad and I
wanted to create a place
that was magical for her
when she wasn't in the hospital, so...
we made this.
My mom, her favorite were the butterflies.
There are some now,
but you come back in the spring,
I'm telling you, you...
you would not believe it.
Y'know, it's been almost eleven years.
But she's still here.
Doesn't it hurt?
Being here?
Well, yeah.
Of course, I miss her, every day, but...
I know that it's just temporary.
- So you'll see her again?
- A hundred percent.
A hundred percent? Wow.
I mean, I guess I don't,
I don't know-know that, but...
Yeah, no, I just choose to believe.
I mean that's faith, right?
What about you?
What?
Oh yeah.
Uh, me too.
Yeah, I was just testing you.
[chuckles] Right.
Okay, well, how did I do?
Nailed it. Of course.
[chuckles]
You're pretty perfect, aren't you?
No.
No, I'm not.
- It's okay, you can admit it.
- No, I can't though, because I'm not.
Look, to be honest with you,
and I know you didn't mean it
in a bad way or anything, it's just...
I hate that word.
Y'know, perfect, it's just impossible.
It's like I find myself doing this thing
I know that I shouldn't but,
I'm, like, trying to be what everybody
expects me to be,
and it is exhausting.
Well, I didn't mean it like that.
I know, I...
It just seems
like you have it all figured out.
[soft music playing]
♪ The wind is moving ♪
♪ But I am standing still ♪
♪ A life of pages ♪
♪ Waiting to be filled ♪
♪ A heart that's hopeful ♪
♪ A head that's full of dreams ♪
♪ But this becoming
Is harder than it seems ♪
♪ Feels like I'm looking for a reason ♪
♪ Roaming through the night
To find my place in this world ♪
♪ My place in this world ♪
♪ Not a lot to lean on ♪
♪ I need your light to help me find
My place in this world ♪
♪ My place in this world ♪
♪ If there are millions
Down on their knees ♪
♪ Among the many
Can you still hear me? ♪
♪ Hear me asking
Where do I belong? ♪
♪ Is there a vision
That I can call my own? ♪
♪ Show me ♪
♪ I'm looking for a reason ♪
♪ Roaming through the night
To find my place in this world ♪
♪ My place in this world ♪
♪ Not a lot to lean on
I need your light ♪
♪ To help me find my place in this world ♪
♪ My place in this world ♪
♪ Looking for a reason ♪
♪ Roaming through the night
To find my place in this world ♪
♪ My place in this world ♪
♪ Not a lot to lean on ♪
♪ I need your light
To help me find my place in this world ♪
♪ My place in this world ♪
See?
I was right.
You're perfect.
So, um...
where do you live, again?
Y'know, after, after the summer?
Oh. Uh...
- I live in New York with my older brother.
- Hmm.
We're super close.
I'm really lucky to have him.
I thought you said you lived in Philly.
[siren blares]
Uh-oh! You are in trouble.
What do you mean?
[tense music playing]
[imitating LTC Kilgore] I love the smell
of paintball in the morning!
- Your dad is really into this.
- Yeah. Like father like daughter.
[man] This is sudden death!
The surviving team
wins the day!
Okay, David, you do realize
they're kids, right?
- I know.
- [Kristin] Okay.
Charlie! No more head shots.
And remember, watch your six.
Not the 666.
No, I was... The six is your back.
'Cause if you say twelve it would be...
I hope you know how to shoot that thing.
- Not the devil!
- No, this is not a Biblical term at all.
Okay. All right, gotcha.
[David] Move out!
- Move it!
- [Kristin] Jesus loves you!
Move it!
[Charlie] Slay 'em all!
- Charlie's really enthusiastic.
- Yeah, we've got to call his parents.
All right, Apostles, listen up.
It is beyond go time.
Now just go out there, okay,
and do your best.
Now, I believe in you.
This is our year, 'cause we have
something they don't have.
We have Will.
I want the new kid taken out first.
Understand?
Do you think they all know
what Apocalypse Now is?
I don't even know
what Apocalypse Now is, David.
- Now, what are we?
- [all] Red hot!
Sorry, I can't hear you. What?
[all] Verdes Maximus!
What are we gonna do?
- Destroy.
- Yes.
Now hands in!
Masks down.
On three. Um...
- [Will] After three
- After three. Yes. Thank you.
Green machine. One, two, three:
- [all cheering]
- Let's go!
[music playing]
♪ I don't know where you lay your head
Or where you call your home ♪
♪ I don't know where you eat your meals
Or where you talk on the phone ♪
♪ I don't know if you got a cook
A butler, or a maid ♪
♪ I don't know if you got a yard
Or a hammock in the shade ♪
Pull harder!
♪ I don't know if you've got
Some shelter or a place to hide ♪
♪ I don't know if you live with friends
In whom you can confide ♪
♪ I don't know if you got a family
And see your mom or dad ♪
♪ I don't know if you feel love at all
But I bet you wish you had ♪
- What are you doing?
- Go. Back.
- Not hard.
- ♪ Go with me to my father's house ♪
- I'm not even worried.
- ♪ Come go with me to my father's house ♪
♪ It's a big, big house
With lots and lots of room ♪
♪ A big, big table
With lots and lots of food ♪
♪ With a big, big yard
Where we can play football ♪
♪ A big, big house
It's my father's house ♪
- [boy] I'm open!
- [girl] Not anymore!
[David on PA] Somebody call heaven!
These Angels got wings!
[woman] ♪ All I know is a big old house
With rooms for everyone ♪
♪ All I know there's lots of land
Where we can play and run ♪
[man] ♪ All I know is that you need love
And I've got a family ♪
♪ All I know is you're all alone
So why not come with me? ♪
[both] ♪ Come and go with me
To my father's house ♪
♪ Come and go with me
♪ It's a big, big house
With lots and lots of room ♪
♪ A big, big table
With lots and lots of food ♪
♪ A big, big yard
Where we can play football ♪
♪ A big, big house
It's my father's house ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
[music continues]
Yay!
[David over PA] Oh, that's gotta hurt.
Points are adding up and it's
not looking good for the Apostles.
[singers vocalizing]
What are you doing? Get up!
George!
[paintball fire whooshing]
- [gasping]
- Wow.
That was the nicest/weirdest thing
anyone's ever done for me.
[chuckling] You're welcome, Georgie.
- Let's go.
- Paintball sucks.
- I know. [chuckles]
- [paintball gun firing]
[Kristin] Charlie!
I will come after you
with the wrath of God!
- I'm not playing, Charlie!
- Hey, hey.
What?
You do realize they're children,
don't you?
[Kristin] Charlie!
[puffing]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [paintballs rattling]
- [grunts]
[automatic paintball fire]
[grunts]
You're going down. Three.
Two.
One!
[rapid paintball firing]
- Huh!
- Whoa!
- Why aren't you shooting me?
We're surrounded. If we reload
and shoot each other then Sean wins.
Okay. What are you proposing?
Temporary truce?
Okay.
Let's Mr. and Mrs. Smith this thing.
Yes! Yes!
What is that again?
What? Y'know, it's like a movie.
Like Mr... No?
- Just follow my lead, okay?
- Yeah, here you go.
No, Will, that's yours too.
You're gonna shoot both.
- Oh!
- Okay.
[Sean] We got 'em, Apostles.
On the count of three. One, two, three!
[intense music playing]
[groans]
Hey! Ow! Ow!
Ow! That is so against the rules!
- [both chuckle]
- [firing]
Ow! Stop! I'm down!
- Ow!
- Wow. That is so wrong.
- Aww.
I told you, Will, I'm competitive.
Excuse me boys.
That's it! Crimson Angels are the winner!
- [Crimsons cheer]
- Looks like we're both losers today.
Just go.
Part of me is proud,
and part of me is neutral.
I think we got a barn burner!
Verdes Maximus is in second place!
[Kristin] That's my baby!
He came from my womb.
And in third place just a couple
of points down the Azure Apostles.
Oh, no, no. This doesn't happen.
Third place!
I pray. I give blood. What is happening?
I'm an Apostle. I went to the Arctic
and I spent two months
freezing my buttocks off
to come back here and we lose.
We lose to some guy,
George's cousin. Who is that guy?
Hello, Mr. Godzilla. That looks like
a tasty Twizzler you have in your mouth.
- [roaring]
- Oh! Thank you so much.
I'm going to keep this Twizzler.
♪ We're jamming bros ♪
[Will vocalizing]
♪ Oh yeah with the C chord
To the A minor chord with the G chord ♪
♪ Camp Aweegaway ♪
♪ We're at camp Aweegaway ♪
[belching] You win.
♪ Aweegaway! ♪
- We suck!
- Why can't we? Why are we so bad at this?
♪ Aweegaway! ♪
[vocalizing]
- [belching] Finished it.
- Oh wow, I'm ashamed.
Life moves pretty fast.
If you don't stop and look around
once in a while,
you could miss it.
- So good.
- Dude, it's a classic.
[Will] You know?
This camp thing's not that bad.
[George] You ain't seen nothing yet.
[Kristin] I just have
one simple thing to say.
I don't know all of you...
certainly not as well as I'd like to.
But God does.
He knows everything about each
and every one of you here tonight.
I don't know much, but this much I do.
He's a fan.
Ahem! Uh...
I don't know much.
But I...
- Err... uh...
- But this much I do.
Seeing George hit that superman pose
trying to save a certain someone.
That was, uh...
That was pretty cool, man.
That was pretty cool.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Well, I don't know much,
but this much I do.
This is the last week of our 24th summer
here at Camp Aweegaway.
As my wife used to say,
God is up to something.
He's up to something good.
He's up to something amazing.
That much I know.
Ah...
I've repeated this
quite a few times to myself.
And um...
These words just mean a lot to me,
so I thought why not share them.
"For I know the plans that I have
in store for you declares the Lord...
plans to prosper you...
not to harm you...
plans to give you a hope...
and a future."
I don't know much.
But this much I do.
♪ Our God is an awesome God ♪
♪ He reigns from heaven above ♪
♪ With wisdom, power and love ♪
♪ Our God is an awesome God ♪
♪ Our God is an awesome God
He reigns from heaven above ♪
♪ With wisdom, power and love ♪
♪ Our God is an awesome God ♪
♪ He reigns from heaven above ♪
♪ With wisdom, power and love
Our God is an awesome God ♪
♪ Our God is an awesome God
He reigns from heaven above ♪
♪ With wisdom, power and love
Our God is an awesome God ♪
♪ Wide awake while the world
Is sound asleeping ♪
♪ Too afraid of what might show up
While you're dreaming ♪
♪ Nobody, nobody, nobody sees you ♪
♪ Nobody, nobody would believe you ♪
♪ Every day
You try to pick up all the pieces ♪
♪ All the memories
They somehow never leave you ♪
♪ Nobody, nobody, nobody sees you ♪
♪ Nobody, nobody would believe you ♪
♪ God only knows
What you've been through ♪
♪ God only knows what they say about you ♪
♪ God only knows how it's killing you
Is there a kinda love that... ♪
[all] ♪ Our God... ♪
♪ God only knows
What you've been through ♪
♪ God only knows what they say about you ♪
♪ God only knows how it's killing you ♪
♪ Is there a kinda love
That God only knows? ♪
♪ God only knows
What you've been through ♪
♪ God only knows what they say about you ♪
♪ God only knows the real you ♪
♪ Is there a kinda love
That God only knows? ♪
[all] ♪ Our God is an awesome God
He reigns from heaven above ♪
♪ With wisdom, power, and love ♪
♪ Our God is an awesome God ♪
That was really cool
what you said about George, I thought.
I think Presley liked it too
I mean, she loved it.
Hey, um... How are y...
How are you feeling about all that?
Because I know it can be...
overwhelming.
It was amazing.
Really?
I don't know.
It's just...
been so long
since I felt so...
connected.
Like I was part of something bigger.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah, I really do.
- Avery.
- Will.
- Sorry.
- Go head.
Just, can you wait just like two seconds?
I have something for you.
- Oh yeah, sure.
- But just two seconds, okay?
Sorry.
[gentle music playing]
Come on, just tell her the truth.
I, um...
I just wanted you to have this photo.
You don't have to keep it if it's weird.
I just, um...
I don't know, it's a good picture.
Avery, I...
Yeah?
Thank you.
Yeah, it's no problem.
- So, I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah, see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Okay.
Goodnight.
[chattering]
- Oh, hey, Kristin.
- Hey, Will.
Hey, lover boy. How's Avery?
She gave me this.
Aww.
Man, I look good in this.
Mind if I steal it?
Yeah, I do. [chuckles]
[George laughs]
[Kristin] Oh, Will, this is yours.
Thanks.
Oh, wow, are those your parents?
That's them.
Can I see?
Sure.
[Kristin laughs]
- You look just like your dad.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- You got a lot of peach fuzz though.
- Peach fuzz? [chuckles]
Will, your mother is beautiful.
She really is.
You know, your parents
would be really proud of you.
They'd be glad I was here.
[gentle guitar playing]
I just thought the moment needed
a heartfelt score, it was so tender.
Nice, George.
You know what would be heartfelt?
If you picked up your drawers.
[George] Mom.
Come on, I just wore them.
Do you expect me
to clean my room at camp?
- [Kristin] Why does it smell so bad?
- [George] Boys only.
[Kristin] That boy stink
that just sticks on you.
[George] They smell like old people.
[Kristin] I can smell your shorts.
How long you been wearing them?
[George] They were pants.
[door creaking]
[papers rustling]
[drawers opening]
[exhales]
[whispering] Gotcha.
No way.
[chuckles softly]
- [reveille playing]
- [David] All right, campers,
now for a Warrior Games update.
In first place the Azure Apostles.
In second the Angels,
and finally Verdes Maximus
coming in third.
Now, don't despair,
I have it from authority on high
that the talent show tonight
is gonna be a game changer.
So warm up those juggling balls,
polish off those tap shoes,
and let's make some magic!
All right,
my fellow Verdes Maximus monsters,
today is the day and if we all do our jobs
I think tears will be shed,
jaws will be dropped,
- and heartstrings will be tugged.
- [all chuckling]
We didn't come this far to be just okay.
- We must be...
- Epic.
- What he said.
- [chuckles]
Let's give it up for our fearless leader
who put this nonsense together, huh?
Okay, we're a team. But, yes,
as the leader I appreciate the validation.
[Will] Let's get started.
I am excited.
It'll be nice to have
some decent talent show competition.
- Yeah, this is a closed rehearsal, Sean.
- I'm aware.
I heard the new kid would be playing
a big part in this year's performance.
So I wanted to stop by
and offer a few pointers.
Will, got a minute?
- No, we have to rehearse.
- It's fine.
Sean, if this is about paintball,
I'm sorry, I just...
Hey, you're good. You're good.
You can't change who you are.
I get it.
What's that supposed to mean?
Like, who you really are.
Will Hawkins.
Vandalism,
disorderly conduct, curfew violations.
Auto theft?
You lied.
You're just a big fraud.
And you need to tell Avery.
Or I'm going to.
Look.
I'm trying to do the right thing.
Yeah.
Sure you are.
Keep up the good work.
Hey.
- Uh, hey. Hi, George.
- Okay.
Have you guys seen Will?
- Why? What's up?
- I don't know.
We were trying to rehearse,
Sean walked in, said something to him
and then Will just walked out.
W-wait, Sean? What did Sean say?
I have no idea.
All right, let's go find out.
- [groans]
- [Avery] Come on.
[door opening]
[Sean] I don't want to tell you this.
Will isn't who he says he is.
What are you talking about?
Ask his cousin.
[Sean] Six years, seven schools,
twenty-two homes.
You can't change who you are. I get it.
[Kristin]
Your parent s would be proud of you.
[Sean] Vandalism, disorderly conduct.
I don't know if she'd be into
the whole stealing a cop car.
[Avery] I just choose to believe.
I mean, that's faith, right?
[Sean] You're just a big fraud.
I'm sorry, but that's the truth.
He's lying to you.
You've gotta believe me.
You're so brave.
Hm!
[Will] Always have an exit plan.
[intense music plays]
Will.
- Dad! Hi!
- Hi, sweetie.
- Uh, can I have your keys?
- Where are you going?
Sean, I guess said something to Will.
I don't know what he said.
All I know is I checked his cabin.
All of his things are gone, he's gone.
- Well, I'll go look for him.
- No, no.
I need to go.
I think he was trying to say
something to me the other day
or I don't know, but if I go
I think he'll listen to me.
Please, you have to trust me.
[intense music continues]
[Avery] Will.
Will.
Will come on, please, where are you going?
Look, I...
I know everything, okay?
Or at least I know some of it.
None of it matters,
so can you please get in the car?
- We can talk about it.
- There's nothing to talk about.
So do you just run away?
- Is that you? Is that the real Will?
- I don't have anybody, Avery.
I don't have a dad to take care of me
or a little magical garden.
That was not fair.
Yeah, you're right. It's not.
It's not fairthat my parents
were ripped from me.
[voice breaks] That I didn't get
to tell them just once more...
You don't know anything about me.
So don't pretend you do or that you care.
Why do you think I'm standing here now?
- I don't know, you tell me.
- Because I care.
- Because you are so loved.
- By whom? God?
Yes!
Then where was he? Where was he?
He didn't take me that night, no.
He left me there.
He wasn't there for me that night,
hasn't been there since.
What kind of a God is that?
Tell me.
But you know what?
It's fine. I'm fine. Okay?
You're not gonna believe me right now,
when I say this to you but I need you to...
I don't need you to fix me, Avery.
- I'm not trying to fix you, Will.
- Yeah, right.
Fine, then you look at me right now.
- Tell me none of this meant anything.
- Get out of my way.
I can't. Because you can't look at me
and you can't say it.
- Because you know it's not true.
- It meant nothing to me.
What?
None of it.
Can I go now.
[sniffles]
[sighing]
Yeah, you can go now.
By the way, you aren't
as good of a liar as you think you are.
[sighs]
[soft music playing]
[engine starts]
♪ I've spent so long hurting ♪
♪ Lying came so naturally ♪
♪ The truth hurts and the truth is ♪
♪ I was only hurting me ♪
♪ Gotta turn around
Gotta do this now ♪
♪ 'Cause I think I know ♪
♪ This is where I belong ♪
♪ It seems like forever
I've been searching ♪
♪ Like I've known all along ♪
♪ Love is the answer
In a sea of questions ♪
♪ All my worry is gone ♪
♪ This is where I belong ♪
♪ I've held on so tight ♪
♪ Now you're holding on to me ♪
♪ For the first time in a long time ♪
♪ Something feels like home finally ♪
♪ Standing here now ♪
♪ So sure I know ♪
♪ This is where I belong ♪
♪ Seems like forever I've been searching ♪
♪ Like I've known all along ♪
♪ Love is the answer
In a sea of questions ♪
♪ All my worry is gone ♪
♪ This is where ♪
♪ This is where I belong ♪
[David] Welcome to the talent show!
[cheering]
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, oh, oh ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Yeah ♪
[David] Wow!
Kristin, I'm looking at the numbers
and with that performance
the Azure Apostles take a commanding lead.
- [campers cheering]
- Ahh! Yes!
We're dead.
You tried your best, okay?
It's gonna be fine.
We're gonna have fun, okay?
I know.
Did you find him?
Yeah.
- Yeah, no, I found him.
- Wait, what's going on? Are you okay?
- [Presley] She. George, she, um...
- I tried.
I don't think he's coming back.
But it's not over yet!
We have our final performance,
Verdes Maximus!
[campers cheering]
Yeah, that's my baby George.
And this should be epic!
- Go get 'em.
- Thanks, Mom.
[sighing]
[Will] I lied.
What?
It meant everything.
All of it.
Thank for coming after me.
Thank you for coming back.
I'm just... I'm so sorry that...
[gentle, romantic music playing]
[chuckling]
Your fans await.
- We'll talk after, okay?
- Okay.
[band begins playing]
- You have to go.
- Okay.
Go! [chuckles]
[sniffles]
[music starts playing]
♪ I never imagined I would be here ♪
♪ I couldn't have planned it
Couldn't have worked it out ♪
♪ I didn't believe it when I said it ♪
♪ Everything's about to change ♪
♪ And now I'm facing all of my fears ♪
♪ Ain't nothing gonna keep me down ♪
♪ A little love is all I needed ♪
♪ Never gonna be the same ♪
♪ Right, right, right where I wanna be ♪
♪ I-I-I don't ever wanna leave ♪
♪ There's nothing better ♪
♪ We're feeling alright ♪
♪ Dancing to the beat
Of the time of our lives ♪
♪ Together ♪
- Hey!
- ♪ This is the best thing ever ♪
♪ There's nothing better ♪
♪ We're out in the light ♪
♪ Moving to the rhythm
Of the time of our lives ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ This is the best thing ever ♪
♪ Under these stars
God's love shines down ♪
♪ No skies have ever been so clear ♪
♪ This is what life is all about ♪
♪ I found myself right here ♪
♪ There's nothing better ♪
♪ We're feeling all right ♪
♪ Dancing to the beat
Of the time of our lives ♪
♪ Together ♪
- Hey!
- ♪ This is the best thing ever ♪
♪ There's nothing better
We're out in the light ♪
♪ Moving to the rhythm
Of the time of our lives ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ This is the best thing ever ♪
[campers cheering]
[both laughing]
[campers whooping]
This has been a week of fierce
competition right up to the very end.
I want to say
that I'm proud of all of you.
But in the end, Kristin,
only one team can reign supreme,
and who is it tonight?
Verdes Maximus!
[campers cheering]
It's all right. It's all right.
[campers chanting]
Verde! Verde! Verde!
[Will and George] Good morning, campers.
It's a beautiful sunny day.
Everybody up. Everybody moving.
[David over PA]
Time to get this party grooving.
- [vocalizing]
- It was a week unlike any other.
Today you take home friendships
that will last a lifetime.
Remember that today is not goodbye,
it's see you later.
Go out in the world,
the great big awesome world
and make some magic.
[Sean] I want to say congratulations.
- You killed it.
- [chuckles]
Thanks, man. It means a lot.
You deserve it.
You can do this.
- Can I talk to you?
- Yeah, what's up?
[sighs]
Man, I just...
just want to say I'm sorry.
You weren't the only one
trying to impress people.
Dude, don't even worry about it.
We're cool.
[both chuckle]
Yeah, but next year you're going down.
Ahh, we'll see about that.
[both chuckle]
- [singing] ♪ Later ♪
- See you, buddy.
- Hey, you.
- Hey, mind if I sit here?
Please.
So...
are you coming back next year or what?
Hmm, well, that depends.
Will you be here?
Yes.
Then chances are pretty good.
[both chuckle]
Hi.
Hey.
Uh... Uhh...
I-I-I, um...
Here.
[gasping] Oh!
[chuckles]
It's beautiful, George.
Um, yeah, the-there are
365 letters in there for you.
Um, I kinda wrote them last year
but I think thematically they could...
I'm sorry.
[chuckles nervously]
It's just, um...
"Life moves pretty fast.
If you don't stop and look around
once in a while you could miss it!"
From my favorite movie,
[both] Ferris Bueller's Day Off.
Wow, someday I'm gonna marry you
Presley Elizabeth Borsky.
Not if I marry you first
George Montgomery Tanella.
[both chuckling]
Here.
See ya.
She gave me her number.
[chuckling] She gave me her number, I...
Jeez. Should I, like, emoji her?
Is that a thing?
[George] So what happens next?
[Will] I don't know.
Figure out my next move.
- I'm gonna miss you, man.
- I'm gonna miss you too.
All right. You boys ready to go home?
What do you mean?
Will, I'd really like for you
to come home and live with us.
I mean, If you want.
- Are you serious?
- So, we're like legit cousins now?
[Kristin] No.
You're brothers.
Yes!
- [Kristin laughing]
- Yes! Thank you.
Oh my gosh! Thank you so much.
[rhythmic music playing]
♪ Oh, I've finally found a place
To be me ♪
♪ I finally know
I'm more than good enough ♪
♪ Baby, there was never a doubt about it ♪
[all] ♪ Everything's about to change ♪
♪ I had to let it go and just be ♪
♪ God only knows that makes two of us ♪
[both] ♪ Just a little bit of love
Is all we needed ♪
[all] ♪ We're never gonna be the same ♪
♪ Right, right, right where I wanna be ♪
♪ I-I-I don't ever wanna leave ♪
♪ There's nothing, there's nothing ♪
♪ There's nothing better ♪
♪ We're feeling all right ♪
♪ Dancing to the beat
Of the time of our lives ♪
- ♪ Together ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ This is the best thing
This is the best thing ever! ♪
♪ There's nothing better
We're out in the light ♪
♪ Moving to the rhythm
Of the time of our lives ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ This is the best thing ever!
Hey! ♪
- [vocalizing]
- ♪ This is the best! ♪
♪ This is the best! ♪
♪ The best thing ever! ♪
On your mark. Oh! Ow!
[rock music playing]
[inaudible]
I hope we are adding a blooper reel.
Okay?
♪ I don't know where you lay your head
Or where you call your home ♪
♪ I don't know where you eat your meals
Or where you talk on the phone ♪
♪ I don't know if you got a cook
A butler, or a maid ♪
♪ I don't know if you got a yard
Or a hammock in the shade ♪
- Dude? [laughs]
- Bro? Okay.
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ I don't know if you got some shelter
Or a place to hide ♪
♪ I don't know if you live with friends
In whom you can confide ♪
♪ I don't know if you got a family
And see your mom or dad ♪
♪ I don't know if you feel love at all
But I bet you wish you had ♪
[all] ♪ Come and go with me
To my father's house ♪
♪ Come and go with me
♪ It's a big, big house
With lots and lots of room ♪
♪ A big, big table
With lots and lots of food ♪
♪ With a big, big yard
Where we can play football ♪
♪ Touchdown! ♪
♪ A big, big house
It's my father's house ♪
No, it's Aweegaway. Like you all
take a week out of your...
No, it's a... One second.
[cheering]
[laughing, chattering inaudibly]
And bonus, one, two.
Hike!
[man] Play ball!
That wasn't too bad.
Now I'll do it again.
Hike!
[laughing]
[man] Wow!
♪ All I know it's a big old house
With rooms for everyone ♪
♪ All I know is lots of land
So we can play and run ♪
♪ All I know is that you need love
And I've got a family ♪
♪ All I know is you're all alone
So why not come with me? ♪
[all] ♪ Come and go with me
To my father's house ♪
♪ Come and go with me
♪ It's a big, big house
With lots and lots of room ♪
♪ A big, big table
With lots and lots of food ♪
♪ A big, big yard
Where we can play football ♪
♪ Touchdown! ♪
♪ A big, big house
It's my father's house ♪
- Let's go.
- [Avery laughing] Wait for me.
- These are both yours.
- Oh, okay.
[Avery] They're both yours. Tighter.
[both laughing]
- This is not it.
- [Will] The first half was good.
- The first half was good.
- It probably won't make the film.
Yes! I'm now in a dance musical movie.
I can't believe it.
[Avery laughing]
- Do you want me to spit it out?
- You should.
So unprofessional, Katherine.
[laughing]
Steady!
Steady! Camera operator!
I always am on the blob.
Yes, Sean. It's 'cause I love it.
That's not part of the script.
Might cut around it.
[vocalizing]
- [squeals] Presley!
- It was my best take!
- Get inside!
- That was my best take!
♪ ...to my father's house ♪
Get inside! That was my Oscar!
♪ ...with lots and lots of room ♪
Sean being a major creep, take one.
♪ With lots and lots of room ♪
I look terrible.
[cheering]
♪ A big, big house
It's my father's house ♪
♪ It's a big, big house
With lots and lots of room ♪
♪ A big, big table
With lots and lots of food ♪
♪ It's a big, big yard
Where we can play football ♪
♪ A big, big house
It's my father's house ♪
She's a classic.
- [sighs]
- That's a word for it.
[banging]
[sighs]
- [door grinding]
- [crew laughing]
Can we start again?
["Best Thing Ever" playing]
♪ Oh, I've finally found a place
To be me ♪
♪ I finally know
I'm more than good enough ♪
♪ Baby, baby
There was never a doubt about it ♪
♪ Everything's about to change ♪
♪ I had to let it go and just be ♪
♪ God only knows that makes two of us ♪
♪ Just a little bit of love
Is all we needed ♪
♪ We're never gonna be the same ♪
♪ Right, right, right where I wanna be ♪
♪ I-I-I don't ever wanna leave ♪
- ♪ I-I-I don't ever wanna leave ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ There's nothing, there's nothing ♪
- ♪Yeah ♪
♪ There's nothing better ♪
♪ We're feeling all right ♪
♪ Dancing to the beat
Of the time of our lives ♪
♪ Together ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ This is the best thing ever! ♪
♪ There's nothing better ♪
♪ We're feeling all right ♪
♪ Dancing to the beat
Of the time of our lives ♪
♪ Together ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ Let's go! ♪
- ♪ This is the best thing ever! ♪
♪ There's nothing better ♪
♪ We're out in the light ♪
♪ Moving to the rhythm
Of the time of our lives ♪
- ♪ Of our lives ♪
- [vocalizing]
♪ This is the best thing ever! ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- [vocalizing]
- ♪ This is the best! ♪
♪ This is the best! ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ The best thing ever! ♪