[foreboding music]
- [Doctor] Tell me what
you're seeing right now.
[sinister music]
[girl screams]
[man groans]
Alice?
What are you seeing now, Alice?
- Tracy!
[girl giggles]
Tracy!
Don't you ever run
away from me like that!
Where did you think
you were going?
- We're going up, huh?
- Yeah!
[ominous music]
- I know. Can I push it?
Can I do it?
- Sure!
- [Man] Hit the
top button, honey.
- I can't reach it.
- Oh, here we go. Ready?
Up!
Ooh, good work.
- And then what?
What are you seeing?
You have to try and tell me.
[man groans]
[girl screams]
- Please! Please
don't hurt my baby!
Please, do what ever you want
to me, but don't hurt my baby.
[girl screams]
[girl squeals]
- Please try.
Try and tell me.
- Up!
Ooh, good work.
Oopsie daisy. Oh!
- Do you live on the 13th floor?
I didn't think they used 13.
- Oh, that was in the old days.
We're not superstitious
anymore, are we, pumpkin?
- No, not me. I'm
not superstitious.
- You're not?
[Alice laughs]
- What else do you see, Alice?
Tell me.
[bell chimes]
[ominous music]
- Oh, god.
Oh, god!
Tracy?
Tracy!
Oh, Jesus!
Oh my god! Tracy!
Tracy! [screams]
Oh, Tracy!
Oh, Tracy.
Tracy.
[machinery whirring]
Tracy?
Oh my god. [gasps]
[Alice screams]
Oh god!
- [Doctor] Try and tell me.
- [sighs] Nothing.
- Well.
[pen scribbles]
Fine.
That was good. It was very good.
You did very well.
Mint.
And just suck on it, don't chew.
Yes, we're proceeding very well.
We'll have you out
of here in no time.
[pensive music]
- How much longer do you
think she'll be here?
- It's really difficult to tell.
Maybe a matter of weeks,
or it may be a considerably
longer period of time.
- Maybe somebody else can do
a lot more for her, Doctor.
She's been here four months.
- I understand your frustration.
- [Victor] Jesus
Christ, look at her.
Isn't there something we
can do? Give her something?
- [Doctor] I have her
on a mild sedative.
- I want my wife back.
Understand me? I...
I want my wife back.
- Dr. Meltzner?
There's a police
officer to see you.
He's waiting in your office.
He's asking about Mrs. Lundgren.
- The police? What the
hell are they doing here?
- Tell them I'll be
right there, okay?
- Now, I told you
nobody, nobody,
was to come near
my wife but you.
Her health's the only
thing that matters to me,
not the goddamn police.
- Mr. Lundgren. Mr. Lundgren!
- What?
- I agree with you.
Now, I will handle this.
- Well, then you go handle it.
- I will. Please
wait for me here.
I'll be right back. Please?
[pensive music]
- God.
[Victor sobs]
- What do you
think you're doing?
- I'm Detective Kurt Williams,
Ravenwood County Homicide.
- You don't look much
like a policeman.
- Yeah, well, I do a
lot of undercover work.
Well, what I need from you
is an introduction to
one of your patients.
Alice Lundgren.
- Out of the question.
- You're not gonna make me
get a court order on this,
are you, Doctor?
- I've already been through this
with several members of
the police department.
Her condition is unstable.
I won't allow it.
Good afternoon,
Officer Williams.
- I'll be back.
[pensive music]
[soft music]
- Tracy?
Tracy?
[suspenseful music]
Don't go.
Don't leave me, Tra...
[Alice whimpers]
[sobs] Oh, Tracy.
[suspenseful music]
- Could you leave us?
[pensive music]
[haunting music]
- So then the cop says,
"Lady, do you know how
fast you were going?"
And I said,
"No, the speedometer only
goes to 120." [laughs]
So what do you do
in here at night?
Are there any cute patients?
Remember Brad?
He started for SC?
I'm seeing him again.
He asked how you were doing.
We're going to Palm
Springs this weekend.
[wistful music]
Alice, do I have to have this
conversation all by myself?
- I gotta get out
of here, Kathy.
- What?
- They're driving me crazy.
- Oh, Alice.
I'm sure they're gonna
let you go home soon.
I'm just so glad you've
finally realized that-
- I want out, Kathy.
I want out now.
- But Alice, that's
not how it works.
- I'm a prisoner in here.
- You're not a prisoner.
You're a patient.
Alice, please tell me the truth.
Are you still seeing Tracy?
- I saw her again
two nights ago.
- Alice.
Tracy is dead.
They're not gonna
let you go home
until you come to
terms with reality.
I'm sorry, but that's
just the way it is.
You're not going
to be here forever.
As soon as you get better
they'll let you go home.
I promise.
[suspenseful music]
As soon as you get better,
they'll let you go home.
Alice.
Alice!
[haunting music]
Now, this will make
you feel much better.
- Kathy?
- Now, this will make
you feel much better.
Tracy?
No.
[ominous music]
No!
Damn! Damn!
No, it's not real.
No.
Tracy.
- Alice, I can't
let you go home yet.
You're not well. You're
still delusionary.
- Not anymore. I'm fine.
I haven't seen Tracy
for two weeks now.
- When a loved one dies, it is
perfectly natural to grieve.
Now, you're denying your grief.
This is why you keep
having these visions.
- The visions are over.
I know Tracy is dead. I
know I won't see her again.
- Well.
I'm very glad to hear you
say that. It's a good sign.
But I still think it would
be in your best interest
for you to stay here with us
until we're sure that
you've completely recovered.
- I am recovered.
If you want to keep me
here against my will,
you need a court order.
So either put me
in front of a judge
or let me go because I want out.
- I'll tell you what.
I'll be happy to
initiate the paperwork
as soon as I've consulted
with your husband.
- It's not his
decision, it's mine!
I want to see release forms
here tomorrow afternoon.
- Alice, you don't understand.
It's more complicated than that.
The forms will take at
least a week to process.
- Then you have a week, no more.
- Charlie, I know we
bought the building.
Now I want to buy
the company. Right.
All right, I gotta go.
Yeah, Victor here.
No, that's good, 90.
Sell at 90, right.
And don't forget to
earmark 50% of the profits
for the children's
hospital, all right?
Great.
Yeah, Bev?
No, no, put him through.
Hello?
- Mr. Lundgren?
Your wife would
like to leave us.
She's aware of her rights
and is quite insistent.
- But I thought she was
still having hallucinations.
- [Meltzner] Well, she
maintains that she no longer is.
- [Victor] Really?
Well, that's wonderful.
- We could keep her here for
further observation if you'd-
- Oh, no, I don't
think that's necessary.
If she says she wants to
come, then let her come home.
That's great. Oh, Doctor?
Do me a favor. Give her my love.
- [Meltzner] Fine. Thank you.
- Right. Thank you.
Yeah.
- Alice, these are beautiful.
"Love, Victor." How nice!
So what's with
the fitness craze?
- I want my body to be in
as good shape as my mind
when I get out of here.
- Oh, you look great.
And you sound terrific.
So what the hell happened?
- What do you mean,
"What the hell happened?"
- It's just that the
last time I was here
you were still kind of...
You know.
- Crazy?
Is that what you want to say?
- No!
- Were you beginning
to like the idea
of having a crazy sister?
- No! Of course not.
- Good. Because I'm not crazy.
Not anymore.
If I ever was.
- Good.
So, uh...
Oh, a cop has come by my place
several times asking questions.
- [Alice] Really?
What'd he want to know?
- Well...
Of course, anything about the...
- It's okay, Kathy. "Murder"
is the word you're looking for.
- Well, he also wanted to
know everything about you,
especially about you and Victor.
I told him everything
is a lot better
now that the divorce is on hold.
- Why'd you tell him that?
- Well, it is, isn't it?
Well, just remember, if
Kurt comes by to see you,
technically speaking, you're
still a married woman.
- Kurt?
- The cop. Kurt Williams.
- Cop Kurt, huh?
[Alice laughs]
- No, that shouldn't
be a problem.
[knock at door]
Come in.
Uh, can I call you
back? Thank you.
Alice.
- I'm ready.
- I can see. You look great.
Sit down.
- I prefer to stand.
- Well.
In that case...
Before I sign this,
I have to make
sure you understand
the conditions of the release.
- Oh, I know, I know.
In two weeks my case
will be reviewed
by the psychiatric review board,
at which time it
will be determined
whether my release
will be permanent
or if I have to return for
further inpatient therapy.
Don't worry, I'm not
planning on coming back, Doc.
- Good.
Well, I guess that's
just about it then.
I do have a little
something for you though.
Kind of a going away present.
- You're so
sentimental. What is it?
- Just a mild sedative.
In case you start
getting to feel edgy.
- Peace of mind in
a bottle, eh, Doc?
- Well, let's call it
a little insurance.
As much as I've loved
having you around here,
I really don't want
to see you come back.
- Agreed.
- Well.
That's it.
- Okay.
- We're done.
Take care, Alice. Be well.
- I will. Can't say
it's been a pleasure.
[soft music]
Tracy? Mommy's coming home.
[suspenseful music]
- I gotta know
everything you know.
[wistful music]
[soft music]
[neon crackles]
Hello, Mr. Bear.
[Alice sobs]
God.
[Alice sighs]
Oh, Tracy.
- "Kabuki killer takes a break."
Fat chance, huh, guys?
Yeah. Okay, just a little bit.
You gotta be up early.
[suspenseful music]
- [Man] Mrs. Lundgren?
- What?
Who is that?
- Uh, my name's Kurt Williams.
Um, detective.
Ravenswood County Homicide.
- You're a cop?
- Some people seem
to think so, ma'am.
- Do you usually break
into people's homes?
- Well, no ma'am, but I knocked
and the door swing open.
I identified myself and called
out, but nobody responded,
so I figured I'd
better take a look.
- Okay, you're here.
What do you want?
- Uh, you want me to
turn on the lights?
- When I'm ready.
- Okay. You mind if I
ask you a few questions?
Can you tell me anything about
the man who attacked you?
- Wait a minute. You're the
cop who talked to my sister?
- Yes ma'am, guilty.
- What can I tell you about the
bastard? He killed my child.
- But he didn't kill you.
And that makes you
very, very special.
- That makes me special?
- You're the only person who
survived the elevator attacks.
It's curious, isn't it? Kind
of makes you stop and think.
- Just catch the guy, okay?
- Listen, do you mind if I
turn on the lights in here?
- What's the matter,
Detective? Afraid of the dark?
- Depends on who's
in the dark with me.
At the time of the attack,
your husband and
you were separated.
And you'd filed for
divorce, is that correct?
How'd he feel about that?
- I don't know, you'll
have to ask him.
- I've tried asking him.
He wouldn't talk to me.
Would you consider your
husband a jealous man?
- Are you suggesting my husband
had something to do
with these murders?
- No, no-
- You think my husband
could murder our daughter?
- I didn't say that, ma'am.
- Look at that.
Can you see that?
That's a picture of a
man and his daughter.
A daughter he loved more
than anything in this world.
Tracy was burned
alive, for God's sakes.
- It's okay.
I know you must be
in a lot of pain.
- Get out of here. I
want you out of my house.
- If you can just let
me explain what I need.
- Leave, now!
- Okay, I'm leaving.
I'm terribly sorry if I upset
you in any way, Mrs. Lundgren.
Good evening.
- Alice?
Hey, what are you doing in
the dark, farming mushrooms?
- Talking to your cop.
Didn't you see him?
He was just here.
- I guess I just missed him.
My cop, in the dark?
Now, that's a bit kinky.
So what did he want from you?
- Oh, it was just all these
dumb personal questions.
I've been through this all
before. I'd hoped it was over.
I don't know. It's okay.
- Well, good!
Now I want you to put on some
makeup and get ready to go.
- Go? Where?
- Out to dinner, you nut.
We are going to
celebrate your new job.
Well, actually,
your job interview,
but with your resume,
you're sure to get it.
- What are you talking
about? What job interview?
- At Wexler Burns. The PR firm?
I set up an interview for
you tomorrow at eight.
- Wait a minute, tomorrow?
- Yeah. Can we
have some wine now?
[both laugh]
[foreboding music]
- What are you...
[woman squeals]
Let go of me! Help me!
[woman screaming]
[ominous music]
- Whatever, let's just have
some dinner, all right?
- [Alice] All right,
you convinced me.
- Great.
Now, I know a nice little
place right by Victor's condo.
Let's see if he'll join us.
- No, Kathy.
- Alice, he's dying to see you.
- No. I mean it.
- You're not still
planning to go through
with this divorce, are you?
Not now?
- Yes, I am.
- But after everything that's
happened, how could you?
- Nothing has happened
to make me change my mind
about being married to Victor.
- Alice.
I don't think you know
how lucky you are.
Victor really loves you.
- I know, but that's
not a good enough reason
to stay married.
I don't love him.
Not anymore.
- But...
He misses Tracy so much.
Victor's never lost
anything before.
If he loses you too
it'll just kill him.
- Being married to Victor
won't bring Tracy back.
- It's just that...
[soft music]
I miss her too.
That's why I...
I couldn't put away
the things in her room.
I don't know, I...
I tried.
But it was...
It was worse than the funeral.
It was like killing
her all over again.
I'm sorry.
- Shh, shh.
It's okay.
That's something for me to
do. You've been wonderful.
Took care of the house.
You took care of me.
Really.
- Alice.
Victor has been more
help than you know.
- I know, Kathy, I know.
He means well, but...
Look, let's not talk about
it anymore, all right?
Come on.
Let's go out to dinner.
- Okay.
- [Kurt] They'll never
learn. Stupid people.
[suspenseful music]
- You coming, lady?
[Tracy giggles]
[man groans]
[Alice gasps]
[Tracy squeals]
- Excuse me.
I have this interview this
morning in the penthouse,
but I can't take the elevator
because I have a phobia.
- A what?
- A phobia.
- Phobia? Okay.
- Yes, and I was wondering
if I could walk up.
- Walk up to the penthouse?
Lady, that's 13 flights.
- Well, I know, but I was...
Well, won't you help me, please?
- Okay, okay, all right. I'll
walk up the stairs with you.
- Thank you.
[guard sighs]
- Here you go, lady.
Last stop, penthouse.
Ladies' foundations,
lingerie, and hosiery.
And heart attacks.
- Here, thanks.
- Oh, thank you.
You know, I never climbed
all the way up here before,
and I'll tell you, ain't never
gonna do it again either.
- Well, I appreciate
it. Thank you.
- I'm taking the elevator down.
- Hi, I'm Alice Lundgren.
I'm here for my interview.
- [Receptionist]
Please, have a seat.
[workers chatting]
Would you like some coffee?
- Um, sure. Thank you.
Kathy? Good news.
I start tomorrow.
Yeah, I got it.
[doorbell rings]
Could you hold on a second?
Someone's at the door.
Actually, I'll call
you back, all right?
Great, thanks. Bye.
Coming!
Victor.
- Alice.
- You're not
supposed to be here.
- I know, I know, it's
just, uh... [sighs]
Christ, Alice, I miss you.
- Well, that's
nice of you to say,
but I'm not ready
to see you yet.
- You sure? I mean, don't
you want to invite me in?
[laughs] Come on.
- Look, I'm sorry. I'm
really busy right now.
I start a new job tomorrow.
- I know.
- Oh.
Damn you.
Damn you, Victor! I
don't need your help!
- Alice, the first thing
the psychiatric review board
is gonna look at is whether or
not you can hold down a job.
- And you don't
think I know that?
I planned on getting a job,
but I could've gotten one on
my own, without your help.
That's what I need right
now, to be on my own.
- Well, uh...
You're still my wife,
you understand that?
You're still my goddamn
wife and I'm your husband.
[suspenseful music]
[haunting music]
- Excuse me.
Excuse me, please.
Excuse me! I need to get off.
Pardon me!
Excuse me!
Tracy!
Come here! Tracy, come here!
[Alice screaming]
Oh, uh...
[guard panting]
Thanks again.
- Yeah.
But listen, just don't make
a habit out of it, okay?
I got more important
things to do.
- I'm sure you do.
I'll see if I can't get my boss
to make me up a key. Thanks.
[suspenseful music]
Tracy?
Hello? Tracy?
Tracy!
- Jill. You okay, honey?
Do you enjoy frightening
little girls?
- No, I'm sorry.
I thought she...
She looked like my little girl.
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
- I suppose there's
no harm done.
[bell chimes]
Come on, honey.
- Okay, I know we
promised you tomorrow.
Don't worry. We'll
have it by tomorrow.
Go over it again line by line
and see what you
can come up with.
- Reporting for
duty, Ms. Wilkes.
- Oh, please. Call me
Midge, everybody does.
- Okay, Midge.
- Welcome to Wexler Burns,
Alice. Glad you could join us.
- Thanks. It's nice to be here.
- Well, come on. I'll
give you the tour.
This is the reception area.
- Mm-hmm.
- This will be your office.
- Mm, that's nice.
- Mm.
Excuse my portable phone,
but I feel naked without it.
The restrooms are
way down at the end.
We're doing some
construction down there
to make way for a
new executive row.
Come on, let me show
you the media room.
Here we are. It's
state-of-the-art,
completely soundproof.
We use it for
viewing videotapes,
client meetings,
that kind of thing.
- Oh, it's great.
I love the artwork.
[phone rings]
- Excuse me a moment.
Sure.
- Yes?
Hi, Jim.
Of course I know how
important this is to you.
In fact, we've hired a new
writer to handle the overflow.
Right. Well, I'll have
to find that for you.
Can you hold on a second?
Come on.
We're working on a publicity
kit for a new horror movie
and I told the client we'd
have it finished by tomorrow.
- Is there anything I can do?
- Only about a million things.
Listen, take a
look at these bios.
See if you can condense
them to a paragraph each.
I'll join you in a
bit in your office.
- Okay, great.
- Jim? Yes, I've got
the file right here.
- Ah, the joys of employment.
[suspenseful music]
[workers catcalling]
[Alice laughs]
Cute, guys. Cute.
[suspenseful music]
- [Tracy] Mommy, Mommy?
Where are you, Mommy?
Mommy?
- Get ahold of yourself,
Alice. She's dead.
- [Tracy] Come to me, Mommy.
- Tracy?
Tracy, are you in there?
[yelps] Oh god, you scared me.
- I'm sorry, I didn't
mean to frighten you.
Are you, uh...
You must be the new girl.
- Huh? Oh!
Yes, I am. I was just looking
for the ladies room and...
- Oh. Well, this is it here.
We've been having so much
construction going here lately
that we've all been using this.
But don't go in here. That's
the construction area.
Someone keeps changing
the signs. As a joke.
I think it's one of the
secretaries, or the workmen.
- Yeah, probably.
- But don't worry, this
door locks from the inside.
- It's okay. I didn't need
it now anyway, actually.
I just wanted to know where
it was. You know, for later.
- I...
Sure.
- Yeah.
- Mrs. Lundgren?
I still gotta ask
you a few questions.
- Look, this is my
first day at a new job.
Can't you just leave
me alone, please?
- I'm very sorry to
disturb you. I really am.
I got no choice though.
I mean, couldn't
we talk over lunch?
- I don't think
so. I'm very busy.
- You gotta eat!
I mean, you know, we could
eat and we could talk
and I could cross my heart
that I'm not gonna ask
any cop questions and...
You know, nothing fancy.
[soft music]
- [Alice] So. You eat
on roofs very often?
- Well, as often as I can, yeah.
It's a nice way to
get away from people,
get some peace and quiet.
You got a lot of peace and
quiet in the hospital, I'll bet.
- If you can call being shot up
with Thorazine peace
and quiet, then yeah,
I had peace and
quiet, a lot of it.
- Why'd you come back
to work so quick?
I mean, you don't need the
money, that's for sure.
- I like to write.
You sound like my husband.
He never wanted me to work.
Wanted me to stay home and
be his good little girl.
- Uh, that maybe
have something to do
with your filing for divorce?
- Partly.
- Yeah.
What was his response?
- I thought you weren't
gonna ask any cop questions.
- I slipped. I
can't help myself.
I'm just a naturally
nosy person, you know?
But, I mean, I care about what
you've been going through.
I care about you. I
care a lot about you.
- Thanks.
- Well, so now that I've
slipped once already
and that we're
such close friends,
could I please just ask
one little cop question?
- All right, but get
it out of your system
because the next time
I answer questions
it's gonna take a lot more
than a deli sandwich
and a pickle.
- In the last year there
have been eight killings.
Did you know any of these people
or was there any connection
with the victims at all?
- None.
- [Kurt] You gonna finish
that pickle or what?
- Let's see, when does
he get in? Okay, good.
[Alice and Kurt laughing]
- I really gotta
get back to work.
- Okay. Thank you
very much for lunch.
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Goodbye.
- An interesting
man. Close friend?
- Not really.
- Listen, the cassette
on that film came in.
Take a look and give
me a two-page synopsis,
say, by five today?
- You got it.
- Okay.
[employees chatting]
- Anyone in there?
[suspenseful music]
[Alice moans]
- Hi, Mommy.
[Alice gasps]
[sighs] What's...
[door opens]
- Alice? Is everything okay?
I mean, are you all right?
- No. No, I'm fine.
- Hey!
- Don't touch that!
- Why not? It's mine.
- It's yours?
- Yes!
It was given to me at last
year's office Christmas party.
I lost it about a week ago,
but I didn't think
it was in here.
I know it's childish to
wear a charm bracelet,
but honey, I can all use
all the luck I can get.
You know, you really
should lock this door.
This is the only restroom
in the office right now.
Are you sure you're all right?
I mean, you look
awfully pale to me.
- I think it's just a case
of the first-day jitters.
I'll be fine as soon as I
get started, I'm sure of it.
In fact, I'm gonna look
at that tape right now.
- Okay.
[pills rattle]
[baby crying]
[suspenseful music]
[girl screams]
[baby cries]
[killer growls]
[girl screaming]
[killer roars]
[girl moaning]
- Oh, that bastard!
That bastard!
Police department. Get
me the police department.
Yes, it's an emergency!
Hello, I'd like to speak to
Detective Williams, please.
Kurt? It's Alice Lundgren.
Alice Lundgren.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Oh, I see. I'm sorry.
I must have the wrong
Detective Williams.
I was trying to get ahold
of Detective Kurt Williams.
Homicide.
What do you mean? There isn't?
Are you sure?
No, no, I'm fine.
I just must've gotten the
name wrong, that's all.
No, I'm sorry. Nevermind.
- Alice?
[haunting music]
Oh! Jesus.
God, what is happening to me?
- [Tracy] Don't cry, Mommy.
- No!
No, this isn't happening!
It's not happening!
- [Tracy] Please don't
cry. I'll take care of you.
[soft music]
[Alice laughs]
- Oh, honey.
Oh, Tracy.
Oh, Mommy loves you so much.
Don't leave me again.
Don't leave me ever.
- I didn't want to
leave you, Mommy.
The angel took me away.
I wanted to stay with you.
- Oh, honey!
Oh, honey!
Oh, my baby.
- Alice! Open the door!
Let us in! Alice!
- Come on, honey.
- What's the matter,
Mommy? Are you sick?
- Mrs. Lundgren, let us in!
- No, honey, I'm okay.
- [Man] Mrs. Lundgren!
Are you okay?
[pounding at door]
[doorknob rattling]
- [Midge] Alice, honey, we'll
help you. Open the door.
- It's locked!
Door's locked!
Oh!
Tracy?
Tracy!
Oh god!
No! Tracy!
Tracy!
Oh god!
Oh god, how could you?
How could you lose her again?
- I'll call an ambulance.
- [Midge] Good. It's
okay, Alice, it's okay.
- No it's not okay!
He took my baby! He
took my baby again!
- [Midge] Alice, did
you take anything?
Are you on something, honey?
- It's not my fault.
Yes it is.
It's all my fault.
- Paramedics are on their way.
- [Alice] It's all my fault.
It's all my fault.
- I wonder what happened to her?
- Another 25 milligrams
of Thorazine.
Hit her with it.
[Alice screams]
Alice?
Can you hear me?
- Uh-huh?
Where am I?
- Everything's gonna be okay.
- Where's my baby?
- Alice! Alice!
Listen. Listen, listen, listen.
Alice, listen.
- Oh, it's you.
- That's right. That's right.
Leave us.
You gave us quite a
scare, young lady.
- I bet I did.
- Want to tell me what happened?
- [laughs] Hasn't
anyone told you yet?
- I'd rather have you tell me.
Alice?
- I'd rather not.
- The paramedics said
you were incoherent.
Something about your daughter.
Alice, have you been
seeing Tracy again?
Alice?
I'm just trying to help you.
Have you?
Oh, I'm just so tired.
I can hardly think.
- All right. I understand.
Just rest. I'll come
look in on you later.
Mr. Lundgren.
- Ah, Doctor.
- Please sit down.
- How is she?
- Well, physically
she'll be fine.
But as you know,
healthy people don't hear voices
and see their dead children.
- So she admitted to
seeing Tracy again?
- She absolutely
insisted she had.
- Well, what's this
come down to, Doctor?
I mean, is she gonna get better
or is she gonna get worse?
- It's extremely
difficult to say.
But based on this
most recent episode,
I'm afraid the
psychological review board
will insist that
we keep her here
for further evaluation
and treatment.
- I understand.
- I want to assure
you that once again
I will personally supervise and
make sure she gets the best-
- Okay, Doctor, what
room's Alice in?
- Excuse me? Who are you?
- Mr. Lundgren,
Detective Williams.
- Detective?
- He's investigating
the elevator killings.
- Right. Look, let
me make myself clear.
Nobody wants the son of a
bitch caught more than I do,
but I don't think it's a
good time to disturb my wife.
She's in a very
sensitive condition.
- Yeah.
I'll bet she is.
It's awful about her
relapse, isn't it?
- Yes, it is.
- Yes, it is. I just dropped
in to see how she's doing.
- I've already told you that's-
- You want me to get a court
order? I'll get a court order.
- Court order?
You think you've got just cause,
then you get the hell outta here
and you find your court order.
- Real nice to finally
meet you, Mr. Lundgren.
- Yeah, you bet.
- Good afternoon,
Detective Williams.
- Jesus Christ.
Son of a bitch.
[pensive music]
[Alice panting]
[Alice gasps]
- Oh god.
Oh god!
It's okay, Alice.
Everyone has nightmares.
You're not crazy.
- [Kurt] No, you're
definitely not crazy.
- Who is that?
- Sanity is just a state of
mind and a point of view.
- What the hell
are you doing here?
- Alice, uh...
Listen, trust me. Just
for a minute, okay?
I think I can help you.
And I hope you can help me.
- Stay right where you are
or I'll push this button
and scream rape.
I want to know who
you really are.
- I told you before. My
name's Kurt Williams.
I'm a police detective and
I specialize in homicide.
- I called police headquarters.
They never heard of you.
- Normally I work undercover.
I mean, crack scams,
bunco chicken markets,
stuff like that,
and it's pretty nasty stuff.
Think you're gonna call division
and ask 'em if I'm a cop
and they're gonna tell you?
- No, I guess not.
- Listen, if you want to
reach me, day or night,
call this number.
Okay?
I'm kind of obsessed
with your case.
Let me explain that.
When you were
attacked, you know,
and you get an instinct for
this kind of thing, it's...
It's hard to explain, but
something wasn't right.
Something just wasn't right.
I mean, I wasn't assigned
to your case or anything,
but I made you my business.
And I gotta be real
honest with you right now.
After six months,
you're nothing but a
file folder downtown
in an overstuffed cabinet.
I think I'm your only shot.
- What's different about my
case? It was a random attack.
- You're alive. That's
what makes you special.
And I'm convinced
that it wasn't the elevator
killer that attacked you.
- What?
- It doesn't fit
the profile at all.
He never would've
murdered your kid.
left you alive.
Listen to me. I need
information from you.
You're the only person left.
- You've come to
the wrong person.
I can't tell you anything.
I don't even know
what's real anymore.
Maybe I am crazy.
- Excuse me for asking, okay?
Were you taking anything?
- Nothing like that, no.
- But you were taking something?
- The doctor here
gave me some Valium
that I've been carrying
around and, you know,
today was the first time I
felt like I really needed one.
That's all.
- How many did you take?
- Just two, I think.
No, I'm sure. I only took two.
- Anything else?
Anything at all?
- Nope. Nothing.
[soft music]
Tell me the truth. Do
you think I'm crazy?
- I wouldn't say
you're crazy at all.
- You know what I'm asking.
I saw my daughter
today. I know I did.
And I also know she's dead.
- Well, it is possible.
I mean, that you actually
did see her in your mind.
It can be very real.
- Not in my mind. I saw her.
I saw her.
- Well, I don't
know what to say.
Unless you believe in ghosts.
- It's wasn't...
[knock at door]
- Knock, knock. Can I come in?
- Kathy?
- Alice! You told me you were
over this and I believed you.
I help you get a job
and you flip out.
The review board will have no
choice but to commit you again
and this time for keeps.
- Why is everybody so
convinced I'm insane?
- Because.
Sane people don't go around
seeing ghosts. That's why.
- I didn't see a ghost!
I saw Tracy.
Alive.
- Alice-
- I touched her.
I held her in my arms, Kat.
I felt her heart
beating inside her.
- No, you didn't.
Goddamn it, she's dead!
- No, she isn't.
[somber music]
- Alice.
They will put you away.
For a long time.
Dr. Meltzner won't
be able to help you
if you won't even help yourself.
I don't want to lose you again.
- And I don't want
to lose Tracy.
I saw her.
- Then...
I don't know what else to say.
- [Alice] You don't
have to say anything.
- Alice.
I love you.
- I know you do.
Take care of yourself.
- I will.
And I know as long
as you're here,
Victor will take care of you.
[pensive music]
[Victor whistles]
- You're late.
- That for me?
- That's for you.
So I guess this means you're
gonna get out of Dodge, right?
- I ain't hanging around
here, that's for sure.
- I was thinking maybe
you'd get a little greedy,
come back for a little more
and maybe bring the police.
- Mr. Lundgren, we had a deal.
- Mr. Norton, you had a deal.
I got a plan.
- Now wait a minute. You don't
have to do this, you know.
I mean, I wouldn't talk.
I mean, you can keep
the money. I won't talk.
- What are you gonna
do, dance for me?
- Mr. Lundgren, please, no.
- You gonna dance?
- Mr. Lundgren-
- Why don't you just dance?
[Norton screaming]
No more hired
killers. [chuckles]
[phone rings]
- Hello? Hello?
- [Tracy] Mommy? Are
you coming to get me?
- Tracy? Where are you, baby?
- [Tracy] I'm here.
I'm waiting for you.
- Yes, but where? Where are you?
- [Tracy] At your office.
[dial tone hums]
Tracy?
[suspenseful music]
- She's on her way.
Just as we discussed.
Don't make pointless threats.
We both have too much to lose.
[suspenseful music]
Goddammit! What the...
Damn!
Dammit!
[bell chimes]
[elevator hums]
[Alice panting]
[Alice screams]
[tense music]
[Alice whimpering]
[suspenseful music]
[Alice screams]
- [Tracy] Mommy!
- Tracy?
- Mommy!
- Tracy.
[haunting music]
- [Tracy] I'm waiting for you.
- Tracy?
Tracy, where are you?
- [Tracy] I'm waiting for you.
- Yes, baby, but where are you?
[line clicks]
Tracy?
Tracy.
- [Tracy] I'm waiting
downstairs, in the lobby.
- Downstairs.
[suspenseful music]
[Alice grunts]
Tracy!
[Alice gasps]
[elevator rumbles]
[Alice screams]
No!
[Alice screaming]
No! Down, dammit!
[tense music]
Tracy?
- Mommy!
[ominous music]
- No!
No!
Tracy!
- I want Mommy!
- Tracy!
- Mommy!
Mommy, Mommy, come to me.
Please come, Mommy.
Mommy! Please come.
[sinister music]
[Alice screaming]
[elevator hums]
Are you okay, Mommy?
[haunting music]
Hi, Mommy.
- Oh, Tracy.
Tracy.
Oh!
Tracy!
[Alice moans]
Oh!
[Alice moaning]
[Alice whimpers]
[eerie music]
[haunting music]
[Alice sobs]
[Alice moans]
Damn!
Damn.
It's the pills.
Oh, these bitches.
Ow! Ooh!
[Alice moans]
Good.
[phone dialing]
[phone rings]
- This better be good.
- Kurt. It's me.
- Alice?
- You gotta help me! I need you!
- Okay, where are you?
- The pills. Remember you
asked me about the pills?
It's the pills.
- Uh, okay. Are you
still at the hospital?
- [Alice] No. I'm
here with Tracy.
Well, that's wonderful
that you guys are together,
but where are you?
Baby, tell me where you are.
- You gotta help me.
The man in the mask.
The man in the elevator is here.
- [Kurt] You gotta tell me
where you are. You can trust me.
I'm the only one.
You gotta tell me
where you are though
so I can come and get you.
[Alice retches]
Alice?
Alice, you can trust me.
- I've been...
I've been seeing things.
But some of it's true.
I know it's true. I
know Tracy is here.
Tracy is here.
I know she is.
- Okay. Now listen, just calm
down, take a deep breath.
Alice, listen, I'm the
only one you can trust.
Come on, baby, where
are you? Alice?
Shit!
- You were here. I saw you.
I saw you!
[door creaks]
[suspenseful music]
- [Tracy] I want my mommy!
- Tracy?
Dammit, I want my
daughter, you bastard!
[Alice groans]
Tracy!
[transformer crackles]
Tracy! Where are you, baby?
- Hello, Alice.
- Victor?
- Mommy!
- You! Goddamn!
- God dammit!
Don't!
- Mommy!
- It's all right,
sweetie, it's all right.
Mommy's just still a
little sick, that's all.
- Tracy, come to Mommy.
- You stay out of our way.
- Daddy, you're hurting me!
- Stay out of our way, Alice!
- Victor, please, let her go!
I'll do whatever you want.
- Well, it's up
to you, isn't it?
Either we live
together on my terms
or we all die together.
[sparks crackling]
- Daddy, you're hurting me!
- I'll stay, I'll do
whatever you want.
- And none of this happened,
did it? Do you understand?
None of it. It's
all in your mind.
Say it.
- All in my mind.
- What?
- It was all in my mind?
- It was all in my mind!
- Good.
Right.
Now.
There's not gonna
be a divorce? No!
- No! No, whatever you want.
- [Victor] You're going to
go the hospital, yes. Say it.
- Yes.
- Very good.
Tracy's gonna remain with me
and then in time,
Alice, in time,
then you're going
to come back to me.
And then you'll be mine forever.
- Fine.
- It's your choice.
- My choice.
It's my choice.
You've already got Tracy.
You've taken everything
from me, Victor!
My child, my...
And my mind.
- Ah. [laughs]
- Jesus, Victor. I saw her die!
She was...
Oh my god.
You burned a child in that oven.
- [grunts] This stupid bitch!
I got a body, a little
body, from the morgue.
She was already dead.
- All those other women, dead
because of you? Because of me?
- I had nothing to do
with the other killings.
You understand? I didn't
kill anybody else.
All right?
- No, Daddy! Don't hurt Mommy!
[shelf crashes]
- [Victor] Damn you!
[Victor groans]
- Tracy, come here! Come
to Mommy, come here!
Come on!
[tense music]
Come here!
- Alice, no.
Please. Please don't do this.
Please. Come on, baby, I...
I love you.
I did it because I
love you. I love us!
I love you.
- Love? Don't say that,
you son of a bitch!
You don't have the
right to use the word.
Not after what you did
to me and my child.
- Alice. I did this
all because I love you!
[Victor shouts]
Alice!
Alice! Help me!
Alice! Alice!
Alice, please!
Alice!
Help me!
[Victor screams]
- Come here, Tracy.
[suspenseful music]
It's okay, baby. It's
gonna be all right.
Oh, darling.
[gasps] Oh! God, you scared me.
- Mommy?
- It's okay, honey.
He's a policeman.
- Yeah, it's okay
now. It's okay.
Where's Lundgren?
- He's dead.
- It was him, wasn't it?
And he was just using the
other killings to get to you.
- Yeah. How did you know?
- I just knew.
I just knew. It had to be him.
Come on, let's go.
[suspenseful music]
[sighs] I knew it. That bastard.
I mean, how the
hell he ever thought
I'd let him get away with
something like that, I mean...
Well, he's stupid.
He's a stupid man.
There's so much stupidity
in this world, you know?
God, I hate stupidity.
I mean, anybody who'd
attack you and your daughter
has gotta be brainless.
You're good people.
I mean, the other people
deserve what they got,
but you guys, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
And I mean, it was his fault
you went through all this pain.
At least you're not my
fault. I mean, you know that.
But it's a difficult situation
because, you know, I mean...
The cops are gonna
start asking questions
and inevitably they're gonna...
Be led to me, and I mean,
you're not gonna be able
to answer the questions.
There's no way.
You know?
A copycat killer,
like your husband,
is never as good
as the original.
I mean, this is not something
I want to do. Believe me.
It's the last thing in
the world I want to do.
[elevator clanks]
You know? But I gotta.
And, uh...
I'll make it as quick as I can.
[Alice yelps]
[Tracy screams]
- Stop! [screams]
[tense music]
- Aw, come on.
Don't make it hard on yourself.
[elevator clanks]
[Kurt screams]
[Kurt groans]
- Tracy, come here!
Come here, baby!
- Are you okay, Mommy?
[Kurt screams]
[Kurt groans]
Oh, Tracy, come here, baby. Oh!
It's okay, darling.
Come on, it's okay.
Come on.
- Mommy, can we go home now?
- Yes, darling.
[ominous music]