"Lot for sale'"
We have evidence
that your husband
entered Dai Thanh floating farm,
to try to steal something.
Following a confrontation,
he jumped into the water.
He drowned, obviously.
Those who discovered
your husband's corpse
noticed this broken
necklace in his hand.
We have many witnesses.
Wait for me there !
I'm going to call them !
"Sao and Thi"
Wonderful !
A true blessing
from our ancestors !
My mom sends us
this fish from Lim Kim !
Oh my God !
Here's another one !
You see ?
Here is the small and the small...
You're gonna make them and eat
them like your mom told you, huh?
Are you still mad at my mom?
I'm going to look for cilantro
to prepare it properly !
Where ?
Nobody has any more.
It's time to sell it all.
Wait a few more days !
The leaves should
be greener than that.
Do you remember what the
grasshoppers did to it last year?
If they dare, I will
eat them in my turn !
We will have what we want.
Leave it to me !
Wash yourself !
We're going to sit down to eat.
This is our last can.
I dare you to jump in.
You are sure of it ?
Go on !
We need it to make coffee tomorrow !
What if I got sick
from not washing?
Wash yourself properly !
Turn around, so I can
caress you properly...
No shower today?
Where would I get the water?
I did it right, today...
Did you like it ?
No.
And I never want
you to do it again.
Yet you had always
told me that you liked it !
That was a long time ago.
I didn't dare tell you before.
Maybe it's because of
the way we do it
that we never get a child.
I've been waiting for two years already.
But still no child.
And each time, it hurts
me more and more.
1...
2...
3...
4... 5...
Darling !
Shit !
It must have happened
yesterday, just before the rain.
It is surely the work
of grasshoppers !
Sure.
While you were busy
caressing me, right?
Are they still
good, do you think?
Don't worry.
I will plant melons
for New Year's Day.
Where are my parents' urns?
There, in a plastic bag.
- You did it right, huh?
- Quick !
Catch this !
It will weigh too much !
The boat is going to sink !
Take this ! That way
we can eat properly.
“Private Property
Access Prohibited”
Who allowed you
to fish here, morons?
Can't you read, or what?
At one time, it may
have belonged to you.
Now the water
belongs to everyone.
Get off my property now !
The more time passes,
the less fish there are.
There is no more land,
people are all
fishing to survive.
Shit !
He must have gotten stuck in the net.
He was eaten alive.
There is also a
huge hole in the net.
Something must have eaten
those fish and then escaped.
Sell ​​the land...
and leave.
Who would buy this?
The big companies are
looking for land to build farms on.
This land has been passed
down for generations.
Mom just passed away.
It would be a
sin to sell it now.
What is happening ?
A huge goldfish
swooped down on me...
and devoured my stomach !
Unbelievable !
You don't have to believe me !
If you ever bury me here,
build my coffin carefully.
"Lot for sale'"
What ?
Really ?
Right away ?
Are you sure?
OK.
Where are you going ?
A madman wants to buy our land.
He wants to see me right away.
At two o'clock in the morning...
Just tell him the price.
Do not sign any documents.
Yes I know...
Darling...
What ?
Collect some rice and oil.
We do not have any more.
OK.
So, what about this land ?
How did you get this money?
I...
Is it a down payment?
Yes, but not for the land.
For what, then?
It's a down payment for a job.
What work ?
Not far from here.
They will let me know.
Crocodiles go on land !
And people go into the sea !
You are very careful !
No, it was Thi who asked me.
He was afraid of
being eaten by the fish.
Why not cremate him instead?
He wanted to be buried in his land.
Please screw the lid on !
Did you buy enough screws?
Otherwise, use ones from your boat !
I could stop fishing
and come live with you.
And then you would
take care of me. OK ?
Hey, Sao !
What a good smell of pandan...
Here ! You will pay me
when you have money.
Where have you been ?
The neighbors were worried.
Where did you find
pandan this season ?
Guys gave it to me.
They might have stolen it...
Don't tell anyone.
They told me that when they
approached Dai
Thannh floating farm,
they heard people fighting,
and someone screamed for help.
Someone yelled :
"Head under water !"
And another: 'To hell with it !'
It's all fucked up these days !
There is no more land.
What do we have left on this Earth ?
Please give me
two cans of water !
There is none left.
Do you know what time it is ?
You didn't wake up ?
Usually this is my  husband's job.
He hung around all night and
he didn't come home. That's it ?
Well, if you need
water, go to Dai Thannh.
You will be asked
for an arm and a leg...
Please give me some !
A can will suffice.
If you want more,
call me tonight !
It's free !
Thanh, my brother !
I took you for Thi.
Did you cremate him ?
He's over there right now.
I'm going to go visit him.
OK.
Then we'll eat something.
In this fish dish...
You have to add onions
for it to taste right.
Like brothers...
For Thi, everything
had to be done right.
We had fun together
from morning to night.
We even shared clothes.
When Thi was getting dressed,
he woud talk about you every time.
But why did you leave
without telling anyone ?
Thi was very sad.
You were there for him,
he didn't need me anymore.
I had bought this for him, for New
Year's Day, but didn't have a chance...
Last year, you gave him
shoes he never put on.
He wanted an outfit
that went together.
You can put them on now.
No, I don't need those things.
I'll wait for the tide to drop...
and put them in his coffin.
Come inside !
Otherwise you will get sick.
Stop it !
I am not a sissy !
Thi left a bottle of alcohol.
You should drink
some to warm up.
Did you discover anything else ?
What more do you want ?
The truth about my husband's death !
What other truth ?
Let's go home !
Go on !
He had started working at night.
But he didn't tell me for whom.
A few days later,
they killed him.
Had he brought a
small tube home ?
What kind of tube ?
A tube ?
How do you
know about it ?
Someone told me they
would give me pain medicine.
Now I remember...
I'm taking you home.
Then you will take...
something at the market for Thi.
Hey, Sao !
Sao !
Did you hear something ?
I do not know !
How do you know it
was my brother-in-law ?
Do you have proof ?
I want to see him !
Calm down !
We are in no rush !
Asshole !
I should have ripped his head off !
Hey ! We don't swear here !
Rip off whose head ?
To that bastard Giang !
This bastard kills
people, without scruples !
Shut up !
If we had arrived later, he
would have ripped your head off !
Please stop !
Could I talk to him for a moment ?
Just a moment.
Then I'll take him to the
provincial police station.
Why did you leave
without saying a word ?
What's the point ? You would have
ended up worrying unnecessarily.
Too late now.
Come home.
There's nothing you can do here.
They got me like a greased pig.
Who is this Giang you were talking about ?
This floating farm boss
thug in Dai Thanh...
He married the boss's
daughter to get this job.
He is as cruel as
a cursed crocodile !
He ordered his gang
to beat up Thi
and throw him in the water !
Have you already forgotten ?
Giang left Saigon
to come and look
for species of seaweed.
You remember it ?
This type of vagabond
invents stories !
Don't believe him !
The sea level continues to rise.
Southern Vietnam is a territory
that stands to lose the
best arable land in the world...
Are you looking for a job ?
Step back !
- Look towards the camera !
Look straight ahead !
You're the thief's
wife, aren't you ?
Your brother-in-law also killed people here.
What do you want ?
I just want to apply for a job.
Did you take us for crazy ?
Go home !
Could I at least
talk to the manager ?
Tell him my name is Sao. I'm
the one who sold coffee near here.
I told you to go home !
Watch out, or I'll
deal with you too !
Are you looking for a job ?
Did you really want
my husband dead ?
But what do you want, exactly ?
I want you to deny everything...
so I can go home...
and console me, knowing
that I have discovered the truth.
The boss will pay you
500,000 dong a week,
We will pick you up
every Monday at 7 a.m.
You will have the right to take two
changes of clothes, nothing else.
And above all, no
phones and no weapons.
Otherwise, you'll
be fired immediately.
"Sao and Giang 10 years ago"
Oh my God ! You want to
demolish my house, or what ?!
Excuse me ! I am really sorry !
I am a student of the
University of the Littoral.
I am here for research
on plants in this area.
Can I ask you a favor ?
What's that ?
I will stay here for a few months.
I rented a house
on stilts there.
I saw smoke coming
from your house.
It smelled so good, and...
The smell of braised
fish is so good...
I wish someone
would give me some...
You just had to
tell me right away !
It's fish soup.
Not braised fish.
Ah, OK...
Are you from Saigon ?
Yes !
I don't really know
your eating habits.
I eat everything !
I just prefer it to be
a little more cooked.
You should look elsewhere.
There are stalls near the market.
Saigon tourists love it.
Mrs !
Excuse me !
Hey !
Is someone there ?
Who are you looking for ?
I'm looking for the waitress.
She left.
I work in his place, at night.
What would you like ?
I had ordered a black coffee...
but she put sugar in it.
Force of habit...
I can bring you another.
We roast the coffee ourselves here.
It is therefore very strong and bitter.
A little sugar
improves the taste.
Just a little bit.
Want to taste ?
You were right !
With a little sugar, it
definitely tastes better.
You pretend to be nice...
Why should I pretend ?
You just want to take advantage
of my mom cooking for you.
That's why you pretend.
How do you know I'm looking
for someone who cooks ?
Mom told me.
And how do you know it's me ?
You're the only one who looks
like a student from Saigon here.
In the age of the Internet, are
there still people
who read books ?
In all sincerity,
I haven't touched a
book for over 10 years.
I knew it.
What did you know ?
And what do you
do to relax a bit ?
I watch TV or stream movies.
What a drag !
TV and movies
make people lazy and
forget the pleasure
of reading a book.
Try to start reading
again, you'll see...
how different it is
from your bright screen.
Last year, I had read a
poem online, by chance.
And I felt no emotion.
Then I read the same
poem, but on paper.
And that really moved me.
Now I no longer have any doubts.
You always firmly believe
in your own opinions.
It's easy to believe
in your own ideas.
Convincing others
is much more difficult.
You have convinced me !
Advise me a book, then ! OK ?
Of what genre ?
Poetry, prose ?
Story, fiction ?
I'm too lazy to
read a long story.
Give me your favorite
short story book.
News ?
News...
What was the title ?
"2020" ?
A brief speculative
narrative about the future.
We are in 2020...
Where would this
speculative narrative be ?
Yes, but the author wrote
this book 20 years ago.
He recounts life today.
And you ?
What would you write about the future ?
Me ?
I would write...
“The sea level will rise,
and submerge this cafe...
"and this shelf too !"
And then all your books
will float in the water...
So even the fish will be
able to read my books !
Just like archaeologists who
would study lost civilizations.
Hey, Sao !
We are dying of thirst here !
Please, two iced coffees !
You'll talk about
science fiction later !
OK, I'll be right there !
When did you arrive ?
What's wrong ?
I do not know.
Can you help me please ?
Could you take me there, please ?
I know where you live.
This boat will have to be repaired.
I just arrived.
How do you know ?
Giang, right ?
It was Sao who told me.
You know Sao ?
We grew up together. Then one
day, she left to study in Saigon.
And where did
she study, exactly ?
At the university, I believe.
I do not know.
Her father died
during this time.
She came back to live here
with her mother last year.
She looks fit...
Sao likes her a lot, doesn't she ?
She's not doing very well these days.
She is famous for
preparing very special dishes.
Everyone here wants
to be her son-in-law.
But it's not that easy...
They would like to be
just to eat well. Not true ?
One marries for questions
of interest or money.
I would marry for food !
OK, let's go.
Thanks.
Here is the money. Thanks !
It's too much. I'm just
taking the gas money.
I have to go fishing early tomorrow.
Thanh will lead you to your boat.
Thanh ?
My little brother.
Thanks a lot !
How would I have
got along without you ?
OK, I have to go there.
Someone there ?
My mother made stuffed calamari.
I brought you some.
Thank you very much
to you and your mom.
I have heard that...
many would like to taste your
mother's dishes, but without success...
Don't trust Thi !
Why haven't you come
to the cafe these days ?
I was very busy.
My darling !
Don't worry. I already
found a place to eat.
Delicious and very clean.
I have already listed
some types of algae.
I'll take them back
to Saigon for analysis.
I have nothing else to do here...
I can fully concentrate
on my work.
Do not worry. Everything is fine.
When will you leave ?
I need this bowl...
to be able to serve
you on your plate.
Do you know where this dish comes from ?
No, but I like this pattern.
It is very simple.
I'm no antiques expert...
but I think you are right !
You can keep it.
No, I cannot accept...
You can put your coffee in it.
It could attract a lot of customers.
You were attracted.
That's already something.
Why do you collect seaweed ?
Algae ?
I'm trying to figure out how...
they can survive in seawater,
since it is salty.
You know there is seaweed...
that lives in both
fresh and salt water ?
It exists ?
Where ?
Wait...
It was a long time ago...
I believe...
But first I want to know
why you collect seaweed...
No, you tell me first
where this type of algae is.
Then I will tell you about my work.
I just told you
half of my secret.
Your turn now.
Besides, you know
everything about me and my
family, whereas I don't
know anything about you.
But don't tell anyone !
I'm researching the genes
of plants living in salt water.
I'm trying to figure out how much...
they differ from those
that live in fresh water.
That's all ?
I thought there was a secret, or something.
- Nope...
In this case,
you're so confident
that you might make a mistake.
You don't know the
potential of this research.
It is something
concrete, I assure you.
Ok, I leave you to your dreams...
I have to go back there.
Wait !
And the other half of the secret ?
You haven't told me where these algae are.
- At the estuary.
Where the river flows into the ocean.
- Could you help me find them ?
Will you pay me ?
No, just a small
gift, in friendship.
When will you be free ?
Tomorrow ?
We'll see...
Do you want to bring
new technologies to us ?
What technology ?
I'm only researching
estuary plants.
Who told you that ?
Since the Xoai Rap
River is polluted, people
are wary of big
companies and scientists.
I do not know why...
Thi is so nice to you...
Not all companies are dangerous.
Many of them help
to make things better.
As for me, I have
absolutely no intention of
contributing to the
destruction of the environment.
Are you sure ?
If you cause
damage in this area,
I assure you
that I will find you.
- Is that a threat ?
Not yet.
One last thing...
Thi adores Sao. Do no damage.
It's here. Get me down !
...but tonight I want
you to stay with me...
This evening ? In fact, I
still have a few things to do.
I have to go back
to Can Gio tomorrow.
You have just returned to Saigon,
and you already have to leave ?
Don't forget your
date with my father
and the Dai Thanh
Board of Directors.
“From a Portuguese ship
that sank 200 years ago.
"I miss you."
At present, the goal
of our company is to
minimize the effective
need for fresh water.
Our priority is
mainly vegetables.
Using the results of
your initial research,
we would like to know...
if there is any chance
to solve this problem.
In order to answer the
question of our director,
I would like to summarize
the results of my research.
I have indeed discovered a type of algae
having developed in fresh
water, but having migrated
to the estuary to adapt
to the new situation.
These algae have mutated genes
in order to survive
in salt water.
But what's more,
I managed to identify
all the mutated genes.
However,
it is a natural process...
extremely long.
In addition...
"Extremely long" ?
That's to say ?
I can't tell you
exactly, but at least
a few decades, maybe even more.
Nevertheless,
the latest breakthroughs
in genetic engineering
allow us to speed up this
process in the laboratory...
by inserting the mutated genes
of this algae into other plants,
which would allow them
to survive in salt water.
Would this imply a
change in color, smell...
texture... of the vegetables themselves ?
I want to reassure you...
This would not happen...
because we would only
modify the genes allowing
the plant to eliminate
the salt in the water.
In other words, the features...
of the plant would remain intact.
In addition,
if successful,
the next step would be to grow
these vegetables directly in seawater
while avoiding the
construction of floating farms.
We're just getting
started, and you're
already dreaming
of a second step !
I believe that the first step
is to establish a partnership
with an advanced genetic
engineering laboratory.
I suggest that Mr. Giang
find the best university in
this field, in order to start
a profitable collaboration.
My dear !
Do you know what I'm thinking ?
I imagine that one fine
day the water will completely
recede, the bottom of the
ocean will be just a sandy beach,
and that I will run with you, until
we are completely exhausted.
Sao, listen.
I have something to tell you.
I have good news.
I have just received a scholarship
to continue my research.
At a university in the USA.
When will you leave ?
In two days.
I'm going to have to go
back to Saigon tonight.
So I won't be able to come
back here very often... For a while.
Sao ! What are you doing ?
Come back here ! Right away !
Sao !
Marry me !
Thi !
You scared me !
The bus will be leaving soon.
Get on, I'll take you !
You will arrive in time !
I came here by motorbike.
It's too nice of you...
We didn't get to
know each other well,
but you've always
been very kind to me.
Yes, but you know...
I think of myself first.
I do not understand
what you mean...
Before Sao's mother died a few
months ago, she
wanted Sao to marry me.
But Sao never stopped hoping for a
moment that you would come back.
Where did you find that ?
Her husband was killed here...
Besides, she works here !
No shame !
Apparently, she loves
to have fun, the naughty...
Even with the director's
husband, it seems...
It doesn't surprise me, by the way...
What a slut !
This fish is perfect
for fish soup.
Fish soup ?
With soy sauce, delicious.
Is she new ?
Since the day before yesterday.
Super hard worker.
How could I make it ?
My husband is a picky
eater, but he loves this dish.
Bring him inside, and
open the kitchen door for...
My name is Sao.
... for Sao...
The secret of fish
soup is no secret.
But the fish must be fresh,
and the soy sauce exquisite.
Exquisite soy sauce ?
Pagoda brand.
No sugar, no water
or MSG in the sauce.
Your mother cooked
very well, didn't she ?
When she was still
alive, I didn't like to cook.
There, I regret not
having learned from her.
Then, as my husband
was very demanding, I
had to remember the
tastes of the food I ate.
And I started practicing.
You often eat at
restaurants, don't you ?
I started loving cooking
since I was a mother.
I am so happy to see my
daughter eat what I prepare...
But unlike you, I couldn't
remember my mother's dishes.
Your mother didn't like to cook ?
No, my mother died prematurely.
At my birth.
You didn't have a mother.
Me, I didn't have any children.
What are you doing, Sao ?
Sao !
I know all your secrets !
- What secrets ?
- You watered the vegetables with salt water !
My husband had discovered
it while stealing cilantro !
And you killed him
so no one would know !
Really ? And do you have proof?
Proof ?
The seeds you use !
It's me !
Go on ! Get back to work !
Sorry, sir... Good night !
My body had started to
react in a strange way...
after years of ingesting
these samples.
I contacted a team
of foreign researchers.
They just want to see these
seeds and my cell samples.
And why forbid them ?
As several cases of illness
such as mine had been reported,
Dai Thanh decided
to close this laboratory
and rigorously control my seeds.
They want to use my
discovery to build hundreds
of floating farms
all over the country.
That's why I need these seeds.
It's not just for me,
but for the whole world.
Wow ! As you are human...
Nevertheless, you are indeed
responsible for the
death of my husband !
One second... At the time...
I had entrusted
Thi with this task.
I wanted him to take care of those
seeds. And everything had gone well.
Then, influenced by his brother,
he betrayed me
and tried to steal our
technology for a
competing company.
Thi got screwed.
It was my stepfather
who had decided to throw him in the water !
They are killers...
And now they are no longer
going to wait for me to die...
and they're keeping an eye on you !
Sooner or later...
they will discover our past...
and my plan with Thi.
I am very worried about your life.
And your life ?
I reflected on my work...
Life or death ?
Either way, this piece
would be perfect as a casket.
Everything you told
me makes perfect sense.
But how do I know
if it's the truth ?
Maximum alert !
A super typhoon is approaching !
Evacuation order
for all employees !
Come, quickly !
Daddy, you're hurting me !
Come with us...
All security guards must
be evacuated immediately !
Translation : Jean-Claude Trovato
Subtitles :
INTERTITULA