[HEAVY BREATHING]
[CAR RUMBLES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
I'm sorry.
[THEME MUSIC]
[THEME MUSIC FADES OUT]
Looks like
I'll be seeing your father...
sooner than I planned.
Well, I'll finally...
get to thank him face to face...
for taking that bullet for me.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Seen my wife?
She's in the bedroom.
Gilda!
[GOONS MUMBLE]
Affairs aren't nearly
as much fun...
Gilda!
when you're the one
being cheated on.
Especially when it's
in the family.
Cooler heads...
must prevail.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC FADES OUT]
[GILDA AND ANTHONY YELLING
IN THE BACKGROUND]
I know you're not your
brother's keeper.
He'll be the first to say
we're not brothers.
Still, he respects you.
He hates my guts.
If I could,
I would leave...
the family business to you.
Thank you.
[GILDA YELLING
IN THE BACKGROUND]
To tell the truth,
I'm way more entrenched
that I ever wanted to be.
I'm here for you,
and only you.
You've got to promise me,
you'll do whatever it takes to
protect the family.
I think of you as a son,
even though you're not blood.
[MAX COUGHS]
Good one.
Matches my outfit.
Your parents
would be proud of you.
ANTHONY: NO!
[LOUD THUD]
I don't think so.
Max is dying.
How did you get your hands
on his medical records?
- Well...
- There's no court order here.
Concierge doctors.
You pay more than their patients
or dig up a little dirt.
You know I don't approve
of your tactics.
- We can't use this in court.
- Every bit of intel helps.
How long has he got?
Scum's a tough old bird.
He's going to hang on for
months.
I hope he dies slowly
and painfully.
That'll put...
- Anthony in charge.
- The most sadistic.
God help us.
Don't hold your breath.
I'm not having this debate
with you today.
But what I can't figure out...
is this guy.
They have
someone clever in there,
laundering their dirty money
through philanthropy,
raw land, franchises,
as you name it.
Even our best accountants
can't track it back.
Yeah...
this guy's the brain
of the bunch.
Hopefully our housecleaning
operation on the call girl ring
will stop their cash flow
for a minute.
We need more.
We really need a break.
I got to run. I have hot meal
duty today at church.
What kind of people you
going to church with?
Come with me and find out.
No.
I feel naked without it.
It's called trust issues.
Yeah, well, I have enough
of them for a lifetime.
Do you blame me?
- Bye.
Have fun at church,
with your gun.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Wait in the car,
Johnny.
Nobody comes in. You
understand?
Come on. Get out.
Get out.
Hey.
Kid!
Get out of here. Go!
Get in there.
[BELLS CHIME]
ELIZABETH: Susan.
SUSAN: Hey. You know that break
you asked for earlier?
Yeah, I actually prayed
for one. Why?
Maybe there is someone up there,
listening to you at least.
An Italian stallion
in the Torino stable
has been dipping his wick
in the heir-apparent's
marital well.
Dumb! How do you think
you could get away with that?
What?
See you next month.
Inside guy says that the boss
to be is on the warpath.
He's a sitting duck
in the collections
over the Gem Theater.
A couple of guys are going
over there to pick him up now.
Catch him in the act.
You know, basically,
save his ass.
If we rescue him
and threaten to cut him loose,
he might flip.
- Cough up some intel.
- You're reading my mind.
They'll let you
have a go at him
once we get him
in a controlled environment.
All right. Thanks, Susan.
How you doing, Cuz?
Didn't expect to see you here.
I like to keep
my people on their toes.
I had some business nearby.
Killing two birds.
Yeah.
You two know each other, right?
We've met.
Everything adding up
with the bookies?
- Yep.
- Unions paying on time?
- Drug sales are steady.
- And the girls?
Not one's given
the D.A. a thing.
They know their place.
Got to ask you, Cuz.
What kind of fool parks his
little scooter in my garage?
Hunh? Hunh?
[DOOR SLAMS]
[DOOR BANGS INTO JULIAN
ANTHONY GRUNTS]
[JULIAN SCREAMS]
[BONE BREAKING THUD]
She told me I was
the best she'd ever had.
Yeah...
Well, she lied to me too.
[SOCCER BALL BOUNCES]
[DOOR SLAMS]
Drop the gun!
[SIRENS IN BACKGROUND]
The People versus
Anthony Torino.
The charge: murder in
the first degree.
What's the plea?
The plea's not guilty.
And The People on bail?
Miss Jones.
It's not often we see the D.A.
at a bail hearing.
Exactly our argument,
Your Honor. Thank you
for making it for us.
I mean, the prosecutorial bias
in this case is unprecedented.
I mean, there is clearly
a conflict of interest
when we have the supposed
witness prosecuting the case.
- You finished?
- I'm done, thanks.
Special circumstances.
A.D.A. Jackson
had a family emergency.
The people strongly recommend
this dangerous criminal
be denied bail.
He is a significant flight risk
- and his family is notorious...
- Ok, Your Honor,
if our court system based guilt
on familial association,
I dare say we'd all be
up here defending ourselves.
Your Honor,
this is the first time
my client,
the individual,
not the whole family,
has ever been charged
with any crime of any sort.
He was caught red-handed,
at the scene of the crime,
still holding the murder
weapon. Your Honor, we...
That's circumstantial,
Your Honor. And self-defense.
- How so?
- My client
walked in on his beloved wife
being brutally beaten
by his cousin after she rejected
- his sexual advances.
- That is ridiculous.
It's a good thing
he arrived when he did
because Mister Torino
saved her life.
He is not the evil-doer,
he is the hero.
Your Honor, we request
a case dismissal
due to lack
of admissible evidence.
That's a bit premature,
Mister Flanders.
His fingerprints were lifted
from the murder weapon.
Ballistics match
the slug that...
Actually. No, Your
Honor.
Unfortunately for us,
the police've misplaced
the alleged murder weapon.
Already anticipated, Your Honor.
The Torinos do have ties,
indeed.
The fingerprints've
been sent to the crime lab...
Sadly, all the evidence
that would have proven my client
innocent has either been lost,
destroyed,
contaminated, or misfiled.
The chain of custody
in this case is so corrupted,
there is no hope of the truth
ever coming to light.
- As such, Your Honor, I...
- I get it!
Next time,
save the theatrics.
Miss Jones.
There are four eyewitnesses...
Five, actually, Your Honor.
Two of whom aren't willing
to testify.
They're not quite sure
what they saw.
We also have
revised statements, Your Honor.
One from Mrs. Gilda Torino,
who, you can imagine,
was very distraught.
We also have one
from a Mister Johnny Graham.
He works for the Torino family,
also witnessed the incident.
I think his statement is...
It is worthless.
Your Honor,
we're talking about a lackey
driver on the Torino payroll.
How is that even remotely
credible?
And I need to see a copy...
I, too, am an eyewitness,
there are two other witnesses.
The forensic...
- Why don't you save it...
- Excuse me!
Well...
That was a lot of fun.
Bail is set
at one million dollars.
Mister Torino
will surrender his passport
and wear an electronic
monitoring device.
Now, get out of my courthouse.
[CREEPY MUSIC]
[CAR DOOR CLICKS OPEN]
[CAR DOOR SLAMS
CAR ENGINE CRANKS]
[CHILDREN YELLING]
Chris, it's homework time.
[TRIGGER]
Well absolutely.
I need to call you back.
That was no gas leak.
That was a hit.
And Chris'd be dead too...
I am telling you, we have got
to get him and Angela
into WITSEC ASAP.
I know you're not a fan
of the program,
but it is the only way
to keep them safe.
It's just so unfair.
We're taking them away
from their families.
Honey, Chris doesn't have
any more family.
Friends. Their entire lives.
Spending the rest of their lives
looking over their shoulders.
Come on, Witness Protection,
that's no way to live.
It's the only way they can live.
And let me remind you,
we have another witness
who is in equal danger.
Oh no. No. Do not start.
I am staying out here.
I'm prosecuting this case.
You know how hard
I've been trying
to get white collar charges
to stick.
If I could put Anthony Torino
away for murder...
Liz, you are in
grave danger, personally.
The man knows who you are. He
knows where you live.
I am you friend. I am just
telling you like it is.
They won't cross that line.
I know
that you don't trust anyone,
except for that God of yours.
But I am telling you, right now,
you've got to put
your faith in me.
Please. Go home.
Pack.
I'll pass.
Your Honor, the medical report
on Misses Torino's bruises
proves that they occurred
many hours
before this premeditated murder.
The G.S.R. results and the fact
that his victim's gun
hadn't been touched in days,
leaves no reasonable doubt as to
Mister Anthony Torino's guilt.
I beg you, for the safety of our
community, to revoke his bail.
He is a dangerous criminal
who ought not be on the streets.
Do you have a rebuttal to
this evidence, Mister Flanders?
A very detailed one, Your Honor.
I was afraid of that.
It's late. We'll reconvene
Monday morning at nine A.M.
Mister Torino,
you may want to pack
some spare underwear Monday.
Miss Jones, what do you think
the verdict will be?
I, I'm confident, I'm confident
that Mister Torino
will be where he belongs,
which is behind bars.
Is Gilda Torino
going to testify?
Uh, no. His wife unfortunately
still refuses to testify.
How are you going
to convince her to testify?
- I, uh...
- Just one more question.
- Let's go.
- How about the jury selection?
I'm confident that any jury we
seat
will see Mister Torino
for what he is,
which is a brazen criminal
who thinks he can kill
in broad daylight.
- A coward who believes...
- I said, let's go.
All right, let's go.
So, you sure about this?
It isn't your business, Johnny.
When Max finds out.
Max ain't going to find out.
She ain't going to rest until
there's a needle in my arm.
You understand that?
It's called self-defense.
Then let me take her out.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah, right. Johnny grows up.
Let me put some of that target
practice to good use for once.
There's a difference
between shooting at a target
and at a living being.
You know you're going to
be the number one suspect,
no matter how this goes down.
You've got a tracking device
on your ankle.
Let me drop you off
somewhere public, really public.
You make a lot of noise,
and I'll take care of it.
You're too chicken-shit
to pull this off, Johnny.
No one knows who I am.
There's no one
lower profile in the family.
Just let me prove myself to you.
You get one shot.
Don't mess it up.
Make sure this is at the bottom
of Lake Norman before morning.
Okay.
[RAP ON CAR WINDOW]
- Gah, man!
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
What the hell are you guys
doing here?
Immoral support, hunh.
She in there?
No, man. I rapped on her door
a half hour ago.
- There's no one home.
- Good.
We can get a drop on her.
- Crap!
- Get up!
Never take your eyes
off the target.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Look, can you guys
just let me do this?
Look at Johnny,
becoming a man, hunh?
- Ha ha.
- Don't want an audience?
Just stay here.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[ALARM KEYPAD BEEPS]
Pssst. I'm sorry.
Told you he could do it.
[ALARM BEEPS]
[ALARM SIREN BLARES]
Finish the job, amateur!
[GUNSHOTS]
Get out of there Johnny!
Let's go!
[POLICE SIRENS BLARE]
Get out of here!
[CAR ENGINE]
I can't believe
they got Johnny.
Oh, I believe it.
Besides,
it's no skin off my back.
It couldn't have
worked out better,
except that D.A. is still alive.
Johnny's not the marksman
everyone thought he was.
He just doesn't look the type.
Oh Honey, they rarely do.
No.
No, there's something else
going on here.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
I, uh.
I'm no lawyer, but,
this... this is like a huge,
big way no-no. Isn't it? I mean.
I managed to hold on
to at least one bullet
for forensics this time.
So, I get why me.
But why you?
I don't follow.
Your record's clean.
Even your credit report
is spotless.
That's a crime now.
This might not even be you.
You're bright enough
for identity theft.
Okay. Well. Quiz me.
- School?
- Wharton. M.B.A.
- Undergrad?
- Wake Forest.
- Parents?
- Both deceased.
Violent crime.
What are you doing, neck deep,
in the Torino cesspool?
Max adopted me when I was...
No, no. I read your file.
I want answers.
What happened to you?
This might be news
to you, but...
You know, my family
might look good on paper,
but they worked
for the Torinos, too.
And you never learned
from their mistakes?
I didn't have much choice
in the matter.
Oh, you always have a choice.
You wouldn't understand.
I said I'm sorry and I meant it.
Back up! Back up!
Okay. Okay.
So you said you were sorry.
And that's going
to make it all better?
Aren't you Christians
supposed to forgive and forget?
Forgiveness doesn't eliminate
the consequences.
As a man sows,
so shall he reap.
Good old Paul, hunh?
Yeah.
You may know your bible,
but you're obviously a stranger
to its author.
We've still got two witnesses
we need to get to.
You get their locations yet?
Not yet. They sunk them
deep into Witness Protection.
Remember that cheating-spouse,
car-jacking hit
I did as a favor
a few months back?
I think it's about time
I called in that chit.
I am done playing with you.
This is your chance.
You can wipe the slate clean
and start a new life.
We've never lost any Witness.
All you have to do
is testify,
and agree to a polygraph.
That's it.
You're just not listening to me.
You don't have to wait months
for a murder trial.
Do you have a pen?
All right, look.
Anthony, he runs a private
sub-s corporation.
Nets him
millions and millions of
dollars.
All right. You can
easily nail him on tax evasion.
Basically, the money comes in
dirty over here,
and comes out cleaned, sourced
and seasoned over here.
Great.
What about Max, Vince?
You're going to have to help us
take down the entire family.
JOHNNY: No. Look, I've given you
Anthony and that's more,
more than enough
to warrant my freedom.
I mean, he's the most
dangerous to you,
and everyone else;
and you know that.
What is this,
honor among thieves?
Max was like a father to me.
What do you mean "was"?
Is.
He's going.
But you're willing to
turn in your brother.
Vince is the closest
thing I've had to a brother,
and I'm not giving you him.
Now Anthony, I'll give you him
on a silver platter.
You get to recoup all sorts of
tax-payer money.
Take the credit for it,
and I'm out of here.
So, you're the brains
in the family.
[HEART MONITOR BEEPS
RHYTHMICALLY]
You got any word
yet from Johnny?
VINCE: Not yet.
I got a couple of names
you can call to get him sprung.
Anthony seems to think
a little time in jail
might do him some good.
It's good medicine for Anthony,
not for Johnny.
I'm not dead yet.
I'm still calling the shots
here, you hear me.
VINCE: Yes, sir.
I'm in no hurry
to chase Anthony around
and cleaning up his mess anyway.
That's why we need Johnny
back here.
Make sure
Anthony
listens to him.
You get Johnny's back.
He's always had yours.
MAX: I've always been able
to count on you, Vince.
You can still count on me.
[FUNKY MUSIC]
That's not bad.
What about these guys?
JHONNY: What can I say?
You'll have to testify.
Testify? Why?
Come on. I've given you
everything.
SUSAN: He's right.
The family doesn't have to know
where the information came from
because
we can prove it all now.
Anthony Torino?
Who wants to know?
Mister Torino,
we're going to
have to place you under arrest.
I think you might have
your wires crossed,
My hearing isn't 'til
Monday morning.
You're under arrest
for racketeering,
bank fraud, forgery, extortion.
Okay.
How about you give me a moment
to say goodbye to my Pops.
He's not well. He
could pass away any time.
Make sure
there are no surprises.
Detective: Let's go.
Can I at least
get a little privacy?
[DOOR BANGS CLOSED]
[HEART MONITOR BEEPS
RHYTHMICALLY]
[SPOOKY MUSIC]
[SPOOKY MUSIC FADES OUT]
MAX: Anthony,
my son.
Your boy, Johnny,
turned on us, Pop.
He did this.
ANTHONY: I'm sorry.
ANTHONY: I'm sorry Pop.
MAX: Vince. Vince.
[HANDCUFFS CLICK]
MAX: Don't let
Anthony
kill Johnny too.
Make Anthony give
Johnny another chance.
You make him.
I promised Graham,
when he died in my arms,
to take care of Johnny.
Now you promise me.
VINCE: You have my word.
[HEART MONITOR STOPS
ALARMS SOUND]
ANTHONY: I need a crew.
Old-timers only. You understand?
FRANK: Only guys we've used
for years. Got it, Boss.
[CAR CRANKS AND SCREECHES OUT]
ANTHONY: You owe me
for taking care of that
problem you had.
I don't want to hear any
more excuses, you understand?
You get their identities and
locations to Vince, pronto;
because
whether I'm in here or I'm out,
I can always reach you.
GUARD: Your dad died.
Told you I'd be seeing you soon.
You take care of that business,
or else.
ELIZABETH : I'll take the
bar all over again,
in whatever state
you put me in.
Susan : We can't, Liz.
That's the first thing
they'll look for.
We're protecting you.
Give this new life a fair
chance.
[THEME MUSIC]
[THEME MUSIC FADES OUT]
[GUNSHOTS]
[SHEEP BLEET]
ELIZABETH: This good for you.
Tell Joe I said "hello", okay?
You could to go try them on.
ELIZABETH: Anyone
know who this is?
CHILD: Noah.
Yep, that's Noah.
So,many years went by after God
made people.
Many families lived
in the world,
but most of them
did not obey God.
But Noah obeyed God.
Police Officer: Unit
fifty-three arriving
at Wise Funeral Home...
supervised visitation by inmate
Anthony Torino.
[CHANTING FUNERAL DIRGE]
[CHANTING FUNERAL DIRGE
FADES OUT]
FUNERAL HOME DIRECTOR:
I'm sorry for your loss.
I'll give you a few minutes.
FUNERAL HOME DIRECTOR:
It's time.
[GUNSHOT]
ANTHONY: No witnesses this time.
[CHAINS CLANK ON FLOOR]
ANTHONY: Go! Go! Go!
[CAR CRANKS AND SCREECHES OUT]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
VINCE: Any last words?
JOHNNY: Just two: thank you.
Don't take
all the fun out of this.
Vince, if I knew my life
was going to come to this,
I would have let Anthony
get away with murder.
I mean, a fricking sheep farmer!
Are you kidding me!
VINCE: -Beg for your life!
JOHNNY: -I would,
if I had one!
There's a difference between
being alive and barely living.
VINCE: Look who's getting all
philosophical.
JOHNNY: Well,
despite the circumstances.
VINCE: Good to see you.
You're not very good at
this, huh?
JOHNNY: Not really.
VINCE: Max was really
hurt by your betrayal.
JOHNNY: I didn't betray
him and he knows that.
VINCE: How do you figure?
JOHNNY: I said I would do what's
best for the family,
and that's what I did.
VINCE: It wasn't in
Anthony's best interests.
Anthony's not what's
best for the family,
and you know that.
I had no choice.
- You always have a choice.
- Not any that I wanted.
No one ever said life is fair.
Now look who's getting
all philosophical.
Vince, I wanted out.
I wanted to just,
I don't know, start a new life.
VINCE: But you can't.
Nah.
I can't.
But I can
give you your old one back.
Now that sounds tempting.
I never thought it would,
but it does.
Anthony will shoot me on sight.
But with him in jail,
Max can pull rank.
Give me another shot.
Don't get much news out
here, do you?
- What do you mean?
- Max wanted just that.
Give you another shot.
That was his dying wish.
Or should I say,
before Anthony
put him out of his misery.
You're the best, Johnny.
I need you.
I know where the D.A.'s hidden.
JOHNNY: All right. Well,
let me have another chance.
Kind of blew up in your
face the last time, didn't it.
JOHNNY: I know.
Please.
VINCE: All right.
Here's the D.A.
Uh oh, Karen, we're running
low on these sandwiches.
Brussels sprouts.
People keep giving us
Who eats Brussels sprouts?
ELIZABETH: Brussels sprouts.
KAREN: No.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[CRATE CLACKS ON FLOOR]
KAREN: Erin, you okay?
ELIZABETH: Yeah I'm
No, I'm fine.
You sure?
I'm okay.
I'll get this.
Ooh, this one's heavy.
[DOOR CREEKS OPEN]
[BOARDS CREEK UNDERFOOT]
I'm losing my mind.
[FOOTSTEPS]
JOHNNY: Shhhh.
Have you seen Erin?
Have you? Erin?
ELIZABETH: SQUEALS
JOHNNY: Shhhh.
Get in!
Erin?
Erin!
Somebody call the police.
They just took Erin.
[TAP ON WINDOW]
[FOLDER HITS TABLE]
Forty years.
Forty years in WITSEC,
we haven't lost one
single witness.
Now you're telling me what?
We've got two,
in the last few days.
Look, I know
she was a friend of yours.
Is.
Is a good friend, Mike.
And this,
is Johnny Graham,
another witness who disappeared
yesterday.
He's worked for the
Torinos for years.
Second generation,
as a matter of fact.
Thank you, Susan.
I read the history report.
Then you should know he's
probably the one who kidnapped
Elizabeth.
Mike: Yeah.
Well, how'd he find
out where she was?
Because I'm telling you right
now, if they've
hacked into our system,
then God help us.
We can do without his help.
We have over seventeen
thousand people in WITSEC.
Now those people gave up
their lives to help us out.
Now someone here tell me
that that's not all compromised.
You're blowing this
way out of proportion.
Both disappearances
are linked the Torino case.
It has everything to do
with that family.
I want the names of every person
that has accessed the file
- on both those two.
- We have one
safeguard on top of another.
Well, how's that working?
Not too good, huh.
Get those other two witnesses
in a safe house.
- And get Marshal Stark on this.
- Oh, come on. Not Stark.
He's the best eighteen-eleven
we've in the field.
And if this isn't a special op,
I don't know what is.
Well, now people!
[TRAIN HORN SOUNDS
AND CROSSING BELLS DING]
[CAR SCREECHES AROUND CORNER]
Hey. Hey.
Stay calm now. Stop. Stop.
Please, just let me out.
- Look.
- Let me out I promise I won't
- Shhhh.
- ...press any charges.
Look.
Just tell me
where Chris and Angela are.
Okay? Okay? Look!
[PLASTIC TIE SNAPS OFF]
- Please.
- No.
No. What? You would have
been dead twice,
twice if it wasn't for me.
I've, I, I mean I
saved you.
-You saved me!
-Yeah.
If you wasn't such a lousy shot,
I'd be dead!
You tried to kill me!
I can shoot a fly off a bottle.
I, uh. I never had
any intention of ever,
ever killing you.
Why on earth would I let
you trip that alarm.
They found you once,
and they can find you again.
You're a lot safer with
me than you are with them.
I swear to God, you'd better
just trust me.
Don't swear to God.
I'm sorry.
I didn't,
I didn't want to do this.
[CAR HISSES TO A STOP]
[CAR DOORS SLAM SHUT]
- You know how to fix a car?
- Do you know how to fix a car.
No. I'm an accountant.
[TRUCK RUMBLES TO A STOP]
- Come on.
- What?
[COUNTRY MUSIC TWANGS]
Hi, Mam. How you doing tonight?
CASHIER: Fine, thanks.
How about you?
I'm good. I'm good. Quiet.
CASHIER: It is
very quiet in here.
Quiet in here tonight.
Yeah.
Peanuts.
I love peanuts.
How, how much is this.
Cashier: Twelve dollars.
- Saint Christopher.
- Yeah, patron St of travelers.
How much for uh, peanuts?
Cashier: Three ninety-eight.
DAN: You Catholic?
Southern Baptist,
but I've got friends and uh,
we're kind of traveling.
- That your car out there?
- Yes.
It doesn't look
like you're going very far.
No, hunh.
You need a lift?
Yes.
Yes, that would be great.
I'd really appreciate that.
All right. I can handle that.
ELIZABETH: You coming?
DAN: Which way you two headed?
JOHNNY: Oh, anywhere but here.
DAN: I've hear that before.
[TRUCK ENGINE HUMS]
[TRAVELING MUSIC]
JOHNNY: Look, they got to the
D.A. before I even got there.
Do you have
the locations of the others?
Look, I'll start heading
in that direction right now.
Just call me when you get the
addresses for the other ones.
Okay, yeah.
Well, we'll probably be in
Charlotte by tomorrow evening.
[FIST SLAMS ON TABLE]
JOHNNY: I'll probably be in
Charlotte by tomorrow evening,
I hitched a ride with a
truck driver.
Yeah, all right, man.
All right. Be cool Bye. Bye.
Let me use your phone.
Not if you're calling WITSEC.
WITSEC is a federal program.
I worked for the state.
We can't trust anyone
right now. When are you going
understand that?
I don't know
where the others are at.
But if you'd let me
use your phone
to make one phone call, I can
probably get that information.
Just let me use your phone.
Hey. No grabby-grabby.
I'm going to bed.
- Maybe you should...
- Don't talk to me.
- Don't talk.
- Talk.
Don't talk to me.
MIKE: Hey. How you holding up?
SUSAN: I've had better days.
Any word on our missing couple?
SUSAN: Not yet.
Stark says he's on it but he's
pulling his usual lone ranger,
keeping everybody in the dark.
You got any news?
Yeah.
We found
a back door into the database.
Lets you switch users
and completely bypass  the
fingerprint and retina scans.
Brilliant. Lowest bidder
contracted that software. Tssst.
MIKE: Well, according
to our computer log,
every single user in the office
has accessed the files
on those four witnesses,
including myself and you.
- How is that possible?
- Well, it's complicated.
But if you've a user name,
a password and
you know what you're doing,
you can pull it off.
Cover your tracks.
Well then it would have to be
someone higher up.
MIKE: Yeah.
Someone like you.
Yeah. That's funny.
Don't be surprised if somebody
else's answering my phone
the next time you call me,
though.
It's only paranoia if
someone's not really after you.
Yeah, we've both made our
fair share of enemies.
Just call me, if you get
something, all right.
Be a whole lot easier to do
if I were in charge.
I know. You've made your
point. Just watch your back.
What's that? Tire
tracks in the sand.
DAN: Yeah.
Reminds me that He's
always with us,
even in the worst of times.
Even when we
think we're on our own and,
I've been there before.
So I don't know how things can
be so bad for you Johnny
with this lovely
lady on your arm.
Oh, no. No. We're,
we're not together.
Ha! You could have fooled me.
You're already at the
bickering stage.
Don't tell me
you skipped the make-up sex.
What's the fun in that? Heh-heh.
[TRUCK ENGINE REVS]
[TRUCK BRAKES HISS]
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
DOOR SLAMS SHUT
DAN: Heh-heh-heh. Women.
You know what? Order me the big
breakfast 'cause
I've just got
to check the load, okay.
All right, I'll be right there.
And get the coffee.
[DOOR LATCH JINGLES]
[DAN POUNDS ON A BOX]
DAN: Matt. Matt,
do you need anything?
- The fresh air is nice, man.
- Okay, we've got two more stops
before we get there.
Nah. No, I think, I think
I'm good.
Got a minute? Want to show
you something cool.
Check this out. I was
watching this sci-fi movie,
totally not when I was working.
And, so, I had
a lot of time on my hands.
And, I whipped this up, right.
You can put this
here. You can put it...
DAN: Matt, you work on that.
ELIZABETH: He's
sure got us all wrong, huh?
[COUNTRY MUSIC TWANGS]
You know what?
I really think
weshould start trusting
each other.
Do you?
Yes, I do.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm gonna make the first move,
because I'm that kind of guy.
Please,
don't make me regret this.
I mean it.
Oh, I see him.
Yeah, back there.
Where are you? What's
going on? Are you okay?
Listen, I only have a minute so
you've to do me a favor.
Would you please pick up Chris
and Angela for me.
I need you to do it personally,
though.
I can't do it. I'm out of it.
Special ops had been
assigned to the case now.
How come they haven't gotten
in touch with you. Where're you?
Ah...
I don't know. We're traveling on
the road somewhere.
"We're"?
Are you with Johnny?
Whoever you're with, can
you trust them?
Well, we don't ever really know
who we can trust, right?
Yeah, well. Good point.
We've got some trust issues
going on ourselves around here.
ELIZABETH: My travel companion
hasn't earnedmy trust yet.
But I'm kind of
between a rock and a hard place.
Yeah, well,
speaking
of your travel companion,
ballistics came back with the
slug from your shoulder.
It matches Johnny Graham's gun.
- Well, yeah.
- But that's not what's weird.
It also matches
the slug that killed the perp
who tried to kill you.
No, you mean
the one that I killed?
Well, that's what
I'm saying. You didn't kill him.
Your slug was pulled from his
leg. His kill shot,
that came
from the same gun that shot you.
[ALARM SIREN BLARES]
JOHNNY: Aaah.
[GUNSHOT]
GOON: Finish the job.
[GUNSHOTS]
ELIZABETH: But that doesn't make
any sense.
If you can't
pick up Chris and Angela,
can you at least tell me
where they are?
Okay. Are you ready?
Write this down as you know.
DAN: I am the Lord your God.
I'm holding your hand,
so don't be afraid.
I'm here to help you.
Hmmph. Isaiah,
forty-one, thirteen, right?
Right as rain.
If only that were true.
I could sure use
a helping hand right now.
You never know
where you might find an angel.
DAN: Heh-heh-heh.
Well, uh. Do you think you could
take us by there?
DAN: Ha. Heh-hee.
Ah, you two are funny.
All right. It's on the way.
["NO WAY OUT" PLAYS]
DAN : You mind
if I ask you a question?
What happened to you?
JOHNNY: What do you mean?
DAN: Well, you know
your bible so well.
But it is obvious
that at some point in your life,
you lost faith.
Yeah. That type of bitterness
doesn't come from apathy.
DAN: How did God let you down?
ELIZABETH: And when?
JOHNNY: Come on.
Isn't it obvious?
Look, I lost both of my parents.
I was left with the Torinos.
Tell me, what kind of
God lets that happen?
No! I get it.
My parents were brutally
murdered in front of me,
and the guy that
did it, he's as free as a bird.
So, yeah. I've had
my struggles with faith,
with our legal system.
But my faith
sees me through.
DAN: There's truth in that.
JOHNNY: Let everyone
else let us down so why not
give God another chance
to fail, hunh.
ELIZABETH: Or see us through.
[ELIZABETH TAPS ON WINDOW]
DAN: All right.
Here we are. Motel, right here.
[TRUCK BRAKES HISS]
ELIZABETH: Well,
why don't you get some rest.
Hey, um, this is
room twenty-three.
Can you
please send a taxi?
Yep, ten
minutes is fine. Thank you.
Hey, come on.
I'll be back in like,
twenty minutes, okay.
JOHNNY: Come on.
Come on. You don't have to go.
I can do this. I'm okay.
Why don't you stay
here because I can handle it.
I don't understand why
nobody picked up Chris.
Or it's a setup
or they're watching the place.
Whatever it is,
I'd feel a lot better
if he was here, like, with us.
ANGELA: Poor kid.
I mean, first his parents,
now this.
- I'm coming with you.
- Well, I'm staying right here.
- Will you lock the door?
- Yeah.
- Don't leave.
- I won't.
We need to hit a store where
we can get some fake blood.
[DOOR LOCK CLACKS]
[PEBBLE CLACKS ON WINDOW]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Well, is this your stuff?
[DOOR RATTLES SHUT]
CHRIS: What are you
guys doing here?
Our locations've
been compromised.
We have to get out of here now.
So we'll just grab this.
Wait. Didn't you shoot her?
- Yeah, he did.
- Whatever.
But we think
he's with us now. We think.
Let's just go.
What am I using
to tie him up with?
JOHNNY: Just use this right
here.
ANGELA: Watching myself get
strangled is creepy.
You're sick, you know that?
Well, you know what, you've got
to know your audience.
ANGELA: What is that?
JOHNNY: Oh this.
You don't want to know.
Pssst. I'm sorry.
[GUNSHOT]
Stay down. Stay down.
You'll have help soon,
okay. I'm sorry.
Why didn't you just
kill me that night?
What?
I mean,
it would have been
a lot easier for you.
Look, I could never hurt you.
[MUTED SQUEELING]
Hey Vinnie.
Johnny finally
did something right.
Looks like he'd fun with her
before he actually did her in.
A little over the top,
if you ask me.
It's messy. Unnecessary.
Yeah, but you got to admit, it's
not bad for a first-timer.
You know, maybe Pops made the
right call after all, hunh.
[DAN CHUCKLES.]
DAN: You're full of surprises.
Yeah, well. Chris,
this is Dan.
Dan, this is Chris. He's our...
- How are you, Chris?
- ...extra passenger.
- Pretty good, and you?
- I'm good.
CHRIS: Good.
Well, let's go for a ride.
["NO WAY OUT" PLAYS]
["NO WAY OUT" FADES OUT]
ELIZABETH: Thanks for taking us
all over Timbuktu.
You didn't have to do that.
DAN: Just another day
at the office, Darling.
Hey. I am so glad to see you.
[POLICE CAR SIRENS]
How did you know?
Is this a setup?
[TRUCK DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
I see you've met Stark.
JOHNNY: What?
DAN: Dan Stark, U.S. Marshal.
Dan Stark. Sorry for the
charade.
We thought you're
better off on the run.
We knew where you were. We knew
where you were headed.
I came along for the ride to
make sure you get there.
Gave me a better idea
whose side you're on.
With us all along, huh.
Matt, I've got a job for you.
See, we weren't as out in the
cold as you thought, huh.
Yeah, right. Like you knew.
- He's been a challenge.
- Yeah.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[CAR DOORS SLAM SHUT]
JOHNNY: You sure
this is a good idea?
[TRUCK ENGINE REVS]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[CAR HORN BLOWS]
BRIAN: All right. Come on.
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[POTS AND PANS CLANG]
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Did you frisk
him? Did you frisk him?
WAYNE: I think he's clean.
Whoa, whoa. Get on him!
Fool! Get away.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
PHIL: Get up!
DAN: Ok.
PHIL: Get in the chair!
DAN: Back up.
Nice work, Boys.
So Johnny.
Who's our new friend here?
U.S. Marshal, Dan Stark.
PHIL: It's good to have you
back, Johnny.
What are you doing?
Payback, Man.
putting my accounting
skill to good use,
counting sheep.
Payback.
This how you pay us back
after we protected you.
JOHNNY: Some protection.
What did you expect me to do?
- Die.
- Oh. Ooh. Scary.
Maybe Johnny's learned
the error of his ways.
We came up with
a mutually beneficial way
Johnny could prove himself.
DAN: How's he going to do so
to a maggot like you?
PHIL: Whoa!
PHIL: Get him up.
[DAN THUDS TO FLOOR]
By eliminating
Anthony's remaining witnesses.
I assume you got
another video for me.
Anthony so enjoyed
the first one.
Here you go.
[LAUGHING]
[CLEARING HIS THROAT]
VINCE: Hold on, Phil.
You feel like proving yourself
to all of us here?
Sure.
Here you go, Johnny.
I'm sorry.
[GUNSHOT]
Clean that up.
Good job, Johnny.
PHIL: Get the other side, Brian.
[ITALIAN MUSIC IN BACKGROUND]
JOHNNY: Phil's ego
has gotten as big as his gun.
FRANK: Don't cross him.
We can't lose you again.
WAYNE: The cops've really been
busting our chops lately.
Cleaning us out.
You're sure there's no mole?
Of course there is.
The question is, who?
[ITALIAN MUSIC FADES OUT]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Hey. Hey! Where's Vince?
I don't know!
I don't know where Vince is!
Go find him.
[PHIL GRUNTS]
You've seen Vince?
Well, yeah.
He's right here.
Phil needs him.
He got shot.
JOHNNY: What? Phil got shot?
WAYNE: Shot.
JOHNNY: Hey, hey.
Phil got shot.
Take care of this guy.
VINCE: What happened?
And Brian?
Brian was F.B.I. Aaah.
VINCE: I knew we had a mole.
But Brian was family!
Well, who shot you?
Brian. I was driving that
Marshal's body to the dumpster.
Brian just pulls
a gun on me.
He said,
drive him to the hospital.
I guess he thought
he could be saved or something.
He's an optimist.
Who knew.
PHIL: Well, we were
driving down this side street
and I noticed he didn't have
his seat belt on,
so I gunned it.
Slammed into a dumpster.
Brian goes flying
through the windshield.
Good riddance, hunh.
CHRIS: Oh yeah.
First my family, now me.
JOHNNY: God!
[GUNSHOTS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
ANTHONY: Wow.
You're quite the auteur, Johnny.
Hey, Anthony.
JOHNNY: I know
where the D.A. is.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Good.
- Oh.
Get him off me.
JOHNNY: I guess I deserved that.
I guess the feds fell for
your and Vince's trick.
Yeah, they bought it.
Good.
So, where is she?
JOHNNY: She's at the City View
apartments on Chipley.
But the place
is crawling with Marshals.
I don't care if she's guarded
by a squadron of marines.
VINCE: Our source's getting
squirrelly.
All we've got is Johnny's intel.
It's enough for me.
Don't roll out
the red carpet just yet.
Killing some witnesses
doesn't erase the fact
that he sold me out
to save his own skin.
He took out that Marshal.
Three days ago
I'd have killed you.
What?
Did all that time
in prison reform you, Anthony?
Being in charge changes
how you look at things.
I got to respect Pop's
final wish. After all,
if it wasn't for his death,
I'd still be in prison.
But it still
doesn't change the fact
that someone hasn't paid
for their disrespect.
Yeah.
JOHNNY: She will.
Relax, Johnny.
She will. Vince, I need a word.
[JOHNNY LAUGHS]
VINCE: I still feel
we're rushing things.
I don't want to give
them time to move her.
There's no way Brian
got a warning call off.
You're the boss.
You want her back here alive?
Yeah.
I want to watch Johnny
finish the job he botched.
And if he doesn't?
I guess I'll have a really
big decision on my hands.
Which one of them
do I kill first.
[CAR SCREECHES TO A STOP]
[CAR DOORS SLAM SHUT]
[SHOTGUN COCKS]
ANTHONY: There you are,
Elizabeth.
[ANTHONY GRUNTS]
[PHONE KEYS BEEP]
[ANTHONY HANGS UP]
[ANTHONY GRUNTS]
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS ON STAIRS]
Susan.
ELIZABETH: Susan!
JOHNNY: That's it.
She's in there.
[DOOR BURSTS OPEN]
ELIZABETH: No. No.
It's me. It's okay.
[SIGHS]
SUSAN: Geez. That's a way
to get your head blown off.
ELIZABETH: Where were you?
CAL: Nobody's here.
VINCE: Impossible.
What the heck, Johnny?
JOHNNY: I don't know.
FBI AGENT: F.B.I. Freeze!
Don't move.
[SHOTGUN COCKS]
Put your hands
on top of your head.
Please give me an excuse.
Maybe another day.
[SHOTGUNS COCK]
What's that?
A sting operation
I just found out about.
Get your stuff.
I'm getting you out of here.
SUSAN: Move it!
[HANDCUFFS CLICK]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hello Vince.
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
How are you, Vince?
I'm curious.
I really would love to know
how that you figured out
the identities and locations
of the witnesses who were going
to testify against Anthony.
Are you charging me
with something?
DAN: 27 felonies,
from murder to extortion.
VINCE: Only 27?
I guess my sources are a little
more thorough than yours.
Well, I can,
be happy to refine
the list for you.
So, let's see. We had 27,
this will be 28, right?
Vince?
You have something we want.
And what is that?
How about we take
the death penalty off the table.
Life in prison, hunh?
I'll pass.
Before you go
play mister negotiator,
will you just
humor me for a second?
How the hell is it that I see
a bullet pass right through you,
and yet, here you sit?
You were treated to a special
effects show compliments
of the United States
Marshal's office.
Not bad, hunh.
[VINCE CHUCKLES]
Looks like I need
a better support staff.
What's it gonna be?
You going to take the deal?
I'm going to roll the dice with
your defective court system.
So, when you get a deal
that's worth chewing on...
you know where to find me.
You're going to regret that.
Every moment of that.
Because when
you're sitting on death row,
it's not a happy place.
So, who was it? Was it Johnny?
Was it Brian? Was it Julian
that betrayed us? All of them?
You first.
ANTHONY: You listen to me.
No more excuses. No more lies.
You deliver Johnny and
that D.A. in the next two hours
or you're dead. Period.
You understand me?
And trust me,
it won't be quick or painless.
ELIZABETH: What you did
was incredibly brave.
And though I hate to admit it,
and
I've completely forgiven you;
the thought of me shooting you
puts a smile on my face,
still.
Oh, wow. So,
you're thinking of me too, hunh?
Oh, so, you do have a sense
of humor after all. Okay.
Ah, well, you know.
It's just one of the many, many,
many fine qualities that
make me the perfect catch.
Oh. Aw, come on.
You're still trying
to pick me up after all this?
You know what they say.
There's a thin line
between love and hate.
- Hunh.
- Yeah. But,
I think most people start with
like and
then they move to love and,
That's at least before
hate and stalking and
trying to kill each other.
I'm dyslexic.
I do everything backwards.
ELIZABETH: You do.
I mean it can only
go up from here, right?
SUSAN: Aah, I do believe
a "thank you" is in order.
Enh. Well,
just doing your job.
Come on. I've got
a surprise for you two.
Just a little token
of our gratitude.
JOHNNY: Cool.
ELIZABETH: Okay.
DAN: Fifteen years.
Got it. Right.
[PHONE CLICKS SHUT]
[DOOR CLICKS OPEN]
What have you got
for me now?
A generous offer
by anyone's standards.
Twenty-five years
in a fine federal facility.
VINCE: Hmm-hmm. Well,
they do have good food.
Weight room, libraries. But
I'd wind up being an old man.
[PHONE RINGS]
[MUMBLING IN BACKGROUND]
PHIL: Sure. Sure.
[DOOR CLICKS OPEN]
PHIL: Okay. Sure.
[PHIL HANGS UP THE PHONE]
[PHIL TAPS ON WINDOW]
A fine federal facility.
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[RELAXING MUSIC]
JOHNNY: In all those years,
I never knew Phil was F.B.I.
SUSAN: Well, that's
what we call being undercover.
SUSAN: Surprise!
JOHNNY: What is this place?
SUSAN: It's a humble little
abode we seized from a drug lord
a couple of weeks ago.
You'll be sequestered here
until we get you new identities.
JOHNNY: Well, how long?
SUSAN: Just a few weeks.
- Okay.
- Where's our protection?
Marshal Stark's coming in
with some deputies.
ELIZABETH: Do we have
to go back into WITSEC?
Half the Torinos are either
dead or they're locked up.
SUSAN: Honey,
Anthony is still missing.
Even if we were to pick him up
and bring him in,
he's still going
to have a hit on you.
Come on. This is the only way.
ELIZABETH: Wow.
JOHNNY: Ah, it beats
a sheep farm.
[SUSAN'S PHONE RINGS]
SUSAN: Hello. Yeah,
we just got here.
DAN: Yeah. This ain't
my first rodeo, pal.
This ain't my first rodeo.
[DAN SLAMS PHONE DOWN]
DAN: Five years.
PHIL: Tssst. No.
[DOOR OPENS]
This has got to be
your lucky day. Ten years.
Consider that a gift
from the U.S. Attorney's Office.
One that I'm going
to return, unopened.
[DAN'S CELL PHONE RINGS]
Agent Steen.
He's in an interrogation.
What?
Five years.
It doesn't get any better.
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
- Phil.
- Well, actually, it's Joe.
Susan Anderson,
she's their mole.
She's got Johnny and Elizabeth.
Get someone over to China Grove.
Call the local authorities.
You, son.
I'm finished with you.
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
[CAR ENGINE SPUTTERS]
Geez.
JOHNNY: Oh my Gosh.
This is nice.
- Aw, is this from Susan?
- I don't know.
[JOHNNY SNICKERS]
ELIZABETH: Please, look. Look.
Look. Look. We have a pool!
JOHNNY: Nice. You sit down.
I'm going to crack open
that bottle.
- So, a sheep farmer, hunh?
- Yeah...
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Johnny.
Your little boyfriend
decided to take a nap.
Finally got you all
to myself, Elizabeth. Hmmph.
[JOHNNY YELLS]
[SCREEN DOORS CLACK OPEN]
[JOHNNY GRUNTS]
[ANTHONY GRUNTS]
[ELIZABETH SCREAMS]
Help! Johnny!
[ANTHONY AND ELIZABETH SCREAM]
[ANTHONY GRUNTS
AND ELIZABETH SCREAMS]
[ANTHONY SCREAMS]
[ELIZABETH SCREAMS]
MATT: Remember me? Geeky rookie.
Yeah, they give us guns too.
Sorry I broke your car.
Actually not, because you're
kind of evil. Put these on.
[POLICE CAR SIRENS]
Come on. It'll match your shirt.
[POLICE RADIOS SOUND OFF]
POLICE RADIO: 1 11 1 10.
Get her out of here.
POLICE RADIO: Roger...
Look what we've got now.
Another friend. Hi, pal.
ANTHONY: That badge make you
a man? Hunh. Does it?!
- Talk your way out of this one.
- I can't get to you!
ELIZABETH: Susan.
SUSAN: Elizabeth.
I'm so sorry.
I never meant to hurt you.
No. Wait.
DAN: She betrayed you.
She betrayed you.
It was payback to Anthony
for taking out her husband.
And his lover, the boss's wife.
Hell hath no fury
like a woman scorned.
Joe: How'd you know?
MATT: Because he's a Jedi.
He told me to follow Susan.
I still don't know why.
It was the look in her eye.
That day in the parking lot.
She's looking at her best friend
and she's so worried
about her best friend.
But in her eyes,
I saw guilt.
I didn't see relief. Let's go.
COURT CLERK: All rise.
Have you reached a verdict?
Yes, Your Honor. On the sole
count of the indictment,
murder in the first degree,
we find the defendant...
guilty.
JUDGE: It is the decision
of this court
that Anthony Torino
be given a life sentence,
without
the possibility of parole.
[JOYFUL TRUMPET-BASED MUSIC]
[GALLERY APPLAUDS]
[DOORBELL CHIMES]
JOHNNY: Coming.
- Ho-ho, Dan. Hey.
- How you doing, Johnny?
- Good.
- I've only got a second.
I just came
to see how you're doing.
- Come on in.
- All right.
JOHNNY: Making some tea.
You want some?
Yeah, I love sweet tea.
You know that.
JOHNNY: Yeah, so, uh. Has
everyone been relocated yet, or?
Yeah. We just put
the last one in place.
- How, uh, how you settling in?
- Good.
Actually, I did want to talk
to you about something.
Elizabeth. I mean,
we haven't seen each other.
I mean, can't we e-mail, Skype?
Why couldn't we
be relocated together?
DAN: Be realistic.
One of you make one mistake,
and you're both dead.
That's why we put the rules.
- Rules.
- I'm sorry.
Man. You know what?
No one understands us
like we understand each other.
That month we spent
together. It rocked.
If it hadn't been for you,
many things'd have turned out
differently for many people.
It's not like
I really had a choice.
DAN: Oh, you had a choice.
And you made the right choice
every single time.
And if no one else
will come in here and tell you,
then I will.
Thank you.
Thank you. I, uh.
I'm telling you though, Dan,
I don't know if I was the one
making all the choices.
JOHNNY: There might've been
something, sort of, guiding us.
Maybe you could call it God.
You think you found redemption.
Redemption's a beautiful thing.
- I've really got to go.
- Okay
You take care of yourself, Adam.
Man,
I can't get used to that name.
Take care of yourself, too.
[DOORBELL CHIMES]
Hi. I'm Eve. I'm your new
neighbor. Nice to meet you.
[JOHNNY LAUGHS]
JOHNNY: Oh my God!
[SINGING] Love comes walking.
Love comes crawling.
Redemption of the soul
Brings a meaning to it all.
Children,
say it again, say it again.
[TRUCK CRANKS]
Children, say it again,
Oh, say it again, say it again.
Children, say it again.
Redemption of the soul
Brings a meaning to it all.
Children, say it again,
Oh, say it again, say it again.
Children, say it again.