[OPENING THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
WOMAN: Come with me, Guinevere.
GUINEVERE : They say
Britain's greatest age began
when Arthur pulled
the sword from the stone.
They got this story
only part right.
History is written by men.
And there is much in life
that they ignored.
WOMAN: Quickly, Guinevere.
GUINEVERE: Mama, mama!
[MOURNFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LABORED BREATHING]
GUINEVERE: My mother died
when I was five years old.
Such things as the passing of
the queen meant little then,
save to her little girl.
My father ruled a kingdom
in the midlands.
But the truth is...
throughout Britain,
only chaos truly reigned.
And so, like all
the other local kings,
my father was consumed
by constant wars.
Unable to raise me himself,
he sent me North
to the sanctuary
of the old religion.
I found I was not alone.
Many other future
Kings and queens
had been sent to
the sanctuary
for instruction.
But from the very first day,
I was singled out
for special attention
from the young priestess,
Morgan L'Fei.
MORGAN: Welcome, Guinevere.
GUINEVERE: In this company,
my childhood quickly passed.
[METAL CLANKING]
GUINEVERE: But among
the royal born, there
was a foundling.
A boy L'Fei had saved
from drowning.
Now grown to be
a fighter, and a leader...
Lancelot.
MAN: Guinevere.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[METAL CLANKING]
GUINEVERE: He was my hero.
He was my friend.
And from the time
I was a little girl,
I hoped he would
become something more.
GUINEVERE: Do you
remember your mother?
I have no mother.
Except for L'Fei.
She fished you out of the lake.
GUINEVERE: Someone had
to have thrown you in?
[WATER TRICKLING]
There was a time
I brooded on that.
That time has passed.
I will never forsake you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MERLIN: I come seeking
Britain's high priestess.
LANCELOT: Morgan L'Fei
is the high priestess.
MERLIN: Tell her I bring word...
of the new high king.
GUINEVERE: We knew nothing
of a new high king.
Isolated in the north,
we heard little from
the rest of Britain.
So when the rare traveler
came, we eagerly gathered
to hear the news.
And though we did not know
the old pilgrim's name,
we were fascinated by
the story that he told.
All save for our priestess,
Morgan L'Fei.
PILGRIM: And then
in a churchyard...
a huge stone appeared.
A stone...
with a sword...
embedded in it,
upto its radiant hilt.
And on the stone was
emblazoned the words,
"Who so pulleth
forth this sword,
"is high king.
"And shall bring greatness."
When all those
battling monarchs,
blustered along...
and came and tried,
[LAUGHS]
[DRAMATICALLY] Huh, Ohh, Uh...
But it was a boy.
It was a boy of 15...
who succeeded.
He pulled out the sword.
A boy raised in a cave,
away from the world,
raised by the mage...
Merlin...
servant to his father.
For it was Arthur Pendragon,
who pulled out the sword.
Son of Uther.
And he is now Britain's...
new crowned king.
Morgan: Then there is peace
across this blighted island?
There will be.
The king, Arthur, has sworn it.
And has he sworn on
his foul conception?
His father raped another
man's wife to bring him forth.
I do none speak more of Igraine
and her murdered husband.
Many are disinclined to
argue with a miracle.
Others are learning not to
argue with Arthur's sword.
GUINEVERE: Maybe L'Fei knew
something we did not.
I thought the unnamed pilgrim
had come by chance,
and that it was an accident
when he found me alone
by the water.
But as we talked,
I began to feel that there
was a purpose to everything
this stranger did.
GUINEVERE: Also Healing,
Geography,
History, and Latin.
I study Mathematics
and science on my own.
Why?
So I may rule my kingdom wisely.
A fearless king and
a mighty army will
do that for you.
Kings and armies have
not done it wisely so far.
Indeed.
They dominate...
Breeding cruelty and resentment.
True government
requires equality,
shared prosperity,
and trust.
So, you too have designs
on the whole of Britain?
My kingdom alone provides
all the challenge I need.
Mm-mmm, what kingdom is that?
Camelot.
[LAUGHING] Camelot!
I've never heard of it.
It must be quite
an insignificant little dot.
Insignificant?
It is the only kingdom
to spare in all Britain.
It controls all movement
North and South.
The Romans wanted it
and never took it.
Look...
We drew the line
the legions never crossed.
Above us, fierce tribes
still keep to the old ways.
Below us, the madness,
the empire, and Uther.
Left...
trading routes shattered,
holy groves laid waste,
the whole fabric of
community unraveled.
And in its place...
Chaos, and Christianity.
Oh, I think if he is
truly to rule all Britain,
this Arthur has
a lot of work to do.
I'll be sure to tell him.
MORGAN: What exactly is this?
MORGAN: Bo... Look at it!
[HORSE NEIGHING]
MORGAN: Sword in a stone?
The fatal phallus.
Trust a man to think that up!
BOY: But, isn't it
a miracle, lady?
MORGAN: Life is a miracle.
Birth!
Creation!
Have you learned nothing here?
But it's a wonderfully
heroic story.
[SARCASTICALLY] Thank you.
And are more heroes
what we need?
MORGAN: Men who stand tall on
the corpses of their victims?
There was a time...
When all Britain
celebrated the Goddess.
We celebrated the bounty
of this Earth.
The gifts she gave us.
And women lay with
her chosen ones,
and embraced them closely.
And we celebrated life...
MORGAN: That grew
within their wombs.
And now, we have heroes...
with bodies piled about them.
Those are the fruits of
the harvest they offer now.
Mens victories in blood
are what they celebrate.
And women's blood?
MORGAN: Once the sacred
symbol of our fertility
now make us what?
Guinevere?
Unclean.
MORGAN: And do you think
all this will change with
Arthur Pendragon?
Crowned in a Christian church
where the only God is male?
[EXHALES]
MORGAN: Worship heroes?
And you join those...
who have abandoned
this earth's beauty.
MORGAN: Worship Pendragon?
And you join those
who have traded life
for death.
MORGAN: You two...
Come to the sacred circle
at midnight.
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[HORSES NEIGHING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Kneel before the power
of the Goddess.
MORGAN: I have waited
a long while for this moment.
Now it is time you knew
what must be done.
MORGAN: Raise your left arm.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Lancelot.
You are my son...
though I plucked you from
the water, not from my womb.
MORGAN: Among boys,
you are a man.
MORGAN: Among men,
you will be king.
No warrior in this land
will defeat you.
You have the strength
to stop the night.
[DRUMS BEATING]
MORGAN: Wear this as a sign
of the covenant you have made.
And you, Guinevere...
Wise priestess...
When you become a woman,
you will rule the heart
of this green island.
No one can control Britain who
does not control your kingdom.
MORGAN: You have the power
to stop the night.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MORGAN: Wear this...
Even unto your grave.
The triple spiral...
The never ending cycle of birth,
and life, and death.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
MORGAN: Rise.
Our blood and power
are joined together.
Nothing can stop us now.
We will defeat Arthur Pendragon,
and rule Britain.
Are we going to make war?
We are already at war!
Don't you understand that?
Where are the women
in Pendragon's world?
Where is this Merlin's
mother, or his wife?
Where is Arthur's
mother or wife?
You said Igraine
was Arthur's mother.
Igraine was my mother first!
But Uther raped her.
MORGAN: He murdered
my father and he raped her.
Then he married her with
the bishop's blessing.
And he ordered me,
a nine year old child,
to be hanged.
GUINEVERE: But you live still.
I was hid here on condition
I never speak my true name,
and I have not.
MORGAN: For too many years
I have remained silent
while the forces of darkness
have run rampant in this land.
But when the Goddess sent you
both to me to be my children...
I began to see how I might
have my voice again.
MORGAN: King and Queen
you shall be.
First of Camelot,
then of all Britain.
All is ready.
Our people nearly
awake their leaders.
You will offer your next
blood to the Goddess.
And the first full moon after...
you shall lie with her.
MORGAN: And thus...
you shall both be wed.
Without my father's blessing?
Long ago, he abandoned you
to me.
MORGAN: And tonight I have
given you to the Goddess,
and to each other.
MORGAN: Your vows
are written in blood.
But it is my father's kingdom,
and what if he will
not accept this?
Then he will die.
And if you deny
your vow, Guinevere...
you will burn.
MORGAN: Just as
your offering did.
[BASS DRUM SOUNDING]
GUINEVERE: I'd sworn to wed
Lancelot when next I bled.
But I could not bring
myself to it without
my father's consent.
GUINEVERE: And so...
When my menses began I tried
to hide it from the world.
How long?
How many days has
it been, Guinevere?
It doesn't matter.
MORGAN: We can begin now.
BOY: Lady...
Riders have come from Camelot
seeking Guinevere.
MORGAN: If your
father is dead...
Then that solves everything.
[HORSE GALLOPING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BOYS CHATTING IN BACKGROUND]
GUINEVERE: Is my father...
MORGAN: Your father is well.
And sends his thanks
to the Goddess.
He simply wanted you home.
Then you must send me.
I said I would.
And I will send your
husband beside you.
MORGAN: And all the warriors
of the triple spiral as well.
Now you must fast and
prepare yourself for
the bride's blessing.
I will come for you
when the moon is high.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
GUINEVERE: I'll take
you to the stable.
GUINEVERE: Come on.
[METAL CLANKING]
[LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING]
[HORSES GALLOPING]
[HOSES NEIGHING]
[PANTING]
LANCELOT: You would leave
without saying goodbye to me?
[WHISPERING] I'm so sorry.
[EXHALES]
GUINEVERE: How could I get her
to this thing she wants?
You cannot marry me?
I cannot do it without
my father's knowledge.
I cannot make war on
the high king, Arthur,
without knowing
for what he stands.
Did you know she was
half sister to this Arthur?
No.
GUINEVERE: Did you know
what she had planned?
LANCELOT: NO.
Then come with me.
GUINEVERE: I'll tell my father
how much I love you.
If I can't have you,
I'll never wed.
I'm of unknown birth.
He won't think me worthy.
Then I'll renounce my crown.
And we can wander together free.
No.
Please, you cannot abandon
your obligation to your people.
And I cannot abandon mine.
Neither to the goddess
or to L'Fei.
You agree with her?
You can't imagine what
it's like to be drowning.
And then when someone
gives you your life back...
You remember it.
Then this is it?
I'll never again see you?
[EXHALES]
[CREAKING]
[HORSE NEIGHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
MORGAN: I order you to stay.
If you defy me,
the Goddess will despise you!
MORGAN: You'll be cursed.
And the dark ones
will possess your life.
No!
I think not, Morgan!
Stop her!
[HORSE GALLOPING]
[BIRD WHISTLING]
GUINEVERE: This place is darker
and sadder than I remember.
MAN: There is no joy
in preparing for war.
[DOOR OPENS]
GUINEVERE: Father?
Guinevere!
LEODOGAN: It has been so long.
So long.
And I must send you away again.
MAN: Not necessary.
MAN: I like this place.
MAN: I'm ready to stay here.
LEODOGAN: Malgin, King of Gal,
has come to seek your hand.
I seek this kingdom!
I will have it
through marriage,
or through war.
MALGIN: Marriage,
of course, will be...
MALGIN: Much more pleasant.
I'll leave you to
plan our wedding.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
GUINEVERE: Father, I come
to you out of obedience,
but I do not want
to marry that man.
I should hope not.
He's a cruel and
ambitious beast.
But the weeks have delayed...
Summoning you,
awaiting your arrival has
given us time to call on men,
and to manufacture arms.
Then this was all a game?
No.
Oh no, Guinevere.
There's no game.
Many thousand of lives will
be saved if you marry Malgin.
LEODOGAN: What they'd
be worth under him...
I cannot say.
Freedom is not easily claimed.
I had to leave
in a hurry, father,
you'll have to lend me
a sword.
Spoken like a true
queen of Camelot.
But I cannot let
you on the field.
I can wield a sword
as well as anyone...
I don't doubt it.
But you are the prize.
Malgin must not seize you.
Forward!
[MEN SCREAMING]
Camelot, and Guinevere!
[METAL CLANKING]
[GROANING]
[MAN GROANING]
[COUGHING]
[FLUTE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
[DOOR OPENS]
GUINEVERE: I will marry him.
Let there be
no more dying.
LEODOGAN: I will send a message.
MAN: My Lord,
visitors to see you.
We fight under no banner.
But we've heard of your
struggles with this ruffian,
and we've come to offer you aid.
I thank you.
But I'm on the verge
of surrendering.
Let us fight alone then.
Even we six can
do some damage.
No, I cannot allow that.
But I will stand with you,
together with what
remains of my army.
[HORSES NEIGHING]
MALGIN: Alone!
MALGIN: Battle line!
Battle line!
MAN: Line for battle!
Form a line!
[MEN SCREAMING]
[METAL CLANKING]
[SCREAMING]
[MOANING]
The king is dead.
Long live the Queen.
My father and I discussed
how we might repay you.
GUINEVERE: Anything
I have is yours.
Anything.
GUINEVERE: Even
the great castle
at Aiden.
On point of fact,
we're not much interested
in real estate.
MERLIN: What he needs is a wife.
[HORSES NEIGHING]
Will you have me, my lady...
as your husband?
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
How can I deny you?
I owe you more than my life.
MERLIN: How can you value
anything more than your
own life, my lady?
The life of my kingdom,
GUINEVERE: the men who
would have been slaughtered,
the women who would have
been taken had the enemy
not been stopped.
MERLIN: And so...
not knowing his name, or birth,
you will give to this
young boy your
maiden hand?
Nobility of heart is
more important than
nobility of birth.
If you are not entitled
to be King, then you shall
rule here as my consort.
And we shall be as
equals, you and I.
GAWAIN: I'm afraid not,
my lady.
Not quite as equals.
For you are Queen of Camelot,
but this man...
who'll be rolling you between
the sheets soon enough,
is Arthur Pendragon,
high king of Britain.
I wanted to win you
on merit, my lady.
That you did, my Lord.
[LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[FLUTE MUSIC PLAYING]
They call me Merlin.
GUINEVERE: So even you
just wanted my kingdom?
If we had wanted that,
we would have taken it by force.
MERLIN: Guinevere...
White shadow.
You have been chosen by me.
Chosen above all others
to be Arthur's queen.
MERLIN: And though
men desire you...
for your lands, and for your...
for your great beauty...
I have chosen you...
For your mind.
MERLIN: I raised Arthur.
I know his magnificence.
And I have made him
High king of Britain.
And I know his flaws.
And that the great challenges
are yet to come.
It's one thing to
conquer a country...
It's another to transform it.
MERLIN: But Britain
must be raised
from its bloody darkness...
into a land of peace,
and law.
Arthur can't do it.
Not alone.
And I...
I am an old man.
I had to find him someone
with the strength and wisdom,
to keep the promise.
MERLIN: And so...
I found him you.
It will not be an easy job.
But it is the one
you were born to do.
MERLIN: So...
Are you ready now...
to wed Arthur Pendragon?
[SOFTLY] Yes.
Are you a woman?
I have taken on the power of
those who bleed but do not die.
MERLIN: And are you pure?
[SNIFFLES]
I have fasted...
and bathed myself
in sacred ways.
Then...
The moon is full.
The Goddess awaits.
[WATER FLOWING]
GUINEVERE: Mother, this is
your daughter, Guinevere...
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
I know you still love me,
despite Morgan's hate.
Tonight, I will be
a child no longer.
As you turned from new,
to full,
to dark.
As all existence turns,
from birth,
to life,
to death.
I too turn...
from maiden to woman.
To be reborn again
in your image.
The source...
of life.
Aah!
[GROANING]
[METAL CLANKING]
ARTHUR: Guinevere!
Who taught you
to fight like that?
At the sanctuary...
I had a good instructor.
I'll say.
Malgin must've sent
these two cowards.
I'll have them dumped
back over his border.
ARTHUR: I haven't seen
a hilt like this before.
It balances the blade
much better than ours.
ARTHUR: I'll talk to Kei,
see if he can come up...
GUINEVERE: Morgan L'Fei!
Oh, God.
[EXHALES]
ARTHUR: You were right.
We shall rule as equals,
you and I.
[DOOR CREAKING]
GUINEVERE: This room has
been unused since I was five.
And now, finally, my
mother sleeps with
my father once again.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
I need not take you for
the first time while
you are in mourning.
But in the eyes of your
religion, we are not wed
until it is done.
All I know about this
is what I read in Ovid.
Well, it's easier lying
down for one thing.
I will try to be gentle...
and quick.
[TRUMPETS SOUNDING]
The king awaits...
his honor guard!
You worship
the white Christ,
Merlin?
Underneath the ritual...
it's all the same God.
Goddess!
[MERLIN LAUGHING]
I want to explain to you
about this coronation.
You may be pagan...
and worth pagan wealth.
But most of your kingdom...
is Christian.
The bishops will
run this coronation.
It's called, uh,
being queen,
to all the lands.
But if I do not
honor this God...
I make my vows to?
You honor the hope of peace.
To which they are made.
Your right to the crown...
perhaps, even to your life...
depends on this.
BISHOP: Merlin.
Merlin, we will speak with you.
My Lords.
MERLIN: Guinevere.
Arthur's bride.
BISHOP: Not in our eyes.
MERLIN: Perhaps you will
be able to rectify that
at the coronation.
The knife.
Remove it.
Arthur wears his sword.
He has said that we
will rule as equals.
An anointed queen
does not shed blood.
Let them have the knife,
Guinevere.
[FOOTSTEPS]
And now I'm supposed to
spread my hands and
let myself be killed?
MERLIN: You'll not go
unprotected here.
MERLIN: You'll have
your own champion.
A brave warrior,
sworn to protect you.
MERLIN: Just as Gawain
is sworn to Arthur.
GUINEVERE: And where
do I find him?
MERLIN: Normally, we'd choose
him from among the best
in the kingdom,
but today...
your champion arrived,
as a gift.
GUINEVERE: And I
must accept him?
MERLIN: Yes.
MERLIN: Yes!
GUINEVERE: Then it was just
the kingdom you wanted!
MERLIN: You're forgetting
everything I told you!
But if you are to rule Britain
you must forget yourself.
No more fear.
No more desire.
No more anything.
There isn't time.
You have a great deal to learn.
MERLIN: Listen...
Your king and your courtier
will be entirely Christian.
But the pagans are powerful.
They must be given their due.
To refuse an offering
from the high priestess...
would be taken badly.
The high priestess?
Morgan sent this champion?
I wasn't sure you
knew about L'Fei.
I know she hates Arthur.
I know she tried to
have me murdered.
We were aware of that.
But we still need
the illusion of her loyalty.
And I am to entrust
my life to an illusion?
MERLIN: It's called politics.
MERLIN: But the warrior
is brave enough.
MERLIN: I believe you know him.
GAWAIN: Merlin,
you're wanted
for the procession.
GAWAIN: He'll be back
with you presently.
[HORSES NEIGHING]
Oh, she sent you too...
To kill me?
Kill you?
It is for the loss of you
that I've wanted to die.
I am so alone, Lac.
When you ruled away
from me, I could feel my
soul wrenched out of me.
This past year I prayed
so often you would come.
Oh!
LANCELOT: I've spent
this past year mad.
Roaming the darkest roads.
Challenging all those
who crossed my path.
I wanted them to kill me.
And Morgan knew it.
Knew that unless she changed,
she could not stop me.
And finally she has let me go.
Let you go?
To be with you.
As I need to.
And I am married
to Arthur now.
LANCELOT: No!
Not in his world,
I heard them.
In our world, the Goddess
knows that you were
pledged to me first.
Or have you come
to love this Arthur?
You are the only
one that I love.
Then come with me now.
Before they set their
crosses on you.
WOMAN: My lady.
They wait on your attendance.
[FOOTSTEPS]
It's too late, Lac.
Then I will kill Arthur!
It is not Arthur who binds me
or sets me free.
As a wheel turns in water,
I too am being
turned by something.
I believe there is a possibility
of peace with this high king.
Out of all this pain...
something new will be born.
GUINEVERE: I have a chance to
make it something good, Lac.
A world of justice.
Not ruled by violence,
nor Morgan's rage and envy.
You think that fair to her?
To destroy Arthur she has
tried to stop me twice.
Once by a murderer's hand...
And now with you.
[HORSE NEIGHING]
[WHISPERING] Kiss me.
[WHISPERING] For the last time.
And then there's nothing
more between us.
GUINEVERE: Promise?
I won't.
Then you must go and
never come back again.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
[LANCELOT WHISPERING] Don't.
[GUINEVERE SOBBING]
[TRUMPETS SOUNDING]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
MAN: Arch!
MAN: Swords!
[METAL CLANKING]
You picked a winner, Merlin.
She's a better queen
than you know, my boy.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[RUMBLING]
Sending Lancelot on ahead.
We're going to try to outfox
these Northern pagans.
Go with the goddess.
MAN: I'll get some more wood.
[MEN CHATTING]
ARTHUR: Guin.
I hoped the fighting
would be over long ago.
There's still too many
local kings who make
war on their neighbors.
Maybe you should
be heading home.
All the other women have.
I won't go home before you.
And when the prince is born,
will you not say
I'm in a midst
of playing of battle?
The "princess" I hope
will be weaned on peace.
[BIRD WHISTLING]
I do not like these woods.
SOLDIER: Rider approaching!
[HORSE GALLOPING]
Rise and identify yourself, sir.
I have been sent
from the castle
seven miles yonder,
to bid the high King,
and his party take shelter
from this night.
ARTHUR: Are there more
horses like these?
I could use more for
such sturdy footing.
Forty brood mares
at least, sire.
And half a dozen stallion.
ARTHUR: Bring the horses.
ARTHUR: Mm-mmm.
ARTHUR: It's too bad Merlin's
gone back to his lair.
He may say he's too old for
all our rampaging about,
but he's not too old
for a feast such as this.
Our cook thought you
might prefer a warming
drink, my lady.
ARTHUR: Go on, Guin,
it's just a bit.
ARTHUR: Mm-mmm.
WOMAN: Your bed is ready, sire.
[LAUGHTER]
ARTHUR: Yes.
GUINEVERE: Stay with me, Arthur.
ARTHUR: No.
I'm too restless
to lie in bed yet.
And there are things I need
to discuss with Gawain.
It would be better for
you to get some sleep.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[EXHALES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[CREAKING]
WOMAN: Our mistress
awaits your pleasure.
[CREAKING]
[GROANING]
GUINEVERE: Arthur?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Arthur!
Arthur.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
GUINEVERE: Arthur?
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
Arthur.
GUINEVERE: Arthur!
[GROANING]
[THUDS]
Leave us.
This is woman's work.
GUINEVERE: Oh, God!
[GROANING]
GUINEVERE: Arthur.
It's ergot.
MORGAN: Do you
recognize its action?
Only ten times more
than we would usually give.
GUINEVERE: Why?
Why did you poison me?
Arthur's seed is now within me.
Child of the queen's daughter
by the old laws.
Child of the King's son
by the new.
But this one cannot be denied.
It will still be second to mine!
Do you really think so?
Your babe is dying.
MORGAN: And you are dying too.
[GUINEVERE SCREAMING] Whore!
Don't torment yourself.
MORGAN: It will
all be over soon.
[SCREAMING]
[MOANING AND SOBBING]
[SOBBING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[HORSE NEIGHING]
[MOANING]
[COUGHING]
WOMAN: It's over now, dear.
You have a sweet young girl.
[BABY BABBLING]
Well, no, you're
not finished yet.
I have to get out of here.
But you must rest.
You'll bleed to death.
No, I can't let Morgan find her.
[BABY BABBLING]
[SOBBING]
When I'm gone...
you must leave
this place forever.
You must... You must tell
no one that you saw me.
[SOBBING]
Raise my daughter as your own.
Mother, guard my baby.
[HORSE GALLOPING]
GUINEVERE: Lac.
[WHISPERING] Where's my baby?
Is she safe?
Everyone searched.
They found nothing.
They say that it
came too early.
They all think your
baby's dead, Guin.
She'll be safe from L'Fei.
I promise.
Now sleep.
GUINEVERE: Lac.
ARTHUR: It's Arthur, your king.
Lancelot is gone.
We're clearing some Irish
invaders from Dundrennan.
You sent him away?
I thought he was to protect me.
I was tired of his
silent accusations!
I was tired of always hearing
you call his name!
I was here too!
Not as often, maybe, but I
have a country to rule.
And without you it
hasn't been easy.
[EXHALES]
ARTHUR: Come on, Guin.
Can we forget what happened?
It was a night's foolishness
and nothing more.
You are my queen.
That woman...
I can't even remember
what she looked like.
Then you should make
an effort, Arthur.
That woman you
lay with was L'Fei.
GUINEVERE: Also known as Morgan.
Igraine's daughter, your sister!
I will have her killed.
And we will never
speak of this again.
GUINEVERE: You cannot kill
the High Priestess of Britain,
without bringing down upon
you all the pagan kingdoms,
and plunging Britain
once more into civil war.
But she has stained
my crown with incest.
She's defiled my kingship.
I can't bear that she's out
there unpunished after
having done that to me!
To you?
And have I emerged unscathed?
ARTHUR: They say that you'll
never bear me an heir.
We will never have our own...
loving family.
[SARCASTICALLY] Uh, not that
I would know what it looks like.
Haven't you heard the stories?
ARTHUR: That my father
raped my mother?
[SCOFFS] Merlin says
that it isn't true.
But he took me the day
I was born. There had
to be a reason.
You never asked your father?
I never saw him.
I never saw either one of them.
ARTHUR: This island
will be my children.
And that is how we will
overcome what has happened.
By not allowing it to
destroy our dreams.
Your dreams.
I'm just here clearing
out all the clutter.
You do more than that, Arthur.
No.
I know my limits,
give me credit for that.
What I am is a great warrior.
And it is time I took
my people back to battle.
Malgin was using my
absence to unite
the last kings in rebellion.
And I will crush him,
end them all... for good.
It will be a magnificent fight.
We've got these new
things called crossbows,
that allows us to fire with
one hand while we ride.
Oh, Guin, you should see them,
well, you will see them.
No.
ARTHUR: But...
They told me you were better.
Just tired.
And fresh air would
do you good, Guin.
This could be our
very last battle.
Arthur, someone will always
be wanting to test his
sword against yours.
There will always be violence
until we say "enough."
Malgin killed your father.
ARTHUR: You think
enough will stop him?
I've had a lot of time
to think about that.
Traveling with you for a year...
Lost in nightmares
these past few months.
It is upto us to create
a different way.
A different way of
solving differences.
A different way
of wielding power.
We have to be better.
Not just in battle.
And make others
want to be like us.
To win not just our protection,
but our esteem.
Well, I can tell you
they'll esteem us when
they see these crossbows.
We seem like an army twice
as fierce as our numbers.
GUINEVERE: Arthur, I will
not be riding with you
again to battle.
It is time I begin what
Merlin shows me to do.
Well, it's easy to say that
with him hidden away in
his lair, now, isn't it?
Nothing is easy anymore.
[DOOR CREAKING]
GAWAIN: Ahem.
My Lord.
Troops are ready.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Then I leave the kingdom in
your capable hands, Guinevere.
I accept the burden gladly.
[FOOTSTEPS]
Arthur.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Return safely.
That is my intention.
[DOOR CREAKS]
MAN: My lady, an envoy.
He demands to see the queen.
Has he come from Dundrennan?
Has he word of Lancelot's army?
He has come from Gal.
He says he has news of the king.
Who's at the end of
the long board always feel
less honored.
Arthur wants every one
of his guests close at hand.
Big and square.
It'd be hard to pass
the haggies, ma'am.
Then make it hollow,
with places for
servers to enter.
[EXHALES]
And make it round.
It's been six months since
I last saw my husband.
What news do you bring me, sir?
That you will never
again see him.
He has been captured and is
prisoner of Malgin of Gal.
And will die.
He and all his army.
Britain will not allow
Arthur to be slain.
I think it will.
For Malgin is high king now.
By who's authority?
One could ask by who's
authority Arthur held it?
When in lying with his sister
he committed incest.
An act which you...
has said to have witnessed...
my Queen.
Is this Morgan's doing?
ENVOY: Only half.
As they say...
The beast has two backs.
It has none!
This accusation is
a damnable lie.
Is it?
The world will see no army
comes to dispute it.
Trial by combat has
been replaced by law.
Not in the rebel kingdoms.
You have till the full moon
to bring your warriors.
Malgin holds most of them.
And the rest...
with Lancelot...
have not been heard from
for many months.
ENVOY: Shall I tell my lord
you concede to the charge?
Tell your Lord I
concede nothing.
GUINEVERE: Tell him he will
have to defend his lies.
Against who?
Against Guinevere,
High Queen of Britain.
And remind him that Britain has
a tradition of warrior queens.
GUINEVERE: Tell him to think
on Boudica, queen of Iceni,
who destroyed Rome's
entire ninth legion.
Tell him to think on Katemanda,
queen of the Buganti's,
from whom I am descended.
GUINEVERE: Tell him though
I have sworn on my crown,
never to raise a weapon,
if he harms one hair on
Arthur's anointed head...
tell Malgin I will
kill him myself.
[FOOTSTEPS]
It's deadly sharp.
And I made it lighter
befitting your size, my lady.
I will not touch it
till I need to.
Then, if you would permit...
I will come along
as your squire.
MAN: We will not
let you ride alone.
GUINEVERE: You are
welcome, my friends.
MERLIN: Arthur...
is a great warrior.
A charismatic leader.
But only an ordinary man.
And you thought he was
sent by the heavens.
Uh, I think...
considering he
was Uther's son...
I did a pretty good job.
So the truth means nothing?
MERLIN: It means a great deal.
But nothing in this
world is either
black, or white.
MERLIN: It's not a bad thing...
Guinevere...
to inspire the world
to true nobility.
One man or one woman...
makes it possible
for the rest of us...
to rise above what
we thought we could do.
One hero makes us all heroes.
One visionary...
can show us all
the way to peace.
And that is why I am riding
armed into battle?
MERLIN: I told you,
you were being tested.
But I know you will
find a way to triumph.
Just as you found a way
to save your child.
You've seen my baby?
She...
She is well.
And well hidden
on the isle of Anglesey.
I told you I was practiced
at spiriting a vase more
wet than Draconus.
MERLIN: I must
tell you something...
Something I told
Arthur's mother.
This child...
belongs to Britain.
Claim her...
and she will be destroyed.
MERLIN: One day...
she will return like her father
to save her country.
But now...
Guinevere...
It is your turn to
save your country.
Will you come with me?
I have never left you.
And I never will, my child.
MERLIN: Go with God.
And with the Goddess.
One day...
we will meet again.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
MAN: We've come to
fight for Arthur.
Onward to the North then.
[TRUMPETS SOUNDING]
MEN: This way... Join us.
[LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING]
SQUIRE: That's the castle,
my lady.
Fortified till the hilt.
No way in, and no way out.
Not only that, but...
four kings have
joined with Malgin.
GUINEVERE: Our men
will be slaughtered.
All will be slaughtered.
MAN: I'm going off
to fetch more wood...
[HORSE GALLOPING]
[LAUGHTER]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
GUINEVERE: Tell your lord
that Guinevere,
High Queen of Britain, would
see him here and now alone.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
SOLDIER: Open the gate.
[MEN CHATTING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
How did you get here?
GUINEVERE: Morgan is not
the only one who knows magic.
I was tutored by Merlin
as well as by she.
Even Morgan isn't leaving
Arthur's death to magic.
Strip her and search her.
You would let other men
touch your future wife?
Stop!
I have come to make you a deal.
What kind of a deal
could you make with me?
Four kings have come
to make sure Arthur dies.
I can offer you something far
better than Arthur's blood.
GUINEVERE: One unfairly when he
and his army are all in chains.
What kind of truth?
What kind of honor will
such a victory accord you?
Release Arthur.
GUINEVERE: And I will
come to you myself.
Freely.
With all my lands
and all my subjects.
GUINEVERE: You will have
no more and no less than
Arthur did when he wed me.
And if you then
unite all of Britain...
you must be acknowledged
greater than he.
I will have you anyway.
No, I will kill myself
if he dies.
And you will have bloody
chaos on your hands,
and Saxons on your shores
quick to smell the advantage.
You will come to me.
You will...
surrender yourself, you'll...
spread your legs for me?
And you expect me to believe...
that you won't change
your mind again?
You have my word.
I will swear whatever
vow you wish.
You will swear also never...
to seek escape...
or accept rescue.
I will swear that also.
You will swear...
in the morn...
before the Goddess
and her armies.
I will come to you in the morn.
In all my finery.
In the morn then...
or when the sun reaches mid-sky,
your king, and your country...
will die.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
GUINEVERE: Make sure
my horse is fed.
SQUIRE: Yes, my lady.
[DOOR OPENS]
[RUMBLING]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
GUINEVERE: Lac?
LANCELOT: Yes, it is I.
[BREATHING EXCITEDLY]
GUINEVERE: Have you
really come to help me?
To save Arthur?
I don't think I would, if it's
all I could to extricate
us from the siege.
He sends us against a force
a hundred times our own.
But you...
You and your army,
you can still rescue him.
Guin, my army...
what's left of my army is
still three days behind.
I could not make them ride
any longer without sleep.
But you came!
You would think of something.
If not I must exchange myself
for him in the morn.
That I will not let you do.
And I cannot let Arthur die.
As he let you lie dying
while he bed Morgan?
He was enchanted,
you know her powers.
Then why they never
worked on us?
Perhaps she plays with us
in a different way.
Or perhaps Arthur
chose to be enchanted!
It would not have
been the first time,
nor the last.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
He's not perfect, Lac.
He is perhaps further
from it than you.
But he has allowed his people
to believe they are a nation,
and they need him if
they are to endure.
No, Guin.
You are what they need now.
Not another warrior with
a blood dripping sword.
It is your wisdom
that will carry them.
Your dreams that
will inspire them.
It is you they followed here!
I will take responsibility,
and I will carry you away,
and not until Arthur is dead
will I set you free.
[RUMBLING]
And then you may
have me executed.
LANCELOT: As you may need to.
LANCELOT: But the people
will understand my passion,
and you will remain
as their high queen.
And I will be asking of Arthur
no more than I ask of myself.
And I will never
have had the pleasure...
of anyone's sheets.
[FIRE CRACKLING]
Tonight then.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[KISSING PASSIONATELY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
LANCELOT: No!
GUINEVERE: I know.
Because your plan
wont work, Lac.
It won't work.
If I refuse Malgin, he'll send
five kingdoms against me.
And without you or
Arthur to protect them
my people will be drowned
in their own blood.
MORGAN: You can
leave Malgin to me.
[SOFTLY] You!
You did all this?
He used me
for his purposes.
And I will use him
for mine.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[GUINEVERE SCREAMING]
LANCELOT: No, Guin!
Now none of us is perfect.
[WHISPERING] What?
GUINEVERE: What do
you want from me?
Nothing other than what
you want for yourself.
MORGAN: Lancelot beside you
on the high throne of Britain.
I know you hate me.
I know you have reason.
Sometimes our paths are crueler
than we would wish them to be.
MORGAN: But I can give
you both a piece of the
love you have dreamed of.
Think back, Guinevere,
of your days at the sanctuary.
And realize that your vision
is not so different from mine.
Where do you think
you got it from, child?
[RUMBLING]
Let Lancelot take you from here.
I will deal with
what comes after.
LANCELOT: It's almost
dawn, Guin.
We should be going.
You serve me...
Not L'Fei.
Her darkness offers
her heart's desire.
It is the darkness still.
And I say I will defeat her.
Arthur will not die.
GUINEVERE: You will fight
one last battle for me.
And then you will be
discharged of all your
vows and obligations.
Perhaps if I'm lucky I will
not survive this battle.
But if I live...
I will accept your release,
and depart this country.
Know that when you leave,
you take my heart with you.
I await your orders, my queen.
Rise, Lancelot.
And hear what you must do.
[HORSES NEIGHING]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't do this.
GUINEVERE: L'Fei has
promised to betray you.
And Lancelot has come
with all his army.
Look up, Malgin,
and face your destroyer.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
By this army...
you know that Arthur Pendragon
is high king.
By this Arthur, you know
that Camelot will live.
And that the time
of swords raised...
Britain against Britain is over!
We are one people.
One nation!
We are sharers of one dream.
Or so you can choose to be.
You can choose to put your might
to the work of greatness.
GUINEVERE: Or you can die.
And miss the splendor
that will come.
Urian!
URIAN: We came
to witness a trial.
Not to be slaughtered.
Stater.
You encouraged my campaign
against Pendragon.
I was wrong.
She is right.
GUINEVERE: I think you
had better you release
Arthur, my Lord.
[MORGAN SCREAMING]
Kill him now, Malgin,
as you promised!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Release him.
Come on, Arthur.
We're going home.
[LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
GUINEVERE: Enter.
GUINEVERE: Kaethi, could you
please excuse us for a moment.
[DOOR CLOSES]
He has left, hasn't he?
Yes, my lady, he has.
Did he...
give you any message for me?
No, my lady, he said nothing.
But he...
just sent you this.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLAPPING]
ANNOUNCER: The King and Queen!
I would have thought Merlin
would have come to see this.
He is gone, Arthur.
Both of them are gone.
We're alone then?
It's just we two together.
It will be enough.
ALL: All hail, Arthur!
ALL: High King of Britain!
ALL: All hail, Guinevere!
ALL: His most high Queen!
[LAUGHTER]
GUINEVERE: And so,
Lancelot left,
Merlin died,
but Arthur and I endured.
Peace came to Britain.
And with it, prosperity.
And Camelot,
became a beacon
to all people
in all lands
for all time.
[MUSIC ENDS]