CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
HALLMARK CHANNEL
- YOU, TOO.
- BYE.
- WASHINGTON "POST," SIR?
HERE YOU ARE.
- GOOD MORNING, NAP.
- GOOD MORNING.
HOW ARE YOU?
- HOW ARE YOU?
- THANK YOU.
- GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- HAVE A NICE DAY.
- YOU, TOO. BYE.
HI.
- MORNING, CATE.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[RING]
- SECOND TIME AROUND.
- HEY, CATE, IT&amp;apos;S FRANCESCA.
- OH, UH, FRANNY. HI.
HOW YOU DOIN&amp;apos;?
- IT&amp;apos;S DADDY&amp;apos;S
BIRTHDAY ON SATURDAY,
AND YOU&amp;apos;RE COMING
TO THE PARTY.
- OH, HOW LOVELY.
A FAMILY OCCASION TO DREAD.
I&amp;apos;M NOT GOING.
- OH, YEAH, WHAT,
ARE YOU GOING TO PLAN
TO HAVE CHICKENPOX THAT DAY?
THAT&amp;apos;S WHAT YOU SAID
LAST YEAR.
A PERSON CAN ONLY
HAVE CHICKENPOX
ONCE IN THEIR LIFE
AND TRUST ME,
YOU HAVE HAD IT.
HOW LONG YOU GONNA
KEEP MAKING THINGS UP?
- UNTIL DAD APOLOGIZES.
UNTIL HIS FUNERAL.
THAT I&amp;apos;LL GO TO.
LOOK, I&amp;apos;M--
I&amp;apos;M REALLY SWAMPED
AND I&amp;apos;LL TALK
TO YOU LATER. OK? BYE.
- HEY, HEY, CATE, WAIT--
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
[BELL OVER DOOR JINGLES]
HI.
UM, FUNNY, I JUST
GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH FRANCESCA.
- OH, DADDY&amp;apos;S PARTY?
- I DON&amp;apos;T GET IT.
IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE
AN ANNUAL EVENT NOW?
- WELL, FRANNY WANTS TO.
YOU KNOW, SINCE MOM DIED.
ANYWAY, IT&amp;apos;S A CHANCE
TO SEE EVERYBODY.
- WHO?
ALL THE OLD PAISANS
STUFFING THEMSELVES
ON MANICOTTI
AND TALKING ABOUT BASEBALL GAMES
THEY SAW IN 1948?
- WE&amp;apos;LL BE THERE.
- OH, SORRY. I KNOW.
I JUST...
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
- LOOK, JUST MAKE AN APPEARANCE.
THEN YOU AND PHILIP
CAN HAVE SOME FUNCTION
YOU HAVE TO GO TO.
ANYWAY, HERE ARE THE THINGS
I TOLD YOU ABOUT.
UM, I KNOW THEY&amp;apos;RE NOT
WHAT YOU USUALLY CARRY, BUT--
- WELL, YOU NEVER KNOW.
- GREAT. [CHUCKLES]
I WON&amp;apos;T KEEP YOU.
OH, CYNTHIA&amp;apos;S COMING DOWN
FOR THE PARTY, TOO--
- OK, OK. SAY NO MORE.
HI.
- YEAH.
WE&amp;apos;RE JUST LOOKING.
YOU GOT ANY FATIGUES
OR COMBAT BOOTS?
- NO. NOTHING LIKE THAT.
I SELL VINTAGE CLOTHES.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
SECOND TIME AROUND.
- HI, IT&amp;apos;S ME.
- HI.
UH, PLEASE...
BE CAREFUL WITH THAT.
IT&amp;apos;S REALLY FRAGILE.
- IT&amp;apos;S PHILIP.
- I KNOW. I JUST--
I HAVE, UH, CUSTOMERS.
- OH. GREAT.
SORRY. SORRY
TO BOTHER YOU.
UH, TONIGHT DON&amp;apos;T--
DON&amp;apos;T BOTHER TO COOK, OK?
I&amp;apos;LL PICK SOMETHING
UP ON THE WAY.
I&amp;apos;LL BE THERE AROUND 7:00.
- OK.
ALL RIGHT. WELL,
I&amp;apos;LL SEE YOU THEN.
BYE.
- BYE.
- THAT&amp;apos;S AN ORIGINAL.
IT&amp;apos;S NICE, ISN&amp;apos;T IT?
- BE A COOL VEST.
JUST CUT OFF THE SLEEVES.
- YEAH.
- YOU CAN&amp;apos;T.
I MEAN, BECAUSE IT GOES
WITH THE SKIRT,
AND IT&amp;apos;S NOT FOR SALE
AS A SEPARATE.
- LET&amp;apos;S GO.
- [GIGGLES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SHOW THEME MUSIC PLAYS]
- LILLIAN, DARLING,
YOU STILL NEED TIME TO RECOVER.
AND I&amp;apos;VE BEEN THINKING...
WHY DON&amp;apos;T WE CANCEL
THE PARTY THIS WEEKEND
AND GO AWAY SOMEWHERE,
JUST THE TWO OF US.
- HOW ABOUT THAT CABIN
IN THE MOUNTAIN
WHERE SHE&amp;apos;S PLANNING
TO THROW YOU OFF A CLIFF?
- PERHAPS THE CABIN
IN THE MOUNTAINS.
YOU KNOW, IT&amp;apos;S BEAUTIFUL THERE
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
- [CHILDREN PLAYING]
AND LAUGHING]
- LEAVE ON FRIDAY?
HOW COULD WE POSSIBLY DO THAT?
- JUST GET ON A PLANE AND GO.
- JUST TO AVOID A PARTY?
- PEOPLE DO IT ALL THE TIME,
GO TO PARIS FOR THE WEEKEND.
- HEH.
- COME ON. WOULDN&amp;apos;T
IT BE GREAT?
JUST TAKE OFF.
GET AWAY FROM ALL OF THEM.
NO ARGUMENTS, NO BICKERING.
WELL, YOU DON&amp;apos;T LIKE
MY FAMILY, ANYWAY.
- I DO.
I LIKE YOUR FAMILY.
I DO LIKE THEM.
THEY&amp;apos;RE NOISY WHEN THEY EAT,
BUT I LIKE THEM.
EXCUSE ME.
- [LAUGHS SOFTLY]
WE COULD GO SOMEPLACE QUIET,
SOMEPLACE NICE,
JUST THE TWO OF US.
- UM, WHEN IS IT AGAIN,
THE PARTY?
- DO WE REALLY HAVE TO GO?
- YES, WE HAVE TO GO.
IT&amp;apos;S YOUR FAMILY.
WHEN IS IT AGAIN?
- SATURDAY.
COME ON.
JUST HUMOR ME.
JUST TELL ME
YOU&amp;apos;RE GONNA TAKE ME
AWAY SOMEDAY, SOMEWHERE.
YOU DON&amp;apos;T HAVE TO MEAN IT.
JUST SAY IT.
JUST...SAY IT.
- WHAT?
- NEVER MIND.
KNOCK, KNOCK.
- AH, CATE.
COME IN. COME IN.
- HELLO. LOOK AT YOU.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. AND YOU?
- MMM. AH, LOOK,
I&amp;apos;M ALL DIRTY.
HERE, TAKE THAT.
- OH, BEAUTIFUL.
- COME ON.
- THANKS.
- I HAVE A LITTLE
SURPRISE FOR YOU.
CATS.
- OHH, WILLIE,
THESE ARE FABULOUS.
- THAT&amp;apos;S A GOOD ONE.
- WHERE DID YOU GET THEM?
- HERE AND THERE.
YOU KNOW.
- COME ON.
YOU DON&amp;apos;T FIND
THIS KIND OF QUALITY
AT GARAGE SALES.
- NO, YOU DON&amp;apos;T.
- COME ON.
- OH, ALL RIGHT, I&amp;apos;LL TELL YOU.
SEEING AS I&amp;apos;VE SOLD YOU MY SHOP,
I MIGHT AS WELL GIVE YOU
MY LAST LITTLE SECRET, YES?
YOU READY?
HERE!
THERE YOU ARE.
FUNERALS.
- HUH?
- YEP.
- THE OBITUARIES?
- THE OBITUARIES.
GOT IT IN ONE.
AND, YOU KNOW...
THE FAMILY&amp;apos;S USUALLY VERY GLAD
TO HAVE SOMEBODY AROUND,
TO HELP OUT, YOU KNOW,
TO DISPOSE OF THINGS.
OF COURSE I SPLIT THE PROCEEDS
WITH THEM IF THEY SELL.
WICKED, EH?
- NO. IT&amp;apos;S A SERVICE, REALLY.
- YES. IT&amp;apos;S A SERVICE
TO THEM AND TO YOU.
- WELL, THE "IF THEY SELL"
PART ISN&amp;apos;T SO PERFECT.
- NO, IT&amp;apos;S THE FUN, CATE.
COME ON, LET&amp;apos;S FACE IT.
IT&amp;apos;S THE FUN.
YOU&amp;apos;RE SITTING HERE
WITH A BUNDLE OF OLD CLOTHES,
AND YOU&amp;apos;RE RUMMAGING
THROUGH THEM,
AND WHAT DO YOU FIND?
A GENUINE GIVENCHY.
I MEAN, THAT&amp;apos;S WONDERFUL.
I MEAN, LOOK AT...
LOOK AT THIS GREEN DRESS.
WOULDN&amp;apos;T THAT BE JUST
WONDERFUL FOR YOUR MOTHER?
THE ONLY WOMAN IN THE WORLD
WHO COULD WEAR
EVERY COLOR OF GREEN
BECAUSE OF HER HAIR.
LISTEN TO THAT.
CHA CHA CHA!
- OH, CYNTHIA&amp;apos;LL LOVE IT.
- OH, CYNTHIA, YES.
- I&amp;apos;LL TAKE IT FOR HER.
- YES.
- I&amp;apos;D LOVE TO COME
WITH YOU SOMETIME.
- WELL, YOU CAN.
YOU CAN COME WITH ME
ANYTIME YOU LIKE.
[CLOCK CHIMING]
- OH, GOD. WILLIE!
- PIERCE!
- UH, UH, UH.
HE&amp;apos;S GOING TO LOSE
ONE OF THOSE CUFF LINKS.
GO ON, GO ON, GO ON, GO ON.
TELL ME I&amp;apos;M RIGHT.
- NO. CYNTHIA NEVER TELLS ME
ANYTHING ABOUT THE PLOT.
- IMAGINE HAVING HIM
FOR A BROTHER-IN-LAW.
- WELL, HE&amp;apos;S NOT YET.
- YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW HIM.
- OH, YEAH.
- SO?
- WHAT?
WHAT YOU SEE
IS WHAT YOU GET.
- WHAT I SEE,
I&amp;apos;D BE THRILLED TO GET.
- BUT, SURINAME, YOU SAID
SATURN IN MY EIGHTH HOUSE
DID NOT MEAN SIMON AND I
WOULD ACTUALLY BREAK UP.
ALL RIGHT. LISTEN,
LISTEN, MY SISTER&amp;apos;S HERE.
I&amp;apos;LL CALL YOU LATER.
OK, BYE.
HEY, SWEETS.
- HI.
- HI. MMM.
- WHAT&amp;apos;S THIS ABOUT SIMON?
ARE YOU BREAKING UP?
- OH, WE HAD A HUGE FIGHT.
HE THINKS
HE&amp;apos;S PIERCE COVINGTON,
TALKS WITH AN ENGLISH ACCENT,
CALLS ME OLIVIA.
HE SAYS HE CAN&amp;apos;T COMMIT.
AFTER I&amp;apos;VE GIVEN HIM
2 YEARS OF MY LIFE.
SO I TOLD HIM
I SHOULD BE COMMITTED
FOR DATING HIM,
AND I WALKED OUT.
- WELL, THAT&amp;apos;S ACTORS FOR YOU.
- RIGHT. LIKE
YOU&amp;apos;D KNOW FROM ACTORS.
HOW&amp;apos;S MR. PHIL?
- PHILIP? HE&amp;apos;S FINE.
ARE YOU HERE FOR
DADDY&amp;apos;S PARTY ALREADY?
- I&amp;apos;M HERE
TO NURSE MY WOUNDS.
- AW!
- DATING A SOAP OPERA STAR
IS BAD ENOUGH.
DATING A SOAP OPERA
CHARACTER IS LUDICROUS.
SO, WHAT ABOUT PHILIP?
IS ANYTHING HAPPENING THERE?
- I&amp;apos;M QUITE CONTENT, THANK YOU.
- QUITE CONTENT?
SOUNDS MADLY
EXCITING. SNORE.
OH, OH, OH, OH.
IT&amp;apos;S NOT FOR YOU.
REMEMBER MOM&amp;apos;S DYING WORDS?
- GREEN...
- NOT GOOD ON YOU.
- I WANTED TO FIX THE SEQUINS
BEFORE YOU SAW IT.
- OH, SWEETIE,
CAN I TRY IT ON?
- YES.
I&amp;apos;M SURE YOU WANT IT SHORTER.
- MM-HMM.
[DOOR BELL JINGLES]
OH.
- OH!
THOSE STEPS.
DON&amp;apos;T YOU HAVE ANYTHING NEW?
- UH, NO.
I SELL SECONDHAND
AND CONSIGNMENT,
JUST LIKE THE SIGN SAYS.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- OH, PRETTY.
MM. VERY FOXY.
VERY, VERY, NICE.
- I HATE SECONDHAND.
I&amp;apos;VE GOT A THING ABOUT IT.
YOU--YOU--YOU KNOW,
SOMEONE ELSE&amp;apos;S CLOTHES.
- REALLY?
- HMM.
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD
SEE A DOCTOR ABOUT THAT.
- OH, CUTE.
REAL CUTE.
- WHY DID YOU
TREAT HER LIKE THAT?
- LIKE WHAT?
- AS IF SHE SMELLED.
- SHE WASN&amp;apos;T GONNA BUY.
SHE WANTED NEW STUFF.
- COULDN&amp;apos;T YOU HAVE SAID,
"MY STUFF&amp;apos;S NOT NEW,
BUT IT&amp;apos;S THE FINEST
IN DESIGNER WEAR"?
YOU COULD HAVE
SHOWN HER SOMETHING
THAT WAS MORE HER STYLE
OR AT LEAST HER SIZE.
- SHE DIDN&amp;apos;T
APPRECIATE MY STUFF.
- WAKE UP, CATE.
WHAT ARE YOU RUNNING HERE,
A MUSEUM OR A STORE?
- I CAN&amp;apos;T FORCE PEOPLE TO BUY.
THEY HAVE TO WANT MY STUFF.
- YOU CAN ENCOURAGE THEM.
I MEAN, LOOK AT
THIS PLACE. IT&amp;apos;S DRAB.
I-I&amp;apos;M SORRY, BUT IT IS.
IT SHOULD BE ROMANTIC AND FUN.
SLAP SOME PAINT ON THE WALLS.
BRIGHTEN IT UP.
OH, HERE.
NICER BAGS WOULD HELP.
AND DOORS ON THE DRESSING ROOMS.
THESE CURTAINS ARE GHASTLY.
AND FULL-LENGTH MIRRORS INSIDE.
- CYNTHIA, STOP.
I KNOW YOUR PROJECTS.
IN A MINUTE,
YOU&amp;apos;LL BE TELLING ME
I NEED FERNS AND CUPIDS.
- NO FERNS,
BUT CUPIDS MIGHT WORK.
- I DON&amp;apos;T HAVE ANY MONEY.
- OH, CATIE,
YOU DON&amp;apos;T NEED MONEY.
YOU HAVE ME.
- YOU KNOW I CAN&amp;apos;T DO THAT.
- SWEETIE, YOU&amp;apos;LL HAVE
TO DO SOMETHING,
OR ELSE YOU&amp;apos;LL BE BACK
WORKING AT THE PENTAGON.
LET&amp;apos;S JUST MAKE A LIST.
A LIST DOESN&amp;apos;T COST ANYTHING.
- YEAH, I KNOW YOU--
- PENTAGON.
- OK.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[RING]
HELLO.
- HI, CATE.
IT&amp;apos;S ME.
- HI. WHERE ARE YOU?
- I&amp;apos;M SORRY. LISTEN,
I CAN&amp;apos;T MAKE IT.
I HAVE AN EMERGENCY MEETING
WITH GRANT WINTHROP IN NEW YORK.
- NEW YORK?
- YES. I&amp;apos;M AT THE AIRPORT NOW.
- AHH.
- SORRY.
IT JUST CAME UP.
SO EXPLAIN TO YOUR FATHER
FOR ME, OK?
- PHILIP, YOU&amp;apos;RE SENDING ME
INTO BATTLE ALONE.
- I KNOW. I&amp;apos;M SORRY.
I HAVE TO DO THIS, CATE.
- OK.
- OK? BYE.
- BYE.
- [PEOPLE CHATTERING]
[LAUGHTER]
- AH. SO THE BIG
BUSINESSWOMAN ARRIVES
AN HOUR LATE, HUH?
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DAD.
- SWAMPED WITH CUSTOMERS,
IS THAT RIGHT?
- NOT EXACTLY.
HERE.
IT&amp;apos;S FROM PHILIP, TOO.
- OH, THANKS.
- HE HAD AN EMERGENCY AT WORK.
HE COULDN&amp;apos;T MAKE IT.
- YOU OUGHT TO MARRY THAT GUY.
I DON&amp;apos;T KNOW WHY
YOU&amp;apos;RE DRAGGING YOUR FEET.
ANYWAY, I THINK
THERE&amp;apos;S SOME FOOD LEFT.
GO GET SOME.
- HEY.
- HI, CATE.
- SWEETS.
- NICE DRESS.
- THANK YOU.
- DADDY LOVES YOUR CANNOLI,
SIGNORA CORETTI.
MOLTO GRAZIE.
OH, GOOD, CATE, YOU MADE IT.
- HI.
- HEY, WHERE&amp;apos;S PHILIP?
- UM, HE HAD
AN EMERGENCY AT WORK.
"WE LOVE YOU MAD"?
- I TELEPHONED
THE ORDER IN.
THEY MADE A MISTAKE.
- [LAUGHING]
- HEY. HOW&amp;apos;S MY FAVORITE
SISTER-IN-LAW?
- THOUGHT I WAS YOUR FAVORITE.
- YOU ARE. AH, YOU&amp;apos;RE ALL
MY FAVORITE.
- OH, WELL, WHY DON&amp;apos;T WE JUST
CHANGE THE "M" TO A "D"?
- WE COULD STICK
AN "LY" ON THE END.
"WE LOVE YOU MADLY."
- I THINK IT&amp;apos;S PERFECT
THE WAY IT IS.
HE&amp;apos;S ALWAYS MAD ABOUT SOMETHING.
- ANNETTE, COULD YOU
PUT THE CANNOLI IN THE FRIDGE?
- SURE.
- CATE, MAYBE YOU COULD--
- GET OUT OF THE ROOM?
I CAN DO THAT.
- OK, MR. ATTORNEY.
WHAT&amp;apos;S BLACK AND BROWN
AND LOOKS GOOD ON LAWYERS?
- DOBERMAN.
- ALL RIGHT. WHAT&amp;apos;S
THE LAWYER&amp;apos;S CREED?
- I DON&amp;apos;T KNOW.
- YOU&amp;apos;RE INNOCENT
UNTIL PROVEN BROKE.
- ALL RIGHT.
WHAT&amp;apos;S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A LAWYER
AND A CATFISH?
- WELL, ONE&amp;apos;S A BOTTOM-FEEDING
SCAVENGER.
THE OTHER&amp;apos;S A FISH.
- HA HA HA!
- OH, YOU&amp;apos;RE BACK ALREADY?
I THOUGHT YOU WENT UPSTAIRS
TO IRON YOUR BLOUSE.
HA HA HA!
- UM, DADDY, IF YOU KNEW
ANYTHING ABOUT FASHION,
YOU&amp;apos;D KNOW HER OUTFIT
IS VERY CHIC.
- BUT SHE LOOKS LIKE
SHE&amp;apos;S SLEPT IN IT.
WHAT&amp;apos;S CHIC ABOUT THAT?
- I&amp;apos;M SURE YOU THINK THAT SHIRT
IS THE HEIGHT OF FASHION.
- HA HA HA!
- HEY, I DON&amp;apos;T CLAIM
TO BE AN EXPERT.
AND I DON&amp;apos;T TRY TO MAKE A LIVING
SELLING OTHER PEOPLE&amp;apos;S
CASTOFFS.
IS THAT BLOUSE AN EXAMPLE
OF YOUR MERCHANDISE?
WHEW, NO WONDER.
- NO WONDER WHAT?
- NO WONDER
YOU HAVE TO COME HOME
TO GET A DECENT MEAL.
LOOK AT YOU.
YOU&amp;apos;RE THIN.
YOU&amp;apos;RE PALE.
I--I--BUT I GUESS
THAT&amp;apos;S CHIC, TOO, ISN&amp;apos;T IT?
- DADDY, YOU&amp;apos;RE IMPOSSIBLE.
- HA HA HA!
JUST WHAT I&amp;apos;VE ALWAYS WANTED.
HA HA!
GET A LOAD OF THAT.
- [CROWD SINGING
"FOR HE&amp;apos;S A JOLLY GOOD FELLOW"]
- NEED ANY HELP?
- NO, THANKS.
OH, HI.
- HI.
- CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING?
- OH, I&amp;apos;LL GET IT.
SO...
YOU&amp;apos;RE CATE.
- THAT&amp;apos;S RIGHT.
YOU&amp;apos;RE CYNTHIA&amp;apos;S--
- ATTORNEY. ONE OF THEM.
HARRY DIETRICH.
UH...
I THINK YOUR BLOUSE IS GREAT.
- THANK YOU.
- IT&amp;apos;S TURN-OF-THE-CENTURY,
ISN&amp;apos;T IT?
- YEAH. HOW&amp;apos;D YOU KNOW THAT?
- I THINK THAT WAS
MY GRANDMOTHER&amp;apos;S.
- OH, SO,
SHE WANT IT BACK?
- TOO LATE.
- GOOD. I WANTED
YOU TWO TO MEET.
HARRY JUST MOVED HERE
FROM NEW YORK.
- I&amp;apos;M GONNA GET THE CREAMER.
IT&amp;apos;S RIGHT UP HERE.
- OH, THAT LOOKS GOOD.
- HOT COFFEE.
- SUGAR IN HERE?
- HEY.
- [ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
- OH, EXCUSE ME.
- I&amp;apos;LL GRAB SOME
OUT OF THE DISHWASHER.
- NAPKINS IN THE DRAWER?
- I&amp;apos;LL WASH THESE OUT.
- YEAH, I GOT THEM.
- I FEEL SO CLOSE TO YOU.
- HA HA HA!
FRANCESCA IS THE OLDEST, RIGHT?
I MET HER WHEN I ARRIVED.
SHE SEEMS VERY DETERMINED.
- OH, YES.
SHE&amp;apos;S AN INTERNIST, YOU KNOW.
VERY SUCCESSFUL.
BUT IT TOOK DETERMINATION.
MORE THAN THE USUAL.
- OH?
- WELL, FIRST SHE GOT
A SCHOLARSHIP
TO JOHNS HOPKINS AT 17,
THEN GOT PREGNANT,
GOT PACKED OFF TO A HOME
FOR UNWED MOTHERS.
BUT AFTER THE BABY WAS BORN,
SHE AND JERRY REFUSED
TO GIVE HER UP
AND GOT MARRIED.
- AND THEN SHE BECAME A DOCTOR?
- ARE YOU SURE
THIS ISN&amp;apos;T TOO BORING?
- NO.
- UH, DAD SAID NO SENSE
WASTING A GOOD MIND,
THEN BULLIED HER
INTO TAKING THE
SCHOLARSHIP ANYWAY.
- AND ANNETTE, THE BLONDE.
- GREAT MOTHER, GREAT WIFE.
THAT&amp;apos;S HER BANKER HUSBAND
PAUL ON THE GAZEBO.
THE MATCHING GIRLS ARE THEIRS.
CHECK OUT THE CLOTHES.
THE WHOLE FAMILY
IS COLOR-COORDINATED.
WHEN WE WERE KIDS,
FRANNY AND ANNETTE
WERE DAD&amp;apos;S FAVORITES,
TILL CYNTHIA HIT PUBERTY
AND TURNED INTO...
- CYNTHIA?
SO THERE&amp;apos;S FRANCESCA THE DOCTOR,
ANNETTE THE PERFECT WIFE,
CYNTHIA THE SUPERMODEL,
AND CAITLIN...
THE RAG SELLER.
NOT EXACTLY MY FATHER&amp;apos;S
DARLING CHILD.
- WELL, I THINK
YOU&amp;apos;RE SOMETHING.
AND VERY BEAUTIFUL, TOO.
- OH.
- CAITLIN...
THANKS FOR THE GLOVES.
OH, HARRY, RIGHT?
THE BOTTOM-FEEDING SCAVENGER.
- THAT WOULD BE ME.
- [LAUGHING]
- MY DAD.
- DO YOU--DO YOU WANT
TO GET OUT OF HERE?
- YEAH.
- WITH A BOTTOM FEEDER?
- ALL RIGHT.
[NO AUDIO]
- THANKS.
- I KNOW YOU&amp;apos;RE
SEEING SOMEONE,
BUT, UH...
I&amp;apos;D LIKE TO CALL YOU ANYWAY.
- THAT&amp;apos;S NOT A GOOD IDEA.
- I&amp;apos;M GONNA CALL YOU.
YOU DON&amp;apos;T HAVE TO CALL BACK.
- I SHOULD GO.
[RING]
[MACHINE PICKS UP]
[BEEP]
- HI. IT&amp;apos;S CATE.
LEAVE A MESSAGE.
[BEEP]
- HI, CATE.
IT&amp;apos;S PHILIP.
YOU BACK FROM THE PARTY? HELLO?
IF YOU&amp;apos;RE THERE, PICK UP.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, UM, I&amp;apos;M AT THE ST. REGIS.
YOU HAVE THE NUMBER.
I&amp;apos;LL BE BACK IN
MY ROOM ABOUT 7:00.
CALL ME, PLEASE.
I LOVE YOU. BYE.
- HE&amp;apos;S COMPLETELY SMITTEN.
I COULD TELL.
- STOP PLAYING CUPID, OK?
I DON&amp;apos;T NEED IT.
- YOU NEED SOME PASSION
IN YOUR LIFE.
YOU THINK YOU&amp;apos;RE IN LOVE
WITH PHILIP,
BUT HE&amp;apos;S JUST A HABIT.
MAYBE IT&amp;apos;S TIME FOR A CHANGE.
- SPEAKING AS SOMEONE
WHO JUST BROKE UP
WITH HER OWN HABIT,
YOU&amp;apos;RE NOT EXACTLY SPEAKING
FROM A POSITION OF STRENGTH.
HMM.
- MAYBE THEY&amp;apos;RE
FROM ST. ANTHONY&amp;apos;S,
WHEN IT BURNED DOWN.
- CLEAN &amp;apos;EM UP, STRIP &amp;apos;EM,
PUT A DOOR FRAME AROUND &amp;apos;EM.
- YOU MEAN YOU LIKE THEM?
- THEY&amp;apos;RE BEAUTIFUL.
HUH? HUH?
- ANYWAY, YOU&amp;apos;RE HARDLY
THE FIRST WOMAN TO DUMP A GUY
BECAUSE SHE FELL
FOR SOMEONE ELSE.
- I&amp;apos;M NOT DUMPING ANYONE,
AND I HAVEN&amp;apos;T FALLEN
FOR ANYONE.
I&amp;apos;M GONNA MARRY PHILIP.
- REALLY?
WHERE&amp;apos;S THE RING?
OR DID I MISS SOMETHING?
- LET&amp;apos;S GO SEE MOM.
- [SIGHS]
- I HOPE HEAVEN&amp;apos;S
A BIG COCKTAIL PARTY,
AND SHE&amp;apos;S THE CENTER
OF ATTENTION IN HER RED SUIT.
A DRY MARTINI--
- PROBABLY HER THIRD.
- THIS ALWAYS BUGGED ME...
HIS NAME THERE.
IT SHOULD JUST READ,
"BELOVED WIFE AND MOTHER."
- WELL...HE WAS HER HUSBAND,
AND HE LOVED HER.
OH, WE WERE ALWAYS SURE
TO FIND OUR CATIE
UNDER THE BED
WHENEVER THEY YELLED.
- WHEN HE YELLED, YOU MEAN.
COME ON, HE NEVER LET UP ON HER.
SHE SPENT HALF MY CHILDHOOD
IN THE GAZEBO CRYING.
- AND GETTING PIE-EYED.
THAT&amp;apos;S WHERE
SHE STASHED HER BOTTLES.
- YEAH, WELL...
IT WAS HIS FAULT
SHE DRANK, ANYWAY.
- COME ON, CATE.
SHE WAS AN ALCOHOLIC.
- YOU&amp;apos;VE NEVER SAID
A BAD WORD ABOUT DAD.
- NO, I HAVEN&amp;apos;T,
AND I HATE IT THAT YOU DO.
I WISH I COULD FIND
A MAN HALF AS GOOD.
- IT WASN&amp;apos;T THAT HARD FOR ME.
- OF COURSE
THEY WANT TO SEE YOU.
- [LAUGHS]
- THEY ALWAYS ASK
IF YOU&amp;apos;RE COMING
WITH ME. THEY DO.
[CLOCK CHIMES]
- THIS POTATO SALAD...
IS DELICIOUS.
UNUSUAL.
- A PLACE IN THE VILLAGE
MAKES IT FRESH.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME MORE?
- THANK YOU.
PHILIP?
- UH-HUH?
- I WANT TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
- FIRE AWAY.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH ME?
- WHAT?
- WHAT--
- DOING?
- WHAT DO YOU SEE IN ME?
- [SIGHS]
I CAN&amp;apos;T CATEGORIZE IT.
- TRY.
- [SIGHS] ALL RIGHT. OK, UM...
YOU&amp;apos;RE NICE TO ME.
EXCUSE ME.
- GO ON.
- UH...
YOU MAKE ME FEEL GOOD.
YOU&amp;apos;RE NOT DEMANDING.
- DEMANDING.
- YOU KNOW, YOU DON&amp;apos;T--
YOU DON&amp;apos;T...
BADGER ME TO GO PLACES
AND DO THINGS
I DON&amp;apos;T WANT TO GO OR DO.
- BUT, PHILIP, THESE ARE THINGS
THAT DESCRIBE HOW
I ACT TOWARDS YOU.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT ME
THAT YOU LIKE?
MY OWN QUALITIES.
- I REALLY DON&amp;apos;T SEE
WHERE THIS IS GOING.
I LIKE EVERYTHING.
YOU&amp;apos;RE PERFECT.
DON&amp;apos;T CHANGE, OK?
PLEASE GET IN THE CAR.
[RING]
- REMODEL INCORPORATED.
LET US REMODEL YOU.
HARRY!
YES, SHE&amp;apos;S HERE.
ISN&amp;apos;T SHE?
WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
- GIVE IT.
HELLO?
HI!
UH...
REMODELING, YEAH.
CYNTHIA TALKED ME INTO IT.
NOW?
OK.
[CHUCKLES] YEAH.
OK, BYE.
- WHAT DID HE SAY?
- NOTHING.
- NOTHING?
- WE&amp;apos;RE HAVING COFFEE.
- LISTEN, HARRY IS CHARMING,
HANDSOME, AND SMART.
IT&amp;apos;S OK TO LIKE HIM.
- IT&amp;apos;S JUST COFFEE.
- WELL, THAT
WASN&amp;apos;T ENOUGH FOR GUS,
SO HE BEFRIENDED THE WIDOW
WHO LIVED ONE FLOOR BELOW US.
- IN THE SAME BUILDING?
- OH, YES. OH, YES.
BUT SHE HAD 2 SONS,
EX-MARINES BOTH,
WHO DID NOT APPROVE OF GUS.
SO HE PUT ON AN OVERCOAT,
A HAT, A SCARF,
A FAKE MUSTACHE--
AND THIS WAS
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE SUMMER--
AND HE&amp;apos;D GO DOWN THE FIRE ESCAPE
TO CALL ON THE WIDOW.
- [LAUGHING]
- AND MY MOM EVENTUALLY
TOOK HIM BACK,
FORGAVE HIM.
AND AFTER SHE DIED,
HE WENT OUT TO CALIFORNIA
TO DO THE RACETRACK CIRCUIT,
WHERE HE DIED OF A CORONARY.
- BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU LIKED HIM.
- OH, YEAH.
WHAT A CHARACTER.
THERE&amp;apos;S A HITCHCOCK FESTIVAL
THIS WEEK AT THE UPTOWN.
- OH, REALLY?
THEY ALWAYS LOOK SO MUCH BETTER
ON THE BIG SCREEN,
ESPECIALLY THE
BLACK-AND-WHITE ONES.
YOU DON&amp;apos;T GET
THAT CONTRAST ON TV.
- WAS THAT A YES?
HOW ABOUT A RIDE?
- UH...
NO, THANKS.
I&amp;apos;LL WALK.
- WELL, I&amp;apos;LL CHECK
THE MOVIE TIMES.
I&amp;apos;LL GIVE YOU A CALL.
- WHATEVER.
- I&amp;apos;M SO GLAD
YOU&amp;apos;RE DOING IT UP.
- YEAH?
- IT NEEDED THAT.
I MISS IT.
- THE SHOP?
- YEAH, MORE THAN
I THOUGHT I WOULD.
THE KIND OF--YOU KNOW,
THE CHATTERING,
THE TALKING TO PEOPLE.
THAT&amp;apos;S WHAT
I REALLY, REALLY MISS.
- WELL, YOU CAN COME BACK
ANYTIME YOU WANT, YOU KNOW.
- YEAH.
LOOK, HONESTLY,
LOOK AT THESE WEEDS.
YOU&amp;apos;D THINK SOMEBODY&amp;apos;D
GIVE THEM A WHACK.
OH, LOOK WHAT
WE&amp;apos;VE GOT HERE.
- WHAT?
- HE&amp;apos;S SEEN BETTER DAYS.
A LITTLE CUPID.
AH, LOOK.
- FUNNY, CYNTHIA AND I
WERE JUST TALKING
ABOUT CUPIDS FOR THE SHOP.
- THERE, THERE, LOOK, SEE?
HE&amp;apos;S SMILING.
DO YOU WANT HIM?
- WELL, HE&amp;apos;S CUTE, ISN&amp;apos;T HE?
- WELL, HE&amp;apos;S
A SAUCY LITTLE CHAP.
[LAUGHS]
COME ON, LET&amp;apos;S ASK HOW MUCH
THEY WANT FOR IT.
- OK.
- UHH!
- IS IT HEAVY?
- YES.
ACTUALLY, I COULD HELP YOU
WITH THE BOOKS.
- YES.
- [PEOPLE CHATTERING]
- FEEL LIKE CHINESE?
- YOU SAID A MOVIE.
WE DID THE MOVIE.
YOU NEVER SAID
A MOVIE AND DINNER.
- TAKEOUT IS HARDLY DINNER.
WE WOULDN&amp;apos;T HAVE TO GO OUT.
WE COULD EAT ON YOUR BALCONY.
- WAIT--
HOW--HOW DID YOU KNOW
I HAVE A BALCONY?
- ALL THE APARTMENTS
IN YOUR BUILDING HAVE
A BALCONY, DON&amp;apos;T THEY?
- OH, RIGHT.
- AH, THIS IS GREAT.
I&amp;apos;M SORRY.
DO YOU WANT A PLATE?
- NO, I THOUGHT
WE COULD EAT FAMILY STYLE
IF THAT&amp;apos;S ALL RIGHT WITH YOU.
- OH, SURE.
THAT&amp;apos;S GREAT.
- MMM, FRIED RICE.
- IS IT GOOD?
- GOOD.
WANT SOME?
TRY IT.
- OK, YOU WANT
TO TRY MINE?
- SURE.
MMM.
THIS IS ONE OF
MY FAVORITES.
CAN I GET YOU
SOME LONGER CHOPSTICKS?
- [LAUGHS]
I KNOW.
HA HA HA!
I KNOW, I--
I HUNCH OVER MY FOOD LIKE--
LIKE I&amp;apos;M AFRAID
SOMEBODY&amp;apos;S GONNA TAKE IT.
I CALL IT...
THE IMMIGRANT HUNCH.
MY WHOLE FAMILY DOES IT.
- I LIKE THAT IMMIGRANT HUNCH.
HMM?
- UH-UH.
- I&amp;apos;LL STICK
WITH THE BROCCOLI.
- NO, I WANT IT BACK.
- NO.
- SO I TOOK THE MONEY
MY MOTHER GAVE ME,
AND I QUIT MY JOB...
AND I OPENED THE SHOP.
AND I&amp;apos;M GLAD I DID.
EXCEPT SOMETIMES WHEN I LOOK
AT MY BANK STATEMENTS.
- DOING WORK YOU ENJOY
IS WORTH EVERYTHING.
- SO YOU LOVE WHAT YOU DO?
- I DO. IT&amp;apos;S MOSTLY
SMALL-TIME STUFF,
BUT MY CLIENTS HAVE
REAL PROBLEMS,
AND SOMETIMES I CAN HELP &amp;apos;EM.
YOU WERE WASHING DISHES
THE FIRST TIME WE MET.
AND YOU PULLED
YOUR HAND OUT OF THE SINK
STILL WET AND SOAPY
AND SHOOK MY HAND ANYWAY.
I LIKED THAT.
- OH, YOU DID?
- YOU DIDN&amp;apos;T HESITATE.
GOOD NIGHT.
[DOOR CLOSES]
- CATE, IT&amp;apos;S PHILIP.
LISTEN, WOULD YOU MEET ME
AT THE HAY-ADAMS
AT 8:00 TONIGHT?
AND WHY DON&amp;apos;T YOU WEAR
THAT LITTLE BLACK DRESS
THAT I LIKE? BYE.
WELL, I&amp;apos;VE BEEN
DOING SOME THINKING--
[CLEARS THROAT]
AND...DO YOU REMEMBER
THE OTHER DAY
WHEN YOU ASKED ME
WHAT I SAW IN YOU?
WELL, I THINK I KNOW
WHAT YOU WERE ASKING,
AND THE THING IS THAT WE SEEM
TO GET ALONG SO WELL
MOST OF THE TIME THAT--
ALMOST ALL THE TIME--
THAT, UH...
WE&amp;apos;VE NEVER HAD
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
I MEAN, WE MAKE A GREAT TEAM,
DON&amp;apos;T YOU THINK?
- YEAH.
I&amp;apos;M NOT SURE "TEAM"
IS THE RIGHT WORD.
- BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN, RIGHT?
I DON&amp;apos;T WANT TO LOSE YOU.
I WANT YOU TO STICK AROUND...
PERMANENTLY.
- I HOPE YOU&amp;apos;RE
NOT DOING THIS
BECAUSE YOU&amp;apos;RE AFRAID
I WOULD LEAVE YOU.
- NO!
NO, I&amp;apos;M DOING IT BECAUSE
IT&amp;apos;S A--MAKES SENSE.
IT&amp;apos;S THE NEXT LOGICAL STEP.
- YOU&amp;apos;RE RIGHT.
- THAT&amp;apos;S GREAT.
THAT&amp;apos;S WONDERFUL.
THAT IS WONDERFUL.
- HI.
- YOU KNOW,
I&amp;apos;VE BEEN THINKING--
IT&amp;apos;S NOT ENOUGH
JUST TO DO A FACE-LIFT HERE.
YOU NEED A WHOLE
NEW APPROACH TO SELLING.
A SNAZZY NEW LOGO,
LOTS OF PUBLICITY--
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS COLOR?
- TRUST ME.
WHAT IS THAT?
WHERE DID YOU GET IT?
- A FRIEND.
IS IT TOO MUCH?
- NO, I LOVE IT.
MAYBE OVER THERE
BY THE DRESSING ROOMS.
IT MIGHT WORK.
- WELL, MAYBE
IT HAS ALREADY.
- HAVE YOU FALLEN FOR HARRY?
YOU HAVE, HAVEN&amp;apos;T YOU?
I KNEW IT. I KNEW IT.
I AM SO CLEVER.
- WELL, I LIKE HIM.
- LIKE? LIKE?
IS THAT ALL?
- HE&amp;apos;S SO DIFFERENT
FROM PHILIP.
- YEAH. HARRY&amp;apos;S ALIVE.
- ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU MUST KNOW,
PHILIP AND I--
- IT JUST GOES TO SHOW YOU
THAT YOU SHOULD ALWAYS LISTEN
TO YOUR SISTER.
- EXCELLENT ADVICE.
- HEY.
- HEY, YOU REALLY
MADE PROGRESS.
HERE, THIS IS YOURS, ISN&amp;apos;T IT?
- YEAH. WHERE&amp;apos;D YOU GET IT?
- DADDY FOUND IT
AFTER THE PARTY.
I FIGURED IT&amp;apos;D BE
ANOTHER YEAR BEFORE
YOU GOT OVER THERE, SO...
- THANK YOU.
- OH, FRANNY,
MY FRIEND--LAWYER--
HARRY, HE NEEDS
SOME SORT OF PHYSICAL
FOR AN INSURANCE THING.
IS THAT SOMETHING YOU COULD DO?
- SURE. HAVE HIM
CALL MY OFFICE.
I&amp;apos;LL HAVE SOMEONE SET HIM UP.
- I THINK THE CLASP IS BROKEN.
- CATE...
- WHAT?
- IS THAT A RING?
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
CYNTHIA!
[LAUGHS]
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
[LAUGHING]
MAN! [LAUGHS]
- WELCOME, PHILIP,
TO THE FAMILY.
- CHEERS.
- TO YOUR HEALTH.
- NOW, YOU&amp;apos;LL BE GIVING CAITLIN
HER FIRST REAL JOB,
AND SHE&amp;apos;LL BE A GOOD WIFE
TO YOU.
- EXCUSE ME, WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
FIRST REAL JOB?
- OH, CATE.
YOU&amp;apos;VE HAD 17 JOBS
SINCE YOU LEFT COLLEGE.
DON&amp;apos;T THINK
I HAVEN&amp;apos;T BEEN COUNTING.
BUT THIS ONE
IS A KEEPER, RIGHT, PHIL?
- I CERTAINLY HOPE SO, SIR.
- AND WHEN MY NEW GRANDCHILDREN
START SHOWING UP,
THEN SHE&amp;apos;LL REALLY KNOW
WHAT A JOB IS.
- I ALREADY HAVE A REAL JOB.
AND IN THE UNLIKELY EVENT
THAT WE HAVE CHILDREN--
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
IN THE UNLIKELY EVENT
YOU HAVE CHILDREN?
IS THERE SOMETHING
THE MATTER WITH HIM?
- NO, THERE&amp;apos;S NOTHING WRONG
WITH EITHER OF US.
JUST WE HAVEN&amp;apos;T DECIDED
WHETHER OR NOT
WE WANT TO HAVE CHILDREN.
FRANCESCA, IS THERE
SOMETHING WRONG WITH YOUR FACE?
BECAUSE IF THERE ISN&amp;apos;T,
WILL YOU STOP SQUINTING
AT YOUR SISTER LIKE
A 12-YEAR-OLD KID?
IF YOU HAVE SOMETHING
TO SAY, SAY IT.
- OK.
I DON&amp;apos;T THINK THIS IS THE TIME
TO DISCUSS THIS.
- OH, YOU DON&amp;apos;T THINK?
WELL, THIS IS STILL MY HOUSE,
AND AS LONG AS YOU&amp;apos;RE IN IT,
YOU CAN STOP TRYING TO RUN
OTHER PEOPLE&amp;apos;S LIVES.
- NO, FRANNY,
YOU CAN&amp;apos;T DO THAT,
BECAUSE, SEE,
THAT&amp;apos;S DADDY&amp;apos;S JOB.
PHILIP, I&amp;apos;D LIKE TO LEAVE.
- OH, CATE, STOP FUSSING.
SIT DOWN.
- I DON&amp;apos;T WANT TO SIT DOWN.
I WANT TO LEAVE.
- THEN LEAVE.
- CATE, LET&amp;apos;S JUST--
- LEAVE.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- WELL, THANK YOU
FOR YOUR HOSPITALITY.
- SO LONG, PHILIP.
- GOOD NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
THANK YOU, AND...
- SO...
MARRIAGE, EH?
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
- I FEEL THAT MAYBE
I SHOULD BE HAPPIER.
- I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
- CAN YOU?
- ABSOLUTELY.
BEFORE MY MARRIAGE,
MR. HENDLEY SAID TO ME
THAT EVERYTHING WOULD BE
ONE BIG, LONG PARTY.
MONTE CARLO,
SOUTH OF FRANCE, CORFU.
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A NICE PARTY.
- YES, BUT, YOU SEE, IT WASN&amp;apos;T.
I MEAN, ALL THOSE...
WASTED HOURS.
I WOULD&amp;apos;VE PREFERRED TO HAVE
BEEN OUT HERE, YOU KNOW.
I HAVE AN ABSOLUTE DREAD
OF PARTIES NOW.
THIS IS--THIS IS
WHERE YOU SHOULD BE,
WITH YOUR PLANTS,
YOUR FLOWERS, YOUR FERTILIZER.
I&amp;apos;VE GROWN TO LOVE
THIS DIRT, YOU KNOW.
IT NOURISHES THINGS.
IT GROWS THINGS.
IT PROTECTS THINGS.
I LOVE IT.
- SO YOU REGRETTED
YOUR MARRIAGE?
- OH, I WOULDN&amp;apos;T GO
THAT FAR, NO.
BUT I WOULD SAY THIS, CATE.
I WOULD SAY THAT...
MY HUSBAND WAS AS DULL
AS DITCH WATER.
AND WITHOUT YOUR MOTHER&amp;apos;S HELP,
I WOULD NEVER HAVE
MADE IT THROUGH
THE THINGS THAT WE CALLED
"OUR LITTLE TRIALS."
- MY FATHER WAS MORE
THAN A TRIAL.
- MM-HMM.
- IF IT WASN&amp;apos;T FOR HIM,
SHE MIGHT STILL BE HERE.
- OH, COME ON, CATE.
YOU KNOW YOUR MOTHER
HAD A BRAIN TUMOR.
- BEFORE SHE DIED,
SHE SAID HER TUMOR WAS...
WAS FULL OF FURY AND
THE RAGING INDIGNATION
OF THE OPPRESSED.
- [LAUGHING]
SHE MUST&amp;apos;VE BEEN READING
TOO MUCH IRISH POETRY,
IF YOU ASK ME.
[LAUGHING]
- WOULD YOU DO ME A FAVOR
AND GET THAT COLANDER, PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
WAS THAT JUST SOMETHING
BETWEEN YOU AND YOUR FATHER,
OR DO YOU REALLY NOT WANT
TO HAVE CHILDREN?
- NO, I DON&amp;apos;T THINK I DO.
- WHY NOT?
- WELL...
THERE ARE NATURAL MOTHERS,
AND THERE ARE NATURAL AUNTS,
AND I THINK I&amp;apos;M A NATURAL AUNT.
- WELL, YOU COULD--
YOU COULD AT LEAST CONSIDER IT.
- I HAVE CONSIDERED IT.
IT&amp;apos;S JUST THE WAY I SEE IT,
ONCE A WOMAN HAS CHILDREN,
NOTHING INTERESTING
EVER HAPPENS TO HER AGAIN.
I DIDN&amp;apos;T KNOW
YOU WANTED CHILDREN.
YOU NEVER TOLD ME THAT.
- THERE WAS NO REASON TO,
WAS THERE?
WHEN YOU&amp;apos;RE DONE
WITH THAT BASIL,
YOU COULD START
ON THE CILANTRO.
EXCEPT DON&amp;apos;T CHOP IT UP
LIKE YOU DID LAST TIME,
JUST...LET THE LEAVES
REMAIN WHOLE.
- WHAT&amp;apos;S THE DIFFERENCE?
IT&amp;apos;S ALL GONNA GET
MUSHED UP TOGETHER, ANYWAY.
- IT&amp;apos;S MOTHER&amp;apos;S RECIPE.
IT&amp;apos;LL BE BETTER
THIS WAY. YOU&amp;apos;LL SEE.
[CASSETTE REWINDS]
- HELLO, CATE.
IT&amp;apos;S ME--HARRY.
WELL, I HEARD
ABOUT YOUR ENGAGEMENT,
AND I, UH...
I DON&amp;apos;T KNOW WHAT TO SAY,
EXCEPT I...I STILL HOPE
TO HEAR FROM YOU AGAIN.
BYE-BYE.
- I KNOW.
I&amp;apos;M LATE.
I WAS AFRAID YOU WOULD
THINK I WASN&amp;apos;T COMING.
- OH, I WOULDN&amp;apos;T THINK THAT.
SO, UH...
WELL, HOW&amp;apos;S THE RENOVATION?
- UH, IT&amp;apos;S GOOD.
IT&amp;apos;S REALLY CHANGING.
CYNTHIA HAS GREAT IDEAS.
SOME...GREAT IDEAS.
- I&amp;apos;LL BET.
- LISTEN, I--I HAVE A PROBLEM.
- WHAT IS IT?
- IT&amp;apos;S YOU.
- I&amp;apos;M SORRY.
I WON&amp;apos;T BE A PROBLEM ANYMORE.
BUT THANK YOU FOR CALLING,
&amp;apos;CAUSE I APPRECIATE BEING ABLE
TO DO THIS IN PERSON.
I, UH...
I&amp;apos;VE FALLEN IN LOVE WITH YOU.
THAT&amp;apos;S MY PROBLEM.
BUT I DON&amp;apos;T WANT
TO BE A PROBLEM FOR YOU.
- BUT YOU ARE...
&amp;apos;CAUSE I&amp;apos;VE FALLEN
IN LOVE WITH YOU, TOO.
NOW, IS THAT GONNA BE A PROBLEM?
- OH, THAT&amp;apos;S A PROBLEM
I CAN LIVE WITH.
- AND THE LAST AND PERHAPS
THE MOST SERIOUS OBSTACLE
TO MEANINGFUL FISCAL REFORM
IS THE CONTINUED EFFORTS
OF THE LOBBYISTS...
- [WHISPERING]
- PHILIP.
- EXCUSE ME.
- THIS JUST ISN&amp;apos;T GONNA WORK.
- HE&amp;apos;S JUST TRYING
TO IMPRESS THE BANKERS.
- AND I JUST CAN&amp;apos;T SIT HERE.
- CATE, RELAX.
WE&amp;apos;RE ALMOST THROUGH HERE, OK?
RELAX.
[CROWD APPLAUDS]
- PHILIP.
I&amp;apos;M LEAVING.
- SWEETHEART, 10 MINUTES.
WE&amp;apos;RE GONNA HAVE SOME COFFEE,
AND THEN WE&amp;apos;LL BE OUT.
RELAX.
- THIS JUST ISN&amp;apos;T
GONNA WORK.
- FISCAL REFORM?
- NO, US.
I&amp;apos;M SORRY.
- THANK YOU.
- SO THE RING IS
NOWHERE IN SIGHT,
AND YOU AND HARRY
ARE AWFULLY COZY.
WHAT ARE YOU NOT TELLING ME?
- NOTHING.
- OH.
- SO THE NEW MIRRORS
GOT HERE YESTERDAY--
WHY ARE YOU LOOKING
AT ME LIKE THAT?
SO IT LOOKS LIKE WE&amp;apos;LL BE READY
FOR THE REOPENING NEXT WEEK.
- GREAT.
I&amp;apos;LL COME BACK.
- COME BACK?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- SIMON CALLED LAST NIGHT
BEGGING ME TO COME BACK
TO NEW YORK.
- OH, NO.
- I MISS HIM.
SO WE&amp;apos;RE GOING TO THERAPY,
ME AND SIMON
AND PIERCE COVINGTON.
THANK GOODNESS, BECAUSE IF
I STAY AT DADDY&amp;apos;S MUCH LONGER,
I&amp;apos;LL BE BRAIDING MY HAIR
AND GOING TO THE ORTHODONTIST.
- WHERE IS DADDY?
- MM, HE SAID HE&amp;apos;D BE LATE.
SOMETHING ABOUT
THE PLUMBING NEXT DOOR.
I THINK HE&amp;apos;S GOT
SOMETHING GOING
WITH THE WIDOW CURRINGTON.
- CATE, I LOVE IT.
THANK YOU.
- OH, YOU&amp;apos;RE WELCOME.
- IT&amp;apos;S GREAT.
LOOK AT THIS.
HUH, WHAT DO
YOU THINK?
[DOOR CLOSES]
- HEY! HEY!
WHERE&amp;apos;S MY BIRTHDAY GIRL?
- [LAUGHS] HEY!
- HELLO, DARLING.
- HEY, DOM.
- HI, HI, HI, HI.
NOW THIS IS THAT THERE
RICE-COOKER THING
THAT YOU&amp;apos;VE ALWAYS WANTED.
I GOT A GOOD DEAL ON IT.
- DADDY, THANK YOU.
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY, ANNIE.
I HOPE I DIDN&amp;apos;T MISS THE MEAL.
- DADDY, YOU REMEMBER HARRY.
- OH, YEAH.
HI. HI, HARRY.
- DOMINIC, HOW ARE YOU?
- FINE, FINE, THANKS.
- THIS MAY BE A LITTLE SUDDEN,
BUT WHILE WE&amp;apos;RE ALL
ASSEMBLED HERE, I, UH...
I&amp;apos;VE ASKED YOUR YOUNGEST
DAUGHTER CATE TO MARRY ME...
AND SHE SAID YES.
- YES! YES!
- WAIT A MINUTE.
DIDN&amp;apos;T YOU--
DIDN&amp;apos;T YOU JUST GET ENGAGED?
- YOU ARE SO DEVIOUS.
WE NEED MORE CHAMPAGNE.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- MY, MY, MY.
WELL.
PHILIP MOVED OUT,
AND HARRY MOVED RIGHT IN, HUH?
- I MOVE FAST.
- YES, YES.
SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, HARRY.
MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME.
WELL, WELL, WELL, WELL.
- HERE.
- NO, I DON&amp;apos;T WANT ANY.
- WHAT&amp;apos;S UP?
- I DON&amp;apos;T WANT ANY.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I&amp;apos;M GOING UPSTAIRS.
- WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO OFFER
MY DAUGHTER, HARRY?
I MEAN, I HARDLY KNOW YOU.
DO YOU COME FROM A GOOD FAMILY?
I MEAN, UH,
DO YOU HAVE ANY MONEY?
IS YOUR LEGAL FIRM
TOP-RANKED, WHAT?
- HARRY DOESN&amp;apos;T DO
CORPORATE LAW, ACTUALLY.
- I ASKED HIM, CATIE, NOT YOU.
- WELL, I&amp;apos;D SAY THAT...
YOUR FAMILY IS ALMOST
AS CRAZY AS MINE.
- AH.
- MONEY--I HAVE ENOUGH.
PRESTIGIOUS LAW FIRM--
DEFINITELY.
- GOOD. GOOD, GOOD.
SO, UH, HARRY,
WHY ARE YOU SO SPECIAL, THEN?
- BECAUSE SHE SAID YES.
- AH.
- AND WE&amp;apos;D LIKE
YOUR BLESSING, DOMINIC.
BUT IF YOU HAVE
ANY OBJECTION,
PLEASE SPEAK NOW.
- OH, WHY BOTHER?
CAITLIN HASN&amp;apos;T CARED ABOUT
WHAT I&amp;apos;VE SAID FOR YEARS,
HAVE YOU, CATIE?
- WELL, WE BOTH DO CARE
WHAT YOU HAVE TO SAY.
- OH, THANK YOU.
GOOD, GOOD.
WELL, THEN, UH...
I HAVE NO OBJECTION, COUNSELOR.
COME ON!
LET&amp;apos;S CELEBRATE, HUH?
COME ON! CELEBRATE!
HERE WE GO.
I DON&amp;apos;T SEE ANY FOOD.
WHAT KIND OF A PARTY
IS THIS? COME ON.
- [WHISPERING] Cate.
Cate, come here.
- What?
- Come here. I have
to talk to you.
IF YOU TELL ANYONE
THAT I TOLD YOU THIS,
I WILL DENY IT.
I COULD LOSE MY LICENSE
FOR TELLING YOU.
- WH-WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- YOU REMEMBER HARRY CAME
FOR HIS PHYSICAL?
THE LAB REPORT
ON HIS BLOOD WORK-UP
INDICATED EXCESSIVE WHITE CELLS,
SO WE SENT A SAMPLE
TO AN INDEPENDENT LAB
FOR VERIFICATION.
NOW, WE&amp;apos;RE NOT GONNA
KNOW ANYTHING
UNTIL WE GET THE SECOND LABS.
HARRY DOESN&amp;apos;T
KNOW ANYTHING YET.
- HARRY DOESN&amp;apos;T KNOW WHAT?
- I&amp;apos;M SORRY, BUT IT LOOKS
LIKE HARRY HAS LEUKEMIA.
- WELL, SHOULD WE
EVEN HAVE A BAND?
IS IT TOO MUCH?
MAYBE JUST A GUITAR...
OR A HARP.
LOVE HARPS,
IF YOU CAN STILL FIND A HARP.
DOMINIC CALLED.
HE WANTS TRUMPETS
AND LOTS OF &amp;apos;EM.
HE WANTS YOU ALL IN WHITE,
THE BRIDESMAIDS IN PINK,
AND A TROOP OF RING BEARERS
ON VALENTINE&amp;apos;S DAY.
- WHY DIDN&amp;apos;T HE CALL ME?
- WELL, HE WAS AFRAID YOU
WOULDN&amp;apos;T GO FOR THE TRUMPETS.
- DO YOU--
DO YOU REALLY WANT
A BIG WEDDING?
- IF YOU DO.
- WELL, IT SOUNDS
KIND OF AWFUL.
DAD YELLING
AT EVERYBODY AND...
- OH, I GET THE PICTURE.
- WE COULD JUST...
YOU KNOW, GET MARRIED.
- NO RING BEARERS.
- NO ANYTHING.
JUST US.
- AND WE WOULDN&amp;apos;T HAVE TO WAIT
TILL VALENTINE&amp;apos;S DAY.
- WE WOULDN&amp;apos;T HAVE
TO WAIT AT ALL.
- I&amp;apos;D LIKE THAT.
- ENOUGH TO DO IT?
- THIS IS NOT ALL ABOUT
ANNOYING DOMINIC, IS IT?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
IT&amp;apos;S JUST, IF--
IF WE WANT TO--
AND--AND I WANT TO--
WHY WAIT?
- GO GET MARRIED.
- YEAH.
- HARRY, DO YOU TAKE THIS WOMAN
TO BE YOUR WEDDED WIFE?
- I DO.
- AND, CAITLIN,
DO YOU TAKE THIS MAN TO BE
YOUR WEDDED HUSBAND?
- I DO.
- THEN BY THE POWER VESTED IN ME
BY THE GREAT
COMMONWEALTH OF VIRGINIA,
I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU
MAN AND WIFE.
YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE,
SIR, AND--
[POUNDING]
- I, UH---
I HOPE YOU&amp;apos;RE NOT
TOO DISAPPOINTED,
NO BIG WEDDING AND ALL.
CATE AND I
PREFERRED IT THAT WAY.
- GIVE ME THAT BRACE AND BIT,
WILL YOU?
OH, CAITLIN&amp;apos;S A GROWN WOMAN.
SHE CAN DO WHAT SHE WANTS.
SHE&amp;apos;S A LOT LIKE HER MOTHER.
- UH, THE BRACE THING
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT?
- YEAH, THAT THING
WITH THE HANDLE THERE.
THE BROWN THING.
- OH.
- NEAR THE WIRE.
- I DON&amp;apos;T KNOW A SCREWDRIVER
FROM A SOCKET WRENCH.
- [CHUCKLES]
DON&amp;apos;T WORRY.
YOU DON&amp;apos;T NEED TO BE HANDY
WITH CAITLIN AROUND.
YEAH.
OK.
GET OUT FROM UNDERNEATH.
- YOU ARE SOMETHING, CATE.
DON&amp;apos;T YOU PAY ATTENTION
TO WHAT ANYBODY SAYS TO YOU?
COULDN&amp;apos;T YOU
AT LEAST HAVE WAITED
UNTIL WE KNEW FOR SURE?
- THAT WOULD BE--
THAT WOULD BE SUCH A MISTAKE.
HE COULD LIVE FOR YEARS
AND YEARS AND YEARS
AND--AND BE FINE.
- LIVE FOR YEARS, YES.
BE FINE, I&amp;apos;M NOT SO SURE.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT AT ALL ABOUT
WHAT YOUR LIFE IS GOING
TO BE LIKE WITH HIM?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
OH...
[RING]
HELLO.
HEY.
YEAH, SHE&amp;apos;S RIGHT HERE.
HANG ON.
IT&amp;apos;S CYNTHIA.
- OH, OH.
HELLO.
- MRS. HARRY DIETRICH.
I AM SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
- YOU&amp;apos;RE THE ONLY ONE SO FAR
WHO&amp;apos;S ACTUALLY SAID THAT.
- WHAT DID DAD SAY?
- NOT MUCH.
HE&amp;apos;S ALREADY GOT HARRY
UP ON A LADDER.
THEY SEEM TO BE HITTING IT OFF.
- HE LIKES HARRY BECAUSE
HE STANDS UP TO HIM.
- I STAND UP TO HIM.
HE DOESN&amp;apos;T LIKE ME.
- YOU&amp;apos;RE HIS DAUGHTER.
OH, HEY, LISTEN.
SIMON IS GONNA COME
TO THE OPENING,
SO WE&amp;apos;LL GET
SOME FREE PRESS.
- OH, GREAT.
FAME AT LAST.
CYNTHIA?
- YEAH?
- THANK YOU.
- YOU&amp;apos;RE WELCOME.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
- OH, HI. YOU&amp;apos;RE HOME.
WHAT&amp;apos;S WRONG?
IS EVERYTHING OK?
- NO.
- WHAT?
- YOU REMEMBER THE, UH...
THE INSURANCE PHYSICAL I HAD
A COUPLE WEEKS AGO?
WELL, HE CALLED TODAY.
I HAVE LEUKEMIA.
YOU KNEW THAT, DIDN&amp;apos;T YOU?
FRANCESCA TOLD YOU.
- SHE WASN&amp;apos;T SURE.
- SHE TOLD YOU BEFORE
WE GOT MARRIED, DIDN&amp;apos;T SHE?
- SHE DIDN&amp;apos;T KNOW FOR SURE,
AND I THOUGHT THAT
IF YOU KNEW OR...
OR EVEN SUSPECTED, THAT YOU&amp;apos;D--
- MAKE AN INFORMED DECISION
ABOUT MY FUTURE?
ABOUT OUR FUTURE?
YOU DIDN&amp;apos;T THINK
I WAS UP TO THAT?
- NO, WAIT.
I THOUGHT YOU WOULDN&amp;apos;T WANT
TO MARRY ME.
- OH.
I PROMISED YOU THE LIFE I--
I MEAN, I HAVE TO GIVE YOU.
- I--
I LOVE YOU, SICK OR NOT.
- I LOVE YOU.
- [PEOPLE TALKING]
- I CAN KEEP THOSE TO THE SIDE
WHILE YOU KEEP LOOKING.
- THANKS.
- NOW, CATE,
EVERYTHING&amp;apos;S MARKED.
EVERYTHING&amp;apos;S FINE.
YOU&amp;apos;RE UP AND GOING, OK, CATE?
- NO!
- NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU KNOW ME AT PARTIES.
I&amp;apos;LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
GOOD LUCK.
- HI.
HELLO, ANGEL.
- CATE, IT LOOKS GREAT.
- THANK YOU. THANKS.
HEY.
- HI. GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- OH, HOW ARE YOU?
- LOOKS GREAT.
- THANK YOU.
- THANKS FOR COMING.
SHE REALLY APPRECIATES IT.
- FAMILY SOLIDARITY.
- THAT&amp;apos;S RIGHT.
- HOW YOU FEELING?
- GREAT.
ASK ME AGAIN NEXT WEEK.
SIMON&amp;apos;S HERE.
CAN&amp;apos;T MISS HIM.
[WOMEN SCREAMING]
- HEY, HOW YA DOING?
HI. ALL RIGHT.
[CAMERAS CLICKING]
ONE MORE.
- LOOK, IT WAS NAMED FOR ME.
- OH.
- WHAT&amp;apos;S GOING ON?
- HAVEN&amp;apos;T YOU EVER HEARD
OF "COVINGTON HEIGHTS"?
- THAT SILLY SOAP OPERA?
I DON&amp;apos;T HAVE TIME--
[GASPS] IT&amp;apos;S PIERCE!
- CATE.
- HELLO.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. GOOD TO SEE YOU.
THE PLACE LOOKS GREAT.
- THANK YOU.
- CAN I HAVE YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
- YEAH, SURE, SWEETHEART.
WHAT&amp;apos;S YOUR NAME?
- YOU NAMED IT FOR ME.
- YES, I DID.
- I MIGHT HAVE TO OPEN
A NEW YORK BRANCH.
HARRY.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
I&amp;apos;M SORRY.
YOU MUST BE TIRED
OF HEARING THAT.
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
IT&amp;apos;S--IT&amp;apos;S
THE BRAVE SMILE I WEAR
THAT GETS A LITTLE EXHAUSTING.
- CHEERS.
- AND THIS MUST BE HARRY.
HOW ARE YA?
- [CHUCKLES]
NICE TO MEET YOU, SIMON.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
CATE, MY PUBLICIST
WANTS A WORD WITH YOU
IF YOU HAVE A MOMENT,
SOMETHING ABOUT THE "POST."
- THE NEWSPAPER?
- YOUR 15 MINUTES OF FAME
COMING RIGHT UP.
- WOW.
- SIMON, LOOK AT THESE HATS.
AREN&amp;apos;T THEY BEAUTIFUL?
CATE&amp;apos;S FRIEND MAKES THEM.
I WANT ALL OF OUR BRIDESMAIDS
TO WEAR ARABELLAS.
WON&amp;apos;T IT BE BRILLIANT?
- WHO&amp;apos;S ARABELLA?
- IF SIMON&amp;apos;S I.Q. WAS HIGHER
THAN THE SPEED LIMIT,
HE&amp;apos;D NEVER SURVIVE CYNTHIA.
- [CHUCKLES]
CAN&amp;apos;T BE EASY
LIVING WITH A GODDESS.
- TELL ME ABOUT IT.
SINCE I WAS 13,
SHE&amp;apos;S MADE ME FEEL ORDINARY.
- THERE&amp;apos;S NOTHING
ORDINARY ABOUT YOU.
- [CHUCKLES]
- YOU&amp;apos;RE A LOT
TO LIVE UP TO, DOCTOR.
- OH, HARRY.
- YEAH?
- HARRY, HERE IT IS.
"SISTER OF TOP MODEL
CYNTHIA De ANGELO,
"CAITLIN DIETRICH
SHOWS FASHION FLAIR
"MORE ATTUNED TO MANHATTAN
"THAN CLEVELAND PARK.
"THIS TINY SHOP
IS A RETRO GEM,
"ITS VINTAGE CLOTHING
"ROMANTIC AND GLAMOROUS,
PERFECT FOR THE 21st CENTURY."
- CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU&amp;apos;RE A HIT.
- YOU WANNA SEE?
- YEAH.
- [SIGHS]
- ARE YOU GONNA BE SICK AGAIN?
- ABSOLUTELY.
PROBABLY NOT IN THE NEXT,
UH, 2, 3 MINUTES.
- IT&amp;apos;LL BE OK.
WE&amp;apos;LL GET THROUGH THIS.
- AREN&amp;apos;T YOU GOING IN
TO THE SHOP TODAY?
- NO. NO, I THOUGHT
I&amp;apos;D STAY HOME WITH YOU.
- [CHUCKLES]
I HATE YOU SEEING ME
SICK LIKE THIS.
- BUT THIS IS HOW YOU ARE.
THIS IS--THIS IS WHAT WE&amp;apos;VE GOT.
- TRUE...
AND SOON I&amp;apos;LL BE BEGGING YOU
TO STAY HOME WITH ME,
BUT COME ON, GO.
TAKE THAT WITH YOU.
- [CHUCKLES]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
MINUTE.
OOH.
OH.
- HI.
- HOW ARE YA?
- FINE. HOW&amp;apos;S IT GOING?
- COME ON IN.
- OH, THANKS.
THIS TIME GOOD FOR YOU?
- SURE, SURE.
- I THOUGHT MAYBE WE COULD
PLAY A LITTLE CHESS.
YOU PLAY CHESS, DON&amp;apos;T YOU?
- YEAH, A LITTLE.
CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING?
- NO, NO, I&amp;apos;M FINE.
- AH, COME ON.
I GOT 52 VARIETIES
OF HERBAL TEA.
YOU SURE?
- [LAUGHS] NO, THANKS,
I&amp;apos;M GOOD. I&amp;apos;M OK.
- I DON&amp;apos;T BLAME YOU.
- WHERE YOU WANNA GO?
RIGHT HERE?
- IS THIS ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, IT&amp;apos;S FINE.
CHECK AND MATE.
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS]
WHERE&amp;apos;D YOU LEARN TO DO THAT?
- SERVICE.
- YOU WERE IN THE SERVICE?
- YEAH, JUST AFTER COLLEGE,
BEFORE LAW SCHOOL.
- OH. ALL RIGHT.
AS ONE SERVICEMAN TO ANOTHER...
HAVE A LOOK AT THIS.
- WOW. WHICH ONE ARE YOU?
- ME AT THE END THERE.
- WHERE WAS THIS?
- KOREA, &amp;apos;51.
I STILL GOT A HUNK OF SHRAPNEL
IN MY SHOULDER TO REMIND ME.
- PURPLE HEART?
- YEAH...AND NAVY CROSS.
- WOW. WHAT HAPPENED?
- WELL, WE WERE
PATROLLING OFFSHORE
TO PICK UP SOME PILOT
THAT HAD GOT SHOT DOWN,
AND ME AND MY BEST BUDDY,
KENNY, THIS GUY HERE,
WE WERE WORKING
THE FORWARD TURRET.
WE GOT A DIRECT HIT
JUST BELOW THE GUN MOUNT,
AND, UH,
IN A COUPLE OF SECONDS,
IT WAS LIKE THE WHOLE WORLD
WAS ON FIRE.
I KNEW THE MAGAZINE WAS GONNA GO
BECAUSE WE HAD
POWDER BAGS ALL OVER.
SO I MANAGED
TO GET HOLD OF THE HOSE,
AND I&amp;apos;M HOSING EVERYTHING DOWN.
WELL, I SEE KENNY ON THE DECK.
HE WAS BURNT.
OH, HE WAS BURNT BAD.
SO, UH,
FINALLY GOT HIM OUT AND...
CARRIED HIM TOPSIDE.
IT WAS OVER.
WHY DON&amp;apos;T YOU--
WHY DON&amp;apos;T YOU STRETCH OUT,
LAY DOWN, BE COMFORTABLE.
- I DON&amp;apos;T MIND IF I DO.
- GOOD, COME ON.
I&amp;apos;LL GIVE YOU A HAND.
HERE, LET&amp;apos;S PUT THIS OVER YOU.
- YEAH, THANKS.
ALL RIGHT, THANKS.
YOU DON&amp;apos;T HAVE TO TUCK ME IN.
IT&amp;apos;S ALL RIGHT.
- [LAUGHS]
I&amp;apos;M SORRY. IT&amp;apos;S A...
IT&amp;apos;S AN OLD HABIT.
[ELEVATOR BELL RINGS]
CATE.
- HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- WELL, SOMEONE
SHOULD BE WITH HIM.
YOU WEREN&amp;apos;T.
- YOU&amp;apos;RE HOME EARLY.
WHAT&amp;apos;S WRONG?
- I&amp;apos;M PREGNANT.
- REALLY?
- IS THIS TOO MUCH?
CAN YOU HANDLE IT?
- OH, YEAH.
OH, YEAH.
WE&amp;apos;RE GONNA HAVE A BABY?
HELLO.
- HE CAN&amp;apos;T TALK YET.
- GOTTA START SOMETIME.
CONGRATULATIONS, MOM.
- YOU, TOO.
- I GUESS I&amp;apos;M NOT
DYING AFTER ALL,
NOT RIGHT AWAY, ANYWAY.
- GOT A LONG WAY TO GO YET.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WELL, TECHNICALLY,
YOUR HUSBAND&amp;apos;S IN REMISSION,
BUT IT CAN REOCCUR AT ANY TIME.
HOWEVER, THE EFFECTS
OF THE CHEMO,
THE WEIGHT LOSS AND NAUSEA,
SHOULD EASE OFF IN A FEW DAYS.
OK, HARRY?
- IT&amp;apos;S OK WITH ME.
- WE&amp;apos;LL SEE YOU IN 2 WEEKS.
- ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, DOCTOR.
- CATE!
- OH, HI.
OH.
- HOW ARE YOU?
- I&amp;apos;M GOOD--I&amp;apos;M GREAT.
- OH, YES.
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
- THANKS.
- AND HOW&amp;apos;S HARRY?
I UNDERSTAND THAT HE--HE--
- HE&amp;apos;S GREAT.
HE&amp;apos;S GOOD.
- LOOK, HONESTLY,
IF THERE&amp;apos;S ANYTHING,
ANYTHING I CAN DO,
DON&amp;apos;T HESITATE.
MAY I INTRODUCE...
CAROL, MY FIANCEE.
- HI.
OH, OH, UH--
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
I--I THINK THAT&amp;apos;S GREAT.
- GOD, IT&amp;apos;S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- YOU, TOO.
- YOU LOOK, UM,
SO...
- ENORMOUS?
- NO! NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU LOOK...
WONDERFUL.
CONTENT.
IT&amp;apos;S A GOOD LOOK.
- [CHUCKLES]
- WELL, WE BETTER RUN.
- ME, TOO.
IT WAS NICE TO MEET YOU.
- NICE MEETING YOU.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
- SEE YOU.
COME ON.
SO?
- SHE&amp;apos;S GREAT.
- LISTEN, WE GOT
A 7:00 TEE TIME TOMORROW.
WE&amp;apos;RE STILL LOOKING
FOR A FOURTH.
- OH, I WISH I COULD BE THERE.
WHERE YOU PLAYING?
- ROCK CREEK.
- OH.
- THANKS, FRANCESCA.
HOW YA FEELING, ANYWAY?
- PRETTY GOOD.
- YEAH, &amp;apos;CAUSE, UH,
I HEAR YOUR LAST TEST RESULTS
WERE REALLY GREAT.
- YEAH, THEY WERE.
I JUST GOT &amp;apos;EM BACK
THIS MORNING.
HOW&amp;apos;D YOU FIND OUT?
FROM FAMILY NEWS NETWORK
OVER THERE?
- WASN&amp;apos;T ME.
CATE TOLD US.
- HARRY, YOU LOOK GOOD,
BUT I WISH YOU&amp;apos;D PUT ON
SOME WEIGHT.
- YEAH, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO START DOING
A LITTLE WALKING
EVERY DAY IF YOU LIKE.
- FOR HEAVEN&amp;apos;S SAKES,
LEAVE THE MAN ALONE.
BUNCH OF INTERFERING WOMEN.
- I LOVE THE INTERFERENCE,
AND SO DO YOU,
ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY INTERFERE
WITH A GOOD MEAL.
- WELL, COOKING IS ONE THING,
BUT THEY DON&amp;apos;T
HAVE TO RUN OUR LIVES.
- NO, COOKING&amp;apos;S--COOKING&amp;apos;S FINE,
AND FRANNY CAN BE A DOCTOR
AS LONG AS SHE SETS THE TABLE
AND DOES THE DISHES.
- SHE WOULDN&amp;apos;T BE A DOCTOR
IF IT WASN&amp;apos;T FOR ME.
I WANTED HER TO GO ON
TO BE A SURGEON.
- IT&amp;apos;S NEVER ENOUGH, IS IT?
- YOU&amp;apos;RE CRITICIZING ME
FOR HELPING YOUR SISTER
MAKE SOMETHING OF HERSELF?
- COME ON.
IT&amp;apos;S THE FOURTH OF JULY.
WE&amp;apos;RE ALL HERE TOGETHER.
LET&amp;apos;S JUST BE HAPPY.
- HARRY, LET&amp;apos;S GO.
- YOU&amp;apos;RE NOT WALKING OUT
ON ANOTHER FAMILY DINNER,
ARE YOU, CATE?
- OH, HONEY, COME ON.
WHERE YOU GOING?
- TAKE--TAKE--TAKE MY PURSE.
WE&amp;apos;RE GOING TO THE HOSPITAL
SO I CAN HAVE THE BABY.
- REALLY?
- YES, REALLY.
I DARE YOU TO TELL ME
I LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
- YOU DO.
YOU&amp;apos;RE BEAUTIFUL.
AND SO&amp;apos;S THIS TINY, LITTLE BOY.
- DIDN&amp;apos;T FEEL SO TINY TO ME.
- NO. [CHUCKLES]
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- I THINK HE&amp;apos;S PERFECT.
STILL A LITTLE RED
AND WRINKLY...
BUT TOUGH.
- ARE YOU OK?
RIGHT THERE?
- YEAH.
- HI!
[ALL LAUGHING]
- HEY.
- [CRYING]
- OHH!
- I WAS JUST SAYING HOW GREAT
IT WAS TO BE HOME
AND ALONE AGAIN.
- DINNER IS IN THE OVEN ON LOW,
THE TABLE IS SET,
AND THE CRIB IS ALL MADE UP...
AND WE...ARE OUT OF HERE.
- OH--OH, JUST A SEC.
- HE LOOKS JUST LIKE
THAT CUPID IN THE STORE.
- COME ON. YOU CAN ADMIRE
THE BABY LATER.
- OHH!
- THAT&amp;apos;S BETTER, HUH? BYE!
- [LAUGHS]
THANKS, YOU GUYS.
- THANKS! BYE-BYE!
[DOOR CLOSES]
NOW, I THINK YOU COULD
USE A FEW MORE SISTERS.
- [LAUGHS]
- ANYONE ELSE
I CAN EXPECT TODAY?
- NOPE.
JUST ME.
ME AND THE LITTLE GUY.
- IT&amp;apos;S GOOD TO BE HOME.
- YEAH.
ARE YOU ASLEEP?
I CAN HEAR YOU BLINKING.
- OH, I THINK OUR SLEEPING DAYS
ARE OVER.
I&amp;apos;M LAYING HERE THINKING
ABOUT PATRICK...
WHAT MIGHT BECOME OF HIM.
- HE&amp;apos;S GONNA BE JUST LIKE YOU.
- THAT&amp;apos;S WHAT I&amp;apos;M AFRAID OF.
PRETTY SOON HE&amp;apos;LL BE DRIVING.
AND WE&amp;apos;LL BE LYING AWAKE
WAITING FOR HIM TO COME HOME.
- THEN YOU CAN GO OUT
AND GET HIM.
- I WILL, TOO.
- I KNOW YOU WILL.
- AREN&amp;apos;T YOU A LITTLE WORRIED?
- RIGHT NOW I&amp;apos;M JUST
HAPPY TO LOOK AT HIM.
- THINK WE&amp;apos;RE UP TO THIS?
- OH, YEAH.
- IT&amp;apos;S WAY PAST TIME
YOU LEARNED HOW TO WALK, PAL.
GOOD MORNING.
- OH, CATE, HI.
COME HERE, COME HERE,
COME HERE. GOOD NEWS.
- WHAT?
- PROFIT, PROFIT, PROFIT.
4 MONTHS IN A ROW.
EVEN THE HATS ARE SELLING.
- NO.
- THIS IS A DEFINITE TREND HERE.
- DID YOU HEAR THAT?
LOOKS LIKE YOU&amp;apos;RE GONNA BE ABLE
TO GO TO COLLEGE AFTER ALL.
OHH. I FEEL LIKE I&amp;apos;VE BEEN AWAKE
SINCE THE DAY HE WAS BORN.
- OH, DARLING, LET ME
HOLD HIM, PLEASE.
I&amp;apos;D LOVE TO, YES.
OHH...[BABY TALK]
HE&amp;apos;S SLEEPY.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
- CYNTHIA&amp;apos;S.
YES?
WHAT--
WHERE?
OH...
STAY WITH HIM.
I&amp;apos;LL BE BACK.
- HE&amp;apos;S DOING FINE.
- TELL ME THE TRUTH.
- HIS IMMUNE SYSTEM&amp;apos;S
SUPPRESSED.
HE APPEARS TO BE
CLINICALLY STABLE,
BUT WE&amp;apos;LL WATCH HIM
FOR A FEW DAYS.
- I WISH I HAD A STRONGER IDEA
THAT YOU PEOPLE KNEW
WHAT YOU WERE DOING.
I&amp;apos;M SORRY.
- DON&amp;apos;T BE SORRY.
I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
SOMETIMES I THINK
WE&amp;apos;VE BEATEN THIS THING.
OTHER TIMES...
IT SEEMS LIKE
IT&amp;apos;S LAUGHING AT US.
WE DON&amp;apos;T KNOW IT ALL.
YOU GO HOME
AND GET SOME SLEEP.
I&amp;apos;LL LOOK IN ON HARRY
LATER TONIGHT.
WE&amp;apos;LL CALL
IF THERE&amp;apos;S ANY CHANGE.
- 7 POUNDS, 11 OUNCES.
OH, YOU&amp;apos;RE GETTING SO BIG.
ARE YOU GETTING ANY SLEEP?
- I NAP AT THE HOSPITAL.
- [CRYING]
- OHH!
- YES, SUGAR.
I CAN GIVE YOU A SEDATIVE.
- NO. I&amp;apos;M ALL RIGHT.
MM. FRANCESCA?
THANKS FOR NOT SAYING
"I TOLD YOU SO."
- I&amp;apos;M SORRY I CAN&amp;apos;T MAKE
EVERYTHING BETTER FOR YOU.
YOU&amp;apos;RE VERY BRAVE, CATIE.
[DOOR CLOSES]
- [CRYING]
[CATE BLOWS OUT CANDLE]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[KNOCKING]
- HI, CATE.
- HI.
- I HAVE SOMETHING FOR THE BABY.
I WAS IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD,
SO I THOUGHT I&amp;apos;D DROP ON UP.
- OH...
UH...
YEAH, WELL, THAT&amp;apos;S--
THAT&amp;apos;S REALLY SWEET, DAD.
THAT&amp;apos;S CUTE.
BUT HE&amp;apos;S--HE&amp;apos;S ASLEEP.
- OH.
WELL, I&amp;apos;LL JUST--I&amp;apos;LL
JUST PUT IT DOWN HERE.
- OK.
- SO, UH, HOW&amp;apos;S HARRY DOING?
- HE&amp;apos;S GOOD.
HE&amp;apos;S HOLDING HIS OWN.
WHATEVER THAT MEANS.
- GOOD. GOOD.
NOW, CAN I SEE THE BABY?
- OH, I, UM--HE WAS
UP ALL NIGHT,
SO I&amp;apos;D LIKE TO LET HIM SLEEP.
- I&amp;apos;M NOT SURPRISED
HE&amp;apos;S UP ALL NIGHT
IF HE SLEEPS ALL DAY, CATE.
YOU DON&amp;apos;T HAVE TO GO TO HIM
EVERY TIME HE CRIES.
LET HIM CRY.
HE&amp;apos;LL GET THE MESSAGE.
NOW, CAN I SEE THE BABY--
- UH, DAD, I JUST--
I JUST PUT HIM DOWN.
I DON&amp;apos;T WANT TO WAKE HIM UP.
- I DIDN&amp;apos;T ASK YOU
TO WAKE HIM UP.
I JUST WANT TO LOOK AT HIM.
I WANT TO SEE
WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE.
LET ME LOOK AT HIM.
- WHY DO YOU HAVE
TO THINK OF EVERYTHING
IN TERMS OF HOW
IT AFFECTS YOU?
HE&amp;apos;S ASLEEP.
UH, COME BACK
LATER OR NOT.
I DON&amp;apos;T REALLY CARE.
BUT YOU CAN&amp;apos;T SEE HIM NOW.
PLEASE GO.
- I KNOW WHAT YOU&amp;apos;RE
AFRAID OF, CATE.
YOU&amp;apos;RE AFRAID
THAT HARRY WILL DIE,
AND YOU DON&amp;apos;T WANT
TO LIVE WITHOUT HIM.
THAT&amp;apos;S HOW I FELT
ABOUT YOUR MOTHER.
BUT YOU&amp;apos;RE GOING TO LIVE, CATE.
YOUR LIFE WON&amp;apos;T BE THE SAME,
BUT YOU&amp;apos;LL LIVE.
- [SIGHS]
- HOW ARE YOU HOLDING UP?
- ME?
- MM.
- [SIGHS]
WELL...
PATRICK IS FINALLY SLEEPING
THROUGH THE NIGHT...
- GREAT.
- AND...
UM...
I TOLD MY FATHER TO GET LOST,
WHICH APPARENTLY HE HAS.
- WHY DID YOU TELL HIM
TO DO THAT?
- HE JUST--HE DROPPED BY
ONE TOO MANY TIMES.
HE SHOWED UP.
I&amp;apos;D BEEN UP ALL NIGHT
WITH THE BABY,
AND HE WANTED ME TO WAKE HIM UP.
- WELL...HE&amp;apos;S LONELY.
- YEAH, WITH GOOD REASON.
- HIS WIFE IS DEAD.
HIS DAUGHTERS HAVE LEFT.
AND THEY HAVE PRETTY GOOD LIVES,
WITH NO SMALL THANKS TO HIM.
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
HE&amp;apos;S DONE NOTHING
BUT SINGLE ME OUT
FROM DAY ONE.
TRIED TO CRUSH ME,
LIKE HE DID MY MOTHER.
I JUST--RIGHT NOW I JUST
WANT HIM OUT OF MY LIFE.
- THERE IS SO MUCH MORE
TO HIM THAN YOU CAN SEE.
AND THERE&amp;apos;S SO MUCH MORE
TO YOU THAN HE CAN SEE.
BUT OUR SON DESERVES
A GRANDFATHER.
ESPECIALLY ONE
THAT WANTS TO BE AROUND.
- IF YOU DIE?
- IF I LIVE, I WANT HIM
TO KNOW DOMINIC.
[BELLS RINGING]
- GOD BLESS YOU.
- THANK YOU, FATHER.
- HELLO, CATE.
- I&amp;apos;M SO GLAD YOU COULD DO IT.
- OHH.
- THANK YOU, FATHER.
- HI, HARRY.
- IT WAS
A BEAUTIFUL CHRISTENING.
SAY THANK YOU, PATRICK.
NOW YOU SAY,
"THANK YOU, FATHER."
- OHH.
- THERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU GO.
[LAUGHS]
YOU WERE GREAT, PAL.
YOU WERE GREAT.
GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
GOOD JOB.
AUNT FRANNY...
UNCLE JERRY.
- HI, SWEETIE.
- AUNT ANNETTE...
- I SEE CAITLIN&amp;apos;S...
KEEPING UP YOUR FLOWERS.
WELL, GRACE, THEY&amp;apos;RE ALL HERE.
EVEN THE ACTOR.
I THINK I&amp;apos;M GONNA HAVE TO GET
A LARGER DINING ROOM TABLE.
OH, GRACIE.
GRACIE, I MISS YOU SO MUCH.
JUST LIKE YOU ALWAYS
SAID I WOULD.
- HI.
- OH, HI.
- UH, NO.
DAD, WAIT. I...
THIS IS AS GOOD A PLACE AS ANY.
BETTER THAN MOST, I...
[VOICE CRACKING]
WELL, I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY,
NOT JUST FOR
WHAT I SAID LAST WEEK--
- I WAS WRONG.
DROPPING BY
WITHOUT CALLING FIRST.
- NO! DAD, WOULD YOU JUST
LET ME SAY IT!
- HE WAS PROBABLY SO STUNNED
TO HEAR THE WORD "APOLOGIZE"
COME OUT OF CATE&amp;apos;S MOUTH,
HE DIDN&amp;apos;T KNOW
WHAT TO DO WITH HIMSELF.
GRACE, MAYA, GO AND WASH UP.
WE&amp;apos;RE EATING IN 5 MINUTES.
- WELL, WE DON&amp;apos;T KNOW
WHAT TO DO, EITHER.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- WELL, WE DON&amp;apos;T.
CYNTHIA, YOU JUST SPOIL HIM,
AND FRANCESCA IS TOO BUSY,
AND I...
HAVE ALWAYS THOUGHT
IT WAS CATE&amp;apos;S ISSUE
AND IT DIDN&amp;apos;T AFFECT ME,
BUT LET&amp;apos;S FACE IT...
IT AFFECTS ALL OF US.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- IS ANYBODY TALKING
TO ANYBODY?
- I TRIED THAT.
DIDN&amp;apos;T WORK.
- CAITLIN.
WHAT WENT ON BETWEEN ME
AND YOUR MOTHER
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU.
- FINE.
- AT YOUR AGE, I SHOULD THINK
YOU&amp;apos;D UNDERSTAND THAT.
- I UNDERSTAND EVERYTHING.
I SAW THE WAY YOU TREATED HER.
I THOUGHT YOU HATED HER.
I USED TO DREAM ABOUT
RUNNING AWAY WITH HER
SO SHE COULD HAVE SOME PEACE.
- DON&amp;apos;T TELL ME HOW I FELT
ABOUT MY WIFE!
YOU THOUGHT I DIDN&amp;apos;T
LOVE YOUR MOTHER?
HOW COULD YOU THINK THAT?
- BECAUSE YOU YELLED AT HER
LIKE YOU&amp;apos;RE YELLING AT ME!
I&amp;apos;M SORRY.
MAYBE I DIDN&amp;apos;T UNDERSTAND,
AND--AND--
I WAS TRYING
TO SAY I WAS SORRY.
- WELL...
BETTER LATE THAN NEVER, I GUESS.
- THAT&amp;apos;S NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
WHETHER YOU ACCEPT
HER APOLOGY OR YOU DON&amp;apos;T.
- MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS,
FRANCESCA.
- THIS IS MY BUSINESS, DAMN IT.
- DON&amp;apos;T CURSE AT THIS TABLE!
- HA HA!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOUR YELLING DOESN&amp;apos;T
INTIMIDATE ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT DOES?
IT GIVES ME A HEADACHE.
FROM NOW ON, IF YOU HAVE
ANYTHING TO SAY TO ME,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
YOU WILL SAY IT
IN A RESPECTFUL MANNER,
LIKE A HUMAN BEING!
- ARE YOU FINISHED?
- NO, WE&amp;apos;RE NOT.
WELL, AT ANY RATE, I&amp;apos;M NOT.
YOU CAN&amp;apos;T EVEN ACCEPT
CATE&amp;apos;S APOLOGY
WITHOUT STICKING
IN YOUR 2 CENTS&amp;apos; WORTH
OF ANGER AND BITTERNESS.
WELL, IT&amp;apos;S NOT RIGHT!
AND I&amp;apos;M NOT GONNA SIT HERE
AND LET IT GO BY.
- HONEY--
- NO! I&amp;apos;M TIRED OF SMILING
AND PRETENDING EVERYTHING&amp;apos;S OK.
IT&amp;apos;S NOT OK!
- YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO SAY THAT TO ME.
I DON&amp;apos;T SEE ANY OF YOU
RAISING 4 KIDS
AND BUILDING A BUSINESS
AT THE SAME TIME.
WITH A SICK WIFE IN BED!
- SHE WASN&amp;apos;T SICK.
SHE WAS DRUNK.
- DON&amp;apos;T YOU
CRITICIZE YOUR MOTHER
AT THIS TABLE.
AND NOT A ONE OF YOU
CAN EVEN COME THIS CLOSE TO HER!
OH, I THANK GOD
SHE&amp;apos;S NOT HERE
TO LISTEN TO WHAT
YOU HAVE TO SAY!
- DAD!
YOU CAN&amp;apos;T JUST WALK
AWAY FROM ME AGAIN!
- I CAN. IF YOU&amp;apos;RE GOING
TO ATTACK HER.
- WHY WOULD I ATTACK HER?
[CRYING]
I LOST HER, TOO!
SHE WAS MY MOTHER!
- [TAKES DEEP BREATH]
I&amp;apos;D FIND HER
OUT HERE SOMETIMES...
CURLED UP ON THIS BENCH.
SLEEPING IT OFF.
I TRIED EVERYTHING I COULD
TO GET HER TO STOP,
BUT NOTHING WORKED.
I COULDN&amp;apos;T SAVE HER.
FINALLY, ALL I COULD
DO WAS YELL,
AND THAT ONLY MADE THINGS WORSE.
FOR YOU AND EVERYBODY.
[SOFTLY] I&amp;apos;M SORRY.
WITH HER GONE, I FEEL LIKE
I&amp;apos;VE LOST SOMETHING OF MYSELF.
- ME, TOO.
- WELL...
AT LEAST WE HAVE
ONE THING IN COMMON.
- [TAKES DEEP BREATH]
THAT AND--
AND YOUR GRANDSON.
- YOU, HARRY, AND THE BABY...
WHATEVER HAPPENS, CATIE...
WE&amp;apos;LL GET THROUGH IT.
- [SNIFFLING]
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
HALLMARK CHANNEL
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--