Man:
ON JUNE 8th, 1712,
THE SANTA CRUZ,
FLAGSHIP OF SPAIN'S
LUCRATIVE GALLEON TRADE,
LEFT BARCELONA HEADED
FOR THE NEW WORLD.
- [ grunting ]
- [ shouting in Spanish ]
SLEEK AND FAST,
SHE CROSSED THE ATLANTIC
IN RECORD TIME.
BUT AS THE SANTA CRUZ
NEARED THE NEW WORLD,
SHE ENCOUNTERED
A STORM AT SEA,
THE LIKES OF WHICH THE CREW
HAD NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
TERRIBLE WIND AND WAVES POUNDED
THE VESSEL,
MAKING IT IMPOSSIBLE
TO NAVIGATE.
[ yelling in Spanish ]
FOR DAYS THE CREW SAILED ON,
OBLIVIOUS TO THEIR COURSE.
THE DOOMED SHIP FOUNDERED
ON AN UNCHARTED REEF
AND QUICKLY DISAPPEARED
BENEATH THE WAVES...
TAKING THE ENTIRE CREW
WITH HER.
IT IS RUMORED THAT
THE SANTA CRUZ
CARRIED PRICELESS DIAMONDS
AND JEWELS--
THE CROWN JEWELS
OF THE SPANISH MONARCHY.
I CAN'T PROMISE YOU GUYS
WE'RE GONNA FIND ANY
DIAMONDS DOWN THERE,
BUT I CAN PROMISE YOU
A BEAUTIFUL DIVE
IF YOU PAY ATTENTION
TO A FEW SIMPLE RULES.
IT'S IMPORTANT WE STAY TOGETHER
AT ALL TIMES AND LOOK OUT
FOR EACH OTHER.
WHEN WE DIVE
AND EXPLORE THE OCEAN,
IT'S POTENTIAL
WILDERNESS ADVENTURE,
BUT IT'S ALSO DANGEROUS.
EXTREMELY IMPORTANT
THAT WE COMMUNICATE.
ARE YOU
THREATENING US, FLYBOY?
IT'S YOUR DIME, PAL.
MISTAKES DOWN THERE
CAN GET YOU KILLED.
I'M JUST WARNING YOU.
WHAT YOU'RE DOING IS,
YOU'RE BORING US SILLY.
- Woman: TYLER, PLEASE.
- WHAT?
WE GOT YOU, MR. WAGNER.
OKAY, IGOR,
WE'RE COMING CLOSE.
BRING US DOWN.
- FIVE MINUTES.
- OKAY.
IGOR?
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
WHAT, DID DR. FRANKENSTEIN
TAKE THE DAY OFF?
- [ laughing ]
- HE'S RELIABLE
AND HE'S REASONABLE.
LET'S HIT THE DRINK,
BABE.
I COULD USE ONE
ABOUT NOW.
THIS IS TYLER'S IDEA
OF CELEBRATING OUR
ANNIVERSARY.
Tyler:
COME ON, RILEY.
YOU KNOW A LITTLE ADVENTURE
ALWAYS SPICES UP THE MARRIAGE.
- YOU KNOW WHAT WE DID
ON OUR FIRST ANNIVERSARY?
- WHAT?
WE GOT CERTIFIED
TO BE DIVERS.
I GAVE RILEY A CHOICE
THIS WEEKEND.
IT WAS EITHER SCUBA DIVING,
OR A MARATHON
OF MUD WRESTLING
AND HOT, STEAMY SEX.
WHICH EXPLAINS
WHY I AM HERE.
THREE MINUTES.
YOU BETTER LOSE THAT TRINKET
BEFORE WE GO DIVING.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW MUCH THIS COST?
JUST DO IT, OKAY?
I WOULDN'T WANT YOU
TO BE TOO APPETIZING
TO THE MARINE LIFE
DOWN THERE.
AYE AYE, MR. COUSTEAU.
OKAY, WE JUMP OUT
HERE AT CAPE DEL ORO,
WE DIVE DOWN
ABOUT 100 FEET,
WE SWIM WEST ABOUT 150 METERS
TOWARD THE VESSEL,
AND THEN THE VESSEL'S
RIGHT ABOUT HERE.
THE WATER'S GONNA BE
REALLY MURKY,
SO IT'S IMPORTANT WE STAY
REALLY CLOSE TOGETHER.
COMMUNICATION
IS VERY IMPORTANT.
YOU'RE AN EX-NAVY MAN,
MR. WAGNER?
YEAH, SEALS.
JUST TRYING TO MAKE
ENDS MEET NOW.
IT SUCKS TO BE YOU,
DOESN'T IT?
- TYLER, PLEASE.
- WHAT?
HEY, DAD, ARE THEY PAYING YOU
ENOUGH MONEY TO PUT UP
WITH THIS JERK?
- NOT HARDLY.
- I DIDN'T THINK SO.
YOUR MOM COST ME MORE
WHEN WE SPLIT UP
THAN SHE DID
WHEN WE WERE TOGETHER.
- YEAH, I KNOW. I'M SORRY.
- DON'T BE. IT'S NOT
YOUR FAULT.
WE'RE JUST HERE TO HAVE
A GOOD TIME. STICK WITH ME.
OKAY.
I TELL YOU WHAT,
HOW ABOUT NEXT TIME
WHEN WE GET TOGETHER
FOR THE WEEKEND,
- WE JUST GO TO DINNER
AND CATCH A BALLGAME?
- DEAL.
- [ beeping ]
- Igor: THIS IS IT.
Wagner:
OKAY, IGOR,
CIRCLE AROUND THE AREA.
- RILEY, YOU'RE NEXT.
- READY.
OKAY, MELISSA,
JOIN UP WITH RILEY.
YOU GOT IT.
OKAY, BILLY,
JOIN UP WITH THE REST
OF THE GROUP.
YOU'RE NOT ASHAMED
OF YOUR OLD MAN, ARE YOU?
WHAT, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
YOU'RE MY HERO, DAD.
YOU ALWAYS WILL BE.
- I LOVE YOU, SON.
- I LOVE YOU, TOO, DAD.
LET'S GO SWIMMING.
Everyone good?
Everything okay?
- Jimbo, you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine, Dad.
- Yeah, we're good.
- Melissa: We're good to go.
Okay, now follow me
everyone,
and remember,
stay together.
Wagner:
Everyone stop!
- What is it, Mr. Wagner?
- Kelp forest.
They provide food
and shelter to the sharks.
Stay together.
Jimbo, you okay?
Okay.
- You doing okay, Melissa?
- Yeah, I'm doing fine.
Come on, let's take
a look over there.
Come on, baby,
We've never done it
in a kelp bed.
They're not listening
to you, Dad.
- Melissa, check this out.
- Right behind you.
Wagner:
Billy, Melissa,
let's stay together.
Give us a kiss.
Tyler, Riley,
let's skip the romance
and come back
with the group.
I'll stick
with this group.
It's so pretty.
Hey, you guys,
let's stay together.
Riley, Melissa, Tyler.
They're not listening
to you either, Dad.
Damn weekend warriors.
Wagner:
Do me one big favor,
Jimbo,
and I'll try
to get season tickets
to the games next year.
What favor?
Don't tell your mother
what we did this weekend.
Okay, you got it.
Tyler:
Hey. Hey, there it is.
Riley:
Wow, look at the size
of that thing.
- Wow!
- Beautiful.
Let's see what we can find.
Riley:
Tyler, be careful now.
It's bigger than I thought
it was gonna be.
Yeah, a lot bigger.
- Hey, Tyler.
- Check this out.
Tyler, wait up.
Wait for me!
[ screaming, growling ]
[ screaming ]
JESUS, SHARKS!
Jim:
SHIT, DAD!
SWIM, JIMBO!
SWIM!
Jim:
DAD, COME ON!
- RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- KEEP SWIMMING, JIMBO!
MOVE!
[ screaming ]
HELP!
COME ON.
IGOR!
I MISS YOU, DAD.
Boy:
HEY, DAD.
MOM JUST CALLED.
SHE SAID DINNER WAS READY.
I'M HUNGRY
AND SHE CAN'T EAT WITHOUT US.
SO COULD WE GO HOME NOW?
YEAH, DANNY.
WE'LL GO HOME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE ANYWAY?
THINKING.
ABOUT SHARKS?
- YOUR MOM TELL YOU THAT?
- YEAH.
- WELL, SHE'S RIGHT.
- SHE'S ALWAYS RIGHT,
ISN'T SHE?
I SUPPOSE
SHE TOLD YOU THAT, TOO.
- YEAH.
- REMEMBER TO PUT
YOUR SEATBELT ON.
- OKIE-DOKE.
MAYOR CORTELL CALLED TODAY.
HE SOUNDED VERY EXCITED
ABOUT THE BEACH FIESTA
NEXT WEEKEND.
HE CANCELED
THE BEACH FIESTA.
- I'M JUST THE MESSENGER.
- Danny: WHY'D THEY CANCEL IT?
WELL, THE TOWN JUST
DIDN'T HAVE ENOUGH SPONSORS
TO FINANCE IT, HONEY.
AMWAY, CORTELL WANTS
TO SEE YOU FIRST THING
IN THE MORNING.
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING?
I WAS GOING TO TAKE DANNY--
PROBABLY JUST WANTS
TO MAKE SURE THE BEACHES
ARE SAFE FOR MEMORIAL DAY.
AND WHAT'S THE VERDICT
ON THAT?
THINK WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT,
BUT I'D LIKE TO SEND OUT
SOME PATROLS.
- OF COURSE HE'S GONNA TELL ME
WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH MONEY.
- WHAT ABOUT THE SHARKS?
[ sighs ]
EAT YOUR VEGETABLES,
DANNY.
WE LIVE ON THE BEACH,
JIMMY,
AND YOU HAVE MANAGED
TO SCARE HIM TO DEATH
ABOUT THE OCEAN.
HE'S AFRAID
TO GO SWIMMING.
AND HE WON'T EVEN
EAT FISH.
YUCK.
OR VEGETABLES.
CAN'T BLAME ME
FOR THE VEGETABLES.
WE'LL MAKE THAT GAME,
DANNY.
THIS IS SO BEAUTIFUL,
HONEY, ISN'T IT?
- NOT AS BEAUTIFUL
AS YOU ARE, DARLING.
- COME HERE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I FINALLY GET YOU
ALL TO MYSELF.
OH, NO.
I THINK WE SPOKE
TOO SOON.
I HATE TO TELL YOU, SEÑORITA,
BUT I THINK WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO HEAD ON BACK.
NOW GET DOWN BELOW.
[ woman screaming ]
Woman: HELP!
HELP!
HELP ME!
CARRIE!
NO!
CAN'T SLEEP?
WELL...
DO YOU WANT ME
TO COME OVER THERE
AND PLAY?
I THINK I'M GONNA HAVE
TO TAKE A RAIN CHECK.
Woman:
DON'T YOU LOOK NICE TODAY?
I'M TAKING DANNY
TO THE BALLGAME.
THAT'S WHY
I'M WEARING THIS.
- MORNING.
- HEY.
I'D LIKE YOU
TO MEET MR. VOLKOFF.
- HI.
- MR. VOLKOFF'S GROUP,
R.S.S. AND ASSOCIATES,
IS GOING TO UNDERWRITE
THE ENTIRE FESTIVAL
THIS YEAR.
- SINCE WHEN?
- SINCE RECENTLY.
THE 11TH HOUR,
IF YOU WILL.
WOW. THAT'S GREAT.
JIM HERE IS IN CHARGE
OF HORSENECK BEACH SECURITY.
THAT'S WHAT I UNDERSTAND.
HOW ARE THINGS LOOKING
OUT THERE?
PRETTY GOOD.
I ALSO UNDERSTAND
YOU ARE ANDREW WAGNER'S SON?
YEAH.
YOU'VE DONE YOUR HOMEWORK.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
MR. VOLKOFF IS INTERESTED
IN YOUR EXPERIENCE OUT
AT THE SANTA CRUZ.
GOT TO SPEND MONEY
TO MAKE MONEY.
IT'S PART OF OUR
BUSINESS ARRANGEMENT.
MR. VOLKOFF HAS BEEN MORE
THAN GENEROUS
AND I THINK THE LEAST WE CAN DO
IS POINT HIM IN THE DIRECTION
OF THE DIAMONDS.
NO. I CAN'T HELP YOU
WITH THAT.
AND WHY IS THAT?
PERSONAL REASONS.
I'LL LET YOU TWO DISCUSS
THE DETAILS.
I TRUST YOU'LL DO
THE RIGHT THING.
I WON'T TAKE HIM
TO THAT SHIP, JOHN.
- JIMMY, YOU KNOW--
- IT'S A LEGEND.
THERE IS
NOTHING OUT THERE.
SO LET VOLKOFF FIGURE
THAT OUT FOR HIMSELF.
HE'S PAYING THE BILLS.
I PAY YOURS.
YOU DO THE MATH.
SO THIS IS WHY
YOU CALLED ME OUT HERE
THIS MORNING?
NO, I ALSO CALLED YOU IN
TO TALK ABOUT NEXT WEEK'S
SECURITY AT THE BEACH.
WE NEED TO TAKE
SPECIAL MEASURES
THIS YEAR.
I'D LIKE TO THINK
THAT I DO THAT EVERY YEAR.
YES, BUT THIS
IS A SPECIAL YEAR.
GOD KNOWS WE NEED IT AFTER
LAST YEAR'S FINANCIAL DISASTER.
OH, COME ON.
I SAW GREAT WHITES
LAST YEAR.
WE AVERTED DISASTER.
AND ANOTHER THING,
JUST PROMISE ME
YOU WON'T WRITE
ANY MORE ARTICLES
IN THE NEWSPAPER
ABOUT SHARK INFESTED WATERS
OFF HORSENECK BEACH.
WELL, I'M HOPING
THAT I WON'T HAVE TO,
BUT I GOTTA TELL YOU THE "SWIM
AND FEED THE REEF SHARK PROGRAM"
CERTAINLY ISN'T
HELPING MATTERS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WHAT I MEAN IS,
EVENTUALLY THOSE SHARKS
MAY START TO ASSOCIATE
FOOD WITH PEOPLE.
- THAT CAN ATTRACT
THE GREAT WHITES.
- GREAT WHITES?!
SIR, THEY ARE OUT THERE.
I'VE SEEN THEM.
AND I'VE SEEN
WHAT THEY CAN DO.
IF THERE'S SO GODDAMN MANY
GREAT WHITES OUT THERE,
HOW COME YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
THAT SEES THEM?
BECAUSE I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S LOOKING FOR THEM!
- MAYOR CORTELL,
I NEED PATROLS.
- WE CAN'T AFFORD IT.
DON'T GO DOWN
THAT ROAD AGAIN, OKAY?
LOOK, THIS SUMMER HOLDS
THAT SPECIAL PROMISE.
I JUST WANT YOU TO DO
YOUR BEST.
- THAT'S ALL I ASK.
- YEAH.
IT'S A DEAL, SIR.
WHAT'S UP?
JUST THIS WEEKEND'S
THE ANNIVERSARY
OF MY DAD'S DEATH.
CAN'T GET HIM OUT
OF MY HEAD.
I KNOW IT'S GOT TO BE TOUGH
DEALING WITH THE WAY
YOUR DAD DIED.
BUT I'M ASK YOU,
AND I'M PAYING YOU,
TO GET HIM OUT
OF YOUR HEAD FOR THE SUMMER.
COULD YOU DO THAT FOR ME?
THAT I CAN'T
PROMISE YOU, JOHN.
[ growling ]
THAT'S GRANDPA?
YEAH, SON,
THAT'S GRANDPA.
WAS GRANDPA COOL?
- WAY COOL.
- WHEN DID GRANDPA DIE?
BEFORE YOU WERE BORN,
DANNY,
WHEN HE SAVED MY LIFE.
SEE, GRANDPA,
HE WASN'T JUST COOL,
HE WAS ALSO
THE BRAVEST GUY I EVER KNEW.
IF IT WASN'T FOR HIM,
I WOULDN'T BE HERE RIGHT NOW.
I WOULDN'T HAVE MET MOM
AND YOU WOULDN'T BE HERE
RIGHT NOW EITHER.
I DON'T GET IT.
THAT'S A STORY
FOR ANOTHER TIME, SON.
WAS GRANDPA ATE UP
BY SHARKS?
- YOUR MOTHER TELL YOU THAT?
- YEP.
AND SHE'S ALWAYS RIGHT,
RIGHT?
YEAH, DANNY,
SHARKS KILLED GRANDPA.
YOU KNOW,
I HATE SHARKS.
THEY SUCK.
YES, THEY DO.
[ engine starts ]
BUCKLE UP,
DANNY.
BRING US DOWN
TO SKIDS OVER THERE.
I LOVE THIS JOB.
HARKER,
DO YOU COPY?
- Harker?
- A BASE TAN IS A TERRIBLE
THING TO WASTE.
HARKER, DO YOU COPY?
I COPY, JIMMY.
HOW WE LOOKING
DOWN THERE?
LOOKIN' GOOD.
LOOKIN' VERY GOOD.
- LOOKIN' DAMN GOOD.
- WHAT?
Nothing.
I DIDN'T COPY THAT.
EVERYTHING LOOKS COOL.
I'M NOT PAYING YOU
TO LOOK AT THE LADIES,
HARKER.
Keep your eyes open.
Stay in touch.
YOU GOT IT, JIMMY.
CHIEF WAGNER HERE.
NATIVES SEEM
WELL BEHAVED.
SO... SO FAR, SO GOOD,
MAYOR CORTELL.
WE DON'T WANT THEM
TOO WELL BEHAVED.
- We don't?
- NO.
THAT WOULD SIGNAL BEER SALES
ARE DOWN.
Good news all around,
though.
THE BEACH FIESTA'S SET
TO GO THIS WEEKEND.
- THANK YOU.
- OVER AND OUT.
- LET'S PITCH RIGHT.
- YOU GOT IT.
LET'S BRING IT
TO A HOVER.
THAT'S NICE.
LEVEL OFF.
OH, SHIT!
IT'S ALL BAD.
HARKER, DO YOU COPY?!
- HARKER?!
- COPY, JIMMY.
GET EVERYONE OUT OF THE WATER!
WE GOT SHARKS!
SHARKS?!
Everyone out of the water!
Let's go!
Sharks! Come on!
- Move it!
- [ screaming ]
Sharks!
Let's go!
Get out of the water!
Everybody out now!
Come on!
We got sharks, let's move!
Get up on the beach!
Come on!
Swim!
Come on, move it!
Leave the raft!
Just move!
Let's go! Swim!
[ screaming ]
Come on!
Out of the water!
Let's go!
[ screaming ]
Move it!
- BP'S DROPPING.
- WE GOT SEVERE INTERIOR
THIGH LACERATIONS.
- PRETTY DEEP.
- WE'RE LOSING HIM.
JESUS!
- YOU HAVE TO CLOSE
THE BEACH.
- WHAT?!
PEOPLE HAVE TO STAY OFF
THE BEACH WHILE I HUNT
THESE SHARKS.
THAT'S INSANITY.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
I KNOW SOME PEOPLE LOST
THEIR LIVES OUT THERE.
I'M NOT COMPLETELY
INSENSITIVE TO THAT, OKAY?
BUT I GOTTA DEAL WITH PEOPLE
THAT MAKE THEIR LIVELIHOOD
IN THIS TOWN.
I'M NOT GONNA LET
A BUNCH OF PEOPLE LOSE
THEIR BUSINESSES
OVER SOME RANDOM ACT
OF NATURE.
WE'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT
A STRAY DOG HERE!
YOU LET PEOPLE OUT
IN THAT WATER,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL BE
RINGING THE DINNER BELL.
- PEOPLE WILL USE CAUTION.
- YOU USE CAUTION WHEN YOU'RE
DRIVING ON WET ROADS!
- WITH THESE THINGS
IT'S KILL OR BE KILLED.
- SO KILL THEM!
IF YOU MESS WITH THIS FIESTA,
IT'S GONNA BE MORE VICIOUS
THAN A SHARK ATTACK.
WE'RE NOT GONNA DO THAT.
IF YOU HAVE EDUCATE THEM,
EDUCATE THEM!
- BUT THE BEACH STAYS OPEN!
- LET ME EXPLAIN SOMETHING
TO YOU.
IT'S A LITTLE MORE
THAN AN EVOLUTIONARY BLIP
THAT SEPARATES
THE GREAT WHITE
FROM THE JURASSIC SHARKS
OF 50 MILLION YEARS AGO.
WE'RE PRACTICALLY TALKING
ABOUT MODERN-DAY DINOSAURS
OUT THERE.
AND JUST LIKE THEY DID
FOR 50 MILLION YEARS,
SHARKS ARE GONNA GIVE BIRTH
IN SPRING AND SUMMER
IN WARM TEMPERATURE WATERS
JUST LIKE OURS.
I'LL TELL YOU
ANOTHER THING--
NOBODY KNOWS
WHAT THE GESTATION PERIOD
IS FOR A GREAT WHITE.
WAGNER, THANKS A LOT FOR
THE NATIONAL GEOGRAPHIC LESSON.
WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU
TRYING TO TELL ME?
THESE SHARKS ARE BIGGER
AND FASTER
AND MORE AGGRESSIVE
THAN ANY I'VE EVER SEEN
AND WE COULD BE TALKING
ABOUT AN ENTIRE SCHOOL
OF THEM.
A GIANT SCHOOL OF MAN-EATING
JURASSIC SHARKS?
YOU'VE BEEN READING
TOO MANY COMICS.
TELL THAT TO THE PEOPLE
WHO DIED TODAY.
GLAD TO SEE YOU GUYS
ARE KEEPING YOURSELVES BUSY.
YOU WANT A TURN?
THE RECORD'S FIVE MINUTES.
FIVE MINUTES,
THREE SECONDS.
NOT ANYMORE MORE.
I'M GONNA BEAT IT.
YOU GUYS HEARD WHAT HAPPENED
AT THE BEACH, RIGHT?
YEAH, WE KNOW.
BUSINESS
IS DOWN 50%.
WE MIGHT HAVE
TO FIND ANOTHER JOB.
WELL,
IT'S GONNA GET WORSE.
BEACH IS ON HIGH ALERT
UNTIL THOSE SHARKS ARE KILLED.
SO I'M GONNA NEED
A LITTLE HELP.
- YOU BOYS UP FOR IT?
- WE THOUGHT YOU'D NEVER ASK.
- YEAH, WELL, SO DID I.
- LET'S DO IT. I'M IN.
HOW ABOUT YOU, GORDO?
THINK YOU'LL BE OVER
THIS HANGOVER BY TOMORROW?
HEY, YOU KNOW ME, JIMMY.
I'M THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
SEE YOU AT THE MARINA
AT 7:00.
DON'T FORGET TO BRING
YOUR GEAR.
IT'S NOT GOING
TO BE A PLEASURE CRUISE.
GOOD AFTERNOON
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
I WOULD LIKE TO EXTEND
OUR DEEPEST CONDOLENCES
to those of you
who lost loved ones
on the beach yesterday.
SON OF A BITCH.
I've assembled a crack team
of divers...
YEAH, RIGHT.
...to go out to the beach
and kill the sharks,
and make our great beach
safe once again.
I'd like to second
the mayor's sentiments.
SO THAT'S
MR. VOLKOFF, HUH?.
YEAH, THAT'S HIM.
And I fully support him.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, I'VE BEEN BETTER.
- WORRYING ABOUT TOMORROW?
- A LITTLE BIT.
IT'S NOT JUST THAT,
IS IT?
CARRIE.
HE DIED A LONG TIME AGO,
JIMMY.
- IT WASN'T--
- WHAT?
IT WASN'T MY FAULT?
YOU DON'T THINK I'VE HEARD THAT
A MILLION TIMES?
IT DOESN'T
CHANGE ANYTHING.
WHEN I WAS IN THAT WATER
AND I SAW THOSE SHARKS...
Move!
Swim, Jimbo, swim!
THE ONLY THINK I COULD THINK
ABOUT WAS SAVING MYSELF.
THE ONLY THINK MY DAD
COULD THINK ABOUT WAS SAVING ME.
YOU'RE NOT ASHAMED
OF YOUR OLD MAN, ARE YOU?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
YOU'RE MY HERO, DAD.
ALWAYS WILL BE.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING,
CARRIE.
I JUST LEFT HIM THERE.
- I LEFT HIM THERE,
AND MY FATHER DIED.
- I KNOW.
AND I'M SORRY.
BUT YOUR FATHER
LOVED YOU, JIMMY.
AND YOU WOULD'VE DONE
THE EXACT SAME THING FOR DANNY.
THANKS.
I WOULD.
YOU'RE THE BEST THING
THAT'S EVER HAPPENED TO ME.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO TAKE
ALL THAT OUT ON YOU.
- IT'S JUST THIS WHOLE THING--
- I KNOW, BABE.
COME HERE.
NOW WHY DON'T WE
GO TO BED?
- I'LL MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
- YEAH?
I PROMISE.
I'LL MAKE YOU FEEL
A LOT BETTER.
I'M GONNA LOOSEN
YOU UP.
BET YOU ARE.
BUT I LIKE TO BE
ON TOP.
OH, YEAH?
YOU'VE BEEN VERY BAD.
GUYS I WANT TO TAG
AT LEAST THREE OR FOUR
OF THESE SHARKS, OKAY?
JIMMY, WHY DON'T
WE JUST KILL THEM?
I NEED TO KNOW
WHERE THEY CAME FROM, GORDO,
JUST IN CASE THERE'S MORE.
WHATEVER YOU SAY, CHIEF.
HERE YOU ARE.
OH.
TOURIST BUSINESS
WAS OFF 40% LAST YEAR
BECAUSE WAGNER
MADE SUCH A BIG STINK
ABOUT A BUNCH
OF GREAT WHITE SHARKS
HE THOUGHT WE SAW OUT THERE.
HIS FATHER
WAS A NAVY MAN, NO?
SO WAGNER MUST KNOW
THE SEA QUITE WELL.
MUST BE
A KNOWLEDGEABLE MAN.
NOT ABOUT ECONOMICS,
HE'S NOT.
THE WHOLE PLACE
WAS EMPTY LAST SEASON.
EVERYBODY WENT TO FUCKING
DISNEYLAND INSTEAD.
WHEN IS HE GOING
TO TAKE US TO THE BOAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S FIGHTING ME ON THAT.
I CAN'T SAY FOR SURE.
MAYOR CORTELL,
THIS WAS PART
OF THE ARRANGEMENT.
I WILL PULL THE FUNDING
FOR THE FIESTA
IF I AM NOT OUT THERE
DIAMOND HUNTING BY THE END
OF THE WEEK.
BUT MR. VOLKOFF--
WHICH WILL LEAVE
YOUR SUNNY LITTLE COMMUNITY
WITH NO MONEY
AND A TERRIBLE SHARK PROBLEM.
THE CHOICE IS YOURS.
MAKE THE RIGHT ONE.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
I WANT YOU TO BE CAREFUL
ABOVE ALL ELSE.
OKAY?
ARE YOU SURE THAT
THESE ARE GREAT WHITES?
I'M POSITIVE, GORDO.
YOU SAW THE DAMAGE.
IT'S THE WAY THEY ATTACK--
FROM BELOW, WITHOUT WARNING.
THERE'S THREE KINDS
OF SHARK ATTACK.
THE BUMP AND BITE,
THE HIT AND RUN AND
THE SNEAK ATTACK.
[ laughing ]
WHAT DO YOU GET
WHEN YOU CROSS
THREE DIVERS IN A CAGE
AND A PISSED OFF
GREAT WHITE?
- HUH?
- WHAT DO YOU GET?
- A BOXED LUNCH.
- Man: OH, MAN.
Jim:
WHERE'D YOU FIND
THIS GUY, CAESAR?
COME ON. IT'S JUST
A LITTLE SHARK HUMOR.
ALL RIGHT, STAY FOCUSED.
ESPECIALLY YOU, GORDO.
Jim:
YOU KNOW, FELLAS,
MOST PEOPLE WHO'VE EVER
GONE SWIMMING IN THE OCEAN
HAVE BEEN WITHIN 15 FEET
OF A SHARK WITHOUT EVER
KNOWING IT.
OH GREAT.
HOW REASSURING.
REMEMBER,
ONLY THE UNDERBELLIES
OF THE GREAT WHITE
ARE WHITE IN COLOR.
THEIR TOPS ARE GRAY
SO THEY CAN BLEND IN
WITH THE DARK WATER,
ALLOWING THEM TO ATTACK
THEIR PREY UNNOTICED.
REMEMBER THAT.
ANY QUESTIONS?
- I'VE GOT ONE.
- WHAT'S THAT?
CAN WE GO HOME?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT US, BOSS.
WE'RE SOLID.
ALL RIGHT. GOOD.
KEEP THAT CHUM LINE GOING.
ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S GONNA DRAM THEM IN?
A SHARK CAN SMELL
A DROP OF BLOOD
IN 2,000 GALLONS
OF WATER.
- THAT SHOULD DO IT.
REMEMBER,
ANY SHARKS YOU CAN'T KILL,
TRY AND TAG.
BUT, ABOVE ALL,
BE CAREFUL.
COMMUNICATE WITH ME
AT ALL TIMES, ALL RIGHT,
GORDO?
Caesar: YOU GOT IT.
WHAT WE CAN'T KILL,
WE'LL TAG.
ALL RIGHT.
GET YOU OUT TO THOSE CAGES,
CAESAR.
- GOOD LUCK, NICKO.
- THANKS.
Caesar:
Nothing so far, Jimmy.
Gordo:
Just the pretty
deep blue sea.
Jim:
Nothing up here either, guys.
[ beeping ]
HERE WE GO.
HEY, FELLAS, THEY'RE COMING
FROM EVERY DIRECTION.
Jimmy, we got one.
- A big one.
- Sneak attack.
Jim:
Talk to me, guys.
What's going on?
Another one!
Over there!
And another one!
Gordo:
Jimmy, they're closing in.
- Nicko: Aw, Jeez.
- Gordo: Not good.
- Caesar, behind you!
- Another one!
Over here!
[ growling ]
Caesar, hug the corner!
Caesar!
- It's breaking up the cage!
- Gordo, hold on!
ALL RIGHT,
YOU SON OF A BITCH.
DIRTY, SMELLY FISH.
ALL RIGHT,
YOU WANNA PLAY HARDBALL, EH?
Gordo:
Kill it!
Get out!
Get away!
- No, no, no!
- Caesar! Gordo!
[ screaming ]
Jimmy, it got Cesar!
GODDAMN IT!
Another one!
Gordo! Gordo!
- OH JESUS.
- Gordo!
Get out!
Get out of the cage!
GORDO, SWIM!
COME ON, GORDO!
SWIM, BUDDY!
COME ON, GORDO, SWIM!
SWIM.
NO!
CHRIST.
[ cage creaking ]
COME ON.
COME ON, YOU PIECE OF SHIT,
JUST A LITTLE CLOSER.
GODDAMN IT!
SWIM!
COME ON, BUDDY!
COME ON!
[ screaming ]
BASTARDS!
HEY.
YOU DID YOUR BEST.
I NEVER SEEN SHARKS
ATTACK LIKE THAT.
MIND TELLING ME
WHAT YOU'RE GOING
TO DO NEXT?
FINISH THE JOB.
MANAGED TO TAG
A FEW TODAY.
GOING OUT
FIRST THING TOMORROW.
WITH WHO?
YOU LOOKING
FOR AN INVITATION?
SHIT, NO.
I DON'T EXACTLY EXPECT
THE VOLUNTEERS TO BE LINING UP.
NEED I REMIND YOU
THAT TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE?
JOHN, THREE MEN DIED
OUT THERE TODAY.
FRIENDS OF MINE.
- YOU'RE TALKING
TO ME ABOUT TIME?
- I KNOW.
I'M ON MY WAY TO MAKE
SOME SYMPATHY CALLS RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, THAT'LL MAKE
THE FAMILIES FEEL BETTER.
BEACHES ARE CLOSED UNTIL FURTHER
NOTIFICATION FROM ME.
GOOD ENOUGH.
FOR NOW.
GOOD LUCK.
THANKS.
[ cheering ]
♪ I'M GONNA ROLL, BABY...
HYDROPHOBIA, JORDAN,
IS THE FEAR OF WATER.
ELASMOPHOBIA
IS THE FEAR OF SHARKS.
AND PHAGOPHOBIA
IS THE FEAR
OF BEING EATEN.
JIMMY, GO HOME.
SO IF YOU'RE AFRAID
OF THE FIRST ONE,
YOU'RE TERRIFIED
OF THE SECOND ONE.
AND THE LAST ONE, WELL,
THE LAST ONE SCARES
THE SHIT OUT OF YOU.
SO I TAKE IT
YOU DON'T WANNA EAT
THE WORM, RIGHT?
[ laughing ]
[ music playing ]
COME ON!
HEY!
- COME ON.
- COMING!
WHOO!
[ screaming ]
[ loud laughter ]
YOU GONNA EAT THE WORM?
VODKA.
IT'S THE ICE CREAM MAN.
LOOK.
[ laughing ]
HEY, ICE CREAM MAN.
MY CONDOLENCES ABOUT
THE MEN WHO DIED TODAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DRINKING?
GOOD RUSSIAN VODKA
KNOCKS YOUR HEAD OFF.
I'LL HANDLE THIS ONE,
JORDAN.
I TELL YOU WHAT,
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
YOUR GOOD RUSSIAN VODKA
AND DRINK IT,
OVER THERE.
'CAUSE I'M NOT
IN THE MOOD FOR CHITCHAT.
- YOUR WIFE SAID
YOU WERE HERE.
- NOT INTERESTED.
LOOK, I UNDERSTAND
YOU LOST FRIENDS TODAY,
SO I'M WILLING TO WAIT
UNTIL AFTER THE FIESTA
IS OVER.
- BUT THEN...
- FORGET IT.
YOU WILL TAKE ME
TO THE SHIP.
- YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE--
- HEY!
I'M NOT DOING IT,
OKAY?
YOU GO BYE-BYE.
IN DUE TIME,
PERHAPS YOU'LL
CHANGE YOUR MIND.
GOODBYE FOR NOW.
YOU BELIEVE
THIS GUY?
LOOK, JIMMY,
IF YOU NEED HELP
WITH THOSE SHARKS TOMORROW,
I'M GOOD FOR IT.
USED TO DO A LITTLE FISHING
WITH YOUR OLD MAN
WHEN I WAS A KID.
NEVER CAUGHT MORE
THAN A HEALTHY BUZZ...
BUT WE HAD
SOME GOOD TIMES, MAN.
JORDAN, YOU KNOW...
THE LAST VOLUNTEERS,
THEY DIDN'T COME BACK.
I MEAN,
THESE PUPPIES ARE BIG
AND MEAN.
SO AM I.
SO WHAT TIME ARE WE LEAVING?
THANKS.
WHAT'S OUR NEXT MOVE, SIR?
WE WAIT FOR WAGNER
TO COOPERATE.
IF HE DOESN'T,
WE MAKE THINGS UGLY.
AND WHEN'S THAT GONNA BE?
YOU HAVE OTHER PLANS
THIS WEEK?
- NO, SIR.
- SHUT YOUR FUCKING HOLE.
MR. WAGNER HAS A SON.
- WHAT'S UP, GIRLS?
- HEY!
I GOT NOTHING HERE,
JORDAN.
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
WHAT'S UP?
A COUPLE OF WEEKEND WARRIORS
DECIDED TO JOIN OUR PARTY.
Hey, knuckleheads,
can't you read the signs?
Get the hell out of the water.
Get the hell out
of the water!
- WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM, MAN?
- TOTAL BUZZKILL.
LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING ELSE
DECIDED TO JOIN THE PARTY.
AND I THINK IT BROUGHT
ITS APPETITE.
Hey, Skipper,
close in on those kids,
fast!
COME ON, MAN.
LET'S GO.
OH, CHRIST.
Skipper, hurry!
DUDE, SHARK!
[ screaming ]
PLEASE, NO.
NOT THE KIDS.
WE GOT TO GET OUT
OF HERE!
SKIPPER,
BRING US BY THOSE KIDS!
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
[ screaming ]
WE BETTER
LOCK 'N LOAD, JORDAN.
Girl: HELP!
SHARKS!
DON'T GET IN, GET OUT!
I'M OUT, JORDAN!
COME ON.
COME ON, KID!
GET US BACK
TO SHORE, QUICK!
HEY, WHAT ABOUT
THE OTHER SHARKS?
WE'LL GET THEM
FROM THE CHOPPER.
JORDAN TO BASE.
- WE NEED AN AIRLIFT, NOW.
- YOU OKAY?
WHAT THE HELL
WERE YOU DOING OUT THERE?
DIDN'T YOU SEE THE SIGNS?
I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE GONNA BE
ALL RIGHT.
HANG IN THERE.
WAGNER!
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON?
THREE KIDS
DIED OUT THERE.
I'M GONNA HIT THOSE SHARKS
FROM THE AIR WITH EXPLOSIVES.
- I CAN TRACK 'EM NOW.
- CHRIST!
THE FIESTA KICKS OFF
IN THREE DAYS.
THEN LET ME DO MY JOB,
MAYOR!
THERE'S OUR SHARKS.
HEY, FOSTER!
50 FEET OFF THE SURFACE!
HOW'S YOUR AIM,
JORDAN?
I'M BETTER AT BETTING
ON GAMES THAN PLAYING THEM.
PRETEND WE'RE PLAYING
FOR MONEY.
- NICE.
- THAT'S ONE.
HEY, HOW MANY SHARKS
ARE WE DEALING WITH?
I DON'T KNOW.
A WHOLE SCHOOL.
BULL'S EYE!
Jim:
THE TRIFECTA!
YOU MUST BE ONE HELL
OF A GAMBLER!
ONE MORE TO GO.
CLASS DISMISSED!
IF THIS ISN'T MILLER TIME,
NOTHING IS.
IF YOU GUYS ARE CELEBRATING
BECAUSE YOU KILLED
ALL THE SHARKS,
I'LL JOIN YOU IN ONE
OF THOSE.
THAT IS WHY YOU'RE
CELEBRATING, ISN'T IT?
IT'S HARD TO SAY, SIR.
THE GESTATION PERIOD
OF THE GREAT WHITE
IS UNKNOWN.
IS THAT A YES OR A NO?
IT'S A MAYBE.
Welcome,
ladies and gentlemen.
I'm very happy to announce
the beach is now open and safe,
Thanks mostly to Jim Wagner
of Beach Security.
And Larry Foster
and Jordan McNeil.
Couldn't have done it
without them.
Due to the courage
and determination
of these fine men,
the beach is now open
and the fiesta will
proceed as planned.
So enjoy the festivities.
I KNOW YOU, WAGNER.
YOU STILL THINK
THERE'S SHARKS OUT THERE,
DON'T YOU?
I'D HAVE LIKED
MORE TIME,
BUT I GUESS THERE'S ONLY
ONE WAY TO FIND OUT NOW.
WHAT'S THAT?
SUMMER BEACH FIESTA.
IF YOU DON'T THINK
IT'S SAFE,
THEN YOU NEED
TO TELL THE MAYOR.
COME ON, HONEY,
YOU HEARD THE GUY.
HE'S ALREADY COUNTING
BEACH FIESTA PROFITS.
Newsreader:
...event will go ahead
as planned.
This is very welcome news...
WELL, LET'S GET DANNY OFF
THE INTERNET AND INTO BED.
[ phone ringing ]
HELLO?
- Man: Mr. Wagner?
- YEAH, THIS IS HIM.
Is this a bad time?
THAT DEPENDS ON WHAT
YOU'RE SELLING.
- WHO IS THIS?
- Vlad Pozerov.
I'm with Volkoff's group.
We'd like to set up
a meeting with you.
MEETING?
WHAT KIND OF MEETING?
We want to know
if you're interested
in investing with us.
INVESTING?
INVESTING IN WHAT?
Your life and the lives
of your family.
- ARE YOU THREATENING ME?
- We'll be in touch.
HEY!
IS EVERYTHING
ALL RIGHT?
UH-HUH.
THANK YOU.
THANKS TO YOU, THIS WENT OFF
WITHOUT A HITCH.
ANYWAY, I HAVE TO GO RUN
SOME ERRANDS.
OH.
- WHOOPS.
- WHERE'S MY QUARTER?
THAT CALL YOU GOT
LAST NIGHT?
YEAH.
IT WAS THE RUSSIAN GUY,
WASN'T IT?
WHAT DOES HE WANT?
HE WANTS ME TO TAKE HIM
OUT TO THE SANTA CRUZ.
HE'S CONVINCED
THAT THOSE DIAMONDS
ARE STILL THERE.
YOU ARE NOT GOING BACK
OUT THERE AGAIN, ARE YOU?
OF COURSE NOT.
I CAN'T.
GOOD,
BECAUSE YOU HAVE ENOUGH
TO WORRY ABOUT RIGHT NOW.
LOOK, I'LL SEE YOU
TONIGHT.
BE SAFE.
HAVING YOUR THUGS THREATEN
MY FAMILY NOW?
I APOLOGIZE
IF SOME OF MY COLLEAGUES
ARE A BIT AGGRESSIVE.
I ASSURE YOU I CAME HERE
TO CONGRATULATE YOU.
OKAY, AT LEAST LET ME BUY
THE LOCAL HERO A DRINK.
- MM-HMM.
- TELL YOU WHAT,
YOU GOT TWO MINUTES, PAL.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT,
VOLKOFF?
I'M WILLING
TO SWEETEN THE POT,
IF YOU TAKE ME
TO THE DIAMONDS.
- HOW ABOUT 50 GRAND?
- 50 GRAND?
GOTTA SPEND MONEY
TO MAKE MONEY.
THERE'S NO GUARANTEE
YOU'RE GONNA FIND ANY
DIAMONDS OUT THERE.
20 GRAND EITHER WAY.
CONSIDER IT AN INVESTMENT
FOR YOUR FAMILY.
NO, I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T HELP YOU.
CAN'T OR WON'T?
LOOK, MY FATHER DIED
OUT THERE.
I CAN'T GO BACK
TO THAT PLACE.
MY BROTHER SURVIVED
OUT THERE,
BUT DIED
THREE MONTHS AGO.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOUR BROTHER?
IN FACT, I BELIEVE
YOU TWO ONCE MET.
HIS NAME WAS IGOR.
- IGOR THE PILOT?
- YES.
BEFORE HE PASSED AWAY,
HE TOLD ME
ABOUT SANTA CRUZ
AND THAT FATEFUL DAY.
ABOUT THE THE SHARKS.
HOW LIVES WERE LOST.
Wagner:
Jesus, sharks!
LIKE YOUR FATHER'S.
HOW LIVES WERE LOST.
- LIKE YOUR FATHER'S.
- [ screaming ]
BUT YOUR LIFE WAS SPARED
BY MY BROTHER.
HOW LIVES WERE LOST.
LIKE YOUR FATHER'S.
Wagner:
Swim, Jimbo. Swim!
CONSIDER THIS PAYBACK
FOR YOUR LIFE.
- PAYBACK?
- OR CONSIDER IT
A BUSINESS DEAL.
MY OFFER
IS MOST GENEROUS.
NO.
THANKS.
BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO COME UP WITH A PLAN B.
THAT IS A SHAME TO HEAR,
BECAUSE PLAN B'S
ARE OFTEN MISGUIDED,
AND DESPERATE ENDEAVORS,
AND HARDLY EVER HEALTHY
ALTERNATIVES--
ARE YOU THREATENING ME AGAIN,
YOU PIECE OF--
GET THE FUCK OFF
MY BEACH, VOLKOFF!
I UNDERSTAND,
MR. WAGNER,
FEAR IS
A POWERFUL THING.
BUT SOME THINGS ARE STILL
WORTH FIGHTING FOR.
WAGNER IS IN
FOR A FEW SURPRISES TODAY.
- [ woman grunts ]
- YES, DO IT.
- LET'S GO!
- MOVE, MOVE, MOVE!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- GET IT OPEN!
- [ screaming ]
- YOU CAN'T COME IN HERE!
EVERYBODY, SIT DOWN!
SIT DOWN! NOT YOU!
- YOU CAN'T COME IN HERE!
- COME HERE!
- HEY, STOP IT!
- GET YOUR HANDS OFF
OF HIM!
- COME ON!
- LET HIM GO!
- GIVE HIM TO ME!
- Woman: DANNY!
BE STILL, YOU BRAT!
GO, GO, GO!
GET IN THERE!
I'M IN. LET'S GO!
WHERE ARE YOU TAKING ME?
FISHING.
[ laughing ]
[ phone rings ]
WAGNER.
[ Carrie sobbing ]
Oh my God
- They've got him.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- They've got Danny.
- WHAT?!
WHO?!
VOLKOFF.
THEY JUST TOOK HIM
RIGHT OFF THE BUS.
Listen to me,
I WANT YOU TO TRY
AND RELAX, OKAY?
I'M GONNA CALL THE POLICE.
IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
I'm gonna get him back.
MY BABY IS GONE.
I'M GONNA GET HIM BACK.
I SWEAR TO GOD I AM GONNA
GET DANNY BACK
IF IT IS THE LAST THING
THAT I DO, OKAY?
JIMMY, YOU'VE GOT
TO GET HIM BACK SAFE
AND SOUND, PLEASE.
YEAH. YEAH,
SAFE AND SOUND.
I am gonna get Danny back
safe and sound.
SON OF A BITCH.
[ phone rings ]
- HELLO.
- NO POLICE OR DANNY DIES.
VOLKOFF,
YOU PIECE OF SHIT!
YOU CAN CALL ME
MR. PLAN B.
WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
I THINK YOU KNOW.
MEET ME AT THE END
OF THE BOARDWALK.
- WE'RE GOING ICE FISHING.
- You hurt my boy I'll--
WHAT IS IT YOU AMERICANS
ARE FOND OF SAYING?
- "Diamonds are forever"?
- YOU'RE INSANE, VOLKOFF.
COOPERATE OR ELSE
YOU'LL SEE DANNY LATER,
BUT ONLY IN PIECES.
GODDAMN IT!
VOLKOFF!
VOLKOFF,
YOU PIECE OF SHIT!
DANNY?
VOLKOFF,
WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU?!
PUSH OFF.
SON OF A BITCH.
I'M GONNA KILL
EVERY LAST ONE OF YOU.
MOVE.
HERE COMES
THE LOCAL HERO.
TIME TO SHOW US
YOUR LIGHTNING BOLTS.
- DADDY!
- DANNY!
DANNY, YOU OKAY?
GET OUTTA HERE!
I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE
A REASONABLE MAN.
VOLKOFF, IF MY SON HAS
SO MUCH AS A SCRATCH,
I SWEAR TO GOD
I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
[ spits ]
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
SANTA CRUZ.
IT'S YOUR FUNERAL.
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY,
DANNY BOY.
IF YOU WANNA STAY ALIVE,
THEN LISTEN UP.
THE SHIP'S SURROUNDED
BY A KELP BED.
KELP BEDS MEAN SHARKS.
SO KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN.
- I DON'T TRUST HIM.
- SHUT UP.
HAVEN'T SEEN THIS IN A WHILE.
YOU'RE GONNA DIVE HERE.
KELP BED
IS A 150 METERS DUE WEST.
WHEN YOU REACH THE END OF IT,
BEAR NORTHWEST FOR 50 METERS.
THAT'S WHERE YOU FIND HER.
I KNEW YOU WERE
THE BEST MAN FOR THIS JOB.
- BLOW ME, ASSHOLE.
- ILLYA, GO WITH HIM.
- I'M DOING THIS FOR MY SON.
- COME ON.
MOVE.
HANG ON, DANNY.
Man:
We can't find it.
IDIOTS.
HEY, EINSTEIN,
YOU NOT PAY ATTENTION
IN SCHOOL EITHER?
AFTER THE KELP FOREST,
50 METERS NORTHWEST,
YOU RUN RIGHT
INTO THE SANTA CRUZ.
TRUST ME, IT'S THERE.
Man:
We found the boat,
Mr. Volkoff.
This was too easy.
FIND THOSE DIAMONDS.
SEARCH HER FROM BOW
TO STERN.
Man:
Skulls. Human skulls.
Man #2:
More of them over here.
Man #3:
Here, too.
ANY LUCK YET?
Man:
Only if skulls
are worth money.
FUCK.
Mr. Volkoff,
get ready to be happy.
[ screaming ]
[ radio static ]
No! No!
[ screaming ]
Boris. Boris!
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON
DOWN THERE?
HELLO?
ANYONE, HELLO!
ANYONE, HELLO?
[ static ]
I'VE LOST CONTACT
WITH THEM.
THERE HE IS.
Jim:
OH! THERE HE ISN'T.
REALLY?
HMM.
HEY. HEY!
QUESTION, MR. WAGNER,
WHAT'S WORSE?
BEING EATEN ALIVE
OR WATCHING YOUR SON
BEING EATEN ALIVE?
JESUS, VOLKOFF,
JUST LEAVE HIM ALONE.
ONLY IF YOU GO DOWN
AND FETCH THOSE DIAMONDS.
WHAT'S THE POINT?
I'M NEVER GONNA MAKE IT BACK.
YOU WON'T SEE THOSE DIAMONDS.
A CHANCE I'M WILLING
TO TAKE.
EITHER THAT,
OR WE FEED HIM TO THE SHARKS.
YOU'LL DIVE NOW.
GO AND GET ME
THOSE DIAMONDS.
I LOVE YOU, DANNY.
I LOVE YOU, TOO, DAD.
DON'T HURT MY SON.
- YOU DIVE, TOO.
- YES, MR. VOLKOFF.
[ grunting ]
[ groans ]
Jim:
I got the diamonds.
I'm coming up.
YOU JUST MAY LIVE
TO SEE ANOTHER DAY.
- YOU'RE A JERK.
- LIKE YOUR FATHER,
YOU NEED TO LEARN
SOME MANNERS.
YOU'RE RIGHT, SIR.
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
TAKE COVER, DANNY!
- [ gunshot ]
- DAD!
- [gunshot ]
- DADDY!
DAD!
DAD, WAKE UP!
- DAD!
- [ coughing ]
DAD!
DAD, HELP ME!
DANNY!
DAD, GET UP!
- DAD!
- DANNY.
GET UP!
- DAD!
- HANG ON, SON.
ATTABOY.
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
HOLD ON.
- OKAY.
- HOLD ON.
ALL RIGHT.
COVER YOUR FACE.
- DANNY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH.
YOU WERE REALLY BRAVE
OUT THERE, SON.
YOU TOO, DAD.
JUST LIKE GRANDPA, RIGHT?
YEAH.
JUST LIKE GRANDPA.
SO, HONEY,
DO YOU REALLY THINK
THERE WERE DIAMONDS
ON SANTA CRUZ?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT ABOUT TO GO
LOOKING FOR THEM.
YEAH? WELL, I'M NOT ABOUT
TO GO LET YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOUR FATHER WOULD'VE BEEN
REALLY PROUD OF YOU.
HE ALWAYS WAS.
AND SO AM I.
THIS WAS A REALLY GOOD IDEA.
I MEAN, LOOK AT DANNY.
HE'S FINALLY GETTING USED
TO THE WATER.
HE'S BEEN IN THE POOL
ALL DAY.
I CAN HARDLY GET HIM
OUT OF THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT SOUNDS LIKE ONE HELL
OF AN IDEA.
YEAH, WELL,
I'LL JOIN YOU LATER.
- Jim: LOOKIN' GOOD.
- [ laughing ]
HEY, YOU KNOW, CARRIE--
[ growling ]
♪ YOU DISAPPEAR IN TROUBLE
♪ DON'T YOU?
♪ THEY NEVER LISTEN,
WILL YOU? ♪
♪ WON'T YOU?
♪ THE MIST HAS COME
SURROUNDING YOU ♪
♪ YOU'RE NOT OUTSIDE
OF DANGER ♪
♪ SOMETHING OUT THERE
TAKES YOU ALIVE ♪
♪ WITHOUT A STARE
AND YOU'RE INSIDE ♪
♪ SOMETHING OUT THERE
TAKES YOU ALIVE ♪
♪ YOU'RE GONE AGAIN
♪ I THINK I KNOW YOU
♪ KNOW YOU
♪ SO FAR FROM HOME
♪ DOES NO ONE OWN YOU?
♪ OWN YOU
♪ THERE'S NO WAY OUT
♪ STUCK IN THE MIDDLE
♪ OF A GREAT MISTAKE
♪ SOMETHING OUT THERE
TAKES YOU ALIVE ♪
♪ WITHOUT A STARE
AND YOU'RE INSIDE ♪
♪ SOMETHING OUT THERE
TAKES YOU ALIVE ♪
♪ TAKES YOU ALIVE
♪ THERE'S NO ONE THERE
IN HEAVEN ♪
♪ FOOLED YOU
♪ SO YOU'RE ALONE
♪ DID NO ONE TELL YOU?
♪ TELL YOU
♪ WANT TO GET OUT
THERE IS A WAY ♪
♪ BUT YOU NEVER TALK
TO STRANGERS ♪
♪ SOMETHING OUT THERE
TAKES YOU ALIVE ♪
♪ WITHOUT A STARE
AND YOU'RE INSIDE ♪
♪ SOMETHING OUT THERE
TAKES YOU ALIVE ♪
♪ IT TAKES YOU
♪ SOMETHING OUT THERE
TAKES YOU ALIVE ♪
♪ WITHOUT A STARE
AND YOU'RE INSIDE ♪
♪ SOMETHING OUT THERE
TAKES YOU ALIVE ♪
♪ TAKES YOU ALIVE
♪ TAKE, TAKE, TAKE YOU.