(dog barking)
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hboy:
WE THERE YET, MOM?
Mom: DIDN'T SOMEBODY PROMISE
THEY WEREN'T GOING TO ASK THAT?
\h\hJUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
YOU WERE PAYING ATTENTION.
DON'T KNOW WHAT I'D
DO WITHOUT YOU, ZACK.
girl: WHY DO YOU HAVE
TO BUG EVERYBODY?
DAD SENT YOU THAT BOOK SO
YOU COULD READ AND NOT TALK.
NO.
HE SENT IT TO ME
BECAUSE HE KNOWS I'M GOING
\h\hTO BE A HERO SOME DAY.
WHAT KIND OF HERO CAN
\hAN 11 YEAR OLD BE?
MAYBE I'LL SAVE YOU FROM
A PACK OF HUNGRY WOLVES.
WHATEVER.
OR MAYBE I WON'T.
Zack:: MOM, WE'RE NOT MOVING
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTO A DIFFERENT TOWN
\h\hBECAUSE YOU AND DAD
GOT DIVORCED, ARE WE?
NO.
WE'RE MOVING TO HOPE SPRINGS
BECAUSE THE COMPANY ASKED ME TO
RUN THEIR BIGGEST NURSING HOME.
IT'S ACTUALLY QUITE AN HONOR.
IF I SEE ONE MORE TREE,
\h\hI'M GOING TO PUKE.
\h\hYOU'RE NOT UNHAPPY
ABOUT MOVING, ARE YOU?
NOT AT ALL.
IT FEELS LIKE A BIG ADVENTURE.
I GOT YOU SOME BEEF JERKY.
THANKS.
WILL YOU STOP THAT?
IT ITCHES.
DID MR. HARPER GIVE YOU
YOUR FINAL PAYCHECK?
YEAH.
200 LOUSY BUCKS.
SO I FIGURE, HE OWED
\h\h\h\h\hME SOME SNACKS.
NOW THAT YOU GOT FIRED,
ARE YOU GONNA --
ARE YOU GONNA,
LIKE, MOVE BACK HOME?
NO.
\h\h\h\hMY FAMILY RENTED MY ROOM TO
SOME GEEKAZOID COLLEGE STUDENT.
WE DESERVE BETTER
THAN THIS, LEO.
WE NEED AN OPPORTUNITY.
LOOK AT THIS.
YEAH.
OH, SOMEBODY LEFT THEIR CAR ON.
\h\h\h\h\h\hHEY, MAYBE WE
SHOULD TURN IT OFF.
THIS IS A SIGN, LEO.
SOMEBODY WANTS US
TO HAVE THIS CAR.
IT'S FIRST PIECE OF DECENT
\h\hLUCK I'VE HAD ALL YEAR.
\hWHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS IS OUR TICKET OUT
\hOF THIS NOWHERE TOWN.
WE CAN'T JUST STEAL A CAR.
WE'RE NOT STEALING IT, OKAY.
WE'RE BORROWING IT.
WE'LL CALL AND TELL THEM WHERE
TO PICK IT UP WHEN WE'RE DONE.
GET IN OR STAY
AND GET BUSTED,
\h\h\h\h\h\hBECAUSE THAT'S STOLEN
MERCHANDISE YOU'RE ABOUT TO EAT.
COME ON, GET IN.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hLeo:
OH, MAN, YOU STOLE THIS STUFF?
(video game beeping)
FASTER.
AH!
IF I COULD JUST GET
TO THE NEXT GALAXY.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hLeo:
THIS IS CRAZY.
I TOLD YOU, WE'RE
ONLY BORROWING IT.
ANYWAYS, THIS IS WILL BE
A GOOD LESSON FOR THE OWNERS
TO NOT LEAVE THEIR
KEYS IN THE CAR.
WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT IT THAT WAY,
WE'RE ACTUALLY
DOING A GOOD DEED.
FRANKIE, LOOK, A COUPLE
OF CUTE DOGS BACK HERE.
I'LL PULL OVER
AND WE CAN LET THEM OUT.
NO, NO.
THEY'RE TOO CUTE.
WE CAN'T JUST LET THEM OUT
\hIN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
ALL RIGHT, YOU BIG SISSY.
WE'LL FIND A GOOD
PLACE TO DROP THEM OFF.
Zack:
\hMOM?
20 MORE MILES.
JUST CHECKING.
\h\h\h\h\h\hLeo: YOU KNOW I'M NOT
SCRATCHING MY HEAD ANYMORE.
FASCINATING, LEO.
\h\h\hYEAH, BUT MY HAD HASN'T
ITCHED SINCE WE LEFT TOWN.
\hI MEAN, I'M ALWAYS
SCRATCHING MY HEAD.
GOOD FOR YOU.
♪
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMom:
ISN'T THIS ADORABLE?
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hIT'S LIKE
A NORMAN ROCKWELL PAINTING.
HEY, EVERYTHING YOU NEED IS
RIGHT HERE ON MAIN STREET.
I HAVEN'T SEEN A MALL.
DO THEY EVEN HAVE ONE HERE?
LOOK, CURIOSITY STORE.
IT LOOKS COOL.
CAN WE STOP IN THERE, MOM?
OH, NO, NO.
THERE WILL BE PLENTY OF TIME
\hTO EXPLORE THIS WHOLE TOWN.
AN OLD TOWN SQUARE.
LOOK OUT!
(tires screech)
\hWATCH WHERE YOU'RE
GOING, YOU ROAD HOG!
I'M REALLY SORRY!
YOU COULD HAVE KILLED ME.
YOU'RE DRIVING LIKE A MANIAC.
IS EVERYBODY OKAY?
OH, MAN.
WELCOME TO HOPE SPRINGS.
ENJOY YOUR SENTENCE.
(dog barking)
HELP!
KEEP THIS DOG AWAY FROM ME!
YOU'RE SUCH A DRAMA QUEEN.
COME HERE.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT RANGER.
HE'S HARMLESS.
I'M JOSH.
I LIVE ACROSS THE STREET.
WELL, WELCOME TO
THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
THANKS.
SEE YOU AROUND.
COOL.
WOW.
HELLO?
HI.
I'M PAULA WELLS.
\h\hOH, MISS WELLS,
HELLO, I'M NATALIE.
HI, NATALIE.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hLISTEN, I'LL CALL YOU
NATALIE IF YOU CALL ME PAULA.
DONUT?
SURE.
I USUALLY WORK THE NIGHTS,
BUT HEAD NURSE HAD ME COME IN
EARLY SO I COULD MEET YOU.
OH, NURSE BLEAKER, I LOOK
\hFORWARD TO MEETING HER.
YEAH, WELL DON'T
GET TOO ANXIOUS.
HER MIGRAINES ARE ACTING UP,
AND SHE'S IN ONE OF HER
NOT-SO-RARE MOODS.
OH.
YOU LEFT THE COOKIES ON
\hTHE LUNCH TRAY AGAIN.
I KNOW.
I FIGURED THAT IF ANYONE WANTED
AN EXTRA COOKIE AFTER LUNCH,
THEY COULD JUST HELP THEMSELVES.
THIS IS A NURSING HOME.
IF WE LET THE RESIDENTS EAT
ALL THE COOKIES THEY WANT,
HOW ARE WE HELPING THEM?
I DON'T THINK AN EXTRA COOKIE
\h\h\h\h\hEVERY NOW AND THEN
IS GOING TO HURT ANYBODY.
AND WHO ARE YOU?
I'M PAULA WELLS.
I'M YOUR NEW ADMINISTRATOR.
OH, WELL, EXCUSE ME.
IT'S VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I WAS EXPECTING YOU
\hA LITTLE EARLIER.
OH, RIGHT.
WELL, I STOPPED TO
\h\hGET SOME DONUTS.
WOULD YOU LIKE ONE?
NO, THANK YOU.
I DON'T LIKE ANYTHING SWEET.
OKAY.
EXCUSE ME, MY BRAIN FEELS
\h\hLIKE A CLENCHED FIST.
SHALL WE?
OKAY.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
BYE.
THANK YOU FOR THE BIRTHDAY
PRESENT, GRANDPA.
THIS IS DODGE.
SHE'S VERY LITTLE TROUBLE.
MR. MCCOY.
\hHIS FAMILY SEEMS TO SHOW
UP JUST AROUND LUNCHTIME.
MRS. GARFIELD, WHO SNORES
\h\h\h\hLIKE A SAINT BERNARD,
\h\h\hAND THE WINDSOR SISTERS, WHO
SPEND HALF THEIR TIME GIGGLING,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT.
AND THERE'S OUR RESIDENT
\h\h\h\hNUTCASE, MR. WEAVER.
\hHE RARELY LEAVES HIS ROOM,
WHICH IS JUST FINE WITH ME.
\h\h\h\hHE'S BEST LEFT ALONE IN
HIS OWN LITTLE CUCKOO LAND.
WELL, I THINK I'D
LIKE TO MEET HIM.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTHIS IS THE NEW
ADMINISTRATOR, MR. WEAVER.
ONE MOMENT.
THIS IS A VERY IMPORTANT STAGE.
TAH-DAH.
\hYOU KNOW I HAVE ALWAYS
WONDERED HOW THAT'S DONE.
WELL, IT'S A SECRET, WHICH I
HOPE YOU CAN BE TRUSTED WITH.
ABSOLUTELY.
NOW, WHO DID YOU SAY YOU WERE?
\h\h\hI'M PAULA WELLS,
THE NEW ADMINISTRATOR.
WELL, HELLO, PAULA WELLS.
YOU LOOK LIKE A FINE
YOUNG WOMAN, STRONG,
BUT NOT TOO STRONG.
WE SHOULD BE GOING.
\h\hTHERE ARE PLENTY OF
RESIDENTS LEFT TO MEET,
\h\hAND IT'S NEARLY NAP
TIME FOR MOST OF THEM.
YOU COME BACK AND SEE ME.
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO
\h\hRIG THE MAINSAIL.
AYE, AYE, CAPTAIN.
MISS WELLS.
(dog barking)
THAT'S IT.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THESE DOGS.
THEY'RE JUST HUNGRY, THAT'S ALL.
\h\h\hWELL, WE CAN'T
AFFORD TO FEED THEM.
\h\h\h\h\h\hTHERE'S A CREEK ON
THE OTHER SIDE OF THESE WOODS.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY TAKE
THEM AND THROW THEM IN.
WHAT, ARE YOU KIDDING?
\h\h\hTHEY'RE LITTLE
DOGS, THEY'LL DROWN.
IT'S THE BEST THING TO DO.
\h\h\h\h\h\hWELL, THE BEST THING TO DO
WOULD BE TO FIND HOMES FOR THEM.
AND TELL THE WHOLE WORLD
THAT WE HAVE THE DOGS
THAT WERE LEFT IN THIS CAR?
I DON'T LIKE IT ANY
\hBETTER THAN YOU,
BUT WE HAVE TO BE HUMANE
AND PUT THESE POOR DOGS
\hOUT OF THEIR MISERY.
YOU DO IT.
ME?
STUPID DOGS.
I'M SORRY ABOUT FRANCIS.
HE'S NOT A BAD GUY, HE
\hJUST -- I DON'T KNOW,
HE'S HAD A TOUGH LIFE.
SEE, FRANCIS --
FRANCIS THINKS BEING A NICE GUY
\hMAKES HIM LOOK LIKE A SISSY.
IT'S JUST HARD TO EXPLAIN.
(dogs whining)
AH.
OH, MAN.
OH, NO.
NO.
YEAH.
I THINK I'M GOING TO
LEAVE YOU GUYS HERE.
\h\hMAYBE SOMEBODY
NICE WILL FIND YOU.
HEY, I KNOW.
YEAH, HERE, HAVE A SNACK.
YEAH, YOU GUYS WANT A SNACK?
YEAH, YOU LOOK LIKE
\hYOU WANT A SNACK.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
SHARE, SHARE, SHARE, SHARE.
SHARE, SHARE.
(horn honking in distance)
HOW'D IT GO?
OKAY.
IT'S THE BEST THING
\h\hFOR THEM, REALLY.
(engine not starting)
WHAT, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHAT'S THIS?
ROBOT VACUUM CLEANER.
REALLY?
\hHOW MUCH IS THIS
REMOTE CONTROL CAR?
TEN BUCKS.
IT NEEDS BATTERIES.
WHAT ARE THESE?
NIGHT VISION GOGGLES.
YOU GOING TO BUY SOMETHING,
KID, OR JUST ASK QUESTIONS?
LET ME LOOK AROUND A LITTLE.
HELP YOURSELF.
ARE WE GOING TO CALL THE OWNERS
AND TELL THEM WHERE THE CAR IS?
YOU PROMISED.
YES, BUT NOT 'TIL
WE GET IT FIXED.
WE DON'T WANT TO GIVE THEM
BACK A BROKEN CAR, DO WE?
LOOK, ALL THIS MEANS IS THAT WE
WERE MEANT TO BE AROUND HERE,
FOR AT LEAST A WHILE.
OW!
\h\hWATCH WHERE YOU'RE
GOING, YOU DUMB KID.
MAYBE THAT WILL SLOW YOU DOWN.
YOU BROKE IT.
YEAH, WELL TOO BAD.
NOW BEAT IT.
SORRY.
HEY, COME ON, FRANK, WHY
YOU GOT TO BE SO MEAN?
COME ON, I WAS JUST
\h\hCLOWNING THE KID.
\hI DIDN'T MEAN TO WRECK
HIS SCOOTER, ALL RIGHT?
HE PRACTICALLY TORE MY LEG OFF.
COME ON.
LET'S GO GET A HOT DOG.
I'LL BUY.
(dogs whining)
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
GUYS DOING HERE?
HELLO?
HELLO!
\h\h\hI WISH I COULD
BRING YOU GUYS HOME.
BUT MY MOM WON'T LET ME.
MY SISTER'S AFRAID OF DOGS.
COME ON.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY.
LET'S GO.
(dogs barking)
COME ON.
I HAVE TO GET HOME.
I HOPE WHOEVER OWNS YOU GUYS
COMES TO PICK YOU UP
\h\h\hBEFORE DINNER.
\h\h\h\hI'LL COME BACK
TOMORROW TO MAKE SURE.
BYE!
(dogs barking and whining)
SORRY, GUYS.
THIS STINKS.
STAY HERE.
YOU DON'T BELONG TO ME.
I'M SERIOUS.
MY MOM WOULD KILL ME IF I CAME
\h\hHOME WITH A COUPLE OF DOGS.
NOW, STAY HERE.
IT'S TOUGH LOVE TIME.
I DON'T WANT YOU GUYS.
NO.
YOU CAN'T COME WITH ME.
I MEAN IT.
NO.
OH, NO, IT'S MY MOM!
QUICK, LET'S DUCK IN HERE.
HEY, STOP THAT.
THIS IS A DOCTOR'S OFFICE.
THE DOCTOR WILL BE WITH YOU
IN A MINUTE, MRS. POLLING.
OH, IT'S OKAY.
MY COUGH SEEMS TO
HAVE CLEARED UP.
IT'S THE DARNDEST THING.
I'LL CALL YOU IF
THERE'S ANY CHANGE.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
CASSIDY, THIS DOG IS NOT YOURS.
\hDO I NEED TO REMIND
YOU THAT YOU'RE SICK?
NO, I'M NOT, MOMMY.
I FEEL ALL BETTER.
LOOK.
OH, MY GOSH, YOUR FEVER'S GONE.
CAN I GO BACK TO SCHOOL?
ARE YOU SURE
YOU FEEL OKAY?
YEAH.
YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL, YES, YOU ARE.
YOU'RE SO BEAUTIFUL.
HEY.
SAY SOMETHING INTO THIS EAR.
SOMETHING INTO THIS EAR.
AMAZING.
MY ACHE IS GONE.
I MEAN, THE EARACHE
\hIS TOTALLY GONE.
\h\h\hBONNIE, CALL THE DOC
AND TELL HIM -- NEVER MIND.
BUT I --
WHO ARE YOU?
JUST SOME KID THAT
\h\hYOU DON'T KNOW.
ARE THOSE YOUR DOGS?
THESE?
NO.
\h\hBECAUSE THERE ARE NO DOGS
ALLOWED IN THE WAITING ROOM.
OKAY.
BYE.
THAT'S WEIRD.
COME ON, PUPPIES.
COME ON.
YOU GUYS CAN STAY HERE FOR THE
NIGHT, BUT YOU CAN'T LIVE HERE.
I'LL BRING YOU SOME FOOD LATER.
YOU'VE GOT TO STAY HERE.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE QUIET.
I REALLY APPRECIATE THE PRESENT,
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hBUT DOES IT HAVE
TO VACUUM ALL DAY LONG?
(vacuum stops)
THANK YOU.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO ME?
UH, WHAT?
WHY IS YOUR SHIRT SO DIRTY?
IT'S JUST A SMUDGE.
IT KIND OF LOOKS
LIKE A PAW PRINT.
UH, WHAT?
WHY WOULD -- NAH.
IT'S JUST A SMUDGE.
\h\hYOU KNOW WHAT, WHY DON'T WE
EAT PIZZA SOMEWHERE THIS WEEK.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
\h\hI BET THERE'S A REALLY GOOD
PIZZA PLACE SOMEWHERE IN TOWN.
YEAH, PIZZA WILL BE GOOD.
OKAY.
SARAH, WHAT ABOUT YOU, YOU
\hMADE ANY NEW FRIENDS YET?
THE BOY ACROSS THE STREET
\h\h\hSEEMS REALLY NICE.
HE'S A JOCK.
OH, RIGHT, THAT WILL NEVER DO.
MOM?
HMM?
YOU REMEMBER WHEN YOU SAID THAT
WHEN I TURN 11 I CAN GET A DOG?
\h\h\hI SAID THAT WE'D TALK
ABOUT IT WHEN YOU TURN 13.
WELL, I'LL BE 11 IN ONE
\hMONTH AND FOUR DAYS.
\h\hI ALSO SAID WE HAD
TO HAVE A BIG BACKYARD
\hWITH A SEPARATE
SPOT FOR THE DOG,
SO THE DOG WON'T BOTHER SARAH,
AND WE DON'T HAVE THAT YET.
I CAN BUILD A FENCE.
NO DOGS, MOM.
DOGS ARE DANGEROUS.
NO, THEY AREN'T.
NOT IF YOU RAISE THEM RIGHT.
UNCLE AUTO'S DOG
WAS RAISED RIGHT,
AND THAT DOG BIT ME
\hRIGHT IN THE EYE.
YOU WEREN'T EVEN BORN YET.
NOW I'M DISFIGURED FOR LIFE.
SARAH, DON'T BE SILLY.
YOU ARE A BEAUTIFUL YOUNG WOMAN.
\h\hAND THE MINUTE YOU
START TO BELIEVE THAT,
\h\h\hYOU'RE GOING
TO BE VERY POPULAR.
YOU MIGHT EVEN HAVE
\hA NICE BOYFRIEND.
A BOYFRIEND?
WHY WOULD I EVEN WANT ONE?
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
\h\hME GETTING A DOG.
I'M FINISHED.
CAN I BE EXCUSED?
SURE.
\h\h\h\h\hTHERE, THAT IS MUCH
BETTER, DON'T YOU THINK?
OH, YES, MUCH BETTER.
EXCUSE ME.
OH.
WE KEEP THIS ROOM DARK BECAUSE
\h\hTHE LIGHT CAN HURT OLD EYES.
OH.
I THINK A FEW HOURS
A DAY IS OKAY.
IT'S MUCH CHEERIER.
IT'S GOING TO GIVE
\h\h\h\hME A MIGRAINE.
I JUST KNOW IT.
BUT NURSE BLEAKER,
WHAT'S WITH THE MUSIC?
IT'S SO OLD.
\h\hIT'S MONTE VINO,
MY OWN COLLECTION.
I FIND IT RELAXES THE RESIDENTS.
PERHAPS YOU CAN FIND
SOMETHING A LITTLE MORE FUN.
\h\h\h\h\hI REALLY DON'T
THINK OUR RESIDENTS
NEED A MAJOR CHANGE
\h\hIN THEIR ROUTINE.
IN ANY CASE, I CAME HERE TO TELL
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hYOU THAT OUR HOUSE DOCTOR
IS COMING HERE TO MAKE
\h\h\h\h\hHIS ROUNDS TODAY.
OH, GREAT.
DON'T GET TOO EXCITED.
HE CALLS HIMSELF DR. JEFF.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF
\h\hA DOCTOR NAMED JEFF?
\h\hHE'S A BACHELOR
WITH AN ATTITUDE.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTHERE'S EVEN
A RUMOR GOING AROUND
\h\h\h\h\h\hTHAT HE'S NOT
EVEN A REAL DOCTOR.
HE CERTAINLY DOESN'T
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hACT LIKE ONE.
FOR YOU, BLEAKER, A PRETTY
\hFLOWER FOR A PRETTY LADY.
HMM, DO YOU KNOW WHAT IN
WILL DO TO MY HAY FEVER?
NOT MUCH.
IT'S PLASTIC.
HELLO.
HI.
\h\h\h\hOH, YOU MUST BE
THE NEW ADMINISTRATOR.
THIS IS MISS WELLS.
YOU KNOW WHO HE IS.
\h\h\h\hGOOD OLD BLEAKER, SHE'S
A BIT OF AN ACQUIRED TASTE,
BUT SHE'S OKAY.
\h\hPROBABLY JUST NEEDS TO LOOSEN
UP THOSE HAIR PINS A LITTLE BIT.
HMM.
WHY DO YOU LOOK FAMILIAR?
I'M THE ROAD HOG WHO
DRIVES LIKE A MANIAC.
OH, NO.
MM-HMM.
THAT WAS YOU?
YEAH.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT,
\h\hYOU'RE THE JAYWALKER WHO
DOESN'T FOLLOW TRAFFIC LAWS.
WELL, NOW, HANG ON A SECOND.
WE'RE NOT USED TO CARS ROARING
DOWN THE MIDDLE OF MAIN STREET
IN SUCH A HURRY.
SO THAT'S WHY YOU STARTED
\hSCREAMING AND POUNDING
ON MY HOOD?
I'LL GIVE THAT ONE TO YOU.
\h\h\hIT'S JUST I WAS
HAVING A BAD MORNING.
\h\hI HAD JUST GOTTEN OFF
THE PHONE WITH MY FATHER,
WHO, LIKE ALWAYS --
IT'S A LONG STORY.
WELCOME TO HOPE SPRINGS.
THANKS.
WELL, DON'T LET ME KEEP
YOU FROM YOUR ROUNDS.
JOIN ME?
NO.
NO, THANKS.
\hI'VE GOT A LOT OF
CATCHING UP TO DO.
\hWELL, IT'S JUST THAT
SOME OF THE RESIDENTS,
\h\h\hTHEY TEND TO SCREAM
WHEN THEY SEE ME COMING,
AND YOUR PRESENCE MIGHT HAVE
A CALMING INFLUENCE ON THEM.
AND I THINK IT MIGHT
\hBE HELPFUL FOR YOU
TO GET THE 411 ON SOME OF
\hTHE MEDICAL CONDITIONS
THAT WE'RE TREATING AROUND HERE,
\hBUT IF YOU'RE NOT INTERESTED...
OH, DEAR, IT'S JUST AS I FEARED.
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT?
THIS WOMAN,
THIS DEAR WOMAN...
NEEDS TO BE TICKLED!
HOO-HOO-HOO-HOO!
WOO-HOO-HOO-HOO-HOO!
HAH, HAH, HAH!
I HAD YOU FOOLED FOR A MINUTE.
THAT IS THE OLDEST TRICK
\hIN THE BOOK, ELIZABETH.
DID YOU BRING ME
SOMETHING NICE?
WELL, THAT DEPENDS.
HOW DOES CHOCOLATE
\hSPRINKLES SOUND?
CHOCOLATE SPRINKLES,
\h\h\h\hMY FAVORITE.
MMM.
HOW WE FEELING?
OH, A LITTLE STIFF HERE
AND THERE, BUT I'M OLD,
IT COMES WITH THE TERRITORY.
ARE YOU STILL TAKING
\h\h\h\h\h\hYOUR VITAMINS?
EVERY DAY.
WELL, YOU KEEP THAT UP,
\hAND MAYBE, JUST MAYBE,
\h\h\h\hNEXT TIME I MIGHT BE ABLE
TO SWING A FEW MINT TRUFFLES.
MMM, MINT TRUFFLES.
THANK YOU, DOCTOR.
SHHH.
CHOCOLATE.
THESE ARE WONDERFUL PEOPLE.
YOU COULD LEARN ALL YOU
NEED TO KNOW ABOUT LIFE
IF YOU KEEP YOUR EARS
OPEN AROUND THIS PLACE.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hZack:
THE PROBLEM IS MY SISTER.
IT'S NOT THAT SHE'S A PROBLEM,
\hIT'S JUST THAT SHE'S A GIRL.
\h\hBUT I BET IF SHE MET
YOU, SHE WOULD LIKE YOU.
YOU GUYS LOOK HUNGRY.
YOU WANT SOMETHING TO EAT?
THIS IS FROM MY ALLOWANCE,
\h\h\h\hSO DON'T GO CRAZY.
I'M STILL TRYING
TO THINK OF A WAY
\h\h\hTO GET MY MOM
TO LET ME KEEP YOU.
BUT I GUESS SHE'S GOT
A LOT OF OTHER THINGS
ON HER MIND RIGHT NOW.
PERMISSION TO COME
\h\hABOARD, CAPTAIN.
AHOY, SAWBONES.
\h\h\hI HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN
THESE WATERS FOR SOME TIME.
NO.
THAT'S BECAUSE LAST TIME I
WAS HERE YOU WERE SLEEPING.
HOW YOU FEELING, PETE?
\h\h\hOH, I HAVE GOOD
DAYS AND BAD DAYS.
HEY, DID YOU NOTICE
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTHAT WE HAVE
A NEW AND VERY PRETTY
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hADMINISTRATOR?
YOU KNOW WHAT, I DID NOTICE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
HUH?
\hI THINK THAT YOU
AND HER SHOULD --
(snoring)
I GUESS WE'LL NEVER KNOW.
MR. WEAVER'S VERY ILL.
\hHE DECIDED TO DISCONTINUE
TREATMENT A FEW WEEKS AGO,
SO I'M AFRAID HE'S NOT GOING
\h\hTO BE WITH US MUCH LONGER.
FORTUNATELY, HE'S
\hNOT IN ANY PAIN.
\h\h\hWELL, IT'S NICE TO
MEET YOU, MRS. WELLS.
MISS, ACTUALLY.
OH, IS IT?
HI.
HI, MOM.
OH, HI.
THIS IS MY DAUGHTER, SARAH.
SARAH, THIS IS DR. JEFF.
HI.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hHELLO, SARAH.
MOM, CAN I BORROW THE CAR?
THERE'S A COOL MALL
\hOVER IN ROSSDALE,
AND I NEED SCHOOL CLOTHES.
ROSSDALE?
NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S 15 MILES AWAY.
WE DISCUSSED THIS,
\hNO DRIVING ALONE UNTIL
YOU'VE HAD MORE PRACTICE.
\h\hWE CAN GO THIS
WEEKEND, TOGETHER.
I'M 16, I CAN'T GO TO
THE MALL WITH MY MOM.
OH.
TRUE, THAT IS A PROBLEM.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW,
\hMAYBE I CAN DROP YOU OFF
WITHOUT ANYBODY SEEING ME.
(scoffing)
WE'LL DISCUSS THIS LATER.
GREAT SHADES.
OH, DO YOU LIKE HIM?
DR. JEFF?
WELL, HE'S NICE.
MOM?
COOL.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PUT THOSE BACK!
COME BACK HERE!
YOU LITTLE THIEF!
WHOA!
DARN NEAR SCARED
ME TO DEATH, BOY.
I'M SORRY.
SOMEONE WAS CHASING ME.
WERE THEY NOW?
AND DID SHE HAVE BLACK HAIR,
AND EYES DARK AND FIERCE
\h\h\h\h\h\hLIKE A SHARK,
AND A LITTLE FUNNY HAT?
YES.
DON'T WORRY, SON,
YOU'RE SAFE HERE.
NURSE BLEAKER DOESN'T DARE
\h\hMESS WITH CAPTAIN PETE,
AND THAT'S ME.
YOU HAVE A NAME YOURSELF?
ZACK, ZACK WELLS.
AND WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
OH, SOME COOKIES.
THEY WERE ON A CART
\h\hIN THE HALLWAY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO STEAL THEM.
WHAT'S FREE CAN'T BE STOLE.
THINK I CAN HAVE ONE?
ZACK WELLS, YOU SAY.
\hNOW, WHY DOES THAT
NAME SOUND FAMILIAR?
MY MOM WORKS HERE.
OH, MISS WELLS.
NOW THERE'S A FINE FRIEND,
AND A RIGHT PRETTY LADY, TOO,
IF YOU DON'T MIND MY SAYING.
I THINK SHE'S PRETTY, TOO.
THEMS THE PLANETS AND THE STARS.
YEP, THAT'S SATURN AND JUPITER,
\h\hAND THERE'S THE BIG DIPPER,
AND THAT'S THE NORTH STAR.
\h\h\h\hCaptain Pete:
WELL, I AM IMPRESSED.
YOU KNOW YOUR STARS.
I KNOW A LITTLE.
I'D LIKE TO KNOW MORE.
\hWELL, YOU CAN LEARN
A LOT FROM THE STARS.
THEY'LL TELL YOU WHERE YOU
\hARE, WHERE YOU CAME FROM,
\hAND IF YOU LOOK WITH
THE RIGHT KIND OF EYES,
YOU CAN SEE WHERE YOU'RE GOING
\hJUST BY LOOKING AT THE STARS.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
OF COURSE.
WHAT IF SOMEONE FOUND SOMETHING
AND MAYBE THAT SOMETHING
BELONGS TO SOMEONE ELSE,
BUT HE DOESN'T KNOW FOR SURE?
HEY, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
\hTALK IN RIDDLES, SON.
A MAN CAN SPEAK HIS MIND HERE.
\h\hI FOUND A COUPLE OF
LITTLE DOGS THE FOREST.
SOMEONE HAD LEFT THEM IN A CAGE,
\h\h\hAND THEY FOLLOWED ME HOME.
\h\h\hWHAT SCOUNDREL
WOULD ABANDON A DOG?
IT'S A TERRIBLE BUSINESS.
IT'S A GOOD THING A BOY
\hLIKE YOU CAME ALONG.
I GUESS.
MY MOM WON'T LET ME
KEEP THEM, THOUGH,
BECAUSE MY SISTER'S
\h\hAFRAID OF DOGS.
OH, NOW THAT IS A QUANDARY.
\hZack: THEY'RE IN MY
CLUBHOUSE RIGHT NOW.
\h\h\hBUT IF MY MOM FINDS THEM,
SHE'LL MAKE ME GET RID OF THEM.
\h\hI NEED A PLACE TO HIDE THEM
UNTIL I CAN THINK OF SOMETHING.
\hWELL, IF IT WILL HELP, I HAVE A
CLOSET THERE THAT I AIN'T USING,
\h\hSO YOUR DOGS WILL BE SAFE
UNTIL YOU DECIDE WHAT TO DO,
AND I THINK YOU'LL
DO THE RIGHT THING.
DO YOU MEAN IT?
OF COURSE.
BRING THEM BY AFTER 6:00,
\h\hBECAUSE THAT'S WHEN
OLD BLEAKER GOES HOME.
\hI'M HAPPY TO HELP
A NEW FRIEND, ZACK.
THANKS, CAPTAIN.
\h\h\hNurse Bleaker:
YES, I GOT YOUR POEM.
THERE WERE FOUR MISSPELLINGS
\h\hIN THE FIRST TWO STANZAS.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO SEND A POEM,
\h\hYOU KNOW, YOU MIGHT
JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THE SPELLING IS CORRECT.
FINE.
YES.
YES, I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
TALK TO YOU LATER.
\hSarah:
WOO-HOO!
YEAH!
WOO!
WOO-HOO!
(music playing over headphones)
WOO!
WOO-HOO, YEAH!
(music ends abruptly)
HELLO.
NICE MOVES.
YOU'RE A GOOD DANCER.
HOW ABOUT YOU, YOU PROBABLY
\h\h\h\hHAVE A NAME, RIGHT?
SARAH.
I LIKE THAT NAME.
I LIKE YOUR DANCING, TOO.
I WISH I COULD DANCE LIKE THAT.
\h\h\h\hSPEAKING OF WHICH,
THERE'S A DANCE THIS FRIDAY
AT THE SCHOOL AUDITORIUM
\h\hBEFORE THE NEW
SCHOOL YEAR STARTS.
IF YOU WANT TO COME, I COULD
INTRODUCE YOU TO SOME PEOPLE.
\h\hMAYBE YOU COULD
MAKE SOME FRIENDS.
I DON'T EXACTLY GET ALONG
\h\h\hWITH THE POPULAR KIDS,
AND YOU'RE PROBABLY
ONE OF THEM, RIGHT?
I GUESS, BUT I DIDN'T ASK TO BE.
AND I SHOOT A PRETTY
\hGOOD THREE-POINTER,
SO EVERYONE TREATS ME LIKE I'M
SPECIAL, BUT TRUST ME, I'M NOT.
ONE THING I KNOW IS, DON'T TRUST
\h\hANYONE WHO SAYS, "TRUST ME."
AH, OKAY.
CAUGHT YOU ON A BAD DAY.
THAT'S COOL.
MAYBE WE COULD TALK
\hSOME OTHER TIME.
YEAH.
I'M GOING TO LEAVE.
SARAH, YOU IDIOT.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hPaula:
SO HOW'S IT GOING, FRANCES?
JUST FINE, MISS WELLS.
MM-HMM, OKAY, EXCUSE ME, BYE.
HELLO.
ROCKIN' OLDIES, PAULA SPEAKING.
\hDr. Jeff:
YOU HUNGRY?
WHO IS THIS?
\hIT'S JEFF, THE GUY
WITH THE STETHOSCOPE.
HI.
HELLO.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT WE'RE NOT GETTING
OFF ON THE WRONG FOOT.
THE FACT IS IS THAT I WAS
JAYWALKING THE OTHER DAY,
AND I APOLOGIZE.
APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
THAT'S GOOD.
I FEEL BETTER.
AND EVEN THOUGH IT
WAS ALL YOUR FAULT,
I WOULD FEEL EVEN BETTER IF YOU
\h\h\hLET ME MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
MAKE IT UP TO ME.
HOW?
\h\hBY LETTING ME TAKE
YOU TO DINNER TONIGHT.
TONIGHT?
REALLY?
BUT ONLY IF YOU'RE HUNGRY,
\h\h\h\hBECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
IT WOULDN'T NECESSARILY
\h\h\h\hBE A DATE THING.
IT'S MORE LIKE TWO PEOPLE
\h\hEATING FOOD TOGETHER.
RIGHT.
HELLO?
YEAH.
YEAH, SORRY.
\h\h\hI WAS JUST SWITCHING
THE PHONE TO THE OTHER EAR.
PICK YOU UP IN 20 MINUTES?
CAN YOU MAKE IT 30?
I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
\h\hFrankie:
HELLO, THERE.
\h\h\hI SAW YOU SITTING HERE BY
YOURSELF AND -- I DON'T KNOW --
\hTHOUGHT YOU MIGHT
LIKE SOME COMPANY.
NOT REALLY.
NICE PARK.
I'M FRANKIE.
YOU LIVE AROUND HERE?
I GUESS SO.
YOU GUESS SO.
THAT'S FUNNY.
SO, LIKE, WHAT DO YOU DO?
ARE YOU A MODEL OR SOMETHING?
A MODEL?
NO, YOU'RE NOT A MODEL?
PLEASE.
ACTRESS.
NOT EVEN.
WELL, YOU SHOULD BE.
SERIOUSLY, THERE ARE GIRLS
MAKING A FORTUNE AS MODELS
WHO AREN'T HALF AS GOOD
LOOKING AS YOU.
YOU GOT NICE STRUCTURE.
WOW, YOU'RE GOOD.
THANKS.
BEEN PLAYING SINCE I WAS SEVEN.
ACTUALLY, I'M ON THE VERGE
OF GETTING A RECORD DEAL.
REALLY?
YEAH.
THERE'S, LIKE, SIX
COMPANIES TRYING TO SIGN ME.
I'M JUST, YOU KNOW, NOT SURE
IF I'M READY FOR THE FAME.
I'M A SIMPLE GUY.
BUT THEY SAY I'M
GOING TO BE HUGE,
SO, I GUESS I'LL JUST
HAVE TO GET USED TO IT.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hIT MUST BE NICE GETTING
SOMETHING YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED.
HEY, I WAS GOING TO
GO GET SOME ICE CREAM.
YOU WANT TO JOIN ME?
(cell phone ringing)
HELLO?
HI, MOM.
OH, JUST SITTING
\h\hIN THE PARK.
OKAY.
OH, MY MOM, SHE'S OUT ON A DATE.
I HAVE TO GO HOME AND MAKE
\h\h\h\hDINNER FOR MY BROTHER.
AND HOW ABOUT THAT
ICE CREAM OFFER?
I DON'T THINK SO.
MY MOM WOULD NEVER LET
\hME DATE AN OLDER GUY.
WELL, IF YOU ASK ME,
I THINK SHE DOESN'T REALIZE HOW
SOPHISTICATED YOU REALLY ARE.
I'D BETTER GO.
ANYWAYS, I'M ONLY
19 -- AND A HALF.
WELL, IF YOU DON'T LIKE MOVIES,
\hWE COULD JUST GO FOR A DRIVE.
\h\h\hI'LL GET A COUPLE
OF MEATBALL SANDWICHES
AND COME PICK YOU UP AND --
\h\h\h\hWELL, WHO SAID
ANYTHING ABOUT PARKING?
NO.
(music box playing)
SIR?
HANG ON.
YEAH.
DO YOU THINK THOSE DOGS COULD
\h\hBE HERE IN HOPE SPRINGS?
\h\hTHAT'S A DALLAS PAPER,
A HUNDRED MILES FROM HERE.
I JUST HUNG IT UP BECAUSE
\h\h\hI LIKE THE PICTURE.
SORRY.
SO IF SOMEONE FOUND DOGS
THAT LOOK A LOT LIKE
\h\hTHAT AROUND HERE,
\h\h\h\hTHEY CAN'T BE
THE SAME DOGS; RIGHT?
HANG ON.
I DON'T SEE HOW THAT COULD
\hBE, BUT I'M ON THE PHONE.
OKAY?
THE MUSIC BOX IS FIVE BUCKS.
(car radio blaring)
AREN'T WE GOING A LITTLE FAST?
WE'RE BARELY DOING 30.
YOU'RE NOT SCARED, ARE YOU?
NO.
NO, NO, NO.
GOOD.
(engine revs)
(screaming)
(laughing)
WE MARRIED YOUNG, TOO YOUNG.
IT TURNS OUT
HE LOVED HIS JOB
MORE THAN HE
LOVED BEING MARRIED.
THAT'S OKAY.
\h\h\hHE'S GREAT WITH THE KIDS,
AND I GUESS WE'LL BE FRIENDS --
SOME DAY.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
UH-HUH.
ALL RIGHT, YOUR TURN.
WHAT BROUGHT YOU
TO HOPE SPRINGS?
I COME FROM A LONG
\hLINE OF DOCTORS.
\h\h\hMY PARENTS EXPECTED ME TO
BECOME A DOCTOR TOO, SO I DID.
AND THEN THEY EXPECTED ME TO
\h\hGO TO WORK AT A HOSPITAL
WHERE THERE'S AN ENTIRE WING
\hNAMED AFTER MY GRANDFATHER,
AND THAT WASN'T GOING TO HAPPEN.
OH.
SO I DECIDED TO LEAVE THE CITY
AND GO SOMEPLACE WHERE I COULD
\h\h\hBREATHE A LITTLE EASIER,
HAVE A LIFE OF MY OWN.
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR KIDS.
WELL, ZACK IS 11.
HE'S INTO EVERYTHING.
\h\h\h\hHE WANTS TO DO
SOMETHING BIG SOME DAY.
AND SARAH IS 16.
AND I TEND TO FORGET SHE'S
NOT A LITTLE GIRL ANYMORE.
IT'S HARD.
'CAUSE I JUST WANT TO PROTECT
HER FROM THE WORLD, YOU KNOW?
OH, I CAN IMAGINE.
I LOVE KIDS.
\h\hI'M GOING TO PICK ME UP
A COUPLE OF THEM SOME DAY.
YEAH.
(laughing)
HMM, WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
NOTHING.
\h\h\hWHY DON'T YOU TAKE A
PICTURE, IT'LL LAST LONGER.
YEAH, RIGHT, OKAY, FINE.
HEY!
OH, GA!
HEY, FRANKIE, LOOK AT THAT.
THERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
HEY, FRANKIE --
HEY, YOU KNOW THAT
LOOKS LIKE OUR DOGS.
GEE, YOU THINK?
IT SAYS THESE DOGS
\h\hCAN HEAL PEOPLE.
MIRACLE DOGS?
WOW.
IT AIN'T FOR REAL.
\h\h\h\h\hIT'S PROBABLY SOME
SORT OF SCAM, YOU KNOW?
\hSOME PEOPLE WILL
BELIEVE ANYTHING.
I DON'T KNOW, I THINK IF YOU
REALLY BELIEVE IN SOMETHING,
ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE.
HEY, MAYBE IT'S
'CAUSE OF THOSE DOGS
THAT MY HEAD
DOESN'T ITCH ANYMORE.
\hIF THOSE DOGS COULD
ACTUALLY HEAL PEOPLE
THEY WOULD BE WORTH A FORTUNE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S TOO BAD YOU
\h\hTHREW THEM IN THE RIVER.
WELL, I KIND OF HAVE
A CONFESSION TO MAKE, FRANKIE.
WHAT IS IT?
BUT YOU HAVE TO
PROMISE NOT TO GET MAD.
\hYOU KNOW I DON'T LIKE
TO MAKE PROMISES, LEO.
I JUST --
OKAY.
I WON'T GET MAD.
TELL ME.
I DIDN'T THROW THE DOGS IN
\hTHE RIVER LIKE YOU SAID.
\h\h\hI LEFT THEM NICE
AND SAFE UNDER A TREE.
SEE, YOU'RE MAD, I KNEW IT.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THAT'S THE BEST NEWS
I'VE HEARD ALL WEEK.
LET'S GO.
WHERE?
TO GET RICH.
\h\h\h\hZack: THERE ARE 88
CONSTELLATIONS IN THE SKY.
A CONSTELLATION IS
\hA GROUP OF STARS.
THE ANCIENT GREEKS NAMED MANY
\h\h\h\hOF THE CONSTELLATIONS
AFTER HEROES LIKE ANDROMEDA,
\h\h\h\h\hORION, AND PERSEUS.
A HERO IS SOMEONE WHO
\hHELPS OTHER PEOPLE,
EVEN IF IT'S DANGEROUS.
I'D LIKE TO BE A HERO SOME DAY.
BUT THERE'S NOT A LOT OF
\hOPPORTUNITIES FOR KIDS.
THAT LOOKS LIKE IT.
WELL, IT'S JUST UP AHEAD.
IT'S JUST A LEFT
AT THE NEXT TREE.
LEFT AT THE --
THERE'S 200 TREES HERE.
OH, THAT LOOKS LIKE IT.
YEAH, THAT LOOKS LIKE IT.
NO, NO, THAT'S IT.
\hWELL, THAT KIND
OF LOOKS LIKE IT.
COME ON, LEO, WHICH ONE?
WELL, ALL I KNOW IS IT HAS
A "NO HUNTING" SIGN ON IT.
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY THAT?
OVER HERE.
THEY'RE GONE.
YEAH, I CAN SEE THAT.
SOMEBODY STOLE OUR DOGS.
THIS IS PERFECT.
SOMEBODY STOLE OUR STOLEN DOGS.
WE WERE MEANT TO
HAVE THOSE DOGS, LEO,
JUST LIKE WE WERE
MEANT TO HAVE THAT CAR.
THE CAR THAT BROKE DOWN ON US?
WE GOT TO GET THOSE DOGS BACK.
YEAH.
HEY, FREE HAT.
IT MATCHES TOO.
HUH, ZACK, PERFECT,
\h\hTHIS IS A CLUE.
\h\hALL RIGHT, WHOEVER THIS
ZACK IS, HE STOLE OUR DOGS.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO FIND THIS
THIEF AND GET OUR DOGS BACK.