♪♪♪
Good morning.
- All rise. Department 116 of
San Diego Superior Court is now
in session.
The Honorable Judge Katherine A.
Woodbury presiding. Please be
seated. Come to order.
- Good morning your honor.
- Morning Millie. Docket
please.
- Number one on the calendar.
Case 327 dash 03 dash 019.
Alberta Johnson versus Henry
Guzman.
Amendment to the child support
order and settlement of back
payments.
Mr. Guzman's gross income is
$2,244.62 per month. He lives
rent free in company housing.
Child support set last year at
$175.50 per week. No payments
made since May 15th.
- You speak English, Mr.
Guzman?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Then you understand the
agreement you made with this
court last year?
- Yes ma'am.
- Then honor it. Provide for
your son or go to jail. Those
are your options.
Pay the bailiff and you may go.
Next.
- Next, 06 dash 419. Ralph
Withers versus Mona Harley
Withers.
- Uh, yes, we're working on a
settlement here, your honor.
- Counselor, you're either
ready to try this case or I'll
rule for the plaintiff.
Your choice.
- Yes, your honor.
- 517 dash 23 dash 774. Jenson
family petitioning the state for
termination of foster care.
- The Jensons want to return
her to the state's custody.
They feel she requires a
situation more fitting for a
young adult.
- Mr. Jenson?
- Ma'am.
Ma'am, my wife and I
don't want anyone to think
we aren't good citizens or
that we don't care.
- No one's suggesting
anything of the kind.
- We've tried our very best
with Sally.
It's the lying, it's the
stealing.
- She took our car. Her and her
boyfriend. Uh, twice.
- Is the girl here?
Sally, is that true, did you
steal the Jenson's car.
- It's not stealing if you
bring it back.
- She took some money, also,
your honor. From my wife's
purse. 50 bucks.
- I didn't take your stupid
money.
- I can't deal with it anymore.
But we've tried our best with
Sally, but she just, doesn't
make an effort.
She doesn't fit in, you know
what I mean?
- Very well, the State Of
California assumes custody of
Miss Sally Ann Powell until such
time as an appropriate foster
family can be secured.
- County homes are at capacity
your honor.
- Well, then we'll send her
some place else.
Who's here from Child Welfare?
- Not a soul. Pretty much
everyone's left.
- Well, this is absurd. The
child has to go somewhere.
The court remands Sally Powell
the Juvenile Correctional
Facility.
We're going to revisit the case
in three weeks, right after
recess.
- That's it, ma'am.
- Thank you everyone.
- All rise. The court is now in
recess.
- I don't know. Putting a
minor in jail because foster
care is full.
How ridiculous is
that?
- It seems like she's got a
little petty larceny going on
there, too.
- Ah.
- Well, either way, it's only
temporary.
- It doesn't matter.
Three weeks in there for a
16 year old. Uh uh.
Oh, Millie, please file this
before you leave.
- Sure.
- And you better get moving,
you have some packing to do. And
remember...
- I know, sun block.
- Yeah, and no more
refrigerator magnets.
Send me a post card
instead. Enjoy your vacation.
- Hello beautiful.
Hey. Hello.
- Davis.
- Am I interrupting?
- Yes. But come on in anyway.
What are you doing in my
courthouse?
- Well, just filed a suit
against Med Phase, they screwed
up a routine surgery
on a 19 year old woman. Top
athlete. It is going to cost
them.
- Let me guess, more than
enough to send you and your
latest to Tuscany for the
entire summer.
- Hey, I'm surprised. Tuscany
is unbearable in the summer.
I'm thinking about Tahiti or
Bora Bora.
- How come you and I never made
it to Tahiti?
- Because you were always too
busy with your work.
The law is
a jealous mistress.
- So was your secretary, as I
recall. [LAUGH]
- Are you free Saturday night?
I'm throwing a little party over
at the grill.
- Saturday? Yeah, yeah, I could
probably stop by.
- Good, there's somebody I
want you to meet.
- Heh, [LAUGH]
you're not setting me up are
you?
- No, God, no. I'm getting
married.
- Ah.
- Her name is Monica Tejada.
She is a civil attorney.
She worked her way through
Stanford, two years in justice
and she just got a spot at
Johnston Sloan. I think you'll
like her.
- She sounds young.
- 28.
- Very young.
- All right, I'm sorry, have I
gone about this in the wrong
way?
- No, [STAMMERS] not at all.
Uh, congratulations. I'd love to
come to your party.
- Really?
- Yes.
- [OVERLAPPING] Good.
- Well, great, who knows, you
may even enjoy yourself, huh?
- I, yeah, yeah. Who knows. I,
I don't mean to be rude, Davis,
but I've got a lot of work to
do.
- Can I give you a little piece
of advice?
- Why not?
- Don't send that girl to jail.
I'm sorry, hey, sue me, I
was eavesdropping.
Kids that age are vulnerable.
They're so easily swayed.
- I know the dangers as well as
you do.
But there was no place
else to put her.
It's the system.
- Kay. You are the system.
- Davis, I know you mean well,
but, I've got a lot of work
to do.
- Which is exactly why we
never made it to Tahiti.
See you Saturday.
- I see her right over there.
Thank you. I know, I know
[LAUGH] I'm sorry I'm late.
- You look tired. I understand.
The week before recess she had a
million cases.
Do they work you
too hard?
- I'll survive.
- Thank you.
Speaking of recess, what's
your project this year?
- What do you mean?
- You always have a project.
- No I don't [LAUGH] .
- Yes you do. Last year you
refinished those old chairs
and the year before that you
stripped your dining room floors
and the year before
that, you had bookshelves made
for the study.
- What is your point mother?
- How about seeing some actual
people?
- You, uh, shouldn't be
referring to you and dad by any
chance would you?
- Kay, this feud you have is
silly.
- It's not a feud mom.
- I don't care what you call
it, it's stupid.
- Are we going to eat or argue?
- Honey, what your father did
was wrong. [STAMMERS]
- Katy, now don't get upset
with your mother, she didn't
know I was coming.
I, I looked at her date book.
- I'm sorry, I didn't know.
- Katy. At least help me
understand.
- [OVERLAPPING] Okay. You don't
understand?
- I asked you for a delay in a
case. Judges do that all the
time.
- Not for their fathers. And
not for some
irrelevant legal matter that
could have gotten us both
disbarred.
- But you haven't heard my
side of the story. At least, let
me explain.
- [OVERLAPPING] I don't want
to [UNINTELLIGIBLE] look, I'll
call you, okay?
- Oh, Kay.
- In regard to Anderson versus
Craig, both parties have agreed
to new terms of custody
and waive hearing on the 14th.
Oh, and Millie, remind me to
follow up with the D. A.
on the Nunez case. We also have
the Peterson matter which...
- [OVERLAPPING] [MAKES NOISE]
I'm sorry your honor, I didn't
mean to startle you.
My name's Miranda, I'm a case
worker with the Child Welfare
office.
- It's late. What do you want?
- I would like to talk to you
about Sally Powell.
- Oh, I see. Now, you want to
talk. Where were you three hours
ago?
- I apologize for that.
- Apologize to Sally. Not me.
She's in jail. Because of you.
- [STAMMERS] It's not entirely
my fault. My department is on
overload right now.
We're understaffed.
- Oh I see, well. Tell me this.
What kind of foster family
rejects a girl just for being
different?
I don't understand that? Where
do you get these families?
- Sally has been through so
much already. She is a bright
kid, full of promise.
- Wow, I, I'm sure she is. But
finding her a home is your
responsibility, not mine.
- If you could just help.
- I'll be happy to take a look
at her file
and assist you in any way I can.
In three weeks.
[doorbell chimes]
- Hi. I, I know it's early but
I wanted to make sure you'd be
home.
- What are you doing here?
- Making one last plea for
Sally.
- Well, I, I've already
explained to you...
- [OVERLAPPING] Your honor, in
all good conscience, how can
either of us complain
about the system if we don't do
everything in our power to
change it.
Just take a look,
get to know Sally a little. If
you see what I see, you'll
realize,
she deserves every break we can
give her.
- Fine.
- Thank you judge. [STAMMERS]
There's just a few pages,
I didn't want to overload you
with the whole case history.
- I, I can't promise you
anything.
- Don't worry [LAUGH] , I have
faith enough for both of us.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
-Bye
- Good morning.
- Morning. Well, visiting hours
don't start for another hour.
You can wait over there if you
like.
- I'm Judge Katherine Woodbury.
- Sorry, judge. What can I do
for you?
- I sent a juvenile over
yesterday, temporary custody.
- Name?
- Powell, Sally Ann.
- 43 unit 221 but she's
probably out in the yard now.
- Can you take me?
- You want to go back there?
- Yes, I do.
- I don't think that's such
a good idea.
- I, I would like to see
the prison yard, sergeant. Is
that a problem?
- No ma'am. Your honor, no
problem at all.
- I would think a stroll in
this place would be an effective
deterrent.
- Worked for my
son. He was acting up so
I brought him down here
for the night shift.
And now it's straight As, every
semester.
The yard's just out
here.
Holly will take you out. Looking
for Powell, Sally Ann.
- Thank you.
-[background chatter] I haven't
seen her, maybe she's inside.
I didn't ask you. [ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
- She's over there.
- I won. [ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
- Thank you. [ALL TALKING AT
ONCE]
- I give up, what are you
looking at?
- Good question. What's the
book?
- It's how to escape from
prison manual.
- Good sense of humor. [LAUGH]
It's important, it'll see you
through a lot in life.
- Sure done wonders for me so
far.
- Nice talking to you.
- Come on come on. [ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
- [remembers Davis] Don't send
the girl to jail.
- [remembers Miranda] Sally has
been through so much already.
She is a bright kid, full of
promise.
- Forget something, judge?
- Hey, you got a form 209A back
there somewhere?
- Yes, ma'am I think so.
- Get your California codes.
- Ma'am.
- Please read, welfare and
institution, section 385.
- Any order by the court may at
any time be modified or set
aside as the presiding judge
deems proper.
- Now read section 319.
- The court may order
the child to be placed in
the approved home of
a non relative for a
period not to exceed
30 juridical days.
- Sign at the bottom and would
you please witness.
- Court's releasing Sally Ann
Powell to the custody of
Katherine A. Woodbury?
- Yes.
- It's a big house. You'll
have your own room and bath.
And I expect you to keep them
both clean.
You can come and go as you
please, but there is a curfew.
10:00 on weekdays and 11:00 on
weekends.
I think that's reasonable.
- Come in.
- Do you own this?
- Yes.
- And you live here all by
yourself?
- Uh huh.
- You're right, it's big.
Don't you get scared?
- Sometimes.
- But you have a security
system, right?
- Uh, absolutely and there's
no reason for either of us
to be nervous.
- I'm not nervous.
- Here, let me help you.
- I'll do that.
- Fine.
Uh, the closet's here.
And you have plenty of room in
the chest of drawers.
Your own TV.
- How many channels you got?
- 150 at last count.
Go ahead and unpack and
I'll go rustle up some lunch.
Come to the kitchen when
you're ready.
- You're in, what, ninth grade?
- Tenth.
- Well I guess there's no
point in going to school. It's
after 1:00.
- I'm always up for a day off.
- Yeah.
- So, what's this court
recess?
- Well, we close down for three
weeks every year to catch up on
appeals and petitions.
- I get it. You baby-sit me for
a while and then drop me off
somewhere on your way back to
work. Right?
- Here's the deal. There was
no place to put you but jail or
my house.
So, you'll stay with me
until we can find you
another foster family.
- I know what's going
to happen. I'm a four
time loser already.
- I'm not saying it's going
to be easy.
- Then why bother?
- Because it beats the
alternative.
- In your opinion.
- Boy you are sure not
out to win any popularity
contests are you?
- I think I'll go keep my room
clean.
- I have a few errands to run.
You want to come along?
- I don't think so.
- Can I trust you here alone?
- I don't know. Can you?
- If that's the way it's going
to be, fine.
But for someone who stole a car
last week, you might want to
briefly consider the entire
range of consequences that a
judge can bring down on your
underage head.
- Fine, I won't run off.
Besides, where would I go?
- Fine, I'll see you later this
evening.
Miranda. I was just coming to
see you.
- Yeah, I just found out what
you did for Sally.
Thank you so much. I really
appreciate it.
- Well, I'm going to need more
than appreciation to get
thorough this one.
- Yeah. [LAUGH] Parenting isn't
easy.
- Well, I'm hardly her parent,
but, uh, if I'm going to battle,
I better be armed so, get me
everything you've got on her.
- Okay, I'm, I'm on a break so
why don't we grab a cup of
coffee.
- Look mom . How beautiful.
Hey, it's Sally. Is Pete around?
No, no message.
I'll call him back, thanks.
Wait.
Yeah, hi, just, um, when you
tell him I called,
will you let him know I'm out.
He'll understand.
Thanks.
- Four families in five years.
That can't be normal.
- It's not. A lot of foster
children stick with one family.
They connect with a parent or a
sibling but
Sally never has. Thank you.
- Well, what about when she was
younger? Didn't anyone want to
adopt her?
- Yeah, she came close when she
was three, but the couple
stopped the proceedings when the
wife got pregnant. A few years
later another couple was
interested, but then
they split up.
- Oh, what rotten luck.
- Exactly. The second time
Sally was old enough to
understand what was happening.
And she took it pretty hard.
That's when she started to
shut down.
- No wonder she's so tough.
Don't you have anything
that isn't a, a report
or an evaluation?
What about a paper
she wrote for school?
- No, that's it except for
sealed records and I don't
have access to them.
- I do.
- Nobody's done this much for
Sally.
- Well, right now, I'm her
legal guardian.
- Still here.
- So I see. You're a reader.
- It's an escape.
- Yeah, I know what you
mean. When I was your age I was
never without a book.
What is it, uh,
David Copperfield. One of
my favorites.
- Yeah, me too.
Well, I have
school tomorrow, I
should go to bed.
- Good idea.
- Good night, judge.
- Please call me Kay.
- All right. Kay.
- Sleep well. Sally. I'm glad
you're here.
-[Sally] I know, I know, I
know.
I didn't want any help.
I can do it myself. I'm doing
fine. So get out and beat it.
- Sally.
- [OVERLAPPING] Please don't
go, come back. Please. No.
- [OVERLAPPING] Sally.
- Mom. [MAKES NOISE] Mom.
- What is it, what is it,
what's wrong.
- [MAKES NOISE] Mom, pleases.
- Wake up, it's a nightmare.
Sally, it's okay, it's okay.
[MAKES NOISE] It's just a
nightmare. Sally, wake up.
- This isn't really my field.
I don't see many kids in my
practice
and, uh, without a clinical
evaluation, it's tough to say.
- Well it must be something
there.
- No evidence of serious
illness, I can tell you that.
- What about the nightmares?
- Well, she's got to have
someone to talk to. Kids have
vivid imaginations.
And this one's hurt because she
was abandoned. The clothes, the
attitude,
the nightmares, she's acting
out because she's all alone
in the world.
- She's smart, Michael.
- The test scores certainly
indicate that. And so does the
behavior.
Bright kids tend to over reach
when they're up against a wall.
- Why?
- Because I think they know
that they're missing
something important.
If you like, I could set up an
evaluation, that might be
better.
- Thanks. I'll think about it.
- Morning.
- Good morning. Sally, this is
Dr. Katsu. He lives next door.
- Hi Sally.
- I was just telling him
that you'd be staying here
for a while.
The Katsu's have a son, Danny,
about your age.
- We'll have to get you two
together.
- What kid of doctor are you?
- I'm a psychiatrist.
- So anything do we ever
committed?
- [LAUGH] Very funny. We need
to get you some breakfast.
Thanks for the advice.
- Not a problem.
- In your office there's some
pictures of you with some old
people.
Are they your parents? [LAUGH]
- Old people? Whoa. My mother
would love that.
- So your mom's alive?
- Alive and kicking. My father,
too.
- Do they live nearby?
- About 45 minutes away.
- What's that like? Having
parents?
- Uh, well, it's, it's
wonderful and it's difficult
and it's very, very complicated.
- What do you mean?
- It means I love my mother and
father very much,
but sometimes it's hard to be
around them.
- Do they love you?
- Too much, I think.
- How can someone love you too
much?
- Trust me, it happens.
- No one's ever loved me.
- I bet you're wrong, I bet
plenty of people love you.
- Well no one's ever said it to
me.
- Well, maybe they're afraid to
say it.
- Whatever. Doesn't really
matter. I don't care.
- [School yard chatter]
- Sally. Do you remember
[STAMMERS] anything about last
night?
It was very late and I heard
voices coming from your room.
So, I went to check on you.
- I'm going to be late for
English period.
- You were talking to someone.
- Big deal, I was sleeping, it
was a nightmare.
- No, it wasn't like that. It
was, it was more like you were
in a trance of some kind.
- I was in a trance. And I was
talking to someone. Who was I
talking to?
- Your mother.
- I don't have a mother.
- You were pleading with her,
she wanted you to do something.
- And why would I want to do
something for my mother?
Huh, why would I even want to
talk to my mother, Kay?
- Sally, please.
- No, she abandoned me. She
dumped me like I was garbage.
- Sally, just, okay, let me
just talk to you a minute.
- Wake up people. Who can tell
me what's really going on
here? Nobody eat breakfast?
Come on you guys. If all George
and Martha ever wanted was to
have a child, how could
George just kill their son off?
What is the playwright trying to
say here?
Did anyone read the play?
- Did, uh, George and Martha
need marriage counseling?
[LAUGH]
- Sally. Help me out here.
- Couldn't have children.
- Sorry.
- They couldn't have a family.
So they made one up.
- Good, that's right. Don't
forget everybody,
there's an essay due on
Thursday which you have to
read the play in order to write
it. Enjoy your lunch.
- So you want to cut class?
- Nah.
- Then again the mind's a
terrible thing to waste.
- That's what I hear. What are
you doing here?
- Looking for you. Where'd they
dump you this time?
- You wouldn't believe me if
I told you.
- Who cares. You're out of
jail.
- And I have some good news. I
got us some money.
- What do you mean?
- Getting out of here, going to
San Francisco like we talked
about. Now we can afford it.
- How much you get?
- You'll see.
- Come on, [SOUNDS LIKE] Sal,
how much?
- I'll tell you after School.
It's going to be great.
- Right.
♪♪♪
Can I help you?
- Yes you can. I have something
to sell.
These wouldn't
be stolen would they?
- My grandmother gave them to
me.
- All right, if you say so.
- James Powell and his wife had
a little girl. And they moved
into a house in Solvang.
He was studying architecture and
she wanted to be a school
teacher.
When Sally was nine months old
they were walking along Pacific
Coast Highway.
A drunk driver jumped the curb.
James's back was broken in three
places.
His wife was killed. She was no
older than you.
- You're 18?
I am.
I'll say, uh, 200 bucks.
-[Kay] James tried to raise
Sally for over a year by himself
with a broken back.
But this letter in the file, to
whom it may concern.
I cannot give Sally what she
deserves and I want her to have
the best life possible.
Maybe we'll meet again when she
is mature enough to forgive an
old man
for not measuring up when he was
young. Until then, make sure
she knows
how much her dad loves
her. Sincerely, James T.
Powell, Junior.
- Poor man.
- Do you have any idea how
important it would be for Sally
to know that her dad cares?
- Every child needs to know
that.
- 200 bucks.
- I couldn't come up
with anything, on
her mother, her,
her name appears on the birth
certificate but I, I can't
read it.
- Is it Margaret or Marjorie.
- No telling and it's the only
place her name appears. It's
not on any of the other forms.
- Well, that's because she was
already dead when the foster
home proceedings began.
Here's a cemetery plot. Uh, Mr.
and Mrs. James T. Powell,
Junior, Rose Hills Cemetery.
It's right here in San Diego.
Bet you'd find the mother there.
- Oh, it's the dad
who I'm interested in.
- You think he's still around?
- I've already checked the
phone book and gone online but
there's no local listing.
Next stops the county clerk.
I'm going to look for a
business license.
Maybe he opened shop as an
architect.
- Maybe James Powell doesn't
want to be reunited with
his daughter.
You ever think about that?
- They're family. They belong
together.
- 200 bucks is not nearly
enough.
- No it's not.
Just take a little more, she's
rich, she won't even miss it.
This is our chance to get out.
No more foster homes, no more
people taking us in so
they can get another government
check.
Come on, Sal, it's the only way
we'll get out of here.
- Powell, Powell, Powell. Here
we go. What'd you say his first
name was?
- James.
- James T. Junior?
- Yes.
- So what's the story on this,
just wait till later?
- Don't push me, okay?
- Sure, whenever you're ready.
But sooner's better.
- You Sally?
- Yeah, who are you?
- Danny Katsu.
- The shrink's kid?
- Yeah. [LAUGH] My dad told me
about you.
- Yeah, I'll bet. You go to Sun
Briar?
- Uh huh.
- How come I've never seen you
there?
- Something tells me we run in
different crowds. [LAUGH]
- So, what do you do for fun?
- I got a chess set in the
backyard.
- Do the cops know? [LAUGH]
- [overheard] Those'll grow good
in your backyard. I think so,
yeah.
Uh huh, yeah, so, um, I don't
know I thought just different
colors. Yellow instead of...
Yeah.
You do such a good job.
- That's a black Australian
tree fern. Pulled it off the
truck this morning.
- Oh, I don't need anything
really. I was just looking.
- Well, if you have any
questions, just let me know,
bye.
- Actually, I do have a
questions. I need some work done
at my house, some landscaping.
Could you help me with that?
- Absolutely.
Why don't you step into
my office and tell me about
your property.
Excuse the mess.
- That's okay.
- I've only been meaning to
clean it up for
about ten years now. [LAUGH]
I'm Jim, I'm sorry, what's
your name?
- Woodbury, Katherine Woodbury.
- Why does that sound familiar?
- I'm a judge.
- That's right, you're
tough.
- Only on the bad guys.
- Well, I'll make sure I watch
my step.
Okay so, um, what kind of place
you have judge?
- Kay, please. I have a Spanish
style home in Coronado.
- Well, it's beautiful there.
I, I do a lot of work in that
area.
- I thought maybe I could add
some boxwoods along my property
line.
- Boxwoods are great. They grow
kind of thick.
You'd be walling yourself off
from the rest of the world if
that's what you want.
- Maybe not.
- Well, let's see if I got some
to show you.
- Checkmate.
- Hey, you're pretty good.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but most girls don't really get
chess. [LAUGH]
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It's not the most feminine
game. I mean,
seems to be more compelling for
guys who like to smoke pipes.
- One of my foster parents
taught me. And for your
information,
I prefer generic cigarettes to a
pipe. [LAUGH]
- How was that, living in a
foster home?
- It's actually okay. Once you
get used to it.
Though you never do get
comfortable. Never know when
it's going to be time to leave.
- It must be hard.
- Yeah, I guess, but you get
by, you know.
Sit here and dwell on how
difficult my life is.
But it won't really make any
difference so, you know, you
just go with it.
So, are you up for another game
or are you tired of losing to a
girl? [LAUGH]
- Bring it on. You are
going down. [LAUGH]
- I'll call you in a day or
two. I just need a little time
to picture all the changes.
- No problem, you take your
time.
- Thank you for your help. I
like your ideas very much.
- Okay, see you later.
- You bet ya.
- There's something you need
to see.
They played four games.
She's won three.
- Ah.
- Danny's the president of the
chess club and she beat him.
- Morning.
- Good morning. You stayed
awfully late at the Katsu's last
night.
- Danny said I couldn't leave
until he beat me two games
in a row.
I finally had to let him win.
- How would you like to be my
date to a party tonight?
- What kind of party?
- It's a nice one. You'll
need a new dress.
- I don't have any dresses.
- That's okay, we'll go
shopping.
- Well.
- Is this what you're looking
for?
- You went through my stuff?
- It was sticking out, staring
at me. I don't know under what
circumstances that came off
but you can probably imagine how
I might feel about that sort
of thing.
- And I bet you're going to
tell me, aren't you?
- It's your body, Sally, you're
a big girl and I'm not your
mother.
[doorbell chimes]
All actions have consequences.
You know?
- Yeah, I get it, okay?
- Oh my...
- What?
- It's nothing, it's nobody.
- Nobody rang the bell. You're
so nervous. Wouldn't be a guy
by any chance would it?
- Yeah, as a matter of fact.
- Good morning.
- Uh, I know it's early but I
thought I'd come by
and take a look at your
backyard and try and come
up with some ideas.
- Sure, no problem, come on in.
- Thank you.
- Sally, this is Jim. He's
going to be doing some
landscaping work for me.
- Sally. I've always loved that
name.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too. I
guess.
- So how many children do you
have?
- Sally's not my daughter.
She's a friend.
- Kay doesn't have any
children. She's single.
- Divorced, actually.
- Um, I'm just going to be out
back taking some measurements if
that's okay.
- Oh, sure, take as long as
you'd like. Uh, Sally and I were
just [LAUGH] going shopping.
- You guys have a good time.
- Kay has a boyfriend.
- Shut up, I do not.
Ah, what do you think?
What do you think?
- Ew.
- What?
- Come on Kay, I'm only 16.
I'm not ready to look like you
yet.
Let's go over there.
So, what do you think?
- Uh, it's a party, Sally, not
a rock concert.
- Go ahead, try it on.
- Oh, no thank you, I don't
think it's me.
- It's an original Meldoney.
My boyfriend gave me one
for Christmas.
- Okay.
- Can't keep them in stock.
- Huh. I like it.
Perfect.
- They're going to love that
down at the courthouse. No,
don't, it looks good..
- Really?
- Yeah, you should get it.
- No.
- Come on, Kay, when was the
last time you bought yourself
something fun?
You know, you actually look kind
of cool in that jacket.
- Thanks, I think.
- What?
- Well, are you saying that I
wasn't cool before the jacket?
- Well.
- Well what?
- No, you just, you look more
relaxed. It's a good thing.
- Thank you then.
[PHONE RINGS]
Excuse me. Hello. Hi, mom.
No, no, I'm shopping. It's
okay. You guys are working this
from every angle aren't you?
Please, please, don't start with
me. Okay, I'll, I'll tell Davis
that dad isn't feeling
well. Bye. Can't believe it.
- What?
- My ex husband invited my
parents to his party tonight.
- So?
- [LAUGH] He knows that my dad
and I aren't speaking.
- Why aren't you speaking to
your dad?
- Long story.
- Come on.
- Six months ago his firm filed
a wrongful death suit against
the power company.
Some problems developed and they
needed time to redirect the
case.
So he approached me, exparte,
that means outside the courtroom
and asked me for a favor, a
delay.
- And did you give it to him?
- I told him if he ever
approached me again,
I'd report him to the
California Bar Association.
What he asked about was
inappropriate, unethical and
illegal.
- One little favor.
- This wasn't just a, a
mistake, it was a crime.
- Did he apologize?
- He tried to.
- Did anyone get hurt?
- No.
- Well, then, forget it, he's
your dad.
- It's not that simple.
- Sure it is. You'd rather be
right than be with your parents.
You've got your priorities all
screwed up.
- My priorities are fine.
- Come on, being right all the
time gets lonely. Admit it.
- I do not have to be right all
the time.
- You mean like now? Cut people
some slack, you take this judge
thing way too seriously.
- Sally?
- Yeah?
- Do you know much about your
birth parents?
- No. And I don't want to.
- Well, aren't you just a
little bit curious?
- I don't want to talk about
this, okay, I told you that
before.
- Well, there may be more to
the story than you know.
Maybe your mom and dad hated to
give you up. Maybe they didn't
have any other choice.
- I mean it.
- All right, look, I won't
bring it up again, I promise.
I'm sorry.
- I want to do my own hair.
- And we should get ready. What
do you think?
- You're going to wear that?
- Basic black, it's classic.
- Yeah, but you wear black,
like, every day to work. Don't
you have anything jazzier?
- [LAUGH] Jazzy is not my
style.
- Come on, Kay, this is your ex
husband's party. You have to
look hot.
- Wait a minute, I haven't
accessorized yet.
That's odd. Could have sworn
I put my grandmother's
brooch in here.
- Yeah, well, you know, you
don't want to wear anything your
grandmother gave you.
You know, you need something
flashy. Trust me, that dress
needs it.
- Yeah.
- Well, I'm going to get ready
myself.
- You look gorgeous.
- No.
- No, I mean it, Sally. You're
a beautiful young woman.
- What are you doing here?
- Just checking in, I hadn't
heard from you yet.
[MAKES NOISE] Man, that dress,
it's...
- You have to go.
- Why, where are you off to?
- I'll tell you later, please
just go.
- Did you get us more stuff?
- Just get out of here, please.
- What's your problem? What
happens next week or next month
or she gets tired of you, you
end up in another foster home.
- I can't believe you.
- I'm the one who's been with
you through all these years.
- Not.
- What are you doing? Stop it.
Are you all right?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Who is that creep?
- Just a friend.
- Oh, nice to see you.
- Good evening.
- Excuse me, be right back.
- A really big house.
- Oh. Davis. Good to see you.
- Thank you.
- Happy to be here.
- Oh, it's good to see you. And
who is this?
- This is Sally Powell. Sally,
this is...
- Davis Woodbury. Your
honor's favorite ex husband.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yeah, very nice to meet you.
Sally are you hungry?
I've got a ton of food out here
and attack it. There's so
much.
You know, my source at
the courthouse told me that
you'd taken custody of her, I
don't believe it.
- Oh, don't give me any grief,
Davis, not after your little
reunion plot with my parents.
- Kay, look, I know what I said
in your chambers.
Uh, Sally is on your docket.
You're her judge.
Have you thought through this?
- I'm a judge half the time.
The other time I'm a private
citizen.
I can adopt a child any time I
want.
- Well, adopt.
- Oh, you know what I mean.
- Whoa, whoa, [STAMMERS] wait,
wait, wait. This coming from a
woman who
I married who never wanted to
have a child.
Suddenly is thinking about
adopting a teenage girl?
- Davis, did you invite me here
for a lecture or a party?
- I'm sorry.
- Champagne?
- I'm, I'm concerned.
- Well, I appreciate that but,
uh, I know what I'm doing.
- If you say so. Would you like
something to drink?
- Love it.
- All right.
- Hope I'm not interrupting.
- Oh, no, no, not at all. Kay,
I'd like you to meet the future
Mrs. Davis Woodbury.
- Monica Tejada. It's a real
pleasure to meet you, Judge
Woodbury.
- Uh, call me Kay please.
- I want to thank you so much
for coming tonight. I know it
means an awful lot to Davis.
- In the meantime,
if you need any tips on how
to handle Davis, I kept
extensive notes.
- Well, I've kept quite a diary
going myself.
- [LAUGH] He's a handful,
that's for sure.
But, hang in
there, he's worth it.
- Oh, my. I'm sorry.
- Don't worry about it, it's
all right.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- You're not fine at all,
Sally.
- How do you know my name?
- I know quite a bit about you.
- Are you a friend of Kay's?
- I like Kay very much. She's a
good person.
You're a good
person, too, Sally.
- No I'm not.
I took something that wasn't
mine. It belonged to Kay.
- Sally, look at me.
You are a kind and
wonderful person.
You're just afraid and there's
no reason to be afraid.
- I know who you are.
- I'm someone who cares about
you very much.
- I don't believe it. You're
here.
- I've always been with you.
You know that.
- But now I can see you.
- Everything's going to be
better now, isn't it?
Everything's going to change.
- You're right. Everything will
change. And everything will get
better if you let it.
But you have to open your heart,
Sally. You have to learn to
forgive.
'Cause if you trust and forgive,
you will be happy.
- I can do that. If you stay
here with me.
- I will never leave you. I
promise. I promise.
- Sally? Who were you talking
to?
- She was just right here.
- Are you all right?
- I'm a little dizzy.
- Yeah, I can smell how dizzy
you are. Let's go. Let me help
you.
- [PHONE RINGS] Hello.
- Kay
- Mom? What, what is it? What's
wrong?
- I'm at the hospital with your
father. He's had a heart attac.
- I'm on my way.
Sit here.
- Oh, Katherine, good.
- How is he?
- We don't know yet. And
we're waiting for the test
results.
Honey, who's that?
- Sally.
- Who?
- She's a foster child.
- Who's foster child?
- Mine. When do we get the test
results?
- The, the doctor says we might
have to wait a couple of hours.
- Hi.
- Oh boy. I really must be sick
if you're here.
- You stop that. You're going
to be perfectly fine.
- [LAUGH] Is that your
diagnosis? Or the doctor?
- Just rest. Just, please,
that's all you have to do. Just
rest.
- Thanks for coming, Katy girl.
Are, are you still angry with
me?
- Come on, dad.
- Kate, I made a mistake. But I
never meant to hurt you. I just
didn't think.
I'll make it up to you. I love
you, Katy.
- Just rest, okay. And we'll
talk about all of this
later, I promise.
Tell you what, we'll go to
dinner, just the two of us,
we'll go to that, uh, the
Italian restaurant
that you love, uh...
- Manzanetti.
- That's it. You and I will
have dinner at Manzanetti's, my
treat.
- And we'll talk.
- We've given him all the usual
tests and everything's fine.
But just in case we'd like to
keep him here for observation.
- Observation.
- We just want to be on the
safe side. Really you have
nothing to worry about.
Your father's as strong as an
ox. He isn't going anywhere.
- Is there anything we need to
be doing?
- Yes. You should go home and
get some rest.
- Thank you doctor.
- Don't let him do too much
too fast. You know how he gets.
- Don't worry, I'll take care
of him. Uh, what are you going
to do about this one?
- Uh, I'm not sure. I think she
stole gram's brooch.
- What?
- It's not where I put it and
there's some other things
missing, too.
- Have you confronted her?
- No. Not yet.
- Honey, are you sure you
really want to do this?
- I don't know. I, I don't know
what I want to do at this point.
Mom, I'm, I'm sorry I stayed
angry for so long.
- Don't apologize.
- No, I shouldn't have been
so pig headed about it.
- You're here now. That's all
that matters.
- You're right. [LAUGH]
- I'm always right.
- Do you have any aspirin?
- The cabinet by the stove. I
didn't expect to see you up
right so soon.
- I promised Danny Katsu I'd go
roller skating with him.
- How do you feel?
- Sick to my stomach with a
killer headache.
- Good.
- I screwed up, didn't I?
- Yep, you did.
- I'm sorry. I guess I was just
nervous.
- Well, at least you learned a
lesson.
[knocking]
- Morning, ready to roll?
- In a sec.
- Are you sure you're up to
this?
- I could use some fresh air.
- Call me if you're going to
be late.
- Thanks, bye.
- See you later.
[doorbell chimes]
- Jim.
- Hi.
- I'm guessing you didn't get
my message. I just said I'd stop
by with some drawings today.
- I'm sorry, things
have been kind of hectic and I
haven't even checked my machine.
- Oh, well, [LAUGH] we can do
this another time.
- No, no, no, no. Come on in.
It's fine.
Would you, uh, like some coffee
or something?
- Oh, no, no, thank you. I'm
okay. I mean, if this isn't a
good time, I can come back.
- No, I'm just tired. I was at
the hospital all night. My
father's ill.
- Well, I hope he's okay.
- Yeah, he's, he's holding his
own. You know what? I'm glad
you're here.
[LAUGH] How did you get into
landscaping?
- Actually I wanted to be an
architect. But I had an accident
and I had to leave school.
Well, I had this buddy that was
starting a landscaping project
and I just fell in love with it.
You know, its like life,
you nurture some
things, you ignore the others.
It's all about choices, right?
- Yeah, [LAUGH] it's funny you
say that about choices.
Because I made a big one
recently. And it's really turned
out great.
You know Sally?
- Yeah, the girl that's living
with you, right?
- Well, actually, she's a
foster child and she's really
smart and terrific.
Which isn't to say that she
doesn't have problems because
we all do.
[LAUGH] You know, I'm, [LAUGH]
I'm rambling. I'm sorry.
But, the poor kid's really been
through a lot, kind of kicked
from pillar to post.
She's never known what it's like
to have a real family.
- That's a shame.
- Yeah, yeah it is because
there's something really
special about her.
Before I met her, I, I thought I
had the answer to everything.
But she's made me question
myself and I think that's good.
- Definitely. Okay, here we go.
- I, I give up. I'm tired and
confused and
I don't know any other way to
do this but just tell you.
- Tell me what, Kay?
- Sally's not just a foster
child. She's your daughter.
- What?
- It's true. She's your little
girl.
She had no place to go so I took
her in and then I found out that
you were her father.
I'm sorry, I know this must be a
shock.
- Does she know? [STAMMERS]
Does she know who I am?
- No, she has no idea.
- Oh, I, I, I have to go. Okay.
- I'm serious, you did really
well for a beginner. [LAUGH]
- Thanks, it was fun.
- Yeah. It was. So, um, you
want to play chess a little
later?
- Sure.
Kay, I'm back in one
piece.
- You must have been curious.
You must have thought about her.
- Of course I thought about
her.
- Well, then, why didn't you
try to find her?
- Because it doesn't matter,
she already hates me.
- How could she hate you, she
doesn't even know you.
- Kay, what do you want me to
do, march in there with
16 years worth of birthday
presents and beg for
forgiveness?
- Of course not.
- Look, I failed her. Okay, I
gave up my own flesh and blood
because I was scared and weak.
- No one's judging you.
- Look, I don't care what
anybody else thinks about me, I
know what I did was wrong.
- Give her a chance. Sally's a
terrific kid. You'll be proud of
her. I know.
- You just don't get it, do
you?
- Yes, I do. I know you made a
mistake but you're lucky.
Because you have a chance to
correct it. Jim,
you have a remarkable daughter
who needs a father.
She deserves a second chance and
so do you.
- Kay, where are you?
- What must she think of me?
- Oh my God.
You liar.
- I can't, I, I can't do it.
Kay, I can't fix what's wrong
with her.
I mean, I wouldn't know where
to start.
- What's wrong with her is she
doesn't have a dad around to
talk to.
- It's too late, okay? Come on,
just happens.
- She's your
daughter, she's your
responsibility.
- You had no right.
- Sally.
- What's going on? Why'd you
want to meet me here?
[LAUGH]
San Francisco, open your golden
gates.
- Let's just get out of here,
now.
- Na uh, you stay here.
You're a minor, remember.
[making call]
- Come on, come on. Pick up.
- [phone ringing] Put it all in
the bag.
Now.
Don't even think about it.
All right, all right. All right,
all right, hey.
[STAMMERS] That's all I got,
that's it, that's it.
All I got, that's all I got.
That's all I got, all right?
- All right.
- Oh my God, what did you do?
- We needed some money, and I
got us some.
- Did you hurt anyone?
- GO He's got a gun
- Sally.
Did you get a license
number?
- Yeah, I got it.
- Well, then call the police.
- You're an idiot. What were
thinking?
- Ow. Stop it, I
can't see.
- You're crazy. Are you out
of your mind? You got to get me
out of here please.
You're driving like a maniac.
- [OVERLAPPING] God, would you
calm down?
- Get me out of this car, let
me out right now.
- [OVERLAPPING] Sally, calm
down.
- I want out of this car now.
- Okay.
- Get me out of this car right
now.
- What is wrong with you?
- I never want to see you again.
- I just did this for us.
Here, here, have a nice life.
Look, I'm out of here.
- We'll let you know as soon
as we hear anything.
If you give me your cell phone
number then, uh, I'll call you
right away.
- Kay.
- Excuse me. Oh, thank God.
Are you all right? He
didn't hurt you.
- No. But he took all the money
from your jewelry.
- Oh, forget the jewelry,
it's okay.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not, I stole your
stuff.
- You stole it because you were
angry with me and you had every
right to be.
What I did was wrong. I should
have told you about your father.
I'm so sorry, Sally.
- He left, didn't he?
- He's scared. People run when
they're scared.
- Do you think he's going to be
back?
- I don't know.
- Pardon me, judge. Is
everything okay here?
- Yeah.
- She's fine officer. Thank
you.
- I'll need to talk to you when
you're done.
- Am I going back to jail?
- Oh, don't worry about it.
We'll take care of it.
- Thank you.
What's wrong with me, Kay?
- There's nothing wrong with
you.
- Yes, there is.
- No, there's not.
- No matter where I go or what
I do, I always end up alone.
I don't fit in anywhere.
- Oh, that's not
true. You fit just perfectly
right here.
- You're coming aren't you?
- Are you sure?
- Absolutely. She'll want to
see you, too.
- Kay. Over here.
Hey, mom, it's me.
Oh, sorry I didn't come to
see you sooner,
but, uh, now that I know where
you are, I'll come a lot more
often.
I promise. I'm doing a lot
better, just like you said I
would.
And Kay's taking really good
care of me.
I think about you
all the time, mom.
- It's okay.
- Kay.
♪♪♪