Cut it out, Nicky.
My name's Nicole, Birdbrain.
My name's Ian, Nicky so Icky.
Hey, do that again and your
name's going to be Deceased.
I'm so scared.
You're so weird.
Hey, Birdbrain, why do you have
all this stuff anyway?
I got to have something to do
out in the sticks.
Grandma has a radio.
She has all this other stuff
too.
Besides, I'm sure you'll hang
out great with the cows.
You smell the same, anyways.
Ha, ha, ha.
This is so unfair.
I'm getting shipped out
to Grandma's, and you get to
stay here all summer,
hanging out with your
smelly friends.
I am not hanging out.
I have a job now.
I'm a productive member
of society.
I have responsibilities.
But hey, we better get going.
Your bus leaves at 12:25.
Okay.
Hey.
I'm going to be busy too.
I'm not going to be around here
much.
Mom and Dad deserve
this vacation.
It'll be like
a second honeymoon for them.
They don't want us
in Hawaii with them.
At least I can take
my man, Bentley.
That dog of yours
is really a freak.
No freakier
than your boyfriend.
Not in my car.
Come on.
How you doing?
Ah. Very nice.
Great.
Hey, watch the curb here there.
I'm only going to be a...
few minutes, babe, all right.
So I want you to keep it
up front, all right.
Just keep it up front.
Come in.
I'm already in.
Your wit astounds me but
with your problems I wouldn't
be in a joking mood, Jimmy.
What can I say?
Your sunshiny-like face
makes me giggle
like a school girl.
So what do you think
about it?
Well, I--geez, I don't know.
I can't believe how broke I am.
Yes, you're absolutely
busted.
All the money your daddy
gave you is gone.
Your trust fund is empty.
Wow.
Empty like that adorable
little face of yours.
You know,
I got to tell you something.
I know that you're enjoying
this, okay?
Because you helped me
spend my money.
Lawyer's fees aren't cheap.
Hey, look, I got to tell you.
As a lawyer, you know,
your prices are reasonable,
but as my girlfriend, uh--
And worth it.
I have a plan.
Well, let's hear it.
You have your uncle's house
in Wisconsin.
What, the chauffeur, he died?
No.
Camille, come on,
we've been through this like
a thousand times, all right?
My uncle's will states that
we can't touch the place
until the chauffeur dies.
No.
Offing Mr. Lyle is not
the plan, Jimmy.
Why not?
Come on.
The guy's old.
He could have a--
Jimmy.
Listen.
Yes, the will gave Mr. Lyle
the house as long as he's alive,
if he pays the property taxes,
and lucky for you, the little
pension your uncle gave him
isn't enough.
So it's ours.
Not quite.
I've requested a local judge
to, uh, permit sale
of the property.
It will go up for auction
and you could stand to make
quite a chunk of change.
After my fee, that is.
Naturally.
And then I'll be broke again.
Don't worry.
I have a feeling there's more
than a house to cash in on.
Oh, see, I like it
when you say cash.
Pay attention, or you won't
be getting any more cash.
I gather you've heard
rumors about the money
your uncle may have hidden away?
Uh, yeah, but I--I thought
it was all baloney.
No, I have a hunch it's more
than just lunch meat, my dear,
but if it does exists,
then the chauffeur never
found it, or else
he would have--
He would have paid the taxes.
Ooh, look at that.
You've been thinking again.
Now it seems a shame
to turn the property over
to strangers with a treasure
buried in the backyard.
You know where it's buried?
What do I look like?
A gypsy fortune teller?
You're gonna have to dig for it.
Go alone.
Try to blend in.
If you can blend in.
Oh, and Jimmy, if you get
in trouble, I don't know you.
What are you talking about?
Discretion's my middle name.
Yeah.
Oh, have that moved.
Ugh.
No!
Ow!
Jimmy!
No way was I going to
let you ride in the luggage
compartment, my man.
Hey, city slicker.
Are you smelling those cows?
Yes, I do.
Well, get over here.
Get over here and give
your grandma a kiss.
Come on.
As soon as I
get everything in here.
That'll be the day.
Think we can get
all that stuff in here?
If we're lucky.
Maybe I should have brought
a horse trailer.
What do you think?
Yes, I do.
And there's that shaggy dog.
Is he coming?
Yes, he is.
Eh, come on, boy.
Come on, shaggy dog.
Come on.
Over here, boy.
Well, give your old grandma
a kiss.
Come on.
Ooh, what do I feel there?
Whiskers?
You better stop your growing up.
I'm feeling ancient.
Let me look at you.
Oh, my boy, you better
watch it.
You're going to turn into
a very handsome guy.
Oh, I'm sorry, kiddo.
Listen, are you hungry?
Is it dinner time?
Uh...
Oh.
Would you like a malted milk?
Well, we don't have any
of those Haagen Daagen shops
here but would
a Dairy Queen do?
Okay, here we go.
Come on, come on.
Ooh.
Whoa!
Gosh darn city slickers!
Oh, there.
Ah ha.
I am so happy you are going to
spend a whole summer with me.
In a couple of weeks
we're going to have our big
Fourth of July celebration.
Oh, you can enter
the hula hoop marathon.
Oh, it's going to be such fun.
You do pretty good, I'm sure.
That's my boy.
Give me a hug.
I was beginning to think you'd
gotten too old to have fun.
Okay?
Right.
Come on.
Come on, Bentley boy.
All right.
Look what you did.
I'm sorry.
Oh my gosh.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Applegate.
Hello, Miss Davies.
Oops.
I'm sorry.
Uh, bad throw, huh?
The rambler's looking spiff,
Ms. Applegate.
Oh, thank you very much.
Here's your Frisbee.
I got to go.
I'll see you.
Mm, bye.
Oh, darn, I wanted to introduce
you to her, but I couldn't
remember the recall device
I use to remember her name.
She's the Davies girl,
and they moved here
about two years ago,
and they live at three doors
down from me.
Father is a dentist, I think.
Or is it a plumber...hmm.
I don't know, but throwing
a Frisbee on a bike is stupid.
Do you like playing with
those flying saucers?
I learned from the old hippy
himself.
Your dad loved those things.
He would always leave his
homework, but he'd never forget
his brisbee.
Frisbee.
Frisbee, bisbee, Frisbee.
Man, whatever.
How are they anyway?
Who, my parents?
Yeah.
They're on their way
to Hawaii.
We're going to Hawaii
next year, you and me.
Ooh, that sound.
Sorry.
Oh, no, it just makes me
melancholy.
Listen, let's forget
about dinner, huh?
Let's go have another malt.
Oh, I wish I could remember
that girl's name.
Come on, boy.
I do like that dog,
but I don't know about that toy.
Let's go.
Oh.
Oops.
Juliette.
What?
But soft, what light
through yonder window breaks?
It is the east,
but Juliette is the sun.
Shakespeare.
That was my memory trick.
She's up at the crack of dawn
every morning with
her paper route.
Juliette Davies.
She can work on her aim.
Well, she usually hits
what she's aiming for.
She's on the baseball team.
Softball?
No, no, she plays
with the boys.
Yeah, got a blistering fastball.
Demoralizes her.
Come on.
Minute, just a minute.
Here you go, Grandma.
Thank you, open the door.
Okay.
Oh, fleas, we better give him
a flea bath.
Yeah, come on. Come on.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
You can do it.
All right.
Come on, one more,
one more, one more.
Let's do it.
Strike two.
Come on, come on.
Right here.
Yeah, let's do it, let's do it.
Yeah, go, go, go.
Strike three, you're out.
Come on.
Watch the ball, watch the ball.
Come on, Ricky.
Come on, Ricky, come on.
Thanks.
You want some cereal?
Got some fresh berries.
Sure.
Ooh.
Ow.
Hi.
Practicing for the Fourth
of July?
Wasn't expecting you.
I wasn't beaned
by a flying object.
Sorry about that.
They only seem to get away
from me when you're around.
May I?
It's all in the hips, see?
Like this.
Nah.
I'm not that interested.
You're not having much fun
here, are you?
It's all right.
Yeah, sure.
Well, look.
My name is Jules.
Ian.
Nice dog.
Nasty toy.
His name is Bentley.
The dog, that is.
Not the toy.
Anyways, I need a substitute
for my paper route.
My family's going camping
this weekend.
My regular sub's
at a big swim meet.
Sure.
You will?
Just like that?
I need you Saturday and Sunday.
Meet me in front of my house,
the brick one at 6:15,
and I'll show you the route.
Okay.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Hey.
Did you win your game?
Of course.
Two to nothing.
You don't want to hit
the geraniums here.
And don't fire low on the next
one or it goes under the porch.
Are you remembering this?
Yeah, yeah, no problem.
♪
I'd be careful with this one
if I were you,
especially with the vases.
Why? What'll happen?
I've never wanted
to find out.
You coming?
So what's with the big house?
You mean the haunted one?
Haunted? Yeah, right.
Do I care if you believe me?
There's a crazy old man
who lives there.
His name is Lyle.
He was a bodyguard
for Tony Murano,
a Chicago Mafia boss
who used to live there
until he got gunned down
in cold blood.
Lyle took a bullet in his head
and they could never get it out.
He's been crazy ever since.
He lives there,
and no one ever sees him.
Yeah, right.
If he never goes out,
how does he eat?
I never said
he never went out.
I said no one ever sees him.
Oh.
And there's also supposed
to be this huge treasure
hidden somewhere in the house.
Mafia blood money.
Guarded by the ghost
of Tony Murano,
and on moonless nights,
people have seen this
flickering candle moving behind
the curtains of the upstairs,
and then there's a wailing moan
that makes your hair
stand up on end.
Golly.
It's fun to have the sounds
of life around this place
again, but I almost dropped
my teeth in the toilet.
Sorry.
Oh, that's all right.
Come on in.
Let's have some breakfast
and you can tell me about it.
Oh, thank you, but I can't.
We're leaving in a half an hour
and I have to pack.
Oh, okay.
Okay, see ya.
See ya.
Watch out for Crazy Lyle.
I'll tell him you said hi.
Crazy Lyle?
Yeah.
The old guy in the mansion.
She says he's totally crazed.
Franklin Lyle?
You know him?
Come on.
Have some breakfast.
I've got some fresh fruit
for you.
Come on.
Yes!
Ah, geez.
That ain't fair.
Bentley, come.
Ah, my man.
What are you doing to me,
my man?
Bentley, come here, boy.
Ow.
What?
So what kind of car was it?
I don't know,
was big and old.
Big and old? That's it?
Lots of chrome, and I was
facing death by whip.
I wasn't into the car.
Cherry shape?
What?
You know. Perfect shape,
like new.
I think so.
But I didn't get much of a look
before my man here barked.
I have to get into
that garage.
It's an old car.
What do you care?
Cars are cool.
Old cars are the coolest.
You don't want to do this.
Why not?
He's going to be
really upset.
Why?
Well, there's something
I sort of kind of left out.
Remember the vase
you told me about?
Well, I broke it.
Perfect, we'll go apologize.
I tried.
He wouldn't answer the door.
Well then, we'll volunteer
to fix it.
I wouldn't recommend that.
It's my paper route.
I have to, I'm responsible.
Where exactly are you from?
Chicago, why?
Not the 'burbs?
No. How'd you know?
Uh, I take it coming out here
for the summer wasn't your idea.
Not really.
My parents had some idea
it would be some big adventure.
Maybe they were right.
1998 Corvette convertible.
Nice car.
What's it doing here?
Disturbing the peace.
Come on.
You're such a show off.
Maybe we should think
about this.
Maybe make a plan or call
the police first.
Are you chicken?
I'm not chicken, okay?
We have Bentley.
Come here, boy.
He's just scared.
Go ahead.
Go ahead what?
You broke the vase.
You should be the one.
All right.
Itchy?
What's the worst
that can happen?
You selling cookies, boy?
I'm the--was the paper boy--
paper girl--paper girl's
boy helper.
What--what he's trying to
say, sir, is that he broke
your vase yesterday
with the newspaper,
and we've come to help you
fix it, or pay for it,
or whatever.
The vase is broken.
You can't fix it.
Well then, we'll pay for it.
What's to pay for?
On second thought, you will pay.
What's your name, boy?
Mickian--I mean, Mickian.
Ian McKinzie.
I think you know my grandma?
Mimian.
Mimimara.
Mimi McKinzie.
McKinzie?
Yeah.
I don't know her.
Never heard of her.
Her maiden name, Ian.
Applegate.
Pamela Applegate?
Well, why Mimi?
When I was little,
I couldn't say “grandma ”.
Ah, that stands to reason.
All right, then what do you
want to do?
Well, um, do you need any
work done around the house?
Mow the lawn?
Clean the garage?
Yes...yes you come back
tomorrow morning.
Okay, great, see you then.
Oh, and my name's Juliette.
You really want to see that
car, don't you?
♪
I'm sorry, okay?
I apologize.
I was wrong.
Hi.
Glenn Miller.
Who?
I had a hankering for some
Glenn Miller, but my partner
can't lead a lick.
Come on.
That's pretty good.
Let's go get some lemonade.
I'm going to make you some
fresh asparagus tonight.
Sure was grumpy.
Well, what do you expect
that from--
I meant the old guy, not you.
That can happen
to older people.
Marriage is no antidote
to grumpiness.
He has no family,
and Sally told me that someone
broke his favorite vase
yesterday.
So maybe, just maybe,
he's perturbed about that.
Perturbed and disturbed.
Hoodlums?
Who knows?
It's such an odd thing.
Beautiful old vase.
I mean, it's irreplaceable.
Probably some nut
from Chicago.
Crazy and perturbed, is that
what you think about Mr. Lyle?
Mr. Lyle?
Yes, Franklin Lyle.
I mean, he may seem that way
because he's been holed up
in that old house for 25 years.
I've seen him only a couple
of times in the last few years,
and always from a distance.
But do you know him?
I did.
Once upon a time.
Was he a gangster?
No.
There's no way, he was
Mr. Murano's chauffeur.
Was Mr. Murano a gangster?
I honestly don't know.
The rest of the Muranos
most certainly were.
I mean, they were always
getting shot up
and being put in jail,
but Mr. Franklin always said
that Mr. Murano--
Tony Murano--was a jeweler,
until they disappeared,
you know?
Who disappeared?
Both of them.
They dropped off the face
of the earth for the better
part of a year.
Where did they go?
I don't know.
They went--they were hiding.
I mean, it was--
there was a--you know,
there was a gang war.
So Tony wasn't gunned down
in cold blood?
No, no, heavens, no.
He died peacefully years later.
Mr. Lyle doesn't have
a bullet in his brain?
Honestly, you know,
you two are morbid.
I never heard about it,
if he did.
I never heard anything
like that, that he was
shot in the head.
What did your friend
tell you?
I never heard from him again.
And then I was swept off my feet
by Ian's granddad.
And the rest is life.
So Mr. Lyle must have driven
some pretty cool cars.
I imagine they were cool.
Do you remember what kind
of car your friend drove
Mr. Murano in?
You should ask Mr. Lyle
about the cars.
He'd like that.
Well, maybe next time.
I better go.
I have to pitch at four,
but thanks for lunch.
Have a great game.
Thanks.
Watch that fastball.
Well, the asparagus
was a big hit.
I'm going to make some
for tonight and tomorrow.
Huh? What? Oh.
What's for sale?
The house?
No wonder he's so grumpy.
Hey!
Hey, hey, come here.
Whatever you're selling,
we don't need it.
Are you buying the house?
I'm selling the house,
little girl.
What, you got a million bucks?
Yeah, but I'm saving up
to buy the Milwaukee Brewers.
We're here to do some work
for Mr. Lyle.
And what kind of work
would that be?
Mow the lawn,
clean the garage,
that kind of thing.
Yeah, yeah, I could see that.
I'll tell you what.
Frank--Mr. Lyle--
isn't here right now, okay?
But I'll tell you what.
Why don't we start off
with a little bonus, okay,
right off the bat.
All right?
Okay, here we go, all right?
Now go fix this place up,
and while you're at it,
I want you to keep your eyes
peeled for anything unusual,
okay?
Oh.
I'll be a little more generous.
I'll double it.
Huh?
Okay.
All right.
All right?
Not bad, huh?
Not bad, right,
for doing nothing.
Don't ever say your good old
Uncle Jimmy didn't look
after you, okay?
What exactly are we
looking for?
Any--ooh.
Anything, you know?
Anything unusual.
A bag, a box.
A--does this dog bite?
Usually not.
Bentley, that's not cool.
Kid, could you call your dog?
He's stepping on my shoes.
He's worried about his shoes?
I'm trying, sir,
but if you'll just bear with me
a minute, though,
I'd like to see if he'll
obey to my commands.
You see, he's going to
obedience school, and they
teach ya to test them regularly.
Please, kid, I--I had a bad
experience with a boxer once.
Bentley, no snuffling.
Now, come on, you bad dog.
Right.
Nice--nice--nice dog, okay.
You keep your eyes peeled,
and if you find anything,
you know, unusual, you bring it
to your Uncle Jimmy, okay?
Because there's plenty more
where this came from, all right?
Plenty more, okay?
And next time,
leave the dog at home.
Ooh, big spender.
You stay there.
Stay.
Wouldn't it be cool if there
really were a Mafia treasure
buried around here someplace?
Yeah.
Obedience school?
Are you serious?
Not at all.
Shouldn't we knock first?
Come on.
Bentley, stay there, okay?
Whoa, this is sweet.
Mr. Lyle?
Mr. Lyle.
Mr. Lyle!
Shh.
What do you mean, "Shh"?
Aren't we trying to find him?
Yeah, but--whoa,
look at those.
There's so much old stuff
in that house, it'll take me
weeks to find anything
without some kind of clue.
You know, I'd love to off
the old guy.
Yeah, I got to tell you,
I can't tear the place apart
with Lyle watching me like some
type of vulture all the time.
Do you have a plan?
I've retained a couple
of kids to poke around for me.
Yeah, Lyle thinks they're doing
yard work.
What, are you crazy?
If they find the cash,
do you think they're going
to give it to you?
Hey, relax, Camille.
They're just stupid kids,
all right?
They find anything interesting,
they'll bring it to
old Uncle Jimmy, all right?
Trust me.
I made it worth their while.
Idiot.
Ouch.
Ugh.
Cool.
Rad.
Come on.
What is it?
Well, looks like an elevator.
Okay.
Let's go.
There you are.
You can trim the garden,
all right?
Whoa, those are old.
And you.
You can mow the lawn.
Whoa, this is older.
This is quaint.
Trade ya.
Sure.
God, these are sharp.
Or not.
Maybe there's some better
tools in the garage.
You mean like a 20-foot long
riding lawn mower
with spoked wheels?
Come on, this is my chance.
Thanks, but I'll stay here
and listen for the death whip.
Okay, just distract him
for me, will ya?
Take care of her, Bentley.
What, she quit already?
I felt sure that she'd--
She, uh, went to get
some newer tools.
She, uh, was looking
for a weed whacker.
Actually, the dog ran in there,
and she ran in after him.
Is there an old car in there
by any chance?
She really likes old cars.
Really.
Are you aware that you have
a 1934 Duesenberg
in mint condition?
Yes.
It's an anniversary edition.
Anniversary edition?
No way.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry, sir.
I didn't mean to be nosey,
I just wanted to see the car.
I understand.
It's perfect.
We have to take her
out for a ride.
No, I only drive at night.
But everyone in town
should see this car.
Well, the Princess is old.
Just like me.
We come from a different age,
you see, we're like dinosaurs.
What's to show off?
Princess?
Yes, Princess Grace
was Mr. Murano's pet name
for this car.
Mr. Murano gave Princess
to you.
Don't you think he wanted
you to enjoy her?
Hmm.
Grandma would get kick out
of seeing this car.
That's a great idea.
Let's take her over to
your grandma's house.
Your grandmother?
Pamela?
Oh, it would be good
to see her again.
And it is a beautiful day out.
Maybe it's time.
Yes.
Maybe it is time.
That's it, it's time.
That's what it is.
It's time.
Of course.
Mademoiselle.
Thank you.
Monsieur.
Come on, Bentley.
Bentley.
He sounds like a butler.
Look at the car.
It's a beauty!
How is your grandmother?
We were friends
a long, long time ago.
Well, she's just as crazy
as ever.
Crazy?
Well, not crazy.
I was just joking.
Ah, she's a fine lady.
She's always danced
to her own music,
but she's a fine lady.
Your grandfather was
a very lucky man.
Say, are you expected home
soon?
Well, yeah, sometime.
My grandma's out shopping.
Oh.
But they can't throw you out.
It's not right.
It's your home.
I don't know what you heard,
but it's my home all right,
but it's not my house.
You see, once the taxes
are paid off the rest
goes to little Jimmy.
That guy back there?
I thought he was just
some real estate dweeb.
What'd you say, dear?
Oh, nothing, sir.
You know, Mr. Lyle,
you're pretty awesome
with that whip.
Uh, how long have you been,
um, cracking one?
Oh, I saw that Indiana fellow
do it in the movies
and I thought it'd be
a good way to scare off
the pigeons.
Pigeons and other birds
like chickens?
What'd you say?
Oh, nothing sir.
Good afternoon, Ms. Pamela.
Afternoon, Franklin.
She is as lovely as ever.
Grace, Grandma.
He calls her Princess Grace.
Oh, yes, Grace.
I knew it was something
like that.
How did you kids get Mr. Lyle
to drive you around
in this beautiful car?
Been a long time, hasn't it?
Indeed it has.
Mr. Lyle drove us around
the lake.
The lake?
He drove us all the way
around the county.
We just took off
on the spur of the moment,
but we should have called you.
I'd like to make amends
by offering you a ride tomorrow.
Thank you, I accept.
Tomorrow, then?
Yes, tomorrow.
Wonderful.
Oh, kids, I'll put your bikes
in the garage, kids.
Bye!
Bye bye.
Bye bye!
See you, Mr. Lyle.
That car was so awesome.
It is awesome.
And he was such a cutie.
A cutie?
Well, I thought he was.
He was so sweet to your grandma,
and he's not a ghoul
as we thought he was.
I'm sorry, but when he cracks
that whip, he's scary.
I heard someone once say that
you shouldn't judge a man
until you've walked a mile
in his shoes--here.
Well, we haven't told you
what's going to happen.
Mr. Lyle can't afford to
pay the taxes, and Jimmy's
going to sell the house
at the sheriff's sale.
And Mr. Lyle's going to have
to sleep in his car.
Oh, don't tell me
all this now.
We'll wait until we get home
and we'll talk all about it,
all right?
All right.
The sale is tomorrow at noon?
On the Fourth of July?
What can we do
with so little time?
Why doesn't he just sell
the car to pay the taxes?
Yeah, he hardly ever drives
it anyway.
The man is a chauffeur.
The car is dear to him.
I mean, I don't know about you,
but when I was young,
being a chauffeur was
an occupation that a man could
be proud of, don't you know?
Maybe we could talk him into
selling the car.
We have to.
We can't let Mr. Lyle
lose his home.
Especially if Jimmy's going
to get the money.
I was wondering when
you two were going to
bring up the treasure.
Oh, come on, Grandma.
You don't really believe in
that stuff, do you?
Yeah, this is the real world.
It's a matter of life and death.
Besides, if there really were
a treasure, wouldn't he have
found it by now?
Mrs. Applegate, you need to
help us talk him into selling
Grace.
The car is just such a part
of Franklin, it would break
my heart.
We'll post her on the web.
Great idea.
Don't worry, Mrs. Applegate.
Everything's going to be okay.
You wouldn't want him
to be homeless, would you?
Yeah, you're right.
I'm just being sentimental.
Thanks for lunch.
Everything was delicious.
Meet me for my route?
Sure.
That girl has charisma.
So, my man.
What are we going to do?
We can't let Mr. Lyle
lose his home.
I mean, that would really
bum Grandma out.
Can't let that happen.
If you were a hidden treasure,
where would you be?
We really got to get you
a new toy, don't we?
Someone wants to talk to you.
Thanks.
Goodnight.
It's a girl.
Jules?
Who's Jules?
Oh, it's you, Icky.
You got a girlfriend already?
Guess those cows really do
like you.
Yeah, right.
So, do you miss me so bad?
Yeah, so bad,
I sold all your stuff
and I'm renting out your room.
Ha ha ha.
So, how are Mom and Dad?
I just got a postcard
from them, they're doing great.
Cool.
Hey, Birdbrain.
Huh?
I miss you.
And that freak dog of yours.
Hi.
Thanks, Jules.
Thanks!
Looks like it's going to be
a great Fourth of July parade
this year.
Looks like it.
Hi, kids.
Let's get our bikes
and come back later.
Yeah.
Hey.
Look at that.
What's he doing?
I don't know.
Let's ask Mr. Lyle.
Should we call the police
first?
Why, what are you thinking?
Nothing,
but it's not even seven.
Where would he be so early?
Do you think Jimmy's
burying him in the yard?
I never said that.
That's what you were
thinking.
Okay, I was.
So were you.
Old junk.
Yeah, look, I'm telling you.
I dug up the entire backyard.
Camille, the money's not here,
all right?
I hope you're being careful.
What are you talking about?
Pussycat, you know me.
I'm Mr. Careful.
Oh!
Ugh.
Like you were Mr. Careful
with your money.
Do I have to hear about that
for the rest of my life?
Camille?
Oh, come on.
I've looked all over the place.
I tried that.
Hey, hey.
Hey, Camille, back off.
Come on.
You know something?
What, what?
Camille.
Camille?
You know, I gotta tell you,
this place is like--
it's driving me crazy.
What about the old man?
Hey, you don't worry
about Frank, all right?
The old man is taken care of.
Oh, the kids.
Oh.
I'm telling you, the kids are--
they're driving me crazy.
Those little con artists,
they vanished with my money.
I gotta tell you, I'm tired
of digging in the dirt.
Did you--did you check
the garage?
Look, I turned it inside
and out.
The basement?
It isn't in there.
Look, Camille, can't you like
look into your little
crystal ball or do like
a trance, or do something?
Nervy broad.
Jerk.
Oh no.
What now?
We got to find Mr. Lyle.
Ha, I knew I'd find you
little weasels back here.
Real funny.
Should have seen the looks
on your faces.
Ha Ha Ha.
So, did you find anything
interesting telling
your Uncle Jimmy about?
No, we're just here
delivering papers.
And get our own bikes.
Oh.
Oh, well, I don't think this
partnership is going to work.
Here's your two dollars back.
Wait a minute.
Hey, hey.
This was good faith money.
You offend me.
I'm sorry, but it's better
this way.
No, you offend me,
you offend my family.
And this, nah ah,
can't be forgiven.
Geez, it's only two dollars.
Imma tell you something.
I'm going to give you a little
bit of free advice.
First, you can cease and desist
on the paper route, all right?
'Cause Frank ain't reading
papers no more, okay?
That's right.
And second, you can take
your bikes out of the garage
before they get auctioned,
okay?
And last, I want you
to beat it and I don't
want you to come back, okay?
Bentley?
Where's a Bentley?
Uh, nice dog.
Nice Bentley.
Nice dog, okay?
All right, easy, easy, easy.
Hey, kid, I gotta tell you,
you're gonna push me a little
bit too far with this
dog routine, all right?
Bentley's a very nice dog.
You should see his tricks.
Leave.
Come on, I got nowhere to go.
Ow.
Hey, kid.
That's right.
Gonna have to do something
about that dog.
I told you we should have
called the police.
Let's tell your grandma.
She'll know what to do.
He wasn't anywhere.
Unless he was locked up
somewhere in the house.
Or buried in the yard.
Oh, come on, now.
There's probably some perfectly
sensible explanation.
No.
We heard Jimmy talking
on the phone.
He said the old guy
was taken care of.
Exact words, and he said that
Mr. Lyle wouldn't be needing
his newspapers anymore.
We saw Jimmy digging
in the yard,
like he was burying something.
Or looking for the money.
The money.
Definitely looking for it.
We heard him talking about
that too.
Look.
There he is.
Follow him.
What, who, follow who?
That car.
It's Jimmy.
Oh, heavens.
I can't keep up with him.
He might be the key.
He could lead us to Mr. Lyle.
Well, that's a job
for the sheriff.
Besides, Jimmy is one
of the other Muranos.
He might shoot ya.
I can't see the car.
See, no answer.
Locked.
We better go around the back.
I want to see
what he was digging.
Me too.
It looks just like a grave.
Looks to me like some fool
digging for treasure
without a map.
Bentley's found something.
I don't think one
of the other Muranos would be
burying a body in the garden
under the broad daylight.
Grandma, you haven't seen
this guy in action.
Huh?
He's nuts.
What is it, Bentley?
It's a shoe.
Oh, my gosh.
Is there a foot?
I don't see one.
There hasn't been a foot
in that boot for 20 years.
No foot, no body.
Now how did that dog know
that that boot was in there?
Bentley loves shoes.
I had to give him that toy
so he would stop chewing
on my tennis shoes.
Franklin.
Mr. Lyle?
What a surprise.
We were just--well, the kids
came by earlier and they saw
Mr. Murano's nephew.
He was digging in this hole,
and they couldn't find you
anywhere, so they--
well, they thought maybe that
something had happened to you,
so they brought me out here.
I didn't think for a moment
that anything had happened
to you.
But you did disappear
really fast
and you shouldn't do that.
I'm sorry, but the picture
of little Jimmy burying me
here in the garden.
It just hit my funny bone.
Well, what was little Jimmy
digging a hole for?
What was he burying?
What's he--
What?
He's looking for the stash,
Grandma.
Is that it, Franklin?
Well, I don't know.
He's probably heard
an old rumor somewhere.
I don't think there
are six inches in this
whole place that he hasn't
poked his nose into.
Well, is there any truth
to it, Franklin?
Well, Mr. Murano's been gone
now for about, what, 27 years,
and I've never run across it.
Never wanted to either.
Why not?
Well, I've seen too much
trouble come from money.
Speaking of money, Franklin,
I understand you're about to be
homeless.
Well, it seems that
my pension just can't keep up
with these darn taxes.
Do retired gangsters
get pensions?
You see, the real story
was that Mr. Murano
was not a gangster.
He was a wholesale jeweler,
but when the gangsters went
after the family in 1948,
they went after him too, simply
because his name was Murano.
The closest they came was one
day outside of Bartolo's
Restaurant in Chicago.
I opened the car door for him
and he gave me a funny look,
said he'd like to sit up front
with me, that he had
something for me.
I saw a little box in his hand.
For some reason,
I glanced up across the roof
of the car and saw a gun.
I pushed Mr. Murano
onto the floor
and dove in behind the wheel.
I could feel the bullets
hitting Gracie.
And that was just about it.
We all went into hiding
for about six months.
It seemed like forever,
and then we all went home,
and Murano family
was pretty much
finished after that.
Yeah.
What was in the box?
Ha ha, never found out,
and it was never mentioned.
Franklin, it's been 50 years.
Nobody even knows if you exist,
much less remembers the money.
You know you're about to be
evicted.
Is there a stash or not?
Well, as he was nearing his
end, Mr. Murano gave me Grace
as a bonus for that day
in front of Bartolo's.
He said, "You take good care
of her, and she'll take
good care of you. ”
Oh, for Pete's sake.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
The answer's got to be
in the car, right?
Right, I guess it is.
Okay, all right.
Mr. Lyle, I think I found
something.
What?
I don't know what this is.
I've never seen that before.
Hey, this looks like
Mr. Murano's handwriting.
Well, what does it say?
Let's see.
"The only way
is the old mill way. ”
A riddle?
Well, what does that mean?
The old mill.
Well, Mr. Murano owned
the old mill up there
on Red Rock River.
Hey, but it hasn't been used
in years, I mean--
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
Well, then, let's go.
Let's go out there.
Come on, Lyle.
Let's go.
Get away.
Hey, hey, stop it.
Stop.
Hey, knock it off.
Hey!
Where'd you get this,
Bentley?
Looks like an expensive shoe.
Must be Uncle Jimmy's.
Hey, hey!
Keep your eye on the time.
It's 10:29.
It's the regret of my life,
my dear.
Tony and I were like rabbits.
We were running, hiding,
reading obituaries.
But you, you were constantly
in my mind.
You were the light at the end,
believe me.
Not a word, Franklin.
In six months.
But I didn't want
to get you involved.
Ah, but it's all over with now.
The blackest day of my life
though was when I came home
and found that--found that
you'd got married.
Oh, Franklin.
So this is the clue.
"The only way
is the old mill way."
What does it mean?
What did you and Mr. Murano
used to do there?
You see, Mr. Murano loved
the game of cards and won
the mill in a poker game, but
as a respectable businessman,
he didn't want to be
caught gambling,
so he asked me to cut some slots
in the floor under his table.
Now if the maître d'
signaled that the police
were coming, the players
all dropped their cards
through the floor.
You kids know the best hand
in poker?
A royal flush.
That's correct.
You can play poker
your whole life
and never hold one.
But one night, Mr. Murano
drew a royal flush just as
the cops pulled up outside.
So what did he do?
He dropped the cards
through the floor.
Did he get caught?
No, no, no.
But he cried about it
for years, but from then on,
the card drop was called
the Royal Flush.
Bar is open.
Sweet.
This is cool.
So, this used to be
an old gangster's hangout?
No, it was called
the Old Mill Tavern.
Yes, I am feeling good,
pussycat.
These idiots are going to
lead me to my uncle's fortune.
I'll tell you what.
You make sure that the sale
goes off right,
and I'm telling you,
when we're done we're going
to make out like bandits.
Okay, listen.
If they find the money,
don't panic.
Legally, it's probably yours.
We can file it in court.
We can get it back,
but whatever you do,
do not let them get back here
in time to ruin the sale.
Oh, and Jimmy,
don't shoot anyone, darling.
All right.
Women lawyers.
So where did Mr. Murano
used to sit?
Well, if I remember
correctly,
he used to sit with his back
up against the wall,
right about in here.
And, yup, there's all the--
what's this?
You a lawyer?
Yes.
You lawyers are always in
such a hurry to get back
to other people's problems.
Read it, honey.
"When thirsty hounds
tops the hill,
turn your back upon the heart."
What?
"At the top of noon,
but not o'clock, you will
find your final start. ”
“Thirsty hound ”?
What does a dry dog
have to do with anything?
Not dog.
Hound.
So?
Dog, hound.
What's the difference?
What?
Thirsty hound is a dry dog.
Yes, that's right.
Dry Dog Road.
Of course.
Up on the hill
on Dry Dog Road.
But where did he go?
We're going to go up
on Dry Dog Road,
see what's up on top
of that hill.
Okay, let's go.
Let me tell you something.
I've always held
that punctuality is just
a waste of time, especially
on a national holiday.
I'm sorry, it's just that
I have a long ride back
to Chicago this afternoon.
Well, what do you know.
It's still there.
What's all this about
a heart and a clock?
I think that tree
is our answer.
Up there, that tree.
Okay.
Why, that silly old heart.
It's still there
after all this time.
Yes, Ms. Pamela, and this
silly old heart is still here
too, after all this time.
I'm glad.
I'm truly glad, Franklin.
What the heck is up
with those two?
Looks like they have
the hots for each other.
You're kidding, right?
Hey, look.
I found the heart.
I turned my back on it.
Now what?
Wait till noon?
How long is that?
If we wait till noon,
Franklin is homeless.
No.
Top of noon.
That's 12 o'clock.
Right!
Well then it must mean
direction, and if directions
are like the figures of a clock,
then 12 o'clock must be--
Well, straight ahead.
Exactly.
Straight ahead is trees.
About a zillion of them.
All I see is a barn
and a silo.
Where?
At 12 o'clock.
What's the next clue?
Oh.
Hey, I've got it.
"A barn and silo
atop the mound,
go back to Grace
and follow the hound. ”
That's it.
Time check.
11:13
You bet.
Told you, come on.
Okay, come on!
"Park in the barn
and head up top.
Where a cow has a kit
is your final stop. ”
Let's follow the directions
and see what happens.
Listen, could you kids
open those two doors?
Double time!
Uh, 11:30.
Let's go.
Franklin, was Mr. Murano
the kind of man that would
leave the crucial bit
of information in a barn?
I mean, this isn't exactly
Fort Knox.
No, he wasn't a very
practical man,
and matter of fact,
he never even learned
how to drive properly.
When does a cow have a kit?
When a dog lays an egg.
There's nothing up here
but hay.
Take a look at the note.
"Where a cow has a kit
is your final stop. ”
Mm, kit, not a kitten?
Kit.
Uh, what's that?
It's the animal
first aid kit.
Every barn has one.
My mom calls it a cow kit.
So, where is it?
It's normally just some box
on the wall.
I knew this was going
to happen.
It got lost.
Dead end.
Okay, okay, he'll be here.
Herb's been our auctioneer
for 15 years
and he hasn't been late yet.
Maybe he's stuck
in parade traffic.
Got a big parade today,
you know.
Fine, but this sale starts
at the crack of noon.
That's in 13 minutes,
not a second after,
and if he's not here,
you're going to do it.
Look.
Something was there before,
but the screw's rusted off.
It's got to be buried
in the hay somewhere, right?
Right.
Ow.
What--What is it?
Something metal.
I hope it's the first aid kit,
so we can fix my toe.
Score.
What, what is it, kids?
Look what we found.
For heaven's sakes.
What's it say?
"Frank, here is a small token
of appreciation I tried to
present to you one evening years
ago, but fate intervened.
Because of your loyalty to me,
you lost the love of your life.
I am forever grateful
and forever sorry.
A reminder to explore
Grace's secrets.
When you step up to Grace,
your fortune is underfoot.
Your friend, Tony.
Please forgive the clumsy
mystery.
Better cryptic
than in a crypt."
Hold on to that, sweetheart.
What's in the pack?
Oh, my goodness.
This is what he meant to
give me that night years ago.
Listen to this.
"A reminder to explore
Grace's secrets.
When you step up to Grace,
your fortune is underfoot."
It's got to be in the car.
It's so obvious.
Oh, oh, my little friends.
I'm glad to see you kept our end
of the bargain, right?
Huh, you know what?
You should have kept the good
faith money, all right,
'cause I'm a man of my word,
and I certainly would have
paid you your finder's fee,
all right.
Get up.
Hey, not so fast.
You know, I got to tell you.
I'm not a man of violence
or anything,
but there's certainly is
a lot at stake here,
isn't there?
You know, I'm sorry to say
this, Jimmy, but you are a fool.
You always have been.
I'm a fool?
I'm over here with all kinds
of possibilities,
and you're over there
high and dry, huh?
Who's a fool?
Move it.
Back up...back up.
Why, Frank, is this where
the secret compartment is, huh?
Is this where the cash is at?
Ah, let's see, let's see.
What do we have here?
Okay.
Why don't you at least stay
for today's Fourth of July
festivities?
Some of us have nail
appointments we have to keep.
Hello?
Hey, pussycat.
You know, you can charge
everything in the whole
entire world on a credit card,
and it's not half the rush
of finding a few hundred
thousand in cold, hard cash.
I found it.
Jimmy?
Oh, God.
Where's that auctioneer?
Oh, ow.
Here, come on.
Here, here.
Hey, hey.
Nice dog.
That's a nice dog.
Geez, nice bull.
Bulls and cows.
Camille will blend in.
Suppose we ought
to get started, Herb.
Um, sorry about that.
Had a hard time getting across
the parade route.
We're going to get started
here.
This lovely parcel includes
the house here,
and the building as well
as a 40-acre hobby farm
down on Dry Dog Road.
Is that Zone A-1,
Sheriff Burke?
I believe that's zoned
for agriculture, Herb,
but we could--
Get a move on.
You carry on, Herb.
I'll take a look-see
at these plot maps here.
Please bear in mind
the rather large extent
of the holdings here as we begin
the bidding, because
we will start accordingly.
It is five after noon.
Let's get started.
You don't want to see me
get angry.
I'm going to start
the bidding at $800k.
Do I hear 800 thousand?
Looking at a bid of $800-.
Do I hear that $800k?
He's gaining on us, Mr. Lyle.
Time check.
12:07.
He's got a gun.
Uh oh.
Gun it, Franklin.
We can make it, come on.
Get that $950 bid.
Faster.
Who's this guy think he is?
James Bond?
That sounds just a little
bit too familiar.
I don't think that boy
could hit the broad side
of a silo with that thing.
Murano's never could
shoot straight.
Too bad for their line of work.
I've got $950--a cool mil.
Who will make it a mil?
A bargain at twice the price.
Looking at a million dollars.
Okay, kids, quick.
Run up and tell them to stop
the sale.
Tell them that we've got
the money for the taxes.
Keep going.
The sale is underway.
You can't stop now.
Stop the sale.
Stop, he has the money.
Hold it, hold it.
Now, what are you saying.
This is outrageous.
Lady, I've had just about
enough out of you.
Now, excuse me,
but shut your trap.
Mr. Lyle has the tax money.
You got to stop.
Who is he?
Mr. Lyle.
Frank has the money.
Yeah, we'll show it to you.
You better hold on here
a minute, Herb, till I get
this all cleared up.
Uh, we're going to take just
a moment here, folks, please.
I'm going to take you
to court.
I'm going to sue every one
of you country bumpkins.
And I'm going to put you
in jail if I hear one more peep
out of you.
Sir, please.
Now, if you'd be so good
as to slow down
and talk one at a time.
Okay, see, it's--
One at a time.
Please.
Sir, Mr. Lyle has the money
to pay the taxes.
Hey, hey.
Hold it right there.
Hold on a second.
Listen up, young feller.
Are you going to
behave yourself?
He'll be fine, Sheriff.
He'll be fine.
He's--I'll take care of him.
Come on.
He's my client.
Okay, you hold tight and
we'll deal with him momentarily.
Frank, you sure you can come
up with that kind of money?
I believe I can, Sheriff.
And it's all legal
and everything?
Yes, it is, Sheriff.
Well, then,
that's all I need.
Herb, folks, we appreciate you
coming by today, but it looks
like our current occupant can
make his tax payment after all.
Since we're small town, and we
like to take care of our own,
we're going to cancel today's
auction.
Thank you very much
for coming out,
and have a happy Fourth of July.
Goodbye.
How about--
It's over.
Did we--
It's over, Jimmy.
So, what you doing
for the rest of the summer?
I don't know.
How about another adventure?
You know, Mr. Murano used
to say, "There are plenty of
tomorrows, but only one today. ”
Well, in that case, Franklin,
I think it's plenty
of yesterdays.
Ms. Pamela, Mimi, I would be
very honored if you would accept
this ring.
It's always been yours anyway,
and I'd just like you
to have it.
Regardless of how you answer
my next question,
I want you to have it,
but would you entertain
the idea of marrying me
and living our tomorrows
together in this old house?
Oh, well, Franklin,
50 years late.
It's better late than never.
Yes.
Oh, finally.
I don't even care
if I miss the parade.
You won't miss it.
I'll drive you.
Oh!
Oh, Franklin!