Good morning Fresno, California.
It's a scorching 97 degrees in the
shade so it feels like Armageddon.
Stay safe and drink
plenty of water.
We have a brand new song for you this morning from our very own
Central Valley artist, Phillip Kellenback and Benjamin Adams.
Keep cool, stay hydrated but most
important, be safe in the heat.
Here is their new song "AO".
Hi Alison.
Hey.
What do we have?
In room 8, we have a 26 year old
female with severe abdominal pain.
The ER doc has seen her
and ordered an ultrasound.
She's now just resting
on some pain meds.
Ok.
In room 9, we have a twenty year old male that came in with
a non-displaced forehead fracture and lac while moshing.
The CT of his brain is negative.
Genius!
In room 11, we have an elderly male with congestive heart failure
and complains of shortness of breath, but his vital signs are stable.
Ok.
And room 12 we have a thirteen year
old girl with a broken jaw from a fall.
And that's it.
Ok, well, that doesn't seem too
bad. I'll take over from here.
You have a good day.
Have a good shift.
Nu pashen rume fah.
What?
New patient room 4.
Oh, Thank you.
Good Morning.
How are you ladies?
Oh. What happened to you?
My boyfriend did this to me.
What about you?
We need moral support too.
So what happened to you?
I was drunk and I fell.
I tripped on something
and I landed on my chin.
Ok, do you have any medical
problems that you know of?
No.
Do you take any medications
or have any allergies?
No.
Doctor, excuse me, she
hasn't had her pain meds yet.
Ya, she has a left angle fracture but she is not
in severe pain right now and no airway issues.
Hey, I need you for
something right now please!
Ya, the girl with the
broken jaw, right?
No. No, can you put
that on hold for now.
Yes.
We have an MVA in the trauma bay and he is bleeding
profusely from his mouth and we need to intubate him.
Oh, shit...
Can I call you back. We have
a bigger problem here. Ok.
EIGHTY PALP.
I just can't see
anything in there.
EIGHTY PALP.
He needs to be
intubated right now!
EIGHTY PALP.
Yeah, I need silk suture with a large needle and
a ton of silver nitrate with packing. Now, Now!
See what you can do.
Ok, I can see the cords
hand me the tube and give
me some cricoid pressure.
Ok, I'm in.
I hear breath
sounds, we're good!
You know, for an intern
he's got some big cojones!
Sorry, I finished so fast.
Same ol story. It doesn't
matter, I get paid either way.
Can you at least humor me
and pretend you enjoy it?
Why should you care?
I don't know. I mean I know I
pay you for sex but come on,
that doesn't mean I have
to get my ego deflated.
Jesus, the Tina thing again?
Oh gawd no. That was a
long time ago. I'm over it.
Sorry, Ron.
My daughter's got chicken pox
and I'm just worried about her.
She wanna come to the ER?
No, she's doing better.
She'll be alright.
Alright, well you know it's
good that she got it so early...
I gotta go.
Remember, chicken soup and rest.
Spend some time with her.
Come on. What the
fuck! Give it back!
Alright we got a
Peepin' Tom here.
Hey man, you're starting to look like a retard with all your staring. Just
because you guys are in math class together, doesn't mean she's into you.
Ya.
She's into studly athletes not
boys that play Dungeons N Dragons.
Fuck you and you.
Really, is that all you got? Come on
man, lets go get something to eat.
I'm good.
Hey man, your going to college next year.
There'll be tons of girls and you'll find one.
Yes, even you.
Come on, let's go eat.
So his painful abdomen pain and nausea was resolved
with 4 milligrams of Zofran and now he's just resting.
Ok.
In room five, we
have a nightmare.
Fifty-three year old male that came
in with a bleeding and painful mouth.
He's been trying to drink from his Gatorade
bottle but now says that his pain is unbearable.
I tried to start an IV on him but he
wouldn't cooperate and cussed me out.
He's very rude and
grumpy to the staff.
I have to say, he's an asshole.
I'll get the doc to call the oral
surgeon for him. Have a good day.
Take care, Ron.
He's interested in that and
good thing its not on backorder.
I'll fill out the forms ASAP.
Yeah, so I will get those forms
sent out to you right away.
Damn, they still
haven't changed my ID.
What's the problem.
It should say head nurse.
Anyhow, uh you have the
yellow pages around here?
Uh...
Yes, what do you need it for?
Need an exterminator. There are
all these roaches in my house.
A... B... C... D...
You can't be putting that shit
in my mouth! It's gonna hurt.
Sir, I'm gonna need
your temperature...
Shit in my mouth!
You ain't putting fuck all
over my mouth, alright?
That's ok, I'll
take over from here.
Sure.
Just relax, ok, calm down.
I'll get you something
for the pain, I promise.
Thank you.
I need to ask you
some questions though.
Ok... fine.
So when did your
mouth start hurting?
About seven months ago.
But the pain got excruciating
about two months ago.
How do you eat?
I don't. I just drink and
now the pain is intolerable.
You waited seven months
to see someone about this?
I don't have a car, my asshole son
wouldn't drive me. I had to catch a bus.
Ok.
Well, any medical issues?
High blood pressure.
Got that in Nam.
They opened me up, put
a malar screen in me.
Took it out a about
two years ago.
War is hell.
Huh,
only two people
made it in my unit.
I got lucky,
or unlucky, I guess.
Man he doesn't look good and he has
no family around take care of him.
I mean he can barely eat from
all the bleeding in his mouth.
Hey uhh, Jim is gonna need a biopsy
on his mouth and possible trach.
Doesn't look good.
So this prostitute comes in,
right, ripped clothes and all
and you can see half of her tit.
She has this huge bruise on the side
of her face and she says that her
boyfriend hit her.
He probably slapped her
on the face with his dick.
The poor bitch suffered
a cheek bone fracture.
Ok, shut the hell up,
already... Both of you!
Hey, man what's with you?
We're just joking around.
She's a patient.
She's a hooker.
You stupid, insensitive
nursing student.
Ok, boss!
Won't do it again!
Hi.
Hey Josh, this is Ron.
Hey Ronny, what's up?
Hey man, umm just wanna check and see if I can stay at your
pad for a couple of nights? I got exterminators at my place.
No, that's totally cool.
In fact, my wife and I are going to St. Lucia for the whole
week and I was gonna ask if you could house sit, if you'd like.
That's awesome. Ya, thank you. And look, I'll take care of
you're place, it will be in stellar shape when you get back.
Cool.
Alright, well, thanks man.
You guys have fun. Bye.
Susan, my love.
Hi Ron, how are you?
Are any of the doctors prescribing
any of your drugs today?
We'll see, I have a presentation
to give them at four.
Well, don't worry, I mean,
you have the charm and
we'll just get the plastic surgery to
fix your looks so it will be all good.
Ron, you're a dork.
Dorks are sexy now.
Ron, who's that guy?
Oral Surgery intern, Dr. Pir.
Wait, you like him?
I mean, I can introduce you if you
want. Don't know if he's single though.
I hear, he's gay.
No, silly.
Best of luck with
the presentation.
Thanks Ron.
Tonight, shocking
developments from "sign scam".
Police say these young men were responsible for
ruthless crime spree after the KMPH sign was stolen.
The save our state initiative to curb illegal
immigration. What effect on valley agriculture
we can't deny many illegal
immigrants do pick up our crops
the situation in Haiti summed
up in one word, hell...
Hi, you reached the
Josh Bergeman residence.
Leave a message after the beep,
but don't be a punk if you get caught
driving drunk, you can call me at my office.
Those stories and the rest of the day's news.
Friday, the last day of September, 1994.
Hi,
I saw the work you did on
thatn girl's face. Impressive.
Oh, thank you... but, unfortunately, I
think she's gonna have some scarring.
Oh. You guys are like,
plastic surgeons.
Well, at least in
this hospital we are.
Hi, I'm Ardy.
Susan. It's a pleasure.
Likewise...
May I...
Absolutely...
Well, you do know I prescribe
your drugs to patients at times.
You know it has...
Yes, I know... It has hydrocodone, which is an opiod,
and acetominophen to help synergistically relieve pain.
You came to my presentation!
No, but I read one
of your pamphlets.
I like to know what it is that
I'm actually giving my patients.
I see... finally, I meet
a well informed doctor.
Thank you...
That pair of legs can walk right up
and make an ass out of themselves.
Shhh...
I gotta have her!
She's from Eastern Europe.
Don't you think you have
enough on your plate right now?
Oh, but look at her... she's
perfect! Smart, beautiful! Uuuhh!
Ya, but you've had good girls
before. You know what your problem is
you're never satisfied.
Look at her! I don't
think she shits.
You know, you and the
doc got a lot in common
both good looking, both
workout, but wait a minute,
he's an Oral Surgeon.
He's a dentist!
Ya, you keep telling
yourself that pal.
Do me a favor, try not to
be too creepy, I'm out.
That's three extra days that
she's here because of placement.
I know, there's your tax
dollars but to good use, right?
Anyway, I have the new
resident directory.
Any hotties?
Oh, that OBGYN guy is cute.
Ya, but he is gay...
Hey, I'm Ron.
Lisa.
Nice to meet you.
Well, a patient needs
placement in 302.
Ok.
I'm a social worker here.
That's great
I started working
about two weeks ago.
Nice.
And you are...
Huh, a nurse.
Um... a head nurse.
So can I take you out some time?
We just met and you
already wanna take me out?
Yup. Shouldn't social
workers be social?
Oh ho... Well, I'm a lady.
That's ok
Ron, trauma activation,
trauma bay four right now.
So you'll give it
a thought, right?
Come on!
Dude, what are you doing.
She's not looking for a partner,
she's looking for a rich doctor.
That's how she's gonna
become suckssexfull.
Then what's the hurt in trying?
You're wasting your time?
I got all the time in the world.
Do ya?
There is no trauma
activation. Is there?
You're gonna thank
me for this later.
Ya, thank you for helping
me to not get laid.
Anyhow, come help me
print out some labs.
Why, all you gotta to do is log
on to the main terminal to the ER.
Come on man, you know that I
don't know shit about computers.
What are you a moron?
Hey Karen. Can I use
you phone please.
Sure.
Thank you.
Hi, yes um, I'm a nurse at the ER. I just wanted
to see if Mr. Maple has had his surgery yet.
Oh... the case has been postponed
for tomorrow... ok, Thank you.
Thank you.
Weren't you terrified that you might
get shot and killed in an instant?
I was young.
You don't think about the extent
of things when your that age.
You just do what
you're told, you know.
If I died, so be it.
My life wasn't very hunky
dory at that time anyway.
Uh.
But I'm glad I made it. I met
my wife a couple of years later.
I hope I get to meet
my wife some day.
She was the sweetest
woman in the world.
And the lord took her away
from me much too soon.
Oh... I'm sorry.
So. Um, about the surgery...
So they're gonna cut a piece of tissue
out of your mouth and send it to the lab.
Then they're gonna create an airway by making
an opening in your trachea so you can breathe.
Ya I know, the surgeons told
me everything about it earlier.
Alright, well just making sure.
Now, be honest with me, what are your
thoughts on this? Is it the big C?
Yes, that's what
they're thinking.
Figures!
But hey, it's not a death
sentence by any means and
at least you didn't get it
when you were younger. Right?
Maybe I should have.
Why?
I would've treated every
day like it was my last.
Eat well, more meth
addicts await us.
I like meth addicts.
Good for business.
Tell me Ron, what do you
want out of life right now.
I'm not talking about helping people
and all that other B.S. but...
What do you really want?
Women, of course.
Oh! My bad!
What do you want Allen?
I want to get the
hell outta this place.
Well, good luck.
See ya.
Well, I didn't realize that destiny
would give me a chance so soon.
Oh hi.
Lisa right?
Yes, that's right... I'm
sorry, I forgot your name.
Ron.
Oh that's right. I didn't
know you live up here?
Um, yah I...
I live in North Clovis. I'm
just out here grabbing some...
Oh.
What about you?
Just, feminine things.
No, no, I didn't mean like..
Where you... nevermind.
So you really live up
here in North Clovis?
Ya, I live in a house
near Nees Avenue.
Oh really... so are you
sharing it with someone?
You mean like do I have
roommates? No, it's all mine.
Wow, that's a
great part of town.
I mean it's the
best... but uhhmm,
how much more shopping
do you have left?
I am pretty much done.
Do you wanna go grab
coffee? Maybe, chat?
Sure.
Let me grab this for you.
Oh, I think I better get this.
So, after nursing school, one
of my uncles suddenly died
and I found out that he left me
all this money for some reason.
So I bought a house, a car,
invested the rest an ah, yeah.
I still have this passion for
nursing and taking care of people, so
kind of ending up in this job.
What about you? How Did
you become a social worker?
Well, sociology was an
easy major in college.
Makes sense.
Umm, tell me this, has a guy
ever cooked for you before?
Not enough times.
Well, uhh, would you allow me
to cook you dinner this weekend?
That is sweet. I think I'll
take you up on that offer.
Cheers!
Hey John, what room
is Jim Maple in?
Let's see... he's
in room 316 bed 1.
Ok. Thank you.
Hey, I know you can't talk now so I
brought you a pen and a pad. Alright.
I talked to you doctors and they are still waiting
for the biopsy result but I just wanted to say...
I know your struggling and I know your
having a hard time but keep hope alive.
"PAIN IS SO BAD, I
WANT THINGS TO END."
Jim don't say that. You survived getting
shot in the war... you can survive this.
Don't give up.
"IF I SURVIVE, WHAT KIND
OF LIFE WOULD I LIVE?"
Nobody knows what the
future holds. Right?
But medicine and technology are changing
all the time. Who knows what can happen?
You got to keep the faith.
Ok, enough.
I need to get some rest and
keep thinking those
positive thoughts. Alright.
I'll ask the nurse to
give you some pain meds.
So um, why did you become an
Oral and Maxillofacial Surgeon?
Uhmm, well love, money,
women,
helping people,
challenging myself
all of those things, not
in that particular order
lets not talk about that. Why
don't we play a little game.
Let's!
Ok. The game is called the getting to
know each other better game. Alright,
this is how it works.
I will tell you something about
myself which may be true or false
and you have to guess. If you
get it right, you go again.
If you get it wrong, you have to
tell me something about yourself
and I have to guess
whether it's true or false.
Ok.
Alright,
alright uumm,
true or false,
when I when I was ten years
old, I shaved my entire body.
Let me see,
hmmm,
I'm gonna go false on this one.
True, actually.
I went through puberty
really young and I...
I didn't like it and one day I went
to town with my mother's razor.
Ardy, that's crazy!
Ya, I know.
Ok, your turn.
Ok. I've kissed a girl before.
That's false.
Yes. But what made
you guess right?
Uhmm well, you're bold,
but not that bold.
Plus, I can tell that
you only really like men.
Ok. Uhmm, I guess
I have to go again.
Uhmm, I have tried
marijuana before.
True. I don't think you use it
on a regular basis but you ah
you definitely,
experimented in college,
and you definitely
inhaled. For sure.
Yes, Ardy, you're
too smart for me.
Hey, your turn
again, go ahead...
Hey buddy.
What's up?
I love this job. Shit, vomit, and piss. All
day, every day. It just gets better and better.
Stop complaining,
we're helping people.
Yah... How about helping myself.
Dude, we do all the crap work,
literally, get none of the credit.
Anyway, what are you
doing this weekend?
I got a date with
the social worker.
The social worker, yah!
Wow man, how did
you pull that off?
So, I got exterminators at my house right, so I am
staying over this guy's house named Josh Bergeman.
Uh, he's a lawyer. So...
He's the hot shot drunk driving
defense attorney? Josh Bergeman.
Ya, with the billboards. Ya.
How do you know
him? He's loaded.
We were friends growing up.
He lived in the neighborhood.
These kids would always
pick on him. One day, I like
stood up for him and shoved this kid
and we've been friends since then.
Anyway...
You lucky dog!
Listen, I bump into her
at a store near his house.
We talk.
She asks if I live in the area.
I might have told her
I live in the area.
I might have told her I inherited
a lot of money from my family.
And I definitely invited
to have dinner at my house,
Josh Bergemen's house.
You're lying to this
girl so you can bang her?
Girl's lie to me all the time.
Uh... No. One girl
lied to you many times.
Now you gotta take that
out on the whole world?
What?...T-T-the walking penis
is now on a moral high horse?
I got a date didn't I?
No, no no, doesn't
count. You cheated.
What are you talking about?
You cheated.
Her mother was diagnosed with schizophrenia. Her father
is an alcoholic, but she denies having any physical abuse
she describes having symptoms of major depression. She was
crying all the time, she felt tired, she lost fifteen pounds.
This episode happened after she broke up
with her boyfriend, when she turned fifteen.
Apparently, she was very attached to him. They had been going out
for eight months but, according to her, he left her for another girl.
Uhh, did they have sex?
Yes, she admitted to that. Then, her dad went on a
drinking spree and didn't come home for several days.
Uh. What's the relationship
like of her parents now?
They are separated now.
OK what's her affect like?
She's reserved and
quiet, but not catatonic.
Ok, what about her meds?
She got started on Fluexetine, one month ago. I
don't know if it had enough time to take effect.
Hey, it's been really busy
this week at the hospital.
What are you doing tonight?
Well, I've got a date.
Who is it?
He's this nurse at the hospital.
A nurse?
Ya, but he's cute and he tells me
he inherited money from his family.
Ok, but it's funny, you work with all these
doctors and you're going out with a nurse...
Well have a good time.
So let me ask you something, do
you think I should sleep with him.
Depends on where he
takes you for dinner...
Just kidding. Just go
and see what happens.
But have him wear
a condom if you do.
Ok, hun, I will let
you know how it goes.
Bye.
No so apparently there was a Rolling Stones concert in Berlin and these
balloons got released and they were floating towards the eastern side.
Um, and there was a member of the band named Nena in the audience
and he saw all the balloons floating towards the Soviet side
and they thought what if the Soviets start
military action and that starts the World War III.
That is what the song "99
Luft Balloons" is..is about.
Wow, that's crazy.
I know.
But I thought the whole
country of Germany was divided.
It was. So was the
city of Berlin.
So, Berlin was a divided city
within a divided country?
Exactly...
Ooh...
Have you ever listened to
the band named "Berlin"?
No.
I'm sure you heard one song.
Ok, which one?
"Take My Breath Away"
from the movie "Top Gun".
Yes, I know that
song. I love it.
Ron, how do you know
all these things?
I don't know, just childhood.
How's your food?
Oh, it's great.
Thank you so much.
More wine?
Oh yes. Please.
Hi, you reached the Josh
Bergeman residence...
Hey, is everything ok in there?
Ya ya, just a little accident.
Do you need any help?
No, it's ok.
You know Ron, I really
appreciate this.
To be honest, no other guy has
cooked dinner for me before.
Thank you.
Sure.
I didn't even know houses
like this exist in Fresno.
When did you end up buy it?
Uhmm, four years ago?
Don't you ever get lonely
in this big ol house?
Well, I'm hoping the situation
will change on that front.
Hmmm! Really?
The hardest part about the
house is maintaining it.
You have to have a gardener
and a pool man and...
Wait, you have a pool too!
Yah, pool and a guest house.
I should give you a tour!
Let's go over there.
Well, why don't we sit on the couch
for a little bit and drink some wine.
Wait, maybe not this one.
Let's just go over there.
Let me... let me just take this.
Oh.
Here?
Yeah.
Ahhh... um huh.
Huh.
So I can't believe that no
guy has ever cooked for you.
Gentlemen don't exist anymore
well, expect for you.
About that tour, you wanna make
the first stop in the bedroom?
Um.
Listen Lisa, it's been a great night
but, maybe we don't rush things, maybe...
Wow!
There'll be other
nights for more.
Ron, you are a gentleman.
Most guys just wanna get in
my pants as fast as possible.
You are special!
Hey man, is Jim
Maple still in 316?
Yes, he is.
Thanks.
Hey, Jim how are you?...I
brought you something.
Check this out.
What do you think?
"THANK YOU. I'M SO HAPPY. MY DOCTOR SAYS
THE CHEMO TREATMENT SEEMS TO BE WORKING!"
That's great news. See, I told
you to stay positive right!
Ok, well, take a look.
Huh, Looks good!
"HOW IS THE THE GIRL
OF YOUR DREAMS?"
Huh, let's just say there's
some uh, heavy competition now.
"DON'T GIVE UP. A WISE
PERSON ONCE TOLD ME THAT!"
I won't... I won't.
Susan?
Yeeesss.
How did you know I was on call?
I have my ways.
How did you know I was here.
So your gonna keep
interrogating me
or you gonna enjoy the
fact that I'm here?
It's always great to see you but
it's the middle of the night.
Well, if it's too
late, I can leave.
Residency is hard enough
but torturing me like this?
Get that grin off your face. But
seriously, what if someone comes in?
The door is locked.
What if I get called in?
You can pull out.
What?
I'm just kidding. I'm not gonna
have sex with you in the call room.
A couple of minutes ago
I was in deep sleep.
Sex was the last
thing on my mind.
That's only because you weren't
awake and you weren't dreaming.
Midnight comedian,
ehh. You're funny.
Ardy...
What?
Shut up and kiss me.
Urine and feces, and blood oh my.
Urine and feces and blood oh my...
So Ronny, how the
ladies treating you?
Well, huh, you can say
it's the dry season.
What about that hot ass social
worker you were scamming?
I made her dinner and
everything at Bergmen's house.
She was falling for me,
ready to go and um...
Then your ass gave me a conscious
and so I didn't go through with it.
Well cheer up sunny boy cause I got two
tickets this Saturday night Selland Arena.
There is a local alternative band
playing and they are pretty good.
I have my reservations
about alternative bands.
It's just corporate America
using the guise of grunge.
No, I mean some of these bands are pretty good you
know, it's not just about big hair, big tits, big ass.
Well, I'm sure their nobility will
lead them to their untimely deaths
as no good deed goes unpunished.
I just wanna blow off some steam for a couple
of hours and get the hell outta the hospital.
Are you trying to channel
in your inner Kurt Cobain?
The way you make it sound, like
have you ever considered
leaving this marriage?
And do what, go home home sit on the
couch, masturbate? Doesn't pay the bills.
So, there was this guy in the hospital and he was selling
these tubes with what looks like a penis head attached to them.
So... he said it's gonna revolutionize
intubations and airway management.
So, you want me to be a sales rep for
something that looks like a penis?
Isn't that what you already
do in your real life?
Uh ho! If its so great,
why don't you sell em?
I like my job.
This looks like superficial
abrasion, just needs moist dressing.
Ok?
Ron, there is a Jim
Maple here to see you.
Thank you.
Jim?
You... you look all swollen!
Ron, can I have a word with
you for a moment right in here?
Ya, sure.
Ok.
I know you have a close
connection with that patient,
but I wanna let you know, it
doesn't look good for him.
I recommend you keep your
distance and face the facts.
Severe cervical lymphadenopathy
indicates dissemination of oral cancer.
I'm sorry,
but hey, we've all
got to go someday.
I, I'm not sure I can do that.
Why Ron? Forty to fifty
thousand people die everyday
and none of them complain.
Because through dying,
I'm learning how to live.
So we performed a trach on
her to establish an airway.
In the ICU, she developed
Reiter's syndrome.
Dr. Pir, do you know the three
classic signs of Reiter's syndrome?
Uhmm... Uveitis,
conjunctivitis, and arthralgia.
Good. Now the disease has a different
name. Do you know what it's called?
Reactive arthritis.
Good. Do you know
why it has two names?
No, I don't.
The disease was identified
by Hans Conrad Julius Reiter.
He was a Nazi with the Third Reich
and he performed human experiments.
The name was changed to
disband the affiliation.
Sometimes, you see, even
medicine has a, an evil side.
But now we will discuss
less severe sins.
However, we have all been guilty of
these sins when treating patients.
What I am talking about
here are sins of laziness,
and the sins of pride.
Both can have dire
consequences for patients.
Hey Dr. Pir.
Hey what's up my man.
You seem deep in thought.
What is it. Whose the girl?
No girl.
What is it then?
I was attending a
lecture today. And
the guy was comparing the
sins that the Nazis made
to the sins that residents make.
What? What a freak!
Ya,
but it got me thinking of my ex.
So, I was right.
It is about a girl.
You got me.
Always is. So what happened.
I had a problem with
her being Jewish and
broke it off with her because she lived
in LA and I was moving to Fresno and
told her I couldn't handle
the whole long distance thing.
Well, you did what you had to do at the
time and what you thought would be best.
Ya, but now I miss
her like crazy.
Aren't you and that fine drug rep hitting it
off. I mean, I see you two together all the time.
Ya, we're doing fine and...
So what's wrong?
Just miss that Jewish
girl like crazy.
Why don't you try to see if you
could get back together with her.
Knowing her, she probably
has a boyfriend by now.
Tough life. We'll if you guys get back
together, send the drug rep my way alright?
Will do man.
Are you having a good time babe?
It's always good to be
out of the hospital.
Well, honey, I am so
happy to be here with you.
Thanks.
Let's get another drink?
We better not. It's getting late and
I have an early morning tomorrow.
Oh, come on Ardy,
have a little fun.
Remember, we talked about this?
Oh yah, I know. Sins of
laziness and sins of pride.
Good. You don't want anyone
dying on me now do you?
Ok, Dr. Drama.
But how about we go
out for one last dance?
Alright, one last dance.
Hey.
Well, Mr. Maple's condition has worsened
so they took him to the ICU last night.
Yeah they found a mucocele on his trach
tube but the nurses suctioned it out.
Ya, mm hum. Ok, alright.
I'll see you there.
Oh, shit I thought you
said the door was locked!
I called your son today to let
him know that you may be passing.
He almost crashed his car rushing
to get over here to see you.
That boy really loves you.
Who am I kidding? I called.
He said he has
work, can't make it.
In fact, I was gonna come see
you before you passed, but
I got stuck with a patient.
So technically you died alone.
They say life is a bitch and then
you die. Well, you proved it.
Let's hope you're in a better
place buddy, let's hope...
Hi, you have reached Ron, please
leave a message after the beep.
Hi, Ron, this is Lisa.
I'm just calling to
see how you're doing.
So I haven't really heard from
you since we last hung out
and I'm really hoping your not judging me
based on what you saw in the film room.
So please give me a call when you get
a chance. Okay, you take care. Bye.
Hey Dr. Pir.
Good morning.
What are you up to?
I just finished my night of call and
going out of town for the weekend.
Oh, where you headed?
LA.
That's like a three and a half hour
drive... Are you going right now?
Ya, I am.
Man you're gonna fall
asleep behind the wheel.
Na, I'll be alright.
Alright well, be safe.
Nothing good happens in LA.
Don't want to see you wind
up in our emergency room.
Huh! You won't.
Maybe you'll bump into
your old flame down there.
I doubt it.
Alright, see ya man.
Later man.
Ron! Ron!
Hey.
Hey, how are you?
What's wrong? Why are
you trying to ignore me?
Look Lisa, maybe what happened the
other night wasn't a good idea.
Why? I had a good time.
Listen Lisa... I'm not rich.
The house you had
dinner at, not my house.
The car you saw in the driveway, it's not
my car. My friend just owed me a favor.
And that inheritance
thing... it's all a lie.
You son of a bitch!
So you lied to me.
Be honest. Would you have gone out with me if
you thought I was earning a nurse's salary?
So, you lied to get in my pants?
Nothing happened, remember?
We didn't have sex.
I didn't deserve
to... I'm not rich.
You're an asshole!
Well, Lisa, you're
a gold-digger.
Look I... thank you for the
greeting, have a good day.
Ron...
I thought we had
something the other night.
What?
The night at your house
or your pseudo house.
What about that doctor you were
just screwin' in the film room.
He wasn't serious. He
just wanted some fun.
Lisa, let me be very
straight forward with you.
I never intending on anything
else but just fun with you either.
I'm sorry.
She a fine young looking thing,
ain't she? And you're staring again.
Yuhh, man I'm crazy about her.
How far have you gotten?
Nothing, nada, zilch!
You suck, Ron!
I know. It's shameful.
Ya... Come on man.
Take a risk, huh.
Stop being such a
vaginus maximus.
Life is but a crap shoot, the
predictable ending for us all, anyways.
I'm gonna go change.
Ya.
Gawd, you even make
drinking coffee look hot.
Ron, you're nuts!
What's up?
Nothing, just
about to head home.
Ya, my shift is over as well...
It's a nice day today, huh?
You wanna go to the fair.
It's right around the corner.
Right now?
Yeah, come on. It'll be fun.
I really shouldn't.
Come on. It's the fair.
Its once a year. Come on.
They have cotton candy and
merry go rounds. Come on.
What am I, four years old?
You can be for a little bit.
Fine you convinced
me, let me go change.
Ardy came all the way here
tonight for my birthday.
Uh, it's not a big deal man.
I mean LA has riots, floods,
fires, and earthquakes. But,
I'll still take it over Fresno.
I'll drink to that!
Um!
I didn't tell her you'd be here but I
wasn't expecting her to bring a date.
No worries, man.
Hey!
Good to see you.
Hi, how are you?
Hello.
Hi, nice to see you.
Umm, This is...
Hi I am Steve, nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Hola.
So uh, you're on time as usual.
Yes... um.
Waiting for us or what?
Yeah... exactly.
Mmm.
Not bad.
Supposed to just
take that and umm.
Don't be shy...
So how are things going in Fresno.
You're a hot shot oral surgeon now.
Oh, lets just say...
keeps me very busy.
What kind of stuff
have you seen?
Crazy things.
Umm, self-inflicted gunshot wounds to the face by
meth addicts who just broke up with their girlfriends.
You know fun stuff like
that. What about you?
Crazy, umm,
I have actually just been accepted
to the program in Fullerton.
Really?
Mmm Hmmm.
That's great.
I know how hard
you worked for it.
That's all you could talk
about while we were dating...
Jess, speaking of dating,
I don't remember
why we broke up?
I'm Jewish, remember?
It was your decision.
That's not an
issue. I'll convert.
I'm already circumscribed.
Ardy, you still have
your sense of humor.
I try.
Religion has never
an issue to me.
What about the distance
thing you kept mentioning.
At the time, I thought it was a
good idea. But, looking back at it,
I think I made a mistake.
And, I can't change the past
or control your happiness.
Hey,
Hi
I'm back!
I actually got to
get going but uh
gonna go say bye
to everybody. But
Steve, pleasure meeting you.
I just wanna let you know that
you got a great girl here.
What exactly do
mean by that DOCTOR?
I'm just saying that you
got a good girl, that's all.
Ya, I know... it's
gonna stay that way!
Ok.
Hello.
Jessica?
Hey, Ardy what are you doing?
Well I drank, so I'm just
reminiscing by the pier.
Look Ardy, I wanna
apologize for Steve tonight.
He's an asshole. And it was
only our second date, so.
Ya uh, so are you
gonna see him again?
No, probably not.
Well that's good cause um... I
think we should get back together.
So you think that you can just walk back into
my life like that after you broke up with me?
Ya... I mean, I'm gonna
give you a good life.
What happened?
The grass isn't greener or
Fresno Women aren't stacking up.
Look, I'm gonna be here for a couple of
days. Why don't we grab lunch tomorrow?
Ok, it's getting late.
Call me tomorrow, ok.
Ok, perfect. Alright,
have a good night.
Who is it?
It's Susan.
Hey babe, what's up?
I got us ice cream.
Hey.
Thanks, that's nice.
Well, you don't seem excited
to see me. What's wrong?
Susan, I have to
tell you something.
What is it?
I don't think we should
see each other anymore.
Bumped into my exgirlfriend
when I was back in LA and
decided to give it another shot.
Listen, Susan you
are an amazing...
Save it.
I am the idiot here...
So, I was your flavor of the month
until you decided to be serious?
It wasn't like that.
It just happened.
Oh ya, it just happened.
You know you're not
even a real surgeon.
Go pull some teeth!
Susan, we can still be friends.
Oh, you're funny!
How yous doings?
Oh, come on... turn
that frown upside down.
Guys are assholes!
What?...what did I do?
Not you.
Then what?
Ardy and I were seeing each other and he
just left me to go back to his ex-girlfriend.
Dr. Pir?
Yes.
Well you guys were just dating right?
Like, right, he wasn't your boyfriend?
I know, but I was
falling for him...
Yuh, ok, uuhh so where
does that leave me?
What do you mean.
We're just friends.
Ya, I know, I have been your friend. But,
I don't wanna be just friends anymore.
You have to sleep with every
girl you hang out with?
No. No. It's not like that. But I can't just be friends with
you with all these feelings that I have. I mean, you know that.
Ron, you're a great guy...
Ya, ya, ya I get it,
ya. I'm a great guy.
I'm just not a doctor.
I'm a male nurse
who... who loves his
job and who works hard.
But that's not good enough, huh!
Oh, I get it.
Ron's talking from
his almighty tower.
I know about you and your track record
with the girls from the hospital.
It's like you have your own
little Melrose Place here.
Ya, that's ok. But when it comes
to me, now your the victim. Right?
Why can't I have what I
want, whoever it may be?
I'm outta here.
Hanab?
Dr. Pir?
Welcome.
Thank you.
So how are you liking it so far?
Not bad. Can't
complain too much.
Ya, did you meet the chief yet?
Good morning gentlemen. Like to welcome
Hanab to the team. Very excited to have you.
Thanks Chief.
Well, hopefully, this is the start to
a very exciting and enriching year.
That being said,
let's get to work.
Well, I just got called from the ER for a
patient with a submandibular space infection.
He is breathing ok, but they
want us to see him right away.
Ok, lets head out,
see what we got.
Hi, uhmm yes, this is Ron, I
think you have the results.
Ok.
Ya, thank you.
No, right now there is no impeding airway
but we would like it to go this morning.
Ok, within the hour?
Yeah, perfect, that works.
So Ardy, Monty wants you
to go in on this case.
Sounds great.
What's with you?
I'm not last on the totem pole
anymore! There's people below me!
Congratulations. Now
go do this fuckin'case.
Alright.
Ardy!
Ya.
Make sure you have a nurse
help you with the pre op.
Sure thing.
Mind helping me out with
something really quick!
Yes, sure doctor.
You know that patient with the neck abscess. Can you give
him Unasyn 3 grams IV and can you witness a consent for me?
Um, I've already seen him. He's allergic to
Penicillin so started him on Clindamycin.
Ok... Uhh, can you help
me with the consent then?
Ya, sure.
So we will make an incision in your neck right
below the jaw line, um to drain the infection.
While we're there, we will place
cultures in the area to see what bugs are
and with an instrument I will dissect the floor
of your mouth and place rubber drains there
um, in order to proceed I will need you to
sign this consent form right where the X is.
Thank you, and Ron if you can sign
the witness line for me please.
Thank you.
Hello... Hi Honey.
Ya, I'm fine. Same ol, same ol... sick
patients, long shifts, mean doctors.
Well, just take of
yourself and eat well,
and remember, you can't solve
all the world's problems.
So how you holding up?
I'm fine Mom, thank
you. Love you.
I love you too.
Mom? I...
Yes dear.
Honey?
How... how's dad doing?
Ohh. He's fine. Same ol, same ol. Is
that really what you wanted to ask me?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Yes mom. Love you.
I love you too. Bye honey.
Bye.
Looks like his sedation
is wearing off.
Please stop moving.
Just bear with us.
Come on sir, don't
move. Please, sir.
He's gonna need more sedation.
Can you give him two more milliliters of
Versed, I'm gonna give him some local.
Hand me the 15 please.
Let's ahh... finish
closing this.
Good. Were' just about done
and he's still sedated.
Looks good.
Hey!
Good to see you.
Where's my brother?
He's in the back with the little
monster. He'll be out. Come in.
How've you been?
Yeh.
So uh, you dating anybody?
It's complicated, as
everything else in my life.
Well, you can tell
me, Ron. I am family.
Remember Amy from high school?
Yes.
So, we get together.
She's a hooker now
um, had a chance to score with a gold digger and
the girl of my dreams just wants to be friends.
Friends? Like the show?
Like, not even friends with
benefits. Just friends.
Damn,
seriously. You need to find yourself
a partner. Not just a score.
Ya, but it's not easy
with... with my job.
Cause I'm always reminded
of how short life is.
Well life doesn't have to
be long to be meaningful.
I mean everyday you help people
when they need it the most.
That makes sense.
Something to think about.
Ya.
Hey!
Hey.
How's it going?
Uhh, same ol, same ol.
How's dad?
You know pops, he's only
happy when we're all together.
Oh my goodness! Come
here you little princess!
Don't fall for any jerks lies.
What?
Too cute. She's gonna be
a little heartbreaker.
Dr. J?
Ah, take a seat doctor Dr. Pir.
So... after uh going
over your evaluations, uh
it appears that your knowledge of the basic
material started slow but it's definitely improving.
Your hand and surgical
skills are there.
Motivation, eagerness
to learn is good.
Bedside manner, relatively good.
Um, there were a few inconsequential complaints from patients but I think,
both you and I know, that sometimes patients can have their own agenda.
Professional demeanor.
The staff thinks your nice.
It does say here you can be clownish and
eccentric at times, that's not an issue.
Oh and Ardy...
Yes.
Be careful when you date
people in the hospital.
That's all over now. You don't
need to worry about that.
Ok.
Listen, there's just one more issue I
wanna address before I let you go... um.
Do you wanna explain why you felt the need to staple a
patient's forehead in the shape of a Jewish star of David?
It was a stellate lac. He needed some advancement
flaps and revisions and it just turned out that way.
Ardy! Cut the crap.
And he had a large swastika
tattoo on his chest.
I think he deserved it.
He can have a scar
revision in six months.
Well, I don't think a three time convicted drunk driver
with a history of meth addiction is going to ask for that.
Alright listen up, Ardy.
You and I both know that
Fresno is just a temporary stop
before you move unto to bigger and
better things in LA. So do me a favor,
stay out of trouble, just give me everything
you have when your here at Valley hospital. Ok?
Sure thing doc.
Alright, keep up the good work.
Thanks.
You bet. Go.
Hey Susan!
What now? You're gonna make
me feel like shit again?
Look, I just wanna
say I'm sorry.
Half of it was the rage I have against
the world and the other half was the
the broken heart talking.
I... I just felt that after the fair
that we had a connection and you know...
Ron, I do like
you as a friend...
I know, I know, just not in that
way. And I have to accept that.
I did have a good time
at the fair though.
Ya, it was fun.
That's why I want us
to remain friends.
Hey.
Oh hey, don't worry about
it. I'm just not feeling it.
You wanna just hang out tonight?
What's wrong?
Nothing, just not feeling it.
OK
Look, you'll still get paid anyway...
Just take a break from sex tonight.
Aren't you a gentleman.
How are you doing?
How's your kid?
Didn't know I was
getting paid to talk.
Well, I paid for this time
so I can do what I want.
You know, I... remember you
being quiet and shy in school.
Huh.
Would never imagine
you doing this.
Well.
I don't know. It's the
most pure and real thing.
What?
They want me for sex and I want them
for money. It's an honest transaction.
Ok, but purity aside, what's
gonna happen in five years.
I mean, do you want your daughter to find out? Kids in
school asking "what does your mom do?" What is she gonna say?
Well, she is gonna say that my dick-head dad left me before I was born
and my dick-head grandfather left my mom before she was a teenager.
Ya, but putting dick-head, poor male role models
aside, there's gotta be other ways of makin' money.
Ya, you try raising a kid and paying for your
mom's hospital bills on a waitress' salary.
I just don't want you to catch
anything or get beaten one night.
Know, I hate when my
clients try to be saints.
I'm your friend.
Ya.
Ok, well ah... I got to get
going, I got a long day tomorrow.
Your money's on the counter.
Thanks.
So you wanna take out all your
cash and close your account?
Ya. Yes.
Is there a reason? Can we do
something to improve our services?
No, just a...
Are you leaving us
for ICAN banking?
No, no no, you guys are
fine. Ah... I'm moving.
Oh, ok, then how would
you like your cash?
Uuhmm, straight
hundreds would be fine.
Alright, I'll be right back.
Ok, well uh, here you...
No, no wait!
Ok. So, you're keepers
are a Bird/Magic rookie,
the Jordan rookie, of course, the
Charles Barkley, and the Olajuwon.
You, ahh sure you
wanna get rid of these?
Ya, I need the cash
I'll give you um
five hundred for all of them.
Five fifty and I throw in
a bunch of Shaq rookies.
Shaq rookies?
Ok..
This is the last thing. I'll
throw in the tape of Ejacula 2.
It has Ron Jeremy in it.
Oh,
that's clearly a copy.
I didn't think authenticity
mattered in these cases.
Deal!
Are you excited for you
first day of kindergarten?
I'm scared mommy.
Don't worry sweety,
you're gonna be just fine.
Mommy can you be
with me tonight?
You promised.
Of course.
Thank you mommy.
Mommy read me something.
Read what's in your hands.
Ok.
Um, let's see what we got.
Ahh, you have ten
days until collections
let's not read that one.
And
eleven free CD's... boring.
Mommy, open the big
yellow envelope.
Mommy read it to me.
What's wrong mom?
Oh, thanks.
Ok, everything seems
to be in the report.
Good job, you can
have her come in.
Thank you, but Mrs. Sierakowski,
when can you do my papers?
I'll do it this week, I promise.
Thank you, I'll get her.
Thanks.
Amy.
Hi.
Good morning.
You want coffee?
Um... I'm fine thank you.
Great, sit down.
So,
you think this plan will work?
Look, you were born in America.
You both went to the
same high school.
I don't see it as a problem.
You have to trust me,
I'm a lawyer.
Ok.
Now, I need you to
sign this right here.
Congratulations. Now, all I need is his
signature and you guys are official.
Ok.
It's just, I never imagined
it being like this.
Well, life tricks you in
certain unexpected ways.
You should know that by now.
Ya, it's just he
he never mentioned any of this
during any of our outings.
Your outings?
We... we didn't just have sex.
As his wife, I'm hear
to talk about Ron...
I'm sorry. I... I wrote a speech
but I can't go through with this.
I just wanna say that with
the exception of my daughter,
nobody has cared for
me more than Ron has.
Hey, I'm sorry to interrupt,
you look really familiar. Have I seen
you around in the hospital at the Valley?
Ya, I use to do
social work there.
That's how you know Ron?
Ya, we met a long time ago.
He actually got me
into the Peace Corps.
I just came back from an
assignment in Africa two weeks ago
and then I found out
about his passing.
Peace Corps in Africa?
That sounds eye opening
I just needed a change in my life and Ron suggested
that it would be an incredible experience.
Interesting.
You know, Ron is the reason
I met my wife, Susan.
Ya, they were
really good friends.
He set us up while he was receiving
treatment at my clinic. He was
you know, losing hair and
growing weaker by the day, but
insisted that I call her.
Is she here?
No she's at home cause she's actually
due any day now for our first son.
We're gonna name him after Ron.
Well congratulations.
Thank you... We're
gonna greatly miss Ron.
Yeah.
I never have to work
the streets again.
And my daughter's
college is paid for but,
I feel like crap.
Taking his life insurance
money makes me feel so empty.
He wanted you to have it.
It was his dying wish.
There was a new chemo
drug called Temzolamide.
It would've given him a
couple more months but
he refused to take it.
We uh, we used to have sex,
up until we got married.
You know, your marriage
was only on paper.
Um hum.
But he found a way for us to not have
to do what we don't want anymore.
Like we're free now.
How can I go on?
Take the money.
Start a new life, out of Fresno.
Oh ya, you're
feeling better now?
Good.
Oh ya, should be
home in a little bit.
Ok. I love you too. Bye.
Checking out the
beautiful scenery, huh!
Ya, you know it. What
was that all about?
Ah, it's just the pregnancy
has been really rough on Jess.
How's the residency
and hospital going now?
Gawd, I've been there so long
I've been institutionalized.
Oh! Uh, last week the hospital commemorated
a nurse that use to work there,
Ron Sierakowski.
Do you know him?
Ron? No, I don't.
I guess he was there
when you were an intern.
But ya, he got sick
and he finally passed.
I do remember the super hot rep
when I was there that I dated.
I remember her.
May God rest his soul. How's
Dr. Hall running the asylum?
You already know how that is.
So uhh, the job search? How's that going?
You've been up and down LA for awhile now?
Ya, it's funny that
you mention that. Uhmm,
Dr. A might have a position
open for me in Fresno.
An associate position. I'm
thinking about taking it.
Really?
Ya.
Going back to the no, huh!
I guess so.
Well, good luck man.
Thanks man