♪ Stuck at work,
looking out my window ♪
♪ Another beautiful day
spent locked in a cage ♪
♪ The weather man
is trying to kill me ♪
♪ Channel nine
is trying to drive me insane ♪
♪ Eight-five
with a chance of perfect ♪
♪ The sun is shining and the
water's screaming out my name ♪
♪ Sick of this isolation ♪
♪ I think it's time
for a little vacation ♪
♪ I'm gonna hit the beach ♪
♪ Take a swim in the ocean ♪
♪ Work on my tan
with cheap crappy lotion ♪
♪ Lay in the sand and watch
the world pass me by ♪
♪ I'm gonna seize the day ♪
♪ Tell my boss maybe later ♪
♪ Rent out a boat
and sail the Equator ♪
♪ Put on my shades
and drift into the sunset sky ♪
♪ Singing my getaway lullaby ♪
♪ Times up, daydream's over ♪
♪ Only 11 o'clock
and it feels like five ♪
♪ I need a little motivation ♪
♪ Otherwise I don't know
if I'll survive ♪
♪ Dirty looks
from my supervisor ♪
♪ Another second and I think
I'm gonna fall off the edge ♪
♪ Doesn't matter
what they pay me ♪
♪ I've had enough
of this nauseating work week ♪
♪ I'm gonna hit the beach ♪
♪ Take a swim in the ocean ♪
♪ Work on my tan
with cheap, crappy lotion ♪
♪ Lay in the sand and watch
the world pass me by ♪
♪ I'm gonna seize the day ♪
♪ Tell my boss maybe later ♪
♪ Rent out a boat
and sail the Equator ♪
♪ Put on my shades
and drift into the sunset sky ♪
♪ Singing my getaway lullaby ♪
♪ Do-do-do do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Do-do-do do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Now I'm living life large
in my flip flops ♪
♪ Sunscreen, tan lines,
itty bitty tank tops ♪
♪ No job from noon to nine ♪
♪ Eight days a week,
no sleep till the end of July ♪
♪ Livin' it up
one day at a time ♪
♪ I'm doin' just fine ♪
♪ I'm gonna hit the beach ♪
♪ Take a swim in the ocean ♪
♪ Work on my tan
with cheap crappy lotion ♪
♪ Lay in the sand and watch
the world pass me by ♪
♪ I'm gonna seize the day ♪
♪ Tell my boss maybe later ♪
♪ Rent out a boat
and sail the Equator ♪
♪ Put on my shades
and drift into the sunset sky ♪
♪ Singing my getaway lullaby ♪
♪ Do-do-do do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Do-do-do do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
Thanks. Uh, excuse me,
Mr. Smith?
Oh, yeah. Hey, guys,
that was a great show.
- Thank you.
- Hey, I got a little something for you.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
How much did we make?
- Oh.
- A gift certificate?
I could go for some Mexican.
Uh, hey, Mr. Smith?
Yeah. Can I help you?
Um, yeah, so we were told
that we were gonna be
compensated for the show.
Well, yeah.
Got that free coupon
and, you know,
the hotel room. Right?
Mm... We just
were hoping for...
monetary compensation.
Well, Dave, we...
We're a not-for-profit.
There's no cash in the budget.
What about, um, all the
money raised from the run?
Well, that goes
to our cause. Right?
I mean, you guys are
compensated by your exposure.
Mr. Smith,
I'm sorry, no offense,
but we just played
for four hours.
That's, um, less than two
dollars an hour for each of us.
Yeah. Well, okay.
Just a second.
I don't normally do this,
you know,
but, you know,
that's a donation.
So here, let me get something
from my wallet for you here.
Hold on one second.
One second...
Just one second.
Just got... Oh, there it is.
Here you go.
Ten cents off a gallon of gas.
At least these are good.
I'm glad, 'cause those two bites
are worth a half hour
of work each.
You think that the bank will
let us deposit the gas coupon?
See, that's the other thing.
Joe, this van gets
terrible gas mileage.
We have to get rid of it.
No. Hey, don't talk
about her like that.
These are actually pretty good.
♪ I never promised you
I'd give up nice ♪
♪ Would I lie? ♪
♪ Yeah, you're asking for it ♪
♪ Asking for a fight ♪
♪ I never guaranteed
a sweet goodbye ♪
♪ Use your eyes ♪
♪ 'Cause you had your last ♪
♪ Had your last good night ♪
♪ You won't be missing sleep ♪
♪ You'll be too busy
missing me ♪
♪ I'll show you what it's like
to live in a cage ♪
♪ You don't know ♪
♪ You don't know
how good it feels ♪
♪ To just walk away ♪
♪ From your lies,
cheats, and tricks ♪
♪ And your sweet dirty spells ♪
- ♪ You don't know ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
- ♪ No ♪
♪ Just how it feels ♪
♪ I'm gonna show ♪
♪ Show you just how I feel ♪
♪ I'm done pretending
you're all right ♪
♪ So tonight
I'll give you a piece ♪
♪ A piece of my mind ♪
♪ Now shut your pretty lips
and hold on tight ♪
♪ I won't lie ♪
♪ You won't enjoy this ♪
♪ Won't enjoy this ride ♪
♪ You won't be missing sleep ♪
♪ You'll be too busy
missing me ♪
♪ I'll show you what it's like
to live in a cage ♪
- ♪ You don't know ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
♪ You don't know ♪
♪ How good it feels
to just walk away ♪
♪ From all your lies,
cheats, and tricks ♪
♪ And your sweet dirty spells ♪
- ♪ You don't know ♪
- Dude, that's totally Amie!
♪ Just how it feels ♪
♪ I'm gonna show ♪
♪ I'll show you
what it's like to... ♪
Hey, guys, I think that's Amie!
- ♪ You don't know ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
♪ You don't know ♪
♪ How good it feels
to just walk away ♪
♪ From all your lies,
cheats, and tricks ♪
♪ And your sweet dirty spells ♪
- ♪ You don't know ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
- ♪ No ♪
♪ Just how it feels ♪
- ♪ I'm gonna show ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
- ♪ Show ♪
♪ You just how it feels ♪
Hey, Amie.
Sorry, I can't see a thing.
Who are you?
Dave Pearson.
Oh.
- I didn't recognize you with the makeup.
- Makeup. Right.
Um... I haven't seen you
since graduation.
- How-how ya doin'?
- Good.
Good.
Uh... you were
really... good.
Yeah, like the best.
- I didn't know you were in a band.
- Amie, we are late for curfew.
Uh...
I guess we're going now.
Bye.
Thanks for coming, man.
That's my brother.
Who's the other one?
I can't believe Dave
just saw me perform.
I know... Wait, that's the Dave
that you used to be
close with, right?
Weren't you, like, trying to
convince him to not do music?
- Yes.
- Guess he didn't listen.
Obviously, you didn't either.
Good thing, too.
Can we just go, please?
I guess we're going. Again.
Is this it?
It's the right address.
I don't know
about this. Um...
We could sleep in the van.
- Maybe they have breakfast.
- - Danny.
So, we don't have a TV.
Living the dream.
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- Listen, I'm sorry about earlier.
- What?
I'm-I'm sorry about earlier.
Oh, no, that's... It's all good.
I guess the, um...
the silver lining
of playing for tacos and...
staying in grungy motels in
the middle of nowhere is, um...
you get to see the stars.
Amie, you were so... Like,
you never spoke in class,
and all of a sudden,
you're this rock star.
Why does that make you smiley?
'Cause that's great... I mean,
when did that happen?
Um, like two years ago.
Two years? Seriously?
Yeah, Charlie convinced me, I...
So, then, Mr. Boyfriend knew,
huh?
No. He didn't.
Really?
Yeah, he would have
made my life miserable.
Telling you your dreams
aren't worth it
and maybe you shouldn't
follow your passion?
- Can we not talk about ex-boyfriends...
- Yeah, yeah.
- Girlfriends, any of that...
- We don't have to... Yeah.
What do you want to talk about?
Um...
What's your favorite
classic movie?
Whoa. Okay.
Uh...
Oh! Jurassic Park.
A hundred percent,
Jurassic Park.
The old one, right?
- What?
- The old one.
There's a new one?
- Yes.
- No.
- You haven't seen it?
- No!
- It's pretty good.
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is.
- No.
- Oh, okay. All right.
Speaking of which,
- have you seen our van?
- Yes, I have.
- You've seen this van?
- Yes, I saw it in the parking lot.
- But have you seen it with the new decal?
- Wow.
No, I have not seen this.
Whose is this?
- Uh, that's Joe's.
- Classic.
- What do you mean, "classic"?
- It just would be Joe's. I don't know.
Could be mine. So are you
living in a single, too?
No. We've got
a double queen in the room.
We're literally
sleeping in the same bed.
No. No.
I actually woke up with Joe's...
You don't wanna...
On my face.
- So, I...
- Do you remember?
Do you remember?
Do you?
Yes. Of course.
Yeah. See?
- You had it.
- Still got it.
Well, on that note,
sweet dreams.
See ya.
Now who's late for curfew?
- Tell us everything.
- Everything.
Um...
I don't know.
That bed was terrible.
Between your elbows in my face,
and the broken spring...
Cockroaches?
We should've slept in the van.
Guys, I can't believe
how well that show went.
I know, but that motel sucked.
I mean, at least
they had mints, right?
Lucy, I don't think
that's a mint.
Oh, my...
What is that ridiculous
smile on your face?
Me? What?
Considering where
we just stayed the night,
you're looking awfully smiley.
- I smell like an ashtray.
- Me, too.
- Why didn't you shower?
- I did shower.
- You showered in there?
- It was not that bad.
Okay, you were barely there.
No, I just... I couldn't...
I couldn't sleep,
so I just went out
and got some fresh air.
Oh, so that's her name?
What? Amie?
I knew it. I knew it.
Oh, look at you.
If he hurts you,
I will destroy him.
We will destroy him.
Got it?
Bye.
Hey, honey. How are you?
- I'm good.
- Are you tired?
Oh, yeah.
- Oh, hi.
- Look at him.
He missed you. Him sad.
So, how was it?
Tell me all about it.
- It was really good.
- Was it fun?
- It was really, really good.
- It was a good time?
- We played for four hours.
- Four hours.
- Yeah.
- That's a long time to play, isn't it?
- Wow.
Everybody was, like,
jogging at first,
not really paying attention,
but then, like, nearing the end,
like, people really started
paying attention
and, like, dancing and,
like, going up to the stage
and like...
I don't know, I thought I saw
some people singing along...
They're like your fans.
No, I mean, we have people
who like our music.
- Your band has fans.
- No, we don't have fans.
- You do. I'm your fan.
- You're my mom.
- I'm your fan.
I know. How did
the other boys like it?
Joe, actually,
was really good this time.
- Joe plays drums.
- Yeah.
Joe's the drummer.
Danny plays guitar.
No. Danny plays bass.
I'm guitar.
They're guitars.
They're both guitars to me.
- Um, how was the hotel?
- Nasty.
It wasn't even a hotel.
It was like a motel.
- Really?
- Like-like...
I mean, that's how we got paid.
That and tacos.
I'm sorry.
It won't always be
nasty motels and tacos.
I promise you.
Is this your, uh, dirty laundry?
Yeah.
Take it to the laundry room
instead of here on the counter.
Yes. Sorry.
Oh... Look at you guys
Clark Kenting it.
You really just gotta own it.
I do, just...
not in front of Amie's mom.
Yeah, well, with me,
she gets what she gets.
Besides, your mom loves me.
She does love me, right?
Yeah.
All right. Let's go.
Do not say a word.
I'm home.
- Hi.
- Hey, Mom.
Hi, Nikki.
So, how was the college visit?
Went really well.
It was good.
Oh, I wanted to remind you to bake
the cupcakes for the bake sale.
- Yes. Yeah.
- It's just that the volunteer hours
are so important for
the scholarship applications.
Yes. Um, thank you.
Right, Lucy?
Yeah.
College is...
It's-it's so important.
Yeah. It is.
Charlie, I didn't know
you were back already.
Yeah, I came in a day early.
Um, we're gonna go to my room,
but I love you.
- Good to see you.
- Bye.
- Hey.
Hi.
So, uh, any idea
what time it is?
No, but I know I'm early.
- It's 12:30.
- Whoa! Geez.
You're the only person I know
who can be late
from the parking lot.
Yeah. It's a gift, really.
Hmm. So...
Oh, yeah! Okay.
You got it. Yep.
What about your...
It's okay. I can do this.
Okay.
Oh! That's interesting.
Hi, uh, welcome to Cinema 10.
How can I help you?
Okay. I've got table six,
large supreme, hold the pep.
Table six, large supreme,
hold the pep. You got it.
Coming right up.
I'm sorry.
- Tonya, I'm sorry...
- It's Taylor.
Taylor, right, uh...
Taylor, sorry.
- Um...
- It's okay.
I just...
ooh, had a late night.
Nice of you to join us.
Where were you?
I didn't realize it would be
this busy on a Tuesday.
Didn't you get Dad's text?
The tournaments are in town.
You're late.
Hey, Sparky, you got that pie
for table three for me yet?
What'd you just call me?
New nickname thing
I'm trying out.
I don't know if you know
what the Color Dash 5K is,
- but it's like this huge...
- Dave.
- Yes.
- Stop wasting your time.
- Ooh, Peppy Joe. Lana, Sam...
- No.
What about Nitro?
- Why? - 'Cause your
kinda cool and smooth.
Oh, okay. Okay.
I like that one.
Can't pay your rent on tacos.
Dude.
Look at my best friends
waiting for me.
I thought you were
at the mechanic.
Did that just backfire?
Are we gonna practice or what?
Shotgun!
What's the first thing
on the agenda?
Our paperwork was received
at Battle of the Bands.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Also, the girls are competing.
We're not taking it
easy on them.
What? No.
Nobody said that.
That's not what
I'm worried about.
What are you worried about?
Half Past Midnight.
Yeah, they're competing.
What? Half Past Midnight cannot
play at Battle of the Bands.
- That's unfair.
- I know.
They've won the last three years
in a row.
If we don't step up our game,
that's gonna be...
I'm not scared of them.
We've worked way too hard
for them to beat us.
Whoa. Okay. Where did
this Danny come from?
Man, I'm done
scooping ice cream!
You know if I quit, we
don't get free pizza, right?
- That's like all we eat.
- Yeah, but if we win,
then we can afford pizza.
- I second that idea. All right.
- We have to kill it.
We have to make sure we get
a spot on The Warped Tour.
You know what? I second that, too.
Do we have a third?
- We have a third.
- All right. We've all hit me.
Second: mail.
Mail.
Give me a record deal.
"We regret to inform you..."
I want an agent.
No, this is life insurance.
"You need to work
on your charisma."
"Dear Summertime Dropouts,
you're not good enough."
You know what, we'll just...
We'll just build our stage on rejection
letters. That's what we'll do.
They can tell us no
as many times as they want to,
but we're not giving up.
- Hey, Joe.
- Yeah.
Do your magical free pizza
powers apply to delivery?
Of course.
Guys! That was
a moment. Like...
"They're not gonna
tell us no." Song.
Like... band. We get together.
We play songs...
You didn't feel that?
- No.
- What?
Just, can we practice, please?
Yeah.
♪ You waltzed in
right through my front door ♪
♪ Your arrogance is amusing ♪
♪ And that smirk on your face ♪
♪ Was just what
I was looking for ♪
♪ When everybody's
in their seats ready to go ♪
♪ I'm gonna light you up,
I'm 'bout to put on a show ♪
♪ Show me
what's the best you got ♪
♪ 'Cause when it rains,
it pours ♪
♪ We don't stop ♪
♪ With the cameras rollin',
flashes blowin' up ♪
♪ Fists start to fly,
'cause we can't control 'em ♪
♪ Better zip your lip, kid,
and watch your mouth ♪
♪ Or you might get a taste ♪
♪ Of the left-right-left,
lights out ♪
♪ Oh, no, like a k-money anthem,
this place about to blow ♪
♪ 'Cause it's one for the
money and two for the show ♪
♪ Three, you're not ready,
and four, you're too slow ♪
Just ask each other questions.
- What? Are you okay?
- No, I am unwell.
No, I mean, do whatever, just...
Let's just ask each other the first
question that comes to your mind.
Okay,
if you had to do
something other than music,
what would it be?
- Graphic design.
- Veterinarian.
Amie, you're allergic to cats.
- You physically cannot do that.
- Can you imagine?
It would just be
a constant sneeze attack.
Wow.
What about you?
If I had to do something
other than music?
- Yes.
- I...
There... I don't think
there's anything else.
What? It was your question.
I know, but honestly
I don't think I'd be happy
- doing anything else.
- Touché.
Well, I guess you have
to make it happen.
I will. We will.
We will. You're right.
Do you guys wanna add more?
- Absolutely.
- Look at her heart.
- It got painted over.
- Oh, yeah, we have to redo it.
- Redo the...
- We must mark our territory.
Check the Battle website.
Competing bands.
- Wait, wait, what's this right here?
- What?
Kevin Lyman.
"It will be bittersweet
each morning
when I see the sunrise
and then watch it set."
Wait.
- Um...
- Stop, stop, stop, stop.
"The enduring spirit
of the Vans Warped Tour
remains as bright as ever, continuing
to inspire creativity and ambition
in new and exciting ways
as we prepare for a 25th
anniversary celebration."
"We truly look forward to seeing
as many of you as possible
during this final
cross-country run.
Thank you for your support
on this wild adventure.
Until then,
take care and be safe.
Kevin Lyman, Founder
of the Vans Warped Tour."
They're canceling Warped Tour.
Those are very black.
I'm putting
pink glitter on them.
Please do not
disturb my process.
You know, the only shame is
that you won't be there to see
when all the kids' teeth
turn black.
I didn't think about that.
- Um, no, Charlie, no.
- This is Charlie.
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
Can you just...
Hi, Charlie. Um, sorry,
I thought this was Amie's phone.
It is. Hi.
Hey, uh, so,
did you guys hear?
Hear what?
They're canceling
The Warped Tour.
So this is the last chance we're
gonna have to play on The Warped Tour.
- Can I help you with that pink glitter?
- Yes, please.
- Awesome.
- Please do.
You know, the-the warped zoo.
Hello?
They took that well.
Metalheads, riot
girls and punks,
what's up
and welcome to the finals
of The Battle of Bands:
Warped Tour Edition.
Each band tonight will be judged
and scored on multiple categories.
The band with the highest
overall score
will go on to join
the infamous Warped Tour.
So, bands, it's your moment.
Get out there
and rock the stage.
Give it up!
Hey.
All good?
Smells like a winner.
They'll call you
when you're next.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
- Cool.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I want you
to keep it clean, boys.
- Understand?
- Sure.
That means anybody
breaches the rules,
you will be disqualified.
- Got it?
- Disqualified.
- Yeah, got it.
- No kids here.
Thank you, guys!
No tolerance!
- Okay, yes.
- You got that?
- Yeah.
- Bet you do. Let's go.
The next show, Warped Tour,
we get this big intro
before the show.
Stage opens up,
kit comes outta the floor.
And then it turns upside down.
- Yes! Yes!
- I've seen that video. That's so tight.
Come on, give me.
- Take it to the bank!
- Hey, guys, look.
The high schoolers
are out to play tonight.
Well, you know,
we graduated, Brent, so...
Oh, congratulations.
Thanks.
Hey, uh, where's your guys'
merch table at?
I could use a t-shirt. The
bathroom's outta toilet paper.
- Oh.
- Nice.
Those guys are losers.
Why do I hate them so much?
'Cause their music's amazing,
girls love them,
and they have merch.
Danny!
♪ Look at all these cats ♪
♪ What's with all these cats? ♪
♪ These scratches make scars,
but they first bleed ♪
♪ There's too many paws ♪
♪ Look at all these paws ♪
♪ Look at all these cats ♪
♪ These scratches make scars ♪
♪ It's time to change the box ♪
♪ Yes cats, no cats ♪
♪ Look at all these cats ♪
♪ Too much poop. ♪
- Uh...
- Meow.
Scary kitty.
Taking the stage next
is Summertime Dropouts!
Uh, hi, um...
We're Summertime Dropouts
and we wrote this song recently.
♪ Monday morning,
here we go again ♪
♪ Let the five day
melodrama games begin ♪
- ♪ Gossip ♪
- ♪ Boring ♪
- ♪ Scandal ♪
- ♪ Snoring ♪
♪ Facebook statuses
and made up stories ♪
♪ She doesn't care
what the backstabbers say ♪
♪ 'Cause they're
neck deep swimming ♪
♪ In their insecurity ♪
♪ Popularity contests
are overrated ♪
♪ And she's not afraid
to say it ♪
♪ She'll never be
the prom queen ♪
♪ She's got one too many
tattoos and a lip ring ♪
♪ She won't swim
the mainstream ♪
♪ And it doesn't even matter ♪
♪ Everybody likes her
better that way ♪
♪ She doesn't care
what Brad Pitt is up to ♪
♪ She'd rather lose herself
in her bright pink guitar ♪
♪ And so far ♪
♪ She's a full time cutie ♪
♪ And a part-time rockstar ♪
♪ Same old story,
take a look around ♪
♪ Mr. Rooney's got his hands
on the school board now ♪
- ♪ Cameron ♪
- ♪ Faded ♪
- ♪ Bueller ♪
- ♪ Made it ♪
♪ Biff's still living
in his mom and dad's basement ♪
♪ Try not to laugh
at the end of the day ♪
♪ It's an Oscar-nominated
action comedy ♪
♪ When they meet up
in ten years ♪
♪ And swear they're happy ♪
♪ She'll be showing off
her Grammy ♪
♪ She'll never be
the prom queen ♪
♪ She's got one too many
tattoos and a lip ring ♪
♪ She won't swim
the mainstream ♪
♪ And it doesn't even matter ♪
♪ Everybody likes her
better that way ♪
♪ She doesn't care
what Brad Pitt is up to ♪
♪ She'd rather lose herself
in her bright pink guitar ♪
♪ And so far ♪
♪ She's a full time cutie
and a part-time rockstar ♪
♪ She'll never be
the prom queen ♪
♪ She's got one too many
tattoos and a lip ring ♪
♪ She won't swim
the mainstream ♪
♪ And it doesn't even matter ♪
♪ Everybody likes her
better that way ♪
♪ She doesn't care
what Brad Pitt is up to ♪
♪ She'd rather lose herself
in her bright pink guitar ♪
♪ And so far ♪
♪ She's a full time cutie
and a part-time rockstar. ♪
Oh, I wanna do that
every day forever.
Up next,
we've got Late For Curfew.
Let's go, give it up!
Have fun.
♪ I'm waking up ♪
♪ The clock hits 7:00,
but I'm not standing ♪
♪ I'd rather jump and sing ♪
♪ Than wait in my daydreams ♪
♪ I kick down the doors ♪
♪ The lights are beaming,
for me they're screaming ♪
♪ I'll teach the world to see ♪
♪ That there's no stopping me ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ And now I'm ♪
♪ I'm breaking out
of faking me ♪
♪ I'll never try
to chain my mind ♪
♪ In the spaces in between ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I'll shed these lies
and sing my dreams ♪
♪ The truth sometime
will the walk the line ♪
♪ I'm finally feeling free ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I shouldn't speak ♪
♪ Or so they told me ♪
♪ When I was only
a pretty pink 13 ♪
- ♪ A perfect beauty queen ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ I found my voice ♪
♪ They couldn't hold her,
she's getting older ♪
♪ Brighter than before ♪
♪ Won't hold back anymore ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I'm breaking out
of faking me ♪
♪ I never tried
to chain my mind ♪
♪ In the spaces in between ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I'll shed these lies
and sing my dreams ♪
♪ The truth sometime
will walk the line ♪
♪ I'm finally feeling free ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I've always had to bend
and break and learn to fake ♪
♪ To fit inside these lines ♪
♪ They drew in sand,
won't even say why ♪
♪ But all this pain
I've had to hold ♪
♪ Won't drain me cold ♪
♪ It only lights a fire ♪
♪ So wild and pure,
it can't ever die ♪
♪ I won't let it die ♪
♪ I'm breaking out
of faking me ♪
♪ I never tried
to chain my mind ♪
♪ In the spaces in between ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I'll shed these lies
and sing my dreams ♪
♪ The truth sometime
will walk the line ♪
♪ I'm finally feeling free ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I'll shed these lies
and sing my dreams ♪
♪ The truth sometime
will walk the line ♪
♪ I'm finally feeling free ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I'm not sorry. ♪
You guys crushed it.
- Yeah.
- It was really good, yeah.
- Thanks.
- Cool.
You guys were good, too.
- Thanks.
- Sweet.
Uh, we just wrote...
three-time
defending Battle champs,
Half Past Midnight.
Let's give it up!
♪ I know
there's no time for me ♪
♪ Now that I'm lost
inside you ♪
♪ You know
there's no time for you ♪
♪ I've got nothing to prove ♪
♪ And I know that I was made ♪
♪ For something
better than this ♪
- ♪ I'm not gonna wait
for tomorrow ♪ - ♪ No ♪
- ♪ I'm gonna seize the day ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm gonna pick up
the pieces ♪
♪ Waiting all around
and I wanna start with me ♪
♪ I can see right through ♪
♪ The cause
of my hologram heart ♪
♪ Songs that I made for you ♪
♪ It sounds like a flood
and I'm coming unglued ♪
- They're amazing.
- What?
They're amazing!
♪ I won't hold it against you ♪
♪ I know you're thinking
this isn't the end ♪
♪ But I've become
one with the silence ♪
♪ So just stop
using your mouth ♪
♪ Your words mean nothing ♪
- ♪ I'm not gonna wait
for tomorrow ♪ - ♪ No ♪
- ♪ I'm gonna seize the day ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm gonna
pick up the pieces ♪
♪ Waiting all around
and I wanna start with me ♪
♪ I can see right through ♪
♪ The cause
of my hologram heart ♪
♪ Songs that I made for you ♪
♪ It sounds like a flood
and I'm coming unglued ♪
- ♪ I'm not gonna wait
for tomorrow ♪ - ♪ No ♪
- ♪ I'm gonna seize the day ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm gonna
pick up the pieces ♪
♪ Waiting all around
and I wanna start with me ♪
♪ I can see right through ♪
♪ The cause
of my hologram heart ♪
♪ Songs that I made for you ♪
♪ It sounds like a flood
and I'm coming unglued. ♪
All right, guys.
All of you bands did
absolutely amazing tonight.
But only one of you gets to take
the final spot on The Warped Tour,
and the results are in.
This year's winner
of The Battle of the Bands:
Warped Tour Edition is...
For the fourth time in a row,
Half Past Midnight!
Give it up for 'em.
Come on up here.
All right!
Nice work, guys.
Nice work.
Go ahead and give 'em a bow.
We'll see you at Warped Tour!
Yeah!
Give it up!
You guys were awesome.
Yeah, you were too.
You were really, really good.
I, uh, I liked your song.
Yeah, it was super subtle.
Actually, Danny's the one who came
up with the pink guitar line, so...
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, I've always wanted one.
You can borrow mine
whenever you want.
You should've called it
"We'll work for tacos."
Wouldn't be lying.
Um, how about we go get some pizza?
A slice or two?
Um, I have an interview
in the morning.
I should probably
get some sleep.
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm kinda tired.
- I just wanna go home.
- Oh, hey, hey, hey.
- Didn't I say to break this up? Let's go.
- Yeah, sorry.
- Sorry.
- Let's go, out.
- We're going.
- I know you guys have a date. Let's go, keep on.
- Charlie, you have my keys?
- - Yes.
- Uh, hey, Amie?
- You're a winner.
- Um...
- Yeah?
Sorry, can I just talk to you
for a second, just real quick?
- Sure.
- I have to get back, too.
- Um, uh...
- What?
I was just...
wondering if maybe you wanted
to go out just the two of us?
Um, I...
Uh, I don't know.
I just... I can't.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay, no, that's...
- Maybe another time, though.
- Yeah.
- Hey, you're a winner.
- Thank you.
It's okay. You're a
winner in my book.
- Appreciate it.
- Have a good night.
I know I should be sad...
but, Charlie...
Yeah.
You know, it's probably
not a good idea
for you guys to date members
of a competing band.
Don't be silly.
There's gum on my bucket.
You guys dare me to eat it?
- No.
Fine, I dare myself.
They don't call me "Double
Dog Dan" for nothing.
- Nobody calls you "Double Dog Dan."
- No one calls you that.
Guys, all great bands have
been rejected at some point.
It's like a rite of passage.
Yeah, I get it,
but we didn't get in.
I just... I don't think
that's such a big deal.
I think we can still play
small shows around here.
We don't have to give up.
Yes, we can play small shows
and build our fan base.
Yes, exactly.
Guys, we gave it our best
shot and that wasn't enough.
Okay, but Warped Tour
was never the end goal.
Like, yes, of course
it would've been nice,
- but we don't need it.
- Yeah, I don't think we do.
So, that song...
Who could possibly be
the full-time cutie?
- Hey, Joe?
- Yeah?
How much gas do we have left?
- Enough, why?
- That was our exit.
"Vans Warped Tour."
Is that like the shoes?
Vans shoes?
Why is it "warped"?
- That's what I wanna know.
- Vans, they must be...
I also wanna know
what time it is. Where is he?
Hey, speak of the devil!
- Hey, congratulations.
- Congratulations.
We got tickets.
Do you have three
so I can go with you?
- What? What happened?
- What?
What?
We, um...
We didn't get it.
Well, there's next year.
No, this was
the last Warped Tour, so...
It's the last tour ever?
I mean, come on.
It's not, like, about the tour.
It's just... it's just
that they didn't want us.
I feel like I have
the best band in the world...
- and nobody cares.
- Honey...
you can't tell me that
there won't be other venues
and other tours to play on.
Your opportunities
are only limited
by your hard work
and your will. Right?
Come on.
Knuckle it up.
Come on, knuckles.
Dad, it's really weird
when you do it.
No, no, it's not.
Hey, how'd the battle
go last night?
Do I need to find
your replacement?
Didn't make it.
Told you.
Look, Danny,
I'm sorry I came down
on you so hard.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I know you're really bummed
'cause things didn't
work out for you, but...
maybe it's time
to... be realistic.
Not everyone can be an artist.
There are gonna be a lot
more opportunities, Dad.
Hey.
You guys really killed it.
Yeah, yeah, we did.
Sorry you didn't make it.
No, it's fine. We're, um...
We're getting back on track.
It's... it's gonna be fine.
Hey, I mean,
worst case scenario,
you can always work at Nick's.
I already work at Nick's.
Yeah.
You're gonna make it.
Hey, I was doing some research.
Uh, we're so close
to Minneapolis,
we should play at The Garage.
Anybody who's anybody
goes through there.
- Okay, that sounds good.
- How soon can we book it?
Also, do you
have any fruit snacks?
I got pretzels,
these cheese things,
- and marshmallows.
- Marshmallows.
Good choice.
Pretty soon, I'm just waiting
to hear back from them.
He loves to make you wait.
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
Oh, wow.
Oh, look what
the cat dragged in.
You live here?
Yeah.
What's up, weirdos?
Uh, we're just doing
some official band stuff
around the neighborhood and so...
Yeah, merch, building our brand.
Super professional.
Getting a huge SD
on our wall as well.
Oh, sounds major.
Do you guys wanna take a break
from your band business?
- Official...
- Sorry, official.
No, we'll like...
We won't bother you guys.
- I mean, I could use a break.
- Same.
Oh, I mean, yeah, we could
totally grab some food.
Yeah, I could eat.
Did you guys know that cats
only meow to mimic humans?
- Danny.
Ew.
Yeah, uh, is that street legal?
Yeah, it's street legal.
Don't worry about that.
That's all the usual stuff.
I am so impressed.
It smells like
high-grade diesel.
I wish it was high-grade diesel.
Thank you.
Um, no, I mean, like...
'Cause if you're asking
about my life plans...
No, I wanna know, like, college
or are you staying here?
Well, you know, I actually
have it all planned out.
- Who made your t-shirts?
- Oh, I did.
I was taking this online
graphics course,
- and I've gotten pretty good at it.
- What?
Really good?
More like really awesome.
- Uh, thank you.
- Yeah.
- Uh, awesome.
- Hey, so, you just moved here?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'm from St. Paul.
- Okay.
Yeah, I convinced my dad
to get a job here.
I think... I don't know,
I think we could do something.
And I don't know if I'm ever
gonna meet these guys again.
And so, like, you live
across the street from Dave?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm there, like, all the time.
Cool.
Like, in college, you know,
I could keep up music, sure,
- but I don't know if I'd ever...
- Yeah, I don't know.
I think maybe
that's not a bad idea.
You know, we wanna start
printing shirts soon.
You should totally
design our graphic.
The guys would love that.
- Oh, my God, I'd love to.
- Really?
- I'd be honored, yeah.
- Yeah!
Friendship.
- From my grandfather.
- Really?
Yeah.
- I think right now...
- Guys, guys!
- We made the cover!
- What?
- Look!
- Wait, let me see this.
- You look awesome!
- Ooh, that's us!
Wait, wait, wait.
"Danny Green, Dave Pearson,
and Joe Seifus take time..."
Does it say my name?
Look at your cute little face.
- Take this.
- Yeah, yeah, no, no.
- Take that.
- We have to take this.
- Put it in the van.
- God, that's sick!
Guys...
My mom is literally
gonna kill me.
You coming?
Uh, yeah.
Hi.
You skipped our Iowa State trip.
No, I... I went.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
I played a show on the way back.
So you toured the classrooms?
And you ate lunch
in the cafeteria?
I saw the outside.
So you buzzed through the parking
lot, and you staged a photo
so that you could lie to me?
I wasn't lying.
Why?
'Cause if I told you,
you would...
- Because I would say no!
- Yeah.
Because we planned this.
Because we've... we planned this.
I know.
Mom, I-I know we planned this.
I know that.
But this...
this is what I wanna do.
And I'm really good at it.
You're acting like you
haven't lied before.
This isn't about me.
And I would not lie to you.
It's been you and me, and
that means something to me.
- And I thought I could count on that.
- You can.
Okay, um...
So you're a musician.
I mean, like,
you're a famous musician,
like, you've made it.
But...
the only thing you can play...
is covers of commercial jingles.
- No, no.
- No?
Yes.
- What? Seriously?
- I mean, okay.
So you can tell
the truth all the time,
- but nobody believes you.
- No, that sucks.
- I can't do that.
- Yes.
Are you just saying yes
to everything?
No, that's my everyday life.
And I love commercial jingles,
they're super catchy.
But more importantly,
if you were given a trough
of ice cream on your birthday,
but the only thing
you could do is bathe in it,
would you be happy or sad?
- Hi.
Um, is Amie home?
She hasn't responded to us.
Yep, she's in her room.
Great.
I can't keep lying to my mom.
It's just the two of us
and she's depending on me.
So...
you're gonna let your mom
crush our dream?
- No, no, no, let me talk to her...
- No, Charlie, stay out of it.
Lucy, do you have anything
to say about this?
Cool, am I the only one here
- who cares at all about this band?
- Are you kidding me?
I wouldn't be lying to my mom
for this long if I didn't care.
I just can't keep
doing this to her.
"Doing this to her"? I'm sorry,
when has she ever put you first?
Seriously?
Lucy, what's up?
Why are you being so quiet?
I got an internship.
What?
You're kidding.
My interview was the day
after Battle of the Bands.
What if we made Warped Tour?
I told my parents
that, if we made Warped Tour,
that I'd cancel the internship.
But the deal was, if we
didn't, then I'd take it.
And-and you just...
You forgot to tell us?
I thought we were
gonna go on tour.
I thought it was gonna be great
and nothing would interfere.
Guys, I really thought
we were gonna make it.
Wow.
When are you leaving?
Tomorrow.
Guys, I didn't mean to hurt you.
You guys know my family
moved here for you, right?
For the band?
You don't even care?
Can you stop thinking about
yourself for one second?
You're not even listening to us.
- I can't believe you guys.
- Charlie, come on.
Charlie!
Hey, Charlie.
Charlie, hey.
- Hey, you good?
- I'm fine.
Okay, what's going on?
You are the last person
in the world
I would talk to about this!
Hey, there, stranger.
Hey! What are you
doing here?
I could really go for a scoop
of strawberry ice cream.
Oh, you got it.
How you gonna pay for this?
What? No way!
All yours.
Lucy, this is amazing.
Yeah, I got
the lightning bolt in there.
Wow.
Is that a birthday Husky?
Oh, yeah.
Awesome!
Do you want my advice?
- No.
- Okay.
But what is it?
Your mom is your mom,
like, that's just...
It's really tough, but...
they're your band. You know,
like, they're your friends and...
I don't know, I think
you gotta talk to them.
I did.
Right, I know you did, but...
I mean, to be honest, I-I saw
Charlie after you talked to them,
and I think you need to talk
to them again, because...
They're not gonna listen.
- What do you mean?
- They don't get it that...
- Okay, but you can...
- They're not listening.
- I-I'm listening.
- No, you're not.
You're trying to fix it.
And I don't need you to fix it.
I need you to listen to me.
I'm trying, okay?
I know.
I really appreciate you trying.
I just can't have
this conversation.
I'm sorry.
I don't think Amie understands.
Like, yes, we wrote
all the songs together,
and we've always performed
together as a band,
but, like, without her,
there is no band.
She's literally the lead singer.
I mean, am I crazy?
I feel crazy. You would tell
me if I'm being crazy, right?
I mean, but they are
your friends.
I know.
I know, I know
they're my friends, but...
Look, you'll figure it out.
Just give them some space,
give yourself some space and...
Is that your lady friend?
I'm hoping
you're my lady friend.
- You have, um, you have...
- What?
- I got it.
- Oh.
Oh, there it is.
Make a wish.
- What did you wish for?
- It's a secret.
Cool.
So, I'll-I'll see you later.
Yeah.
Sweet.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Bye.
- Hi.
- Hey, there.
I honestly thought
you guys were gonna let me go
without saying goodbye.
No.
I'm still mad at you,
but I wouldn't do that.
I'm so proud of our little baby.
All grown up.
Are we good?
Maybe.
Come here.
I can't believe Lucy made this.
This is ridiculous.
Oh, my.
Huh, huh.
What in the world
are you boys up to?
We're trying to make shirts.
Oh.
Sweetie, what is
that design supposed to be?
There it is.
Yeah, nice job.
- Thanks for the lemonade.
- Oh, sure!
♪ I'm breaking out
of faking me ♪
♪ I never tried
to chain my mind ♪
♪ In the spaces in between ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
Wait, hold on, sorry. I don't
remember what she did there.
- Um...
- I think it's... Yeah.
That sounds weird, um...
That wasn't it.
Uh...
- Yeah.
- All right, cool.
- Let's just go with that.
♪ I'll shed these lies
and sing my dreams ♪
This isn't gonna work.
No.
Can I sit here?
As long as we
don't have to talk.
You wanna get out of here?
Yeah.
♪ I'm trying to pick up
where I left off ♪
♪ Maybe I've burned
my bridges ♪
♪ Lost in flames ♪
♪ And I've been thinking
a lot about this life ♪
♪ And about that road ♪
♪ That I won't let
another summer win ♪
♪ No, I won't let
♪ This town hasn't been
the same, anyway ♪
♪ Since I've taken
my chances on you ♪
♪ Now all the stars,
they'll align ♪
♪ When I look into your...
never mind ♪
♪ So take my hand ♪
♪ Don't let
another moment pass ♪
♪ But it's late and I
might need some time alone ♪
♪ But I don't wanna go home ♪
♪ I don't wanna grow up ♪
♪ But I do want to walk
the stars with you ♪
♪ Let's not give up ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Now my thoughts
are running wild ♪
♪ In my mind like a riptide ♪
♪ Trying to hide it ♪
♪ Don't think I can share them
with you or anyone ♪
♪ I could leave this town ♪
♪ But I'd leave
my friends behind ♪
♪ And the people
who are more than friends ♪
What are you doing?
Just wanna remember.
♪ So take my hand ♪
♪ Don't let
another moment pass ♪
♪ I know it's late, but maybe ♪
♪ This was meant to last ♪
♪ I don't wanna go home ♪
♪ And I don't wanna grow up ♪
♪ But I do want to ♪
♪ Walk the stars with you ♪
♪ Let's not give up ♪
♪ Up ♪
Hey, guys.
What's up, my little dove birds?
- What's the problem?
- Excuse me.
- Ow.
- All right, you guys.
- Bro, oh, don't!
- No.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Hello.
- Hi.
We thought we'd just have
a little sit down with y'all.
We know how much the show meant
to all of you.
And with it coming up,
there's probably not a chance
you're gonna get on that stage.
It's really too bad, too.
I mean, those Warped Tour
people are never gonna see
what they're missing out on.
Or will they?
What are you talking about?
Yeah, what do you mean?
If you can't get
on the Warped Tour stage...
build your own.
Wait, I'm liking
where you're going.
Yeah, well, I have this client
who has a very big parking space
that happens to be right across
from where the Warped Tour plays.
Pretty sure I can get them
to sponsor you.
We'd bring the Summertime
to them.
We would play there,
and then everyone who was
walking by would have to...
- walk by us.
- Yes, I love it!
Wait, that's brilliant.
Warped Tour, here we come.
Anybody gonna eat that?
- No, Danny, it's all yours...
- Yes, I was...
- I was going to.
- - Oh, well, I gave it to Danny.
What do you think?
What do you think of that?
If it's like a...
- Right?
- It's okay,
but it should go up
on the second riff.
Play it.
Yeah.
- That's good.
- Yeah, that's better.
- Yeah.
- That is good.
It's better than what you wrote.
True.
Why don't you play with us?
Like, as a part of Summertime?
Yeah, you should.
Okay, we all know they should,
so is it a yes or no?
Amie?
Could you come sit?
What's up?
I've been thinking
a lot about what you said.
And I...
I... I wanted
to show you this.
What is this?
- You were in a band?
- I was.
Why haven't you told me this?
It's a... different life.
When I was your age,
I met this really great guy,
and we played music
and we were good.
And a promoter heard us
and we started touring.
It was like
this great adventure,
and then it ended.
What happened?
Well, we had you.
So I ruined your career?
No.
No, you were the best thing
that I got out of my career.
But the industry's really hard.
And I watched it...
really chew up
a lot of my friends.
It's a hard life and I wanted
something better than that for you.
And I want you to be happy.
But I am.
I'm really happy.
Your father gave me that
our first paid gig.
- This?
- Yeah.
- Can I borrow it?
- You can have it.
We have a show coming up.
I really want you to be there.
- Mom.
- Oh, hey, hun.
Hey, what's up?
We're about to perform.
I know.
It's so exciting.
What are you doing?
Um, just getting the word out
about the show online.
- Ooh, smart.
- Yep.
- I already have 36 retweets.
- Oh, oh.
We know all the real bands
have merch.
This is so cool.
No, no, they're not.
But these? These are cool.
What? No, Dad, come on.
Are you serious?
Yes, yes.
How did you...
How did you do this?
It's Lucy's design.
Thank you, thank you.
♪ I know
there's no time for me ♪
♪ Now that
I'm lost inside you ♪
So we didn't quite make it
to Warped Tour.
But this is really cool.
Yo, what's up, guys?
This is you boy Cash Baker.
Hey, guys, what is up?
It's Olivia Ooms here.
Hey, guys, it's Alex Hager.
What's up, guys?
Jason Stacks here.
What's up, you guys?
- I'm Joe Waud.
- I'm Jason Waud.
And we're the Waud twins.
What's up, guys?
It's Grant Knoche.
So, right now
I'm at The Warped Tour.
You guys already know
how much I love pop punk.
I'm at Warped Tour right now
and there's this new band
called Summertime Dropouts.
And they're performing
outside The Warped Tour.
They rock.
- This is literally crazy.
- It's crazy out here.
My Snapchat and Instagram
is blowing up.
My new favorite band,
Summertime Dropouts.
They're playing right now.
Go check 'em out.
I'm gonna go, but you guys
should definitely come with me.
I'll see you guys there, okay?
Let's go check it out.
I'm gonna go check them out. If
y'all are here, come meet me.
- ♪ Hey ♪ - ♪ We're not
gonna wait for tomorrow ♪
- ♪ Hey ♪
- ♪ I'm gonna seize the day ♪
♪ I'm gonna
pick up the pieces ♪
♪ Waiting all around
and I wanna start with me ♪
♪ I can see right through ♪
♪ The cause
of my hologram heart ♪
♪ Songs that I made for you ♪
♪ It sounds like a flood
and I'm coming unglued. ♪
♪ Another jam packed day ♪
♪ Of everybody on the planet ♪
♪ Telling me to cram it ♪
♪ Telling me I'm not okay ♪
♪ Another troubled
little failure ♪
♪ Dangerous behavior ♪
♪ Why can't they just behave? ♪
♪ Another silly little misfit
trying to be different ♪
♪ Look at the clothes
they wear ♪
♪ The definition
of an outcast ♪
♪ Bottom on the cool graph ♪
♪ Skinny jeans and pink hair ♪
♪ I know that I might be
a little bit overwhelming ♪
♪ And I know that you
think something must be wrong ♪
♪ Inside my head ♪
♪ Let go ♪
♪ I'm gonna chase my dreams ♪
♪ And pray for a happy ending ♪
♪ You can take me or leave me ♪
♪ Just the way I,
just the way I am ♪
♪ They say I might be sick ♪
♪ A psychological condition ♪
♪ Typical musician ♪
♪ Doesn't want
to fall in line ♪
♪ Another sticky situation ♪
♪ Insubordination,
keep it contained this time ♪
♪ A personality disorder ♪
♪ Put him in the corner ♪
♪ Hook 'em on the dollar sign ♪
♪ We'll tell him money
is the answer ♪
♪ Music is a cancer ♪
♪ Prove it all onDateline ♪
♪ I know that I might be
a little bit overwhelming ♪
♪ And I know that you think
something must be wrong ♪
♪ Inside my head ♪
♪ Let go ♪
♪ I'm gonna chase my dreams ♪
♪ And pray for a happy ending ♪
♪ You can take me or leave me ♪
♪ Just the way I,
just the way I am ♪
This song is dedicated to all
the lost and the hopeless,
to anyone
who's ever been abandoned
by their friends
or their family.
To all the laughed at,
the spit on, the rejected,
the abused and the broken.
You are loved.
You are worth it.
You are more beautiful
than you can possibly imagine.
You're a fighter,
an undefeated champion,
created in the image
of absolute perfection.
So hold your head up high, kid.
We're all in this together.
♪ I know that I might be
a little bit overwhelming ♪
♪ And I know that you think
something must be wrong ♪
♪ Inside my head ♪
♪ Let go ♪
♪ I'm gonna chase my dreams ♪
♪ And pray for a happy ending ♪
♪ You can take me or leave me ♪
♪ Just the way I,
just the way I am. ♪
Summertime Dropouts, right?
You guys are really good.
Wait, you're...
Yep, Simple Plan.
- You guys are our heroes.
- Yeah.
We need a band to open up
for us on our next tour,
and we thought
it could be you guys.
- We're in. Uh, right?
- Yeah.
- Yes, yes, yes!
- For sure.
Nice! We have a show
to play now.
- You guys wanna come with us?
- Yeah.
Way to go, pal.
Hey, that's my brother.
This is gonna be sick!
- 'Sup.
- What's up, man? How you doing?
How you doing?
Hey, Dave.
They turned out
pretty good, huh?
♪ Boom, boo, boo, boo, boo
boo, boo, boo ♪
♪ Boo, boo, boo, boo
boo, boo, boo, boom ♪
boo, boo, boo ♪
♪ In a world
full of heartache ♪
♪ Seems like
everyone's burning out ♪
♪ You and me,
we did it our way ♪
♪ And this love
ain't running out ♪
♪ We got that fire, that glow ♪
♪ Yet, I just need you
to know ♪
♪ You're my favorite song,
my sing-along ♪
♪ You shine bright
like lighters in the dark ♪
♪ And you're my clarity,
the best part of me ♪
♪ You still make my crazy
little heart go boom ♪
♪ Boo, boo, boo, boo
boo, boo, boo, boom ♪
♪ Boo, boo, boo, boo... ♪
♪ Another jam packed day ♪
♪ Of everybody on the planet ♪
♪ Telling me to cram it ♪
♪ Telling me I'm not okay ♪
♪ Another troubled
little failure ♪
♪ Dangerous behavior ♪
♪ Why can't they just behave? ♪
♪ Another silly little misfit
trying to be different ♪
♪ Look at the clothes
they wear ♪
♪ The definition
of an outcast ♪
♪ Bottom on the cool graph ♪
♪ Skinny jeans and pink hair ♪
♪ I know that I might be
a little bit overwhelming ♪
♪ And I know that you
think something must be wrong ♪
♪ Inside my head ♪
♪ Let go ♪
♪ I'm gonna chase my dreams ♪
♪ And pray for a happy ending ♪
♪ You can take me or leave me ♪
♪ Just the way I,
just the way I am ♪
♪ They say I might be sick ♪
♪ A psychological condition ♪
♪ Difficult musician ♪
♪ Doesn't want
to fall in line ♪
♪ Another sticky situation ♪
♪ Insubordination,
keep it contained this time ♪
♪ A personality disorder ♪
♪ Put him in the corner ♪
♪ Hook 'em on the dollar sign ♪
♪ We'll tell him money
is the answer ♪
♪ Music is a cancer ♪
♪ Prove it all onDateline ♪
♪ I know that I might be
a little bit overwhelming ♪
♪ And I know that you think
something must be wrong ♪
♪ Inside my head ♪
♪ Let go ♪
♪ I'm gonna chase my dreams ♪
♪ And pray for a happy ending ♪
♪ You can take me or leave me ♪
♪ Just the way I,
just the way I am ♪
This song is dedicated to all
the lost and the hopeless,
to anyone
who's ever been abandoned
by their friends
and their family.
For all the laughed at,
the rejected, the spit on,
the abused and the broken.
You are loved.
You are worth it.
You are more beautiful
than you can possibly imagine.
You're a fighter,
an undefeated champion.
Created in the image
of absolute perfection.
So hold your head up high, kid.
We're all in this together.
♪ I know that I might be
a little bit overwhelming ♪
♪ And I know that you think
something must be wrong ♪
♪ Inside my head ♪
♪ Let go ♪
♪ I'm gonna chase my dreams ♪
♪ And pray for a happy ending ♪
♪ You can take me or leave me ♪
♪ Just the way I,
just the way I am. ♪
♪ I'm waking up ♪
♪ The clock hits 7:00,
but I'm not standing ♪
♪ I'd rather jump and sing ♪
♪ Than wait in my daydreams ♪
♪ I kick down the doors ♪
♪ The lights are beaming,
for me they're screaming ♪
♪ I'll teach the world to see ♪
♪ That there's no stopping me ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ And now I'm ♪
♪ I'm breaking out
of faking me ♪
♪ I'll never try
to chain my mind ♪
♪ In the spaces in between ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I'll shed these lies
and sing my dreams ♪
♪ The truth sometime
will walk the line ♪
♪ I'm finally feeling free ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I shouldn't speak ♪
♪ Or so they told me
when I was only ♪
♪ A pretty pink 13 ♪
♪ A perfect beauty queen ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ I found my voice ♪
♪ They couldn't hold her,
she's getting older ♪
♪ Brighter than before ♪
♪ Won't hold back anymore ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I'm breaking out
of faking me ♪
♪ I never tried
to chain my mind ♪
♪ In the spaces in between ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I'll shed these lies
and sing my dreams ♪
♪ The truth sometime
will walk the line ♪
♪ I'm finally feeling free ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I've always had to bend
and break and learn to fake ♪
♪ To fit inside these lines ♪
♪ They drew in sand,
won't even say why ♪
♪ But all this pain
I've had to hold ♪
♪ Won't drain me cold ♪
♪ It only lights a fire ♪
♪ So wild and pure
it can't ever die ♪
♪ I won't let it die ♪
♪ I'm breaking out
of faking me ♪
♪ I never tried
to chain my mind ♪
♪ In the spaces in between ♪
♪ I'm not sorry ♪
♪ I'll shed these lies
and sing my dreams ♪
♪ The truth sometime
will walk the line... ♪