[tense ominous music]
[police siren blares]
[police radio chattering]
[chopper whirring]
[Rouse] Los Angeles.
[with heavy accent] Los Angeles.
LA.
I've been a lot of places,
and every place in this world has a price tag.
[horns honking]
And this place where I'm standing now,
this Los Angeles place,
it has the biggest price tag of 'em all.
[lighter flicks]
[Rouse] Maybe I've lost an angel,
but I don't think angels can be lost.
That's why they're angels.
[police sirens blaring]
[Rouse] No matter how you think you're hidden,
you're always where somebody can see you.
I gotta find out who I am.
I'm ready for anything.
Just bring it to me. I'm ready for anything. Just bring it to me.
Dealer takes... two cards.
[clears throat]
[Conover] It's about that time, man. Getting late.
[sighs] Shit.
Same day, same shit.
You love this job, man.
Huh, who are you kidding?
But I'll tell you, in no time, man, I got two years left,
I'm gonna retire,
get me a little piece of property.
You eat this shit up. You love this stuff, man.
And what about me?
You ain't got to worry about it, man.
-Your partner's always got your back. -That's right.
[announcer] If you're a basketball fan, you'll be happy to know...
-Whoa, whoa. -...the Bears were victorious tonight
stomping out the Wildcats,
-final score 74-54. -Damn!
-Back to... -We lost again.
[exhales] What else is new?
Hey, Paxton. You read me?
Yo, yo, what's up?
[Jose over radio] Oh, man. Wildcats lost again.
[laughs] What do you expect?
Out.
I tell you, you'd be better off to bet on the lottery.
At least you'd only lose a dollar. [laughs]
[dog barks]
So what's the deal, man? You gonna dance with him or are you gonna play?
[dog barking]
Hold on, man. All right. I'm in.
I'm in, and I'm gonna bump you another $20.
-[laughs] -Hey, Dinelli, will you quit
with the pacing, man? You're getting on my nerves.
Your nerves? What about mine?
Hey, come on. Give us a break.
What the hell you got to bitch about?
You got a get-out-of-jail free pass.
Just... play your cards.
[sighs]
[dog barking]
[phone rings]
Give me a sec.
Don't touch that. I'm gonna take a piss.
-I'll be right back. -[phone continues ringing]
-[phone beeps] -Yeah?
Jack, it's Buzz. We have to talk.
Listen. I told you to quit bugging me, all right?
[Buzz over phone] No. Please, please. Just listen to me.
-Lose this number, all right? Forget it! -Don't--
Don't hang up on me, please.
[sighs]
Who was that?
It was, uh...
[sighs] it was my dog.
German Shepherd.
You ought to hear it, man. It speaks perfect German.
Should get 'em together with my Schnauzer.
Read 'em and weep.
Oh, man! [slaps the table]
My man, I love you. You don't know how much I love you, partner.
Youngster, you got a lot to learn.
But I'm gonna teach you good.
Yeah.
[upbeat music]
[dog barking]
[taxi driver] Okay, ladies. Here we are.
-[Eve] Yeah, yeah. Thanks, good night. -Mm-hmm.
[Eve chuckles]
♪ Take me, oh, baby ♪
-[humming intelligibly] -Hey, yo. What's up with that?
-[Conover] Mm, mm, mm. Whoa, look at them. -[Jose] Oh, my. Ask for dates.
-[Conover] Look at that, man. -[Jose] Oh.
I could rock that all night long.
[Jose] No. Don't tell me they're going to our room.
[Eve] Don't worry about it. Just do as I do.
-Yeah. [sighs] -All right. Let's do it.
[knocking on door]
[ominous music]
[gun clicks]
-Who is it? -I came to see John.
John who?
John Wayne.
[whispering] John Wayne, my ass.
-Go! -[gun clicks]
[Paxton] You think you're funny?
What's going on?
Whoa, whoa. Take it easy.
Ladies, cut the crap.
-Who sent you? -[Dinelli] Hey, guys.
They're okay.
I called 'em.
Come here, you. One at a time. Frisk 'em.
Hey, baby. How you doing?
[Burton] Yeah. She's okay too.
[Jose] Paxton's got everything under control.
Hey, honey. How you doing, baby, huh?
Hey, guys.
Don't you got a poker game to play?
Yeah. Right.
[laughs]
Come on, honey. Let's party. [laughs]
-[Eve] We've got something special for you too, honey. -[Angel chuckles]
So I guess that's protocol?
-[women speaking inaudibly] -[Dinelli] Yeah, baby.
-What goddamned protocol? -[women giggling]
-[Dinelli] Oh, honey. That's sweet. -[women laughing]
[sighs]
-[Dinelli] Oh, yeah. [moaning] -[women laughing]
-Yeah! -Yeah!
-You look good tonight, huh? -Yeah?
-Hey. -Yeah?
-Uh, looking-- -You having fun?
-Oh, I'm having fun. -Oh, good.
Are you hot or what? Are you hot? Does your--
Does your mommy know how hot you are?
Because Daddy, Daddy does.
[chattering in the room]
I don't like this.
Hey... there's a lot of things
we don't like, but we gotta do 'em anyway.
Yeah? That son of a bitch gets more action than I do.
Yeah, well, I can understand that.
It's 'cause you're married.
On top of that, you're ugly.
-[women laughing] -Thanks.
-My man. -Deal.
-Whoo! -I'm Angel.
Yeah, you are an angel.
-Thank you. -Oh, look at-- Oh, look at you with your titties.
-Oh, yeah. -You'll see 'em.
-Oh, look at you. -[women laughing]
Hey, what's your name, little girl?
My name's Eve.
-[Dinelli] Hey, you. -[Eve] Yeah?
[Dinelli] What are you gonna do for Daddy?
-You make-- -[Eve] What do you want, huh?
I want, I want you to make Daddy so happy.
-Yeah, yeah? -I want you to be a nasty little girl.
-[women giggling] -And I want you to go play
-with Angel for Daddy. -[Eve laughs] I want you to sit back a little bit. Yeah?
-Gi-- You gonna give me a show? -It'll cost you a little extra. Do you have a little extra?
-That's gonna cost you. -Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, baby! Daddy's got so much money!
-[Eve] Daddy's got so much money? -I've got so much money!
[Eve] How much money does Daddy got?
-Daddy's got all the money he needs. -Yeah?
-I got a lot of money for you. -[whispering] I'm gonna make you so hot.
-Oh, you-- -Tell me what you wanna do to me.
-I want you-- Baby, yeah. -Yeah, yeah.
-I wanna see you do that with her. -Oh, you do?
-Yeah, baby. I want you, I want you to give her a kiss. -Yeah?
-Go ahead. Oh, yeah, baby. -[Eve] Is that what you want, huh?
-Yeah. Kiss my girl, yeah. -You want me to give her a kiss?
-Yeah? Is that what you want, huh? -Yeah, baby. Go ahead.
Oh, that's a... [clears throat] Yeah, baby. Yeah.
-Now that's what I'm saying. You whore, yeah. -[Angel] Uh-uh.
-No way. -[Dinelli] Hey.
-Hey, what the fuck? -Hey! Hey! Calm down, got it?
-[Dinelli] Get back here! -[Eve] Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Calm down.
-[Dinelli] What the fuck is she-- -[Eve] Shut the fuck up!
-I need you to calm down. No! Shh! -[Dinelli] Hey!
[Eve] Take it easy, all right?
-Fucking bitch! -Hey!
Listen to this, baby. I want you just to be really calm.
You hear me? Calm down. That--
-Is she coming back? -Yeah, she's coming back.
-Please fuck Daddy. God. -I'm gonna go talk to her.
-Let me talk to her, okay? -Yeah, baby. You're so fucking hot!
Daddy! [moans]
[sighs]
[exhales] What is wrong with you?
I can't go through with this.
Oh, look, honey. Come on.
It's not that bad, I promise you.
The first time is just a little rough.
I can't do it.
Look.
Here.
[key jangles]
Look. Take this, all right?
I'll go take care of him.
You stay here.
Hey.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hey, baby.
-Hey. -Yeah.
-How's my little girl? -Just fine.
-Everything's just fine. -Oh, yeah. [moaning]
[Eve] Yeah. I took care of it.
[upbeat music on radio]
-[man] I asked you not to lie to me, right? -[woman] Right.
[man] Did you eat my dinner tonight?
Now what's going on with these fools over here?
-[man] You ate my fucking dinner. -[woman] No, honey. I didn't eat
-your fucking dinner tonight! -[man] You're fucking lying.
If you're gonna lie about something like that,
I know you'll fucking lie to me about fucking Frank!
-That-- That ain't right, man. -[man] You're lying!
-[woman] I'm not lying. -Let it go, partner.
-No, that ain't right. -[man] You fucked Frank!
-I loved you. I... -[Conover] Let it go.
I ain't having it, man.
-Jose. -[man] Don't you lie to me!
I loved you and you fucking lied!
-Fucking bitch! -[Jose] Hey, hold it.
[man] Don't fucking lie to me!
-I loved you! -[Jose] Hey, asshole.
-What's your problem? -What the fuck do you want?
-Is any of this your fucking business? Is it? -[Jose inaudible]
-[Jose] Back off. -[Conover] Oh, shit.
I'm a cop.
Hey, are you okay?
-[gunshot] -[Jose groaning]
[dramatic music]
-[gunshot] -[woman groans]
[groans]
[tires screech]
[gunshots]
[tires screeching]
Shit.
[Eve gasps]
[gunshots]
[glass shatters]
[man] Get down!
[Paxton] Go dial for backup!
[gunshots]
[gunshots continue]
[groans]
[gunshots]
-[man] Damn it. What the hell? -[screams]
-[indistinct chatter] -[man] Cover me!
[gunshots]
[groans]
-[screams] -[groans]
[man] All right. Come on.
I got him.
-[man screams] -[glass shatters]
[gunshots]
[dramatic music continues]
[groaning]
-[groans] -[gun clicks]
[gunshots]
[screams]
[moans]
[breathes heavily]
-You all right, partner? -[coughs] I've been-- I've been better.
-[chuckles] Yeah, so have I. -[car door slams]
[breathing heavily]
Jesus Christ!
[footsteps approaching]
[breathing heavily] Where the fuck were you?
[gun clicks]
Et tu, Brutus?
[gunshot]
-[gunshot] -[chokes]
[breathes heavily]
[suspenseful music]
[people chatter outside]
Here.
Stay here. Don't say a word.
-How you doing? Shut up! -Oh, please, please! Please, don't!
-Sh-- Get in the corner! Get in the corner and shut up. -No! What?
-Shut up, get on your fucking knees! -[screams]
Please, no! Please, please!
-Sit down! -Please!
-No! -[gunshot]
-How you doing, Mel? How you doing, all right? -[Dinelli] Good.
-I'm good, I'm good. -Yeah, you're good? You never expected to see me here, huh?
-No. Yeah, yeah, you know. -How's everything?
-You all right? Yeah? -[Dinelli] Yeah.
-Did you get a blowjob tonight? -No.
Don't lie to me. I'm gonna tell your wife.
-[Dinelli] I didn't get a chance to. -You didn't get a chance?
-[Dinelli] No. -Mel, how can you fucking go against my father?
-[Dinelli] I didn't. -After all he did for you, you're gonna rat on my father?
-[Dinelli] No, I-- -You stool pigeon bastard--
-[Dinelli] I swear to God, no. -You swear to-- Shh.
Mel, come on!
-I'm sorry. -You're a tougher guy than that.
Stop stammering and crying like a three-year-old.
You gotta talk, you gotta pay the price, Mel.
-All right? I'm gonna try to help you out of this, all right? -Yeah--
-I'm your friend here. Where's the money? -What?
-Where's the money? -[Dinelli] I don't know.
-Mel, where's the money? -[Dinelli] I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know!
-Where's my fucking money, Mel? -[sobbing]
-Where's my fucking money? -It's in the fucking locker!
-Shut up! -It's in the locker.
-There's a fucking key in the-- there's a fucking key-- -Let me have the key.
-The money-- [screams] -Mel, where's the fucking--
-No, no, no! -Shut up.
-[sobs] -Shut up, Mel!
Mel, Mel, calm down. Mel, Mel.
Calm down, it's all right. Mel, I'm not gonna hurt you.
Mel, what's the locker number?
[Dinelli stutters] It's locker 32C.
-32C? You wouldn't lie to me? -[Dinelli] I sw-- I swear,
-I swear on my mother's grave. I swear to God. -All right.
-I've got the key. -If you swear on your mother's grave, I believe you.
-All right, all right, relax. Mel. Mel. -[sobbing]
-Let's talk like we used to talk back in the day. Remember? -Yeah.
-Huh? When you used to come over and eat with us? -Yeah. [sobbing]
All right, Mel. Come on, come on. Come here, come here.
It's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
-Mel, Mel. Melvin. -[Dinelli sobs]
-It's all right. It's all right. Relax. -[Dinelli] I'm sorry!
Come here. Stop being a girl. I love you too, Mel.
-Come on, we're like family. -[sobbing]
I'm not gonna hurt you. What I'm gonna do-- All right.
Stop, stop, stop. You're sweating like a beast. Take it easy.
-I'm gonna get the guys to come and get you, okay? -Right.
All right? You do the right thing. They're gonna come pick you up.
-You don't mention anything about my father. -No.
-Don't tell anybody anything. All right? -I won't.
-You promise? All right. -I promise, I promise.
I'm not gonna hurt you. Just stay there. All right?
-I'm gonna order you some food. -Yeah.
All right? I'll talk to you later.
[gunshot]
[bedsprings creaking]
[police sirens approach]
[footsteps retreat quickly]
-[body thuds] -[man groans]
[blows thudding]
[mugger] That's it. [laughs]
-[man grunts] -[mugger laughs] Work him over good.
[blows thudding]
[mugger] Come on, get the money.
What's going on?
What's it to you, motherfucker? Get the fuck out of here.
[blows thudding]
Dukem, shoot him.
[dramatic music]
[men grunting and groaning]
[groans]
-[bone snaps] -[screams]
[men grunting and groaning]
[Tyler] Hey.
Fuck. A cop.
Hey, it's cool.
And we're out of here.
[man moaning]
-You all right? -Uh-huh.
♪ Joy to the world ♪
♪ The Lord has come... ♪
At least it's a little more special than last year.
Sherry, I would rather eat pretzels with you
than turkey and all the fixings with anybody else.
Is that the best you got?
-Yeah. -[chuckles]
So what about you?
-What are you doing for the holidays? -Oh, um...
Chris and I were going up to Big Bear.
Um, we got a little log cabin.
What are you doing for Christmas?
Same old same old.
[jazzy music playing on piano]
[woman groaning]
-Leave me-- Leave me alone. -[man laughs]
-[man] Come on. -[woman] You're getting nothing from me.
Come on now. You know I got this. Hey!
-[woman] Jerk. -[Sherry] Cut that shit out.
-[man sighs] -Get the fuck out of here!
Now!
[door slams]
Merry Christmas.
-Merry Christmas. -[glasses clink]
[phone rings]
-[phone beeps] -Hello?
[Rouse] Tyler, this is Rouse.
I've got some bad news.
Paxton is dead.
You need to get over to the safe house right now.
I'll be right there.
[somber music]
I gotta go.
[sirens blaring]
[police radio chattering]
[background chatter]
Why the hell weren't you wearing your vest?
I don't think it will have made any difference.
Look, he got shot at close range.
I know it's not like him to let the bad guys get that close.
[sniffs]
[Buzz sighs] It's Dan.
[sirens blaring]
[police radio chattering]
[sad music]
What happened?
We don't know. We're trying to sort it out.
He was the reason I stayed on the force.
[cops chatter quietly]
Hey, Nick. Can I talk to you for a minute?
He really fucked this one up, huh?
-What the fuck do you mean by that? -You know exactly what I mean.
-No. I want you to tell me what you mean. -You know what I mean.
Okay, okay. Wait, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, Danny. Okay. Let's just calm down.
I feel the same way. Come on, let's go back to the station.
Come on. Come on, let's go back to the station.
Just give me a minute.
[police radio chattering]
[somber music]
[traffic humming]
-[bell rings] -[door clicks shut]
-Tino! Tino! -What's going on, mija?
-Let me back there, please. -What you--
What's going on? You should be outside working, mija.
-You know not to come back before 9:00. -Please, please.
-Are you fucking high, or what? -No, no, no, no, no.
-What is going on? -Just trust me.
-What the hell happened? -I'll tell you back there.
-Just let me in there. -What's wrong with you?
-Come on. I swear to God-- -Get inside.
Shit.
Oh, my God.
-Oh, my God! -Wh-- What's--
Relax, mija. Relax.
-What's going on? Breathe. -[breathing heavily]
Eve's dead.
What happened?
I saw Eve get shot.
[Angel sobs] Fuck. Fuck!
Tell me everything, and tell me the truth.
I don't know, it was at the hotel.
What do you mean you don't know? You're fucking blind or what?
These guys came in, and I was in the bathroom.
-What do I do? -[exhales]
Angel, I swear to God,
you have been working for me less than a week.
And the first thing I told you is to be aware of everything around you,
everybody around you, not to go to the hotel by yourself,
and that's the first thing that you did!
And now look what happened!
I think there were cops involved.
[laughs] There was a fucking cop involved.
There was a fucking cop involved?
I have worked too damned hard to get this business going
for you to come here in one week, and fuck everything up for me!
[sobbing] Where do I go?
-What do I do? -I'm gonna tell you what to do.
I'm gonna tell you to turn around,
to walk through that thing that's called a fucking door.
You're gonna get out of here!
And when I call, you come back! Fuck!
[breathing heavily]
Fuck!
This quiet downtown hotel appears
to be the scene of multiple homicides.
In fact, there are four police detectives,
several unidentified men,
and a woman have been found dead inside
in what sources indicate has all the makings of a gangland style slaying.
Now, police officials won't confirm or deny this,
but one of the victims appears to be the prosecution witness
against the Teflon Don himself, Franco Nugentti,
he, of course, of the Faustino crime family.
He is being held on bond during one of the, well,
one of the most historic organized crime trials in the history of Los Angeles.
His son, Franco Jr., is said to be running the family business in his absence.
[JJ] So what time'd this happen?
-[Buzz] About 10:00, 10:15. -[Tyler] Jack was shot a close range.
Well, that doesn't make sense. How does a seasoned cop like Jack get shot at close range?
We can't figure it out.
So for someone to come in the room and get that close,
it would have to be his wife or his mother, right?
Or maybe a cop.
What? Come on. You know it happens sometimes,
you know, for the right price, I mean, it happened before, right?
Wait, wait, wait. I thought there was a dead woman found in that room?
[Tyler] Yeah. Hooker.
What's a dead hooker doing in the room?
Well, maybe Jack and Sid were doing the hooker.
What? You never had a hooker? I mean, come on.
Just 'cause you're happily married, it doesn't mean
you don't cheat on your wife. Right, Danny?
Are you ladies through, or should I leave and give you some more privacy.
-No, we're done. -[sighs]
[Lawlor] All right, here's the latest on the case.
Captain.
Let's get down to the business. You've read the report.
We're dealing with an inside job.
Okay. Backup arrived on time.
He was shot at close range, like Jack.
But the shooter wasn't a stranger.
It was done by a cop.
I hate this.
The dead girl was found with some mesh stockings...
...belonged to someone else. We ran the preliminary tests,
and they didn't match the hooker that was found dead on the scene.
Oh, shit.
Another hooker.
That's possible.
There's a witness that said they saw a half-naked woman
running from the hotel where the event went down.
[sighs] Now, if this mystery woman wasn't in on the hit,
maybe she knows the killer or the killers.
We've got some work to do here...
...and we're not gonna let it go...
...and we're not gonna have loose ends flapping in the wind.
Double J, Buzz, you're on the murder investigation.
You two...
...come with me.
By the way, you'll be happy to know
we have an ID on the mystery woman.
Her name is Angel.
I want an APB on her.
You go and find her, and you call me.
Use your cell phone. Do not call dispatch.
And don't bring her in.
As I said before, this is leaning to an inside job...
...so we need her testimony.
She remains safe.
I don't wanna lose her.
Well, after what happened to Paxton and Sid,
uh, I think the FED should handle this.
No, sir.
This is our collar.
Oh.
-This is for you, Tyler. -What's this?
Congratulations.
You have been deputized. You are US Marshals.
And you are my lead detective on this case.
The DA's gonna call us when to bring the witness to court.
And her testimony will be the final nail
in Nugentti's coffin.
Sir, Buzz is my partner, not Yordan.
I can't work with this guy.
I trust her with my life every day.
If you got a problem with Buzz, you got a problem with me.
I picked you two because you're the ones I trust on this.
You understand me?
And you are my best homicide detective.
Yordan works vice.
He knows the street, and we're under the gun
to get this hooker before it's too late.
I'm counting on you.
I'm counting on you too. You're dismissed.
I like your suit.
You gonna wear it all the time?
"My, my, my." said the spider to the fly.
Buzz! Buzz! Samantha!
-What? -Jesus, hold up.
That little powwow up there where you were pulling the charade
about Jack wouldn't cheat on his wife.
Come on. We're supposed to be working together
and you can't be honest with me about that?
Look, JJ, you get off my back,
because I will not take these kind of insinuations from you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Easy.
Let's just put our personal differences aside, okay?
This thing is a little bigger
than we all can imagine.
-Hey. -[scoffs]
She loves you.
What's tougher than one female blonde cop?
I don't know.
Two female blonde cops.
You like my jokes, right?
Four, five, six blonde cops.
[dramatic music]
[Yordan] So where do we go first?
Escort service or taxi company?
[Tyler] We start with the escort service,
find out what they know.
That's the best bet.
Detective Dan Tyler, LAPD homicide.
I'm sorry, but police night is on Saturdays.
I'd like to ask you a few questions
about a couple of your employees, Eve and Angel.
There's no Eve or Angel that works here tonight.
And besides, we're closed.
I'm sorry, if you can come back tomorrow or next week,
that would be great. I'm sorry, mijo.
That's just the way it is. Okay?
Well, hello, papi chulo.
[tense music]
You know this is a homicide investigation, right?
-No, I didn't get the invitation to that party. No. -[Yordan] Oh, you didn't know?
[Yordan] Did you know Angel was with her?
I don't know. What does that have to do with me?
I'm sure you do know. And I'm sure you can help us out
trying to find her. Right? Right?
Frenchy, nothing would make me happier
is to help you out.
How do you contact Angel?
I don't know how to get ahold of Angel,
because I don't know her phone number.
How do you reach Eve?
I don't know where she lives.
I'm... I don't even know where to find her.
Do you know what they do to pretty boys like you in prison?
-Well, hopefully, ugly things. -Oh, yes.
She is getting fucked every night at the pool hall
by Bill, the guy that owns the place, okay?
-Now-- -[Tyler] Bill what?
What am I, information all of a sudden?
Bill Jones, Bill Smith.
Oh, you're talking about the famous...
...Bill Slater, right?
Well, if he's famous for selling drugs
to underage children, then, ding!
Yes, the "famous," uh, Bill Slater.
I know where he is.
Thank you for coming tonight.
Oh, and one more thing.
Uh, when you guys walk, your asses seem a little bit tight,
so you may wanna get a massage on the way out.
I wouldn't mind, but you know my partner, you know how he is, right?
-I know how he is. And I know how you are. -There you go.
-Thanks for your help. -Wish you could stay.
[speaks in Spanish]
[upbeat rock music playing over speakers]
Listen to me.
I know how you're used to working,
and I don't like it.
Just let me question him.
Sure.
I'm looking for Bill Slater.
Bill Slater?
Who wants to know?
-LAPD. Homicide. -[chuckles]
Look, I've got some bad news. I don't have an easy way to say this,
but your girlfriend Eve was killed last night.
Angel was with her. We need to know how to get in touch with Angel.
I don't know shit.
You probably killed her.
Look. I know you're in contact with Angel.
Now tell me where she is.
I said I don't know shit.
What the fuck? [laughs]
I can bust you for narcotics for this.
Bust me.
[tense music]
[laughs]
He's not talking.
[background chattering]
[sighs]
[groans]
-Where is she? -[Bill groans] Fuck.
[Yordan] Where is she?
[screams] She's at the train station! [groans]
[men grunting and groaning]
[dramatic music]
See?
[man groaning]
-You can lose your badge for that. -Sure.
[train horn blaring]
[ominous music]
[dog barks]
[sirens blaring]
[Yordan] You know, the hooker may have set up Jack and Sid.
-Yeah? What are you getting at? -I'm getting at we have to be careful with her.
If she's working for Nugentti...
...I'm telling you, it will take only one phone call
and we end up dead like Paxton.
[Tyler] Yeah, but if she's not working for him
and she IDs the hitter,
we could connect him to Nugentti,
and put 'em away for life.
It's worth the risk.
[Yordan] Look. It's her.
[Tyler] Get her.
[dramatic music]
Police! Stop.
-[Angel screams] -[Yordan grunts]
I'm a cop.
[Tyler] Put her in the car.
[suspenseful music]
-[Yordan grunts] -Hey, hey, hey. Back off! Back off!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm detective Dan Tyler, LAPD homicide.
We're not here to arrest you, we just need to ask you a few questions.
Where were you last night at 10:00 p.m.?
I was at home.
You're lying.
We know you were in the hotel room.
We've got your stockings.
Talk to me.
Fine. I was there, but I didn't see anything.
Why did you run?
Because I was scared.
What were you doing?
Working.
I could arrest you right now for accessory to murder.
You better cooperate.
Fine. I saw him do it.
Saw who?
That mob guy that's always on TV.
Nugentti?
Why would he do it himself?
Guess he wanted something very bad.
Am I done now?
No.
[Yordan] Hey, it's 6:00 a.m. He should be in his office by now.
You better make the call.
[tense music]
[phone beeps]
[phone rings]
-Tyler. -We got the girl.
I'm proud of you.
Listen, it's very important. We need to get her
into a covert environment where she is safe.
Just meet us at the, the corner of Burbank and Van Nuys.
I'll be there in about, uh... 20 minutes.
Great.
[phone beeps]
Hey, you gonna get rid of that suit?
We are supposed to be undercover, you know?
[Tyler] Look, I'll change when we get to the safe house.
-[gunshots] -[Tyler] Damn!
[tires screech]
Holy shit, just back up. Back up!
Get down!
-[tires screeching] -[gunshots]
[car alarm blaring]
[tires screech]
[gunshots]
-[Tyler] What the hell was that? -[Yordan] They must have followed us
from the train station.
[Rouse] Someone got to Tyler and Yordan.
I now know one of you is a traitor.
[suspenseful music]
[Rouse] And I will find out who it is.
So just know this, that I'm going to be watching
every one of you very closely.
So do your best to stay straight...
[sighs] and let's wrap this thing up...
...before it explodes inside the department
and we don't have a department anymore.
Hey, Lawlor. I hear Tyler got your case, huh?
Well, you know what they say, Bill.
Every dog has his day.
[people chattering]
[phone rings]
-See you. -[Bill] See you later.
[ominous music]
[sighs] Empty.
[patrons chattering]
-Oh. Hi, Bobby. -How you doing?
Where's, uh, where's Frankie?
He's in the kitchen. Is something wrong?
Yeah. I got bad news for him.
Oh, he's already in a bad mood today.
-That's wonderful. -Good luck.
[suspenseful music]
Tomasino.
How we doing, buddy?
-[Tomasino] I... -Ah, come on.
You gotta move. You gotta mo-- This--
You gotta chop, fine, fine, fine, all right? This is very important.
There's 50 people in the banquet room.
We gotta take care of this. This is important to my father.
Do it again. Do it again.
Do it again. Come on.
[oil sizzling]
-What are you doing? -[Nugentti Jr] Come over here.
-[chuckles] What's going on? -What's going on?
I'm cooking. I'm behind schedule.
The guy who was supposed to show up didn't show up with him.
-[inaudible] -The smell. Look.
It smells good, like my mom's.
Your mom. I love your mom. How's she doing?
Do me a favor, take a look at this.
-Is that too oily? -No, no. It needs some olive oil.
What are you? A chef all of a sudden?
-What the fuck? You asked for my opinion. -Oh.
Keep your opinions to yourself. Don't curse.
I gotta go. I'm behind schedule. Get out of my way.
-What do you mean "behind the schedule"? -Get out of my way.
-What are you doing? -What am I doing?
I gotta chop the garlic, is what I'm doing.
The other kid didn't show up.
[Bobby] Which one? The bus boy?
[Nugentti Jr] Uh, what's his name?
Listen, uh... I couldn't find that thing.
-[chuckles] You couldn't find that thing? -I couldn't find that thing.
We looked in every fucking locker. Nothing.
Come here.
You get Jimmy, you get Tommy, you hear me?
You go back to those lockers, you find that thing.
-I'm sorry, I just-- -You don't fucking tell me you're-- Look at me.
[suspenseful music]
I want the money.
You find the money,
then you find the girl.
What about the cops?
Surprise me.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
Tomasino! [speaks in Italian]
[Bobby] I'll take care of it.
You okay?
[people chattering]
[Bobby scoffs]
[tense music]
-[Yordan] What is this place? -[Tyler] I used to work out here when I was a kid.
It should be a safe place to talk.
Looks empty.
[gentle music]
What do we do now?
We wait.
Here?
No, we gotta find a safe house.
I know my rights. You can't keep me here like some kidnap victim.
[light suspenseful music]
You think you've been kidnapped?
You're in protective custody.
Without us, you'd be dead.
Yeah. Cops protecting me from cops.
How do I know you guys aren't a part of this thing?
You're still alive, right?
How many cops know I'm here?
Just us.
Oh, that's great.
So they sent you two fuck-ups to protect me?
You know what? You've got a hell of a mouth.
Give me the key.
Give me the key!
None of us wanna be here.
Then why don't you fucking let me go?
One of my best friends was killed in that hotel room.
For all I know, you were in on the hit that got him murdered.
So don't push me.
I don't fucking have to take this.
I want to get out of here.
[gun clicks]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
Back off.
I swear to God I'll shoot.
Yeah? You're gonna shoot me?
Back off! I mean it!
Yeah.
Go ahead.
Shoot.
[gun clicks]
[somber music]
You should have told me.
If we wanted you dead,
we wouldn't be sitting here talking.
I'm here to make sure you don't get killed.
Maybe you want something from me.
What do you mean?
You're not here to protect me.
You're just here to keep me from escaping.
Angel.
Angel, listen to me.
Look, look at me.
If you fight us...
...if you try to escape...
...they'll find you.
We're your only chance to get out of this alive.
You need us as much as we need you.
I got a place where we can hide.
[tense music]
[phone rings]
-Hello? -[Bobby on phone] Frankie?
-Yeah. -[Bobby on phone] They're on the move.
-Should I call your cop friend? -We got 24 hours.
Do you understand what's going on here?
This whole thing is gonna come crumbling down.
You better take care of this.
-[Bobby on phone] What about the hooker? -No.
-You know where she is? -[Bobby on phone] I'm on it.
And do me a favor, do not call me back until you take care of her,
and then you find my money.
They might be bugging this phone.
[tense music intensifies]
-[Tyler] Whose place is this? -That's Paula's place.
She's a flight attendant. You know how they are. They're always out of town.
But I got a spare key.
Is this place safe?
Of course, it's safe. It's one of my girlfriends.
I'm gonna check it out.
-Sure. -How long are you planning on keeping me here?
[Yordan] As long as it takes.
Just sit down and make yourself comfortable.
[Tyler] Only one window on the second floor.
It looks clear.
I'm starving. Are you at least gonna feed me?
She's right. Is there anything to eat here?
No, there's nothing in there. But you know what?
I know this great restaurant around the corner.
I don't eat meat.
She'll eat anything.
Screw you.
You making an offer?
There's not enough money in the world.
[Tyler] Yordan, just go get the food.
Sure.
Just watch her.
[ominous music]
[knocking on door]
Who is it?
Yordan. Open up.
[sighs]
Come on down.
French fries.
Your hamburger.
Hey, I think they found us.
[Angel] Hey, stop it!
What the hell are you doing, huh? That's my purse.
What? Are you gonna strip search me now too?
Sure. Can I?
Yeah. You bet.
Hey.
She's not dangerous. Hell, she had a gun
pointed right at you, couldn't pull the trigger.
She doesn't have to be a killer.
You're crazy.
You know, we still don't know how Nugentti got into the room,
and you know she could have distracted him.
No way.
Jack was a happily married man.
He wouldn't leave his post for some hooker.
Come on, man. Wake up and smell the coffee.
You know Paxton was doing Buzz.
[chuckles] What? You didn't know that?
Jesus, the whole department knew.
Look at her.
You're telling me you don't want a piece of that?
Just... keep an eye on her.
[somber music]
[guns click]
[suspenseful music]
[gentle somber music]
-[ominous music] -[Tyler grunts]
[gun clicks]
[attacker groans]
[bone snaps]
[men grunting and groaning]
[gunshots]
[man groaning]
[men grunting and groaning]
[groans]
[arm snaps]
[guns click]
[gentle music]
[Yordan] Who the hell are these guys, anyway?
I recognize him. One of Nugentti's men.
Hey, Frankie. I got some bad news for you.
What do you want?
Frankie, Bobby's gone.
-[sighs] -[Max] I'm sorry.
[ominous music]
[sighs]
Max, come here.
You send everyone we have.
Everyone.
I want my money...
...I wanna know who killed Bobby, you hear me?
Find out who killed him.
[Tyler] You know, Phil, they didn't follow us this time.
Somebody got careless and made a call.
This is bullshit.
[suspenseful music]
What are you trying to tell me?
[chuckles] You know, it's funny.
It's always the one you least expect.
Maybe you're a dirty cop like your father was.
-Fuck you! -Fuck you too.
-Fuck you. -Fuck you.
-[Angel claps] -[Yordan] What? You gonna hit me?
-Huh? -Hey!
Nice job, ladies.
What about if it was the pop tart, huh?
Oh, yeah. That's it.
This whole thing is my suicide plan.
Think, buddy!
I don't like you.
I don't trust you.
You're just a fucking whore.
It's not her.
You know, they found us once, they can find us again.
[gunshots]
Move it!
[groans]
[Tyler] I think we lost 'em.
We can head out in the park.
[tense music]
[vehicle approaching]
[Angel] It's them.
How'd they find us?
Haven't made a phone call this time.
[Yordan] There's a parking lot on the other side.
What we should do is go over there
and hot-wire a car and just go.
-No. It's safer if we wait here. -[Yordan] I'm telling you!
-We should go right now! We're gonna get killed! -[Tyler] And I'm in charge, I--
-Guys, stop it! Stop it! -I don't care if you're in charge. We should go now!
-You'll get us killed! -You wanna stay? You wanna stay?
-Fine, you stay, I'm going. -Stop arguing!
-I'm going! -All right, all right.
Come on.
[tires screeching]
[tense music intensifies]
[gunshots]
-[Tyler] Split up! -[Yordan] Go!
[attacker] Don't shoot the girl!
[gunshot]
The location where Tyler and Yordan took the girl got hit.
-Did they get the girl? -No.
No, they didn't. But I think
the phone lines here have been tapped.
[Buzz] Captain, I wanna help Dan.
I know you do.
But I can handle this by myself.
-Do you think that's wise? -The less involved in this,
the better their chances are of living.
[tense music]
Wait. In here.
You know how to use this?
Just point it and shoot.
-[attacker 1] Hey, there he is. -[attacker 2] Get him!
[suspenseful music]
[gunshot]
[groaning]
[gunshots]
[both groaning]
[men grunting and groaning]
-[neck snaps] -[groans]
[screams]
-Angel. -[gasps]
It's okay.
They're gone. Come on.
[tires screech]
Put the gun down. Get in.
[Tyler] Nice work. How'd you get this?
[Yordan chuckles] It was a piece of cake.
I hope they don't find us again,
because this is the last flight attendant that I know.
[suspenseful music continues]
[Yordan] Lock the door.
Nice place.
-I'll check the perimeter. -Sure.
[gentle music]
Hey. You have a family?
What do you care?
I have a son who lives in Arizona with his grandma.
How old is your son?
He's five.
He has the most amazing spirit.
He's really funny.
He can walk into any room and he makes everyone laugh.
-Looks good. -Do you think they're gonna find us here?
That car was the last connection to the department.
We should be safe.
We left everything else behind.
Yeah, like our toothbrushes
and clean clothes.
Well, I don't think Judy would mind
if you borrow some of her things.
-Okay. -Yeah.
-Are you hungry? -[chuckles] Starved.
Let's go into the kitchen.
-Judy is a great cook. -[chuckles]
[Tyler] Right about now, I could go for a big juicy steak.
[Yordan laughs] What about the sweet little Pop-Tart?
[ominous music]
[buttons beeping]
Hey, it's me.
No, I can't talk long.
[crickets chirping]
[door slides open]
You were right about Judy.
Best peanut butter and jelly sandwich I ever had.
Hey, where'd you get that accent?
[scoffs] Hey, I'm just trying to make conversation.
Then don't.
You know what I said about your father?
I'm sorry.
You know what?
When I was a kid, my father used to own this little store in the ghetto.
He helped everybody.
He always saw the good in people, no matter how bad they were.
One day, some gang members showed up...
...robbed him...
...and they killed him.
You know what?
He died for a lousy 20 bucks.
So after that, I decided to get out of there,
and I became a cop.
Here I am...
...a lousy cop.
[melancholy music]
Where'd you get that?
Oh, leftovers in the fridge.
You want a fortune cookie?
[gentle music]
What's your fortune say?
I don't read fortunes.
[Angel] "You will follow a hard and rigorous path
towards enlightenment."
They got the hard part right.
[Angel chuckles]
"A dark and brooding man
will walk the path of happiness with you."
Well?
Well, what?
Are you that dark and brooding man?
I told you, I don't read fortunes.
-Can I ask you a question? -Sure.
What is a beautiful, intelligent...
-...woman like you-- -Doing in this job?
Yeah, I guess I'm not the first guy to ask you that question.
It's not that bad, you know?
Selling your body?
You're a cop.
So?
Well, you and I kind of have the same problem. Don't you think?
How do you figure?
We both wanna forget what we do at the end of the day...
...and I think I can, and I don't think you can.
Well, at least I, um, can say
I took the bad guys off the streets.
-[ominous music] -[gun clicks]
Goddamn!
-Damn, you scared the shit out of me. -[exhales]
-God, what are you-- -You miss your flight?
-Well, the flight was canceled. -I'm sorry.
-Oh! -I'm glad to see you, though.
What are they doing here?
[sighs] It's just a long story.
Okay.
I'm gonna go unwind.
-Okay. -[chuckles]
[gentle music]
[door lock clicks]
You're a pretty lonely guy, Danny.
I bet you're divorced.
Right?
-Your wife couldn't handle the job? -[chuckles]
I wish it was that simple.
For the record...
...my wife left me for another cop.
Sorry.
You learn to live with it.
You know, I got caught up in the fast lane...
...and I lost custody of my son.
So I'm only doing this to make enough money to get him back.
Pretty risky way to do it.
Where does he live?
He's in Arizona with his grandma.
How did you get to be a cop?
Runs in the family.
My dad was a cop.
Is he still on the force?
[sighs] He's dead. He, um...
...committed suicide.
When, when he started out, he was, he was really a good cop.
I mean, everything was by the book.
But, um...
...after my mom died, he, um,
seemed like a different person.
He was taking money on the side,
he got investigated by internal affairs...
...and one day, he just, uh, got in his car,
drove it to Malibu,
put in his favorite CD...
...he took out his gun...
....he put it to his head...
[sensual blues music]
[Angel breaths heavily] I can't.
[sighs]
What's wrong?
I can't go through with this right now.
[sensual blues music resumes]
[sighs]
[ominous soft music]
[suspenseful music]
[crickets chirping]
[bush rustling]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[dramatic music]
[Angel panting]
[dog barking]
[sirens blaring in distance]
[Angel panting]
[man groans]
[Yordan] Where's the girl?
Put your shirt on.
Let's go.
[tires screeching]
[Angel screams]
[Angel panting]
[Angel screaming]
No!
[panting and groaning]
[Yordan] I got the shot.
No. No guns.
It's too dangerous.
[suspenseful music]
[Angel crying] No!
[man grunting]
[man groaning]
[men grunting and groaning]
[dramatic music]
[police sirens blaring in distance]
Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
[tense music]
What the hell were you doing outside?
I was just getting some air.
Yeah, what were you doing out there?
Thinking.
About you.
How come they didn't kill her?
-I don't know. -She's hiding something from us.
She must have something they want.
[phone ringing]
[phone beeps]
[exhales] Phone.
It's the phone.
They've had us bugged the whole time.
[Yordan] You mean Rouse had us bugged the whole time.
It could have been anybody in the department.
Anybody?
Come on.
He was my father's best friend.
I know.
Your dad is in a great place,
and he's still with you.
And you can call him to be with you.
You can pray to him, you can laugh with him.
He's not gone. He's still here.
But you disappear when you are so sad...
...over a loss that's not counted as a loss.
It's counted as a higher moment in the evolution...
...of what we call, what's that word?
Uh, destiny.
Let go of the pain and sadness, because it's selfish.
Let's be selfless.
When we're not thinking about ourselves so much, then we're...
...understanding the reality of someone passing on and going to a better place.
And I got good news for you. You're gonna see him again.
You're gonna be with him again. And right now, he's looking after you.
He's looking over you. He's not looking out for you,
you have to out for yourself, but he's looking over you.
He's proud of you. You're his son.
[Tyler] I called Rouse.
He wants us to meet him at the Old Valley Airfield.
It's time to settle things.
Are you all right?
Did they hurt you?
[gentle music]
I'm sorry.
It's just that I was worried about you.
[stutters] I was afraid they might have killed you.
Why don't you trust me?
Should I?
[sighs] I've been a cop too long, I just...
[people chattering]
Um... Uh... [sighs]
-Hello. -Ciao, Rosie. How are you today?
-Fine, thank you. -No, just a little bit. Just a little.
-You look beautiful today. -Thank you very much.
-You doing okay? -Yeah.
You're doing a good job.
-Thank you very much. -Appreciate it.
[phone rings]
-Excuse me a second. -Okay.
-[phone beeps] -Hello.
They're at the old airport.
-What? -I want you to send your men in in a couple of hours
and I'll be gone with the prize by then.
[suspenseful music]
[Nugentti Jr] That's not the deal, Rouse.
That's not the deal.
Fine, I'll be there.
You be there.
[phones beep]
Come here. [sighs]
Take care of Rouse.
He's done.
Do it.
[Rouse whistling]
Good evening, Captain.
Good evening. Good evening, Buzz.
I have something I wanna show you.
-Oh, really? -You wanna s-- You wanna see it?
-Come on. Let's go this way. -Sure. Let's go.
Good to run into you. Uh...
Oh! Sorry.
-It's okay. -Oh, well. I stumble around sometimes when I'm nervous.
I want you to know something...
...that you have been inspirational to me in this operation.
You're a lovely woman. When you stand up for yourself
and what your beliefs are, it's very rewarding.
So I have a gift to give you, and it starts with a hug.
-[gunshot] -[Buzz groans]
[suspenseful music]
But I still love you.
I gotta find out...
[sighs] ...who I am.
I'm ready for anything.
Just bring it to me. I'm ready for anything, just bring it to me.
[engine starts]
[tense music]
[chopper whirring]
[Tyler] Stay in the car.
How many clips you got?
-Three. -Three.
Where do you think you're going? He told you to stay in the car. You're safer in the car.
-He's right. -Trust us.
-We'll come back for you. -Okay. Be careful.
[Yordan] I think she's mad at me.
-Good luck. -[Yordan] Hey, don't shoot at me.
I'm the guy with the green jacket.
[tense music continues]
[chopper whirring]
[guns click]
[gunshots]
[dramatic music]
[groans]
[gunshots]
[vehicle approaching]
[whispering] I told you to stay in the car.
-I heard gunfire. -[sighs]
I'll come back for you.
-[gunshots] -[groans]
[suspenseful music]
[man groans]
-What are you doing here? -It's a long story, Dan,
but I am not the model cop I used to be.
Rouse convinced your dad and me to work with Nugentti Jr.
But then Rouse started killing our own,
and I bowed out.
What are you talking about?
Paxton.
Rouse and Nugentti killed Paxton.
What do we do now?
Well, we kill Rouse and Nugentti.
[chuckles]
After you.
[suspenseful music]
[gunshots]
[both groans]
[footsteps approach]
You know, it didn't have to be this way.
[gunshots]
[Nugentti Jr] I want this girl alive.
This Jap fuck is giving me a headache!
-Put down your weapons. -[Nugentti Jr] All right, Danny.
-[Tyler] Where's Rouse? -[Nugentti Jr] He's on his way.
You got me. Take it easy. It's okay.
Put your guns down, it's okay.
All right? I'm gonna put it down.
Slow.
Good. Come on. What's it gonna take, Danny?
Huh? How much? What's your price?
I don't have a price.
You got a price. Your father had a price.
I got what you want, you got what I want.
-What are you talking about? -I got the rat.
I'll hand 'em to you on a silver platter.
Just give me the girl.
Dirty cops get caught sooner or later. No deal.
You know, I'm sorry about your father.
But it wasn't suicide.
Rouse felt he was becoming a risk,
so we had to do what we had to do.
[dramatic music]
-Now! -[gunshots]
-[screams] -Don't you say a word.
[grenade whistles]
[grenade explodes]
[groans]
[gunshots]
[sobbing]
Jesus. Where's Yordan?
Shit, I lost him, but he's called for backup by now.
Goddamn it.
[Nugentti Jr] Get the chopper. Let's go.
-He's on my tail. Let's go. -All right.
[Angel screaming and sobbing]
-No, no, no, no! Come on, come on, let's go! -[Angel] No!
[dramatic music continues]
[gunshots]
[chopper whirring]
-[grunts] -Give me your gun!
Get off me, motherfucker!
You never learn, huh, Tyler? Don't take off, he's got my leg!
[screams] Give me your gun!
-Get him off! -[screams] Give me your fucking gun!
-[JJ] Get him off! Get him off! -[grunting]
[Nugentti Jr] Give me your fucking gun! Quick!
[Nugentti Jr screams]
[gunshots]
[Yordan over radio] Land your helicopter right now!
[screaming]
[Yordan over radio] Put it down now!
[dramatic music continues]
[chopper whirring]
[police sirens blaring]
[gentle music]
[police radio chattering]
[birds chirping]
[calm music]
So what are you gonna do now?
Well, after I go to Arizona...
...I'm gonna live the rest of my life.
Well, you got a fresh start, so don't blow it.
Aren't you gonna stick around and see how it turns out?
I'm still looking for that dark and brooding man.
[chuckles]
I'm not sure you'd be happy living on a cop's salary.
Maybe we don't have to.
We've got Nugentti's money.
[tense music]
[tense music intensifies]
[calm music]
[tense music]