so
james kelly come on down the party's starting
i hate this house i hate our parents i hate
birthdays most of all i hate her she still
thinks i'm ten she's a [ __ ] that's why our
mom is a you know where dad is probably where
he's been since we moved into this [ __ ] locked
himself in the bathroom do you blame him
this is unacceptable i worked all morning
on this cake making it just the way you like
it so you better come down now come on we
better go down and face the torture last time
she was screaming like this while the neighbors
called the cops on us was she really that
surprised to see birth control pills in my
room i'm 18 for [ __ ] sake i am going to
burn that thing i'm going to dig a hole in
the backyard and burn it god damn him for
bringing something so ugly into my house
there's my birthday boy i remember the day
you were born 39 hours of labor the doctor
didn't think i'd make it you were a fat baby
where's dad forget about him this is james's
day let's sing happy birthday to you
time to make a wish shouldn't we ask dad to
come down oh he'll be coming it's a surprise
shh you don't want to ruin james's surprise
do you
make a wish james dear
now remember don't tell anyone you wish or
it won't come true you've got your wish son
this isn't funny
is this recording
started over 40 years ago at that house
for the next several decades the evil spread
like a plague you can't control it's like
a disease infecting everyone and everything
he comes in that wretched place was destroyed
a long time ago but not before
there are dozens of documented and apparently
related incidences of unexplained phenomena
dating back to the 1980s then an old clock
later a mirror in the replica dollhouse our
believed to possess the same evil that was
birthed in that place
that wicked toy was obtained from that very
home
but even i know
keep it down will ya oh [ __ ] you nobody's
gonna hear us down here anyways
so why are we here again instead of at the
movies movie you want a movie do you know
what happened in this house don't know don't
care last week ty pangborn a rhode island
state senator dressed up as a clown for his
son's birthday oh well holy [ __ ] that's
more than enough reason for me to break into
an abandoned house and crawl around a dark
basement it gets better it better get better
while the mother son and daughter were all
downstairs lighting the candles of the birthday
cake dear old dad came down in full bozo regalia
and blew the entire family away with a shotgun
and as you can tell by the dry state of my
pants i have clearly not pissed myself in
fear
we are here on a mission and that mission
is money see there are a lot of sickos in
this world and rumor has it somewhere in this
house tucked away is a bit of memorabilia
from the murder scene get this and there's
freaks who collect this [ __ ] i mean we can't
sell anything on ebay but in the dark web
well let's just say that what we're looking
for has a pretty high asking price okay money
i like what exactly are we looking for a painting
of a clown oh i [ __ ] hate clowns nobody
likes clowns but we better start looking for
it i'll search down here with sarah guy why
don't you search upstairs we'll meet on the
second floor in 20 minutes sounds like a plan
all right
so
oh you [ __ ] you [ __ ] [ __ ] why do you
have to be such a [ __ ] [ __ ] when i see
an ass that shapely i just have to grab a
handful
you know that sexual harassment i don't have
to tolerate it oh can you tolerate this
i could find the time but not right now
come on let's go upstairs and see if guys
found anything yet fine
come on guy let's get the [ __ ] out of here
there you are
sarah i found it i found it grab guy and let's
get the [ __ ] out of here
let's have some fun mother you know
what fun is fun is where i eat your [ __ ] heart
out of your chest
so
this is the one are you serious
i know it's exactly like the one i had as
a kid honey are you sure you wouldn't rather
get that new ps4 game instead no way this
is perfect i can't guarantee that that's all
right i don't mind i'm great with my hands
sure i could fix him up how much did you say
he was fifty dollars fifty dollars what's
sold out online he is so worth it i won't
be needing one i'm keeping goodbye
come back soon
what do you think i think you need help
hungry i'm starving i should have ordered
more egg rolls i still can't believe you got
that kid's toy the monkey is awesome what
do you want with that thing i'm gonna fix
him up give him life again i lost my old one
when we moved when i was a kid i always missed
him this sort of makes up for that what am
i gonna do with you
what on earth was that probably rats it's
that time of year rats you serious
the ones around here are harmless if it makes
you feel better i can set some traps in the
morning oh i think i'd like you to do that
i'll do it tomorrow afternoon i got that meeting
in the morning and i need to hit the haze
soon promise you'll take care of it i promise
ah
hey sexy how'd you sleep last night nightmares
i'm running late what about
your coffee it's okay i only woke up an hour
early to make it for you honey
did you forget something
then
is that you
wow
which
two
hmm
sisters
oh
tt
pieces
yes
over there and i see a moon
wow
this is about the monkey again damn it ben
i've been hearing strange noises all day footsteps
doors slamming first i thought it was you
coming back for something but you weren't
there when i went to look it's probably the
rats in the attic making that noise i told
you i'd set some traps today it's not rats
rats don't slam doors it's something else
look i don't know what to tell you i've had
a long day i'll go set the traps and then
i'm going to bed you're not even listening
to me
oh wait baby
there are droppings everywhere definitely
rats i'm sorry for getting so upset it's fine
the traps are set let's go to bed
so
what's the matter are you okay
i can't sleep i'm going for a drive
so
hey baby how you doing tonight good now that
i found you good are you looking to party
always get in oh okay
so where are you taking this your place
my daughters
so if you like
hey you're going too fast what is wrong with
you dirty
stop [ __ ]
so how do you feel this morning rejuvenated
where did you end up going last night just
around cleared my head listen i'll see you
tonight i love you
there's no droppings no footprints traps haven't
been hit either what are you saying you got
no rats up here ma'am you're clean as a whistle
i don't understand my husband said he saw
droppings and i hear them or something up
here moving around all the time well whatever
it was it's gone now you got nothing up here
wait what do i owe you don't worry about it
this time just keep the trap set and you'll
be fine i'll see my way out
foreign
wow
what is it now michelle there's a ghost in
this house a ghost what are you talking about
it threw a knife at me a knife yes this afternoon
after the exterminator left wait what was
the exterminator doing here i already set
the rat traps it's not wraps you said there
were droppings you lied to me why did you
lie about it get off my case michelle i've
been working all day i just want to shower
before bed what's wrong with you why are you
acting so different it's that monkey i know
it is the monkey the monkey get off that already
you know sometimes i think you just don't
want me to be happy ben what are you talking
about benny please
ben are you awake
i'm sorry i guess maybe sometimes i overreact
a little
oh okay honey honey slow
such a oh mouth [ __ ]
ah
i just don't know what to do with you michelle
i think you need help this house isn't haunted
you're acting crazy i think you need to see
someone maybe we should split up temporarily
split up we can't go on like this michelle
you haven't been a wife to me in months what
did you call last night what are you talking
about you beat the [ __ ] out of me and then
it had your way what are you talking about
all these bruises what bruises
we'll finish this conversation when i get
home tonight i don't have time to deal with
your neurosis right now but the monkey
so
yes
is is he beating you
oh you poor thing
thanks for listening i just didn't have anyone
else to talk to
well if you ever need a safe place to go i'm
right next door i really appreciate that thanks
the other day and i noticed
you know there's a there's something up there
that she doesn't like thanks for stopping
over i'm feeling better now okay well don't
be a stranger you know if you need anything
just come by all right thanks again
you little baby what was wrong what was happening
did i imagine that
jungle
um
and i tried to give you a receipt
an estate
i don't know anything about that i don't have
time for this lady i've got better things
to do i'm gonna go now bye wait
so
just in 12 confirmed dead just outside of
lincoln in the state of nebraska information
is coming through when 12 bodies have been
found just outside of lincoln police have
yet to release the names of the dead but most
are believed to be members of the same family
witnesses are said to have heard several gunshots
coming from the house in the area believed
to be owned by mr mark jensen we go over now
to lincoln police to speak to officer chad
wilson officer wilson hi peter yes i'm afraid
that the final number of deaths has now been
confirmed at 14 and i can also confirm that
the body of mr mark jensen was one of them
mr jensen was and remains our chief suspect
in this investigation due to his having shot
himself at the roadside however what led mr
jensen to kill his entire family still remains
a complete mystery he was a well-known and
respected member of this neighborhood if all
is as it seems we've closed off the surrounding
areas to present visitors and respectfully
ask all members of the public to stay away
whilst we continue to invest thank you officer
wilson apparently we've got a recording of
a neighbor of mr jensen's let's see what he
had to say
i heard all these gunshots
so that's why i came outside to see what was
going on
and that's when i saw the blood i'm sorry
i i can't say anymore so what makes a man
turn a gun on his entire family i have with
me today father hudson west and retired police
detective dustin stafford gentlemen hi peter
how would you evaluate this situation uh well
situations like this are a difficult of the
best of times uh coming into it from um you
know fairly cold like yourself i've just seen
what's been going on in the news and things
like that um without knowing any kind of background
information on uh mr jensen i believe his
name was it's very very difficult to actually
appreciate what's going through his head at
the time um you know i don't i personally
have no uh working knowledge of him so i you
know it's very difficult to assess as to whether
there was any kind of mental instability there
whether it's being drug led whether you know
excuse me you guys you you always go down
that it's it's drugs and it's it's it's bad
family homes well i wasn't saying that but
you do you that you you people just don't
understand that there are other things happening
that there's there's other forces and and
something like this you know somebody just
wiping out an entire family and you know this
gotta be more than just a guy flipping on
drugs this is nothing to do with drugs and
this is this is spiritual i'm telling you
right i'm telling you that what happens here
is that they get possessed it winds me up
so much all right obviously i'm just looking
at the information that we're getting on on
the news ourselves well i'll give you information
i'll give you information i'll give everybody
information have you ever seen when a wall
just comes to life have you ever seen mirrors
have you ever seen furniture houses have you
ever seen a theater full of people dispossessed
have you ever seen a church have you have
you ever seen a doll's house have you ever
seen blood just spreading from the wall have
you ever no you couldn't have seen it because
you know why you couldn't have seen it because
you wouldn't be sitting there just like a
normal guy going it's drugs it's it's racist
it's it's not sure i mean i i don't know where
you're getting your information from you know
we're looking at the fact that there's 12
12 dead here um you know reports i'll tell
you i'll tell you i'll tell you i'll tell
you where to get my information i've been
there i've i've seen i've seen this i know
what it looks like i've seen it with these
eyes these eyes no no you you people you you
just don't want to hear the truth i can't
do this i'm sorry i can't do this
okay and i think we should just go to a commercial
break
what are you okay
thank you
you've got 10 minutes
so tell me what happened in your words you're
in great danger what do you mean you have
a monkey don't you how did you know about
that
that's the only reason why you'd be here it's
evil isn't it
it's more than just evil it's it's the vessel
for which evil transfers between physical
locations spreading all over like like a plague
it all began back in amityville
after he murdered his entire family everything
from the estate sale went to auction houses
and antique shops could be a
whole 40 years before i would find it i don't
understand so the ghosts of the family entered
the monkey and made it evil it's the monkey
itself that caused murders in the first place
something demonic took over that toy very
long time ago and won't let go how do you
know all this it was me that brought it back
home
it's my fault my father killed my entire family
i purchased that monkey from the amityville
antique shop as a present for his 50th birthday
it all started when i bought that [ __ ] monkey
wow ah mom would you look at this it is
this looks like just like the one i had when
i was a kid where did you find this at an
old antique store back home i saw it and i
remembered you said you had one when you were
little so i figured you'd like it
like it i love it dear thank you you're welcome
brown knows her wind it up all right
sorry i didn't think to check to make sure
if it actually worked it's all right let me
take a look at it
pathetic of course he doesn't want you
stop this you're better than him you're better
than this you don't deserve this do you do
you who is it
who's there
dad
dad it's julia i don't mean a bargain but
are you okay
dad
dad oh [ __ ] sorry dad um we're all ready
to go go yeah you know to the zoo
i'm not feeling well i'm gonna stay here you
kids have fun
are you sure your family won't miss us we
can meet up with them later i want you now
what about your grandma won't she hear us
or your dad don't be such a baby grandma's
basically deaf my dad's probably holed up
in his room and cheyenne's probably dead drunk
soon so don't worry about her either
come on stud
this is how you raise your kids mark to [ __
] where their grandparents can hear them and
out of the holy union of marriage
it's shameful really something should be done
god damn this is some good food i haven't
met don't you talk like that in this house
you got me there babe
go take care of that racket with
so
stop me daddy
you got julia the know-it-all spinster jenny
the drunk you let brianna [ __ ] that dimwit
under your own roof britney knocked up don't
even get me started on that [ __ ] anthony
my children are good decent people you're
losing your family right under your own eyes
and you don't even see it
jesus weeps for your family mark
what do you want me to do well you're off
to a good start you just need to keep cleaning
house
dad oh my god what have you done
no no no no oh my god i think the baby's coming
you can't hide them forever finish it no do
it
what's wrong daddy i don't know nothing's
making any sense anymore i know
i know
you look so much like your mother that's why
i'm your favorite
stop me daddy
that's not what i meant by saving family son
this this is the solution save them from themselves
just like you did carol
oh
daddy
and not just the toy either there's been murders
connected to that house every few years for
the past several decades lamps and and clocks
and mirrors and even a dollhouse from that
evil place have all been present during several
copycat killings in the 90s i think i remember
reading about some of those weren't there
some movies made or something hollywood loves
to exploit what makes money
maybe maybe i'll even sell my story for a
made-for-tv movie so how do we get rid of
it
we must destroy the physical body forcing
it to leave and move on so then that won't
really stop it will it
can't stop evil only ward it off
evil never dies time's up
you must destroy it you can't let it take
over anyone else
is
where have you been i want to see someone
you man
oh
hmm
flies
what happened what's going on let's get out
of here
how may i help you
so
but we made
and they demonized
he's shy
oh
this is
is
shine
shout out
so
you