Hello everybody
My name is Abdeen
in this world
Everything is fine to me
And it will always be beautiful...
I hope you'll keep looking down
This is my first time on TV
If you want to know how I act
Then please keep watching
All right
The show is on!
Title: Slaughtered Vomit Dolls (2006)
aka: Vomit Gore 1
Will you do anything for me?
Um
- are you willing to say anything I say?
- I will do whatever you want
willing to die for you
Murder for you
This is my little yard
please, please
do not do that
please don't do this
I was insulted by a priest
Wish he went to hell
Wish this never happened
- help , help - i'm fucked
so painful
I can't forget all that
because it hurts so much...
It hurts to the bone
I used to trust him so much
But he's stubborn...
God, save me
I really can't forget all that
I used to trust him so much
God save me
But I can't resist that temptation...
That was April 5, 1949
i can't forget
My name is Angela Abdeen
this is my profession
I want to live in a big house
drive well
why am i like this
but i like men
like to be fucked by men
it's hell
It's a fairy experience
The devil in me drives me
drives me to have fun
make me want to die
feeling of orgasm
make me irresistible
It's like a demon is holding on to me
Are you happy? !
Cool!
This is life
for this life
I swear
I swear to give my soul to Satan
hope he bless me
bless me for 13 years
After 13 years I will be dedicated to him
Dedicated to the so-called hell kingdom
I swore
my child
Come with me to sacrifice to Satan
I promise Satan will kill them
Damn Satan
Lord of all evil!
This is my home...
March 31, 1994 at Excel Theron Hotel
Look at my embarrassment
Oh my god
Can you do me a favor?
Can you help me?
Hold!
You know, I'm very expensive
Do you have money?
My price is very high
If you have no money...
you don't even want to sleep with me...
I am very expensive
I am back again
look over there
See so many horses?
Everybody look over there
there
That foal is mine
How am I doing?
I'm doing well
I'm so good
I have got. a little tired
Stop filming, I'm going to bed
want me? !
i still remember her
Hope she is still alive...
hurry up, hurry up
hurry up
Can you still breathe?
Can you still fucking breathe?
now it's right
very good
do not want
Can you still speak?
Can?
oh my gosh it's so cool
It's so cool
i don't belong here
...I don't belong here
It's hard to be a dancer
make me feel sick
This is the last time I swear
you are my only friend
the only good friend to me
I don't know...I...
Oh
I am a call girl
That's right
what's your name…
How much money do you have?
watch me perform
I can speak slower than you
I can…
speak the slowest
This time let you have enough addiction
help
I beg you
am i sexy?
You like this? !
Oh my god…
I can not stand it any more
help...
10:47pm
- your face is so pretty - of course
Want to be on TV?
and more
This world is just hell...
i'm so stupid
stupid? !
just stupid
I don't think you are stupid!
I am the person
respect others
sit there and listen to me
one thing after another
just for the money...
For my money... I became a showgirl
Guys pay to go to bars to see me perform
to sleep with me
just pay
Anyone can sleep with me
who are you? !
my name is busters
- is it cool? ! - very cool
I only care about money
Just give money
I do it every day
People only give money to dance
I only have feelings for you
I don't care who is looking for me
Nobody can find me
I don't care. I don't like people finding me
Look, I made it myself
I didn't know you just...
How about me?
Oh
Because I don't...
feel like... don't belong here
Maybe he's been hurt a lot before.
That's when I was a kid
I'm very good in bed
How do you want me to serve you tonight?
Anyway, do what you want
I don't know what I am...
i don't care
i don't care about anything
I want…
want to be a big star
I want everyone to see me on TV
Better than a Hollywood star!
I don't care about anyone
13 years old
I burned our church down there
a fire
Later I...
I ran away from home
He raped me the day before
I was still a virgin
I started selling myself so I could have money to go to school
I always wanted to grow up
be a cinderella
But I became a showgirl
huh... huh
uh... uh...
Nas, blah blah blah...
Nas Pata
Whether you believe it or not
Before I was 13, I had big dreams
much bigger than now
have to face them
I have to whet the appetite of the spectators
Those guys like to be sexy
I was drunk once
On stage
I am dancing...
he did a lot of bad things
I just quit drinking
That's why I drink
Because I like being drunk
i had a nightmare
it's about a girl of mine
I'm doing it now in Texas
far from home
Texans are cool
straight eyes
Texas is such a weird place
People are very generous
Believe it, they love blowjobs make me feel like throwing up
So I deliberately let myself vomit
I made myself nauseous afterwards
But then again
I still think Texans are better
There is. just disgusting
I even use my own fingers
to adjust your throat
Digging my fingers deep into my throat...
It feels very strange, you know?
But only if you practice
Look, put it in your mouth like this
very very disgusting
[died on March 3rd, 1994 in Queens, New York] Must put your finger on this part...
Sometimes the hand touches the teeth
have. Do you feel like dying?
I break my mouth sometimes
But you have to practice
Because those disgusting Texans like to put their ass on your face
very very disgusting
I have it later. I vomited blood...
I still vomit when I get home...
Horrible
Poor Sophne
how miserable
Do you think you are thin and beautiful? !
[Henry] I want you to see what is beautiful
Hello!
i like to peel
Especially like to skin people
Like it?
how beautiful
There's more to come...
I just have...
have a feeling
that is…
i'm in trouble
Will you do anything for me?
- are you willing to say anything I say? - I will do whatever you want
willing to die for you
Willing to kill for you
that's more interesting
i am a prostitute
I just go to bed
I can't bear to watch it
It's still pretty though, isn't it?
I burned our church down there
a fire
Later I...
I can't dance at home anymore...
I've been on the road of no return
Dancing at night
Standing on the street during the day…
I don't care about anyone, I don't care about anyone
It makes me feel sick
Godfather likes to drink whiskey
like…
Likes to abuse me... I can't resist...
after he drinks
lifted my skirt
He shoved the bottle into my body and he saw blood
Since I was a virgin at the time he continued...
I was only 13 then
I later burned that church down
Burned down that church...
Burned the priest...
I ran away from home later
I grew up wanting to be…
quick!
Hurry up!
help
No, help
don't, don't
i can't sleep
i am always awake
I am really scared
I always have weird dreams
I dreamed of monsters...
Want to sleep with me? !
I don't want to die...
I feel like I'm dead now
i don't care about anything
do what you want
get on me
I'm also addicted to smoking
I wasn't like this before
I used to be very lively and cheerful
you are my patron
i like to be fucked
April 5, 1994
I'll give you a blowjob for $20
$60 can sleep with me for an hour
Give me another $20 for blowjob and cumshot
Add another $16 for anal sex
All right
My name is Angela Abdeen
I always hit myself when I dance
hurry up
let's go hunting
bye, i'm leaving soon
hurry up