[UPBEAT MUSIC]
[GRUNTS AND CHUCKLES]
[CHUCKLING]
[GRUNTING]
Why? One of the kids
stuck some stuff.
[GRUNTING]
We are now approaching
the cookie section.
Would anybody like to select
some cookies?
[GRUNTING]
"...chemically
separated chicken.
"Modified wheat flour.
"Twice as sodium erythorbate.
"Sodium nitrate." Tempting.
No, thanks.
Let's find something to eat.
Xanthan gum.
Sorbic acid,
sodium benzoate,
calca...
David, this is not for you.
This will give you
brain damage.
Stop staring, you're not
so pretty yourself.
Hi, David.
[CHUCKLES]
[DAVID GRUNTING]
SALLY: Hold the door. Hold it.
Oh, yeah. All right, get
the door open and let me in.
SALLY:
Yes! Home sweet home.
Take off the shoes,
turn on the TV.
And yes, ladies and gentleman,
it is another scintillating
afternoon at the Goodson home.
All right.
For our matinee today
we are pleased
to present
The Wizard of Oz.
"Yes, isn't that the movie
you've only seen
like 30,000 times?"
Yes, but,
it is starring Judy Garland,
Frank Morgan, Ray Bolger,
Bert Lahr and Jack Haley.
Approximate screening time,
one hour forty-one minutes.
Copyright Loew's Incorporated.
Enjoy.
What do you want
for lunch, sweetie?
Huh?
All right, here are your
choices.
I have, I have...
Lasagna?
And I have cabbage rolls.
Lasagna, cabbage?
Cabbage, lasagna?
Cab... cab...
Which one do you want?
May I suggest the cabbage roll,
because tonight we are having
spaghetti and meat balls.
Which do you want?
Come on.
Cabbage rolls!
Good choice, honey.
This is living.
Hmm.
[GRUNTING]
Mrs. Goodson?
Somebody here for you.
SALLY:Yeah.
This is Gladys Johnson of
The Department of Child Welfare.
Who did you say
you were looking for?
Mrs. Goodson?
Mrs. Sally Goodson.
Mrs. Goodson isn't in,
this is the maid.
Mrs. Goodson, it is urgent
that we speak.
I said this is the maid
and I got to go clean
or I'm gonna get fired.
The wolves are
nipping at your heels,
honey bunch.
Don't worry.
I won't let them
get their hands on you.
Hi, Sid.
Is my sister home?
I don't know.
She just said
she was the maid.
Oh! Delusions
of grandeur, huh?
David, use the spoon.
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
I'm not playing
Miracle Worker
here, David.
Use the spoon.
[LAUGHING]
Use the spoon, David.
Love of my life,
use the spoon.
Hello! David!
Use the spoon.
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
BEA: Open up.
I know you're in there.
Oh, great!
David, Aunty Bea has come
to call. What a treat!
[INCREASES TV VOLUME]
Sorry, I didn't hear
the bell.
Yeah, right.
I would think that you would
welcome someone to talk to.
I have someone
to talk to.
David and I were
just discussing cutlery.
So I heard.
So did everyone else
on the floor.
[KISSES]
Everyone except David.
Okay. Sit down.
I wanna talk to you.
Who's dead?
Abraham Lincoln. Sit down
All right,
you are drinking wine
in the afternoon now.
It's leftover from
the Academy Awards.
I had a party.
I bet that's the last time
you cleaned this place. Oh,
why doesn't that surprise me?
Go home.
Eat off your floor.
What are you doing
here anyway?
I was at the dentist.
And I thought I come by
in person,
and make you promise me
something.
What? I shudder to ask.
Promise me that you'll have
lunch with me on Sunday.
[TSKS] You and who else?
He's very charming.
I'm sure.
And he's on his 40's.
Don't fix me up
anymore.
Recently widowed,
has no children.
[SIGHS]
Sounds really hot.
Look. Look.
Just do me a favor.
He's lonely.
Oh, so now what are you
doing? Setting up the 100
neediest cases?
I told him all about you
and David. He'd love
to meet you.
Uh-uh. I can't do it.
I'm busy on Sunday.
Doing what?
Dancing
Swan Lake,
that's what.
Sally, just do it.
I mean, you owe me this.
Can he come?
No, he cannot come.
This is for adults only,
except for you.
God, you turning
into a recluse,
you know that?
Thank you very much. [SIGHS]
Okay, honey,
your cousin Justine
is gonna come over on Sunday
and spend the day with you.
You like that? Now, why
don't you just eat it
with a spoon, right there.
[SCREAMS]
Ah! What did I do?
Only the right hand can put
food in the mouth.
Don't you know anything? Why?
I don't know, it's a little
secret between David and God.
All right, I'll see you
on Sunday.
And if you please, wear
something that doesn't have
dried food all over it.
Yes, go. Give me time
to scrape a dress.
Walk me to the elevator.
[SCOFFS]
Like you're six-years-old
and you can't
get there yourself.
[SCOFFS]
You need a babysitter.
I got a letter
from Susan.
Susan who?
Susan, your daughter Susan.
She's pregnant.
[SIGHS] What?
[SCOFFS] She's only 18.
She's 19.
Already?
Did she happen to mention
whether or not she's married?
She's getting married
in a few weeks.
I like that.
First things first.
Why don't you call her?
Nah. I call her,
she'll probably miscarry.
[SIGHS]
We haven't been so close
and she chose to move
3,000 miles away from me.
You should go
to the wedding.
I don't have the wardrobe.
Well, buy the wardrobe.
Yeah. Freelance editors
make that kind of money.
I'll give you the money.
No, you will not give me
the money.
It would be my pleasure.
It was your pleasure
to buy us a VCR.
You know, I don't like you
that much to
make you that happy.
[ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS]
But don't worry about those
hemorrhoids, they'll go away.
The itching will stop.
[SIGHS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[GRUNTING] David.
Did you hear that?
Your sister's pregnant.
And getting married.
In 19.
[GASPS]
I think you and I are
a little bit
out of touch, buddy.
[GROANING]
Don't be upset that you
weren't invited
to the wedding.
She didn't
invite me either.
But maybe that's better.
You know
that person's gonna
show up.
[SNORTS]
Remember him?
He used to be your father.
But, you know what?
It wouldn't have killed her
to invite us.
I used to be her mother.
SUSAN:
I don't wanna
talk about it.
PHILIP:
Come on, Susan,
you were fine.
Everybody forgets lines.
Daddy, will you stop?
Will you forget
the damn play!
Susan, watch your mouth.
What happened?
PHILIP: She's upset.
She forgot a few lines
in the play.
SALLY:
Honey, Shakespeare,
who knew?
I bet everybody thought it was
supposed to be that way.
How would you know?
You weren't there.
Sweetheart, the babysitter
canceled at the last minute.
What was I supposed to do?
[SCOFFS]
Get a different babysitter.
Sweetheart, David doesn't
like strangers.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
For once
he could have adjusted.
Wouldn't have killed him.
Well, it didn't
kill her either.
You know, if you weren't
in here sulking,
you could come out here
and have some
terrific brownies.
Sweetie...
this is Junior high school,
the critics weren't there.
Neither were you.
You can be a real beast
sometimes, you know that?
Yeah?
I hate you, too.
You don't hate me,
I'm your mother.
You may resent me,
and you may be filled
with ambivalence,
offended,
and indignant as hell,
but trust me,
daughters don't hate
their mothers.
Except in my case,
that's different.
Why not we just...
cut the crap and you give me
a big old kiss.
Huh? [LAUGHING]
[SIGHS] So what if we weren't
invited to the wedding.
[TSKS] To hell with it.
I've got an idea.
Why don't you come in my room
with me and help me pick out
a dress for my blind date?
Please, God, he'll be blind.
Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man.
Oh, here's one.
This is good.
How is this?
What? What?
Don't give me that look.
You think I look like
a prison matron in this,
don't you?
[SCOFFS] You're right. I do.
You're always right.
Oh, now here's one. This.
It's a little acrylic creation.
Sally Goodson, equally at home
yachting the afternoon away,
or in the frozen
produce department
of her neighborhood A&P.
Honey?
All right. Tomorrow you and I
will go out shopping and buy
me a new dress.
[HORN TOOTING]
Mrs. Goodson?
Yes.
I am Gladys Johnson from
The Department
of Child Welfare.
Please don't make me
file a report on you.
Can we go somewhere
and talk?
If I buy you a cup of coffee,
is that considered a bribe?
I'll buy you one.
Got an expense account
up to a dollar.
Let's go, David.
I sent you two letters.
Damn, that post office.
Slipped the last one
under your door.
Yeah, it's probably
still there with the rest
of the debris.
In it I explained
the department
is taking a new census
of handicapped children
in the Tri-state area.
Now, when computers
in Connecticut were put online,
a discrepancy was noticed.
Yeah? What?
New York has David assigned
to a facility in Connecticut,
but Connecticut never heard
of him.
Well, that is a discrepancy,
isn't it?
You jerking
me around, lady?
I'm trying.
It's a state law.
Every handicap child who can
benefit from a program must be
in one. Is he in one or not?
It's not a difficult question,
Mrs. Goodson.
If he's in a program
just say, otherwise
I'll have to report it.
Why?
Because if I don't,
I could lose my job.
And I can't afford
to lose my job.
Be straight with me, okay?
All right, go ahead.
What do you wanna know?
The last information we have
is from the Reynold school.
That's his last placement?
Yeah.
Then where did the authorities
get the idea that David
was going to a program
in Connecticut?
From me, I told them
we were moving. Why?
To protect him.
From what?
The bastards at
the Reynold school.
There are other programs.
We have been there.
Programs, and schools
and rehab centers,
and all they did
was terrify David.
My son is damaged.
He's not gonna wake up
in a couple of days
and go,
"Oh, now I feel great,
send me off to college."
This is as good as it gets.
But this only get this good
at home.
Within those four walls,
badly needed paint,
that's where he's safe,
that's where he's happy,
and that's where you can
leave him.
There are so many different
kinds of programs.
Oh, man. You know,
I'm talking to a wall.
Come on, David,
let's go.
Sally, sit down.
David, move it.
Hey, come on.
But, come...
[SIGHS]
GLADYS: Sally?
Sally, I'm trying
to help you.
Well, put in your report
you didn't find me.
I can't do that.
You can't do that.
Of course not.
You and the whole medical
establishment think they ate
the Last Supper.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[HORN BLOWING]
What?
Stupid, son of a bitch.
You like your work, Gladys?
Not always. Mostly I like
the paycheck that almost
supports my two kids
now that their
father took off.
You, too?
Me, too.
You think they can smell this
planet from the next galaxy?
If they got noses.
So, what you gonna do?
[SIGHS]
Come back another day.
You weren't home.
But David is going
into a program.
The sooner you get used
to that, the sooner you both
will be happy.
Hey, Gladys.
Thanks for the coffee.
[MELANCHOLY PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hi, there, champ.
It's me, momma.
Come here.
Come here. What are you doing
over here, stuck at the corner?
Shh. What are you doing?
Let me see you. [GRUNTING]
Ooh! Mmm!
Mrs. Goodson, you'll have
to wait outside.
SALLY: In a pig's eye.
I beg your pardon?
He has peed himself.
[MUMBLING]
He's sitting over here
in the corner
in his own urine and nobody
even noticed.
Mrs. Goodson, I think you're
making too much of this.
It happens.
It doesn't happen
in my house.
In my house he doesn't
pee himself.
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
So, Dave, you think they'll
let me in the restaurant
wearing this thing?
I hope so.
Um, I can't believe I'm going
on a date at my age.
This is so stupid.
David. David.
You be my date, okay?
You sit here like we're in
the restaurant, okay?
All right, you're my date.
[HUMMING]
So...
whatever your name is.
Um, I must admit
that I expected
a much older man.
[CHUCKLES]
Do you like that?
[CHUCKLES] Get this.
So, then I'll say,
um...
"What is it you said
you did for a living?"
[GRUNTS]
"You manufacture
toilet seats?
"Oh, my God, that is
so interesting." [LAUGHS]
[LAUGHING]
Come on, David, it's okay.
We're having a good time here.
Come on, sweetie,
kids tell jokes
all the time.
You know this joke...
you know this joke?
"Why did the moron tiptoe
pass the medical cabinet?"
Because he didn't want
to wake up the sleeping pills.
Oh, come on, sweetie,
tell me a joke.
Mmm, David.
Out of all the kids in
the whole world, you ought to
know a few moron jokes.
Tell me a joke, David.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on, sweetie.
Tell me a joke.
[LAUGHTER]
At ease, soldier.
John, this is my sister
Sally Goodson.
Sally, this is John Nils.
Hello.
Hi.
How are you?
Hi. You want a drink?
Yes.
I'll get the waiter.
Is that what you did
to you hair?
I couldn't decide between
dreadlocks and cornrows.
Shut up.
Oh, you know that
wallpaper store across
from Bloomingdale's?
John owns it.
Yeah? Wow.
Excuse me, waiter.
Come here. Can I have
a Bloody Mary? Double.
And stick around.
Yes, ma'am.
Isn't it a beautiful day?
Oh, it must be 75 degrees
out there.
You know, I just love it
when there's that little...
Christmas, you know,
there's that little nip
in the air, but...
Ah, still...
She always wanted to be
a weather girl,
but our mother
wouldn't allow it.
Shut up.
Those two. [CHUCKLES]
Be right back.
What's the matter
with you?
What?
Will you stop pretending
you're a mute!
I talked.
A nod and a grunt is not
what I consider talking.
Now, when he gets back here,
I wanna see some charm,
some sparkle, some vivacity.
Hire a clown.
I already got one.
Just relax.
[BLOWS]
Make up your mind.
You want a relaxed mute,
or frenzied debutant?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Is something going on?
No.
Yes! Yes.
She is mad at me
because...
I am so uptight that I won't do
my Oprah Winfrey imitation.
[JOHN LAUGHS]
I haven't been in
a social situation
with a man...
other than my dentist,
for I don't... What?
Since
The War of The Roses?
I'm out of practice.
But you're very funny.
[SALLY CHUCKLES]
[BLOWS]
This guy's a piece of cake.
You are the easiest audience
I've ever had.
[LAUGHING]
That's because
you're so funny.
Justine?
The Governor called,
your apartment came through.
They're not here.
[SIGHS] This is it.
It's very nice.
Mm-hmm. Have you had
your tetanus shots?
[CHUCKLES]
No, this, this place
is for living, it's not
for showing off.
That's right.
We're definitely
downwardly mobile.
Can I get you a drink?
I have some cheap gin
and some flat tonic.
How can I resist?
So, you live in the same
building as Bea, huh?
I live in the penthouse
upstairs.
Oh, the penthouse.
Whoo-whoo-whoo.
It's just a little balcony
really, but I can see
the new store from there. I...
Did I mention that I opened
another store?
Oh, maybe a couple of times.
[CHUCKLES]
Well...
business is good.
Oh, are you applying
for something?
[CHUCKLES]
JUSTINE: Aunt Sally?
We're back.
Ah.
Come meet the family.
[GLASS CLINKS]
We went to the zoo.
Hi, John. How was lunch?
None of your business.
John, I want you
to meet my son.
This is David.
The one you've heard so much
about. Come on, David,
be polite, shake hands.
[GROANS]
John is speechless.
He didn't think you were
so handsome, probably.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no, no, no. Don't sweat it.
You know, most people don't
expect David to be so handsome.
How about
Pinocchio
, honey?
Haven't seen that
a couple of days.
Ow. Don't bite.
He loves
Pinocchio,
up to the part where the boys
turn into donkeys.
And then that is just a little
too close to home,
you know what I mean?
Now where were we?
I remember, we were talking
about your new store.
Say, you know what?
David and I should swing by
someday and say, "Hi."
Oh, don't worry.
He can only eat
so much wallpaper.
Sure, anytime.
How about tomorrow?
Sure, give me a call.
Okay, I will.
Listen, can you
do me a favor?
Could you drop Justine off
at her house, because
I have a manuscript that
I just got to finish tonight.
Justine?
[DAVID GROANING]
I found you a ride.
Oh, sure.
See you, kiddo.
I'll give you a call.
Yeah, you do that.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SCOFFS]
What is it with people?
Why can't they see
how beautiful you are?
SALLY:
Phil?
PHILIP:What?
Come in here
and look at our
beautiful son.
I'm in bed.
Who would know to look at him
that he is not just like
any other five-year-old boy?
Always getting into stuff,
answering back.
He throws the same tantrums
in the checkout line
when he doesn't get gum.
I'm reading.
I don't want you to read.
I want you to talk to me.
David has
your mothers nose.
The only good quality
in your family
and David has it.
Hmm.
You have
your father's nose.
Thanks.
But you have
other body parts
that make up for it.
I'm not in the mood
for sex, Sally.
So, who's asking?
When we talk about
my body parts,
that's where
the conversation's going.
Is that such a bad place
for it to go?
Just not in the mood.
[SCOFFS]
When do you think
you might be in the mood?
You wanna make
an appointment?
Well, I guess so. Maybe,
that way I'll have something
to look forward to.
Phil, where have you
been lately?
Where have I been?
Right here.
Try to look in at someone
besides your son
once in a while.
My son?
Wow, I guess that says it all,
doesn't it?
That's not what I meant.
I do the best I can.
Prove it.
What do you mean?
How am I supposed
to do that?
Leave the kids with Bea
for a weekend,
let's get out of here.
You know that I cannot
leave David.
Well...
That says it all,
doesn't it?
Getting it somewhere else?
No, I'm not getting it
somewhere else.
I'm not getting it.
And you know what?
I don't miss it.
You know what I miss?
I miss coming home
and arguing about politics,
and how much money you spend.
I miss new recipes
and watching my daughter
get giddy over nothing.
I miss laughter.
That's what I miss,
not sex.
I'm sorry.
Sure, you're
always sorry.
Well, I'm sorry because
I always do something
to be sorry for.
Ask Bea,
I was a rotten kid.
Now, I'm a rotten grownup.
I love you.
I even love your nose.
[LAUGHS]
Someday...
Someday what?
Someday nothing.
You love me too much
to ever leave me.
You are here
for the duration.
JOHN: You look nice.
Yeah? Well, this is it.
This is...
my wardrobe.
'Cause if you ask me out again,
you gonna have to take me to
someplace I can go naked.
[SIGHS]
Surprised you asked me out
this time.
Why?
Because you got
a load of David.
Look, if my candor
approaches rudeness,
you're gonna
have to forgive me.
I don't like it when people
freak out over my kid.
Yeah. Well, you know, maybe
this was not such a hot idea.
Oh, please stay.
It wasn't David.
Yeah, right.
All right.
I wasn't really prepared
for him, I guess.
He did stop me in my tracks.
But it was...
It was something you did.
It... What?
You made fun of him.
Well, at least I thought
you did.
But, then...
I spoke to Bea and she said
that sometimes
when you sound like
you're being cruel,
you're really just making
jokes to cover up how uptight
you feel.
It doesn't mean anything.
So, you discuss my so called
sense of humor with my sister
behind my back?
Don't get mad.
You are one presumptuous
wallpaper hanger.
I don't hang it, I sell it.
Except for you,
I'd give it to you.
Hand painted.
Silk screened.
Flocked.
Am I tempting you?
You're nauseating me.
Excuse me.
Are you ready
to order?
What's the most
expensive thing
you got on the menu?
Suffer, you.
[SNORING]
SALLY: Ah, please. Eh.
Garbage, garbage, garbage.
[SNICKERS]
Hey, babe.
You wanna hear some crap?
Listen to this.
"Montgomery left Greystone
as he had entered it.
"Penniless.
"Save for his silken
waistcoats and
golden fobs.
"Upstairs Melanie lay prostrate
on her bed,
"weeping scalding tears
for her profligate lover."
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I know how you feel, honey.
Take it from somebody
who's been there.
It gets easier.
PHILIP:
I left you some money
in the top drawer.
SALLY: Do you need
your hair dryer?
This is a separation,
you're not supposed
to help me pack.
Sorry, I don't know
the etiquette of divorce.
Not a divorce,
this is a separation.
I want you to tell me the truth,
because if you don't, you won't
come back.
It's easier to stay away
than to come back to a lie.
What do you
want to know?
I want to know
about the woman
you're going to.
The one who
is waiting for you.
[ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS]
MAN: Hey.
Who is she?
[ALARM BUZZING]
Just a girl at the office.
She's nothing.
Then why are you
going to her?
MAN: Open the door.
Because I don't know
where else to go.
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
What's going on there?
You got a problem? Open up.
You could stay here.
I can't.
Why?
I can't do it anymore.
Do what?
I can't face one more father
at the playground.
I can't watch the look
on his face...
when he looks at David,
and then his own boy.
I, I can't bear the relief
on his face.
The pain in the eyes
of the women when David
falls down and hurts himself.
I just can't bear it.
And you think I can?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think you can.
I think you can do anything.
Taxi.
[SIGHS]
Wait a minute, hold up.
Before you turn me into
some kind of saint here,
and I lose you for good,
I want you to
know something.
There's not one day
that goes by
that I don't blame David
for what isn't his fault.
Not one day that I don't...
I don't wake up and ask myself,
"What the hell did I do
to deserve this?"
But I feed him,
and I clean him,
and sometimes I hate him.
I have this fantasy that
one day David is just gonna
wake up healed,
and he's gonna tell me that
he knew all along everything
that I did for him.
He's gonna tell me that
he knows every time
that I wiped his ass,
and sat with him watching
some stupid movie.
[CRYING]
That's the worst part.
Because I need him
to thank me.
He can't thank me.
[SNIFFLES]
But I do what
I have to do.
And I want you to know that
if you come back,
that you're coming back as
somebody who knows how hard
it is to do what you have to do.
And who understands that
some times you, you just have
to get away and rest.
So, I want you to go away
and rest.
And when you're rested...
[SNIFFLES]
I want you to
make up your mind.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I love you.
Of course you do.
[SNIFFLES]
[SIGHS]
[TV PLAYING SOFTLY]
[DAVID GROANING]
[KIDS CHATTING]
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
SALLY: Look. Look, David. Look.
[DAVID GRUNTING]
Look at the carousels.
See the horses?
[DAVID AND SALLY LAUGHING]
MAN: [WHISTLES] Come on.
Oh, David. Whoa. Whoa.
Are there seat belts
on this thing?
Yeah, for sure. I...
Hang on to him very,
very tightly, because
he doesn't have balance.
Don't you worry.
I'm not worried.
David, listen to me.
Listen to mommy.
Hold on to the horsie.
Hold on tight.
I'll be right there with him,
I'll hold him. Now, come on.
[LAUGHS]
Hold his arm. Hold his arm.
Hold his hand.
Like this horse, David?
MAN: There you go.
[LAUGHING]
Here. Come on let's
get up on here.
That's it.
You have to put him on there.
He can't just...
He doesn't get,
get on.
Up!
I got him.
[GRUNTING]
Okay, seat belt.
[LAUGHING]
David? David. Hold on
to the pole, David.
Hold onto the pole.
Put your hand on there
for your mother.
[LAUGHING]
Okay.
Here we go.
Hold on tight, David.
[LAUGHING]
Great.
Careful with this pole now.
[YELPS EXCITEDLY]
There's your mother.
[DAVID LAUGHING]
Hi, David. Hi, David.
[LAUGHING] David.
JOHN:
You worry too much
about him.
SALLY: I get scared.
He wasn't scared.
This once he wasn't scared.
Maybe you're the one
who gets scared.
Oh, boy, you are just determined
to get me mad, aren't you?
Man.
I'm sorry.
It was two minutes
and already
you're an expert.
God bless men,
they're so smart.
Sorry.
It wasn't called for.
Maybe it was called for.
Yeah, it was.
But let me apologize anyway.
I'm working on becoming
a nicer person.
You're nice enough.
[GRUNTING]
Where have you been?
A mental home?
You are a, what's the word,
volatile.
[SCOFFS]
It's exciting.
All right. Listen, I got
a pot roast on at home.
If the apartment
isn't burnt down.
You like pot roast?
I can't today.
Okay.
I'm supposed to be
at the store now.
We're doing inventory.
You don't need to make excuses.
We got to get home anyway.
Thanks for
a great afternoon.
I'll call you.
Sure.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Bye, David.
David says bye.
No, you're not.
Yes, I am.
I said no!
Well, I said yes.
Brenda, do you want to lose
your phone privileges?
Mom, I am going!
Yes, yes, yes. Come in, now!
Mom, I am going
whether you like it or not.
You're gonna be sorry,
young lady.
Mom!
Brenda!
SALLY:
Susan?
SUSAN:What?
SALLY: Put the clothes back.
No.
You're not going anywhere.
Why?
"Why"?
Look, this is your mother
you're talking to.
I am not a moron.
I know what kind of girl
Sandra is,
and you are not spending
the night over at her house
without her parents.
Nothing's gonna
happen to me.
You're right. Because
you're not going.
Ma, that's so unfair.
Uh, and what am I supposed
to do here?
I don't know.
Why don't you do
what you always do?
Watch you take care of David?
It's all you ever do.
Do we have to
do this again?
David cannot take care
of himself and you can
take care of yourself.
Then let me
take care of myself.
Let me go.
Look, do we have to have
this fight?
I don't want to have one.
Come on, I'll owe you one.
You can be a pain
in the ass tomorrow,
but today, would you
just please lighten up
a little bit?
You know where
I really wanna go.
No, where would you
really wanna go?
I wanna go
live with daddy.
Go ahead,
who's stopping you?
Sam would let me move in.
[SCOFFS] Yeah, well,
you know what?
I don't really give a damn
what your father's wife
would do.
I mean,
what kind of a woman has
a man's name anyway?
Sam? That sounds like
somebody on a sitcom.
You will make it a sitcom.
A new wife,
the daughter comes
to live with them,
they all laugh, and they learn
something new every half hour.
So you will let me go?
[SCOFFS]
And get a little peace
and quiet around here?
I would be a fool if not to.
All right then, fine.
I'll call right now.
No, you will not.
Yes, I will.
Give me the phone.
I will.
No. You said I could go.
Stop it!
You want me... [GRUNTS]
Let go of the phone!
What's your problem?
[PHONE RINGING]
All right. All right.
Hold your horses.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on.
Hello?
GLADYS:
Sally?
It's Gladys Johnson.
You have some good news.
Yeah, what?
We located a facility
in 11th Avenue.
It's one of the best
in the city.
They only take
a limited number
of kids,
but I got you an interview.
Oh, hello,
excuse me a sec.
You told me that you're gonna
give me some time.
I have.
What are you talking about?
I just saw you.
Sally, just go to the place
and check it out.
I don't wanna pull rank
with you.
Just be there, 11 o'clock.
[DOOR OPENS]
MALE TEACHER: Okay, kids,
stay together. Watch yourself
on the steps.
FEMALE TEACHER: It's good,
everybody. Stay together,
single line now.
MALE TEACHER:
Lisa, can you take
Billy's hand?
Thank you.
Good girl.
FEMALE TEACHER: Get back in,
you know. Come on now.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hey, Marky, check it out.
[LAUGHING]
Hey, what's the matter
with you, lady?
[MEN LAUGHING]
BEA:
I heard about the school
down the village,
it's supposed to be good.
SALLY: Ugh!
Here we go again.
I'm not putting David
in a home, Bea.
It's not a home, it's a school
for special children.
But, to be eligible you have
to live in the district.
So?
So, David's father moved into
the district.
Good. Let him go
to the school.
You're impossible.
How much is this?
$100 an ounce.
Oh! She'll take a pound.
Philip said he would pick up
David on Tuesday afternoon
to keep him over night.
That way, you could
have some time off.
Just forget it!
Excuse me.
You're denying yourself
to punish Phil.
[SCOFFS] He walked out
on his kid.
David is as much his fault
as he is mine.
I'm not gonna let him
ease his conscience
just cause he takes him
for pizza once a week.
Fault? David is
nobody's fault.
Yeah, right. David is
Well, he isn't.
God, that is so nice.
Wouldn't it be wonderful
if life was so nice?
No fault. No fault accidents,
no fault divorce.
No fault movers.
Can I help you?
Where is the ladies' room?
God!
Why are you attacking me?
Because it's bull.
God!
They don't have a clue
what caused David to be born
with scrambled eggs for brains,
but you know
it wasn't my fault.
I wish I knew that.
I wish I knew that [STAMMERS]
it was something,
it was the fluoride in the water
or the, uh,
the asbestos in the ceiling,
or the lead in the paint.
I wish I knew that it wasn't
the joint that I smoked
when I was carrying him.
Or that wine that I was
so sure that it wasn't
gonna hurt him.
Or that I had some
screw up in my genetics
and my chromosomes.
Stop it! You're gonna
drive yourself crazy
thinking things like that.
I stopped.
Give me one of those.
No.
You quit.
You're making me crazy,
just give one over.
[SCOFFS]
"Give one over"!
[SNIFFS]
This is good. We're back
in high school,
smoking in the bathroom.
Why didn't you show up
at the school this morning?
They were expecting you.
I did show up.
I just didn't go in.
Why?
Because I didn't like
what I saw, okay?
What?
I didn't like the way
they herd the kids.
My son is a human being,
he's not a sheep.
Sally...
I hated it.
GLADYS: Sally, it's the best
place in the country for David.
You should get down
on your hands and knees
and pray they take him.
He'll have his own room,
he'll learn how to
dress himself,
how to prepare food.
What do you mean
he'll have his own room?
What? You mean,
he'd sleep there?
Yes.
Then when would
he come home?
On weekends.
Oh, God...
You gotta give me
some more time.
Again?
Yes, again.
[STAMMERS]
Just a couple of weeks.
What's a couple of weeks?
Come on, you could go harass
somebody else for a change.
Well, thanks for that.
Look, will you have
a heart here?
Don't be mad at me. You know,
you're not talking my kid for
a walk around the park.
You are taking him
away from me.
Two weeks.
That's it.
[ELEVATOR APPROACHING]
[JOHN LAUGHING]
Uh, more wine?
Thanks.
I don't have any.
[LAUGHS]
Then why did you ask?
To be polite.
You want me to
go get you some?
You know I can,
it no problem, really.
We got all night liquor store
just around the corner.
Between a crack house
and a welfare hotel.
I could just put on some pearls
and strut down there and
get you some.
You talked me out of it.
[DAVID GROANING]
What?
[GRUNTING]
[SCOFFS] It's a movie.
The movie's over,
big deal!
it's not the end
of the world.
Come on, sweetie,
let's turn in.
[GROANS]
Come on.
[GRUNTS]
David, come on. Come on,
let's get you to bed, sweetie,
come on.
[GRUNTS]
Stop it!
Would you mind
if he stayed up?
Of course, not.
Right.
No intro, no sound,
and no more tantrums.
Why don't you teach him
to do it himself.
That way he won't
have to bother you.
Yeah, I'm gonna
do that tomorrow,
right after I teach him how
to operate the computer.
It's not that hard.
Look, David.
David, look,
this is the side...
that goes into
the machine. See?
It just slides right in.
Excuse me, Mr. Wizard?
It took me a month to learn
to run that thing. What do you
expect from him?
Patience, Rome wasn't built
in a day.
Here.
First we have to...
[GRUNTS]
David, first we have to push
the button with the arrow.
See?
JOHN: David.
[SCOFFS]
God, he does not understand
what you want him
to do!
Press the button
with the arrow, David.
[GROANS]
Come on.
Press the button, David.
[DAVID SCREAMS]
Just turn the damn movie
for him.
[SCREAMING]
SALLY:
Just turn the movie on!
God! Come on, David, sit down.
Calm down, get up here.
Settle doe... David,
settle down.
You're fine. You're fine.
Why do people think if they
just talk loud to him,
he's gonna be normal?
He's not. You can wake him up
in the middle of the night and
he's still gonna be like this.
He's not kidding around.
JOHN: I know.
I'm sorry.
Still, I think I could teach
him, I'd like to try.
Will you just take it easy
with him, though?
Got to...
So, what do you want
for dessert?
I have frozen pound cake,
or microwave brownies.
Neither,
I better get going.
So soon?
Yeah, I was up
at crack of dawn.
Oh.
Were you, were you
doing inventory again?
[CHUCKLES]
No, you better hit the road.
There.
Sorry.
Oh, don't be.
No. No, I'm...
Well, I never was one to wait
to be asked. [CHUCKLES]
I guess you don't find me
attractive in that way.
Oh...
No sweat.
I don't find myself attractive
in that way either.
It's not that.
Then what?
Ah...
[SIGHS]
Are you gay?
[SCOFFS] You're gay.
I...
No, that's cool. No, you know,
I know a lot of gay guys and
sometimes gay guys come out
late in life and that's cool.
I'm not gay.
[SCOFFS]
I'm...
[SIGHS]
I'm married and...
What?
No, I thought
your wife died.
She did.
About a year ago, but...
She's still my wife, I've...
Well, that didn't die. I...
I feel like I'm
cheating on her.
Oh.
[STAMMERS] Is that why you
ran out of here so fast...
Yeah.
...after every date?
Can you understand that?
Can I understand that?
Honey, I can top that.
You know my husband,
he thinks he has a new wife.
The government thinks
he's married to another woman,
but I know the truth,
he's still my husband.
I think the only difference
is that
I've had more time to get
used to the idea of cheating
than you have.
Get out of here,
or I'll hit on you again and
that'll really embarrass you.
I'll call you.
So, David, did you hear?
You mother has not lost
her allure after all.
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
SUSAN:
I won't lose it,
I promise.
Just be careful with it,
it was grandma's.
You didn't like grandma.
[SIGHS] Yeah, well,
I liked her diamond.
SALLY: Oh, is this
the Goodson wedding?
Yes.
Oh, this must be David
and Susan.
Come in, darlings.
I'll be back to pick
them up later.
David, be good.
Susan, watch after him.
Oh, won't you come in?
One glass of champagne?
No. No, thanks.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
We're here.
Whoo! [LAUGHS]
Go.
David, destroy your aunts
apartment.
[LAUGHING] We're gonna do
just fine, who needs you?
So, you spending the night
at John's tonight?
I hope so.
Slut. [CHUCKLES] Good luck.
I'll need it.
Come on, he's a man,
you're a woman.
I don't think he noticed.
[SIGHS]
He noticed.
What?
Nothing. [GIGGLES]
You are beautiful,
you know that?
[CHUCKLES] Yeah, right.
I mean it.
Mm-hmm.
I'm also blonde, 5'2',
very slim hipped.
When are you gonna let me
wallpaper your apartment?
[LAUGHS]
Oh, my God.
I mean it.
[LAUGHS]
It would make
my furniture look shabby.
So, I'll buy you some
new furniture.
[LAUGHS] You don't owe me
anything.
You got laid,
I didn't give you a kidney.
I do, I owe you a lot.
You're like the sun shining
its light at me.
[CHUCKLES] Oh, God.
John, do yourself a favor,
play a little bit hard to get.
Wow. We did it
in Versailles.
My wife's hobby was
interior decorating.
You hate it?
[CHUCKLES]
How about
Bea's apartment?
Ugh.
Why?
Because you've both been
architecturally digested.
Give me a place where
the pigs can roam free.
I take it back,
I like it.
Oh, look at this place.
Wow.
[GRUNTS]
Man. Man... Uh!
You got yourself
a regular restaurant here.
You cook?
No.
Oh, God. When you're rich,
the birds sing.
Look at this. It's nice.
Nice fridge.
Beer? That's good.
That means you remember
your roots.
You want one?
No, thanks.
Watch this.
Souvenir of
my mis-spent youth. Mmm.
Mmm. [CHUCKLES]
This woman is cute,
very cute.
JOHN: I had
ice cream at home.
I didn't want ice cream,
I wanted yogurt.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
Nice.
[UPBEAT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
JOHN: Okay. Why don't you
try it again.
[GRUNTING]
See?
This is the side that
goes into the machine,
one with the wiggly
edge, okay?
So, you put it in.
[MOTOR BUZZING]
Now, see the button
with the arrow? Okay.
Yeah. Well, he's in there
right now teaching David
to be a brain surgeon.
JOHN: This is the side...
Yes. That is so nice, Bea.
It is also a waste of time.
Okay. You just put it in.
Now...
[CHUCKLES]
See the button
with the arrow?
That's the play.
Press it, David.
Sally? Come here.
Just a sec.
I have to go.
My gentleman caller
is calling.
I'm always nice, Bea.
That's my fatal flaw.
Uh... Hello? Excuse me.
Was somebody
asking you for your advice?
Goodbye.
Yes. What do we have?
JOHN: We've got something
to show you.
[DAVID GRUNTS]
JOHN: Patience.
First you got to show
your mother
how smart you are.
Okay. Okay, do your stuff.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
See? He knows how to put
the tape in.
That's terrific.
Now, remember the arrow?
Press the button
with the arrow.
Press it, David. No, no.
That's rewind.
[GROANING]
The one with the arrow.
See the button with the arrow.
[GROANING]
Okay, okay. Okay.
That's enough
for one evening.
So? Do I deserve a kiss?
You call that a kiss?
I call it the only kind of kiss
I'd give in front of my kid.
You can't be too...
I just...
All right.
Hold on a second.
There. Go.
[GIGGLES]
Mmm, I created a monster.
You didn't create him,
you just woke him up.
You know, put him back to sleep,
will you, because David's just
right in there.
Please? Later.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
Second suggestion.
Bea said that your daughter's
getting married in California.
Uh-hmm.
So, how about I fly out there
after the wedding,
we grab up the coast?
Uh, that's good, but I'm not
going to the wedding.
Why not?
Well, among other things,
I wasn't invited.
But, you know what?
Even if I was invited,
I wouldn't go.
How come?
Because we've beat up
on each other enough.
I think that it is just
let things lie.
Better than what?
Better than the way
it used to be.
Look, you're gonna have
a hard time believing this,
but I don't have a winning
phone personality. [LAUGHING]
I mean to. I mean I call up
and I mean to say,
"I, I really miss you,"
and it comes out,
"Why the hell don't you ever
call me?"
And, you know...
That doesn't make you
a particularly desirable
personality.
So, anyway, my daughter ends up
with a chip on her shoulder
the size of
the Rock of Gibraltar
and me too, and...
and...
Anyway, I just decided that...
That I would just keep
my mouth shut.
And that I would keep reminding
myself that I wasn't that close
with my mother and
my daughter is not that close
with me and...
[SIGHS] In the end
when we were all
raised and alienated our kids
and we turn to dust,
that it won't really matter
in the least.
[DAVID SCREAMING]
Okay.
Uh...
I'll go.
[DAVID GRUNTING]
[PLANE ENGINE REVVING]
ANNOUNCER:
Flight 628, non-stop
service to Chicago
is now ready for boarding
in Gate 17.
This is as far as I go.
Call when you get
to your father's house.
Okay.
Okay. Oh!
I got you the sun block
and want you to use it,
because everybody
in California
has got skin cancer.
I saw it on Oprah.
Promise me
you'll use it.
I promise.
Don't let your father
buy you a new car.
Everybody in California drives
like a lunatic.
Will you stop worrying?
So, who's worried?
Everything is fine.
You're leaving because
you hate my guts.
Which you're supposed to hate
my guts because you're 16.
That way you'll grow up
mature and independent.
Solid, you see.
I don't hate you.
I know, I just said it.
I feel like the continent's
tilted here, they keep sliding
to California.
Just think we'll be happier
if I live with dad
for a little while.
You have enough to do,
you don't need me around
to fight with.
Which translates into,
I don't spend enough time
with you
because I'm too
busy with David.
ANNOUNCER:
Flight 728 from...
Let's not do this again, okay?
Okay, fine.
ANNOUNCER:
All passengers
should now be on board.
I've got to go.
So, go.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
You're breaking
my heart, kid.
I've got an idea.
Yeah, what?
The week of the wedding,
let's go down to Key West.
For what?
It's called a vacation.
You know, sunburn?
And have drinks
with umbrellas in them,
and sandy beach...
It sounds really good,
but I can't.
Why not?
I just can't.
Everybody deserves
a vacation,
even you.
I'll call Bea,
maybe she can take David.
No, look, Mr. Take Charge.
I said I can't because I can't.
Why?
David and I are moving
in a few days.
Moving?
Where?
To Fort Lee,
New Jersey.
Why?
I don't know.
I have my reasons.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm telling you.
No, you're not.
You're mentioning it
in passing,
like I'm not
worth confiding in.
Well, what did you want?
A hand engraved
change of address?
Let me call Tiffany's.
Don't do that.
What? Now what am I doing?
Don't mock me.
I'm not mocking you.
Come on, John,
you know my mouth.
There's someone listening
to what comes
out of your mouth.
Don't use it as a weapon.
[SCOFFS] You put out
a couple of times,
they think they own you.
I can't tell you.
I couldn't tell you because
I'm breaking the law.
What?
If, if I stay here,
they're gonna take
David away from me.
And you kept that
to yourself?
It's not your problem.
Of course it's my problem.
John, you know what?
You're a really nice guy.
You laugh at my jokes,
and we have a good time
in bed together,
but, this is my problem, alone.
I've been doing it
for 16 years,
I'm real good at it.
In other words, butt out.
Have a heart. I'm fighting
for my kid's life here.
I don't have time to tip-toe
around and wonder if I'm
hurting somebody's feeling.
Why not?
I fought for my wife's life,
I had time.
That's different.
I'm his mother.
Why is that different?
Do you think you love your son
more than I love my wife?
No I don't.
I think I am the one
that takes care of him
and you know how he is.
I know how you let him be.
What?
Uh, never mind.
I'm going to take a walk
around the block.
Where is my jacket?
Where you left it,
on my bed.
Great!
Go. That'll solve everything,
won't it? Just go.
Just let me
take a walk, huh?
I'll regret anything I say now,
and so will you, I promise you.
SALLY:
So what is that, a threat?
No, it's an observation,
based on a 100 fights
and a thousand regrets.
Don't go.
It's better if I do.
I don't want to say anything
to hurt you.
Do you have something to say?
Go ahead and say it. Go ahead.
Come on, haven't you heard,
I have thick skin.
It was very hard for me
to put my wife in one part
of my heart so I could let you
into another.
I don't think you'll ever
do that with David.
Well, there's one
big difference here,
David is not dead.
No matter what
some people wish.
What, are you crazy?
I don't wish him dead,
I'm his father.
I love him.
Yeah.
From afar.
That is love.
What you do, breathing in air
as it comes out of his lungs,
it's lunacy.
It's not good for him.
I think I know a little better
than you what's good for David.
Do you?
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
It means, I have to beg you
to let me help your son.
You should thank me.
Working a VCR is not gonna
change his life.
Nothing is gonna change
his life.
You won't let it!
You're so sure you know
what he can do
and what he can't do,
you won't let him
do anything.
What do you
want from me?
I want a wife.
I don't want to be alone.
I don't want
David to be alone.
How can he be alone?
You wear him
like a second skin.
I am fighting for
my kid's life here.
I don't have time
for all these other feelings.
That's the second time
you've said that.
You're not fighting
for his life, you're fighting
to control his life.
You use him,
don't you see that?
I have sacrificed everything
for him.
You have sacrificed everyone
You said you wanted to leave.
So, leave.
[FOOTSTEPS FADING]
"As taut as a pulled trigger,
the shattering climax will
leave you gasping for more."
Yeah, right.
There we go.
"The joyous escape
of two Siamese cats,
and a bull dog
"turn a provincial mining
town upside down. A mirthful.
G-rated movie. 110 minutes."
What do you say, David,
you ready for a little mirth?
David?
[GUN FIRING]
[DAVID LAUGHING]
[HORN TOOTING]
NARRATOR:
The old Union Jack
still waves triumphantly
over the land.
[LAUGHING]
MAN:
Still stands the...
[INDISTINCT CHATTER FROM TV]
MAN:
Cutting across
main street on the left to
the railroad tracks.
Beyond the railroad tracks
is Polish town.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
FROM TV CONTINUES]
[LAUGHING]
[CHANGES TAPE]
Oh! Hi, Sid.
Is my sister in?
Uh, she's in there.
She's in there?
Right.
[DAVID LAUGHING]
What are you doing in here?
SALLY: Just waiting
for the rain to stop.
I've been trying to reach you
for over two days.
So has John. The next time
you to go into hiding
would you please switch on
the answering machine?
What's the matter with you?
You look like hell.
I spend my time sleeping
a lot lately.
What's the matter?
You two
have a fight?
Big deal, couples fight.
Oh, honey.
Bea.
What? What?
Will you tell me
something?
Am I a bad person?
What do you mean?
You're the best.
No, come on, just give me
the truth, okay.
[SIGHS] All right.
What happened?
David can work the VCR.
What?
In a million years, would you
ever have believed that David
could work a VCR?
I guess not.
[SCOFFS]
I had that damn machine
in the house for three years
and he never touched it.
Two weeks with John
and he's an expert.
Do you remember how long
it took you
to teach me how to use it?
How are we discussing how smart
David is or how dumb you are?
[DAVID GRUNTING]
John said that I don't let him
do anything.
I think he's right.
I mean,
if he can work a VCR...
I mean, who knows what else
he can do, what he can be.
What he can be?
Honey, David is
what he can be.
He's impaired.
That's just a word.
Am I the one who said
what it meant?
I mean, did I make him
like this?
Stop that. You're not
that important.
God made him this way.
Well, Bea, maybe there's
two gods.
The one that cooked his brains,
the one that made sure
they stayed that way.
What do you think you did
that was so terrible?
You had an afflicted child.
You took care of him.
That's all. Nobody could have
been a more devoted mother.
Yeah, well...
[SCOFFS] I mean, Susan would
agree with that.
Do you think
she thinks she had
a devoted mother?
And how about Phil?
You did the best you could.
That's all anybody can do.
How good was my best?
David, come on, honey,
you want...
You want to go upstairs?
Let's go up, come on,
stand up.
[GRUNTS]
I'm gonna zap something
for lunch.
Weren't you radio active?
Please.
SALLY: Good. That'll
leave more for us.
[GRUNTING]
Just this once
don't be hard on yourself.
You know, doesn't make you that
important just because your
punishment's always the worst.
Now, don't worry,
John will fix everything.
Yeah? And how is he gonna
do that?
Well, when you two are...
When we two what?
You know...
You... Ugh, Bea,
don't dye your shoes yet.
Now, what does that mean?
It means I don't know
if I'm interested.
Of course you're interested,
you like him.
Yeah, but what if
I don't love him?
Love him? Who expected you
to love him?
Didn't you?
Of course not.
I was hoping
for companionship.
Sally, he's a very rich man.
He can take you out
of this crummy life.
You can get someone
to take care of David.
You can...
Vacations in Europe.
You can walk the aisle
of Bloomingdales like
a normal person.
Did you hear
what you just said?
I don't care
what I just said.
There's nothing
he wouldn't give you.
Well, then why marry him?
Why don't I just
forge his name
on a check?
Why don't you just
stop making jokes
and ruining your life?
Uh, I don't believe what
I'm hearing here.
Did you love Stephen
when you married him?
Oh, love?
That's absolutely irrelevant.
I was 24-years-old,
I was entitled to be in love.
And I'm not?
Well, when did
that happen, Bea?
When David was born?
When David turned out
the way he turned out,
did that make me [STAMMERS]
unworthy of love?
That's not what I'm saying.
God!
What are you saying, then?
No matter what harm I've done
anyone else,
I've done more to myself.
I'm not gonna settle.
I wouldn't degrade myself
any further
than I already have.
I won't settle.
I'm not asking
you to settle.
Yes, you are.
Of course you are.
I'm asking you
to save yourself.
No you're not!
You're demanding it.
Why?
Because I'm exhausted from
worrying about you.
I haven't got the energy
to do it anymore.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, then don't
do it anymore.
Don't do it.
I never asked you to.
I never wanted you to.
Tell me something.
Why is it that
the people who don't
screw up their lives
always feel guilty
about people who do?
I don't know.
Hug me.
[SNIFFLES]
I resent you.
I know that.
I got the gifts to prove it.
Sometimes I hate you.
And I love you.
Ours is not a simple
relationship.
Well, who says
simple is good?
[SNIFFS] You know all the parts
I meant and the parts I didn't.
[DOOR CLOSES]
It's back ordered.
Four, maybe five weeks.
What can I say, I sell it,
I don't manufacture it.
Uh, excuse me, sir.
The wallpaper you sold us
has peeled off the walls and
is lying in my
dining room floor.
What are you doing here?
She's kidding.
I'm not kidding.
Please come in the back before
you wreck my business.
Excuse me.
Come on, honey.
I am not kidding.
Oh, here they are.
Put this in you hand. come on.
Come on.
[GRUNTING]
David.
I want you to sit down
here, okay?
Here.
Sit.
Play solitaire, okay?
[GRUNTS]
Stay there and don't move.
JOHN: I'm surprised to see you.
Oh... [SIGHS]
We just left Bea running
amok in Bloomingdale.
[GRUNTING]
I'm glad you're here,
gives me a chance
to apologize.
For what?
Everything you said was true.
I should thank you.
You can thank me tonight.
I can't.
Tomorrow night?
You're such a nice man.
You really helped my kid.
You really helped me
and I owe you.
JOHN:
You can pay for dinner.
I owe you too much
to keep seeing you.
That I don't understand.
Sure you do.
You don't have to...
love me to
keep on seeing me,
you know?
[CHUCKLES] Yeah, I do.
You're that kind of guy.
Besides, before you know it,
the mistake,
the relief of being with anybody
with real feelings for me.
Then I will hurt you.
You might learn
to feel something for me.
Miracles happen.
I already feel
a lot for you.
Enough to know
I won't feel more.
You don't know that.
I do.
I have so much to do,
just please go.
Go find somebody
who's normal.
Go find, go find some woman
who thinks you're as funny
as you think I am.
She's out there.
And you'll find her.
Now that you're not cheating
on your wife anymore.
Okay.
You go do what
you have to do.
But if you need me,
call me.
No promises necessary.
No promises given.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
David.
We got to go,
let's let this man
sell wallpaper.
[GRUNTING]
Goodbye, kiddo.
Goodbye, David.
David says bye.
SALLY:
Okay. Roll them.
Okay.
One, two, three, four,
five, six.
North Carolina Avenue,
you want to buy it?
You want to buy it?
It's going out for auction.
[MUMBLING] Sold to me
for one dollar.
That was
a good property, David,
you should have bought it.
All right, now, your turn.
No, it's my turn.
It's my turn.
All right, um...
Come on, little lowly,
come on co-co-mo.
Come on, little...
Yeah.
Fitner. I own it already.
I hate that.
Here, David, your turn.
Come on, sweetie.
Roll the dice. Roll the dice.
Come on, baby, Come on.
Roll the six. Roll the six,
David. Roll the six.
Land on Park Place.
Come on, I got a hotel
in Park Place. Roll the six.
David, roll the six.
Let me help you.
Roll it. Roll it.
Yeah! Six!
One, two, three, four,
five, six.
Yeah! I'm hot. I'm hot.
Where's the hotel?
I had a hotel in six.
Give me my hotel, David.
Stop eating my hotel.
All right. [SIGHS]
[GRUNTING]
David, you didn't
roll a six.
[GRUNTING]
Honey.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I cheated.
Boy, you got to know when
people cheat you, David.
I may not always be here
to tell you that.
Got to be able to stick up
for yourself.
[MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING]
[UPBEAT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
CHILD: Come on,
man, hurry up.
WOMAN:
Can I help you?
Yes, we're looking
for Gladys Johnson.
I'm sorry,
I don't know who that is.
Department
of Child Welfare.
I see.
Come have a seat.
Your name?
Sally Goodson.
Your son's name?
David.
Sit down.
[GRUNTS]
Nice place, huh, David?
Homie.
[TAPPING FEET]
Fill these out, please.
All of them?
Yes, please.
I'll take this.
Miss.
I don't have a pen.
[GRUNTING]
[DOOR OPENS]
I'm sorry.
We were here at 9:00.
Just like you told us.
Well, my son
woke up with a 102.
I called...
They didn't say a thing.
Come on, David.
I am so sorry.
I asked if we could have
some time here before
David joins his group.
So what
do you think, David?
Isn't it nice?
[SIGHS]
So, David...
Oh, don't you look
handsome today.
Come, let's hang
this jacket up.
Come here, come on.
[GRUNTING]
David, don't do that.
David, honey,
that's not allowed.
Please.
[CRYING]
All right.
It's all right.
It's all right, David.
You can keep it on
if you like.
It's all right, honey.
It's fine, keep it on
if you like. I just want
to show you around.
Come on, let's go this way.
[GRUNTING]
SALLY: David. Cut it out.
[SCREAMING]
SALLY: David. David!
Knock it off.
Come on, sweetie,
calm down.
Calm down.
Come on, sweetie.
It's okay, sweetheart.
[YELLING AND SCREAMING]
GLADYS: What is it?
Because he been in places
like this. I told you that.
Stop it. Stop it, David,
stop it!
[GRUNTING]
Don't you bite me!
Leave us just
few minutes alone,
will you?
Please!
[DAVID CRYING]
Can you give us just
a little time to get around...
Ow!
David! Get out!
Look. Look! David,
stop it, okay?
Stop it, David,
listen to me.
Look at me. Look at me!
Look at me!
Look here. Who is this?
Who is this, huh?
[CRYING]
It's me. It's mama.
[SIGHS] Honey.
We got to talk here, okay?
I'm gonna talk and,
David honey,
you're gonna do the best
you can o listen
to everything I say.
All right?
Please, come on, baby.
Okay?
David, I want you to stay here
with Gladys.
I know I promised that
you wouldn't have to,
but I was wrong.
Things stink.
They have for a long time.
I'm just getting
a whiff of the stench.
Sweetheart,
it's not your fault,
it's my fault.
Listen to me, David.
My whole life
I never felt special,
I never felt it.
Pretty enough or talented
enough to be anything
but ordinary.
And then you came along.
And you were the way
you were, David.
You know what?
I was the only one
who could handle you.
Do you have any idea
how special
that makes
a person feel, David?
Oh, honey, you're a piece
of work, just like me.
But I could get you up.
And I could get you dressed,
I could feed you,
and I could make you
real happy.
And that's the way
I kept you.
But not for you, honey.
I did it for me.
I kept us watching movies...
and I stayed special.
And you stayed calm.
[SIGHS]
Sweetie, you know what?
There's a lot more out there
than calm.
There's a whole world
out there, sweetie.
Even for you.
[SIGHS]
And you know what?
Hey, you can work a VCR.
[SNIFFLES]
I want you to stay here
with Gladys.
I wanna see
if you got any other
tricks up your sleeve.
You can stay, but listen,
the truth is this.
I may not be special,
but, oh boy,
[CLICK OF TONGUE]
you sure as hell are.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SHUTS]
[UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]