♪ [Multicom Entertainment
Group jingle] ♪
[wind blowing]
♪ [The Charlie Daniels Band -
"Across The Line"] ♪
-Whoo!
-He he.
Look at the way this baby
handles a curve, Billy.
I'm telling you.
Nothing beats the
suspension on a Bronco.
Yeah, I was thinking about
getting me one of
them new Tahoes.
That's if they give it to me.
Don't you tell me
you're a Chevy man, boy?
I don't know.
I guess I haven't decided yet.
I mean, look at this thing!
It red-lines about 6000 RPM.
It's like a fucking Ferrari,
man.
A Tahoe?
Shit!
A Tahoe's a housewife's car.
Eat my dust!
You fucking Chevy! [laughs]
♪ Where the sun goes up
and the sun comes down ♪
♪ Nothing ever changes
in a border town ♪
♪ It turns around
and starts all over again ♪
♪ It's alcohol and nicotine
and everyday's like Halloween ♪
♪ It's a muy loco world
we're living in ♪
♪ It's broken dreams
and shady deals ♪
♪ Red hot cars
and cold blue steel ♪
♪ And every night,
temptation comes around ♪
♪ And down on the border
where the coyotes howl ♪
♪ The hot winds blow
and the big boys prowl ♪
♪ Always something evil
going down ♪
[Walt]
Yee haw!
-♪ Look out boy you're gonna
lose control ♪
♪ Blow your cool
and curse your soul ♪
♪ Open up your eyes
and read the signs ♪
♪ Are you gonna be a man
and stand up tall ♪
♪ Or turn your back
and say the hell with it all ♪
♪ Don't you know that
the blind can't lead the blind ♪
♪ And you're just about to
cross the line... ♪
You know, this truck's no
license to drive like an
asshole, Walt.
Sorry about that, Sheriff;
we didn't see you
when we was coming over
that hill there.
Yeah, I noticed.
Just, uh, showing off some of my
driving skills for Billy here.
He's one of our new boys.
And Ty put you
in charge of him?
Go figure, huh?
Billy, meet the Sheriff.
That's Sheriff Johnson.
It's an honor to meet you, sir.
Any relations to Chief Johnson?
Yeah, Ty's my brother.
Yup, you want to get anything
done in Maverick County, these
are the boys to know.
The Johnson family's been
running this land since
before The Alamo.
Wow.
Where you boys headed?
We got us
an appointment with Timex.
Uh huh.
I want you to behave
yourself out there, Walt.
Oh, I will, Sheriff.
[laughing]
[Walt]
Yee-haa.
[tire screeches]
[sewing machines whirring]
Que es esta mierda?
[Diamando] You've ruined it.
I don't need this shit.
I can get a healthy worker.
You heard me, old man.
Get lost. Get lost!
What about the years of work
my father gave to this place?
Years of loyalty.
For what?
For the pennies you pay him?
[Mama]
Miranda, stop it.
No, I will not.
You have no heart.
We may be poor, Diamando,
but we are not stupid.
Señor Diamando,
she doesn't mean it.
She's just a little angry.
That's what happens when you
send your daughter to
the university.
She opens her eyes
and gets ideas.
If my father goes, so do I.
And so does my mother.
We will go, too!
Yeah, if he goes, we all go.
A la mesa.
Food is ready.
Just come.
Come.
You too, Lauro.
[Pedro]
Let us eat.
[Mama] Go ahead, sit.
I'm coming.
[Miranda]
Mama, you never sit.
Come.
Let me do it this time.
Sit down, all of you.
So we can say our prayer.
Then go on with it.
Yo también.
Thank you, God, for all
that you have given us:
a home, food on the table,
a dear family.
Blessed are you, Jesus, and this
food we are about to receive,
through your grace,
and through Christ, our lord.
[loud thud]
[Miranda]
Luciano, que paso?
They’re coming, Miranda!
They’re coming.
They are looking for you.
-Who’s coming?
-The soldiers.
The soldiers?
Oh, my God!
But, but why?
What did I do?
He said you were making trouble,
Miranda.
They want to take you in
for questioning.
Miranda, you want me
to push you?
[Miranda] No.
No. You two, get back
in the house.
Go before they see you, too.
-Are you sure?
-Go.
-Okay.
-Let’s go.
-Go! Go!
-Come on.
-Let’s go.
[Pedro]
Quick! They’re here.
[speaking Spanish]
[Luciano]
It's the soldiers.
[loud knocking on door]
[Comandante] Policia!
Open the door!
[loud knocking on door]
[Comandante]
Policia!
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
[Mama]
Please...
We’re just working people.
We don't want any trouble.
[Pedro]
It's okay, Mama.
Calma.
What do you want
with an innocent girl?
I don't need
to give you answers.
You see this uniform?
That is your answer.
Now where is she?
[snaps fingers]
♪ [music intensifies] ♪
[Mama] Dios mio!
No.
[Mama]
[objects crashing]
[Mama crying]
[Mama]
No. Oh, no!
[Mama screams]
She’s not here.
What is your name?
Lauro.
You are
a good little soldier, Lauro.
So tell me.
Where, uh... where is Miranda?
[Comandante]
Hhmm?
She's not here.
She left.
She didn't come to dinner.
Will you bring her back?
Hey!
We'll be back for her.
[wood thuds]
[cars revving]
I can't stay here anymore.
[Luciano] If they take you,
Miranda, they’ll never
bring you back.
You know what happened
to the Gardella's son...
We know that.
We know what happens.
I must leave this town,
this whole country.
No, mi hijita. No.
[Miranda]
Luciano, Jesus...
Now is the time for us
to go to America.
America again?
Miranda, why?
It is a great country, Papa!
People come from all over
the world to America.
I will be one of them.
I will work hard,
and then send for all of you.
Daughter...
Stop dreaming.
They don't want
any more immigrants there.
They look down on you.
No. No, not Miranda.
She speaks English so good.
You and Mama,
you will be so happy.
We will have freedom.
[gun shot]
One hell of a shot, Sheriff.
Must be terror in the hearts
of Pepsi cans everywhere.
Can't remember last time we had
to shoot for real, though.
Yeah, we surprised old Denver in
his house.
Nobody wanted to shoot.
You know, sometimes I don't
feel like we're real cops.
I mean, border patrol gets
all the action around here.
And when I talk to Hector in
L.A., man, it's like a war zone
out there everyday.
You wouldn't like it out there,
Sanchez.
Trust me.
[Sanchez]
Oh, yeah?
Now the women on the other hand.
Oh, the women.
Maybe we should take a trip
out there some time together.
We could stay with Hector.
He knows all the right places.
What'd ya say?
Well, maybe after the election.
Not much going on after that.
Yeah, it might be fun.
[can rattling]
[zipper closing]
"Tonks" will be coming over
that hill any second, Billy?
[Billy]
Tonks?
Yeah, you know, the wets.
Tonks tonk.
It's the sound it makes when you
hit 'em over the head
with a flashlight.
[snickering]
-Well, here they come now!
-Yeah.
Yeah, Jesus, Walt.
How'd you know that?
Now, you see that boy in front
there who's got the
walking stick?
-Well, yeah? -Yeah, well,
that's their coyote.
He brings a bunch of them
through that pass about
three times a week.
We call him Timex. Hell, you
could set your watch by him.
You gotta be kidding me.
Why doesn't he just
change his routine?
Well, ‘cause, uh, ‘cause we got
a little deal with him,
that's why.
He, uh, gets his peso
from the wets on the other side,
then he gets his dollars
from us on this side.
[Billy]
Real bastard, huh?
That's a good businessman, boy.
Ready to rock and roll, rookie?
[Billy]
I guess.
-[door slams]
-[engines start]
[Ty] You know, I could see it
right now; headlines.
First Johnson ever loses
election in South Texas.
[Grant]
Thanks, big brother.
[Ty]
Trying to help.
[Grant] Well, I don't need your
help.
He won't win.
[Ty] He will win.
You wanna know why?
‘Cause his last name is Alvarez.
[Grant]
Uh huh, like our last name
has never won us an election,
huh?
Is that what you are saying?
[Ty] It wasn't because we were
white.
It was because we were good.
[Grant]
We'll, we're still good.
[Ty]
Doesn't matter.
Johnson's just another name now,
and a common one, too.
And it sure as hell
isn't Mexicano.
Well, we always got
the Mexican vote before.
Well, the old ones we did.
They knew Dad.
He was the only white sheriff
to ever give them a fair shake.
This new bunch... they only
been here a couple years.
These Mexicans
don't know about Dad.
They don't know about Frannie
or Scarface Charlie.
They don't know about
Watson's watering hole.
Hell! They never even heard
of the McKinley Ranch.
And there's more on the way.
It's not like the
tide's gonna slow.
No, you are a dying breed,
baby brother.
A white sheriff
on the Mexico line.
♪ [dramatic Spanish guitar] ♪
[Luciano] What's happening?
Why we stopping?
-Que te paso?
[mumbling]
[Coyote]
Okay, give me all your money.
We had a deal!
[Coyote]
I make you a new deal now.
You give me all your money
and you live.
Or what?
You're gonna kill us all?
[Coyote] No, mamacita.
We'll keep you alive for fun.
Move your ass.
Come on!
Everybody out of the truck!
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on!
Hands on your head.
Let's go.
[Jesus]
We had a deal.
Your time will come.
[spits]
Hey, leave her alone!
Okay. Keep quiet.
[Luciano]
Miranda?
[Coyote]
Vamonos!
[Luciano] Miranda, let me see.
Okay?
Estoy bien.
[speaks Spanish]
♪ [country rock playing] ♪
[men laughing from a distance]
[Walt] Hurry up, rook!
Come on now.
Let's go.
Hells the matter with you?
Pass ‘em out, boy.
What kind of rook
are you, anyway?
[Franco] They don't teach them
nothing down in Georgia anymore.
They got to start teachin'
‘em practical stuff.
Yeah, like handin' out beer
to their elders.
Instead of watching El Norte 18
times, they show you that movie,
Billy?
Yeah, it was pretty good.
What a pile of horse shit, man.
You think you can learn how to
work the line off a movie?
Nothing prepares
you for the line.
That's right. We're fighting
a war out here, boy.
And you're on
the front lines of it.
Why don't you tell Franco
where you're from?
-Oklahoma. -Ok-la-fuckin'homa!
You hear that?
[laughs]
Why, are you
from Oklahoma, Franco?
Nah! I'm from Tucson.
But I took Oklahoma
and six and a half points.
That's right and my longhorns
raped them.
Thank you very much.
Damn! What time is it?
Ahh, it's 10:30.
[Walt]
What's the matter, Briggs?
You worried Darla's gonna whoop
your butt for being in late?
I wish.
I got a double shift tomorrow.
I’m back on in six hours.
I'll catch you all later.
[Billy] Yeah.
Bye, Briggs.
[Franco]
Hey, Walt,
I heard them new Tahoes
won't be coming in on time.
Well, that's okay, ‘cause Billy
here's got his heart
set on a Bronco.
Ain't that right, Bronco Billy?
[Franco]
Ain't no Bronco's neither.
Yeah?
Walt, what is he gonna
be doing on Friday night?
Well, he's going to be out
at Eagle Pass with us, I guess.
What's in Eagle Pass?
Looks like you're gonna
find out, Bronco.
Drink up.
[Jesus] I'm sorry.
The others were right.
I took you the wrong way.
[Miranda] Jesus, you were right,
because, look,
going north
will bring us closer to America.
I tell you.
[Luciano] Look!
Look! There's
something up there.
[Miranda speaking Spanish]
[Jesus] Mira.
Look. Do you see that?
[Luciano]
I see it. I see it.
[Miranda excitedly panting]
[Jesus] Okay.
Look. I think we should try.
No, no, no, no.
We can't do that!
They'll see us for sure.
Three of us...
but one of us?
One of us should try.
I can't believe this.
We said we will stick together.
We told her parents
we would protect her.
We told them we'd get her
to America, too.
[Miranda]
Luciano, Jesus is right.
Look what happened to us.
Everything changed now.
We got to do whatever we can.
♪ [music on radio] ♪
-Hola.
Cuanto esto?
Veinte pesos,
para ustedes especial.
I ain't leaving without
one last souvenir.
Yep.
-Ain’t it gorgeous?
-Mm-hmm.
Gracias.
Es, uh, muy bonito.
Oh, si.
Okay, darling, but this is
surely the last thing we're
gonna buy today?
Hmm?
Well...
-There you go, dear.
-Gracias.
[Jesus] Hurry, Miranda,
before it's too late.
Who are they?
They're on their way
to America.
This is their last stop
before Texas.
You will follow me?
Promise.
In trouble or good... we
are behind you.
We’ll see you soon...
in America.
Okay.
Now. Go.
Go!
Go, Miranda, go.
[Mrs. Randall]
I'm not finished.
[Mr. Randall]
Well.
[Mrs. Randall]
John!
[Mr. Randall] Oh, lord.
Well here's a handy little
item right here.
I think this might fit.
Well, that's real special,
ain’t it?
Just like you, babe.
-Thank you.
-De nada, señora.
[Mrs. Randall]
You want me to drive?
[Mr. Randall] No, no.
Give me a couple more hours
and, uh, you can take over.
[Mrs. Randall]
All right.
[engine revving]
They’re good people.
I feel it.
♪ [music on the radio] ♪
[Mr. Randall]
Sugar dumpling.
Banana pie.
[Mrs. Randall]
I’m awake.
[laughing]
Wake up, hun.
It's going to be a
beautiful sunrise.
♪ [hard rock music] ♪
[engines revving]
[Mr. Randall]
All righty.
♪ [Spanish guitar playing] ♪
-[Mrs. Randall grumbling]
-[engine stops]
[Mr. Randall]
I'm gonna go get the camera.
Oh, bless you, darlin’!
-Warm up.
-Ah.
[Mr. Randall]
Ahh-hah...
Here they come.
♪ [Spanish guitar playing] ♪
[Mr. Randall]
Oooh, hello...
[camera shutter clicking]
[laughs]
-What do you see? -Hun, come
here.
Take a look at that.
-Looks like border patrol.
-Uh huh.
A little early morning
excitement here.
Is that the big man?
Yeah.
I talk to the big man.
Nobody talks to him.
I talk to him or no deal.
You all put your weapons away.
[speaking Spanish]
[ominous music intensifies]
-Yeah.
-[camera clicking]
-What are they doing?
-I dunno.
♪ [tense music] ♪
-[camera clicking]
-Huh!
[camera clicking]
♪ [tense music heightens] ♪
[gunshot]
[camera clicking]
Buddy.
[gun shot]
Oh, my God!
[camera clicking]
[gun shots]
[Mr. Randall] Oh, my God!
All right.
Oh, Jesus.
-Buddy?
-All right. All right. I'm out.
-Are they killing people?
-All right. It's all right.
I'm gonna reload.
It's okay, honey.
It’s all right.
-They can’t see...
-What are they doin’?
It's all right.
They don't see us up here.
[Briggs] This time, Walt,
you've gone too far.
[gunshot]
-[Mrs.
Randall] Buddy? -[camera clicks]
[Mr. Randall]
Oh, my God!
[Mrs. Randall]
Let's go.
Honey, we better get the hell
out of here.
Come on.
You grab the case.
Grab the case.
Come on, dear.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Let’s go.
Come on, baby.
Take the camera.
Get in the truck.
You boys clean this up.
Make sure the young boy
stays honest.
[Franco] Come on, kid.
Come on!
Let's go!
Move it!
-♪ [chase music] ♪
-[tires screeching]
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
-Are they the same men?
-I don't know.
-You saw ‘em. I did’t see ‘em...
[Mr. Randall stammering]
Who the hell knows?
It’s okay, hun.
Uh, yes, sir.
What can I do for you?
[Walt] Why don't you step out
of the vehicle, sir?
Well, can I ask
what the problem is, officer?
Aaah!
Buddy! Buddy!
-No, you can't.
-Buddy! Buddy!
What did you do?
Buddy! Buddy!
[Walt] Ma'am, all you gotta do
is tell us what you saw.
[Mrs. Randall]
We didn't see a thing.
I guess we're just gonna have to
take them in for questioning.
No. No.
What are you doing this for?
We didn't see anything.
[Ty]
Uh, huh.
[Mrs. Randall]
Buddy!
[Ty]
Come on.
[Mrs. Randall struggling]
♪ [Spanish guitar playing] ♪
[footsteps]
[Mrs. Randall]
Buddy. Honey.
Hey, Billy.
Why don't you give me
a hand here?
[Mrs.
Randall] Buddy?
Buddy, wake up.
Honey.
[Mrs. Randall crying]
Buddy!
[Mr. Randall groaning]
[Mrs. Randall]
He's hurt.
[Mr. Randall]
Huhhh...
[Mrs. Randall]
Buddy?
[Mr. Randall panting]
You, uh...
You want to wait out here,
Billy?
Well, what, what are you going
to do with them, Walt?
[panting]
[Mrs.
Randall] Oh, please.
Why are you doing this to us?
Please!
-Maybe I better keep watch.
-Yeah, wait out here, Billy.
[Mr. Randall panting]
Please.
What are you doing?
He's hurt! Can't you just stop?
Please!
Buddy! Please stop.
We won't tell anyone!
We won’t tell anyone!
[Mrs.
Randall] Stop!
Please don't do this.
-Please, please don’t do this.
-[punches and kicks]
-[stronger punches and kicks]
-Oh, God! Stop!
[Mrs. Randall]
Please! Please!
[crying] Don't do anything else.
Oh, please.
-[punches and kicks continue]
-Please don't hurt him!
Don’t do anything else.
Please, please.
We won’t tell anyone.
We didn’t do anything.
Please! Don’t hurt him!
-[Mr.
Randall groaning more] -[Mrs.
Randall] Please!
Don’t hurt him!
-[Mr.
Randall moaning intensely]
-[Mrs.
Randall] No!
[Mrs. Randall crying]
Oh, God. No!
-[gunfire] -[Mrs.
Randall] No!
Oh, God!
[Mrs. Randall screaming]
-[gunshot]
-[loud falling to the ground]
♪ [Spanish guitar playing] ♪
♪ [Spanish guitar continues] ♪
-[loud thud sound effect]
-♪ [single guitar chord] ♪
[footsteps fade
to the distance]
[owl hooting, cicadas chirping]
[horse snorting]
[spigot turning,
water running]
♪ [Spanish guitar playing] ♪
♪
[horse snorting, owl hooting]
♪ [slow guitar music] ♪
[police radio chatter]
[Hydstra]
Jesus Christ!
Wait ’til you get
a look at this, Sheriff.
Hey, boys.
Why don't you take a step
backwards, huh?
Show a little respect
for the dead.
What do you think happened
to the rest of his head?
Set up your police line,
deputy.
[fly buzzing]
Sanchez, you got your camera?
Yeah.
-[camera clicking]
-[fly buzzing]
[camera clicking]
They weren't killed here.
Listen, I want you to go back up
on the road.
See if you can find
some tire tracks. Huh?
Danny.
Oh, yes, sir.
Who called it in?
Oh, the old couple.
Hi, folks.
I'm Grant Johnson,
Maverick County
Sheriff's Office.
How do you do, Sheriff?
My name is Rob, and this is
my missus here.
I have a name.
My name is Bess.
-Bess, how are you?
Good to meet you.
Now I understand you folks found
the bodies.
Is that correct?
Yup, yup, yeah.
We was out huntin'
and my dog pooch here,
well, he found ‘em just,
just lying there.
He calls it hunting,
but it's just walking really.
-We never shoot anything...
-Now, how long ago was that?
Oh, that's a tough question,
Sheriff.
I think it’s about, oh...
I'd say about,
about an hour or so ago...
No, no, I really can't say
because we just don't
wear watches.
When you're retired,
who keeps track of time?
I'm afraid that my dog might
have licked up some
of the blood.
Is that right, baby?
Is that right, little girl?
[old woman]
Bad dog. Bad dog.
[Grant] You don't recognize
either of the victims?
Ma'am, you don't recognize
The way they look, could you?
[old woman]
Uh-uh.
[Sanchez]
Hey, Sheriff!
Excuse me.
Yeah, what do you got?
[Sanchez]
Over here.
Looks like fresh tracks.
Those are fresh all right.
Looks like a four-wheel drive
came right down through here.
All right.
Mark this right here.
Hydstra!
I want to lock this off
right here, okay?
[helicopter approaching]
Jesus Christ!
[Grant] Hey, hey, hey.
You can't park this thing here.
I'll take it under advisement.
-Sheriff?
-Alvarez, hold it.
Alvarez, you can't be here.
These people can't be here.
This is a crime scene.
-Yeah, well, it looks like we
don't have much of a choice now,
does it, Sheriff?
Ladies and gentlemen of the
press, please gather around.
[Grant]
Hey, you can’t be there.
Please gather around.
[reporter]
Over here!
Thank you.
Now you see this is exactly what
I'm trying to tell you.
The Sheriff's Department
has been using outdated methods,
outdated equipment,
and outdated people.
That's for sure, and I'm gonna
bring this to the light.
[Grant] Hey, this is a crime
scene.
That means you.
Now get back, all right?
You want to take a picture?
You gotta go through me.
Now get back.
Hydstra, Sanchez, get over here.
Sheriff, have the victims
been identified yet?
No, I have no comment at this
point.
We just found the bodies.
This is a crime scene.
Please step back.
-Hydstra?
-Do you have any suspects?
Ma'am, you heard me.
I have no information
at this time.
Sheriff Johnson, do you think
this will affect your chances in
Tuesday's election?
There's two people brutally
murdered right over there.
This isn't about any goddamn
election.
Now get back.
How much does it cost?
How much you have?
Twenty dollars each.
Twenty dollars?
[laughs]
Amigos!
You're O.T.M.
What do you mean by O.T.M.?
Other than Mexican.
[laughs]
O.T.M.'s get caught
by La Migra.
Then, they're back home on a
plane faster than you
can shake shit.
[Timex] You gotta make sure you
can make it, amigos.
Some O.T.M.'s pay five,
ten thousand dollars.
Ten thousand?
We only have twenty.
Twenty? Ha!
I'm a businessman, amigo.
I have to make money.
I have people to support.
Come on, mister.
They said you could help us.
Maybe.
[laughs]
♪ [slow slide guitar music] ♪
Muchas gracias.
We were out sayin’ I’m gonna
head up to San Anton tomorrow.
Check out
those people's backgrounds,
see if I can make
some sense of this whole deal.
What about the election?
Well, it's not looking
too good right now.
These murders,
they might be just what Alvarez
needs to push him over the top.
What are you gonna do about it?
[sighing]
What am I gonna do about it?
You know something, big brother?
What I've been realizing?
Without this job,
I ain't got nothing.
This little piss-ant house.
No family.
You always got us.
The kids, they love you.
You know Margaret.
Oh yeah, that's your family, Ty.
Me, I got nothing.
I've never built nothing.
I haven't created nothing.
Like I've been married to this
damn job, and this community...
my whole life,
and now they want a divorce.
You don't have to lose
this election, Grant.
It's not too late.
Listen, I just need you to help
me find out who killed
those people.
That's the only help I need
right now.
All right?
You're gonna get it,
but who knows how long
that's gonna take.
Election's on Tuesday.
Let me make the phone calls
I need to make.
I'll get the vote out for you.
What do you suppose old Daddy
would say if he was
alive right now?
What would Dad say?
Goddamn it, Grant.
Would you quit idolizing Dad?
He’s into more shit
than you can ever imagine.
You just too young
to know about it.
Oh, that's real nice.
I can't believe
I'm hearing you say that.
Quit being so goddamn naive.
Dad did whatever
was necessary to stay in power.
Well, he didn't break any
goddamn laws.
I know that much.
Bullshit!
Dad was above the law.
And he sure as hell wasn't gonna
let some Mexican car dealer kick
him out of office.
Now you listen to me.
You don't have to do
a damn thing.
I'll take care of it, all right?
All right?
♪ [Spanish guitar playing] ♪
-Ah!
-Oh.
[Miranda]
Sorry.
I looking for someone.
Well, this is my diner.
Who are you looking for?
My cousin, Raul.
I heard he was working here.
Raul...
I don't know any Raul.
He's not so tall,
straight, dark hair.
He speaks a little English.
Maybe you mean Joaquin.
Yes, Joaquim, Joaquim.
We call him Raul
because it's his middle name.
Joaquim left about a month ago
for California.
Is he coming back?
I don't think so.
Did he know you were coming?
No, not really.
Well, sorry.
Sorry!
Maybe you need someone
to work
in the place of...
in the place of uh...
-Joaquin...
-Joaquim.
[yells in Spanish]
Hey, slow down, mister.
The boy can't keep up.
Well, you stay with them
if you want.
Watch out for the skinheads.
Skinheads?
What skinheads?
Ah, you know.
They're fighting a holy war
for the white race.
They like it up here
this time of day.
Like, uh...
Hunting you "chickens" with
high powered rifles.
Boom!
[laughs]
Check this out.
♪[heavy rock music
with sirens] ♪
Scares the shit
out of them wets, boy.
[laughs maniacally]
[in unison]
What is it?
[music continues]
[all together]
La Migra! La Migra!
[yelling in Spanish]
Yeah!
♪[heavy rock music
with sirens continues] ♪
Yee-haa!
[loud grunt]
[groaning]
[Jesus]
Luciano!
[Walt] What do you think you
doing, tonk?
Huh?
You dented my goddamn truck.
[Jesus] Hey, you hurt my
brother, stupid gringo.
[Jesus]
Hey!
You hurt my brother,
stupid gringo.
[grunting]
[Jesus] Leave him alone!
Leave him alone!
Hey, Walt.
Here comes some more of
‘em right there.
Goddamn!
Where are they all coming from,
boy?
[Alvarez on T.V.]
Hi, my name is Richard Alvarez
and I’d like to invite you
and your family to come on down
to your local Alvarez car
dealership for a
free test drive.
[Loretta] Hey, Javier.
Egg salad, light mayo.
[Alvarez] Don’t forget to
stop by our special...
One more coffee
over there, Miranda.
[Alvarez]
of your new automobile.
And I'd sure appreciate it
if you’d vote for me
in the upcoming elections
for Maverick County Sheriff.
Buy American.
Vote American. Be American.
I thank you.
They're calling it
Bloody Friday,
one of the deadliest days
in Maverick County history.
[news anchor] Just hours after
the border patrol
was involved in a shoot-out with
drug smugglers at Eagle Pass.
In an unrelated event, two
murder victims were
discovered in a field
outside of Crystal City.
[news anchor] Ryan Walters was
at that scene.
He now has this report.
Ryan.
[Ryan]
Thanks, Molly.
The victims of this gruesome
murder have been identified.
They are Mr. and Mrs.
John Randall of San Antonio,
Texas.
According to friends and family,
the Randalls were vacationing in
Mexico in their R.V.
They were expected
to return home this weekend.
Maverick County Sheriff Grant
Johnson has vowed to bring
these killers to justice.
Observers say that if he's to
have any hope of
winning re-election,
he'll need to deliver on that
promise before next
Tuesday's election.
Ladies and gentlemen, the couple
that we’re looking for
were driving a late model
green and white motor home.
It's got a Texas flag
painted on the back.
Texas plates B13DGW.
Now if you've seen this R.V., or
if you have any
information at all,
I want you to call me at the
Maverick County
Sheriff's Department.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
[Ryan] The sheriff has set up a
hotline for you to call
if you have any information.
This is Ryan Walters
for KBKB Channel 5 News.
Honey, you sure
are interested in that T.V. set.
Oh... or, is it that Sheriff
Johnson you're interested in?
Now there's one tough catch.
I’ll tell you.
All the good women
of Crystal City
been chasing
that one for years.
Not one of ‘em's got a ring yet.
Oh, orders up.
Thanks, Javier.
Honey, come on.
More coffee.
Que paso, Miranda?
I want to ask you.
You've been here a long time.
Six years.
If, if you... knew something,
You know, you saw something
you shouldn't see.
Something bad.
Would you tell the police?
What did you see?
It doesn't matter what.
Would you... trust the police?
Miranda, you're
illegal here, verdad?
Si.
If you talk to the police,
they're gonna make
your life hell.
They're not gonna leave
you alone.
They're gonna take you to court
and make you talk.
[speaks Spanish]
So, they can send you back.
No, mi hija.
You do your work.
[speaks Spanish]
In this country,
every man... is for himself.
♪ [music playing on radio] ♪
[Harmon]
Hey, Sheriff.
Hey, Gene.
How's it goin’?
[Harmon]
All right.
[Loretta]
Get the salt, honey.
Hey, kid.
How you doin’? [speaks Spanish]
-He-hey, Sheriff.
-Hey, Loretta.
Let me have the regular
with a glass of water please.
-Any sign of the R.V.?
-Nope.
How about the helicopter?
Last I heard, still up there.
Neighbors see anything.
Nothin'.
It's a goddamn 50 foot R.V.
It don't make any sense.
Somebody saw something.
Hey, Sheriff.
Get a load of that new girl.
[Grant]
Yeah, I saw her.
See this?
Page three.
[Grant]
There ya go, sugar.
-There ya go.
-Thank you, Loretta.
[Loretta]
Uh, huh.
"County supervisors
back Alvarez.
Just four days
before the election,
the Maverick County supervisors
announced their support
for local car dealer, Richard
Alvarez, in the race
for sheriff.
The council's endorsement
is seen as a lethal blow
to incumbent
Sheriff Grant Johnson."
Well, the same to you,
county supervisors.
Hey! Loretta, darling, uh...
Would you have the new girl
wait on us please?
Mr. Sanchez here
would really appreciate it.
I'm not good enough
for y'all anymore, Sheriff?
No, you're too good, Loretta.
You're too good.
-Yeah, whatever. Ha.
-Thank you.
Hey, you listen to this.
"The Sheriff's Department relies
on outdated equipment,
outdated methods,
and outdated people."
Sheriff, you're gonna have
to answer this guy.
Yeah, you should make
a speech or something.
Let me tell you something.
I don't have to
bullshit these people.
I've been in this town a long
time.
They know what I'm about.
Listen Grant...
People that know you, and knew
your father, they're loyal.
You're forgetting how many new
people are here and how many
friends are gone.
Hell, if this murder happened
back in your Dad's day,
heh, whole community
would pull together.
But nowadays...
everybody keeps to themselves.
Here.
Let me help you with this.
[cup rattles]
Ahh!
So sorry...
It's okay.
It’s okay.
Oh, dios mio.
-It’s okay.
-Perdon.
I'm sorry, Sheriff.
Honey, it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
[Grant]
Loretta, it's my fault.
You know, we'll be right back
to take your order, all right?
Come on honey.
Listen. Listen to me.
I told you
they are not immigration, okay?
So you are just gonna have to
trust some people in your life,
all right?
Even if they have a gun,
for God's sake.
All right; look, you know what?
You just go take care
of yourself.
I'll, I’ll deal with them, okay?
All right?
All right, Sheriff.
Sorry about that.
Can I take y'all's order here?
Yeah, we're ready, Loretta, but
I still want the new
girl to help us.
Well, you know, and her English
is not so good.
So I'll...
Her English is just fine,
Loretta.
Please go get her.
Yes, sir.
[Loretta] They want you to
take this, honey.
Hello.
I'm Grant Johnson.
This is Jimmy Hydstra.
And this, this fine young man
here, this is Danny Sanchez.
Mucho... [mumbles]
We come here all the time.
And your name is?
I'm Miranda.
Miranda?
Miranda.
Well that's, that's,
that's a very beautiful name.
Uh, “mira,” to see, right?
The one who saw?
[radio reporter] The promising
campaign of Richard Alvarez
for Maverick County Sheriff.
Federal tax officials
launched an investigation
into allegedly
fraudulent tax return filed
by three of Alvarez's
six South Texas car dealerships.
Mr. Alvarez released a statement
denying the affair with
the housekeeper,
and reassuring the community
that he would be absolved
of all wrong-doing
in the investigation by
the Internal Revenue Service.
Nevertheless, Maverick County
supervisors quickly withdrew
their endorsement of Mr.
Alvarez in the race for sheriff,
suddenly leaving incumbent
Sheriff Grant Johnson in
excellent position
to reclaim the seat that he and
his family have controlled
for over 30 years.
Johnson has been struggling to
overcome his waning popularity
in the face of increasing
violence in the county
highlighted by last weekend's
bloodshed at Eagle Pass.
You remember Sheriff Johnson,
don't you, Billy?
I sure do.
How you doing, Sheriff?
Good, Billy.
I'm doing good.
Have you ever been out
to the old McKinley Ranch?
McKinley Ranch?
Um, I don't know.
Well, we found
some tire tracks out there,
right where we found
those bodies.
-Is that right?
-Yeah, that's right.
Looks like a Bronco
might've passed through.
Well, Sheriff, you got it all
wrong.
I mean, I...
Billy, Billy, it's all right.
Sheriff's not accusing
you of nothin'.
I mean now we's not the only
Bronco passin'
through that area.
Sheriff knows that.
Our boys are out there all the
time.
Just not last night.
Of course, we been working out
that Eagle Pass bust for quite
a while, you know.
[Grant]
Let me ask you something, Billy.
You see anything strange
last night?
Well, yeah.
I seen something real strange.
I never seen nothing like that
before in my whole life,
all that shooting and all,
but...
It's like I told you, Sheriff.
None of my boys seen nothing.
But, uh, be happy to keep
checking into it for you.
[screen door slams]
Good luck in the election,
Sheriff.
[door closes]
What the hell's
the matter with you?
Can't you keep
your goddamn mouth shut?
I’m, I’m sorry, Walt.
I was just trying to answer his
questions the best I could.
Oh, Mr. Harmon.
I fell asleep... a few minutes
before you come.
Miranda, why didn't you tell me
you had no place to stay?
I have a place.
I just tired.
Don't lie to me, Miranda.
I can't have my employees
with no place to sleep.
Where are you gonna take
a shower and all?
-Do I smell bad, Mr.
Harmon? -No, no, no.
You know what I mean.
Mr. Harmon, I gonna find a
place.
I promise.
I just need my first money.
All right.
I'll give you an advance today.
But I want an address from you
right away.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
Right away.
What about that new kid?
What's his name?
Billy Mercer.
Yeah, Billy.
Well, he's doing all right
I guess. I mean, uh...
all things considered.
You sure?
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know.
He gets this funny look in his
eyes sometime like he's
thinking too much.
I think it was a mistake
to take him up to Eagle Pass.
Ty, boy's riding in my truck.
We was gonna have to clue him
in sooner or later.
Well, is he with us or not?
I don't think
the boy's made up his mind yet.
Well that, by God,
is not gonna flush.
That boy cracks,
we're all goin' down.
What do you want me
to do about it?
♪ [Spanish guitar playing] ♪
[Grant]
Careful.
[coffee pouring]
Porque tiene miedo de mi?
You are police.
Donde aprendiste Ingles?
Porque no estas aqui
mucho tiempo.
La mayoría
de los nuevos immigrantes...
En Guatemala.
Does everyone from your country
speak as well as you?
No.
Pero para mi fue
muy importante aprender inglés.
I'm sorry if I sound mad at you.
But you know,
people in my country...
They study.
They shower.
They have a phone...
even if they are poor people.
Well, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to offend you.
Since I come here,
everybody tell me,
you are so pretty;
you're so clean.
You speak English so good
like it's not normal.
Did you learn to speak
English in Guatemala?
I study.
I study hard.
I read every,
every English newspaper.
I went to the university.
I didn't finish, but...
I took classes, and there were
a lot of American students.
Well, why didn't you finish?
[Miranda sniffling]
I had to help my family.
I went back to work
in the factory.
I wanted to study.
I wanted to... to finish the
university, to study the law.
Law?
In my country,
freedom and justice
are only words.
So when I come here,
I thought in the United States,
it will be different.
But you don't like cops, right?
Policia?
With them, I don't have
such good... experience.
Do you like to be... a cop?
A cop?
I don't know.
It's uh...
You know,
it's all I've ever known.
Me and my whole family's been in
law enforcement ever since
I can remember.
Do you have a family?
Do I?
Yeah, I have a family.
Why are you so surprised?
You come to eat here... always.
No, I have a brother.
He lives in Del Rio.
He's got a wife,
bunch of little kids.
He was the sheriff before me.
And your mama and papa?
My Mom passed away.
My Dad... well...
My Dad was the sheriff in this
county.... a long time ago.
That was back when being a Texas
lawman still meant something.
He died on the job trying to
break up a fight between a
drunk and his wife.
Took a stray bullet
in the head for his trouble.
That's not much
of a death for a hero.
Do you... where...
Do you have a wife?
Wife?
No, no wife.
They say
I'm not the marrying kind.
I don't think they know.
[screen door slams]
Can I help you?
Uh, yeah.
Is, uh, Sheriff Johnson here?
He's sitting over there
at the counter.
Or he was.
Maybe he went in the back.
[screen door shuts softly]
Grant, there's a guy over there
that wants to talk to you.
That's strange.
He must've left.
Who was it?
I don't know. Some kid.
I never saw him before.
Hey, what do you think
if I walked you home? Huh?
My home?
There, there are a lot of people
in my home, right now.
No, no.
I didn't mean I'd go inside.
I mean, I'll just walk you to
the door.
Would that be all right?
Okay.
So this is it, huh?
This is... where you live?
Your home?
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mister Johnson.
Call me Grant.
Please?
Good night, Grant.
Hey, listen.
Uh...
I’m not a very good cook, but...
Why don't you come over
Wednesday night, and I'll
make dinner for you?
Pick you up at the diner?
Okay.
Yes, I come.
Good night.
[cicadas chirping]
What's on your mind, Billy?
Nothin'.
Come on, boy.
Speak up now.
It's just...
I didn't think
it was gonna be like this, Walt.
[clears throat]
Well...
Nobody thought things was gonna
turn out the way they did,
Billy.
It just doesn't seem right.
I mean, not for me, at least.
I... I, I don't know.
I... think I
gotta get out of here.
You know, start on
something different.
You know, go back to Oklahoma
and get my head straight.
[engine stops]
[sighs] Billy, let me
tell you something.
There ain't
no getting out of it.
Okay?
You was there.
You was part of it.
You saw the killing.
And now you're part
of it for good.
What are we doing here, Walt?
It's a surprise, Billy.
I don't think I like
surprises too much.
Come on. Come on.
[open car door buzzing]
Go on. Go on.
♪ [dramatic slow music] ♪
So what do you think?
About what?
About your new vehicle.
Ha ha.
Look it there, boy.
That's a brand new Chevy Tahoe,
is it not?
[laughing]
You... you got
to be kidding me, right?
Hell if I am.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Come on.
I tell you, Billy.
Things ain't all that bad, boy.
Right? Let's do it.
Let's go for a ride. Come on.
-All right.
-All right!
I still think you should have
gone for a Bronco.
[phone rings]
Yeah, hello?
[Ty]
It's your brother.
What's up, Ty?
I just called to tell you you
can get a good night's
sleep tonight.
Election's tomorrow.
It’s all taken care of.
Jesus, Ty!
I don't want to hear about that!
God, would you relax?
Look, I just want you to know
that the Johnsons still
run this county.
[phone beeps]
♪ [country blues song] ♪
You two.
Come on. You two.
Let's go. Both of you.
Come on.
Let's go.
Come on!
There you go.
Okay.
We're let you boys go now.
I don't never want to see
your faces again.
Go on. Get out of here.
Comprende?Entiendes?Muchachos.
Andale.
Vamos.
Just keep going.
Don't turn around.
To the right there.
Keep going now.
A la derecha.
[Jesus] Luciano, this is the
same camper Miranda got on.
[Luciano] No.
No. It can't be.
[Jesus] I'm telling you, man.
Es el mismo.
Sheriff, there's a radio call
from the border patrol.
[Grant]
Put it through.
Yeah, go ahead.
[Walt]
Sheriff, it’s Walt.
I think we might have spotted
that R.V. of yours.
You know the old dirt road
off of old highway 41,
about two miles
east of the county line?
You reading me, Sheriff?
Yeah, we copy that.
We're on our way.
Okay.
I'm gonna check the barn.
Go. Hello?
Hello?
Is anybody here?
Buenos dias?
Hello?
There's no one in the barn.
Look, their stuff is here.
Hey!
You can't take those, Jesus.
Necesitamos ropa.
We need the clothes.
They'll never miss them.
Something doesn't feel
right though.
We gotta get out of here.
Come on.
Okay. Okay.
Espérame. Espérame.
-Jesus, come on.
Rápido!
Look! There’s food in here.
-Okay. Just bring it with you!
Come on.
-Let’s go! Rápido!
Let’s go!
You sound like grandma,
you know.
Corre!
Run! Run!
-[sirens]
-Run! Luciano, Run!
-Run!
[sirens blaring]
[Police Officer]
Stand on the car!
[Jesus] We didn't do nothing.
We just took some food.
[Hydstra]
Shut up!
[Grant] Hey!
Hey! Hey.
That's enough, Hydstra.
That's enough.
[Grant]
What's the matter with you?
Are they armed, Sanchez?
No, sir.
[Grant]
Just check that.
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Look!
-No, that's not ours.
-That’s impossible!
Hey! Watch where you're
pointin' that!
-That’s not ours!
-That's impossible!
[Grant]
De donde son ustedes?
Somos de Guatemala!
We’re political refugees.
Then where'd you get the gun?
I swear, mister.
That gun does not belong to us.
-Yeah, right.
-It's not ours.
[snorting]
Ahhh, there.
Hey, Billy, did'ya hear
about the, uh, the wetback
who got the job
in the east Texas sawmill?
Nope.
Well, uh, first day of work,
wet loses a finger, right?
Boss comes up to him
and says, "How did you do that?"
Wet says, "Well, I stuck my
finger in this spinning wheel
like this here.
See!
Oh no! I did it again.”
[laughs]
Hey, Billy. Come on now.
Take it easy on the nose candy.
I think you're startin'
to like it too much.
Okay.
So, uh, what do you call a
thousand wetbacks jumping
out of an airplane?
A good fucking start!
[everyone laughs]
How many wetbacks does it take
to change a light bulb?
How many?
-They ain't got none!
-[everyone laughs]
♪ [romantic Spanish music
playing on stereo] ♪
Almost ready.
Is this your car?
Yeah, it's a... Pontiac GTO 64.
It's a classic.
Americans love big cars.
Well, I love that car.
Longest relationship
I've ever had.
But why is it here?
It's, uh, marking
a poem that I like.
Mario Benedetti?
Yeah, right.
You know him?
Yes, I love him.
He's one of the best.
"Tactica y Estrategia."
Tactic and Strategy.
Hey, can you say the whole poem
in English?
It will help me learn.
Maybe.
[clears throat]
My tactic is to look at you.
-To... learn?
-Learn.
The way you are.
To love you the way you are.
My tactic is to talk to you.
To... build with...
To build with words
an indestructible... bridge.
My...
My tactic is to be honest
and...
and to know
that you are honest.
And that...
What's that?
And that we, uh,
we don't sell.
And that, and that,
thank you.
And that we... we don't sell
lies to each other.
So that between us, there won't
be a curtain or a chasm.
[Grant]
My strategy is...
[Miranda and Grant] “Mi
estrategia es que un
dia cualquiera,
no se como
ni se con que pretexto,
por fin me necesites.”
I think, um, we can eat now.
I like your dishes.
They remind me of my home.
There's an old Mexican lady
downtown that makes them.
-Salud.
How is your, um, investigation?
About your murder case?
It's a tough one.
Nobody saw anything.
[Miranda]
I saw their daughter on T.V.
It's very sad.
But you will find some... you
will find the truth for her,
right?
Well, yeah, not just for her,
but for everyone.
It’s my job.
You will find witnesses.
You are real concerned
about this, aren't you?
Um, I, I bring more stuff
from the...
No, no, wait.
Not here.
You're not a waitress here.
No. Stop please.
I can't.
-Did I hurt you?
-No.
-What is it?
-I... I...
What is it? Miranda, please.
You've got to trust me.
I saw it.
-You saw what?
-The murder.
I saw everything.
I was there. I was hiding.
I was, I, I was gonna
tell you before.
Believe me. I want to,
but I was too afraid...
Now, wait... You...
You saw what?
You were hiding where? What?
I, I was with the husband
and the wife.
-The Randalls? -Yes, I was in
the big... the big truck.
I was hiding in the back.
We all saw it,
and, and, and the killers,
they came in and they took the
husband and the wife, and
they killed them.
-Who did it?
-But they didn't see me.
They were...
La Migra.
La Migra!
Did you get a close look at
them?
Did you see their faces?
Well, there was one man.
He came in the back where I was.
He came to take the camera,
and I saw him.
I saw his right arm, like that.
And he had a tattoo.
-A tattoo? -Yes, a tattoo of a
snake and a knife.
In the name of God, you must
believe me.
It was La Migra.
All right.
You stay here.
I've got to make a phone call.
Margaret, this is Grant.
Is Tyrus there?
[Grant] No, it can't wait,
Margaret.
Please go and get him.
♪ [intense rock music] ♪
[cavernous sound effect]
[mumbling]
No.
Miran...
Until the case is solved,
everybody's a suspect.
[Grant on T.V.] Currently,
members of the Maverick County
Sheriff's Department are
bringing in two men for
questioning...
Where are you
rushing off to, Miranda?
Mr. Harmon, I'm sorry.
I cannot work here anymore.
Thank you for everything
you did for me, but I must go.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
At least tell me what's wrong,
so that maybe, I can be
of some help?
[Grant on T.V.]
Now, two men
we're bringing in for
questioning are brothers
from Guatemala.
It's our understanding that they
entered the country illegally.
Um, their names are Jesus and
Luciano Diaz.
That concludes my comment.
No.
Impossible. No.
[Walt] I don't know what the
hell you want with this place,
Billy.
Copper joint.
-Hey, Walt.
-Yeah?
I got something real
important to tell you.
What's up?
I, I... I know I should’a gone
and told you before.
I, I...
Well, spit it out, boy.
Well, you remember that night...
Now, when those people...
those people died?
When Briggs died, Billy.
Yeah, when Briggs died.
When I went back
and cleaned up in the barn,
I saw some girl
get out of the R.V.
You're shittin' me.
No, I, I, I...
I think she saw everything, too.
Are you a crazy son of a bitch?
And that girl...
She, she works here.
She's a waitress here
in this diner.
♪ [chase music] ♪
[Miranda screaming]
[Walt]
Open the door.
Open the fucking door!
[Harmon]
This is my diner.
[Miranda screaming]
Let's go.
Let's go. Come on.
[engines revving,
tires screeching]
[Miranda panting]
[engine roaring]
Miranda, get the...!
[Miranda hyperventilating]
Come on. You gotta trust me.
Get in the car, please.
That girl's illegal, Sheriff.
It's my job to deport her.
No, you can't deport her.
She's a witness
through the state.
You can't deport her
'til she testifies.
Heh, testifies for what?
Don't worry.
You'll be there in handcuffs.
[Walt] Is that right?
You're gonna arrest me, Sheriff?
That's funny.
You can't do that.
You can't do nothin'.
You ain't nothing, but Ty
Parker's little brother, buddy.
You wouldn't even be sheriff
if he didn't fix the election...
Ugh!
You think this is a game, homie?
You think this is
a goddamn game?
You're wrong.
You can't do whatever you want.
You're fucking with
the wrong people, Johnson.
You're gonna end up more dead
than your old man, buddy.
Game's over, Walt.
Ha ha ha.
It ain't over, Grant.
[Walt into C.B.]
Get me the chief.
[engine cuts]
[car door closes]
[door creaking]
All right.
Listen to me.
You'll be safe here.
But you got to promise me
that you are not gonna leave.
No matter what,
you don't leave this room.
All right?
Promise me.
Will you come back?
Of course, I’ll come back.
What do you think?
I’m gonna leave you here?
I gotta talk to my brother.
Now look.
Here's the keys.
He killed people for nothing...
For nothing.
What?
What? He's gonna kill me?
He's my brother.
But how can you trust him?
Hey.
I'll be fine.
All right.
Now you stay right here.
All right?
Promise me.
Okay?
Now lock the door behind me.
[door creeks]
[car approaching]
No, he's alone.
She's not with him.
[Ty]
Just find her.
[engine cuts]
[door closes]
[knocks on door]
You crazy?
Getting the kids and Margaret
all worked up like that.
No, you're the crazy one.
Does he know you killed
four people to get
-that diamond ring?
-Just keep it quiet?
Now you leave
my family out of this.
They don't need to be hearing
this.
If you wanna talk, let's go.
♪ [Spanish guitar playing] ♪
It's time you wake up, Grant,
and make something of yourself.
Think about a new house,
a new car.
A new car?
Is it that important to you,
huh, to kill people?
Is it that important?
They were Mexican drug runners
we killed.
Scum of the damn earth.
Yeah, what about the two people?
Those two good old people
in that R.V., huh?
What'd they do?
It's just wrong time, wrong
place.
I couldn't risk everything.
♪ [Spanish guitar playing] ♪
What the hell
happened to honor, huh?
Dignity, respect, loyalty?
-Doing the right thing?
What... -What the hell
does that get you?
You slave away day in, day out.
You get nothing, while the
scumbags get rich.
Grant, you know the drugs are
coming in no matter what we do.
We can't stop it.
Why shouldn't we
cash in on it, huh?
[glass breaks]
[bath running]
What's happened to you?
What's happened to our family?
If Dad were here, right now...
If Dad were here,
he would do the same damn thing.
If somebody encroached on
his territory...
Dad would never take out
one of his own. Never!
Oh, yeah?
How do you think
Scarface Charlie died?
-Just like Dad said he did.
-No, not like Dad said.
Pop sent him in first.
He didn't back him up
’til it was too late.
What are you saying, huh?
You saying Dad's a murderer?
Is that what you're sayin'?
Ain't murder.
It's self preservation.
[Ty]
Goddamn it!
I don't want to hurt you.
Hell, you can't hurt me.
Hell! You wouldn't even be
sheriff if it wasn't for me.
I got you elected.
It's payback time...
I never asked you to do that.
Quit acting so noble,
so goddamn innocent.
You knew exactly what I was
doing.
You never even tried to stop me.
Well, I'm stopping you now.
Grant... you gotta think about
what you're doin', man.
You're gonna disgrace
the whole family...
Get your stink off me.
You already
disgraced the family.
You turned out to be a real
sorry son of a bitch.
You know that, Ty Parker.
I got the same Mom
and the same Dad as you do.
Yeah, but you ain't my brother.
You ain't my brother no more.
[floor creaking,
bathroom door closing]
[Miranda screaming]
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut the fuck up!
I'm gonna enjoy this.
I'm gonna enjoy you
before I kill you.
[Miranda muffled screaming]
Now you probably don't
understand a goddamn word I
am saying, do you?
[Walt]
You stupid wetback bitch.
-[Miranda muffled screaming]
-There you go.
Sheriff give it
to you good, huh?
Did Sheriff give it
to you good, baby, huh?
[Miranda]
No!
Listen to that.
You speak English.
I'll be a son of a bitch!
[Miranda muffled screaming]
[Billy]
Walt, Walt, don't do this.
All right?
This is, this isn't right.
No, she doesn't know nothing.
All right.
She doesn't know nothin'...
Shut up!
Shut up, Billy!
Get out of here.
You'll get your sloppy seconds,
boy.
Get out.
Close the fucking door.
Get out. Get out.
[Miranda]
Nooooo!
[Miranda crying]
[door creaking]
[gunshot from outside]
No!
Billy?
Billy! Billy?
Oh, my God!
God, Billy!
Oh, my God.
Oh, man.
Oh, Billy.
You crazy son of a bitch.
What the hell did you go
do that for?
♪ [serious slow string music] ♪
[Walt] Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
[Walt breathing
and groaning deeply]
[car screeches up]
[gun shot]
It's all right.
It's all right. It's okay.
-[Miranda crying]
-It's over.
[Miranda crying]
[car door closes]
[indistinct police
radio chatter]
[Grant] No, no.
That won't be necessary.
He'll come out on his own.
[Grant] Tyrus Parker Johnson,
you're under arrest.
You're gonna arrest
your own brother.
I can't believe
you're gonna do that.
Well, you've given me no choice.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a
court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney.
If you cannot afford
an attorney,
one will be appointed to you and
one will be present
for questioning.
An attorney will be appointed
to you at no charge.
[cell phone rings]
Yeah?
Yeah, could you
hold on one second please?
Phone call for you.
-For me?
-Yeah.
Yeah, I got them right here.
Hold on.
Hello, Miranda!
Jesus! Luciano!
You saved our lives.
We're free, Miranda!
We're free!
We'll see you soon.
[speaking Spanish]
Yeah!
I will see you soon.
[everyone laughing]
-[Miranda crying]
-♪ [Spanish guitar playing] ♪
[Minister]
You may kiss the bride.
[cheering, whistling,
and clapping]
♪ [upbeat Spanish dance music] ♪
[glass breaks]
[Mama]
With this rope,
it's a symbol of a bond
between a man and his wife.
Take this.
[Mama] By binding you together,
it symbolizes the perfect union.
And it is my prayer that it
should never, ever be broken.
[Mama laughs]
Mi hijo.
-Bravo!
-[clapping, cheering]
♪ [slow romantic
Spanish music] ♪
♪ [Lynette Brehm -
“When Dreamers Fall In Love"] ♪
♪ Life hasn't been that kind
but I never had the time ♪
♪ To sit and think
what might have been ♪
♪ I've had my share of sorrow
but every new tomorrow ♪
♪ Brought me the chance
to try again ♪
♪ I never stopped believing
someday I'd be receiving ♪
♪ The things that I
was dreaming of ♪
♪ And gray skies turn to blue
and fairy tales come true ♪
♪ When dreamers fall in love ♪
♪ I knew that you will only when
I filled your eyes upon me ♪
♪ There across
the crowded room ♪
♪ The smile that you
were wearing ♪
♪ The feeling we were sharing ♪
was like the scent of
sweet perfume ♪
♪ Then your strong arms
were around me ♪
♪ And I could hear the sound
of angels singing up above ♪
♪ It's precious and it's rare ♪
♪ This magic in the air
when dreamers fall in love ♪
♪ My love
my own ♪
♪ All is in me
now I give to you ♪
♪ Mi corazón ♪
♪ You are the answer ♪
♪ to my dream come true ♪
♪ My head's in the sky
and my heart wants to fly ♪
♪ Just like I had
the wings of a dove ♪
♪ But everybody knows ♪
♪ That that's the way it goes
when dreamers fall in love ♪
♪ [Multicom Entertainment
Group jingle] ♪