Hey, wake up! Hurry!
Is this the rain, mummy?
No, this is like rain!
Don’t! Come back!
He went away, he’ s gone!
He flew away!...
Stop it! I told you not to joke about it.
He went away...
Are you hungry?
This is the only food we have left.
Eat!
I’ m going to eat with Cloudy.
I'm going to eat quicker.
A spoon for me...
a spoon for her.
Yummy!
Have you finished your studying for today?
Yes!... Should I say it?
“A”...
”F”,
”H”
No!... It’s A, B, C, D, E, F...
Let’ s see what you can read!
This is the only book we have.
Here!
There ....
There is... C’ mon Sarah, try it!
There... is...
a spe- cial
There is a special procedure in
order to operate the uterus.
I don’ t understand.
We should work on a little bit more..
What’ s the uterus?
Uterus!
Well, it’ s Cloudy’ s home... It was
yours and your brother’ s home.
Every woman has inside of her a little
house for the babies. You, too.
I want to see them.
Sometimes I think it’ s better
for them not to be here.
Maybe you shouldn’ t think
about them that much, honey.
They see the real stars, right?
Yeah...
Mum, in which house where you born?
In grandma’s home. I’ ve
already told you, remember?
I want to meet grandma.
She’ s upstairs...
Doesn’t want to see us?
She doesn’ t know we are here...
or maybe she doesn’t even care.
Did you draw the line for today, sweety?
Well, go!
Every seven days we have to count them.
1, 2 ,3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
It’ s 8182 days.
Mum!
Mum! I’ m hungry.
I want to eat bulbs.
Here, drink some water! You’
ll not be hungry anymore.
Do you like it?
It’s a rabbit? Very nice. Well done!
Please now, let’s sleep!
I’m not feeling well.
Ma mamma, non voglio dormire.
Oh, God...
OK. Think about an animal
that starts with an “E”.
Hum... Hyena?
No! But you should try drawing it, anyway.
Oh, sweety! What happened?
Oh, maybe it’s the hot temperature downhere.
Let’s take a shower!
You’ll feel better.
I will do it by myself.
Really? You want to take
the shower by your own?
Now that’s my baby!
Drink that tea, honey!
Sarah, did you eat the butter?
Without any bread?
There were no bulbs.
Now we know how you got sick!
Did you take your shower?
You know that you shouldn’ t lie to mummy.
Why don’ t you ever wash yourself?
Don’t you realize how much you stink?
I don’t stink!
Yes you stink!
No, I’m not. No, I’m not. No, I’m not!
Oh, my God! You have flies
hanging around your head.
How horrible creatures they are!
They will eat your brain, too.
Oh, no. Please take them off , mummy!
OK, OK, I’ ll help you take your shower.
Do you want to make the rain?
Yeah, I like the rain. Please take them off!
Flies hate the rain, did you know that?
Do you like it? Can you see that?
It’s very funny!
Father, thank you for the food
that you put on our table today
for all the goodness that you give us!
Be loved here and everywhere, just
the way we feel loved by you!
God bless you, father!
Sweety!...
Please, say it!
Thank you , father!
Total lack of manners!
Now, before I forget...
Take these!
It’ s too early. I haven’ t even
reached the seventh month yet.
Shut up!
Where is my glass?
Like mother, like daughter.
No!
You! You go and get your father a glass!
Did you hear what I said, you little shit?
Please, leave her alone! You
know she’ s not able...
You, idiot!
OK, fine! You don’ t wanna obey?
You don’t eat!
I’ ve learned gratitude in my life...
And you? You’ re gonna learn it too.
Respect is earned, is not given.
It’ s two way street.
You don’t show respect, you don’t get any...
This, not to be eaten.
Julia, Christian, Michael, George, Mathew
Yeah! That was taken into our swimming pool.
See what a good time they’ re having?
I treat them with love.
What’s the matter with you? You look
like a bladder that’ s gonna burst!
They live here with me and we’ re a family.
You should be happy.
Please, leave it to me!
At least the photo...
He left...
Hey, sweety! Everything is OK. Come to mamma!
I want to see the real stars.
Yeah, I know.
Mum, why do you always cut my hair?
Well, because he said so...
But I need to have a very long hair so the
prince can climb on and take us away from here.
Are you sure the fairytales princes exist?
I’ ll throw my hair out the window, anyway.
Well, this isn’t a castle tower,
it doesn’t even have windows ...
it doesn’t even have windows.
Now help me with some housework! OK?
Hi! Nice to meet you. My name is Rapunzel.
Stop fooling around! Give me a hand here!
This is Pascal, my little chameleon friend.
Pascal, this is my mum. Do you like her?
Isn’t she beautiful?
That’s it! You don’t want to have fun.
My hair is not magic at all!
Put those scissors back!
Now I’ m going to cut it!
Sarah, stop it! I need those scissors.
Put them back!
Put them back in the drawer!
Come here and help me!
Take this!
Why is dad so mean to us?
Can he just be nice to us?
Because he’ s an ogre. You should know that
an ogre never changes, he remains the same.
I tried them all. Worse is
when you go against his will.
Never do that again, Sarah!
He can get even meaner.
I do as I want!
No, you do whatever I ask you to.
I do whatever I want, this
is how it’ s going to be!
Oh, yeah? Now, you’ re old enough to
understand how it works, young lady!
Can you see these? Can you?
As you play with it, these aren’ t
for your entertainment, young lady.
These were for me!...
I was chained like a dog for a year,
with no food, no electricity,
For weeks, for months... And this was
only because I was a rebel girl.
There’ s no way to transform
an ogre into a prince.
A charming prince!
Behave yourself, missy!
Oh, my God! I’ m sorry, honey. I’ m sorry.
I just want you to be good when he’ s around.
Be good! Be good when he’ s around!
Don’ t you ever do that again!
You’ re going to break it!
It’ s amazing! These walls are full of condensation
during the summer. One day we might wake- up in a broth.
You wanna become the chicken in the broth?
No, I don’ t wanna stay in a broth!
Well, that’s going to happen if
you put the pencil in the rotor.
I think you wanna be tickled.
Come here you little chick!
That’ s it! You made me sweat.
Let’s lie down for a bit!
Mum, have you ever run in
the woods like Rapunzel?
Yes, I did.
And the woods has a different
fragrance, especially when it rains.
The earth is covered with green moss and makes
a strange noise while nourishing with water.
Then the wind moves the leaves,
the birds sing all together.
The rain makes a different rustle if it falls
on the leaves or if it falls on the concrete.
When the drops fall on metal,
they seem like stilettos.
We used to go to collect mushrooms,
chasing each other around the trees
We laughed and played
It was an enchanted world
in all that symphony.
Where you living in a cartoon?
Sometimes I think I was. This is
reality, that was only a cartoon.
I would like to live in a cartoon, too.
I don’t like life.
If I could I would draw it for you, baby.
Oh, my God!...
It’ s too early.
Help!
Oh, my God!...
I cannot take it anymore.
Somebody help me. please!
Help me!
You’ re so beautiful!
Mummy’ s sweetheart...
The scissors! I need to take the scissors.
Did you see it? It’ s a baby boy.
Really? Can we call him Pascal?
Pascal, the chameleon?
I’ ll think about it.
Dad will not take him away, too. Am I right?
I don’ t know, sweety. Maybe... He
has too many children up there.
He’ s making strange noises.
Bring the book to mummy!
I think he’ s having a breathing failure.
Go get the cooling fan to mummy!
Did you hear that? Go get the fan!
Now what?
Say it!
It’ s not working.
Help! Somebody help me, please!
Oh, my God! What should I do now?
Help!
I need to give a good impression to Pascal.
You have to take him to the hospital.
He’ s not breathing well.
Please, I cannot even feed him.
Are you listening to me?
I’ ll do whatever you want me to do. Please!
Please!
That’ s a great idea! What am I supposed
to say when they ask me where I got him?
No problem. We’ ll do the same you
made me do with the other babies.
Right! Just as with the others.
Dear mum and dad
I cannot take care of my newborn baby.
His name is...
Pascal... Right! Pascal!
I am fine but I have some money problems
Thank you for the help you’ re giving me!
Love, Sharon.
This kid will get you more
social security checks.
You’ ll have more money,
just like with the others.
C’ mon! Quite a big number, yeah?
You always complain about money!
Have you finished?
I’ m begging you!
Take him to the hospital,
you can leave him there!
You should burn in hell!
Dear God, tell wind to blow a bit of air!
My little brother needs it and mum
says that you can make things better.
I’ ll teach my brother to be nice to you and
I’ ll never use the pencil against you.
Never ever and forever. Amen.
He’ s eating, you see?
Now he has to take some breaks
so he wouldn’ t suffocate.
Everything will be ok, sweety.
I’ ll write his name so I can
attach it next to the others.
Mum, maybe you should write it.
No, sweety, you can do it! C’ mon, try it!
P – A...
S...
Honey, are we sure that we want to call your brother
like that lizard or chameleon, whatever it is?
C–A...
and L.
Is it right?
That’ s perfect. Good girl!
When will dad come back?
Now that I remember, it passed ten days
since you were born and he didn’ t know it.
I’ ve always been in this tower, right?
Honey, this is not a tower, it’ s a basement.
Anyway, yes. You were all born here.
Did you see what I’ ve done? It’ s Pascal.
Nice...
I wonder how is their basement.
Did they have one?
Mummy...
I wanna play with my brothers.
Yes, I know, sweety. Mum’s very tired. Why don’ t you
go and check out whats’ s in the box he brought.
Hi!
What are you?
Hello!
C’ mon! Talk to me!
I don’ t understand.
What are you trying to tell me?
Do you understand me? Do you
understand what I’ m saying?
Mum! Mum! I have a friend.
Mum!
He lives in the box.
What’ s this?
Oh, no!
No!
He’ s dead!
Hey! My new tenant complained about hearing
noises from down here. I bet it was you!
Was it you?
Have you seen what you’ ve done?
You killed him!
What?
Where do you take him?
Bring my baby back to me!
Shut up! Another word of either of you, another sound and I
will kill the kids upstairs. They’ ll all look like this.
It’s broken!
Oh, sweety! Calm down!
OK, I got it! It’ s right
for you to be angry.
Please, Sarah! The only thing that keeps me going
on is the hope that one day we will al be together.
I know we’ ll make it. I don’ t know how,
I don’ t know when, but we’ ll make it!
I’ m angry, too, you know?
Listen! Why don’ t you introduce me to your
new friend? That’ s goldfish, you know?
C’ mon! Take off that fake belly.
Kids don’ t born to pillows.
Yes, they do.
I did nothing but protect you. You
were 16, you were so rebellious.
All you wanted to do was run around with
boys and get yourself into trouble.
I thought it was safer to protect you.
Oh, yeah? This is why you planned to design
this place ten years before I got here?
Shut up! I’ m your father, I
know what’s best for you.
I’ m a respectable man, I would have
had the whole town laughing at me.
I’ m a good man.
I brought you some food.
Non volevo che finisse in questo modo ...
End what?
I didn’ t want to burn the baby.
You did what?
I put the little baby on the fire.
You, bastard.
You killed him, you murdered my baby...
I hate you... I hate you with all my heart.
You don’ t have the guts!
I have the code to that
door up here in my brain
But you wouldn’ t understand that, would you?
Because you don’ t have a brain!
You were about to kill your only hope.
Thank you!
I have a fever. I think I got an infection.
Did he bring the medicines?
Wake me up if he comes!
I think somebody’ s spying on me.
Come up and say hello!
What an ungracious girl I raised!
Look at this! These are your brothers.
They’ re crazy about me.
Oh, yeah! We laugh and we have fun... And we go to
the park and at the cinema, and we go in the woods.
I’ d like to be friends with you, too.
Would you like that?
What’s the matter? Cat got your tongue?
Did you see what your mother did?
She threatened me with a knife. Yeah! I was just bringing
some food and some apples for you and she wanted to kill me.
Did you see that?
Answer me!
Spiteful! Just like your mother.
So he passed by. What did he say?
Stop mouthing like a fish! What did he say?
Why didn’ t you wake me up as I told you?
Damn it!
How the hell am I supposed to take this?
He left us without water again!
Talks about friendship!
OK, I’ ll chew it.
He doesn’ t talk anymore.
I swear, sweety, I didn’ t mean to.
You killed fish.
No, you don’ t have to say that!
My only friend.
Come here! I told you I didn’ t mean to.
I am depressed, I’ m on the edge.
There’ s no difference between us and
this little fish, do you understand?
He lives in a bowl and
we are locked in a cage.
Non riesco a ricordare come
ci si sente a stare fuori.
I was free, I was awake, I was alive.
Look at you! It’ s like you were never born, you
are dead. We are dead! Just like this fish.
Oh, my God! What did I tell you?
Honey, did you understand
what I’ ve just said?
OK! Let’ s clean this mess up!
You and I have to come up with something...
If we get out of here, you’ ll have all the
friends you want, but not your father.
I have a feeling, he’ s up to no good!
We have to avoid that before it happens.
I have to think about it.
Now, go draw the line for today!
P - L - E– H
Bravo! That’s my girl. Give me five!
Surprise!
Merry Christmas!
Yeah, it’ s Christmas.
Go on, give your father a kiss!
Oh, I got...
I got something for you.
I knew you’ d like it... I have good tastes.
Well, we’ re freezing down here. You should
bring us some blankets, we really need it.
Always needs... Why you wanna... Why you
wanna ruin my Christmas with your needs?
C’ mon! I’ m happy today.
Oh, these braids look pretty on you! Huh,
I told you they’ d look good on you...
C’ mon!
Please, it’ s too cold.
I’ ll warm you up. Get on your knees! C’ mon!
Get off! What’ s wrong with you?
Did you forget how to do it?
I’ m coming back for lunch, set the table!
Hey, Sarah! Wake up!
Remember our “help note”?
Today is our chance!
C’ mon, Sarah!
There’ s also something you would really like.
00:58:35 – 00:58:36 Today is Christmas!
Today is Christmas!
He’s finally wearing a jacket. When we’ ll sit down to eat,
he will put it on the backrest, I’ m sure. You gotta help me!
Did you bring the tree
from the cartoon, mummy?
Yes, sweety!
Listen! You stay here, I
got some things to do.
He’ ll see the flooded bathroom and
will have to check the piping system.
Here’ s the note! Remember
what you have to do?
You have to put it in his jacket, ok?
No, you do it!
I’ ve already done it, it didn’ t work!
Since then, he always gets his eyes on me.
He will not expect this from you...
I’ m scared.
Oh, amore... Nel caso peggiore, penserà che sono lettere
casuali che hai scritto per imparare l'alfabeto.
He will not understand that
this is a secret code.
We have to try. Otherwise,
we’ll never leave this place.
Then we’ ll live in a cartoon as Rapunzel?
In fairytales cartoons, right!
Oh my gosh! Let’ s get out of here!
I turned on the heat.
You’ re welcome!
Father...
No!
It’ s Christmas, I want her to do it! I
wanna see if she’ s got any gratitude.
You know that she’ s not able...
Shut up!
I’ m waiting.
Father...
Father, thank you for this food, for all
the love and affection you give us!
Be loved here and everywhere...
Be here and everywhere loved by all as we... Your
daughters feel loved by you. Thank you, father!
Cheers!
Let’ s eat!
Oh, I love chicken!
With its tiny brain ...
its stupidity it’ s legendary.
Just gaze into the eyes of a chicken and you’ ll
see its incredible stupidity staring back at you.
Yeah! It’ s the one animal in the world
that deserves to get its throat cut.
And your mother is the queen of the chickens.
Does she ever ask about me?
Where I am, things I do...
Oh, yeah! She loves to talk about you because
of all the children you sent her to care for.
She curses you every day.
Oh, my God! What happened?
Jesus Christ! Get a bucket! Go!
Did you loosen that bolt?
All this cold with the water...
It doesn’ t make sense.
Was it you? Speak up! Did
you loosen that bolt?
She doesn’ t even know what it means.
You made it!
Oh, God, make this time work!
Who knows what is he up to now.
Mom, who sings in this box?
People.
People fit?
Honey, I’ll explain it to you later.
Maybe you should go to your room now.
May I watch Rapunzel?
Yeah, watch Rapunzel!
Music? You never listen to the music.
What is this all about?
It’s a party. Your daughter’
s gonna dance for me.
She can’t . I’ll do it!
All right. Call the little brad in here!
Come here and have a dance for
your father, little girl!
Please! She is unwell She has a stomachache.
Stop that!
You wanna defy me? Uh? You wanna defy me?
Get rotten there, bitch!
Please, open!
Open the door!
You don’ t have to hide.
You’ re already hidden by me.
Listen to her! Your mother is such a killjoy.
Open the door!
You know what?...
Please...
I brought you some food and music
and a nice Christmas tree...
because I wanted you to have some fun.
I’ m sorry!
You and your mum, you ruined my party.
1:10:33 – 1:10:35 You made me angry.
Let me get out of here!
Fammi uscire da qui!
But you know what?
You and me can still have a good time.
Open the door!
Please!
Open this door!
Let me get out of here!
You see? There’ s nothing to worry about!
You’ re just making your father happy...
You bastard! Did you touch her?
Honey, did he do something to you?
I need an answer right now!
I swear to God, if you dare to touch her, you’ll see a
different side of me, the one that you have never seen!
Mum, I don’ t want to write.
What good is writing?
Well, if you know how to write, you’ll be able to
read, too. Reading books is very important, sweety.
Outside they will judge your
intelligence with that.
But we only have one book.
It doesn’t matter. You have to be
ready for when we get out of here.
You know, I have this feeling... He hasn’ t found our coded help
note. He was just angry with me because I flooded the bathroom.
Somebody will come and save us, you’ll see!
We’ re so close, sweety!
At school, I was taught writing
using drawings of animals.
If I need an “E”, I use an elephant and then, for
an “L”, I use a lion, for an “H”, I use a horse.
Go on! Write it!
No! I don’ t want to write anything.
Take this pencil and write!
Sarah, I said “write”!
OK. Honey, would you do
this for mummy, please?
That’ s my baby!...
Where are you going, missy?
The bastard! He touched her.
I remember something, it
seems like it was yesterday.
One morning, I started acting out because I didn’t want to go to school and my mum
said that it was OK if I provided to finish my homework while she went shopping.
That’ s the way it started.
Over ten years of abuse.
It was my father...
Your father.
I didn’t know if it was right or wrong, I
only know that I was terrified to death.
I was ashamed and I was
afraid to tell anybody
In all this... I hated my mum!
I hated her for all the times she left me home
in that bad wolf’ s den to live my nightmare.
I hated her for all the times she looked at my strange
drawings saying “Oh, they are beautiful!” ...
for that time when I wrote
in my notebook “I wanna die”
“We don’ t say things like this”, she said.
Stupid mum! Stupid!
I don’ t want things like these
to happen to you, sweety.
Mum’ s here to protect you.
You’ re not alone.
You bitch!
Mum!
Hey, baby! What did he do to you?
This is all my fault.
Hello, ladies!
You know, when I was a little boy, my mother used to leave me at home,
all alone for weeks, sometimes months, without anything to eat...
and I didn’ t have a father to take care of
me, not like I take care of you. With love...
But the more kindness and affection I show you, the
more you take advantage of me and that hurts me!
But... I’ m gonna give you another chance!
I’ m gonna leave the key to the padlock here and if
either one of you dares to touch it, you’ll burn in hell!
Why are you doing all this?
Why?
This is why!
“HELP” spelled backwards?
What do you take me for? An idiot?
Have you ever wondered of why I
chose you, out of all your sisters?
Because you never obey me!... You always do what you
want. Your stubbornness is why all this is happening.
And you’ re teaching her to be just like you.
Well, this is gonna be a test for her.
Leave her alone! I’ m here all for you.
I’m for you... All yours.
You got nothing I want, you’ re worn out.
You’ re old.
Even out there, no one would even look
twice at you unless it was to pity you!
Your own children don’ t even
know you exist, you’ re nothing!
Before I forget, this is for you, little one!
You make sure she knows how to do it!
No, Sarah! Don’ t do it!
Put the key back where you found it!
Be a good girl, Sarah!
You will never see your brothers again.
Take off that lipstick!
Mum’s thirsty. Can you bring
me some water, please?
Did you draw the line for today?
Go draw the line!
Mum, wake up! Please!
Please, open your eyes! Mum, answer to me!
Mum, why don’ t you open your eyes?
Mum, don’ t leave me alone!
Do you want some salt and
pepper on these stakes, sweety?
Oh, yes. I’ ll get it.
This is delicious, isn’t it?
Want some fresh juice, too?
This is not a juice!
Yes, it is.
No, it’ s not!
OK, I’ll drink it all.
OK, I want the fresh juice, too.
Now you’ve changed your mind, isn’t it?
Got you!
So I give you a chance to improve
yourself and you unlock the chain?
Now you’ ll learn your lesson, young lady!
I was only gone for a week...
Can’ t I enjoy a little holiday in
Thailand without all this shit?
It was a simple test! All
you had to do was pass it.
What the hell is this?
I will not be disobeyed!
You know, without me you’ d be dead.
Oh, you’ re not talking.
Well, that’ s a change!
You know what? You need me, I don’t need you!
He left!
Hey, sweety! Can you hear me?
You did well not to answer. You never know
what’ s best with him when he’ s around.
Yes. Now what?
We’ll wait... Mum has been waiting for a
lifetime, you have to learn to do the same.
Maybe it’s better for us to sleep.
Time goes by faster.
Please!
I’ m begging you, please!
You cannot stay here! Run! Run away!
I’m not the only one here...
Mum, I’m cold!
Yes, I know, sweety...
Let’s start running around the room, OK?
Do you remember how to do it?
Are you doing it?
Yes.
Now, let’s do some exercises, OK? One and two and
three and four. One and two and three and four.
Are you doing it?
Does it feel better, sweety?
Does it?
OK. Let’s do it one more time!
God, where am I?
Now we’ll do some genuflection.
Do you remember how to do it?
With the knees?
That’ s right!
Oh, I’ m still freezing!
One and two and three and ...
Hello!
Hello! Is anybody there?
Yes, we’ re here! Open!
Who are you?
I’ m Sharon. In the other bedroom
there’ s Sarah. She’ s my daughter.
Do you know that man?
He’ s our father.
How long have you been here?
More than eight thousand days...
Oh, God! So many years!
It’ s 24 years. Listen! Go find the
keys and open the door. Please!
I don’ t know what to do,
maybe he’ll get angry.
Well, you need more courage to live in here than to kill
yourself. We have to get out of here! Come on, open!
Wait! I have my cell phone.
A cell phone in here!...
Emergencies.
Hello! My name is Cristina Rosenberg and I’ve been kidnapped
by this man and now I’ m in his house, at least I think so...
No, his daughter is here, too. I mean his
daughter and his niece... I didn’t understand.
Yes, they’ve been kidnapped , too.
Wait a minute! Hey, hey! What’s the address?
It’ s Franklyn Street number 2.
I beg you, come as soon as possible!
He hit me several times.
The line went dead.
Fuck! It’s not working anymore.
Oh, c’mon! Answer!
What the hell? Don’t stop trying!
Maybe I should just wait until they
call me back. They’ll find us, right?
Yeah, today is our lucky day! I’m sure
this time we’ll manage to get out of here.
I’ll put the silent mode on and I’ll hide
it in my purse in case he’ s coming.
How will you know if they’ re calling?
I’ll check from time to time...
Right! This way they will find us for sure...
How did you meet him?
He’s a regular at the bar I work at.
Last night my car broke down
and he offered me a ride.
I trusted him...
He’s well known in town...
I mean, he’s a gentleman!
Talks to everyone...
Are you his daughter? The one that escaped
with the religious cult?
He made me write a letter,
everybody bought it!
Once at the bar he was telling us about how much he missed you
and he burst into tears, we were all trying to comfort him...
Wait a second! What about me?
Does that mean I will not get out of here?
Tears are useful in here.
You’ d better keep an eye on your phone!
Could you check and see if he brought
something to eat? We’re starving in here.
Sweety, are you still with us?
I’m drawing Rapunzel.
I prepared everything. Do you promise that if I open
the door you won’t run away? I’m really afraid of him.
OK, don’t worry! I will not do it.
Give it also to Sarah, please!
For all these years nothing good ever happened to me. You’re a kind of a
miracle. They will find us, I’m sure about this! You need to stay strong.
How can I be strong when
he’s stronger than us?
No, not at all, he’s not stronger than us.
We need to trick him!
Since you are here, we have better chances to do
so. We’ll find a solution, I’m sure about that!
All my children are waiting for me
upstairs, I need to get out of here!
I just want to go back home.
My parents are waiting for me.
Well, tears won’t help!
Maybe it’ s like what happened in the mountains last year
when those people were missing. They never found them.
Police will arrive, your family
will start looking for you!
Fuck! It’s him, he’ s here!
Dress up!
Oh! Have you eaten?
Yes.
You haven’t lost your appetite,
that means you’ re settling in.
Now, there’s some rules you have to follow.
Do not talk to the others
or give them food or water.
When I arrive, everything’ s clean and
that table is set: for lunch or dinner.
I want you to look nice
for me when I come here.
You’re gonna be a role model for the others. If you
follow the rules, you and me are gonna be just fine.
Hey, you have to pretend that you like it here, that you’re
getting used to it. I’ve never try that, maybe it works.
But I can’t. That’s disgusting!
Listen to me! Do you want to
see your family again or not?
I’m sure my mum is worrying about me.
Don’ t get things impossible!
You have to earn his trust.
Maybe he will take you out with him once in a while. This
way you will save yourself, you will save all of us!
There’s no call.
Go get ready, be nice to him... Don’ t cry, he doesn’t
like to see you crying. He could arrive at any moment, OK?
God knows what will happen to me.
There you go! This is
what I was talking about.
I’m home!
Are you ready for me?
Did you primp for me?
What a smart girl! C’mon!
My time is precious.
You’ re good at that! Tell
me you can cook, too.
Yes.
Well, I found myself a very nice young woman and
she found herself the best man in the world.
Unfortunately not everybody
here appreciates me.
You know what? I’m gonna go get us some food and
then we’ re gonna have a nice dinner together. OK?
Of course.
Didn’t you have a purse when you came here?
You did, I remember.
Yes, sure...
Here it is!
You called the police?
Well, you can’t trust anybody!
You shouldn’t have fucked
with me, little girl!
This is your fault! If the police come by,
I’m gonna put you in a bag! You bitch!
Honey, are you OK?
Shall I draw the line, mummy?
Yeah, draw the line!
I have to pee.
There’s not much choice, do it in a corner!
Sooner or later he will
decide to open the doors.
Better sleep and not to think about it.
Hey, what are you?
Are you hungry?
Honey, are you ok?
It hurts, mummy!
What does it hurt, sweety?
Everywhere.
Can you tell me what happened?
I don’t know. Somebody hurt me.
There’s nobody inside here, sweety!
Try to stay calm, OK?
Don’t be scared! Mum will come and get you!
Listen, sweety, it’s your favorite!
Sarah!
Damn it, Sarah! Can you hear me?
Oh, my God! She doesn’t answer.
OK, calm down! Maybe she just felt asleep...
Sarah, can you hear mummy?
Can you hear me?
Oh, baby, you’ re here!
This is a rat.
He’s been here.
I wanted to play with him.
Sarah ...
Honey, can you hear me?
Answer to mummy, please!
- Open the door!
- Jesus!
Damn it! What in...
I swear to God, this time I’ll end it! My
baby’s sick. If you don’t help us, I’ll do it!
She’s not breathing!
She is.
Wake up, girl!
She doesn’t answer. Do something!
Like what?
Take her... and leave her... at the hospital!
Don’t be stupid! I’ll get some medicines.
If she dies, I’ll have no
reason to live anymore.
Be strong, sweety!
No notes!
Please, at least she’ll remember our games.
I’ll never see her again.
Show me!
- It’s childish drawings, it’s nothing.
- Fine!
You... You stay right here!
Hey, Buck! C’mon!
I expect you inside, let’s go!
Oh, no! I had to bring my
wife at the hospital...
John, no...
OK, five minutes!
You’ re going but you can’t hide! OK?
Get me the police right away!
Of course, doctor Holly!
Unbelievable!
I’ ve never seen anything like this before.
Hey, little lady!
You can make a sign if
you hear me, anything...
Detective! She’s in a very bad state of malnutrition. She was bitten by a rat, she
has a serious infection which is not good because of her metabolic unbalance.
Sooner or later she would have come to this.
We’ve searched all the medical records, she has never been here before but somebody,
maybe has the same genetic data and it’s something that we can look into.
No, we didn’t find anything. No match!
The only thing we found was this! She had it in her
pocket. Maybe it’ll be useful in your investigation.
Kids drawings.
I know somebody who can interpret this so I’ll get it to
him. Meanwhile, I’m gonna be here, she might wake up.
OK. Detective, even though it’s a dangerous
situation, we must remain hopeful.
Thank you!
Before I forget... She was sexually abused, not
recently so we don’ t have important proof.
Hi, doc! I got these kid’ s pictures
I need you to interpret so ...
Yes. So, I’m gonna take a photo, I’m gonna send
it to you and you get back to me right away.
Right!
Look at you!
You’ re not going anywhere, you’ re
safe here! I’ m not gonna let you down.
And the bastard that did this to you,
he’s gonna get what he deserves.
Tell me something good!
So you looked to the drawings and...
Thanks! OK. Yeah, bye!
Any news, detective?
They say probably an adult did the drawings and not her. It’s
like when this big black cloud right now and my instinct says...
Somebody come, please! She woke up!
OK, girlie! What’s your name?
Mum!
What’s your mummy’s name? Look!
Stay strong, sweetheart!
What’s this mean here?
“H” like horse, “E” like elephant...
"H" ...
"E"
One, two, three, four, five...
“HELP”
Ten, eleven ...
“TWO FRANKLYN STREET”
Twelve, thirteen, fourteen...
It’ s a code! It’ a code!
We’ve lost her!
Get a squad car to Two, Franklyn Street! Now!
JOSEPH FRITZL RECEIVED A LIFE SENTENCE AND HE IS
STAYING IN THE PSYCHIATRIC BLOCK OF THE PRISON.
HE GROWS VEGETABLES IN HIS CELL AND CONTACTS
JOURNALISTS TRYING TO SELL HIS STORY.