(MultiCom Jingle)
(dramatic music)
(siren blaring)
(clock ticking)
(car horn blaring)
(explosion)
(yelling)
(alarm sounding)
(door banging)
(explosions)
(alarm ringing)
(door knocking)
- Yes.
- Hi, Daddy.
I just wanted to let
you know that everyone
is arriving downstairs.
- Oh, good.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Joseph here?
- [Diane] Daddy, is everything all right?
- Mm-hmm.
(soft music)
- Oh, Daddy, that's terrible.
How many died?
- 19, it's barbaric.
Virtual slavery, in this day
and age and in this country.
And it disturbs me, deeply.
- Sorry, everyone, sorry.
I was getting something from the car.
You will see why, hello, Mom.
So what do you think?
- Nobody's gonna eat my dinner
with a desert like that.
- Are you kidding, miss your dinner?
- All right.
I think it's time we sat down and
enjoyed your mother's wonderful dinner.
Joseph, Robert?
- Sure, Father.
Oh heavenly Father, we all
thank you for this bounty
that you've given us here tonight.
We thank you for showing us
what is good and what is right.
Keep this family together
in love, forever.
- [Group] Amen.
(laughing)
(singing)
- Justin, I spoke to Allen today.
He says the quicker you pass
the bar, the better for him.
He wants to retire.
(applause and cheering)
I think this is the time to make
another announcement of another first-rate
addition to the ranks.
It's time that Joe here becomes familiar
with the workings of our business.
- Excuse me, Father, can I speak?
I mean, Joseph's young.
He's just graduated.
- Right, none of the
rest of us started out
in the family business
just like (snaps fingers).
- Joseph has excelled in his studies.
He's demonstrated his readiness.
He begins by helping Ashton and
you, Robert, with the bookkeeping.
- Yeah but, Father, wait a second.
Ashton's doing great in
accounting, you said so yourself.
- Excuse me.
I'm sorry, Mother.
(murmuring)
- What's this about?
- I'm sorry, but that
position was promised to Ash
and only Ash.
He's worked very hard, and
he's done an excellent job.
- He still has his job, his position.
- Well obviously not.
As soon as Joe learns the
ropes, isn't that just the way
it is around here, Father,
especially when it comes to Joe?
- Sit down, I've made my decision.
Ashton's position is secure.
Joseph is only gonna be an apprentice.
(throat clearing)
- Father, may I, you know.
Maybe I can help Simon on the docks
or do something else, or?
- I know, but working
with Ashton in bookkeeping
is where I want you to start.
Robert will supervise, is that clear?
- Excuse me, Dad, may I be excused?
I would like to go talk
to, to Ash, please.
- All right.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Simon, you have something to say?
- Yeah, I say it's unfair.
This is a joke, right?
- Well, everything's a joke to you.
- What I mean
is that Joe is just handed everything,
opportunities none of the rest of us had,
like this so-called apprenticeship?
- What have you done with
your opportunities, Simon?
- Oh, Jacob, not now.
- Thrown them away.
Got yourself a police record.
In the process, dragged
Lee here into the mess
just for good measure.
Is that what you mean by unfair?
- I was a kid.
- When are you gonna grow up?
- Jacob.
- All right, all right.
I'm sorry, I apologize.
The past can't be undone,
but it can be learned from.
I'd like to show you
something, all of you.
Take at a look at this,
if you wanna know what
unfair can really mean.
(horn blowing)
(upbeat rock music)
- Good morning.
Say, you're early.
- Yeah, I was trying to impress the boss.
And this coffee, ugh.
I thought we ran a successful company.
- Ooh, oh, you're fired.
Just kidding.
Uh, you've been here.
My office there, keep your
grubby fingers off my desk.
Come on, I'll give you
the new employees tour.
You'll find Grant in these
departments, most of the time.
(singing)
Oh here it is, your desk.
Get to work, now.
Got you again.
We just moved Simon into
that office over there.
It's closer to his department.
Sometimes, you're gonna find Lee there.
But well, you know.
Hey, guys, come on, what is this?
Look, huh?
- Hi, Ash.
(dramatic noises)
(explosion)
- Hey, hey hey hey, are you all right?
- Come on, let's get him inside.
- Maybe you should go home.
- No, I'm fine, really I'm fine, you guys.
- Ash, Ash please, would
you mind repeating that?
- Our dear little egg white half-brother
said he felt this wave
of power wash over him,
just like in his dreams.
- Oh.
- I'm flying, I'm flying.
Really, I'm flying.
- That's good, the little twit.
- I think he's all right.
He's in his room.
- Oh.
Have I not been listening?
- I know you love your children.
But sometimes, you see Joseph
and hear Joseph a little more
than you hear the others.
- How can I not, I mean, see
him at least differently?
And Joseph is our child.
He's the only child of our marriage.
- They're all our children.
And blood related or
not, I'm their mother.
Joseph is our gift.
- Oh.
I love them all.
I do, I love them all.
- I know that.
Do you think of her?
- [Jacob] Sometimes.
- She gave you six wonderful sons.
And she gave you a lovely daughter.
If you had another child,
what would you want?
Another son or another daughter?
(laughing)
- I think we're getting a little too old
for that sorta nonsense.
- We're not.
- We're not?
(chattering)
- Well, it's taken us a couple of months,
but I think our coffee problem
is finally solved, you guys.
- You're sure these figures are right?
- Ash, listen to me.
Father expected us to need
money for the next season.
- Yeah, well, I had
intended to show Father
that I could increase our profits.
- You know, he's right, Ash.
It's not your fault.
- Ash, look, remember Simon's suggestion?
He and Justin, they're
working it out right now.
Right now, as we speak.
That's gonna help us out a lot.
- Is this something that you
guys have gone over with Dad?
(horn honking)
- Joe, Joe.
When Father established this
business, labor was cheap.
Now, with the laws and the unions,
our competitors are just
blowing us out of the water.
What are we gonna do?
- Father just doesn't
understand today's market.
The competition, you know,
it's just tougher out there.
- So, what is that you guys plan to do?
- Okay, see, it's the cost
of labor that's killing us.
So that's the one area that
we can probably cut back on.
- You can't cut pay and
benefits, you can't do that.
- Not exactly.
It would be having to let some people go.
You're just contracting
it out to somebody else.
- Wait a minute.
Are you talking about using sweatshops?
- Look, I've arranged it with Justin.
He can arrange the whole thing
so we won't be legally connected.
- That's not the point, and you know it.
Ash, you can't agree to this.
- Grant says these places,
they're not as bad as reported.
- Of course they are.
Why do you think they stay underground?
Because they're such nice places to work?
Dad will never agree to
this, and you know it.
- Joe, he can't stop
what he don't know about.
Besides, these shops are right
here in the United States.
They're not in some third-world slum.
Right here.
- That doesn't change anything.
- I'm not gonna risk losing
this company that it took
Dad a lifetime to build, what about you?
- This is the future
of our family business.
- Yeah.
- But the costs.
- Joe, sometimes things do cost.
But in this world, you gotta
protect your own first.
- So it's,
it's us or them?
- I'm not gonna argue ethics
and morals with you, Joe.
This is my decision,
and there's no reason
to involve Dad in it.
- Oh no, you will not do this thing.
- It was just an idea, Dad.
Joseph had no right.
- He had every right, every right,
and he was man enough
to do the right thing.
- We were thinking of
the business, of you.
- Thinking about me?
I worked in a sweatshop when I was a kid.
Three years of my life, I slaved.
For scum who had the gall to tell me
that they were doing me
a favor, letting me work
in their stinking shop
for 15, 16 hours a day.
You dare tell me that I raised sons
who would do what those
dregs of humanity did to me?
- I'm sorry, Father.
- I want everybody at the house tonight.
Six o'clock, no exceptions.
(birds chirping)
- I planned to present
this with a little bit
more pomp and circumstance
on Sunday dinner, but.
Try it on.
I made it, with these old hands,
so I'm not so sure I
haven't lost my touch.
- I don't think so.
Not hardly, I would say.
- [Jacob] Not bad, not bad.
I mean, I haven't touched
a needle and thread
for 15 years, but not
bad if I say so myself.
- Not bad at all.
Thank you very much.
But why this?
What did I do to deserve this, why now?
- I'm proud of you, Joseph.
My hopes are with you.
Well, let's just say that
this marks the beginning
of what I expect will be a,
a very successful career and life.
- How you holding up?
- Okay, for now, ask me again in an hour.
- Is everyone here?
- Yeah, I think so.
- I haven't seen Joe.
- I hate this.
How could he do this?
How could he just stab
us in the back like that?
- Well why not?
This is Daddy's good little boy.
A shining example to us all.
Joe isn't one of us.
But as long as he's around
doing Daddy's little spying,
we're all gonna be under the microscope.
- So what are we gonna do about it?
- Nothing.
Not yet.
- Joseph was right in coming to me.
And I think, Robert, if you're honest
with yourself, you'll agree.
- Yes.
- And you realize that
there are consequences
for your actions?
- Yes, sir.
- I will not be signing
the business over to you
next fall as planned.
I will be releasing it to you,
conditionally, in five years.
- Five years, oh, Father.
- I need to know that you can
run the business, profitably,
without resorting to intolerable
solutions to problems.
If you want to work with us,
you'll be going to New York
next week as planned to secure a loan.
And taking Ashton and
Simon and Joseph with you.
- Robert, I know you're angry with me,
but just hear me out, okay?
I've been studying the
market with my eye towards
getting us very very
favorable terms on a loan.
I'll give you my advice.
You don't have to take it, but I'm betting
I can get you the best
terms you've ever seen.
- All right.
But, the final decision
on the loan, that's mine.
- Yes, yes.
All right.
- Justin.
- Simon, I thought you'd left.
- No, I just wanted to talk to Ash
about what happened downstairs.
Robert got the worst of it.
- Ash didn't fare much better.
I was gonna go talk to him.
- He'll be okay.
- We all got a chewing out.
Our little half-brother
should feel very proud.
There's nothing we can do.
- Yeah, I'm not so sure about that.
(upbeat music)
- Oh, Tattinger, way to go, Robert.
- Here's to a job well done.
Loan terms that brought
tears to a banker's eyes.
- [Ashton] So what's
the plan for tomorrow?
- How about some sightseeing?
Huh?
We got two days to kill.
- Yeah, sure.
- Man, what a day.
I've about had it.
- I'll tuck you in, come on.
- Yeah, yeah, good night, Robert.
- Good night, you guys.
(upbeat music)
Okay.
All right, well, I guess
I'll see you tomorrow, right?
- Yeah, good night, Joe.
(upbeat music)
- I tried, Lord.
I really did.
But,
they're still so angry with me.
I don't know what else to do.
- Can I come in?
- Yeah, yeah.
What time is it?
- It's about 8:30.
- Oh yeah?
- Look, Joseph,
I know things have been bad recently.
I think, well, can I say we all think,
maybe it's about time
we buried the hatchet.
What about it, how do you feel?
- I don't know what to say.
- Well, why don't you get yourself ready
and join Ash and me?
We're going out on a little
excursion this morning
while we're waiting for Robert.
- Oh yeah?
Where to?
- It's a manufacturing plant.
Actually, it oughta be pretty interesting.
Seeing how one of these
local operations is run.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ooh.
Give me about 15 minutes.
- Good.
See you in the lobby, champ.
(mysterious music)
- Kellers.
We're expected.
(mysterious music)
- Not the best part of town, is it?
- Serves the purpose.
Joseph.
- Good morning, gentlemen.
Frisk him.
- They don't take any chances, do they?
- Can't afford to.
- Right there.
- Trade secrets.
- [Thompsonn] Mister
Childress, they are all here.
- Good, let's get this over with.
- This is Ashton.
That's Joseph.
- Gentlemen.
(grunting)
- Just get the coat off him,
and then we're finished here.
- I think I was clear on what will happen
if this is not the agreed upon amount.
- What are you doing?
- No.
No, buddy.
- It's too late for all that.
Now listen to me.
Listen to me, listen.
Are you listening?
- Yeah.
- From this point on,
he's as good as dead.
Do you understand, that's it.
Let me deal with this, okay?
- Okay.
- I need the coat.
- Take it.
- All right, he's all yours.
As far as we're concerned,
he never existed.
That's what we paid you for.
- Agreed, now get outta here.
- Let's go.
- Show him the coat.
- Look, we really messed it up,
made it look like he was
in a fight or something.
- We're gonna show the coat to Dad,
tell them that we found it, in an alley.
Let him draw his own conclusions.
- You idiots, what are we doing with this?
How come the police don't got it?
- What?
They look for it, but they're
not gonna find anything.
There's no blood, nothing.
So they return it to the grieving family.
- The grieving family?
- Yeah.
- You don't feel anything, do you?
- Feel?
I feel we did what was
right for the family.
- Welcome to the presidential suite.
- Bye, Father, I'm sorry.
- Well?
- What he say?
- The boys can't handle this.
I mean, they're not even making any sense.
They're all over the place.
- He said that he loves us,
and that he trusts that
we're doing everything
that we can to find Joe.
- That's perfect.
- Jacob, please, sit down.
- I gotta go there, talk to the police.
- If we leave tonight, we
could be in New York tomorrow.
- I can look for Joseph myself.
- Joseph is my son too.
(crying)
- Mother?
- Rachel, are you all right?
- It's not the baby.
- I'm sorry, I'll be all right.
- Shall I call the doctor?
- No, don't.
- [Diane] Are you sure you're all right?
- Yes, darling, fine.
- I'll stay.
- No, don't stay.
Jacob, listen, you go.
I'm worried.
I'm frightened, I don't know why.
Not just about Joseph, about all the boys.
- Room service please.
(upbeat music)
(yelling)
Noooo!
- [Thompsonn] Easy.
- [Joseph] Let me go, let me go.
- Easy.
- Your friends went to much trouble
and expense to put you here,
and here you will stay.
Now you have a choice.
Stay put, do what you're told
and keep your mouth shut,
and you'll survive.
Otherwise, in here you're nobody.
Out there, you're as good as dead.
I can and will do whatever is necessary
to maintain the status quo, understood?
- You can't just make me disappear.
- I already did, happens all the time.
- These friends of mine, they
didn't tell you, did they?
- Tell me what?
- They're my brothers.
Puts you in a rather uncomfortable
position, doesn't it?
- No.
Get him outta here.
- You said that no deceased person fitting
his description has come in
in the last couple of days,
and that you've checked hospitals.
Because you see, he sometimes has,
I don't know, I mean,
something like a lapse.
- Maybe we should just go
out and start looking again.
We did come up with his coat.
- Maybe he was epileptic, you
know, maybe it was epilepsy.
You asked me that 10 times,
I already told you that.
Last time I saw him was in the morning.
- I remember what he had for breakfast.
We'd always get together as a family,
have our breakfast together.
- I just turned back, and
I looked, I didn't see him.
I figured, well, he just
stepped into the shop.
So I went back, maybe
I don't know, two or.
- Please, God, where is my son?
(dramatic music)
- Everyone works.
(speaking foreign language)
No one looks up at me.
You don't wanna see my dirty face.
Nobody wants to look at my dirty face.
Everyone look at the machines.
No one wants to see me.
And nobody talks.
(speaking foreign language)
Everyone works, everyone, everyone.
- You okay?
Let me see.
Who did this to you?
Huh, he did?
- Mr. Childress wants to see you.
- This woman needs a doctor.
- She's lucky she can still walk.
- No one deserves that.
Look, look at her face.
- Maybe you want some of the same.
I said Mr. Childress wants to see you.
- I said she needs a doctor.
- Now.
- One of the women has been beaten.
She needs help.
- That's not your concern.
She tried to smuggle a letter out.
I can't allow that.
- So what?
She's hurt, she needs help.
- I suggest you drop the subject,
or do you need Thompsonn's assistance?
All right then.
I've been doing a little checking.
It seems that your family owns
quite a successful little firm.
- Yeah, it's my father's.
So?
- Did you work there?
- I started to.
- How did that go?
- If you're asking me was I
good at my job, yes, I was.
- Well my accountant went skiing
and decided to hug a tree.
He'll be laid up for a while.
In the meantime, I've got books
to balance and bills to pay.
Think you can handle it?
- I've done it before.
- All right.
We'll see.
This is where you'll work.
However, any phone calls
will be made by me.
There'll be no attempt
at outside communication.
Let me be clear on this.
My back's against the wall,
and that's given you a chance.
Abuse it, and you'll live
just long enough to regret it.
- I understand.
- Let me add a last word of caution.
You may understandably care
nothing for your brothers,
but I'm sure you wish no harm
to come to your parents or sister.
- Don't touch them.
- You don't wanna test me on this.
- Don't touch them, okay?
Just don't touch them.
- I'll have no need to,
as long as you cooperate.
("God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen")
- Dad.
- Ashton.
- What are you doing?
- Look, look.
No blood, no blood.
- It's late, Mom'll be worried.
- There's no blood, but every time I dream
it's covered with blood.
- Father, please, you're just,
it was just a dream, that's all.
- How could it be?
How could it be?
Three and a half months,
and no trace, nothing.
Why can't they find my son?
The police, the people I'm paying for,
why can't they find him?
There's no blood, there's no blood.
- You need some rest.
- [Jacob] There's no blood.
- Will you please get some sleep?
- No blood, no blood.
- Be careful with that material.
Bring it to the machine shop,
they're waiting for you.
- Mr. Childress?
- I'm glad to see winter winding down.
The gray and cold depress me.
- Ah, we that have free
souls, it touches us not.
- What?
- Shakespeare, I used to read a bit.
- Let's sit down.
You did a good job on the accounting,
but that's not why you're here.
It seems that made in America
is less important these days.
That market is shrinking,
and my profits are dropping.
- Price versus quality.
That's the bottom line,
not where it's made.
- My accountant had a few suggestions.
I'd like to hear yours.
- Oh, oh, okay.
Well, as a contractor,
you're just a hired hand
at the mercy of the market.
Supply and demand.
If I were you, I'd create my own demand.
- How so?
- Well, do some homework
on some current trends.
Then move towards design
and manufacturing.
You've already got the labor,
maybe even some untapped
talent if you check, you know.
- No, there's no way I can risk
calling attention to my business here.
- Oh, of course, of course.
And that's why, that's why
you set up a legitimate arm
of business out of state.
You know, kind of like a
front or something, you know.
Then you funnel your
products through that.
- And why would David help Goliath?
- A chance.
- Hi.
- [Woman] Hi.
- Remember the designs we talked about?
Did you think of a few.
Remember the designs we talked about?
No, no?
Remember the designs we
talked about earlier?
You think you can maybe write a few down?
No.
- Hi, Emily.
Hi, remember the designs
we talked about earlier?
- Hello, Martha.
How are you?
Well, I came by to drop off a pad.
I know you had a few designs
you wanted to write down for me, right?
Right?
Well, I'll tell you what.
I'll.
Bye, Martha.
(dramatic music)
- Joseph.
Joseph.
(dramatic music)
(yelling)
- Mother, oh.
(church bells ringing)
- He's a beautiful baby, our Benjamin.
I wish you could see him.
(footsteps)
But don't worry, Diane's
taking care of him.
Just the way you took care of her
when she was a little girl.
- Can I get you anything?
I miss Mama so much.
- So do I.
(machines running)
- Thank you, thank you,
these are great, thank you.
Hi, Emily.
- Hi, I've got the designs for you.
Do you like them?
- Ho ho, do I like these?
Mr. Childress is gonna love these.
Thank you very much, Emily, thank you.
Hi, Martha.
Hello, I was just.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Martha, these are, these are fantastic.
Thank you, thank you very much.
Bravo.
Look, everybody, Martha.
Bravo, Martha.
(applause)
(triumphant music)
- Did you have a chance
to look at the sketches?
I may have found these
people down and out,
but, Mr. Childress, there
is definitely talent here.
- Maybe.
You know, my wife liked these.
- Oh, Martha.
You know, she had dreams
of becoming a designer.
She even studied.
- If I establish this
legitimate front then disappear,
how do I know I won't be arrested
five minutes after I close down?
- Well, because the way this is set up,
the authorities will never find you.
- Except through you,
another interesting problem.
- No, no.
I, I give you my word.
If it doesn't work,
you can always go back.
- Well the accountant thinks it'll work.
I mean, if we're cautious.
And my wife, well, she
hates this place as it is.
I'll tell you what.
Bring Martha and Emily to my office
this Friday, and we'll talk.
- Okay.
Okay, thank you very much, Mr. Childress.
(seagull calling)
- And the spirit of God moved
upon the face of the waters.
- And God said.
- And God said, let there be light.
- You already know it
before I even say it.
And,
and there was.
- And there was light.
- Bravo.
- [Childress] I'll have
Dr. Russell take a look
at the workers.
- Dr. Russell?
Frank, I'm sure you could
find someone better.
- Nonsense, Russell's a fine doctor.
Joseph, this is my wife, Clara.
Clara decided it was
finally time to take a look.
- Mrs. Childress, how are you?
Pleasure to meet you.
- Joe, or do you prefer Joseph?
- Joe is fine, it doesn't matter.
- I must say, you're not
at all what I expected.
All these improvements,
they're your ideas?
- Well, let's call it
a cooperative effort.
- With Frank out of town
so much more these days,
I decided to check out the competition.
I'm impressed.
- Clara has chosen some of
our more successful fashions.
She has a great sense of design.
She was a model, you know.
- Well, I wish I could stay longer,
but my afternoon's completely booked, so.
- [Childress] Well then,
let's finish the tour
and I'll show you out.
- I was a pleasure to meet you, Joe.
- [Joseph] Pleasure to
meet you, Mrs. Childress.
- I'm sure I'll see you again.
(classical music)
- Ah, come in, Joseph.
You remember Clara.
- Mrs. Childress.
- She dropped by to talk over
some marketing ideas with me,
but unfortunately, I've
got an appointment.
- I thought I could stay
anyway, talk to you,
if that's all right.
- Of course.
- Good.
Listen to her, Joseph,
she has some great ideas.
She'll surprise you.
Fill me in when I get back this afternoon.
- Yes, sir.
- I have a confession
to make, so they say.
I knew about Frank's appointment.
I wanted to speak to you alone.
- Oh?
- I wanted to thank you for
everything you've done here.
You've accomplished something I couldn't.
- And what is that?
- I hated this place, hated
the way Frank made his money.
When anybody would ask,
what does your husband do,
I would hedge, evade, lie, anything.
- So,
what ideas do you have to help us now?
- Take a seat.
Thanks again, Joe, thanks for listening.
- Any time.
You have some workable ideas.
- I was thinking that next time we talk,
maybe it could be somewhere
else, somewhere nice.
- If you mean away from
here, I doubt Mr. Childress
would okay that.
- Let me work on that,
catch him in the right mood,
a little bit off guard.
- Well, I should be getting back to work.
Good day, Mrs. Childress.
- Goodbye, Joe, thanks again.
- I'm really gonna miss you.
Genuine.
Bye, Frank, I'm really gonna miss you.
Bye, Frank, I'm really
gonna miss you, hurry back.
- I like these, I do.
I like those right there.
- [Martha] You think this is a good one.
- [Joseph] Mrs. Childress, hi.
- [Clara] Hi.
- It's nice to see you.
I didn't hear you were coming.
- Surprise inspection.
- Really?
- Hi, Martha.
- Oh, hello.
- I've been hearing about all
these wonderful new designs.
May I look?
- Of course.
- They're wonderful.
- Thank you.
- Now, I have another surprise.
Can I whisk you away?
- Of course.
- Ta-da.
- Wow.
What's all this for?
- Frank is being so stubborn
about not letting you go out,
so.
Well, we can stand here and stare at it
until Frank gets back, or we can dig in.
What'll it be?
- I vote we dig in.
- Good decision.
- What about Mr. Childress?
Why isn't he here?
- Frank is out of town again.
I'm so glad I have you
to talk to sometimes.
Well, shall I do the honors, or shall you?
- I'll do it.
- And do me a favor, please.
Take off that appalling tie.
I promise I'll buy you a replacement,
one that won't ruin my sense of taste.
- I have, I've got to thank you.
I haven't eaten like that
in a very long, long time.
Your husband missed out on
a very enjoyable afternoon,
I must say.
- I'm not sure he would
have appreciated it
the way you did.
Too bad this place isn't
a little more comfortable.
- But still the company is good.
- I agree.
I'm glad you think so too.
Look, even your place has
got to be a little better.
Let's go there a while, relax, talk.
- Uh, I don't think that'll
be a very good idea.
- Why not, Joe?
Where's the harm?
We're friends, aren't we?
- Of course, but.
- But I'm married.
- [Joseph] Yes.
- To the man who basically owns you.
So what?
I can help you, Joe.
I can help you get out of here.
- Stop, please stop.
Clara, listen to me, just go home.
Go home to Frank.
He loves you, and needs
you very very much.
I know this.
- But I need you.
- No, no.
I can't.
I can't do this, okay, I can't.
(dramatic music)
(door opening and closing)
- Frank, I'm just so shocked.
He just grabbed me.
I didn't know what to do.
No, he won't go for that.
Oh God.
(dramatic music)
So I just thought I'd
be nice and have lunch
and had a glass of wine,
and I think he must have
just thought I was coming
on to him or something,
because, all of a sudden, he
leaned over and kissed me.
(dramatic music)
And then he put his hands on
my breasts, my breasts, Frank.
- You scum.
I trusted you.
Come here.
She's my wife.
You might have gotten
outta here in a few years,
but not where you're going now.
I got a doctor I want you to meet.
Sedate him.
(dramatic music)
- I didn't do anything.
Mrs. Childress, I.
- He's here.
No no, the papers are ready,
all I need is the money.
Schizophrenia, acute onset.
Yeah, we'll keep him
drugged up for a while.
Any claims he makes later
on'll just sound delusional,
paranoid, just what the
doctor ordered, so to speak.
(dial tone)
(screaming)
(drawer opening)
- [Parker] I really hope you're Forrester.
- John Forrester.
- Parker.
- You look desperate.
- A week alone on this ward,
I'm starting to talk to myself.
Pretty soon they'll think
I'm one of the patients.
- If by they you mean
the doctors, I doubt it.
For a psych hospital,
the presence of doctors
is noticeably lacking.
- You catch on fast.
Now let me show you
around our little place,
introduce you to our group.
This is Alice.
Hello, Alice.
- Most of them been here a while?
- Yeah, once they get
here, they seldom leave.
Like Lydia here.
She'll probably die here.
She hasn't said more
than a couple of words
in a couple of years.
No one seems to be able
to get through to her.
And watching television,
we have Mr. Martinez.
- Shh.
This is a good plot.
- [Parker] And he's fine,
until he gets a message.
- [Forrester] From the TV?
- Just restrain him, get
him back to his room.
The nurses will take care of sedation.
- Who's this guy?
- [Parker] That's Carl.
- I ask you very politely
just to keep quiet, okay?
- Sorry.
Carl has spent every
morning since he got here
staring at the chess board.
He's yet to move.
- What if somebody else moved first?
- No, no, wouldn't wanna do
that, apoplexy, you know.
- Oh, got it.
- And here's our newest arrival.
According to his chart,
acute schizophrenia.
- Hey!
Now that's twice.
- He was really out of it for
the first couple of weeks.
Delusions, hallucinations, most of it
was probably the meds he was on.
Here, watch this.
- Whose move?
- Mine.
- He'll sit with him every
morning for a little while.
- Does he know?
- That Carl won't move?
Yeah, yeah, I think he does.
He just doesn't talk
much, paranoid, you know?
- [Forrester] What's his name?
- [Parker] Well he calls himself Joseph,
and the name on the
chart's something else.
I call him Joe, he seems
to be all right with that.
And over here.
(mysterious music)
- I'll be back, Carl.
I'll be back.
(woman screaming)
(crying)
- What am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do, how do I save myself.
How do I save myself?
Are you listening?
(laughing)
Treat me like a fool
Treat me mean and cool
But love me
Break my faithful heart
- Do you think he'll move today, Joe?
You know, I think you're wearing him down.
- Please, shh, shh.
Yeah?
- The paper.
- Joe, it's just the financial section.
- I know, that's why I'm interested.
- Yeah, take it.
I don't need it back, I'm finished.
- Thank you.
Your heart, beating close to mine
So close to mine
(door slamming)
(dramatic music)
- He came to me, he came to me last night.
He came to my room, and
I told him, in my dreams,
I told him everything.
But I've still got the
moves, I've got the moves.
- What's this?
- Night school.
It's killing me.
- Man, I'd help you, but you're set
on passing the class, right?
- Passing, graduating
and getting outta here.
I need some coffee.
- [Carl] Frank?
- [Parker] Yeah.
- You just go ahead, you keep on living
in your world of your dreams.
But you're a prisoner
of all of those dreams.
You don't wanna die, do you wanna die?
I don't wanna die.
- [Joseph] Don't move here, Carl.
- I can move, I can move if I want.
You can't tell me not to move.
Look, see.
Why can't I kill God inside me?
Why does he go on living like this?
It's humiliating, it's
painful, I wanna rip him out.
But still here he is, and he's crazy,
and he is afraid.
(dramatic music)
But I gotta move.
- You almost had it.
- I've got to move.
I got the moves.
Can't touch me now.
- He's got a point there, Joe.
- [Parker] Joe, okay if I come in?
- Yeah, of course, what's going on?
- I brought you a couple more journals.
- Thank you.
- You know that assignment
you helped me with
the other day?
You were dead on with those
market predictions, thanks.
- Oh, just some minor
adjustments, you know.
- I'd have gotten it wrong.
- Is there anything else?
- I've been going to school
for a long time, Joe.
I work hard, I'm a good student.
- But a little extra help wouldn't hurt.
- You see things differently.
I can't learn that in school.
- Sure, I seem to have
a little extra time.
- Morning, Joe.
- So how'd you sleep last night?
- What's sleep?
These tests, I've been
having these dreams,
over and over.
I'm exhausted.
- What's the dream?
- Really?
Okay.
It's like I know I'm
awake, but I'm asleep.
It's pitch black, I can't
see anything out there,
but I know that there's
something in the room with me.
And I'm scared, I panic.
And I know if I get on the
other side of the door,
I'll be safe.
And I'm fighting to find the door.
And I walk through the door
and into this light, and there's somebody
sitting at a desk.
And he looks up, and it's me.
It's me, it's me.
That is kid stuff, right?
- No, no, not kid stuff.
You know dreams, dreams are a,
a kind of a communication.
- Well, whatever this one's communicating,
it's making me jumpy.
- It's the future that
frightens you, the unknown.
Don't let it.
You're not going into it alone.
Study, prepare, kinda like
what you're doing now,
and you'll be ready.
It's not so bad.
So where we starting?
(dramatic music)
You need me to read you something?
Oh.
Yeah, you like this one, don't you?
I like this one too.
Okay.
(clearing throat)
To suffer woes, which hope has taken.
To forgive wrongs, darker
than death or night.
To defy power, which seems omnipotent.
To love and bear.
To hope til hope creates
from its own wreck, the
thing it contemplates.
This is alone, life.
Joy.
(dramatic music)
And victory.
- Wow.
- Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, congratulate me.
- All right, congratulations,
I take it it's good news.
- I not only passed, I
graduated and I got a job.
A really good job.
I'm outta here a week from Friday.
- Didn't I tell you?
- Well I owe a lot to you.
- Nah.
You did all the necessary
work, that's what's important.
Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Oh, and Forrester wants to talk to you.
Seems he's been having his own
little weird dreams lately.
You're getting famous.
- I had the creepiest dream last night.
I was in a black room, all
dark, with white furniture.
And there was a gold chest
in the center of the room.
And Marcel Marceau was there.
And he was doing a mime of a snake
with his left arm and hand.
(dramatic music)
Then he vanished.
And I opened the chest.
(lid creaking)
And there was a real snake.
And then there was a flash of light.
(explosion)
- The conquest is dragged happily.
Ho ho ho ho ho.
Look at you, you look ready for the world.
- I just wanted to say thanks and goodbye.
- Oh.
Any time, you know that.
I'm truly sorry about what
happened to Forrester.
- Me too.
They said he died instantly.
You knew what was gonna
happen, though, didn't you?
- No, not exactly.
Not about the car going off
the road and the explosion.
- His dream was what, a warning.
- In a way.
He was being given time to prepare.
- He was so sure you were wrong.
Well, I gotta go.
Joe.
You don't belong here.
I believe that.
I won't forget you.
(dramatic music)
- Mr. Saunders.
We finished the loan reports,
and we're in very good shape.
- That's great, Parker.
- By the way, sir.
There's a wonderful article on
you in the news this morning.
- Yeah, it's not bad.
Parker, I do need your help on something.
- Sure.
- You've been tracking
business and market trends.
- Of course.
- Have you noticed anything
unusual in the market,
trouble signs?
- No, I, do you think
I've missed something?
- It's nothing I can put my finger on.
It's just a hunch.
- Based on anything in particular?
- It's nothing tangible.
This is gonna sound ridiculous.
The last few nights, I've had this dream
that I'm missing something.
It's disturbing.
- I don't know what to
tell you, except that
I'll look harder at the market.
- Okay.
I'll see you in the morning.
- Good night.
(phone dialing)
- Yes, for Graymount.
Graymount Psychiatric Hospital please.
(dramatic music)
(horn honking)
- To defy power, which seems omnipotent.
To love and bear.
To hope til hope creates,
from its own wreck, the
thing it contemplates.
(dramatic music)
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
Have a seat, have a seat.
- Thank you.
- What did you wanna talk to me about?
- Well, I was thinking about
our conversation last night.
There is someone I know that
I think could be useful.
He helped me, he's incredibly intuitive.
And he taught me a lot.
- And the weekday weeps
that it should be so.
- [Nurse] This is for you to sign.
- I don't,
I don't understand.
- You're being released.
Tomorrow afternoon, four p.m.
Here, someone sent these for you.
- But who, who signed this?
Who's Dr. Wyatt?
- You haven't heard.
Dr. Russell's gone, lost his license.
- I can't believe this.
Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
I'll come back for this later.
(dramatic music)
- Lydia.
- Til hope creates.
- Lydia, you're talking.
- The thing it contemplates.
This is to be free.
- Lydia.
(triumphant music)
- Joe, you okay?
(giggling)
- I've been locked up so
long, I forget how it smells.
How it feels.
I can walk through that door,
and no one will stop me.
It's gonna take a little
time getting used to.
Thank you.
(dramatic music)
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Nice meeting you.
- [Joseph] It's a pleasure.
- Just relax.
- Have a seat, have a seat.
Is it Joe or Joseph?
- Either is fine.
- Well, Joe, let's get down to business.
I went through a lotta
trouble to get you here.
- So I understand.
I hope you will find
that, that it's worth it.
- I expect to.
As Mr. Parker no doubt told you,
the holdings to my corporation
are extremely diversified.
And recently I had some misgivings.
That's why you're here.
He says you're something of a genius.
- He said that?
Well, I do study the market
and have a pretty good
handle on interpreting it.
What are your concerns based on?
- Dreams.
Every night for a month now,
I've had this same dream.
And I can't help feeling that it means
something very important.
- Please, all I do is listen.
- All right then.
My dream always starts
right here in this office.
- His opinion of my dream
didn't make me happy,
but it was honest.
He truly believes his
explanations come from God.
- Yes, yes, he does.
- I asked him, I said, why does God
talk to people that
don't wanna talk to him?
And you know what he said?
He said sometimes when people
don't wanna talk to God,
he jump-starts the conversation.
- That's a good thought.
How'd he explain your dream?
- It appears that the market is in
for seven very prosperous years.
And then seven very bad years.
The market's gonna take a dive.
- A crash.
- Exactly, nationwide.
And Joe's idea is to prepare the people.
Help them stay afloat.
- Did Joe have any ideas
of what steps to take?
- He had a solid plan.
This was a good call, Parker.
(siren wailing)
(phone dialing)
(phone ringing)
- [Jacob] Hello.
Keller residence, hello.
Hello.
Keller resi-
- Are we on, guys?
Jane, I'm standing here
in the corridor of power,
where there's been yet another
downturn in the market.
Following a seven-year boom,
Wall Street now endures
its second straight year
of falling stock prices.
Joseph Keller, the leading spokesman
for Silver Falcon Financial,
explains how while
other firms have managed to--
- Joe, I was looking forward
to your television debut.
What did you say?
- While other businesses were riding high,
James A. Saunders had the foresight
to prepare in the event of a downturn,
et cetera, et cetera, mumbo-jumbo.
- [Parker] The entire country's
just beginning to hurt,
and you still think there's
five more years of this?
- Yes I do.
- Gentlemen, gentlemen.
- Mr. Saunders, it's good to see you.
- Joseph, do you have
that report on the crash?
- Finished it this afternoon.
I analyzed all the different figures,
from all the different departments.
They confirmed that we are very stable.
- We did our homework.
- Yes, sir.
- And, Parker, good call again.
- [Parker] I'll make sure
that the executive directors
have a copy of that tonight.
- Thank you.
Keep it up, keep it up.
- Well, good night, everyone.
- Goodnight, Lydia, thank you.
Well I'm gonna call it a day.
What about you, Joe?
- In a few minutes.
- Oh, oh, I almost forget.
There are some guys
waiting to see Mr. Saunders
about a loan.
He'd asked me earlier if I would
ask you to take care of it.
- Sure.
What company?
- [Parker] Keller
Manufacturing, any relation?
- What?
- Keller Manufacturing.
What's wrong, you know these guys?
- No.
No, no, nothing.
Uh, give me, give me five minutes please.
- Sure.
- Parker?
- [Parker] Yeah?
- Did you,
did you give them my name?
- No, they were waiting to see Saunders.
- Don't, let me.
- Sure, five minutes.
- Thank you.
- Good evening, thanks
for seeing us so late.
I'm Robert Keller.
These are my brothers,
Simon, Justin, Ashton.
We're from Keller Manufacturing.
Clothing.
- So you told my assistant.
- That's right.
We understand that you're
in the position, this bank,
this institution, of giving
rather substantial loans.
- Go on.
- Mr., I--
- [Joseph] Gray.
- Mr. Gray, we are a
proud foundation, 40 years, clothing.
We have great references.
- If it's such a successful company,
why do you need me?
Or perhaps you're borrowing in panic.
Taking money from smaller
firms in real need.
- No.
And there's more than
just business at stake.
We have personal considerations.
People.
- What my brother means to
say is that this is a business
that our father started 40 years ago.
And he's depending on us, Mr. Gray.
- As are the workers and their families.
And our own families, as well.
- With so much at stake,
why isn't your father
here to see me himself?
- He couldn't make it out here.
It's his memory.
He's quite elderly.
- He hasn't traveled much
since the death of our mother.
Stepmother.
- I'm sorry.
May I ask how she died?
- Childbirth.
That's our youngest brother, Ben.
- The death of a wife, a mother,
is very hard.
It's fortunate that the child lived.
Still, the man who
stands to lose the most,
meaning your father, should be here
to negotiate with me himself.
- He can't, he won't.
He hates New York.
He lost a son here.
- Lost?
- He disappeared.
A few months before our mother died.
He may have been murdered.
- Yeah, and I was the one who was supposed
to look after him, yeah.
- We're all to blame.
All of us.
- It's late.
Give me your financial report,
and I will look it over.
- You may have some questions
regarding some of the
family history with loans.
- I will give you my answer
tomorrow.
- You've been most kind.
Thank you.
- Carl, please, please excuse me.
(dramatic music)
Why do you send them to me?
After all this time.
I can
ruin them.
Destroy everything they've worked for.
And they wouldn't even know why.
My mother.
Damn them.
19 years.
How do I forgive that?
How do I forgive any of it?
- This is a generous loan.
And the rates, they seem more than fair.
Justin.
- Everything seems to be in order,
but I'm unclear on these
last two provisions.
- The first provision simply
means that for the duration
of the loan, one of you will stay here
and be available for consultation.
- That's unheard of.
- The second requires Jacob Keller,
as principal owner of
Keller Manufacturing,
to come to New York and sign the papers
in person, and all of his
sons will accompany him.
Those are the conditions.
- Mr. Gray, with all due respect,
Robert and Justin have power of attorney.
Father's presence, it's uncalled for.
- These are special circumstances.
It is a requirement,
if you wish a loan to save
your father's business.
- I'll stay.
- What?
- I said I'll stay.
- Why?
- I have my reasons.
Let's just say I owe it to Dad.
I'll be all right.
- [Robert] Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Good, fine.
- Is this guy wacko?
He's certifiable.
Nobody does business like this.
- It was the only way to get the money.
- Well return it.
We don't need it, not this way.
- Father, listen.
Please, we do need the money.
Without it, we stand to lose everything.
- We'll get it someplace else.
- Don't you think we tried?
Everyone's hurting now, Dad.
- But why keep Simon?
And why would this man want Dad?
- I don't know.
- Benjamin's staying here.
I'll not risk his going.
- Well, Mr. Gray, he said
all of us together, Dad.
I'm sorry.
- I fear for Benjamin
because he's my youngest,
but I fear for all of you.
So I'll go and see this Mr. Gray.
- I'm going with you.
Don't look at me like that, I'm going.
(dramatic music)
- How long are we supposed to wait?
We've been here half an hour already.
- As long as it takes.
Simon.
Are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine, really.
It's good to see all of you.
- Do you know what's going on here?
- Yeah.
- So where is this Mr. Gray.
- Well that's just it.
I couldn't tell you right now.
I haven't seen that much of him.
His assistant, Mr. Parker,
wanted me to give this to you, Dad.
- Like the big city?
- Diane, I don't have my glasses.
- Dear Mr. Keller,
I will meet you and your
sons in my home at seven p.m.
Transportation is awaiting.
Mr. Gray.
- Can't we sit down?
- Father, I'm sure it would
be all right if you sat.
- [Jacob] It's all right, all right.
I'll only have to stand a while.
- [Justin] Maybe we're
supposed to start without him.
- Gentlemen.
Thank you for coming.
Welcome.
All of you.
- What's this all about?
Why are we here?
- I would like to propose
a toast to your family.
To those who are no longer here.
To those who sit in health before you,
and to those who are lost.
But now is found.
Salute.
Father.
I am Joseph.
Your son.
- That can't.
This is too cruel, no.
No, no, no.
- Yes, I am Joseph.
My mother is Rachel.
We had a house next to an empty lot.
My room was down the hall from Ash.
I worked one summer at the factory.
You gave me a coat.
(crying)
- What happened?
What happened, what happened?
- To be honest, Father,
those are not memories
I wish to recall.
Ever.
But I will say this.
What might have destroyed me
has instead shaped me.
Shaped this moment.
I am here to help you.
All of you.
And many other people besides.
(dramatic music)
- Joseph, forgive me.
- Forgiveness will always be in my heart.
I know what you planned.
But fate always takes its course.
We are all right now.
All of us.
In time, you will see what I say is true.
A second chance.
(glasses clinking)
- To that grace which
has brought us together.
- To my children.
I love you all.
- Thank you.
(dramatic music)
(gentle music)
Mother, sit beside me
Don't you fall asleep, oh please
Listen to me talk a while
It won't take too long
I've been betrayed by my brothers
They tore my coat of colors
Insomnia, why don't you
let me sleep a while
This game has gone too far now
I have been exiled
The gift God placed inside of me
Has been a curse, it seems
Insomnia, why don't you let me sleep
A while
Let me sleep a while
Father, sit beside me
There's so much that you can't see
My brothers left me high and dry
Did you believe their lies?
For so long I've been restless
All I want is forgiveness
Insomnia, why don't you
let me sleep a while
This game has gone too far,
And now I have been exiled
The gift God placed inside of me
Has been a curse, it seems
Insomnia, why don't you
Let me sleep a while
(gentle music)
(MultiCom jingle)