Good day, Stafford.
I'm Rick Stockwell,
filling in for Samantha Burns, who's
feeling a bit under the weather.
Samantha, we're all dying to have you back
with us, and we wish you a speedy recovery.
With that, let's head on down
to Gene Porter, who has news
about the alarming increase of
wait time at Stafford Memorial Hospital.
Gene, what can you tell us about this
developing situation?
Gene...
Gene!!!
♪ Oh, yeah. ♪
♪ Oh, no. ♪
♪ I've got these people here ♪
♪ Telling me how they understand ♪
♪ They've been here before
and walked through that door ♪
♪ Into becoming a man. ♪
Darn kids are going to be the death of me.
♪ But I don't think they understands a thing ♪
Sid, Sydney, get over here... now.
♪ As I'm climbing up the walls ♪
Come on. Alright, now.
These are for tonight.
♪ Ocean of emotion crashing on my shore ♪
Okay. No, no excuses. Do you understand me?
Do you understand? All right.
♪ Oh, all to hell it all ♪
Go... Go!
♪ Mystification about the education ♪
♪ That they really want ♪
I swear they're going to be the death of me.
♪ Fumbling in cars reaching for the stars ♪
♪ Oh no, just figure it out ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Oh nooo, no ♪
I'm picking you up around six thirty
and we're going to go to the...
that's for you
♪ Mystification about the education ♪
♪ That they really want ♪
What!
So I'm not going to be if I get you
around six thirty ♪ fumbling in cars ♪
♪ Reaching for the stars ♪
Well yeah!
♪ On no, just figure it out ♪
I mean, I can just get you at eight.
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Oh, no, no, no. ♪
Dude you got to stay.
♪ It will be alright ♪
Kill me.
Ahem.
Uh, Chef, I, I, I, I
I need you to stay late.
Well, now I have a note
from the principal here.
Some kids are going to be staying after,
and you need to give them sustenance.
Do you understand?
Thank you for your cooperation. Ahem.
Mm mm mm mm mm.
I didn't order...
They always mess things up. Always.
Oh, good. Glad you're here.
Come here, come here, come here.
I'd like to show you what we're doing here.
Okay., now, first off,
everything is fragile...
Glad you could join us.
Come on in, please.
Please come in. You, too.
Come on. I haven't got a day.
I don't want to be here all evening,
and I want to get this assignment done.
You too, missy. Come on.
Get over here.
Pay attention.
Okay, now, this is your assignment.
I want to get this done this evening.
The rat maze, I got several pieces
So the fatter one is Ginger.?
Essentially. Yes. I've
nicknamed the more sedentary
one Ginger and the more active one Fred.
You know, smooth moves like Fred Astaire.
I think Ginger might be a dude to you.
Ewe!
Actually, they're both female.
Nice observation skills Bull.
Hey, wasn't Ginger Rogers like Fred
Astaire's dance partner or something?
Why is she the sedentary one?
So misogynistic!
We can change the names if you want to.
Whatever.
Listen, Frankie, let's
just not get too caught up in the names.
The important thing is
that we can observe their behavior.
And so we can see how their lifestyle
affects their cognitive ability.
Put your money on the active one, boys.
We all know it's survival of the
fittest. Like Dagwood said.
Darwin!
Whatever freaks, it's a fact.
It's always the strongest
who survive in the end.
Hey, where are there three cages?
Oh, there were actually three rats, but.
Well, you see, Ginger.
Well, rat cannibalism is actually very...
Ewe, never mind.
What?
Dude, she the rat.
Who?
Frankie?!?
NOOOOOOO
No, Ginger did.
Oh, whatever.
I don't know I was signing
up to babysit rats.
Actually, Alexis I specifically chose this
because I thought it would be pretty easy
for us to get this done tonig...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Are you saying
that this was all your idea?
Well, yeah, but...
This whole... the rats...
Well, no...
Us! On a Friday!
Okay, Not tonight, but listen...
Come on, man!
Not tonight. That's not what I meant.
This is so lame.
I can't believe it.
But I actually agree
with little Miss Pompoms.
Listen, guys, it's really not that bad,
and it won't take that long.
Besides, we know I'll be doing
most of the work anyways.
Now, if we can just get this done,
you all can go back to living
your very important lives.
And how are we doing...
my students?
I see you've made some progress.
Tell me.
Have you made any preliminary
observations and hypotheses?
There is a general consensus between us
that the more active of the two rats
will have at least a slight advantage
in cognitive testing.
Yeah, what he said and
I have observed that the more active rats
eat more like, you know, other rats.
You can't fool me, students.
You need to focus on your work.
Now, you knew when you took up my class
that the labs would require
time to put in.
And you waited to the last minute
And here you are.
And now it's on you.
Now, no one.
No one is leaving here tonight
till I see preliminary results.
Okay.
Yeah.
We better be done with this by,
like, eight,
because I have a date tonight with Mason.
Yeah, he's picking you up here.
So whatever.
Okay, we just better be done soon.
Let me be perfectly clear.
No one leaves tonight until I see results.
Understand?
So no visitors tonight?
What?
What you children
are going to be the death of me.
No more distractions,
no more phones, hand 'em in.
You're killing me Smalls!
Yours too.
Seriously? Yes, ma'am.
I don't want to be here all evening.
And you all need to focus.
Weird flex. But, okay.
Wow, thanks.
That was smooth.
Whatever.
Okay, let's just let these disgusting
things run around so I can go out tonight.
I know you might not understand,
because it's not like
you have anything else to do, Frankie.
Ouch, chill.
Just because I'm not a cookie cutter
Barbie doesn't mean I don't have a life.
A life?
What would you know about a life?
You think black... is the new... black?
Hey, Alexis, how about you grab Ginger?
It's about time we get a trial run
The carnival one!?!
Cannibal!
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
She looks hungry.
I hope you don't bite me
now like she can eat you.
Yeah, but it can still bite, right?
A little rat nip? That ain't nothing.
My brother Dexter.
Now he's a fricking biter.
We were fighting in the morning,
and he really got me good.
Check it out.
Ahem... Thank you all
for your stimulating discussion
and hard work.
And you, can you at least
try to help out a little?
We need to see how long it takes
Ginger to get to her food.
Dude,
my stomach. I think...
I think I'm getting hungry.
Man, I wonder what
they're making for dinner.
So, like, how many more
of these rat maze things
do we have to do before we can just, like,
name a winner and get out of here?
Well, unfortunately, there
hasn't been a statistical difference
between the two conditions yet.
A statitica what?
Simply put, we need to do more trials.
And besides, we're out of food.
So why don't you guys just take
another five, and I'll go get more pellets
And just where do you think you are
scurrying off to?
Oh, well,
I was running to get more rat food
so we can do some more trials.
Wait, where's that odd looking girl?
Uh, Francine.
She really prefers to be called Frankie.
And, I don't know, Sir.
Perhaps the bathroom. I mean...
Speak of the she devil!
I can't have you running
around the school at night.
Now you need to tell me if you ever need
to leave the lab for whatever reason.
Like to go get a pizza?
No sir, absolutely not.
Until you're done,
I'm responsible for you.
And as such,
no one is to leave this school
for whatever reason.
As for your sustenance.
I've asked the cook to remain behind,
to prepare your dinner,
which should be ready sometime soon.
So I must ask you to stay on task.
Only a proper lab report which characterizes
the experiment will be accepted!
Ugh. What a douche.
So anyway, about the cook.
I went to the kitchen to see
what was for dinner.
You're welcome Bull.
And the cook was just standing
in the middle of the room,
staring at the wall... like a statue.
Really freaky.
Nothing's cooking.
So then I ask him, what's for dinner?
And he just shushes me.
And gives me this really chilling look.
Soul piercing, really.
You are so dramatic.
Whatever.
It was weird.
Like serial killer weird.
I just thought it was best
to get out of there
before he decided to put me on the menu.
I think Bull has the right idea.
Order takeout.
Pizza.
Pizza. Pizza.
Another fascinating story, really.
But, guys,
we just need to get back to work here.
And besides, I'm
sure there's a logical explanation
for as to why all of this is going on.
Just adults can be odd sometimes, right?
Anyways...
We need to do more trials.
I'll go get more rat pellets.
Shhh. Stop your screaming boy.
Those damn rats!
They're everywhere.
You see where it went?
Uhhhhh... uhhhhh
Oh, you're one of those rat kids.
What are you doing in here?
Kitchen's closed!
Can't you see I'm busy?
I am. I just... I heard. I just.
I was just wondering what time dinner is?
Dinner will be ready when I say it's ready!
Now go back to playing with
your little rat friends.
Oh, hey, Oz.
We're getting better numbers from Fred.
I think you would say
we're starting to see
a statistical difference.
So, I see you brought the rat food.
But man...
when do we get to eat?
Funny you should say that. Bull
I actually bumped into the cook.
And Frankie's right.
He's clinically insane.
And besides,
I saw what he's making for dinner,
but I'm not so sure
we're going to want to eat.
Yeah, well,
it better not be loaded with carbs.
One of us has got to watch her figure.
Listen, I'm not so sure
about the carbohydrate content.
I'm not even sure
if it's fit for human consumption.
Oh, come on, Oz. It can't be that bad.
At least you didn't try to kill you.
All I'm saying is that what
I saw in there would make this stuff
look tasty.
Let's just look at it.
Okay, so show me what's going on here.
You saw different numbers, but
we didn't have any different numbers,
clearly.
Yeah, sorry.
I wrote their behaviors, their numbers,
like it's all right here
under the...
Excuse me. Ahem.
Is this on?
Students, please proceed in an
orderly fashion to lab B and enjoy
your freshly prepared sustenance.
Thank you.
Dude.
Are you sure you don't want to finish that?
Because I could totally eat it.
Ugh, you are such a pig.
Seriously, dude, that's disgusting.
The food is so gross.
It's probably left over from the eighties.
I was thinking.
I mean, look at us.
I think maybe Professor Romero
is doing an experiment on us,
you know,
trying to see if we'll eat this stuff.
Who knows what's in it.
Just look at this food.
This room.
Our rats trapped in a maze project.
I think maybe... Sure Frankie.
Conspiracies much?
No, I'm serious.
Of course you are.
If you ever noticed how he kind of just
lurks around and watches us,
I think maybe, just maybe, we're
he's rats... in here.
Come on, man.
Like I said, I don't think this stuff
is suitable for human consumption.
Huh. Well, if that's the case, Bull's safe.
Even though I think he's had enough
Anyways, we should probably get going
so we can finish our experiment
and just get out of here
and get some real food.
O. M. G. Bull!
That so noxious Oh, I.
I don't think I should be eaten that much.
I think I overdid it.
No, dip Sherlock.
We should really go.
Damn dude! Again?!
I don't feel so good.
I got to go take a dump. Huh?
How could he be so stupid?
I got to admit, I'm not a picky eater,
but that stuff was not food.
Speaking of eating,
did you guys realize that Ginger isn't
eating that much anymore?
Even after she goes through the maze,
she still isn't even touching her treat.
Do you think maybe
she had too much to eat?
I don't realize you're paying
that much attention, but,
yeah, I've noticed Ginger's behavior
in our logs
and it's difficult to tell whether
she's not eating because she's not hungry
or if something else is causing her
lack of appetite.
Yeah, I think both noxious fumes
are contributing to my lack of appetite.
Where is the fat boy?
Why can you not just all stay together?
Oh, uh, Bull, he wasn't feeling well,
so he went to the restroom.
I think he might have indigestion.
You tell Mr.
Bull I want to see him when he returns.
I will be waiting in my office.
Yes, Professor.
Come on, you guys.
You gotta admit.
Professor Romero is a bit strange.
I think he pays more attention.
To our behavior than the experiment.
I hate to agree with anything
that vampire says,
but the professor is a bit... odd.?
Whoa, what, the...
Oh, what happened?
Uh, the lights went out. Duh.
Nice one, Frankie.
Alexis, look, I'm sure it's just...
Students, I need to go to the basement work
room immediately!
Grab everything and go now.
GO!
Frankie, the professor needs us to get
down there, so can you please just help?
I am helping, Oz!
Can we just go, please?
Oh, Mason. I'm not ready to die yet.
I'm not ready to kill you... yet.
I can't see anything. Oh, my God.
I can't see anything.
Mason!
I wish I was with Mason!
This step.
Oh, thank God.
Can you quit going on and on now?
Guys, enough.
Can we just get down to the workroom?
My arms are about to fall off.
Why is it so dark and like...
Oh, my Gosh. Just chill!
Watch the corner.
Mason.
All right, this is good.
Let's just set our stuff up down here.
What?
We're really going
to keep doing this stuff
down here?
Don't you think something crazy
is happening out there?
Do you really think that Professor Strange
is worried about us
finishing this project?
I don't know. I don't know.
I just don't know.
All I know is it Professor
Romero needs us to finish our project.
Okay.
Don't you mean your project?
This whole rat maze
thing was all your idea.
And if you ask me,
you are just as weird as he is, Oz.
I'm so done with this sh...
Hey, Alexis, you signed up for this
class, too, and it requires lab work.
Okay, so I'm sorry if that makes you late
for your stupid date or whatever,
but it's not my fault that the power
went out and we're stuck down here.
So can you please just help
get Ginger ready for her next run?
Okay. Now Frankie.
So I see...
That was upstairs.
Hey, guys.
What do you want me to do with...?
I guess it's just you and me now.
Oh, you dirty.
Where are you?
Don't you... Ugh!
When I find you, I'm going
to personally feed you to the other rat!
Kitchen
Hello?
Yeah, this place is getting
creepy by the minute.
Hey, Oz, check this out.
Do you think this is blood?
Hard to tell.
Maybe the chef cut himself
or cut one of those rats he was chasing.
There are rats running around in here.
I mean, I don't know.
That's what the chef said.
Though his objective
awareness is questionable.
At any rate,
I'm sufficiently creeped out by now.
Should probably get back to the basement,
wrap it up and get out of here.
Yeah, I'm with you.
Rats, blood, crazy cooks.
Oh, my!
Alexis, you'll never
believe what we just...
Oh, my God. What happened to your finger?
Where's Bull?
He come back yet?
Hmmm, uh, that...
I don't know. No.
Hey, that rat Ginger...
bit my finger.
And, well, she ran off somewhere.
Oh, no.
She's got to be around here somewhere.
I keep listening,
trying to hear her scratching or whatever.
Well, we have to find that rat before
Professor Romero finds out
or this whole night will
have been for nothing.
Oh, no, no.
I'm not doing this
crap with you guys again.
No offense.
We're just going to have to find Ginger
What's going on in here, huh?
I keep hearing rustling out there.
Wait a second.
Have you all been wondering about.
I brought you down here for a reason.
Where is that Bull?
I swear I heard him
sulking around upstairs.
So, professor, we actually just finished
the observation phase of our experiment,
and we just need to collect the data
and write a report... why, what's going on.
Oh, yes.
That...
nothing to worry about children.
There was a vehicular accident outside.
A power poll hit
the car and caught on fire.
I thought it would be more prudent
and safe if you were down here
away from the windows.
You know, for safety purposes.
But you're safe there. All is well.
You may resume.
I'm still unhappy about Bull.
Send him to me when you see him.
And hurry this up. Wrap it up.
I don't know how long
the generator will last.
And I don't want to be around
when the backup power runs out of juice.
Yes. Yes, of course Professor.
We've got to find Ginger.
Sure.
But I don't know if I believe
what the professor was saying
about what's going on.
Guys, my finger... Shhh!
Do you?
Do you hear that?
No. Hear what?...
Shhh!
Listen.
I caught the end of it,
and it can't be good.
Maybe it's just Bull, you know?
Frankie, we should probably
go check up on him.
You stay here and look for Ginger.
This isn't good.
I can't believe he bit me!
What the hell's wrong with him?...
Did he just say someone bit him?
Don't they have any respect?
God!
I think that's Ginger.
You see what's up with Bull?
I'm going to go get the rat.
Oh, don't pee, don't pee,
don't pee, don't pee...
Alexis, there is some weird
stuff going down... out.
Alexis.
I'm going to kill her.
Professor Romero.
Is that you?
Are you okay in there?
Professor...
Oh, man.
What the...?
This is not happening.
I'm out of here.
Oh, my God.
He did not!
Alexis!
He bit me!
Who bit you, Ginger?
I know, oh, my gosh.
Okay, look...
Oh my god!
Okay, okay, I'm, I'm gonna
go get you some help...
Okay.
Just... stay there.
Don't... Don't move.
What... What the...
It's me.
It's Oz. It's me.
It's me. It's me.
Sh.
What the H?
Alexis is hurt bad.
Sh...
I think. I think I saw Bull, but he
he had turned into some sort of a
I don't know,
a zombie!
This is impossible
from what I've seen and smelled tonight.
I certainly think it is.
How could this happen?
Do you think this is all part of
the professor's twisted experiment on us?
I mean, do you think he had the cook do it?
Maybe it was in that awful food.
That stuff was really nasty.
And Bull was the only one who ate it.
Yeah, perhaps.
But Professor Romero was mumbling
something about how someone bit him.
Maybe that was Bull. He did seem sick.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, my God. You're right.
Karma's a bitch.
Oh, and Professor Ratzo,
he was in his office moaning,
you know, like a zombie.
Maybe it was him or Bull
who bit Alexis.
Took a big chunk right out of her face.
Oh, my God.
I don't think she's going to make it.
We got to get out of here.
There's the Professor and Alexis, too.
I don't understand.
I'm sorry, Oz.
I'm sorry.
Maybe it wasn't the professor or the food.
You know, Alexis was bit.
Maybe it has something to do with that.
And Bull, he was saying that his
little brother beat him this morning, too.
It just.
It just doesn't make any sense. I just.
Regardless, we've got to get out of here
before the zombies
or whatever it is to
trys to snack on us, too.
Let's just go.
Yeah. Oh. Wait?
What about the cook?
Oh...
Shouldn't we like...
Well, the thing is,
I don't think he's going to make it.
When I walked in on Bull, he was munching
on what looked like the cook's arm.
Yeah, I think we're on our own here.
We should just get out of here.
Wait.
I don't know if you've noticed,
but brilliant professor zombified
really did chain all the doors shut
Frick!
Maybe we could go to his office
and get his keys.
Yeah.
You have fun with that.
That's easier said than done.
Last I knew, Bitey McBitey Face
was locked in his office,
and I ain't going back to check
There's got to be another way out
How about the lower loading docks?
We've loaded tons of sets
through there before.
Well, I mean, wouldn't that be locked, too?
Yeah, but being a theater
kid has its perks.
We keep a spare set of keys backstage, you
know, for all the after hours load outs.
Oh, my God.
I think I love you!
You know, in, like, a totally congenial,
sort of, kind of way.
Um, so, anyways, we should get going.
Uh huh.
You stay here here and get the keys.
I'll go distract Bull
then meet you at the dock.
Hey, Bull,
you big lummox
come munch on me.
Come on. Over here.
Come get me.
Come on.
No!
Oh, my God.
Oz, thank you.
I thought I was a goner.
I'm starting to realize
that killing zombies
isn't as easy as it seems in movies.
Luckily, they're super clumsy.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Let's just get out of here.
That's..
For being such a douche.
Professor.
And that's..
For trying to take a bite out of me.
Okay, I'm good now.
Let's go.
Bull's right about one thing.
Survival does favor the fittest.
And I, for one, need to work on my cardio.
Come on!
Dude this is so not my day!
I know this is kinda obvious, but
could you go any faster?
Like I didn't think of that already!
Whoa!
Retained digital grasp strength!
Fascinating.
Whoa.
Bull!
I don't know how much
longer I can hold this!
I'm going as fast as I can!
Uh, Oz!
Let's Go!
Hey, hey, hey Officer! We need help!
Oh, my God.
They're everywhere.
This is the freaking end!
No! Don't say that.
Everything will be all right.
♪ My Dear ♪
No, it won't.
♪ Oh, my, my ♪
♪ You gonna die! ♪
♪ Standing on top of the world ♪
♪ Got it all in your hands ♪
♪ With the sun shining down
on your perfect little life there ♪
♪ Oh, you got it all planned ♪
♪ Suddenly the clouds the clouds do form ♪
♪ I see them in my way ♪
♪ Now you're trapped now ♪
♪ Shake down, get it all right now ♪
♪ C'mon I see no way ♪
♪ My dear ♪
♪ Oh, my, my ♪
♪ You gonna to die ♪
♪ Oh, I hear you fighting ♪
♪ For your life ♪
♪ Don't know how you got here ♪
♪ But here you are ♪
♪ Come on, now ♪
♪ It's do or die ♪
♪ Oh, now, here you fighting ♪
♪ For your life ♪
♪ Don't need this, man ♪
♪ What's the plan ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
♪ Fight or flight ♪
♪ My dear ♪
♪ Oh, my, my ♪
♪ You gonna die ♪
♪ Trapped in a world ♪
♪ That feeds ♪
♪ That you don't understand ♪
♪ Chased by an adversary ♪
♪ Wants you to die now ♪
♪ On, game must win ♪
♪ I know it ain't fair ♪
♪ But the justice of it all ♪
♪ Is that nobody gives a sh♪♪ ♪
♪ We can dial this back ♪
♪ Can talk about it later now ♪
♪ If we survive this sh♪♪ ♪
♪ My dear ♪
♪ Oh, my, my ♪
♪ You gonna die ♪
♪ Oh, I hear you fighting ♪
♪ For your life ♪
♪ Don't know how you got here ♪
♪ But here you are ♪
♪ Come on, now ♪
♪ It's fight or flight ♪
♪ Oh, now, here you fighting ♪
♪ For your life ♪
♪ Don't need this, man ♪
♪ What's the plan ♪
♪ Come on now, do or die. ♪
This is the emergency broadcast system.
This is not a test.
Repeat, this is not a test.
Stay tuned for further instructions.
This is not a test.