(Man Screaming)
It's been three years
and the nightmares just beginning...
(ominous music)
(Horror Music Plays)
J-bird its gonna be on to night! (oh, yeah)
(and I can't wait to go to
get to the movies either.)
Break with that Batman flick!
Check the babes and then afterwards...
(Yeah, I wanna see that..) I don't know?
I heard it was good...
Better not be two babes
sitting next to each other either!
(No!...)
No! This can't be!
(Listen at this man?)
(What's the matter with this guy?)
They gonna let him out man!
(Let who out?)
My brother Irving! He's getting loose!
Aw man I can't believe this...
They let him out man from the Insane place.
The Restau - - torium??? Informatory..
They're gonna let him out of there man..
I tried to kill him three years ago man,
He cracked on me.
I tried to saw him in half man (okay)
But they let him go.. He's coming back man,
I'm telling you., he's coming
back... No! They can't let him go!
Is he dangerous?
(Is he Dangerous?)
Well I don't know?
But if the joker comes this
way, I got something for him!
Watch...
(Old West Music Playing)
(Shotgun Pump)
All you guys are crazy!
I'm going to get something to drink.
(Yeah, Yeah, Yeah... Get outta here!)
(Horror Music)
Oh! Oh, No!
(Boy struggling)
Oh! Oh, No! Oh...
(Garbage Disposal Noise)
Oh... Oh No!! Oh No!
Oh, Oh...
(Crunching bones sound)
Oh... Oh!!
(Garbage disposal shuts off)
(Band Rehearsing)
I Gotta Be Next To You!
Ok fellas. That's it for tonight...
That's it for tonight. (I
need to get home to the pad.)
Say what? (Get to the pad man, )
(Yeah. I'm tired.)
Better hurry up man,
I heard that guy..
Irving is roaming the streets man,
Irving? (Yeah!)
Man, I ain't worried about no Irving man,
If Irving dream about bothering me,
he better wake up and apologize! (Right)
(Outgoing Music Plays)
(I see y'all later!)
Alright! I'll see y'all later
Ugh..
(Garage door opening)
Uh, boy.. Along day
Where my keys?
Man, I'm telling you...
(Suspense Music)
No..No..No... Nooooo!
Uhh,
Uhh..
Ahh..
(Bat Crushing Bones)
Tony, they found two more people dead!
(Where?)
(Let me see that...)
It must be that crazy son of a...
Is he dangerous?
(Suspense Music)
Okay, make sure you like it doors and
windows now.
We don't want him getting in here!
(Car engine stalling)
(Spooky Music)
(Chocking and gurgling sounds...)
(Big Dog Growling)
(Dog Attacking)
(Horror Music)
Irving? I know you're
hurt! I came to help...
(Rats squeaking)
Irving?
(Ominous Music)
(Cat Screeching)
(Neck Snaps)
(Cleaver Strike)
(Radio Station surfing)
(Music playing - Cash "Slingshot")
Whats... Whats..It's
you! What do you want?!
Get.. Get Outta Here!!!
No! NO! Stop! Stop!
Ah-ugh...
(Man screams) Ah...
(Thunderstorm looming)
What a dreary day.
Well, I don't feel like cooking,
I don't feel like... Washing!
So I guess I'll just sit
here and watch some TV
Wonder what happened to Tony?
Should've been here by now...
(TV playing...)
(Crazy Music..)
Tony?
Is that you?
(Glass Breaking)
(Woman Screaming)
(Punch Sound) - (Falling Down steps)
(Body in dryer sound)
(Car keys picked up..)
(Car drives off...)
Let me see what's in today's paper..
Mad Man, claims another life...
Victim...
Michael Camper!!
What? That's Mike!!
That's it!!
Irving dies tonight!!
(Hero... Music)
(Click sound of Shotgun)
Where are you Irving?
I want You!! Just me and you!!
(Footsteps down the stairs)
(Horror Music)
(Heartbeat Sound)
(Shotgun Blast)
Whew...
(Knife Sound) Ahhhhh...!
Ah... Uhh...
Uhh... Ohh..
(Suspense music...)
Uh... uh...
(Heavy Breathing...)
Uh... ah...
(Struggling)
Uhm...
(Thump!)
(Match lighting wick!)
(Explosion!)
(Car Alarms Blaring...)
(Jeff, struggles down steps...)
(Picks up Irving's mask)
(Music... "Don't be Sad")
(IRVING!!)
(Ending music)