CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
TRIMARK HOME VIDEO
[RADIO CHATTER]
Woman: WITH SERVICE
TO 26 COUNTRIES ON 4 CONTINENTS,
WE PUT THE WORLD
WITHIN YOUR REACH.
FLY TRANS-CON AIR.
RELAX, SIT BACK,
ENJOY.
30% OF AMERICAN ADULTS
ARE AFRAID TO FLY.
THE NATIONAL INSTITUTE
OF MENTAL HEALTH
PLACES IT ONLY SECOND
TO THE FEAR OF PUBLIC SPEAKING,
SO WHAT YOU'RE
DEALING WITH HERE
IS VERY COMMON.
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
IT CAN BE OVERCOME.
REMEMBER, JUST RELAX,
SIT BACK, AND ENJOY.
UHH!
AAH!
OH, MY.
OHH!
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE
TURBULENCE.
YOU'LL BE FINE,
ELLIOT.
JUST TAKE
DEEP BREATHS.
[INHALES,
EXHALES]
WELL, I SUPPOSE
IT COULD BE WORSE.
I COULD BE LIKE...
LIKE POINDEXTER OVER THERE.
VIEW OPTIONS.
SELECT WIREFRAME.
ROTATE WIREFRAME
TO DELTA 2 AND ENHANCE.
IF HE ANALYZES ANY MORE
CHARTS AND GRAPHS,
THE AIRLINE'S
GOING TO HAVE TO GIVE HIM
A MASTERS IN AERONAUTICS.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
HE'S ALREADY GOT ONE.
OPEN SPECIFICATIONS.
YOU'RE JOKING.
WHAT, SO, HE CAN BUILD THEM,
BUT HE CAN'T FLY THEM?
OH. THAT'S A STITCH.
OH, GOD.
THE FACT IS, AN AIRPLANE
IS ONE OF THE SAFEST
PLACES YOU CAN BE
ON THE FACE
OF THE PLANET.
UHH.
OHH.
[PANTING]
[WHEEZING]
SIR! PLEASE, SIT DOWN!
I CAN'T TAKE IT!
I GOT TO GET
OUT OF HERE.
I C--I CAN'T TAKE IT
ANYMORE!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
YOU'RE FREAKING ME
OUT, MAN!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
DON'T DO IT!STOP!
COME BACK HERE!
DON'T DO IT!
HAROLD!
MMM.
DON'T WORRY.
I'M OK NOW.
I--I JUST NEEDED
SOME FRESH AIR.
OH, MAN.
I THOUGHT YOU IRS GUYS
WERE INVINCIBLE.
YOU SHATTERED THE ILLUSION
AGAIN, DUDE.
THAT POOR GUY.
CAN'T DO THE MACHINE
WITHOUT THE NICOTINE.
[SIGHS]
WELL, AT LEAST YOU
DIDN'T VOMIT THIS TIME.
NOW, I KNOW EACH OF YOU
HAVE DEMONS TO CONQUER--
CLAUSTROPHOBIA,
FEAR OF TECHNOLOGY,
[LAUGHS]
BAD AIRLINE FOOD.
BUT FOR THOSE OF YOU SUFFERING
FROM A FEAR OF HEIGHTS,
THIS NEXT EXERCISE
MAY BE A BIT TRICKY,
BUT IT'S OFTEN
VERY EFFECTIVE.
SO LET'S SEE
IF YOU CAN DO THIS.
Hazel: NOW,
IF YOU'RE HAVING TROUBLE
GETTING NEXT TO THE WINDOWS,
TRY CLOSING YOUR EYES FIRST
AND THEN OPENING THEM
ONCE YOU GET NEXT TO THE GLASS.
Jessica:
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
IT'S NOT SO TOUGH.
MAYBE NOT FOR HER,
BUT I'M A FREAK
ABOUT HEIGHTS.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
BUT...
WHATEVER DOESN'T KILL US
ONLY MAKES US STRONGER.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
YEAH, I SUPPOSE SO,
EXCEPT IN THE CASE
OF GOITER
AND IRRITABLE
BOWEL SYNDROME.
I DON'T THINK EITHER OF
THOSE MAKES YOU STRONGER.
YES. THAT'S GOOD.
RIGHT. COME ON.
WE'LL OPEN
OUR EYES ON 3.
ON 34 RIGHT.
PAN PACIFIC 400,
CONTACT GROUND CONTROL.
READY?
1, 2, 3.
SOMEBODY GET HIM
SOME WATER.
YOU ALL RIGHT,
BUDDY?
Jessica: MARTIN, MARTIN,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
I WANT TO COMMEND ALL OF YOU
FOR PUSHING YOURSELVES
THESE LAST 3 WEEKS.
NOW IT'S TIME
FOR YOUR DIPLOMAS.
LET'S GIVE YOURSELVES
A ROUND OF APPLAUSE.
YOUR TRIP
FROM SEATTLE TO L.A.
WILL BE IN A 747 IDENTICAL
TO OUR BOEING SIMULATOR.
THE FLIGHT HAS ONLY A SMALL
NUMBER OF PASSENGERS,
SO THE ATTENDANTS CAN GIVE YOU
THEIR FULL ATTENTION.
OH, AND DON'T FORGET
TO ARRIVE EARLY
FOR OUR WALK-THROUGH.
SO I'VE, UM...
HEARD ABOUT THIS
QUAINT LITTLE RESORT
ON THE ISLAND OF LANAI,
WHERE YOU SLEEP
IN THATCHED BUNGALOWS
ALONG THE BEACH.
PERHAPS I COULD RUSTLE US UP
A PAIR OF TICKETS
AND SOME GRASS
HULA SKIRTS.
YOU REALLY SURE YOU WANT
TO GO TO THE ISLANDS NOW?
I MEAN, IT SEEMS LIKE
YOU ALREADY HAVE
THAT HAWAIIAN DISEASE.
WHAT DISEASE?
LACK-OF-NOOKY.
OH, DEAR GOD.
I'M SORRY,
BUT DON'T YOU THINK
WE SHOULD GO ON ANOTHER DATE
BEFORE, YOU KNOW...
AND I THINK I SHOULD
FINISH MY TRAINING,
GET A FEW SUCCESSFUL FLIGHTS
UNDER MY BELT.
JESSICA, TRUST ME.
YOU'LL MAKE A SPLENDID
FLIGHT ATTENDANT.
[THUD]
AW.
SORRY, I'M KIND OF, UH,
FUMBLE-FINGERED.
OH, THAT'S, UH,
THAT'S NOT MINE.
THAT'S, UH,
RAPTOR THE DEATH-KNIGHT.
ARRGH!
I HOPE
IT'S NOT A BAD OMEN.
ACTUALLY...
WE'RE IN LUCK,
STATISTICALLY SPEAKING.
THERE HAVE NEVER BEEN
2 747 CRASHES
WITHIN 3 MONTHS
OF EACH OTHER.
AND SINCE THAT
AIR MOROCCO JET WENT DOWN
KILLING THOSE
213 PASSENGERS,
I'D HAVE TO SAY THE LAW
OF AVERAGES IS ON OUR SIDE.
THANKS AGAIN.
WELL, HE'S JUST A REAL
WINNER, ISN'T HE?
DEAR GOD.
I CAN'T WAIT TO MEET
THE WIFE AND KIDS
ON FLIGHT DAY.
MARTIN'S A LITTLE NEUROTIC,
BUT I THINK HE'S NICE.
AND ACTUALLY, I DON'T
THINK HE IS MARRIED.
AH, WELL, PERHAPS
I SHOULD BE JEALOUS.
WELL, HERE'S TO, UH--
HERE'S TO WINNING YOUR LOVE
ON TRANS-CON 110.
Woman on P.A.:
ATTENTION ALL PASSENGERS,
FLIGHT 118 TO LaGUARDIA
AIRPORT IS NOW...
MMM. MMM.
OH, GOD,
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE
ACTUALLY DOING THIS.
DOING WHAT?
HEY, RALPH.
FUNNY.
TODAY'S THE DAY.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS
FEELING?
HI, LENNY.
HEY.
Hazel: HAS EVERYONE
GOT THEIR CARRYON BAGS?
IF YOU WANT TO HEAD DOWN
THE JETWAY,
I'LL BE RIGHT WITH YOU.
OK?
[SIGHS]
ALL RIGHT.
ANY TIME YOU NEED
TO GET AHOLD OF ME,
YOU KNOW THE NUMBER.
ALL RIGHT?
OK.
MMM!
[SIGHS]
OH, JUST A HINT, DAD.
YOU KNOW
WHENEVER I GET SCARED,
YOU TELL ME TO THINK
ABOUT DISNEYLAND?
THAT'S WHAT
YOU SHOULD DO.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
DON'T THINK ABOUT CRASHING
AND BURNING TO DEATH
IN A MILLION TINY PIECES.
THANKS A LOT, PAL.
[LAUGHS]
MMM.
OOH. I'M GONNA
MISS YOU SO MUCH.
ME, TOO.
DON'T YOU GIVE ELENA
ANY PROBLEMS NOW, OK?
ALL RIGHT. BYE-BYE.
GOOD LUCK.
BYE. CALL ME AS SOON
AS YOU GET THERE.
GOOD-BYE,
MR. MESSERMAN.
BYE, DAD.
LOVE YOU.
Hazel: OK, EVERYBODY,
LET'S KEEP TOGETHER.
WATCH YOUR STEP.
THIS IS HUGE.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE SWIMMING
WITH THE WHALES.
LOOK AT THIS.
COME ON.
RIGHT OVER HERE.
TO SAVE TRANSFER TIME,
THE LUGGAGE IS STORED
AND MOVED IN METAL BINS.
THE DE-ICING FLUID
IS A MIXTURE
OF 50% GLYCOL
AND 50% WATER.
GREAT.
THIS WAY. WE'LL TAKE A LOOK
AT THE LANDING GEAR NOW.
THIS IS THE ENGINE.
MAKES THE PLANE
FLY LIKE A BIRDY.
YEAH, IT LOOKS LIKE A, UH...
ROLLS-ROYCE RB11-524
WITH A TRENT 700 CORE.
THIS BABY HAS ONE ADVANCED
FUEL FLOW SYSTEM.
MAKES THE ENGINE
RUN COOLER.
HAPPY TO SEE THAT.
OH, YEAH? ME, TOO.
WELCOME ABOARD.
FEEL FREE TO GO
WHEREVER YOU'D LIKE.
TRANS-CON GIVES YOU GUYS
THE RUN OF THE PLANE.
HI.
WHERE'S SHEILA?
SHE'S SICK.
HER REPLACEMENT
IS SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
STANLEY NILES JR.
NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
PROBABLY A NEW GUY.
I HOPE YOUR PATCH WORKS.
IT'S A 2-HOUR FLIGHT.
I THOUGHT IT
WAS AN HOUR 45. 2 HOURS.
E AND F.
WHERE THE HELL'S E AND F?
I CAN NEVER FIGURE
THESE THINGS OUT.
OH, THAT'S FINE.
YOU CAN KEEP THAT.
THIS PLANE GONNA
LEAVE ON TIME?
YES, IT IS, SIR.
AS SCHEDULED.
Kit: WELCOME ABOARD.
HELLO.
HI.
YOU'RE ON THE AISLE.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
IT DOESN'T FIT.
PULL THE THING,
PULL THE THING.
PULL IT.
OH, LET ME HELP YOU
WITH THAT.
IT'S, UH, KIND OF
CROWDED UP THERE.
YEAH.
DR. KESSLER,
EVERYTHING'S
GOING TO BE JUST FINE.
I'M GOING TO BE SITTING
RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU,
ALL RIGHT?
OOH. STRONG.
THERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
SURE.
HI.
THIS IS IT.
YEAH, IT SURE IS.
AHH.
WELL...
LOOKS LIKE
THE GANG'S ALL HERE.
MAN, HOTTIES LIKE THAT
DO NOT TRAVEL BY BUS.
NO. UH-UH.
OK, WE'LL HOLD THE FLIGHT.
WHAT'S THEIR E.T.A.?
THANKS.
SORRY I'M LATE.
I JUST GOT THE CALL.
IT WENT OUT
LAST NIGHT.
I KNOW, BUT, UM...
HI.
HELLO.
PASSENGER LOAD
LOOKS PRETTY LIGHT.
MIDWEEK DEAD.
ONLY 83 IN COACH,
BUT, UH, BUSINESS CLASS
OUGHT TO KEEP US BUSY.
[WHISPERING] Another
fear of flying group.
OHH. I'LL PASS OUT
EXTRA BAGS.
YOU CAN MAKE
THE DELAY UP TO ME
BY CHECKING THE GALLEY
AND DOING THE PREFLIGHT.
SURE. NO PROBLEM.
UH, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN--
[LOUD FEEDBACK]
ON BEHALF OF
TRANS-CON AIRLINES,
I'D LIKE TO WELCOME YOU ABOARD
FLIGHT 110 TO LOS ANGELES
WITH CONTINUING SERVICE
TO, UH...
TO HONOLULU.
PLEASE FOLLOW ALONG WITH
THE SAFETY REFERENCE CARDS
AS YOU WATCH THE VIDEO
ON THE MONITORS.
EXCUSE ME, SIR,
THIS BRIEFCASE HAS TO GO
IN THE OVERHEAD COMPARTMENT
OR UNDER THE SEAT
IN FRONT OF YOU.
I KNOW THE DRILL.
GOOD AFTERNOON, SIR.
GOOD AFTERNOON.
13-D IS IN
THE CENTER SECTION.
IT'S GONNA BE
A FEW MORE MINUTES.
4 PASSENGERS ARE BEING
ROUTED THROUGH CUSTOMS
FROM A AEROFLOT FLIGHT.
THEIR INBOUND
WAS DELAYED.
I HAD THE SAME PROBLEM
COMING FROM SFO.
A STORM'S SOCKED
IN MOST OF THE COAST,
[OVER P.A.] AND IT'S DUE TO
ARRIVE HERE BEFORE NIGHTFALL.
A STORM?
WE'RE NOT GONNA FLY
THROUGH THAT, ARE WE?
[OVER P.A.]
MORE SNOW?
AWESOME. I'M SKIING
WHISTLER THIS WEEKEND.
AH, NO SNOW. MORE RAIN.
[OVER P.A.] THE CAPTAIN SAID
IT'S GOING TO GET ROCKY.
WE MAY BE OVERNIGHTING
IN L.A.,
SO BE SURE THAT EVERYTHING
IS LOCKED DOWN TIGHT,
BECAUSE THIS FLIGHT
COULD GET HELLISH.
HELLISH?
WHAT DOES SHE MEAN
BY THAT, HELLISH?
[SIGHS]
Kit: OH, GOD.
MR. BREWSTER,
PLEASE SIT DOWN.
I WANT OFF.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT.
WE'RE STILL ON
THE GROUND, AREN'T WE?
THEN IT'S NOT TOO LATE.
I AM NOT FLYING THROUGH
ANY STORM. NO WAY.
IT'S NOT SAFE.
AND IT'S BAD KARMA.
LOOK, MR. BREWSTER,
PLEASE TRY TO UNDERSTAND.
EXCUSE ME. OUT OF MY WAY.
THANK YOU. EXCUSE ME.
[SPEAKING CZECH]
I'M SORRY
ABOUT THAT, SIR.
PLEASE,
EVERYONE JUST SIT DOWN.
Kit: ROW 16,
ON THE AISLE.
[SPEAKING CZECH]
YEAH.
Man: BOY, I COULD
USE A DRINK.
HAVE A GOOD FLIGHT.
THANKS.
OK, OK.
IT'S JUST A COUPLE OF HOURS,
NO BIG DEAL.
PRETTY SOON
IT'LL ALL BE OVER WITH.
THAT'S WHAT
I'M AFRAID OF.
[SIGHS]
DON'T WORRY, YOU GUYS.
EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
I HAVE A FEELING.
Controller:
TRANS-CON 110 HEAVY,
YOU ARE CLEARED THROUGH
RUNWAY 3-1 LEFT
VIA THE NOVEMBER
TAXI WAY.
TRANS-CON 110
TAXING TO RUNWAY 3-1 LEFT.
EXTERIOR LIGHTS ON.
TRANSPONDER
SET TO T.A.R.A.
Controller:
TRANS-CON 110 HEAVY,
CLEAR FOR TAKEOFF.
THANK YOU, TOWER.
TRANS-CON 110
ROLLING.
I HAVE 102%.
I HAVE 100 KNOTS.
AAH!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
P.A.: WE ARE EXPERIENCING
SOME SEVERE TURBULENCE.
OH, MY GOD.
UHH!
AAH! JESUS!
[SPEAKING CZECH]
MMM. MMM.
TAKE MINE.
HERE, TAKE IT.
[VOMITING]
P.A.: PLEASE, EVERYONE,
RETURN TO YOUR SEATS
AND FASTEN YOUR SEAT BELT.
THANK YOU.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THIS IS LLOYD REYNOLDS
YOUR CAPTAIN SPEAKING.
AS YOU NO DOUBT NOTICED,
WE HIT SOME UNSTABLE AIR
ON TAKEOFF,
BUT NOW THAT WE'RE
ABOVE THE STORM,
WE SHOULD HAVE
A SMOOTH RIDE.
I'LL BE TURNING OFF
THE SEAT BELT SIGN,
SO FEEL FREE TO MOVE
ABOUT THE CABIN.
JUST RELAX, SIT BACK,
AND ENJOY THE FLIGHT.
THANKS FOR CHOOSING
TRANS-CON.
[FAINT WHIRRING]
WHAT WAS THAT?
OH, IT'S, UH,
IT'S JUST THE LANDING GEAR.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
WHAT YOU JUST HEARD
WERE THE FLAPS
RETRACTING.
YOU SEE, IN A 747,
THE FLAP MECHANISM LOCKS
TO AVOID WING VORTEX DAMAGE
AT CRUISING SPEED.
IS THAT RIGHT?
THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
YES, WELL...
OH, WELL,
DON'T BE IMPRESSED.
I'M MORE SCARED
THAN ANYONE.
NO, I'M MORE SCARED
THAN YOU.
YEAH? YOU EVER BEEN
IN A CRASH?
YOU WERE IN A CRASH?
A PLANE CRASH?
[SIGHS] I, UH...
JUST--JUST--I'M SORRY.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID ANYTHING.
WHEN I GET NERVOUS,
I TALK A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
YES, WELL, YOU'VE
GOT IMPECCABLE TIMING.
WELL, JUST SAY
IT WASN'T DURING TAKEOFF
WITH A 747.
NO, ACTUALLY,
IT WAS, UM...
IT WAS DURING LANDING.
WE WERE COMING BACK
FROM A SKI TRIP,
AND WE WERE IN ONE OF
THOSE SMALL TURBO PROPS.
WAS ANYBODY HURT?
WELL, THERE WERE A LOT
OF BROKEN BONES,
AND, UH, ONE PERSON
WAS PARALYZED,
AND ANOTHER ONE
PASSED AWAY.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
HMM. THAT'S
THE FUNNY PART.
I...I GOT OUT
WITHOUT A SCRATCH.
BUT RIGHT AFTER THAT,
I SWITCHED ENGINEERING
SPECIALTIES
AND BEGAN STUDYING
AERONAUTICS.
SO YOU DECIDED TO DESIGN
AIRPLANES BECAUSE YOU CRASHED?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
BUT UNTIL THIS CLASS,
I NEVER SET FOOT
ON AN AIRPLANE AGAIN.
NOT EVEN THE ONES
THAT I HELPED ENGINEER.
I'M GONNA GET BACK
TO MY MAGAZINE.
ANYTHING
TO DRINK HERE?
OH, NO.
NO, THANK YOU.
WELL, YOU SEEM TO BE
HOLDING UP VERY WELL.
YES, WELL...
NOT MUCH WE CAN REALLY DO
AT THIS POINT, IS THERE?
APART FROM HAVING
A COMPLETE ANXIETY ATTACK.
[LAUGHS]
ACTUALLY, I KNOW...
AN EXCELLENT WAY
TO REDUCE STRESS.
I DON'T THINK
I OUGHT TO HEAR IT.
NO?
HERE'S SOME WATER.
MAKE IT
2 JOHNNY WALKER BLACKS.
ON THE ROCKS?
LOOK, JUST GIVE ME
THE BOTTLES.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD STICK
WITH THE WATER.
YOU KNOW, ELLIOT,
I JUST READ SOMETHING
ABOUT IN-FLIGHT
RELAXATION AND YOGA.
YES, WELL, I'D LOVE TO
HEAR ABOUT IT SOMETIME.
UH, I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT
WHEN YOU COME BACK.
SPLENDID.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SAFETY CHECK.
YOU AREN'T SMOKING
IN HERE, ARE YOU?
'CAUSE IF YOU ARE
THAT'S AGAINST
FEDERAL REGULATIONS.
YOU KNOW THAT,
DON'T YOU?
I'M GOING TO HAVE
TO DO A FULL EXAMINATION
OF THE AREA NOW.
DON'T LOCK IT, BECAUSE
IT MAKES ME FEEL LIKE--
YES, I KNOW. WELL, I'M HERE
TO HELP YOU CONQUER YOUR FEARS.
IT'S JUST TOO SMALL
IN HERE,
AND I CAN'T--
I CAN'T BREATHE.
LOOK AT ME, LOOK AT ME,
LOOK AT ME.
LOOK AT MY EYES.
LOOK ONLY AT ME.
LOOK AT ME,
LOOK AT ME.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
WELL, JUST THINK OF IT
AS A LITTLE, UH...
HANDS-ON EXERCISE
IS ALL.
SIT BACK, RELAX,
AND ENJOY.
WOULD YOU LIKE
ANOTHER, SIR?
[SPEAKING CZECH]
SURE, YOU GOT IT.
OH, MY GOD,
I GOT TO GET THESE SHOES.
THOSE ARE GREAT.
SO...WHAT DO YOU DO?
Both: WE WORK AT
THE KILAVEA BEACH CLUB.
[GIGGLING]
PAID TO PAR-TAY.
THAT'S COOL.
SO, UH, YOU GIRLS
GO ALL THE WAY?
TO HAWAII?
YEAH, TO HAWAII.
[GIGGLING]
I CAN'T.
SHH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
NO, I CAN'T, I CAN'T.
I CAN'T.
YES, YOU CAN.
NO, I CAN'T, I CAN'T.
NOT HERE, NOT NOW.
I CAN'T. I CAN'T
BREATHE IN HERE.
ALL RIGHT, I'M SORRY.
I GOT CARRIED AWAY.
I'M SORRY.
I UNDERSTAND.
DO YOU REALLY?
YES. RIGHT, RIGHT.
TIME AND A PLACE
FOR EVERYTHING, RIGHT?
YEAH.
WE'LL SAVE IT
FOR HAWAII.
HONEY.
I'M SORRY.
OHH.
TRANS-CON 110
TRACKING SOUTH-SOUTHWEST
OF PORTLAND V-O-R,
HEADING 1-6-5.
ARE YOU FINISHED, GENTLEMEN?
OH, THANKS, PEGGY.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
HI, PEGGY.
HERE YOU GO.
TRANS-CON 110
CLIMBING TO 3-3-0.
THE CONTROLS
ARE YOURS, TODD.
THANKS, LLOYD.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
GENTLEMEN...
I NEED TO MAKE
A PIT STOP.
AL, COULD YOU
GIVE ME A REPORT
ON THAT WEATHER SYSTEM?
YOU GOT IT.
HI.
THE MILE-HIGH CLUB
IS ALIVE AND WELL.
YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT?
HONEY, I FOUNDED IT.
SIR?
ARE YOU FINISHED
WITH THE GLASS?
AAH!
[SCREAMING]
ANYONE,
PLEASE OPEN THE DOOR!
HURRY!
CAPTAIN,
I'LL GET YOU OUT.
HEATHER!
ARE YOU OK?
YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
[SPEAKING CZECH]
SHIT!
GOD DAMN IT!
COME ON!
[SPEAKING CZECH]
CAPTAIN,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY'RE OUT COLD.
TODD MUST HAVE
DISENGAGED THE AUTOPILOT
WHEN HE FELL FORWARD.
WE'VE GOT PEOPLE UNCONSCIOUS
DOWNSTAIRS, TOO.
HIS PULSE IS FINE.
THANK GOD FOR THAT.
OK, UH, WE BETTER
MOVE THEM BACK
TO FIRST CLASS.
Sikes: THAT STORM
IS GAINING SPEED.
50 KNOTS.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO SHUT HER DOWN.
OK, PEOPLE,
THAT'S AN FAA LIMIT.
ALL OUTBOUNDS ARE GROUNDED.
REROUTE ALL THE INBOUNDS
AND NOTIFY SPOKANE.
SIR, TRANS-CON 110
IS DECLARING AN EMERGENCY.
REQUESTING VECTORS FOR
IMMEDIATE RETURN TO SEA-TAC.
CO-PILOT AND NAVIGATOR
ARE INCAPACITATED.
PUT IT ON SPEAKER.
Reynolds: SEATTLE CENTER,
TRANS-CON 110.
WE ARE DECLARING
AN EMERGENCY.
WE HAVE CREW
AND PASSENGERS DOWN.
REQUEST VECTORS
BACK TO SEA-TAC
AND MEDLINK TIE-IN.
UH, TRANS-CON 110.
GO TO HEADING 0-4-0.
BE ADVISED SEA-TAC IS CLOSED
DUE TO WEATHER CONDITIONS,
BUT WE WILL LAND YOU
WITH FAA EMERGENCY PROTOCOL.
UH, MAKE
YOUR ALTITUDE 2-0-0
AND COMMENCE FUEL DUMP FOR
EMERGENCY LANDING PROCEDURE.
TRANS-CON 110
DESCENDING TO 2-0-0.
CONFIRM HEADING 0-4-0.
WE ARE COMMENCING
THE FUEL DUMP.
[BEEPING]
Sikes: AT PRESENT TIME,
WE HAVE YOU
AT 27 MINUTES OUT.
EXCUSE ME A MINUTE.
I'M FEELING A BIT WOOZY.
BUT THEY'VE
ALL BEEN POISONED!
MA'AM, PLEASE!
WE HAVE TO TURN BACK.
MA'AM, PLEASE--
NO!
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
[SPEAKING CZECH]
Woman: YOU HAVE
TO LISTEN TO ME!
THEY'VE ALL BEEN
POISONED!
I KNOW IT! LOOK AT HER!
MA'AM, YOU NEED TO TRY
AND STAY CALM.
THAT'S HOW YOU CAN
HELP US RIGHT NOW.
Woman:
SHE WON'T WAKE UP!
IT'S OK. SHE WILL.
MA'AM, WE'RE DOING
EVERYTHING WE CAN.
SIR, PLEASE SIT DOWN.
EVERYTHING IS UNDER
CONTROL HERE.
NOW, WHAT DID
SHE HAVE TO EAT?
NOTHING.
WELL...
MAYBE SOME PEANUTS,
A CLUB SODA.
BUT THAT'S ALL.
WHAT ABOUT HIM?
I DON'T THINK
HE ATE ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW, BOTH OF THEM
JUST HAD WATER.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
IT'LL BE OK.
WHO PREPARED
THE DRINKS?
IN COACH, IT WAS
JUDY AND VIRGINIA,
BUT THEY'RE BOTH
UNCONSCIOUS NOW, TOO.
AND UP HERE IT WAS
THE NEW GUY--STANLEY.
Stanley: HERE'S
YOUR WATER, SIR.
NO, NO, NO.
HEY!
GET YOUR OWN, BUDDY!
DID YOU SEE THAT?
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
STANLEY NILES. WHY?
LET ME SEE
YOUR GODDAMN ID.
OK.
[KEYS JINGLE]
I--I DON'T HAVE IT
ON ME.
I MUST HAVE LEFT IT
AT HOME
BECAUSE I WAS IN A HURRY
AND I'M KINDA NEW
AND I DIDN'T
WANT TO BE LATE.
I WANT YOU TO STAY...
RIGHT HERE,
STANLEY.
WATCH HIM.
DON'T LET HIM MOVE.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
EVERYBODY CALM DOWN
AND BE QUIET.
I'M RUSS BELL,
TRANS-CON SECURITY.
I ASSURE YOU,
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE
IF EVERYBODY COOPERATES.
NOW, PLEASE--
SIR, SIT DOWN.
YES.
HOW MANY PEOPLE HAD A DRINK
SINCE THEY BOARDED?
HOW MANY HAD ICE
IN THEIR DRINK?
THANK YOU.
GET ME A PASSENGER LIST.
SURE.
HERE YOU GO.
DR. KESSLER?
YOU ARE A MEDICAL
DOCTOR, CORRECT?
DR. KESSLER?
DR. KESSLER, LISTEN TO ME,
WE NEED YOUR HELP.
[WHEEZING]
DR. KESSLER, LOOK AT ME.
YOU CAN DO IT.
I KNOW YOU CAN.
I CAN'T.
GET IT TOGETHER.
THESE PEOPLE MAY BE DYING.
[UNFASTENS SEAT BELT]
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
OH, MY GOD!
HELP! SOMEONE!
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
GET BACK!
GET ME SOME TOWELS! NOW!
TOWELS! ANYBODY! TOWELS!
HERE!
THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO STAY PUT.
WHAT, YOU THINK
I DID THIS, TOO?
[MEN SPEAKING CZECH]
Man: JOSEF.
[SPEAKING CZECH]
ALL RIGHT, I WANT
EVERYBODY IN THEIR SEAT.
MOVE.
Old man: OH.
NOBODY MOVES UNTIL WE
FIGURE THIS THING OUT.
[RADIO CHATTER]
[ALARM SOUNDS]
SHEAR ALARM, SIR.
TRANS-CON 110 HEAVY,
GROUND RADAR
SHOWS WIND SHEARS
DEVELOPING IN
YOUR FLIGHT PATH.
REDUCE SPEED TO 2-2-0 AND
AWAIT POSSIBLE REDIRECT.
ALSO, WE SHOW YOU A HALF-MILE
OFF YOUR CENTER LINE.
MAKE YOUR NEW HEADING 2-9-0
IN ORDER
TO REINTERCEPT ILS.
TRANS-CON 110,
CONFIRM. OVER.
Reynolds:
STAND BY, PLEASE.
STAND BY.
SEATTLE CENTER,
WE HAVE A FATALITY.
[ARGUING]
THIS ISN'T
SALMONELLA, BOTULISM,
ANY KIND OF
FOOD POISONING.
THESE PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN DRUGGED.
Elliott:
SORRY. SORRY.
[SHOUTING IN CZECH]
WHAT DID I TELL EVERYONE?
TO SIT DOWN!
KIT?
THOSE GUYS DON'T
UNDERSTAND ENGLISH.
WHAT LANGUAGE
ARE THEY SPEAKING?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
EXCUSE ME.
I--I THINK IT'S CZECH.
CZECH?
YEAH. I HEARD IT BEFORE
AT THE TICKET COUNTER.
MY GRANDMOTHER WAS POLISH.
I SPOKE IT AS A CHILD.
THE LANGUAGES
ARE SIMILAR.
THEY WERE TALKING
ABOUT SOMETHING
THEY BROUGHT
ON THE PLANE.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT
THE HELL IS GOING ON HERE.
[SCREAMING]
SEATTLE,
TRANS-CON 110
ENCOUNTERING
SEVERE TURBULENCE.
REQUESTING
A HIGHER ALTITUDE.
AAH! AAH!
OH!
WHAT THE HELL?
OH, MY GOD!
COME ON!
[SHOUTING]
KIT! CALL THE CAPTAIN!
OK!
[SHOUTING]
CAN YOU ASK HIM
WHO HE IS?
I ONLY KNOW POLISH,
AND NOT VERY MUCH OF IT.
TRY!
[SPEAKING POLISH]
[SPEAKING CZECH]
HE SAID--HE SAID
"BACK",
AND THE SECOND PART WAS
SOMETHING ABOUT MURDER.
HE'S JUST A...POSTMAN.
A POSTMAN.
UM, A DELIVERY MAN.
WHAT IS THAT?
IT LOOKS TOO SMALL
TO BE A BOMB.
I THINK HE USED
THE WORD "POISON."
AND--AND THE BUTTON
MAKES POISON.
IT'S A TRIGGER,
AND IT'S CONNECTED
TO THE CARGO AREA.
BELOW US?
[SPEAKS POLISH]
JA! JA!
I NEED BETTER
ANSWERS THAN THIS.
[SCREAMING]
JESS!
WHAT'S HE SAYING?
DON'T SHOOT,
OR HE'LL TRIGGER IT!
IT'LL SIGNAL
SOMETHING!
IT'LL DO SOMETHING!
2 CHEMICALS!
HE'S GONNA--
PUT THE GUN DOWN NOW!
PUT THE GUN DOWN!
PUT IT DOWN!
Bell: SORRY ABOUT THIS,
CAPTAIN.
[SPEAKING CZECH]
HE SAYS TO LAND
THE PLANE NOW,
OR ELSE HE'LL KILL
EVERYONE ON BOARD.
Sikes on radio:
TRANS-CON 110,
TERMINATE FUEL DUMP
AND STAND BY.
WHOA! WHOA! JUST TELL HIM
I'M TURNING ON THE RADIO
TO COMMUNICATE
WITH GROUND CONTROL.
TRANS-CON 110
TO SEATTLE CENTER.
WE HAVE A SPECIAL EMERGENCY,
SITUATION RED.
REPEAT, WE HAVE
A SITUATION RED.
Sikes: ROGER, WE HAVE
YOU SITUATION RED.
IS THE FLIGHT DECK
SECURE?
NEGATIVE. HE'S HERE.
Sikes:
CAN I SPEAK WITH HIM?
Reynolds: HE DOESN'T
SEEM TO SPEAK ENGLISH.
HE'S DEMANDING THAT
WE LAND IMMEDIATELY.
Sikes: NEGATIVE,
TRANS-CON 110.
WE'VE GOT CLASS ONE
MICROBURST WIND SHEARS.
REDIRECT TO CLEAR
AIR HOLDING PATTERN
OVER PACIFIC.
CIRCLE 75-MILE RADIUS
FROM VOR 2-2-8.
JUST INLAND
FROM THE COAST.
FUEL STATUS?
35,000 POUNDS.
FUEL IS LOW,
BUT IT'S ALSO LOW ON MY LIST
OF PRIORITIES RIGHT NOW.
UNDERSTOOD, 110.
CLIMB AND MAINTAIN 1-5-0,
CIRCLE ON AUTO.
WE'LL ADVISE FAA
SITUATION RED.
STAND BY.
TRANS-CON 110
CLIMBING 1-5-0.
CIRCLE ON AUTO.
YOU TELL OUR FRIEND
HERE THIS--
WE BARELY SCRAPED
OUT OF SEATTLE,
AND WE'RE RUNNING OUT
OF PLACES TO LAND
BY THE MINUTE REGARDLESS
OF WHAT HE WANTS.
WE HAVE TO HEAD BACK
TO A SAFER ALTITUDE AND WAIT
WITH LIMITED FUEL UNTIL WE GET
THE GREEN LIGHT TO LAND.
IF HE CAN'T WAIT AND
HE WANTS US ALL TO DIE,
YOU TELL HIM TO GO AHEAD
AND USE THE BOMB.
[THUNDER]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT DOES IT LOOK
LIKE I'M DOING?
[TURNS AIR ON]
MR. KAPINSKI--
GIMME A BREAK. WHAT
DIFFERENCE DOES IT MAKE?
SHUT UP AND GIVE ME
ONE OF THOSE.
OK.
UH, SIR, PORTLAND
IS STILL OFF-LINE,
SOCKED IN TO REDMOND.
TRANS-CON ONLY HAS ABOUT
60 MINUTES FLIGHT TIME.
YOU THINK WE SHOULD JUST
TAKE THE CHANCE BACK HERE?
OH...
EVERYTHING
WANTS THEM DOWN--
THE PILOT, FUEL TANKS,
THE TERRORIST.
EVERYTHING
EXCEPT THE WEATHER.
WELL, SOMETHING
MIGHT BREAK.
MR. SIKES?
DIRECTOR HOBBS,
FAA FLIGHTCON.
THIS IS LIEUTENANT
DICKSON OF THE FBI.
SEATTLE P.D. IS ON-SITE
WORKING WITH HIM.
EXCUSE ME.
TRANS-CON 110,
RADAR REPORTS YOU'RE IN
FOR SOME CHOP. OVER.
Reynolds: ROGER THAT,
SEATTLE CENTER.
SORRY.
HOW'S IT GOING?
OH...I'VE HAD
BETTER DAYS.
[MAN SHOUTING IN CZECH]
[WOMAN MOANS]
[THUNDER]
YAAH!
UNH!
AAH! AAH!
[WOMEN SCREAMING]
[SHOUTING]
AAH!
[SCREAMING]
SEATTLE CENTER,
TRANS-CON 110.
WE HAVE GUNFIRE
ON BOARD.
REPEAT, WE HAVE
GUNFIRE IN THE CABIN.
YAAH! YAAH!
[APPLAUSE]
YEAH!
THANKS.
THAT'S A GOOD JOB.
Martin: YES, ELLIOTT, THAT WAS
VERY COURAGEOUS OF YOU.
I GUESS FEAR DOES
WEIRD THINGS TO PEOPLE.
I DON'T LIKE VIOLENCE.
I DON'T LIKE
BEING THREATENED.
NO, OBVIOUSLY NOT.
OBVIOUSLY, IT BROUGHT OUT
THE BEST IN YOU.
I NOTICED IN ALL THE CONFUSION
THAT HE DROPPED THE DETONATOR.
I ALSO NOTICED
THAT YOU PICKED IT UP
AND PUT IT IN YOUR POCKET.
YOU OBSERVED A LOT
FROM YOUR SEAT.
YES, I DID.
WHERE DID YOU
PUT IT?
WELL...
I WOULDN'T DO THAT
IF I WERE YOU.
I NEED TO SHOW YOU
SOMETHING.
ALLOW ME?
UH-UH.
BRITISH INTELLIGENCE?
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
TAKE A GOOD LOOK
UNTIL YOU'RE SATISFIED.
AND PUT THE GUN AWAY,
WILL YOU?
I THINK WE'VE ALL HAD
QUITE ENOUGH OF THAT.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
HE WAS TELLING THE TRUTH.
THERE IS A TOXIN ON BOARD.
IT'S A BINARY NERVE GAS.
CAME OUT OF TURKMENISTAN.
IT'S A LITTLE LEFTOVER
FROM LESS STABLE DAYS.
ONCE DETONATED,
IT MIXES IN 15 SECONDS,
AND EVERY LIVING THING
IN A 5-MILE RADIUS DIES.
SO YOU'RE--
YOU'RE THE ONE
TAKING THESE GUYS OUT?
TAKING
EVERYBODY OUT?
I AM UNDER ORDERS
TO TRACK THESE FOUR
AND RECOVER
THE TOXIN.
SO BY JOINING THE CLASS,
THE AIRLINE LETS YOU ON
THE PLANE A HALF-HOUR EARLY,
AND YOU HAVE ACCESS TO
ALL THE RESTRICTED AREAS.
ACCESS TO THE ICE BINS.
YES. VERY GOOD.
SO YOU DOPED
THE ENTIRE PLANE?
IT'S A SIMPLE SPRAY.
A TRANQUILIZER.
EVERYBODY WILL BE AWAKE
BY OUR ARRIVAL.
THE THING I DON'T
UNDERSTAND,
IS WHY GO AFTER
THESE GUYS ON A PLANE?
SEEMS LIKE AN AWFULLY
CROWDED PLACE
FOR AN ARREST,
DOESN'T IT?
IT'S THE ONLY PLACE
THEY'RE VULNERABLE.
IF YOU KNEW
THE KIND OF ARTILLERY
THESE BLOKES CARRY,
YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
NOW, I NEED TO SPEAK
WITH THE CAPTAIN.
[MAN SHOUTS IN CZECH]
HE SAYS YOU'RE LYING.
LOOK, I KNOW I HAVEN'T
BEEN UP FRONT WITH YOU,
BUT YOU CAN
UNDERSTAND WHY.
I THINK OUR CZECH FRIENDS
HAVE SAID AND DONE ENOUGH.
NOW, WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
[MAN SPEAKING CZECH]
HE SAYS WE SHOULD
TIE YOU UP, TOO,
AND GIVE THAT
TO THE PILOT.
[MAN SPEAKING CZECH]
OR ELSE WE'RE ALL DEAD.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY.
LOOK, I UNDERSTAND
YOUR CONCERN.
THIS MAN
IS A TERRORIST.
HE'S ALREADY HELD
THE ENTIRE PLANE--
HELD ALL OF US HOSTAGE!
ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S ENOUGH.
I DON'T RECOGNIZE
YOUR AUTHORITY
ON THIS AIRCRAFT.
I'M IN CONTROL HERE.
NOW GIVE ME
THE DETONATOR.
[LAUGHS]
NO, THIS ISN'T
GOING TO WORK.
NOW!
[PASSENGERS SCREAMING]
OH, SHIT!
[NO ACCENT] WELL, THAT
SHUT YOU UP, DIDN'T IT?
NOT THINKING ABOUT
THE FLIGHT ANYMORE
ARE YOU, MARTIN?
[PASSENGERS SOBBING]
SORRY.
REALLY.
ALL I NEEDED WERE
THE LUGGAGE TAGS
AND THE DETONATOR
AND THAT WOULD HAVE
BEEN IT, YOU KNOW?
THEY JUST WEREN'T
THIRSTY ENOUGH, I GUESS.
THEN THE WORLD'S
GREATEST DAD HERE
HAS TO PLAY
JUNIOR DETECTIVE.
ALL RIGHT,
THE CABIN IS YOURS.
BUT PLEASE TRY
TO REMAIN SEATED
WHILE THE SEAT BELT LIGHT
IS ILLUMINATED.
ANYBODY WHO DOESN'T...
DIES.
OH, AND THANKS FOR
FLYING TRANS-CON.
WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU?
I'M YOUR NEW BOSS.
[THUNDER]
IN CASE
YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
HE'S TOASTING US
ONE AT A TIME HERE.
I SAY WE STAY PUT.
NO. I TELL YOU,
WE CAN STOP HIM.
EVEN WITH A GUN.
HE HAS CONTROL
OF THE TOXIN, TOO.
YEAH. OR DID YOU
FORGET THAT?
NO, NOT AT ALL.
IN FACT, THAT'S WHY
WE HAVE TO ACT NOW.
I THINK WE SHOULD WORRY
ABOUT STAYING ALIVE UP HERE.
LET THE POLICE OR THE FBI
OR WHOEVER HANDLE IT.
YOU'RE TRUSTING THE SITUATION
IS GONNA GET BETTER.
LOOK WHAT HE'S ALREADY DONE.
HE'S UP IN THE COCKPIT
RIGHT NOW,
CONFIDENT THAT
WE'RE ALL COWARDS.
THIS MAY BE OUR ONLY
CHANCE TO STOP HIM.
THE ONLY HOPE,
NOT JUST FOR US,
BUT FOR A MILLION
OTHER PEOPLE AS WELL.
I'M IN.
ME, TOO.
ME, THREE.
ALL RIGHT.
LOOK, YOU KNOW, WE'VE
ALREADY DUMPED FUEL.
WE'VE GOT A HALF-HOUR
LEFT IF WE'RE LUCKY.
SEATTLE'S
THE ONLY GAME IN TOWN.
I'LL MAKE THAT DECISION
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
[LAUGHS]
ALL RIGHT...
YOU ARE GONNA HAVE
A LITTLE QUIET TIME...
WHILE I GO MAKE
SOME NOISE.
WELL, HOW'S EVERY
LITTLE THING DOWN HERE?
UNH. REMEMBER...
JUST SIT BACK, RELAX.
YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
ELLIOTT?
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
WHAT?
I'LL TAKE THAT.
Man: IS EVERYBODY OK?
OK, I GOT HIM COVERED.
ALL RIGHT, GET UP.
NOW!
SLOWLY.
[LAUGHS]
Drake: WATCH IT.
Man: JUST
SHOOT HIM.
NOW GET BACK! MOVE!
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
I WAS STARTING TO WONDER
IF THEY HAD THE BALLS.
THESE GUYS? BARELY.
THE WOMEN MAYBE.
Woman: OH, MY GOD!
[SOBBING]
[UNCOCKS GUN]
UNH!
[MARTIN GROANS]
NICE TALKING TO YOU.
KEEP AN EYE
ON EVERYBODY.
Man:
NO PROBLEM.
NOW YOU KNOW
THE ONES TO WATCH.
I'LL KEEP THEM IN LINE.
AND STAY THERE!
[SOBBING]
[COCKPIT DOOR OPENS]
UH...
I NEED TO CHECK
WITH SEATTLE.
I NEED THE RADIO
BACK ONLINE.
UNACCEPTABLE.
LOOK, WE HAVE
NO CHOICE.
SEATTLE HAS THE GROUND
WARNING RADAR SYSTEM.
SO UNLESS YOU WANT
THOSE WINDSHEARS
TO SLAM US INTO
THE RUNWAY ON LANDING,
YOU GOTTA DO WHAT I SAY.
LOOK, I WANT YOU
TO UNDERSTAND SOMETHING--
[GUNSHOTS]
AAH!
EXCUSE ME, I--I HAVE
TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
LOOK, I'M
NOT STUPID, LADY.
COME ON.
I'M NOT GONNA
FALL FOR THAT.
YOU CAN CONTROL THE PLANE,
BUT NOT MY BLADDER.
[WHISPERING]
This is a passenger
on Trans-Con flight 110.
I need to reach Seattle
Flight Control immediately.
YOU CAN WATCH
IF YOU WANT TO.
FINE.
JUST KEEP
THE DOOR OPEN.
This is an emergency.
ARE YOU GONNA BEHAVE?
YAAH!
Yes, thank you.
Would you please just
connect me immediately?
Harold: MARTIN.
MARTIN!
WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO PULL?
Woman: SEATTLE
INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
UNH!
SON OF A...
GET THE ICE!
AAH! GET OFF ME! AAH!
OPEN UP!
THIS'LL HELP.
SAY "AHH,"
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
[GAGGING]
SAY "AHH"!
NOW!
[GASPING]
[THUNDER]
HELLO, OPERATOR?
YES, THIS IS A PASSENGER
ON TRANS-CON FLIGHT 110.
PLEASE LISTEN TO ME.
THIS IS AN EMERGENCY.
WE'VE BEEN TAKEN HOSTAGE.
[CLICK]
HELLO?
[STATIC]
SHIT!
TRANS-CON 110 HEAVY,
DO YOU COPY? OVER.
WE HAVE HIM ON RADAR
AND ON TRANSPONDER.
TRACKING NORTH-NORTHWEST
3-3-0 NOW.
HE'S STILL IN PATTERN.
BUT WHY AREN'T
THEY ANSWERING?
WHAT TERRORISTS HAVE
NO DEMANDS TO RADIO IN?
CIRCLING, NO GAS,
AND NO INTENTION TO LAND?
I'D SAY A SUICIDAL ONE.
[DIALING]
GUESS WHO.
YEAH, WE'RE STILL ON.
YEAH.
SHUT UP. SHUT UP.
I NEED YOU TO LISTEN
TO ME CAREFULLY.
[SIGHS]
HE KILLED THE PHONES.
HE KNOWS THE PLANE.
WE GOTTA FIND A WAY TO
GET RID OF THOSE TOXINS.
WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
[SIGHS]
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT WE CAN GET
THE CLAIM TICKETS
OFF THESE GUYS,
WE CAN FIND THEIR BAGS AND
FIGURE OUT HOW TO DUMP THEM.
IF IT LANDS IN THE OCEAN OR
EVEN AN UNPOPULATED AREA,
EVEN IF IT DETONATES,
IT WON'T HURT ANYBODY.
HOW ARE WE GONNA
DUMP A BAG?
THERE'S HUNDREDS OF BAGS.
HOW ARE YOU GONNA FIND IT?
HOW DO WE EVEN KNOW
WHAT'S BELOW US?
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO GET
AHOLD OF THE CONTROL TOWER.
YOU SAID ALL
THE PHONES WERE OUT.
WELL, THEY ARE,
BUT I HAVE AN IDEA.
NOW, THERE'S A SECOND
RADIO ACCESS POINT
IN THE EQUIPMENT BAY.
THE GROUND CREWS USE IT
TO TALK TO THE TOWER.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
WON'T ELLIOTT HEAR THAT
IN THE COCKPIT?
YEAH, BUT MAYBE...
WE CAN USE THE VOR
AND SEND A SIGNAL
TO THE GROUND
THAT LETS THEM KNOW
TO CHANGE
THE RADIO FREQUENCY.
MAYBE WE CAN BYPASS
THE COCKPIT.
I'M COMING WITH YOU.
WHAT ARE OUR ASSETS SO FAR?
Radio: THE SNIPERS
WILL HAVE
A CLEAR SIGHTLINE
FROM THE TERMINAL.
WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON UP THERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
110 IS UNRESPONSIVE
TO HAILS.
THAT LAST REPORT
HAD GUNSHOTS ABOARD,
BUT SHE'S CIRCLING
STEADILY.
[STATIC CRACKLING]
WHAT IS THAT?
Hobbs: IT'S STATIC.
STORM'S INTERFERING
WITH THE VOR SUBSYSTEM.
[RHYTHMIC CRACKLING]
THAT'S NOT THE STORM.
IT SOUNDS TOO REGULAR
FOR STATIC.
IT'S LIKE A PATTERN.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
Sikes: MORSE CODE?
SHORT, SHORT, SHORT,
LONG, LONG, LONG,
SHORT, SHORT, SHORT.
THAT'S AN SOS.
WRITE IT DOWN.
RIGHT.
[CLICKING]
[HATCH DOOR CLOSES]
HEY.
I GOT THE CLAIM TICKETS.
GREAT. GOOD JOB.
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING, RIGHT?
YOU KIDDING ME?
I DESIGN THESE THINGS
FOR A LIVING.
NO. I MEAN
THE MORSE CODE.
YEAH, WELL, I THINK SO.
GOT A BUDDY THROUGH
A FEW FINALS WITH IT.
"A" IS A DOT-DASH.
A TAP OF THE FOOT,
THEN A DRAG.
YOU USED IT
TO CHEAT ON TESTS?
I
DIDN'T CHEAT.
HE CHEATED.
I JUST TAPPED MY FOOT.
MUST HAVE BEEN
A GOOD FRIEND.
NO, NOT REALLY, BUT
HE HAD A CUTE SISTER.
I SEE. YOU JUST USED IT
TO GET A DATE.
BETTER THAN THAT.
I MARRIED HER.
THAT WAS OUR SON TREVOR
YOU SAW BACK
AT THE AIRPORT.
FOR SOME REASON I DIDN'T
THINK YOU WERE MARRIED.
I'M NOT ANYMORE.
MY WIFE DIED RIGHT AFTER
TREVOR WAS BORN.
"TRUNS-COP 1-1-0 TO
SEUGO FRED 2-2-1."
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
THEIR RADIO MUST BE OUT.
WHY ELSE WOULD THEY BE
SENDING MORSE CODE
ON THE VOR SYSTEM?
UM, F-R-E-D.
MAYBE THAT'S SUPPOSED
TO BE F-R-E-Q.
FREQUENCY 221.
"GO FREQUENCY 221."
GET ON 221. SEE IF YOU
CAN PICK ANYTHING UP.
YOU GOT IT.
[TAPS KEYBOARD]
SHE WAS THE PASSENGER
THAT DIED
IN THAT PLANE CRASH.
YEAH.
YEAH. I NEVER THOUGHT
I WOULD FLY AGAIN,
BUT AT LEAST MAYBE
I CAN MAKE IT SAFER
FOR THOSE WHO DID.
WANT TO KEEP AN EYE
ON THE HATCH?
YEAH.
[FLIPS SWITCHES]
TESTING, 1, 2, 3.
Martin:
DO YOU READ ME?
WHAT WAS THAT?
THIS IS TRANS-CON 110.
DO YOU COPY?
TRANS-CON 100 HEAVY.
WE READ YOU
LOUD AND CLEAR.
WHAT IS YOUR STATUS?
WE HAVE AN EMERGENCY.
WHERE'S THE CAPTAIN?
WE DON'T KNOW. WE THINK
HE MIGHT'VE BEEN KILLED.
UM...
MY NAME IS
MARTIN MESSERMAN.
I'M WITH THE FEAR
OF FLYING GROUP.
YOU--YOU MIGHT
REMEMBER ME.
I'M THE ONE WHO PASSED OUT
IN THE CONTROL TOWER.
OH, RIGHT.
I REMEMBER.
WELL, WE'VE BEEN HIJACKED,
AND THERE IS
A CHEMICAL WEAPON ON BOARD.
WE ARE AWARE
OF THE HIJACK SITUATION.
WHAT, UH...
WHAT TYPE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS
ARE WE DEALING WITH HERE?
Martin:
IT'S SOME KIND OF GAS.
I DON'T KNOW
THE SPECIFICS,
BUT HE SAID THAT
IT WOULD KILL EVERYTHING
WITHIN A 5-MILE RADIUS.
IT'S IN THE CARGO BAY
IN--IN ONE OF THE PIECES
OF LUGGAGE.
WE DON'T KNOW WHICH ONE.
WE NEED TO FIND A WAY
TO GET IT OFF THE PLANE.
Sikes: ALL RIGHT,
MARTIN, ALL RIGHT.
YOU JUST STAND BY.
GET FIELD OPS
ON THE LINE.
NOTIFY THE DIRECTOR.
TELL HIM ABOUT
THE SITUATION,
PRIORITY ALPHA.
WE'LL DO EVERYTHING
WE CAN TO HELP YOU.
THANK YOU.
I'M GOING TO NEED A FEW
OTHER THINGS FROM UPSTAIRS.
OK.
LOOK, I'M THE ONE WHO
FOUND OUT ABOUT THESE GUYS,
AND I'M THE ONE WHO HAD
THE BALLS AND THE BRAINS
TO SNAG
THEIR PRECIOUS PACKAGE,
SO YOU JUST HANDLE
YOUR END, OK?
OHH!
SORRY. WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING FOR?
UM, WE NEED DETERGENT
AND DESSERT GELATIN.
OH, AND WE NEED
RALPH'S NITRO PILLS.
I'LL GET THOSE.
OH, I NEED
YOUR CIGARETTES--
ALL OF THEM.
HERE, YOU MIGHT AS WELL
TAKE THE LIGHTER.
THANKS.
SORRY.
Sikes: NOW, IF THEY WERE
THE LAST TO BOARD,
THE TOXIN
WOULD PROBABLY BE
IN ONE OF
THE FIRST THREE BINS
ON THE PORT SIDE.
3 BINS.
COPY THAT.
WE HAVE YOU
AT 15,000 FEET
OVER WASHINGTON
COASTLINE,
APPROACHING
A LARGE BODY OF WATER
CALLED GRAY'S HARBOR.
IN ABOUT
7 OR 8 MINUTES,
YOU'LL BE OVER IT.
IF HE MAINTAINS
SAME COURSE AND SPEED,
YOU'LL HAVE
A 3-MINUTE WINDOW
BY WHICH TO DUMP
THE CONTAINER
BEFORE HITTING
POPULATED LAND.
REMEMBER THIS--
YOU MUST DROP IT
OVER WATER.
THEY'RE GOING
TO DOWN THE PLANE
IF IT MOVES INLAND
WITH CHEMICALS ON BOARD.
WHAT WAS THAT, SEATTLE?
COULD YOU PLEASE REPEAT?
DID YOU SAY
DOWN THE PLANE?
PLEASE CONFIRM.
THIS DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
THERE ARE INNOCENT PEOPLE
ON BOARD THIS PLANE.
WE CAN'T EVACUATE
EVERYONE IN TIME.
WE'RE TALKING A WEAPON
OF MASS DESTRUCTION
AND A HALF A MILLION
PEOPLE
ON THAT FLIGHT PATH.
WE HAVE TO ACT NOW.
YOU'LL GUARANTEE
AUTHORIZATION?
I MEAN, ROCK-SOLID,
STAND BY IT ALL THE WAY?
THE PRESS, THE INVESTIGATION,
THE WORKS?
BECAUSE THE FAA'S
NOT GOING TO DESTROY
A PLANELOAD OF
INNOCENT PASSENGERS
UNLESS YOU GUYS TAKE
FULL RESPONSIBILITY.
WE'VE CONFIRMED
THE IDENTITIES.
CZECH INTELLIGENCE
HAS ALSO CONFIRMED
THE THEFT OF A TYPE ONE
VIRAL DISPERSION DEVICE
APPROXIMATELY
2 WEEKS AGO,
AND THEY CONCUR ON
THE TRAIL TO FLIGHT 110.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
THIS IS ON FBI DIRECTOR
AUTHORITY ALONE.
Man: UM...
I'VE GOT BREMERTON
NAVAL AIR STATION.
THEY'RE TRACKING,
BUT THEY WANT
SECONDARY AUTHORIZATION
FROM FAA.
LET ME TALK TO THEM.
Sikes:
MARTIN, LISTEN.
THEY ARE PREPARED
TO SHOOT YOU DOWN
IF YOU MOVE OVER
ANY POPULATED AREAS.
THIS IS BEYOND
MY CONTROL.
MY GOD,
THIS IS CRAZY.
YOU CAN DO IT.
BELIEVE ME,
I KNOW YOU CAN.
OK...
UNDERSTOOD.
WHAT ABOUT
THE BIN NUMBERS?
HANG ON.
Sikes: WE'RE TRYING
TO MATCH THEM NOW.
HOLD ON.
YOU GOT A PEN?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, HERE GOES.
BIN NUMBER A-4-5--
HELLO?
HELLO, SEA-TAC CONTROL,
DO YOU READ ME?
Martin: YOU GOT
THAT CIGARETTE?
YEAH. HAROLD
MADE A BIG SACRIFICE.
HE PROBABLY NEEDS
A NICOTINE PATCH
THE SIZE OF NEBRASKA
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
WELL, THANK GOD
FOR THE TOBACCO COMPANIES.
THIS IS ONE BAD HABIT THAT'S
GOING TO SAVE OUR LIVES.
HERE YOU GO.
OK, STEP BACK.
[PEOPLE SCREAM]
OH, GOD.
UHH! UHH! UHH!
CHECK THAT FIRST BIN
FOR A-4-5.
HERE. THIS ONE
SAYS A-4-5.
SO DOES THIS ONE.
GREAT.
THIS ONE DOES, TOO.
SHIT. WITHOUT
THE REST OF THE NUMBER,
IT'S GOING TO BE
LIKE TRYING TO FIND
A NEEDLE
IN A HAYSTACK.
WE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO CONTACT THEM AGAIN.
WHAT?
WE DON'T HAVE TIME,
AND THE PHONES ARE OUT,
AND SO IS THE RADIO.
SHIT.
IF WE JUST HAD A...
WAIT A MINUTE.
A CELL PHONE? THAT DON'T
WORK ON A PLANE.
I GOT AN IDEA.
WHAT? WAIT.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
DOESN'T A CELL PHONE
INTERFERE
WITH THE NAVIGATIONAL
SYSTEM?
NO, IT DOESN'T.
IT WORKS OVER LAND CELL
SITES UP TO 10,000 FEET.
WELL, THEN WHY DO THEY
TELL YOU NOT TO USE THEM?
BECAUSE THEY WANT YOU
TO USE
THEIR
PHONES.
WHY? WHAT'S
THE DIFFERENCE?
ABOUT 3 BUCKS A MINUTE.
I'M GOING TO, UH...
USE THE SPOILER...
TRY TO GET US LOWER
WHERE THE CELL PHONES
ARE WORKING.
OK.
WE NEED TO GET
TO 10,000 FEET ANYWAY
TO OPEN THE BAY DOORS.
OTHERWISE, WE'LL BE SUCKED
OUT BY THE DECOMPRESSION.
[ALARM BEEPING]
SHIT.
GREAT.
I'VE GOT A SIGNAL.
COME ON.
YES. IN SEATTLE,
SEA-TAC AIRPORT,
AIR TRAFFIC CONTROL.
YOU'RE CALLING
INFORMATION?
YEAH.
COULD YOU HOLD THIS?
HELLO?
[STRAINS]
[SCREAMING]
WHOA, GOD.
DAMN IT, NOW WHAT?
PRESSURE.
IF IT CROSSES
THE COASTLINE
AND THAT SARIN GAS
DETONATES,
WE'RE LOOKING
AT A CATASTROPHE.
WE'RE LOOKING AT ONE
EITHER WAY.
A 747 JETLINER--
MY GOD.
SIR, THERE'S SOMEONE
ON THE LINE
CLAIMING THEY'RE
ON THE TRANS-CON FLIGHT.
WELL,
PUT HIM THROUGH.
UHH!
AAH!
WHAT IS IT
WITH YOU PEOPLE?
GOD!
Sikes: 1-1-4.
COPY. A-4-5-1-1-4.
OK, WE'RE LOOKING.
STAND BY.
I GOT IT.
WHERE SHOULD WE
MOVE IT?
PUSH IT OUT OF THE WAY.
WHAT? NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO.
SHE'S FINE.
YOU'RE COMFORTABLE,
RIGHT?
NICE FASHION STATEMENT.
YOU LOOK LIKE A DUCK.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO STAY PUT!
NOW, DO YOU WANT TO DIE?
HUH?
NO!
HUH? ALL YOU BASKET CASES!
DO YOU WANT TO DIE?
THIS ONE DOESN'T HAVE
A TAG ON IT. LOOK.
OPEN IT UP.
Jessica:
WHAT'S THIS?
THAT'S NOT IT.
IT'S A LOCATOR.
GPS BACKPACKING EQUIPMENT.
KEEP LOOKING.
TRANS-CON 110...
I MEAN, MARTIN,
YOU HAVE LESS THAN 2 MINUTES
BEFORE YOU HIT LAND.
CAN YOU CONFIRM
THAT YOU HAVE THE TOXIN?
SHIT.
BREMERTON,
PLEASE STAND BY.
HERE IT IS.
LOOK.
UHH!
OPEN THIS DOOR!
OPEN THIS FUCKING DOOR,
OR EVERYBODY DIES!
AAH!
Martin:
GET DOWN!
GET DOWN.
PUSH! PUSH!
AAH! AAH!
[GUNSHOTS]
[CLICK CLICK
CLICK CLICK]
DAMN IT!
COME ON!
OUR RADAR SHOWS THEY CROSSED
OVER GRAY'S HARBOR,
AND WE HAVE
NO CONFIRMATION
THE TOXIN
HAS BEEN DROPPED.
[BEEPING]
DAMN IT!
THIS FLIGHT
IS GETTING EXPENSIVE.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE
TO GET A SIGNAL AGAIN
UNTIL WE'RE OVER LAND.
BREMERTON...
YOU ARE GO FOR LAUNCH.
I REPEAT--YOU ARE GO
FOR LAUNCH.
THE RADAR'S LOCKED.
MISSILE BATTERY LAUNCHING.
GOD HELP US.
HERE, CATCH.
Man: OH, MY GOD!
DON'T DROP IT!
OH, IT DOESN'T MATTER
ANYMORE.
WELL, YOUR BRAVE
EXPEDITION PARTY
JUST HAD THEMSELVES
AN ANTHRAX COCKTAIL
IN THE LOUNGE BELOW.
NOW, I SEALED THE LOWER DECK,
SO IF WE'RE LUCKY,
THE WIND DOWNSTAIRS
MIGHT SAVE US.
IF NOT,
THESE MARGARINE CUPS
WON'T HELP ANY.
SO, GIVEN THAT
UNFORTUNATE LOSS,
I'M FORCED TO IMPROVISE,
AND I'M IN A REALLY...
BAD MOOD.
SEA-TAC?
IT'S FLIGHT 110.
I'VE GOT HIM.
110, WE CONFIRM YOU HAVE
DROPPED OVER WATER.
BREMERTON,
BELAY THAT ORDER.
BREMERTON, DO NOT LAUNCH.
I REPEAT--
DO NOT LAUNCH.
SIR, THE MISSILES
ARE ALREADY AWAY.
WE HAVE THEM LOCKED ON
AND TRACKING TO THE TARGET.
SEATTLE, IT'S GONE.
HELLO?
HELLO, SEATTLE?
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
SHIT.
WE LOST THE SIGNAL.
ABORT THE MISSILES.
I REPEAT--
ABORT AND SELF-DESTRUCT.
ROGER. SENDING
ABORT SEQUENCE NOW.
[BEEPING]
Elliott: WHO WOULD'VE THOUGHT
THAT YOU FREQUENT CRIERS
WOULD BE MY BEST TICKET
OUT OF THIS MESS?
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO FETCH,
BUT WE'LL SEE.
FIRST, THOUGH, I NEED...
A VOLUNTEER FOR
A PATRIOTIC MISSION.
DAMN!
HE MUST'VE LOCKED IT.
OH, WHAT ARE WE
GOING TO DO?
[SIGHS]
FOLLOW ME.
COME ON.
I--I CAN'T GO IN THERE.
JUST PRETEND IT'S ONE OF
THE EXERCISES IN CLASS.
I CAN'T.
COME ON. I'LL BE
RIGHT NEXT TO YOU.
WE DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
IT'S OK.
COME ON, NOW,
THIS IS GOING TO BE FUN!
ALL RIGHT, NO VOLUNTEERS?
LET'S TAKE A VOTE.
WHO'S THE BIGGEST PAIN
IN THE ASS ON THIS FLIGHT?
HERE, CONTESTANT
NUMBER ONE.
RIGHT HERE.
COME ON, PEOPLE,
I WANT TO SEE SOME HANDS.
COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON, COME ON!
HANDS! IF YOU DON'T VOTE,
YOU DIE!
[LAUGHS]
WHAT'D YOU DO TO HIM?
ALL RIGHT,
HOW ABOUT OUR TEACHER?
RIGHT HERE.
HOW ABOUT HER?
HOW ABOUT THEM RIGHT HERE?
HER? HIM, HER?
DUCK, DUCK, GOOSE?
PEOPLE, COME ON. YOU ARE ALL
REGISTERED TO VOTE.
HOW ABOUT HER?
HOW ABOUT HIM
RIGHT HERE?
YOU'RE--YOU'RE
A LAWYER, RIGHT?
HOW ABOUT THE LAWYER?
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW,
I'M NOT SEEING ANY HANDS.
NOW, I KNOW YOU HATE
THIS GUY!
YOU KNOW WHAT? WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO FLIP FOR IT.
OK, HERE WE GO.
HEADS, IT'S THE TAXMAN.
TAILS,
ONE LESS LITIGATOR.
OH, NO.
DAMN.
IT'S LOCKED.
[GASPING]
IT'S TAILS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THESE MOTHERFUCKERS
HAVE AUDITED ME
FOR THE PAST 2 YEARS.
[WHIMPERS]
NO.
I'M JUST FUCKING
WITH YOU.
OK, LET'S GO.
WHAT IS--
COME ON, GO UPSTAIRS.
LET'S GO.
LISTEN, I CAN NEGOTIATE
FOR YOU ON THE GROUND.
GOOD. UP.
NO, WAIT!
WELL...
IF IT ISN'T
THE MOUSEKETEERS.
I GOT TO SAY,
I'M IMPRESSED.
OHH!
WELL, COUNSELOR...
I GUESS THIS IS
YOUR LUCKY DAY.
IF YOU KILL ME,
YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO LAND THE PLANE.
YOU SHOT THE ILS SYSTEM.
GO AHEAD. LOOK.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
AUTOPILOT
CAN'T LAND THE PLANE
WITHOUT AN ILS LINE
TO FOLLOW.
IT WON'T KNOW OUR POSITION
RELATIVE TO THE GROUND
UNTIL WE SMASH INTO IT
ANYWAY.
IF WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
ANY CHANCE AT ALL,
YOU NEED ME ALIVE.
I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO HAS A SHOT
AT LANDING THIS PLANE.
YOU?
MR. FEARFUL FLYER?
WITHOUT AN ILS LINE,
IN LOW VISIBILITY,
WITH 15 MINUTES OF FUEL?
HOW ARE YOU GOING
TO MANAGE THAT?
IN THE BAGGAGE AREA,
WE FOUND A GPS.
IT'S A GLOBAL
POSITIONING SYSTEM.
WITH IT, WE CAN FIX
OUR POSITION
ALL THE WAY
TO THE GROUND.
YOU NEED ME...
AND NOT JUST
TO RIG THE EQUIPMENT.
YOU MAY BE ABLE TO PROGRAM
THE AUTOPILOT,
BUT FLYING THE PLANE SOLO
AND LANDING IT,
THAT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT
BALL GAME ALL TOGETHER.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
Elliott: GO.
IT'S OK.
[GASPS]
[BEEPS]
Jessica:
FOUND IT.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
HERE.
PUT THIS UP
TO THE PC CONNECTOR.
IT'S THERE ON THE FLOOR.
OK.
[LINE RINGING]
Martin: ALL RIGHT.
GOOD. WE'RE ACQUIRING
SATELLITES.
IT'S ME.
GOT A PEN?
YEAH.
UH-HUH.
OK, I GOT IT.
OK.
HERE GOES.
I'M GOING TO NEED
TO LAND MANUALLY,
AND I'LL NEED ACCESS
TO THE RADIO
TO MAKE SURE
AIR TRAFFIC IS CLEAR.
ALL RIGHT, FINE,
BUT IF YOU TRY ANYTHING,
SHE DIES.
WHAT IS THIS ALL FOR?
MONEY.
IT MAKES THE WORLD
GO ROUND.
SO YOU JUST WANTED
TO SELL IT?
NO. WE WERE MORE
INTERESTED IN USING IT.
IN THE RIGHT PLACE,
AT THE RIGHT TIME,
A GOOD, SOLID
TERRORIST THREAT
IS MUCH MORE
FINANCIALLY REWARDING.
ALL RIGHT.
GO AHEAD.
TRANS-CON 110
TO SEATTLE CENTER, OVER.
Sikes: SEATTLE CENTER.
GO AHEAD.
THIS IS MARTIN.
I HAVE AN UPDATE
FOR YOU.
I'M NOW AT THE WHEEL.
I'M GOING TO NEED
A LITTLE HELP.
THE HIJACKER IS HERE
WITH ME,
AND I'M COMING IN
TO LAND.
TELL THEM
YOU WANT TO REFUEL.
WE WANT TO REFUEL.
NO POLICE,
NO ARMED PERSONNEL.
YOU WILL AWAIT
FURTHER INSTRUCTIONS.
NO POLICE,
NO ARMED PERSONNEL.
AWAIT FURTHER
INSTRUCTIONS.
I CAN KEEP
THE POLICE BACK,
BUT I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
ABOUT THE WEATHER.
ARE YOU ORDERING MY MEN
BACK ON FAA AUTHORITY?
WELL, I DON'T SEE
ANY OTHER WAY AROUND IT.
YOU WANT MORE PEOPLE TO DIE?
IF I HAVE TO PULL RANK
ON YOU, I WILL.
I'M NOT LETTING SOME
MADMAN CALL THE SHOTS.
GOD ONLY KNOWS
WHAT HE HAS PLANNED.
YOU KEEP YOUR MEN
IN POSITION
AND BOARD THAT PLANE
THE FIRST CHANCE YOU GET.
[ALARM BEEPING]
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S A FUEL WARNING.
WE ONLY HAVE
2,000 POUNDS LEFT.
IT'S ENOUGH FOR ABOUT
5 OR 10 MINUTES.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO MAKE THIS WORK
ON THE FIRST APPROACH.
NO.
I WANT YOU TO PASS OVER
THE AIRSTRIP FIRST.
WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH
FUEL FOR THAT.
YES, WE DO.
YOU'LL DO AS I SAY.
OR WHAT?
IF WE TRY A FLYOVER,
WE'RE ALL GOING TO DIE
WHEN WE UNDERSHOOT
THE LANDING.
YES, BUT IT'S NOT JUST
ABOUT US ANYMORE, MARTY.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
[RINGS]
HERE.
I THINK IT'S FOR YOU.
HELLO?
[PEOPLE YELLING]
TREVOR?
SON OF A BITCH.
ALL RIGHT, LINE IT UP
FOR THE FLYOVER.
YOU'RE INSANE.
THE FUEL'S JUST--
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE FUCKING FUEL!
NOW I WANT TO DROP THEM
A MESSAGE.
OW!
WHERE ARE YOU--
JESSICA!
STAY THERE.
WELL, SINCE
YOUR BOYFRIEND
ALREADY HAS
HIS HANDS OCCUPIED,
WE SHOULD PROBABLY KEEP
YOUR HANDS OCCUPIED, TOO.
WHY DON'T YOU
SHOOT ME?
COME ON.
I THINK YOU KNOW
THE ANSWER TO THAT ONE.
WE GOT SOME
UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
[LAUGHS]
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
OH, GOD!
PLEASE DON'T HURT ME!
COME ON.
GO, GO, GO.
FOR GOD'S SAKES, HAVEN'T YOU
DONE ENOUGH ALREADY?
SHUT UP!
[PEOPLE GASP]
GOD, I'M JUST
SICK OF YOU!
YOU--
GO! COME ON, MOVE!
[CRYING]
LOOK...
WAIT!
AAH!
YOU'RE KIDDING ME,
RIGHT?
[SCREAMING]
YOU'RE JUST FUCKING WITH ME
LIKE YOU WERE BEFORE,
AREN'T YOU?
OW!
GOD! AAH!
OH, MY GOD!
DID YOU SAY YOU'D NEGOTIATE
FOR ME ON THE GROUND?
YES! YES!
ABSOLUTELY!
GOOD!
NO!
PUT IN A GOOD WORD FOR ME!
AAH!
OHH! OHH!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[AIRPLANE]
WHAT IN THE HELL
IS GOING ON BACK THERE?
WELL...
REMEMBER HOW I SAID
WHATEVER DOESN'T KILL US
ONLY MAKES US STRONGER?
HEH.
WELL, LET'S JUST SAY
WILCOX...
WON'T BE GETTING
ANY STRONGER.
ALL RIGHT, GO AHEAD.
PUT THEM BACK ON.
Martin: SEA-TAC CONTROL,
THIS IS MARTIN.
HE SAYS
THAT'S A WARNING--
THAT IF YOU DON'T COMPLY
WITH ALL OF HIS DEMANDS,
THE REST
OF THE PASSENGERS
WILL BE LANDING
THE SAME WAY.
[SIRENS]
I'M HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE
STABILIZING THIS THING.
I'VE GOT THE FLAPS
SET TO FULL,
THE THROTTLE
AT ONE THIRD.
YOU SEEM TO KNOW
THE PLANE WELL ENOUGH.
THAT'S HALF THE BATTLE.
NOW EASE OFF
ON THE AILERON.
LET HER SETTLE.
THERE'S A CROSS WIND
OF 20 KNOTS.
IN ORDER TO COUNTER
THE YAW,
YOU HAVE TO PUSH
THE RIGHT RUDDER.
ROGER THAT.
COUNTERING.
MY SPEED AND MY ANGLE
ARE WAY OFF.
Sikes: TAKE IT EASY, MARTIN.
TAKE IT EASY.
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN DO THIS.
YOU'RE DOING JUST FINE.
YOU'RE GOING TO LAND
THIS BABY.
NOW LISTEN TO ME.
THE ILS SHOWS 2 LINES.
WHEN THEY CENTER UP
ON THE SCREEN
IN A PERFECT CROSS,
THAT INDICATES
THE PROPER GLIDE SLOPE.
ROGER, SEA-TAC.
Computer: WARNING--
LOW FUEL.
WARNING--LOW FUEL.
SHIT. THAT'S
THE NUMBER ONE ENGINE.
THE NUMBER ONE ENGINE
IS DOWN.
I DON'T KNOW
THE RESTART PROCEDURE.
YOU HAVE TO PURGE THE LINE
BY THROTTLING UP
ONLY THE NUMBER ONE ENGINE
AND THEN HIT RESTART.
ROGER THAT.
[SIRENS]
[BEEPS]
WE'RE OUT OF FUEL.
WE'RE NOT GOING
TO MAKE IT.
THE NUMBER 4 ENGINE
IS NOW GONE AS WELL.
Man: OH, MY GOD!
WE'RE GOING TO DIE!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
OH, GOD,
HE'S COMING IN TOO LOW.
YOU'VE GOT TO COMPENSATE
FOR THE LOWER VELOCITY.
PULL UP.
PULL UP, MARTIN.
THAT'S IT.
REVERSE ENGINES.
YOU'RE DOWN.
Martin:
REVERSING THRUST,
BUT ENGINES ONE AND FOUR
ARE STILL OUT.
WE'RE NOT STOPPING.
LOOKS LIKE 300 FEET--
YOU'LL HAVE TO LEAN
ON THE HYDRAULICS.
THAT'S IT!
WHOO!
THAT'S IT.
JAM ON THOSE BRAKES.
Man: WHOO!
OH, I WISH I HAD
A CIGARETTE.
I TOOK THIS
OFF OF LENNY.
HIT THE WHEEL BRAKES.
[APPLAUSE]
Woman: YES!
Man: TEAM "A"
IS MOVING INTO POSITION.
LET'S GO!
SNIPERS WILL HAVE
A CLEAR HIT ON THE PLANE.
Martin: THE HIJACKER
IS SENDING OUT
2 WOUNDED HOSTAGES
IN EXCHANGE FOR FUEL.
Man:
LET'S GO! LET'S GO!
JUST MAKE SURE THE 2 HOSTAGES
ARE CLEAR FIRST.
Man:
ROGER THAT.
[SIREN]
TEAM "B,"
MOVE INTO POSITION.
GET READY TO FIRE
ON MY MARK.
WE HAVE ALL
THE ANGLES PINNED DOWN.
Man:
ROGER THAT.
WE'RE TRAINED
ON THE DOOR.
NOBODY IS GOING ANYWHERE.
WE HAVE MOVEMENT.
REPEAT--WE HAVE MOVEMENT.
STAY BACK!
HE SAID STAY BACK!
OH, GOD.
HE'S INSANE.
HE'S SPEAKING IN
SOME FOREIGN LANGUAGE.
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND
A WORD HE'S SAYING.
WELL, ONE BIG
HAPPY FAMILY.
[BEEPS]
YOU DON'T REALLY THINK
YOU CAN JUST WALK
OUT OF HERE, DO YOU?
WE'RE ALREADY
HALFWAY HOME.
SIR?
YOU BETTER
LISTEN TO THIS.
Sikes: JUST PUT IT
ON THE SPEAKER PHONE.
SHUT UP AND
JUST KEEP MOVING.
Martin: YOU KNOW, YOU'RE NEVER
GOING TO GET AWAY WITH THIS.
[LAUGHS]
JUST WATCH ME.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
GOING TO DO WITH MY SON?
HE'LL BE FINE RIGHT
THERE IN THE TERMINAL
AS LONG AS
YOU PLAY IT COOL.
NICE, MARTIN,
VERY NICE.
TACTICAL,
LISTEN CLOSELY.
ROGER. CAUCASIAN MALE
WITH TAN OVERCOAT.
REPEAT--
WITH A CHILD?
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HEY. HEY!
Trevor:
DADDY!
Man:
I SAID COME BACK!
DAMN IT!
THERE! DROP HIM!
[GUNSHOTS]
[SIREN] TREVOR!
TREVOR!
DADDY!
HEY!
NO!
BYE-BYE, MARTY.
STOP!
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[SIREN STOPS]
Driver:
OH, MY GOD.
JAY, I'VE BEEN SHOT.
WHATEVER DOESN'T KILL US
ONLY MAKES US STRONGER.
TREVOR!
DAD!
ARE YOU TWO OK?
YEAH.
Trevor:
I WAS SO SCARED.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
MOVE IT OUT,
MOVE IT OUT.
YOU OK, PAL?
YEAH.
IT'S GOING TO BE
ALL RIGHT NOW.
OH, I LOVE YOU.
COME ON.
WE'RE GOING HOME.
HELLO?
WE SHOULD FLY
MORE OFTEN.
HELLO?
HOLD YOUR FIRE.
IS IT OVER?
IS HE GONE?
[COUGHS]
MARTIN?
MARTIN MESSERMAN?
I'M ROBERT SIKES,
SEATTLE ATC.
I'M THE GUY
YOU'VE BEEN TALKING TO.
GOD, CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU DID
AN INCREDIBLE JOB.
THANKS.
THANKS A LOT.
DO ME A FAVOR,
WOULD YOU?
THE NEXT TIME YOU LAND
A PLANE ON MY STRIP,
BONE UP
ON YOUR MORSE CODE.
[LAUGHS]
WELL, IT WAS A PLEASURE
MEETING YOU.
YOU, TOO.
THANKS.
Jessica:
MARTIN!
MARTIN.
OH, MY GOD,
YOU DID IT.
GO, DAD.
SORRY.
TREVOR...
THIS IS MY GOOD FRIEND
JESSICA.
MY VERY GOOD FRIEND.
YOU REALLY LANDED THE PLANE
BY YOURSELF?
WERE YOU SCARED?
HEY, IS YOUR DAD
SCARED OF ANYTHING? HUH?
CAN WE GIVE YOU
A RIDE HOME?
YEAH.
COME ON.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
TRIMARK HOME VIDEO
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--