Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Hey! The freighter's
ready for lift-off!
The team's all loaded up!
[rumbling]
I'm all set!
Something messed with
my latest reading, though.
You guys mess with
my equipment again?
Whatever.
I think we have
everything we need.
Copy that.
Wheels up soon.
Couldn't come
at a moment too soon.
The O2 levels are
starting to look off.
I don't like the looks
of ol' smokey over there.
Oh, yeah.
Let's get outta here before
she blows her top, huh?
All right.
Calling base. Let's hit it.
Yeah.
Space Force, this is IMC Five.
Crew is all packed in,
ready to come on home.
Affirmative, IMC Five,
you are clear for return.
Safe journey home, boys.
[rumbling]
Mayday! Mayday!
This is IMC Five!
We are experiencing
seismic activity!
Come in, base!
Bryant!
Ah!
Chase, this is
Space Force Rescue Unit 4A
proceeding to pull out
stalled transport shuttle
from the main flyway, over.
That's Captain Chase
and you are not yet cleared for
your maneuver, Lieutenant Young.
With all due respect,
Captain,
how much longer is
this babysitting gonna last?
Well, as long as
you have problems
following commands,
Lieutenant.
Yes, Captain,
but surely you have better uses
for your best pilot trainee?
I still haven't decided if
you're my best trainee
or my worst.
I outmaneuvered everyone in
class every session, ma'am.
Sounds like she
is your best pilot.
Hmm.
When she obeys orders.
Which is why Lieutenant Young
is going to pass probation
by adhering to
standard operating procedure,
correct, Astrid?
I'm here to color
inside the lines, Captain.
Ah, see that you do.
Show me you can follow commands,
and then I'll put you back on
the wait list for Squad 1A,
I promise.
You're gonna slow-roll me
to get back on that rescue team
'til I'm dead.
Repeat transmission, Astrid.
I did not copy.
I said, "Copy, ma'am."
Captain.
[ speaking Russian ]
[beeping]
Lieutenant Young, there
is an urgent distress call
portside 32 degrees,
quad 86, 40 miles.
Russian solar farm
"Zolotse" reports
a failed spacewalk on
its starboard side.
Captain, you hearing this?
Astrid, this is Major Hawkins.
The solar farm is
Russian jurisdiction only.
You heard the Major.
Stay the course.
Let the Russians
handle their own rescue.
Our 1A Class Rescue ship
is prepped for launch
if they're needed.
But the solar farms are
usually a one-man operation.
You are to focus on the shuttle,
not the cosmonaut!
Status update.
Spacesuit Oxygen readings have
triggered a biometrics APB.
Cosmonaut Vasily Petrakov
is in distress.
His air regulator is breached.
Oxygen is depleting rapidly,
58% remaining.
Captain, the shuttle has
plenty of air in reserves.
There's not a Russian ship
anywhere near.
Even if Team 1A gets off the
launch pad in the next minute,
this Petrakov will
be dead!
[ speaking Russian ]
Status update.
Cosmonaut oxygen level
is at 16%.
1A is cleared for rescue.
5A is within 40 kilometers
of the target.
Okay, Chase.
Has 1A left the launch paid?
They will in
t-minus five minutes.
All right, I got no choice.
Astrid...
That man will die out there!
Astrid, you are
veering off-course.
Turn your ship around
and stand by!
I'm sorry, Chase! No!
I can't leave a man to die!
You know the protocol!
That man is not your concern!
The shuttle is!
Mayday, mayday!
I have no air.
Please help me.
Mayday!
He knows his people
won't reach him in time!
He's broadcasting in English!
Central Command, I have no air.
Send help.
Major Hawkins, I am "go"
for the Russian cosmonaut!
4A, this is in
direct violation
of the international rules
of engagement.
Team 1A has
priority clearance.
Abort mission.
Major, I'm sorry.
Transmission's cutting out!
Losing radio signal!
Intel!
Cosmonaut status log!
Oxygen level, 11%.
Deactivate hazard
avoidance system.
I need full control to be able
to reach this solar farm.
Hazard avoidance
steering deactivated.
[speaking Russian]
G-force stress factor 4.2.
Current trajectory collision
warning, solar farm.
Retrograde portside! 40%!
Intel, prepare decompression
for the cosmonaut.
Engage robotic arm
to pull him in.
Rescue mission accomplished!
Lieutenant Young, report to the
Command Satellite immediately!
You are to surrender
to the MPs upon arrival.
Yes, sir.
Alert!
Astrid, you are wanted by
military law enforcement.
Yeah, I know, Intel.
Thank you.
Why'd you have to be Russian?
Military Police is en route.
Give me your tracking device
and your biometric beacon.
This is exactly what got you
into trouble last time.
You know what happened.
I shielded that crew
from the debris.
No one cares.
You caused an accident
and lost your ship and
lost all credibility.
I was saving lives, ma'am.
You know what?
Even as far back as
flight school, you were a pain.
And I kept telling myself,
I kept thinking no, no, no.
Keep training her,
she's a promising pilot.
I really believed in you.
Chase...
Captain, I had to.
We are not fighter pilots
and, as a rescue
flight division,
we work for the military.
You know what that means?
That means this
is my career, too.
We don't even know who
the cosmonaut is.
We don't even know if he's KGB.
I can't stop them
from arresting you.
You were gonna save him
with the other ship!
I don't see a difference!
You don't see the difference?
Well, the difference
is they have clearance
with foreign nationals.
You don't.
You broke military law
by disobeying a direct order
and an international
treaty of zero engagement
between Russian and
American forces!
He saw the inside of
a Space Force Rescue ship,
not a combat craft!
You don't get to decide
if that's important.
You know...
I covered for you the
last time, the last incident.
But this is really too much.
There's gotta be some other
option than locking me away.
What about
a rehabilitation program?
No.
I called in
all my favors last time.
You are a great pilot,
but I can't make that case
to Command anymore.
Okay. Would I qualify for
Education-Based Discipline?
Hard labor beats the brig.
Ma'am, you don't
owe me anything.
But if I go to prison,
that's a waste of my talent
and your training.
If you refer me to a labor
assignment in the penal system,
I promise you I will repay you!
If I request a labor program,
you're gonna be flying
an F-level tugboat
and doing community service.
Okay, so it's an MOLV-One ship?
Yes, the lowest class there is
and it's a dangerous assignment.
And, Astrid, you'll be working
crew with other criminals.
Wait. I can't fly alone?
[laughs]
No, not anymore.
Okay, I understand.
Major Hawkins,
this is Captain Chase
requesting a labor assignment.
Go for Hawkins.
Yes.
Former Lieutenant Young is
waiving her right to a hearing.
And is requesting
a hard labor assignment
commensurate to the charges.
I'll have the hearing officer
draw up the paperwork.
She can start today, Captain.
There's a tug ship
scheduled at 1700.
The freighter?
Okay.
You're in.
I think you might
change your mind about prison
when you meet the crew.
Ma'am, seriously,
I will repay you.
You are going to another
solar system
on a last-tier assignment,
dead last, desert planet.
Planet Dune?
It's a freighter lift
from the surface.
It's a six-crew members.
They reported mechanical
problems when they had takeoff.
And then we lost contact.
We're gonna send you in
to check and rescue.
Ma'am, seriously,
I'm in your debt.
Go get your new uniform.
Get your ship dock number
and report to me at 1630.
- Thank you so much.
- Go, go.
[snoring]
Astrid, meet your new crew.
What's up?
You must be Astrid.
Your reputation precedes you.
Like it's tattooed
on my forehead.
Trying to change that, though.
Sure. I'm ship's mechanic.
There's nothing
I can't fix...
unless it gets broken
by a reckless pilot.
Good thing we don't have one
of those around here then.
You disobeyed a flight directive
and lost your ship, right?
No, my engine went out when
I was saving someone's life.
That's why you're here giving
guided tours to cosmonauts.
Okay, let's get
something straight...
Cool your jets.
This is the only crew
you have now.
Hey, there.
I'm Ronnie, your navigator.
Nice to meet you.
I know you.
Oh, yeah. My face was all over
the interstellar coms.
Took 'em forever to catch me.
They said, "Prison or
Risky Probation Flights"?
So I said, "Give me Flights."
Hey, a great navigator
can get out of anywhere.
It's like a daredevil
rescue pilot, right?
Yeah, well, at least
you're free now.
I wouldn't say that.
I've got this lovely keepsake.
Can't wander too far from home.
Well, shall we?
Brad!
Sorry. What'd I miss?
Nothing at all.
I was just introducing
your pilot.
I'm Brad, tug line operator.
If it's stuck, I unstick it.
Everyone, this is Astrid Young,
former Lieutenant of the
Space Force Rescue Division
and one of our greatest assets.
Unfortunately, one of our
greatest liabilities also.
But, fortunately,
I believe in rehabilitation
and not in punishment.
So don't let me down.
Skis up at 1700.
Well, you heard her.
Let's load up.
That's our ship?
I thought I was being punished.
[sighs]
All right.
Crew up here.
[chattering]
Yo, Astrid!
Uh... Lieutenant.
Oh, that's how it's gonna be?
Okay... Lieutenant.
Gear's all stowed and
crew is buckled up.
Flight crew, prep for liftoff.
Don't look so worried.
We know what we're doing,
"Lieutenant Young".
MOLV One, you are
clear for take off.
Be advised, we are
getting reports of
an asteroid debris field
near your route. Stay safe.
Copy that.
Gear up.
Ahead one-quarter.
Course laid in.
At full.
Nice takeoff, pilot.
No, seriously, they gave us the
most raggedy piece of garbage...
Yeah, it's not that bad.
It'll get us there.
We'll be lucky
if someone doesn't sneeze
and blow a
hole through the hull.
All right, Ronnie.
If you don't need me up here,
I'm gonna go on ahead and
mosey down to the engine room
and give it a once-over.
- Yeah, just make sure...
- Uh, make it quick.
I expect a full
debrief on return.
Will do, boss.
It's Lieutenant.
Lieutenant Boss.
Okay, are we gonna
have a problem here?
I get the feeling
we're gonna have a problem!
- Well, maybe.
- There's no problem right?
Happy crew, happy ship, right?
I don't think the guy
who steals ships
with his tow line
should tell the rest of us
- how to run our ship!
- I was broke.
I needed the money.
A lot of people go broke,
but they don't go on...
[alarm blares]
- Asteroids!
- Bring up the map!
This ship's tracking
lidar is crap!
Yeah. We're three
degrees off-course.
I can reroute us manually.
Damn it!
We have damage, starboard side!
Wait, why are we
in an asteroid field?
How'd that happen?
Astrid?
Yeah, I'm a little
busy right now!
I'm losing pressure!
Rebecca?
On it!
All right, pressure's leveling!
We have damage
on the starboard side.
More good news.
The landing gear is toast!
Oh, that's fine.
We can just use the landing
skis instead of the wheels.
Skis?
The surface is sandy.
We can glide on in.
Clear field.
Clear field? Our new pilot
here didn't even realize
we were approaching
an asteroid field.
The Lidar's faulty.
We were having troubles
with it on the last run, too.
Someone didn't fix it, Rebecca.
You know I haven't
had a chance...
Okay, Rebecca! It's nobody's
fault, all right?
We were three degrees
off-course!
Clearly, nothing works
well on this rig!
You all handled yourselves well.
Well, at least this time,
it wasn't your fault.
You better check yourself,
civilian!
We got a long road
to walk together!
What? You wanna go?
Hmm?
Well, at least
we're all in one piece, right?
It's good enough for me.
Assess the damage on the hull.
Find out what got knocked loose.
Brad, get this rig cleaned up.
What is her deal?
Rebecca doesn't like anybody.
Yeah, no.
I got that.
I seem to be special, though.
She is fifth-generation
Space Force.
Entire family is military,
by the book.
You come here,
Miss Poster Child
for "regulations
don't mean jack".
Just breeze in,
the gifted one.
Yeah, okay.
I got it.
How'd she wind up here?
I don't know.
I do know that she's pretty
ticked off that you just
got away with a little
slap on the wrist
for breaking military protocol.
What? This is a slap
on the wrist?
Yeah, compared to what
it could have been, yes.
You have friends in high places.
Well, not high enough.
Yeah. Watch me try and wreck
a ship and get away with it.
Fair enough.
You just need to keep your nose
clean for the next few days.
And then it's back
to being Lieutenant Hero.
It's not like that.
You could have fooled me.
What do I know?
Spent most of my time
in the brig.
Hey, can I ask what you did?
You can ask.
I'm gonna go check out the ship.
Something somewhere
is broken down, I guarantee it.
[exhales]
Beginning descent
to Planet Dune,
engaging orbital boosters.
Gravity assist is
slowing our trajectory.
Copy.
Okay, Rebecca, how's it looking?
Still getting a damage reading,
but the skis are intact.
Okay, Brad, stand by.
Anchor standing by!
All right, everyone,
hold what you got.
I'm gonna set us down as close
to this freighter as possible.
We come in, we come out.
Reminds me of my last job.
Isn't that how you
wound up on this one?
I can neither confirm
nor deny that.
The air's too obscured from
that smoke from the volcano.
I can't get a reading.
Atmosphere's bouncing
back the lidar.
All right. We'll have to do it
the old-fashioned way.
Clear the coverage
and set her down.
Easy. We don't
wanna wheelbarrow.
I know.
Increasing back
pressure and power.
The planetary profile says that
the atmosphere's totally clear.
Yeah. Since when has Space Force
been right about anything?
Caught your ass, didn't they?
I have visuals and reading!
500 feet!
Reconfiguring flap settings
from 30 to 40 degrees!
Coming in hard!
Landing gear skis down!
All right, Brad! Go!
On it!
Tow system is go!
Droppin' anchor!
[grunts]
Good job, everyone.
Let's find this freighter
and get outta here.
I thought it was supposed
to be winter here.
It is.
Hang on, guys.
It's too hot.
It is hot!
Yeah.
I think it's gonna blow soon.
Then we hurry.
[rumbling]
Careful!
I don't see the freighter.
It's supposed to be here.
We probably overshot
the landing.
Hang on.
There's a trail over here.
Straight through the sand,
like it was dragged.
No, a ship that big can't
be dragged without a tow line.
Stay sharp, guys.
I see it!
Over there!
Perfect...
We'll be skis up in an hour.
Hang on, guys.
Stop!
Yes, "Lieutenant"?
Something's not right.
What? I don't see
anything wrong.
There's no one outside.
They're supposed to be on
the lookout for us.
Well, they're probably inside,
away from this heat...
like we should be.
No. You don't understand.
When a rescue ship arrives,
they should fire a flare gun
or send a ground crew
to meet us.
There's no one
even waving us in.
It's a six-man crew, Lieutenant.
If there's people hurt,
there is no ground crew.
We have seen no one!
That is a bad sign!
Guys, we don't even
know why it's so far
from the landing zone.
Maybe some of your
Russian friends
showed up to lend a hand?
They're not my friends!
And I'm the only one
violating treaties lately!
Well, it's just them
on the planet, right?
So what could have happened?
We're gonna find out.
We gotta be ready for anything.
So stick close, work fast.
You got it, boss.
IMC Five, this is MOLV One,
your rescue ship.
Come in. Over.
IMC Five, this is MOLV One,
do you copy?
Not good.
Okay, let's just see
what we're dealing with.
We'll check on the crew and
we'll move the tug ship closer.
Brad? Rebecca?
You guys get a tow line going.
Ronnie and I will
move into position.
We gotta hurry.
Oxygen's dropping
faster than I'd like.
It's only minus 10% of
what's normal on earth.
It's like a mid-altitude
hike, easy-peasy.
There's an active volcano
less than 15 miles away.
And we do know what we're doing.
We've been working together
before you showed up...
Okay, if we keep
dragging our feet,
we're gonna keep losing oxygen.
I'm just saying,
maybe we should go back
and get the spare oxygen...
Okay, listen, listen, okay?
We gotta stick together on this!
We might have an answer
once I fire off this flare.
You gotta be kidding me.
It's a family heirloom!
That better be water in there.
What is that? Gasoline?
Okay. It's moonshine,
but it was a gift from
my mom before she died!
Really?
Mama's moonshine?
Yeah.
My great-great-grandmother
was a shine runner
back in Prohibition. So what?
That's nice.
Were you drunk flying us here?
No, I wasn't drunk!
But you were drinking, right?
I had a drink, okay?
What?
I knew when I read the dossier
you must have been hammered
when you wrecked your ship!
Okay, I wasn't hammered,
all right?
I had just saved a ship's crew
and I saw debris
flowing from their craft
heading toward the I.S.S.
So, yeah, I disobeyed orders
and I deflected it and
I burned out my engine.
And then I had a drink,
one drink, to calm down after!
Did you need to calm down
after the asteroids?
No, I didn't.
Thanks for your concern.
This says otherwise.
Guys, I don't even need that!
Oh, good!
Then you won't mind if
I pour this out.
No, go right ahead!
Go! Run! Run!
A cave, come on!
Well, what now, Lieutenant?
Guess we know what happened
to the freighter crew.
No, we don't know anything.
There could still
be survivors out there.
We need to get off this planet.
No. We need to find
the survivors!
Then we go.
Well, we can't
go back out there.
Looks like we'll be
in here for a while.
What if it can burrow under
the rock and get in here?
Yeah, that's a good point.
There could be worms inside.
We just don't know.
Does anyone have
any weapons on them?
It's not much,
but it's better than nothing.
Against that worm?
You know, if it could
have come over the rocks,
it would have followed us in.
So we should be safe in here,
for now at least.
Okay, I say we go deeper in and
maybe there's another way out.
What if we find something
else in here, something worse?
I'm having a
real problem with worse.
Something that had
to outrun the worm
and it got stuck here
and it's hungry too?
You have a point.
[growling]
I think it can
probably still detect us
'cause we're so close
to the entrance.
- We should move.
- Ronnie's right.
It could be trying to find
another way in as we speak.
Let's go find another way out!
Go, go, go.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hey...
What was that?
- Was that a person?
- Is somebody there?
I'm not sure.
- Watch your six.
- You got it.
Can you hear me?
[coughing]
Careful.
Brad, you see anything?
Who's that?
Help!
I'm here! Help!
Come on!
Help!
Hey, you okay?
Do you have water?
Water, water, water, water!
Are you hurt?
I think I broke my leg.
The worm was chasing me.
I fell into this rock.
Yeah. We had a few words
with him too.
What uniform is that?
It's, uh... Public Services.
We're with the tug ship crew.
That smarts.
Yeah? Kills the germs.
Look, I don't think it's broken,
but be careful
putting weight on it.
Where's the rest of your crew?
I don't know.
We scattered.
My girl, Marilyn,
and the rest ran to the rocks
in the east and I made it here.
[rumbling]
The worm's directly beneath us!
Oh!
We gotta get off this rock!
Your leg's really gonna hurt
when we do this.
I don't care.
Just get me out of here!
It's pushing the rocks aside!
Um, I'll jump across.
You hand him to me.
Go!
It's trying to get
through the rocks!
Harley, step out and reach
for Astrid on the other side.
I got you here.
[grunts]
Let's go!
You guys, we can't stay here.
Okay, you ready?
Wait, wait. Look.
No, no, no, no, we gotta
go back out the way we came.
No, there's a small tunnel
over that I crawled in through.
with some light.
There's probably an exit.
Well, do you know how
to get there?
- Yes, I...
- Shh!
Okay. Here we go.
It's there.
Okay.
Okay, I think we're good.
[clattering]
- [gasps]
- Shh!
Run!
Wait, wait, wait.
I need a minute to rest.
We're not stopping, are we?
We almost died back there.
Shh! Do you want to live?
- You?
- Yes.
Then stay quiet and calm.
We're gonna have
a tough time finding everyone
and getting off this planet.
How many do you think
made it from your crew?
I was the only one
who made it to the cave,
probably three more.
Okay, do you have any weapons?
No. We're a mining rig.
Well, what's the plan?
We get to the freighter
and get out of here.
The Corrections Department
gave us explicit orders!
What about his crew?
We can't just leave them here.
No, no, no.
We'll rescue the crew.
We were sent
to rescue the freighter.
That includes the crew.
It's too risky
without backup, Astrid!
You need to think clearly.
I'm not leaving these people
stranded on a ridge to die!
Isn't this what got you in
trouble in the first place?
Disobeying orders to play hero?
As I said,
I am not disobeying orders.
We are bringing
home the freighter.
That means the crew, too!
We are a rescue team!
End of discussion!
Oxygen levels are
down five percent.
- That's not good!
- Same. Dropping.
It's the volcano.
There are vents
on the side that's
releasing carbon dioxide
and toxic fumes.
Okay, okay.
This cave is a death trap.
We got to get out of here,
come on. Let's go.
Our friend is back!
There's the freighter!
Oh, thank God!
Okay, Ronnie? Rebecca?
You guys get it
ready for launch.
Brad and I will go to the ridge
and look for survivors.
Okay. And the worm?
It can't chase both of us.
Just run like hell.
Uh, ladies?
He's okay.
He's just passed out.
We can't travel
with dead weight!
Okay, Brad.
You stay here with Harley
and I'll come back with
the tug for you.
- I'll stay.
- All right.
- Time to go, ladies.
- Yeah.
We're gonna have
to make a run for it.
What about the worm, Lieutenant?
It's more important that you
guys get to the freighter.
I'll keep him busy.
I'll go first.
Wait...
She's insane.
Let's go.
All right.
[panting]
Hello?
Anyone?
This is rescue!
Hello?
Oh, God.
Coming.
Are you okay?
Water...
I got you.
Whoa, slow slips!
Easy does it.
I'm Astrid.
Marilyn.
You injured?
No.
Just... Thirsty and hungry.
Here.
I'm so glad you're here.
- Here. Try this.
- Thanks.
Is there anyone else with you?
No.
They tried to make
it to the freighter.
But it... the worm...
it was waiting for them.
I'm sorry.
Look, we can't stay here.
We gotta get to my tug.
- Can you travel?
- No.
No, we can't.
They're too fast.
Whoa, hang on, they?
There's more than one worm?
Four that I've seen.
Four...
[beeps]
Ronnie, Rebecca and
Brad, this is Astrid. Come in.
MOLV One!
This is Astrid!
There are at least
four worms out there, guys!
I repeat, multiple worms!
Over!
[panting]
I think we're in the clear.
- I don't hear it.
- I hope Astrid made it.
[radio static]
...More than one...
More than one?
Go! Go! Go!
We're almost to the freighter!
Ronnie, repeat that
transmission!
Okay, look.
Tell me everything you know
about these worms.
I've been using
a telemetric scanner.
The worms...
they feed on trace
amounts of iron in the sand.
Okay, okay.
Then we arrived?
Yes.
They can smell the iron
in our blood.
But there's iron in the ships!
Right, but not
in the form they can use.
Okay, okay, all right.
What else?
There's one big one
and three smaller ones.
I think they're babies.
They follow the big one
around at times.
Go on. Look, any information
can help us.
The big one...
he... he grabbed the freighter.
He attacked the freighter.
And he just dragged
it across the desert.
I mean, we didn't
stand a chance.
Brad, this is Astrid!
Maintain your position.
I repeat, stay in the cave!
Here. Try this.
Come on, take this.
- What is that?
- It'll take the edge off.
[coughs]
Wow, that burns like...
Like rocket fuel? Yeah.
It's actual moonshine.
My grandma made it.
Go ahead, have a swig.
You, uh... you could use it.
What is this doing on a ship?
Isn't this contraband?
More or less.
It's all I have left
of my parents, though.
Your parents
made homemade booze?
Kind of a family legacy all
the way back to prohibition.
Hell, your great-great
grandfather
probably even had our stuff.
Oh, that's bad.
It's an acquired taste.
I'm sorry.
I think I drank the last of it.
Not exactly.
Should I be concerned?
No.
I told you,
it's a family legacy.
It's the last batch
they made before...
My mom sent this to me
as a present when I graduated
from flight school.
Last thing she ever sent me.
Anyway, I didn't want it to
be confiscated, so I hid it.
Maybe I should just
hang on to it.
I'm good.
We gotta go.
No, we can't!
The worms... we can't.
Ronnie? Rebecca?
Have you reached the freighter?
Over.
[static]
We can't get
any signal up here.
I need to get to higher ground.
No...
There.
We can run to that taller rock
and I'll radio from there.
Marilyn, come on!
We can't stay here, okay?
We're running out of water
and the air's getting thinner!
Marilyn, we gotta go.
Marilyn, we gotta get
to higher ground
so I can radio the crew, okay?
I got two in your
freighter standing by.
I got one more in a cave
over those rocks
with a survivor
from your team.
They're all waiting on us
to get off of this planet.
Another survivor? Who?
Harley...
Harley? He's okay?
He didn't die?
Yeah. Yeah, no, no.
He's a tough guy.
Okay?
Here.
Left foot up.
You good?
Hang on, listen.
I don't hear the worms.
This could be our best chance.
You ready?
Let's go.
- Ah!
- What?
I got you!
[roaring]
What about this one?
[panting]
I'm not dying like that.
Not like that.
Almost makes me want
to get back in the brig.
Seriously?
Oh, yeah.
Hell of a lot safer.
Okay, you need to get
this engine up and running.
We don't even know
what's wrong with it.
That's your job.
It's right below us!
It's following us.
Keep moving!
Everything looks the same.
Where are we?
- Headed towards the engine room.
- Great.
If you can't fire up the ship,
I say we cut our losses
and run for the tug ship.
No. We stay and
fix the freighter.
Did you feel that?
I say we just leave it!
No! I want this ship!
What do you mean,
you want this ship?
I'm with IMC.
I don't care who you work for.
Besides, I thought
you were an ex-con.
That's why I'm here.
This thing is worth $300 billion
and my cut is $100 million,
all right?
If you help, I'll give you 20%.
You in?
Look, it can't hurt us in here.
I say we save the people
and the freighter.
I'm not interested
in the people. I want the money.
Well, we can save
the crew on the rocks, too.
Be my guest!
Fine, but if it comes
down to a choice,
I'm ditching the freighter!
Sure. The crew outside
would love some company!
Huh.
What do you mean, "huh"?
Let's go.
Well, I got partial power back,
but the diagnostic says
the intake ports
need to be cleared
from underneath the ship.
If not...
If not, the ship won't start.
They're under the ship,
aren't they?
If we clear them from
inside the ductwork,
you won't be exposed
to the outside.
No, when I was in
the brig I mapped out
the entire ventilation
system...
Wait, wait. Why?
I had a lot of time
on my hands,
But if I get inside the vents,
it's gonna put me
five feet above the sand.
I don't wanna be
that close to the sand.
So what do we do?
Just give up and
run to the tug ship?
No.
I can try to clear
them using the exhaust system
in the HVAC room.
Okay, yeah.
That'll work!
- Radio me once it's done.
- Okay.
[roars]
Rebecca!
The worm is in the ship!
Repeat!
Worm is in the ship!
Ronnie!
Get out of there!
The heater's on, I can't
shut it off!
I know!
Hit max power on
the heat exhaust!
You'll be burned alive!
Do it!
[screeches]
Ronnie, come in!
Damn it, Ronnie! Come in!
This is Rebecca! Come in!
Just had to be a primary switch.
Can't start the engine
without the primary switch.
Ronnie, come in!
Anyone! I need backup!
Okay.
I'm gonna have to go outside.
No wonder it wouldn't start.
The landing severed
the external power line.
[sighs]
Ah!
[screams]
Rebecca, nice work!
Two down.
- Two?
- I got one, too.
Yeah, but we just
doubled our repair time.
How many worms are there?
I don't know.
I only saw the one.
For the record, I'm impressed.
I just did what
needed to be done.
Exactly right.
That's why I'm gonna
give you a cut.
You're a good team player.
First time anyone's ever
said that about me.
All right.
Let's get the rig running
and get outta here.
What about the others?
What about them?
They make it back here, great.
If not...
Are we clear on this?
Yeah.
All right. Check the
conduits in that panel.
We got a lot of work
ahead of us.
This should be good.
You okay?
Yeah.
I think I twisted it.
I didn't notice the pain then,
but it's killing me now.
All right.
Get your boot off.
Okay?
All right.
This should keep
the swelling down.
Okay.
All right, the tug should
be just right over there.
I'm gonna piggyback
my signal off its antenna,
radio home base.
My captain should be
able to send help.
Is that the same captain that
sent you to this death planet?
She didn't know.
Neither did you.
Mayday, Space Force!
This is MOLV One pilot,
Astrid Young.
Do you copy?
[static]
Space Force, this is MOLV One.
Mayday! Do you read me?
Copy, MOLV One, This is
Space Force. We read you.
We need immediate backup rescue
and fire power.
We are not alone here!
[static]
Space Force, do you copy?
We need help!
We read you, Lieutenant.
Chase... uh, Captain!
This is a secure line.
Define the full nature
of the emergency.
Is this a Russian incursion?
Russians? What...
You just indicated there
was a hostile force
and requested backup
and fire power.
No, ma'am, it's not Russians!
It's worms, giant worms!
We need rescue now!
We don't have the capability
to fight them!
I'm sorry,
but I'm not authorized
to send a retrieval ship.
Not authorized?
Are we not worth rescuing?
Am I getting that right?
Lower echelon status
means less support.
You knew that was a part
of the probation deal.
Yeah, but I would think
that goes out the window
when we start dealing with
giant man-eating worms, Chase!
Danger detail, Astrid.
You requested it.
Your job is to
get the freighter.
If I didn't think you could do
it, I wouldn't have sent you.
The freighter...
ma'am, you are not gonna get a
freighter if my crew is dead!
Not to mention
the civilian survivors!
Why don't you tell me the Space
Force's response is to that?
Bring everybody back.
That's the job.
Chase!
God...
Okay.
Come on.
They're not coming.
Then we're on our own.
Let's get off this planet.
Major, pilot Young
has reported
that they are under
attack by worms.
The worms were supposed
to be dormant now.
And?
And I'd like to request
a retrieval team.
Denied.
Sir, I'm aware that
retrieval squads
are not usually called
in for probation crews.
But under the circumstances...
They're no different.
We'll recover the freighter
when the worms are dormant.
The crew's expendable.
Dismissed.
- Sir...
- Dismissed, Captain!
Astrid? Ronnie? Rebecca?
Anybody? Come in! Over.
[static]
MOLV One, come in!
Can anybody hear me?
[static]
Okay, buddy.
We can't stay here much longer.
We gotta move.
How long was I out for?
Not long, maybe an hour.
Wish it had been longer.
I was dreaming about
my Hawaiian honeymoon
with my girl, Marilyn.
We were planning it for a while.
For the pain.
The air feels thicker.
Oxygen levels are down.
CO2 is up.
We need to try to get
to the freighter on our own.
It's closer than the tug.
I can't do anything
with this bum leg.
Here.
Tie this around your waist.
I can drop you down and
support you from up here.
What about the worm?
I haven't seen it in a while.
Besides, we can't stay here.
The air is getting toxic.
Oh, by the way, it's gonna hurt
a little bit on the way down.
So do your best to keep
as quiet as you can.
Okay. Slow?
- Uh-huh.
- Go.
Brad, there's a worm!
Pull me up!
Brad, there's a worm. Brad!
[grunting]
Brad!
I got it! I got it!
Got it!
Maybe we can try again
in a little bit.
No, we can't.
The worm knows we're here.
It's just gonna wait us out.
We're gonna die here.
There's got to
be another way.
We need to find another
way outta here.
[hissing]
The volcano's getting
ready to blow!
We have to get out of here!
Those gases are toxic!
Sulfur...
I...
[coughs]
I can't breath!
We have to get outta here, Brad!
Come on.
What are you doing?
If you fire that thing,
it's gonna cave in!
I know.
That's exactly what I wanna do!
I'm gonna create an air vent.
Cover your head.
[grunts]
Look out!
[shouts]
Well, there's that.
Change of plans.
We're going out
through the ceiling.
I can't climb.
Well, you're gonna have to.
All right.
Hop on!
Hold tight!
We're going up!
I got an idea!
[blows whistle]
Hey! Over here!
It's coming!
[grunts]
Come on!
What? No!
I'll stay right here,
thank you very much!
Harley, the only way
we're gonna get back
to the freighter is if
the worm takes us!
I can control it with the hook!
[grunts]
See, I'm in control!
Now skootch on down here
and get onboard!
We don't have all day!
Hold on to me!
[grunts]
Rebecca! Worm!
Ah!
No!
No! Ah!
[screaming]
I'm so sorry.
She was gonna get
us out of here.
She was the only one
who knew how to fix the rig.
It'll be okay.
How is it gonna be okay?
We're stuck here.
Astrid's gonna come back
and we're gonna figure out
how to get to the tug.
This is not over.
Yeah, I don't see any
movement around the tug.
Think we'll make it.
How far is it?
Not far.
We'll have to make a run for it,
but we gotta get out
of the sun anyway.
I know.
Another day out here
in this sun and no water...
Here.
Lean on me, all right?
I'll guide you down.
Watch where you put your foot!
You okay?
This would have been
my last mission.
Yep.
Harley and I were
supposed to get married
when this one was done.
He was ready to go home,
take up a teaching position.
But I needed this one last run.
He only came to be with me.
So... it's my fault
that we're here!
You couldn't have known
this was gonna happen.
You weren't told.
None of us was.
Still...
Still, if it weren't for me,
we would be on a beach
somewhere sipping Mai Tais!
You got plenty of
beach out there.
I guess this place is kind of
beautiful in its desolation.
I think you been
in the sun too long.
I guess it is their world,
after all.
World full of worms.
Wonderful.
Technically, I would put them
in the Hirudinea family.
You know, leeches.
Blood-sucking worms with teeth.
Fantastic.
Giant worms that eat blood.
You think your ship was
the one that woke 'em up?
Possibly, but I suspect
another cause.
Yeah, we gotta pick up the pace.
We can't stay on
this rock.
Is there anything else
you can tell me about
these worms' detection method?
I mean, sound?
Movement?
Can they see us?
Based on my observations,
they can sense ferrous
compounds, oxides and such.
They seem to be
attracted to them.
Yeah, they like rust.
Simplistic, but yes,
as well as human hemoglobin.
They also have some sort
of sensory system in their skin
that allows them to
detect soundwaves
and ground vibrations.
They can track us.
Yeah.
We gotta get off this rock.
And we have to be
aggressive about it.
Do we have weapons?
Not exactly.
Maybe we can come up
with something.
What you got in your backpack?
Most of my equipment isn't
gonna be all that useful.
It's for collecting samples.
Well, anything could help.
What you got?
Plastic petri dishes,
sample vials,
Ph strips, funnels,
test tubes, cork,
this glass bottle.
- The sample vials?
- Yeah.
And this...
Got anything flammable in there?
This bio stain...
and this fixative.
Why?
I'm gonna make a bomb...
or 10.
[mumbling]
So, that gets us
a total of 10.
I hope it's enough.
If you wanna hurt them,
aim for their mouths.
Their hides are too tough.
Honestly, I don't
wanna get close enough
to hit their mouths.
Just gonna be a distraction.
Gotcha.
You ready?
No, but let's do this anyway.
We're gonna make it!
I think you're just
making it angry.
Just buying us time!
Go!
- Oh, it's the mother!
- Run!
She's too big!
She'll tear this ship
open like a tuna can!
I know.
I'll get us airborne.
We'll get the others,
we'll get off this planet!
[crash]
Mayday! Mayday!
To all rescue crew of MOLV One!
Over!
We're on our way!
Mayday! Mayday!
Lieutenant Young to Base.
We need immediate rescue!
Captain Chase, come in!
We need immediate rescue now!
Hold on.
We're losing fuel.
Can we make it
to the freighter?
No. We're losing it too quick.
I gotta set her back down.
I got a plan, though.
What is all that stuff?
It's an abandon-ship
survival kit
just in case my plan
doesn't work.
Plan? What plan?
You'll see.
This was your plan?
The ship will explode!
That is the plan. Jump!
What was that?
Our ride home.
We're stranded.
Your crew?
And my team?
Marilyn?
Not Astrid.
She's tougher than that.
Come on, Astrid, don't be dead.
[coughing]
The air's getting thinner.
The fire, the explosion,
it's eating up all the oxygen.
Here.
What about you?
I'm okay.
Just take it!
- No, I can't take your last bit.
- Just take it, Marilyn!
Let me feel like
I'm doing my job!
Space Force rescue unit 4A,
you are not clear
for departure.
Cut engines and
return to base.
That's a noncompliance, base.
One of our own is stranded,
and I'm going in as backup.
Over.
Captain Chase,
this is Major Hawkins.
You are in direct violation
of Protocol Number 127...
Wow, that is so weird
being on the other side
of that conversation.
It didn't even work!
What have I done?
Oh, my God, I shouldn't
even be here!
I shouldn't even be here!
God, why can't
I just follow orders?
Just do what
people expect of me?
That's not what good people do.
Oh, yeah?
You think good people leave
their crew for dead
just to go off
and play super hero?
No.
No, Rebecca was right!
I'm a reckless pilot!
Now they're all
paying the price!
Look, Harley and I wouldn't even
be here if it wasn't for you!
And if I'm not mistaken,
there's an entire crew out there
that is waiting
for someone
to get them off of
this planet.
Maybe even someone
a little reckless.
Okay, you're right.
We're gonna suffocate
and you're worried about
a couple of boo-boos?
Oh, my God!
I know it hurts,
you big baby.
Not that. Look!
It's... It's Marilyn!
Marilyn!
Where's the team?
I'm sorry, Harley.
I'm glad they're back,
but that tug was our
ride out of here.
We've got nothing.
Even if we fight off the worms,
we're gonna run out of air.
Whoa!
It's a Space Force
Rescue Ship!
Hey! We're over here!
MOLV One team!
This is Captain Chase
with Space Force!
Prepare for extraction
and rescue!
Looks like someone
broke the rules!
Hey, where's Rebecca?
Okay, come on!
Everybody hold on!
Buckle up!
We gotta move.
Look out!
We lost one of our thrusters.
I can't get any higher.
We need something to take
this thing out permanently!
We've got missiles!
Use them!
I did.
This is a rescue ship,
not a fighter.
We're empty.
But we're not entirely
out of options.
Brad, open that red case
on the floor.
I was hoping for a bazooka.
I didn't have time to steal one.
It's a timed fusion grenade.
It'll blow a hole in
the side of that worm.
So how do I deploy it?
It's a time delay.
Set the timer and throw it.
Get us in the air!
I'll deploy it!
If I get us up in the air,
we are just leaving.
I like that plan better.
Everybody please hold on.
Go, go, go, go!
Working on it!
We're still too low!
Brad, give me that!
Bon appetit!
It's pulling us down!
5-0 seconds and counting!
Very much aware, Lieutenant.
Ah!
Chase!
We need maximum thrust!
Astrid, no!
The ship's about to break apart!
The bomb is gonna detonate!
Do it!
Pushing thrusters to 100%!
It's not enough!
Astrid, it's clamping down
and breaking the ship apart!
That's all we've got!
No, we can get more.
The thrusters are maxed out!
Yeah, but I'm gonna
super-charge it!
Get the controls!
We're headed straight
for a volcano!
Pull up!
Astrid, Chase is still out.
She's not breathing.
Come on, Captain,
Stay with me.
Come on, Captain! We been
fighting the worms all day!
You can handle
a bump on the head!
Come on, Chase.
You broke the rules
to save us.
Now I just need you to wake up
so I can say I told you so!
At least let me
to say I'm sorry!
[gasps]
I never gave up on you.
I know.
Oh, what...
Hang onto something.
It's gonna get rough.
The volcano is about to erupt!
Altitude 100,000 feet!
- Maximum thrusters?
- Max thrusters.
Hold on.
We're clear.
Space Force,
this is pilot Astrid Young.
We are clear of Planet Dune,
looking for
homeward escort to Earth.
Pilot Young, this is
Space Force command.
You are cleared for escort.
Ship manifest, we have
lost one member of our crew,
five members of the freighter,
the tug ship and the freighter.
Pilot Young, this is
Major Hawkins.
We're glad to hear there are
survivors from the freighter.
Your probation is complete.
Thank you, sir.
Congratulations, Lieutenant.
I'm pleased to inform
you you're being reinstated
to Rescue Team.
We're happy to have you back.
Yeah, I'm happy to be back, sir.
I thought...
Because of the cosmonaut,
I thought I was in trouble.
Quite the opposite.
Vasily Petrakov isn't
just any Russian.
He's a national hero who
designed new solar panels
that improve power grids 200%.
They weren't going to share
that tech with us,
but thanks to you
diplomatic relations
with Russia are ongoing.
Lieutenant?
Yeah, Major, sir.
You did the right thing.
We're a better division for it.
Thank you, sir.
I'm gonna need a crew
when we get home.
You in?
It'd be an honor.
Brad?
You know it.
I don't wanna be working
tug ships forever.
Captain Chase?
I'll put in a request.
I think it'll be approved.
All right.
Now let's get home
and save some lives.
Can we at least
take a shower first?
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull