(intense music)
(music drones)
(car engine roaring)
(car engine roars)
- [Driver] Where you heading?
- Ellington.
- Hop in. I'm going that
way, I'll give you a ride.
- Thanks.
- So what's your name?
- Ryan.
- Ryan, how are you
doing? The name's Jason.
So what brings you to Ellington?
- (indistinct)
- Come again?
- Oh you know, starting all
over. Forgetting the past.
- You sound like me.
- [Ryan] So how long have you been there?
- Three years.
- Really?
- Yeah?
- [Jason] So what is it that
you're really looking for?
- [Ryan] Well, just the basic stuff.
You know, a place to stay,
a job that pays more than minimum wage.
And a girlfriend.
- Now you really sound like me.
- So did you?
- Did I?
- Did you find what you were looking for?
- Well, got my own place.
I share it with my
sister and my girlfriend.
Got a pretty good job.
Have a terrific girlfriend.
So, yeah I have to say
I did find everything I was looking for.
- So honestly, Jason,
what are the chances of me
finding a motel room tonight?
- Slim to none.
They're having a big convention downtown.
Everything's going to be
packed for a few days.
- Great.
- You don't know anybody in LA
you can stay with for a couple of days?
- Not so.
- Well, I could let you crash
at my place if you don't mind
for a couple days.
- [Ryan] I really don't
want to be a bother.
- Listen,
I was in your shoes once
before three years ago.
I can't just let you stay on the streets.
I know what it's like.
- I really appreciate it.
- You probably won't
thank me after a few days.
You know what it's like
living with two girls?
Hope you don't need to use the bathroom.
(laughing)
(eerie music)
- Well, that's a pretty
wild time in your life.
- Yeah I gotta admit it's pretty crazy.
But your life doesn't seem
that difficult either.
- Yeah.
I got a pretty wild imagination.
- Jason, you ever just think about
strange things?
- Just out of nowhere?
- Yeah.
Like when we were kids,
we had this neighbor,
we used to cut across his
backyard on our way to school.
I mean, this guy was a real dickhead.
He used to come out of his
house every day and yell at us,
screaming at the top of his
lungs, chasing us off his yard.
But we didn't care. We used
to do it every morning.
So finally,
you know, we got tired of
this old man yelling at us.
We said we'd get him back.
We got this paper bag.
Not like some lunch bag,
I'm talking like a wig
Safeway shopping bag.
And we shit in it.
All of us took turns shitting
in it until it was full.
I mean God damn. This thing stunk so bad.
We got it, we tied up really tight,
and we went up to his front door,
set it right there on the porch.
We soaked it in lighter fluid.
And we rang the doorbell. We
rang it, rang it, mad times.
We lit on fire, and took off running.
You know,
not far enough away where we
can't see what's happening.
Just far enough
where he wouldn't see us
when he came out the door.
And he came out the door and
saw the fire on his doorstep.
So he tried to stomp fire out.
He went, "Oh shit,"
when he realized he was knee-deep in shit,
trying to put the fire out.
It was so funny.
I know he suspected it was us
because from that point on,
he never messed with us ever again.
- And?
- And, you know, it was funny cause
you know, he came out and-
- Yeah.
Oo, pretty bad.
- And you've done something worse.
- Well, actually Jason, I have.
I had a pretty mean neighbor too.
A real cocksucker.
But even worse than him was his dog.
Oh my God.
That dog was so bad.
It was the meanest,
scariest son of a bitch you ever did see.
It was huge.
I don't even know what kind of dog it was.
The thing was,
I think it was part breed,
like big-as-hell and scary-as-shit.
Well, one day I just got tired of him
always chasing me.
So I saw him sleeping there,
I had it all planned out.
So I crept up real slowly on the dog,
Took me 20 minutes.
Well, I got there,
I had this water-
- Water balloon?
- Yeah. And it gets better.
It's full of gas.
So I huck it at this dog and
it hits him right in the face.
Dog wakes up automatically. Oh my God.
She doesn't see me.
It was strange. It never ran,
like trying to get me.
It just
shook its head back and forth
and repeated this really
God-awful sound.
It started having seizures.
I started to feel bad. Like
maybe I did something wrong,
but I kept my cool and I
threw the match anyway.
- Fuck.
- Yeah. And the dog caught on fire.
Just like I imagined it would.
But what I did not imagine,
is that he is running,
catching everything on
fire. Caught a bush on fire.
I got so scared. I just ran.
I ran, and I ran.
Pretty soon I started hearing
like whistles and sirens.
Well like 10 fire trucks showed
up with a bunch of police.
The whole damn town was
there for just one dog.
So,
I thought I'd won and everything,
but I had to go back.
I went back just to see.
When I went there,
I saw the charred remains of the dog.
- You're a sick bastard.
- Sick?
Why do you say that?
I mean, I just want to
put a hurt on that dog.
I mean, I didn't mean for
the bush to catch on fire.
I mean the dog deserved it.
It bit a kid a week
before that. A little kid.
Kid had to get stitches, about 20 of them.
Left a big scar.
Don't act like you've
never done anything violent
in your life.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, see?
So tell me what was the most violent thing
you've ever done in your life?
- Well, you haven't met my little sister.
I'm sure you will.
But, I love her. I love her to death.
She's like the greatest
thing in the world.
And there was this guy,
he was a real loser.
He kept trying to get
her to go out with him.
She didn't want anything to do with him,
but he wouldn't give up.
He kept asking, and asking.
And I don't know, maybe
she felt sorry for him.
I don't know.
But she agreed to go
out with him one night.
Well, he tried to rape her.
And when I found out, I was so pissed.
I hunted him down and I
beat the shit out of him.
I just kept hitting him, and hitting him.
You know,
he quit fighting, he quit moving,
and I just kept hitting
him right in the face.
I just kept hitting him, and
hitting him, and hitting him.
God, he was a mess when I was done.
- Did you kill him?
- I wanted to,
but I don't know what happened, you know?
He moved out of town and
I never saw him again.
I don't regret doing it.
I do anything to protect my little sister.
(ominous music)
- Would you kill for her?
- I suppose.
If I had to do it to protect her.
- Do you know what it's
like to kill someone?
- No, and I suppose you do?
- Well, yeah.
- Bullshit.
- No, I'm serious.
I've killed someone.
- Yeah, like in a war or something?
- Oh, no.
Just this guy.
I wanted to and
well, he was there.
I took the rope and I just did it.
- Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
We both had a little too much to drink
and we've told some pretty tall tales.
I think it's time to go to bed.
'Cause you got to be
shitting me on this one.
- No, no, no, no, no, I can prove it.
- How can you prove something like that?
What have you got there?
- You got a VCR?
- [Ryan] I think you're
going to enjoy this.
- Ryan, what are you doing?
Ryan, what's wrong?
You can talk to me, I'm your friend.
- Ryan-
Oh Ry-
(choking on TV)
- [Ryan] Pretty good, isn't it?
- [Jason] Yeah, that was pretty good.
That kid's a good actor.
- You think I faked that?
- Yeah.
You mean,
you're trying to tell you
actually killed that kid?
- Yeah. The guy was a real bastard.
What he did was a hell of a lot worse
than what they guy you told me about
tried to do to your sister.
- What could he have possibly done to-?
Nevermind, that was fake anyways.
I don't even believe it.
- I'm telling you.
I really killed the guy.
- Kylie.
- Hey, what's going on?
- I'm sorry. Did we wake you?
This is Ryan.
That's my sister, Kylie.
Kylie, he's going to stay
here for a couple of nights.
He's kind of stuck for a
place to stay, so I told him
he crash here if he wanted to.
- Nice to meet you, Ryan.
I'll see you guys in the morning.
- Man is that your sister?
Hot damn, she is fine.
- Yeah, she-
Hey, don't be getting any ideas,
she's got a boyfriend.
- Oh, yeah?
- Well I'm going to hit the rock.
You can go ahead
and crash right there on
the couch if you want,
and I'll see you in the morning.
- Hey Jason.
Thanks again, I really appreciate this.
- Hey, no problem, man.
(bright, droning music)
(birds chirping)
(shower running)
(creepy music)
- Julie?
(water stops)
- [Jason] Hey, morning, do
you want a cup of coffee?
Hope that couch wasn't too
uncomfortable for you last night.
- Oh no, it was fine, thanks.
- There you go.
You can go ahead and have a seat out there
in the dining room.
- Morning Jason.
- Oh morning, Sweetie.
Hey hon, this is Ryan.
He didn't have a place to stay last night,
so I told him he could crash at our place
for a couple of days
until some motels open up.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Well I'd love to stay and chat,
but I'm running late for work as it is.
- All right. Well, I'll
see when you get home then.
- Okay, love you.
- Love you too.
Hey Kylie, sorry I woke you up last night.
- Oh that's okay, I fell
right back to sleep.
- [Ryan] Hello again.
- Hi. Ryan, right?
- Yeah.
(knocking)
Come in.
- What's up Jason?
- [Jason] Oh, not much.
Hey Ryan, this is Rick.
Rick, Ryan.
- How's it going?
- Pretty good.
- Are you ready?
- Sure.
Bye.
- Take it easy, guys.
- [Jason] See you later.
- [Ryan] Nice meeting you.
- Listen, I need to get going to work too,
otherwise I'll be late.
- Okay.
- I'm going to give you the
key to my car out there.
She don't run too good, but beats walking.
Go ahead. Run around town,
try to find yourself hotel,
some place to stay tonight, all right?
- Hey thanks, I will.
- No problem. Just lock it
up before you leave, okay?
- Okay.
(ominous music)
- How about a cold one?
- I'm down for that.
- Going down pretty smooth tonight.
Told you you wouldn't have any any luck
trying to find a hotel tonight.
Not with that convention.
- You were right.
There was nothing.
Hey Jason, I just want to say thanks.
I mean, a lot of people
wouldn't even help a guy out like me.
Not even knowing me or anything.
- Hey, that's just the kind of guy I am.
- Jason?
You trust me, right?
- Yeah. I trust you.
I mean, you're a pretty cool guy.
Little crazy, but so am
I. But yeah, I trust you.
- Then why'd you call me a liar?
(ominous music)
- A liar? I never called you a liar.
- You said I faked it on the videotape.
- That's different. I mean,
it's not like you
actually killed that kid.
- Yes, I did.
- Let's not get into this again.
- No, I really did.
I can prove it to you.
- How are you going to prove at this time?
- Watch.
- Look, man...
- Holy shit, that's Matt.
That's the kid that works
over at the gas station.
What the hell are you going to him?
- [Ryan] Watch.
- What are you doing, man?
Get away from me, man.
Come on.
I'll give you the money, dude.
I'll open the safe, whatever you want.
Let me go. Let me go.
- You're not going to kill him, are you?
What are you doing?
- Just watch.
(coughing)
- I'll give you what you want,
just please don't kill me man.
Come on.
(choking)
- What the hell do you do that for? Why?
- To prove to you that I'm not a liar.
- What if somebody saw
you? Somebody saw my car?
- No one will find him.
And nobody saw me.
I put him someplace
special, you might say.
No one will ever find him.
- But don't you think
I'm going to turn you in?
- Seems to me it could have been you.
- [Jason] What?
- Didn't you notice that
I was wearing your shirt?
I was driving your car.
I don't know that guy from Jack.
But he was one of your friends, wasn't he?
- You think I'm not going
to tell somebody about this?
You just fucking killed somebody.
- If the police ever found out about this,
or found this video tape,
seems to be on the evidence
would be pointing towards you.
I gotta admit,
I left a little something out.
A little piece of evidence.
Something that might belong to you.
- What are you talking about?
- You're not going to tell
the police about this,
or anyone else for that matter.
Unless you want the same
thing to happen to you
or someone you care about.
- You're crazy.
- You think?
- So
I think the best thing would be
just keep your mouth shut about
his whole ordeal, don't you?
I thought you'd see it my way.
Besides, this could be fun.
I mean, you and me have a lot in common.
I could get used to staying here.
And I could get used to
Kylie.
Yeah, I could get used to this.
(droning music)
- Kylie.
Kylie.
It's me, Kylie.
Come here, Kylie.
I won't hurt you.
It's me, Kylie.
Kylie.
Come here Kylie.
I will always have you, Kylie.
Always.
Always have you.
(gasping)
(balls clacking)
- Jason, what's up with Ryan?
I thought he was only going
to be here for a few days.
He's been here for two weeks now.
- He's looking for work.
- Looking for work?
Why isn't he looking for a place to stay?
- How is he supposed to pay for a place
when he doesn't even have any money?
- Why is that your problem?
- I just can't do that to somebody.
- Why not?
I mean, you don't owe him anything.
For God's sake, you
don't even know the man.
- Look, I don't want to
talk about this anymore.
- Jason, there's something
not right about him.
(knocking)
I'll get it. It'll be Rick.
(balls clacking)
- Hi.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Oh not much, just downstairs
and we're playing pool.
- Everything okay?
- Well, he is still here.
- Want me to tell him to
get the hell out of here?
- No, that will just cause a
fight between him and Jason.
Besides, he will fight
to stay for some reason.
- Hey, you two.
Why don't you come back down?
- I'm just going to talk
to Rick for a minute, okay?
- Okay.
- See what I mean?
It's like it's his house
and we're the guests here or something.
Why don't you come stay
with me for a couple of days
and get out of here?
- I don't know, I just...
- [Jason] Hey Rick.
Yeah, he thinks he's some kind of
billiards pro or something.
- Hey guys,
I'm gonna stay at Rick's
for a couple of days, okay?
- [Ryan] Aw, come on now, Kylie.
You know how much you'll
be missed around here.
Want a drink?
- No thanks, I don't drink.
- [Ryan] Aw, come on, one won't kill you.
- She doesn't drink.
- [Ryan] Julie, how about you?
- [Julie] Sure, I'll have one.
- [Ryan] Jason, can I
hook you up with a drink?
- [Jason] Oh no thanks, bro.
- [Ryan] What about you, Rick?
- No, I don't drink either.
- [Ryan] Aw what a bunch of pansies.
- Hey Julie, guess who I saw today.
- [Julie] Who?
- [Kylie] Cara.
- [Kylie] Cara,
you know, runs the
restaurant down on fourth?
- [Julie] Oh yeah, how's she doing?
- Oh, she's doing good.
She happened to mention
that her head counter person just quit.
- Very subtle, Kylie.
- Excuse me?
- Why didn't you just
come right out and say it?
You want me to go down there
and apply for the job, don't you?
- Well, Ryan, you always say
there's nothing out there.
Here's an opportunity.
- Working for a restaurant
for minimum wage.
Yeah. I would just love that.
I don't think so.
- It's a job.
- Not what I want to do.
- [Jason] Kylie. Mom called the other day.
She said she's coming for a
visit in a couple of weeks.
- Well, I hope there's room for her.
- Hey, anybody want to play doubles?
- No, we're going to get going.
Do you want to get something to eat?
- Sure.
- Hey, I'm going to
stay with Rick tonight,
so don't wait up for me, okay?
- Okay.
- Hey Kylie.
Don't stay away too long.
Things won't be the same
around here without you.
(ominous music)
- Julie?
- What?
- Are you mad at me or something?
- Jason, how can you be so stupid
as to not see what's going on?
- What?
- How can you be so blind?
- What are you talking about?
- When is he going to leave?
- Oh, you mean Ryan?
- What was going through your head
when you brought him here, anyway?
- I was just trying to help the guy out.
- And what are you doing now?
Still helping him out?
When are you going to
be the man of the house
and kick him out?
Can't you see what's going on?
How he's affecting us? And Kylie.
She can't do anything
without him being up her ass.
He wants to do this for her,
he wants to do that for her.
Can't you see what's going on?
- I think you're just overreacting.
- No, I'm not.
It's like he's taking control
of your life, our lives.
You used to watch out for Kylie and me.
And now it's like, you've
picked him over us.
- That's ridiculous.
- No, it's not.
You've changed. He's
taken charge of your life.
Of our lives.
- Will you shut up?
I'm not picking him over anybody.
I'm just trying to help the guy out.
- Jason, will you just listen to yourself?
You'd never raised your
voice to me before.
Just think about it, Jason.
Something's going on
here and it's not right.
You've changed.
And whether or not you want
to admit it, he's changed you.
- Hey, what's up man?
- Hey, not much. Went
out looking for a job.
- Any luck?
- Man, there ain't nothing in this town.
- Tell me about it. Took
me forever to find a job.
- So what's up with Kylie?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, every time I go
to do something with her,
she seems so mad at me.
- Oh, you know girls.
- Yeah.
Jason,
I really like your sister.
I mean, I really like her.
I mean, I know she has
a boyfriend and all,
but I just like being around her.
I want to take her out
on a date some time.
Just me and her to dinner
and a movie or something.
Just a little something that's fun.
Have a good night out on the town.
- Man, you know she's got a boyfriend.
She really loves Rick.
They've been going out for a long time,
I don't think she's going to do it...
- Look, I want you to tell
her to take me up on my offer.
Nothing's going to happen to her.
No one will come near her.
I'll protect her.
Look,
just a little something.
Just me and her, a night on the town.
Nothing big.
She might have fun. You never know.
I mean, she might even get
second thoughts about Rick.
I mean, you know, how
much of a jerk he is.
Joke.
Come on.
But it's true enough.
I joke again.
- All right. I'll talk to her.
But I can't guarantee anything.
But I'll talk to her for you.
But you gotta do something for me.
- Name it.
- Well, you're gonna-
- You want me to leave.
- No.
- Yes.
Look, I know the girls knew
anyway, it's your place, man.
You're just so kind for
trying to help me out.
You said I could stay for a couple of days
and here it's been a couple of weeks.
Look,
you hook me up with your sister,
the next day, I'm going. Promise.
- All right, then. I'll call her.
I'll talk to her.
- Thanks.
Hey Jason.
- Yeah?
- You still trust me don't you?
- Sure.
- Look, I swear,
give me a night on the
town with your sister,
the next day, I'm history.
- All right. It's a deal.
(eerie music)
(phone ringing)
- TradingView Video. Can I help you?
Jason.
How you doing?
Well, great.
Yeah, hold on. She just walked in.
It's Jason.
- Jason, what's up?
- Kylie, you gotta do me a favor.
All right? I talked to Ryan.
He said he's going to leave,
but he wants to take you on a date first.
Otherwise he won't.
- What?
No way.
- [Jason On Phone] Listen, he said
he just wants to go out to a movie
or out to dinner or
something. Just as friends.
- No.
Why should I have to go out
with him if I don't want to?
- Come on, you gotta,
you gotta do this for me. All right?
Do you want him to leave or not?
- Yeah, I want him to leave,
but what's him leaving have to do with me?
- There's gonna be all
kinds of people there.
What's the big deal?
- That's not the point. The
point is I don't want to,
and you can't make me.
- Kylie, what's going on?
- There's this guy staying with us
and it was only supposed
to be for a few days,
but now he won't leave.
And he keeps looking at me. He scares me.
- What guy? Who is he?
- Just some hitchhiker my
dumb brother picked up.
- What?
Listen to me.
You don't have to do anything
that you don't want to do.
If you don't want to go
out with this guy, don't.
Besides what about Rick?
Doesn't he have anything
to say about that?
- Oh my God. There he is.
- Look, go to the back
room. I'll talk to him.
Can I help you?
- Oh, I'm just a friend of Kylie's.
- She's-
Kylie's really busy right now.
- Won't keep her but a minute.
- I really don't think she
wants to talk to you right now.
- And I really don't think
it's any of your business.
- Well I'm making it my business.
I think you better leave.
- You're going to be all right?
- Yeah, I'll be okay.
- Come on, I'll walk you to your car.
- Okay.
- Listen, if you guys need
anything, you know my number.
- You're so sweet.
- What can I say?
- No, but really Steve.
I really appreciate what you
did for me in there tonight.
- Promise to call if you need anything?
- I promise.
- Okay. See you tomorrow.
- Yeah, see you.
(creepy music)
(choking)
- You should mind your own
business, shouldn't you, asshole?
There you go.
You would have been a good boy.
You wouldn't have had to
worry about protecting her.
- Rick?
What are you doing here?
Where is everyone?
- First of all, I don't
need a reason to be here
except that my girlfriend lives here.
And second of all, I don't
know where everybody is.
Kylie hasn't come home yet.
And if she doesn't come home soon,
I'm going to go looking for her.
But while you're here,
why don't you take a seat?
We need to talk.
- So talk.
- I want to know what
the hell is going on.
- With what?
- With you. You know
Kylie and I are dating
and are probably going to get married.
But you keep,
you keep going after her.
So what's wrong with you?
She doesn't like you. And
matter of fact, she hates you.
So why don't you just stay away from her?
We love each other very much.
So why don't you just stay away?
Take the hint.
- She never told me that.
You know, I think she
wants to date other guys,
but you won't let her.
All she knows is you,
you won't let her see
that there's a lot more
that the world has to
offer besides just you.
A little red neck, little town, boy.
- Look, Ryan,
you seem like a nice guy and
I don't think there should be
more problems.
Am I right?
I think it'd be best if you
just packed your bags and well,
and just left.
(dramatic music)
- What's wrong with you?
- What do you mean?
- You're psycho.
- Psycho.
I guess you should stop me then.
That was okay.
Let's see if you can take mine.
- Man, what's your problem? Just back off.
- Back off?
- Yeah.
- Hm,
You're right. Definitely back off.
(grunting)
(creepy music)
- Hello?
Anybody home?
- [Julie] Kylie?
(music intensifies)
(muffled screaming)
- Julie? Kylie?
Anybody home?
Where the hell is everyone?
(bag unzips)
(choking)
(muffled screaming)
- See what I did to your friends, huh?
You want some of that?
Oh, yeah.
(screaming)
- No!
No!
- Shut up!
- No!
- That sick motherfucker.
(indistinct shouting)
- How many people did he kill?
(grunting)
- Please just let me go.
- Yeah, I can't do that. You know why.
- I'll do anything.
- Look, I really don't see
what the problem here is.
I mean, we all die sometime.
- Please I'll do anything. Anything.
I won't tell anyone.
- You know, maybe I
should just let you go.
(screaming)
- Holy shit.
- What are you doing with me Ryan?!
Oh God, what are you doing?!
No!
(screaming)
- What are you doing?!
(indistinct crying)
- [Ryan On TV] You taste
as good as you smell.
(screaming)
- No!
Get back!
(screaming)
- What are you doing?
- Oh my God!
Julie!
(music intensifies)
(choking)
(grunting)
- Son of a bitch!
- I will fucking kill you.
(grunting)
(gunshot)
(Jason groaning)
- I guess I can't find here
everything I was looking for, huh?
(gunshot)
- Well, now we can be together.
I mean everything that
was in our way before
is now not.
I won't hear anybody say anything now,
right?
I think we have their approval.
- Why are you doing this?
- Why?
So we can be together.
Just like it was meant to be.
Because I love you.
- You're crazy.
- Crazy?
Crazy for you.
Crazy cause I love you.
- [Kylie] I don't love you!
I hate you!
You make me sick!
- Hey, don't say such silly things!
- Help me!
- Shut up.
Shut the fuck up, you stupid bitch.
Can't you see that I love you?
No, you can't see it. You want Rick.
Just like Mary wanted Peter.
Just like Cara wanted Chris.
You want Rick over me, huh?
Well, it's a good thing.
Tell you what,
I'll take you to him now.
Aw, don't cry.
Close your eyes and say good night.
Because it's the last thing
you'll ever say in this world.
(sobbing)
(screaming)
(gunshot)
(ground crunching)
- Need a lift?
- Uh yeah, sure.
(music intensifies)
- [Driver] Where you headed?
- [Ryan] Oregon.
- So what are you headed to Oregon for?
- A new beginning.
(music drones)