(upbeat music)
♪ Got a hot white heart
and a steady hand ♪
♪ And I can feel this hourglass
is runnin' outta sand ♪
♪ And I got nowhere to and
all night to get there ♪
♪ We're too young for this rockin' chair ♪
♪ My nerves are jangled,
crackle like a hickory fire ♪
♪ One look in her eyes ♪
♪ You know she's everything
you ever desired ♪
♪ Ooo, somethin' wild ♪
♪ I'm scared of my future and
I'm runnin' from my past ♪
♪ I wanna make each and
every little moment last ♪
♪ I'm gonna howl at the moon,
I'm gonna shout at the stars ♪
♪ I'm gonna be four on this old guitar ♪
♪ My nerves are jangled,
crackle like a hickory fire ♪
♪ One look in her eyes ♪
♪ You know she's everything
you ever desire ♪
♪ Ooo, somethin' wild ♪
♪ Oh ♪
- OK.
All right we're lookin' for an eight,
looking for an eight.
Give these a kiss for luck.
All right, here we go, eight.
For and eight!
- Come on.
- Seven.
- Damn!
- [Croupier] Better luck next time folks.
Please place your bets.
- Doesn't seem to be my night.
- Hey, you can afford to
lose every once in a while.
Now that you're big
timer Hollywood writer.
- I like the sound of that.
♪ It's brought up from my past ♪
- Nice lookin' place huh?
- Yeah.
- Let's go see what happens.
How you doing?
- Hi, welcome, to the
Riviera Hotel and Casino.
- I think we'd like to get
one room for tonight, please.
- If you could just fill this out.
- Uh, Sir, I'm afraid with room and tax
this card is at its limit.
Any incidentals you will
have to pay cash for.
- It's OK, we're leaving tomorrow morning.
Back to LA.
- Your card.
And have a good night.
- We sure will, thanks.
(Sally giggling)
You ready?
(tense electronic music)
Here's to us.
Cheers.
(upbeat rock music)
- Was it worth it, honey?
- Every minute.
- Let's get outta here.
Glen, thanks.
- Thanks sir.
(engine rumbling)
♪ Pack up your bags, baby ♪
♪ Grab your cigarette ♪
♪ Headin' back to the wild, wild west ♪
♪ Throw what you need
in my old Chevrolet ♪
♪ With little bit of luck
we can make out get away ♪
♪ Now all my friends say
I'm crazy for leavin' ♪
♪ But every day it gets
little harder to believe ♪
♪ And the sky so big my heartache ♪
♪ I've had all the
Tinseltown that I can take ♪
♪ So I'm headin' back
to the Lone Star State ♪
♪ Gonna try and find what I left
behind before it's too late ♪
♪ Wanna see my family in
the Red River Valley ♪
♪ And the desert ♪
(pensive music)
(birds calling)
- Hey honey?
- What?
- While you're out buy
yourself something special.
- With what? My good looks and charm.
- No, we get that check today.
So write a check, OK.
(phone ringing)
Good luck.
Hello.
- Jed, Marty, we need to talk.
- Hey Marty, man, how you doing?
It's a great day.
What do you gotta talk about?
- We better do in person, you know,
why don't you meet me for lunch.
- Sorry, I can't Sally just took the car.
- All right, I'll stop by your place.
How about a half hour?
- I'll see you then.
- See you then, OK, bye.
(engine rumbling)
- Hey, Marty.
- Jed.
- So what's up?
- Why don't we go inside?
You know, when you two took off to Vegas
to celebrate over the weekend?
Well, I have to empty feeling
inside, know what I mean?
- No, don't know what you mean.
(Marty sighing)
- Well, they started playing
the Hollywood Shuffle
over the weekend.
They sold the studio, fired all my people
(Marty sighing)
and canceled your contract.
- Oh God, dammit, Marty.
Hey, I am screwed, man.
You know that sale came just in time.
God dammit!
Man I am broke.
- I know. Jed.
Look, I'm sorry.
I mean, I know words
don't mean a damn thing
at a time like this.
Come on, perk up.
I got a few more places to send it, OK?
- Forget about it, forget about it.
- Look, if you need a little extra cash.
- I'm not taking any more money from you.
No.
- OK, but you know where
it is if you need it.
- Yeah, thanks, appreciate it.
- I'll call you later.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Fuck!
(pensive music)
- Jed, is everything all right?
I got something for you.
- Yeah. Well, you better take it back
before the check bounces.
The deal fell through.
We don't have any money.
- [Sally] How did it happen?
- Marty stopped by, gave me the bad news.
Something happened over the weekend
and the whole damn thing fell apart.
I told you we should have gone over there
and signed those god
damned papers on Friday.
- You told me that it didn't matter.
- I don't know what the
hell we're gonna do.
- Hey, it's gonna be OK.
We're really not any worse
off than before Friday.
- I had a taste of it, OK?
It's just kind of hard going
back to being a a nobody.
See things, were gonna be different.
- I know.
It's all right though.
- No, it's not all right.
It's not all right for me.
- Jed, why don't we go
get a drink, you know,
relax and try and think things over.
- Look, if you wanna go get
a drink, we can go to Chicks.
- Forget it, I'm not going in there.
- Oh, come on Sally,
it's the only place we can drink for free.
- OK?
Just this once.
(jazzy electronic music)
(jazzy rock music)
(crowd cheering)
♪ Hmm, Pauline ♪
♪ Let me take you for a ride ♪
♪ Whoa, Pauline ♪
♪ Well I wanna find out what you
been tryin' so hard to hide ♪
♪ You tell me everything is fine ♪
♪ Baby I can tell that's a lie ♪
♪ It's a lie, it's a doggone lie ♪
♪ You tell me everything is fine ♪
♪ Baby I can tell that's a lie ♪
♪ It's a lie, it's a doggone lie ♪
♪ Yeah you mope around all day ♪
♪ And all night long you cry ♪
♪ Cry and cry and cry and cry ♪
♪ Pauline, let me take you for a ride ♪
♪ Oh, Pauling, let me
take you for a ride ♪
- So what's up?
- I got engaged.
- Get outta here, to who?
- Actually, she's here.
Honey, come on over here.
You are gonna love her.
Honey. I want you to meet
my friends, Jed and Sally.
- Hi. Nice to meet you both.
- Hi.
- It's nice to meet you.
You're a terrific dancer.
- Thank you.
Some people would call it
an art form, write Chick.
- You know, you're the best baby.
- Well, it would be nice to
hear it a little more often.
- Hey, Nikki, you shouldn't
be so hard on yourself.
You're very good.
- You think so?
- Yeah, I watch your, you're good.
- Chick, make me a martini.
- You've already had two.
- Shut up.
- Honey, I really think-
- I don't care what you think.
You can go up on that stage and strip.
- So how long the two of you been engaged?
- 10 days.
- Two weeks.
- So, which is it?
- You know I'm right.
- Two weeks.
- Gotta go.
- Hell of a woman you got there, Chick.
- You know I may be able
to help you guys out.
- How.
- Let you in on this
little thing I have going.
- I don't think so.
- [Chick] You don't even know what it is.
- I, I know you.
- Come on, let him tell us about it.
- Horse race, I'm going to Vegas tomorrow.
Gonna lay down a bundle.
It's a sure thing.
It's paying two to one.
It's gonna give me a quick 40 grand.
They've got it fixed.
- Yeah, that, that's what they say.
- No, it's guaranteed.
Four of the jockeys are in on it.
- Well, Chick, man, you're gonna be rich.
- I do whatever it takes
to get on this one.
Beg, borrow, steal.
This is the chance of a lifetime.
- OK, so say we wanna get into this?
Midnight's, the deadline,
five grand minimum.
- Gee, honey, you got five
grand laying around somewhere
I don't know about?
- Well, there is money my parents sent us.
We were saving on down
payment for a house.
- What?
- Excuse us a second Chick.
Jed, let's do this.
- Are you crazy?
- Just place the bet.
We'll tell Chick we have
the money in the bank.
Even if we don't, the race is fixed.
It's a sure thing.
No one will ever have to know
we never had the money in the first place.
- It is kind of a good idea.
OK, but now what if it doesn't work?
What if the horse loses?
- It'll work, I can feel it.
Come on Jed, let's do this.
- OK, let's go for it.
You wanna do it.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
OK, Chick, put us down for five-
- $30,000.
- You guys don't have that kind of money.
- Yeah, yeah, we do.
Yeah, we do.
We just didn't want to, you know,
use the money for the house.
But if it's a sure thing, like you say,
we will never have to touch it, right?
- Nothing's ever a hundred percent.
This is as close as you get though.
(Jed imitates swooshing)
- Let's go for it.
(phone clanging)
♪ Night for you to let her mess with me ♪
♪ Ow ♪
- $60,000.
- Oh my god, Jed.
- 60.
- $60,000.
$60,000.
- $60,000, damn.
- Oh my God, what are we
gonna do with it all, Jed?
- God, I don't know, but
I feel like I, I feel,
I feel like I got the
palm with my hands on it.
- Feel a little bit bad
about lying than Chick,
though, myself.
- Me too.
But hey, even he said it's a sure thing.
- Hey, you're, you're right.
You know what, what he don't
know won't Hurt him, right?
I never knew Chick
was gonna be the answer of our problems.
- Jed.
- What?
- Let's hurry up and get home.
I have something I wanna give to you.
- What'd you have in mind?
(jazzy electronic music)
So what are you gonna give me?
(zipper unzipping)
(phone ringing)
All right.
Yeah, hello?
- Hi, it's me.
- Hey, what's up?
- All bets are in, the race is at four.
I'm leaving for Vegas right now.
- Make sure you call
the, the minutes over.
- All right, I, I just wanted
to confirm it with you.
Listen, Jed, if you want out,
I got somebody I can pass your back to.
- Hey, no, no, no.
I, no, we, we want in, man, wanna do this.
- All right.
- Hey, what's the name of the horse?
- Morning Glory.
I'll call you as soon as it's over.
- OK, talk to you later.
(Sally yawning)
- Who is that?
- It was Chick.
It's leaving for Las Vegas.
He wanted to give us a chance to back out.
- What'd you tell him?
- I told him we wanted to go through it.
- Great.
Go back to sleep.
- Sleep.
How can you sleep?
There's 30 grand on the line
that we don't even have.
- I can't.
Let's go then.
If we leave right now
and drive really fast,
we can make it in time for the race.
- Really?
- Well, if we stay here,
we're just gonna go nuts.
If we win when we win,
we can stay for a few days and celebrate.
(jazzy rock music)
(engine rumbling)
♪ Got a hot white heart
and and a steady hand ♪
♪ And I can feel this hourglass
is runnin' outta sand ♪
♪ I got nowhere to and
all night to get there ♪
♪ We're too young for this rockin' chair ♪
♪ My nerves are jangled,
crackle like a hickory fire ♪
♪ One look in her eyes ♪
♪ You know she's everything
you ever desired ♪
♪ Ooo, somethin' wild ♪
- Hey, what's the name of our horse?
- Morning Glory.
- Oh, I like that name.
Oh, hey, our luggage.
- Oh, let the bellboy get it.
We're gonna miss the race, come on.
- OK.
- Jed, Jed.
Over here.
- Hey, Chick.
Good to see you, man.
- What are you guys doing over here?
- We keep over to watch it in person.
- It's about to start.
Stan, I want you to meet
my friends, Jed and Sally.
- [Jed] Hey.
- Hi.
- I'm Sherry.
- Why don't you guys
pull up right here. OK?
It's gonna start.
- Right here. OK?
- Looks like you two got in on the action.
- Oh yeah, Chick's a friend of ours.
- [Sherry] I hope he's right.
- [Sally] So do we.
- Well if you need a place
to stay, mention my name.
They know me here, they'll
give you a good deal.
- OK, thanks.
(bell ringing)
- [Race Announcer] They're
up and they're off.
Pack is breaking evenly.
It's Morning Glory in the lead.
Morning Glory pulls out by two.
Morning Glory, followed by Forever Yours.
Forever Yours moving back by two.
Coming up to the first turn.
Still Morning Glory in the lead.
Moving out and the crowd
is starting to thin out.
It's morning glory, breaking away by four.
Morning glory by four.
Forever Yours in second by two.
Coming up back.
- Oh my Jed, we're gonna
win, we're gonna win.
Oh my god Jed, oh my god!
- [Race Announcer] It is Morning Glory.
No, it's Forever Yours, pulling up.
They're going neck and neck.
It's Forever Yours, Forever Yours.
Forever Yours is the winner.
Morning Glory in second.
- Oh well.
Better luck next time.
Ta ta.
- You gotta be kidding me.
I lose my own money on this race.
A sure thing, god I can't believe it.
Look, you're in big trouble.
You just better get all the bets.
You got that?
- I'm really sorry, Jed.
- Yeah, well that doesn't
do me much good now,
does it Chick?
I can't believe I'll let
you talk me into this.
You know, the minute that he
suggested this, I said no,
because I know Chick.
I know that Chick is full of shit.
And then you had to go and
stick your nose into it
and say it was OK to do.
- It's not my fault, Jed.
- It was a fluke, Jed,
we all went down on this.
- Look, I've got to be
the biggest freaking idiot
that ever walked on the god damned Earth.
I should have known that my
old buddy here, Chickster here,
was involved, and I was
going to get screwed somehow.
And I did.
- Now that you had your little tantrum,
I hope you feel better,
but I still need the money.
- Of course, of course.
You need the money, yeah.
Yeah.
- I assume you don't
have it on you right now,
so I'll give you to tomorrow
morning to get it to me, OK?
- That's fine, Chick.
- So how about you meet me
at the bar in the casino
tomorrow at noon?
- No problem.
- I'm sorry.
- Jed, I have an idea.
- Honey, if I were you,
just get as far away
from me as possible, OK?
Just run.
Because he's gonna have men
come and do things to me.
I don't know.
- I'm not you, Jed.
I love you, no matter what happens.
I think it's time we had some good luck.
You're gonna have to trust me though.
- Come on, come on.
- Look, you said you
had a plan, what is it?
- Come on, come on, Jed.
- What are we gonna do here?
- I'd like to have this change into chips.
- Where'd you get that?
- It's our rent money.
Relax, I brought it just
in case I'm emergency.
- How would you like that?
- Honey, don't you think
we've pressed our luck enough for one day?
- Jed, just let me do this.
I know we're gonna win, I can feel it.
In $50 pieces.
- Thank you.
OK, we're gonna put all of this
on red and we're gonna win.
Then we're gonna double down
and we're gonna keep winning.
And then we're gonna go home
and forget all about this
terrible night.
- [Croupier] Everybody
please, place your bets.
- Everything on red?
- No, no, just do half.
- [Croupier] All bets are final.
- To black, black.
Can I, can I still change the black?
- Quickly?
- I, I just feel Black.
I feel Black.
- Come on, come on, come on, come on.
- Black, Black.
Black, Black.
- Come on Black.
- Black, Black.
(ball rattling)
Ah shit!
- [Croupier] Red 16. Red 16.
- OK, OK, forget it.
Gimme the rest of the chips,
we have to win this one.
Black.
- Black, Black, Black, Black.
(ball rattling)
- [Croupier] Red. 23, Red 23.
- Oh my god, Jed, I'm sorry.
- [Croupier] OK, place your bets please
ladies and gentlemen.
(pensive music)
- [Clerk] Sir, this is not a pawn shop.
- Yeah, I know, I know.
Look, we got ourselves into
a little bit of a bind.
Th these are very expensive rings
and I will sell these to
you at a real discount.
- These are both beautiful rings.
Clearly bought in better times.
- That was my grandmother's.
- [Clerk] How much do you want for both.
- I don't know, make an offer.
- I'll give you $3750.
- Three-
- I know they're probably
worth more than twice that.
Tell you what, I'll just
hold them for 48 hours.
If your luck changes,
come back and I'll let you buy
them back for the same price.
- OK?
- Thank you very much.
- Take some advice though.
Use the money.
Pay off whatever it is
you have to pay off.
Don't press your luck, this is Vegas.
(ball rattling)
- [Croupier] Red. 34.
- Yes, yes!
(Sally screaming)
- [Croupier] And we have a winner!
Congratulations.
- Thank you God.
- Oh my god.
OK, let's go again.
Everything on red, I can feel it.
OK, come on.
- Hello, Roberto.
- Good evening, Ms. Landis.
Is everything OK?
- Everything's great.
I feel like playing a
little blackjack tonight.
- I can take you to your table.
- Great.
Oh, wait, that couple.
I recognize them.
What do you know about them?
- [Roberto] They're causing quite a stir.
- Really?
How are they doing.
- So far, they're winning.
(sultry jazzy music)
(gasping)
Perhaps I'll play some roulette instead.
(ball rattling)
- [Croupier] All bets are final.
Here we go.
Red 17.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God.
- [Croupier] Congratulations.
- $15,000.
- That would've seemed like
a lot of money 24 hours ago.
- We've got 15,000 here, honey.
- Yeah.
- Good evening, Ms. Landis.
How are you tonight?
- Just fine.
Jed, what is your favorite number?
- My favorite number is lucky number 13.
- OK, $10,000 on 13.
- Oh, 34 Red.
Sorry, Ms. Landis.
- Oh, well I'd pay a lot
more for a man like you.
- I'm sorry, what was that?
- Nothing.
You two look like you've had a hard day.
- We have.
- Allow me to do you a favor.
I have a few suites
that are kept available
for myself and my guests
and I'd like to give
you one for the night.
- I don't know.
Would you like to?
- We still need $15,000 more,
but I am kind of tired
and I'd like a hot shower.
Something along those lines.
- OK, great, we'd like to.
- Great, I am delighted.
It's on the top floor.
Have a nice night.
(jazzy electronic music)
(Sally moaning)
(Sally panting)
- Oh yeah.
- What time is it?
- Hmm?
- I don't know.
Oh, Jesus, one o'clock in the afternoon.
- We were supposed to meet Chick at 12.
- I know, I know.
Let me call him, I just wanna
make sure it doesn't worry.
Hey Chick, hi, it's Jed here.
Sorry, we missed you at 12 o'clock.
We'll have the money for
you by this evening, OK?
I'm sorry about this,
but I'll call you room back
and let you know where to meet us, OK?
Thanks. Bye.
- What did he say, did he freak out?
- No, he wasn't there.
Left the message on his hotel voicemail.
- So what do we do?
- Get dressed.
Go down to the casino and
win 15,000 more dollars.
(upbeat rock music)
- Here we go.
- Roll it!
- Yes.
- Snake eyes.
That's it, buddy.
- Where do we start?
- [Croupier] Congratulations,
place your bets.
- OK, what we're gonna do this time,
we're gonna be small portions
and we're gonna bet smart.
Hopefully we'll get on a roll pretty early
and get the hell outta here.
- Let's go.
- OK, let's go, roll the dice.
- Come on now.
(dice rattling)
(patrons cheering)
- Yes, Ms. Landis?
- That couple from last night,
they're back on the floor.
- [Roberto] I already noticed that.
I'm on top of it.
- Here we go, big eight!
- You're kidding me, right?
- No, I just had this little problem
that I was gonna tell you about.
- You're $30,000 short.
- This guy and, and his
wife, they took off on me.
- Wait a minute.
Is this the couple that
was at the sports book
at the casino?
- It's them.
(ominous music)
- This is not good Chick.
'Cause I don't know where they are.
They could be anywhere.
However, I know where you are.
(Chick yelling)
Tell me where they are.
- You're gonna break my arm.
- That's the whole idea, talk to me.
- I don't know.
They were supposed to meet
me at the casino by the bar.
- First, you turned me on
to that stupid horse race.
And then you take a
$30,000 bet and it walks.
I gotta tell you something, Chick.
I am really unhappy with you right now
so you better think where they might be.
- Stan, I swear to God, I
don't know where they are.
- I don't got no reason to
keep you around anymore.
- [Chick] Stan.
I thought they were OK.
- You thought wrong?
Put him out of my misery.
(punch pounding)
(Chick groaning)
(slap popping)
- Stan, don't do this.
Please.
- Shut up.
- He's bad luck.
I don't want to see or hear
from that fuck ever again.
Do it.
(gun ratcheting)
- Please don't.
(gunfire booming)
- Sherry, I was just
taking care of business.
So what can I do for you?
- Well, actually, Stan,
that's what I came to talk
to you about, business.
You miss me.
- Sure.
- Good.
(pensive music)
(jazzy electronic music)
- [Croupier] Black 15,
Black 15, sorry, folks.
(pensive music)
- We're broke.
That's it.
- I can't believe we lost it that quickly.
- Well, we did.
We got about about a hundred bucks left.
That'll be about enough to
get us back to Los Angeles.
- We can't go home, Chick will kill us.
- I don't know what else to do.
- We can go to Florida.
- No way, you can just forget about that.
- I'll call my parents, they
can wire us plane tickets.
We can stay there until
we get back on our feet.
- Yeah, yeah, I, I can just see the look
on your father's face
when he comes to pick
us up at the airport.
That's self righteous prick.
- Don't talk about him like that.
What else are we gonna do?
Can't go home.
We certainly can't go to your parents.
- I'll tell you what,
I'll go back to Los Angeles and get killed
before I take a god damn
dime from your parents.
Let alone live with them in Florida.
- Well, what then?
- I don't know, Sally.
But yelling in my face is not gonna help.
- I'm just trying to
figure out our options.
- Look, why don't you just leave me alone
for a little while, OK, I gotta think.
- Gladly, in fact, I'll leave
you alone for a long while.
How's that?
- That's great.
- Hello.
- Hi, what you live here?
- Practically?
You don't look so great, is everything OK?
- My wife and I just
lost all of our money.
We came in here, we thought
we could win back enough money
to pay back the money we
lost at the horse races.
- That's a bad idea, the
odds are against you.
- Yeah, but where else can
you win $30,000 in two days?
- I can think of a few ways.
$30,000 isn't that much money.
- Maybe not for you.
- I can think of a way that
you can get that kind
of money very quickly.
- Really, how?
- Spend the rest of the
night with me. In my suite?
(Jed chuckling)
- Yeah.
That's a joke, right?
- No joke.
- No, I really couldn't.
Nah.
- Well.
- Well just, just outta curiosity.
Well how much are we talking about?
- $40,000, payable at sunrise?
- Well you know, you know I'm married.
- I don't wanna know.
Do we have a deal?
- Are you serious?
- Totally.
You turn me on.
- Well, I've never
cheated on my wife before.
- Well, if what you say is true
and you're really need the money,
well you're probably doing
it for your wife in a way.
Plus no one says she has
to find out about it.
Right?
- She's staying right here in the hotel.
You know that?
- Well, I saw you two were in a fight.
Why don't you just tell her
that you spent the night out
wandering around thinking.
- $40,000.
- $40,000, uh-huh.
- OK.
It's a deal.
- I'm delighted.
Come with me.
(pensive music)
Sorry I took so long.
- It's OK.
Why, why are you so dressed up?
- Well, I'm paying for it,
so I thank you to indulge me.
- OK?
- Is everything all right?
- [Jed] Fine.
- Take a look at this.
- It's an incredible view.
- Yes, it is.
I thought it would be nice
if we just relax, talk,
get to know each other.
Hope you're thirsty.
- Yeah, you know, as a matter
of fact, I'm very thirsty.
- So, aren't you gonna
tell me how nice I look?
Hmm?
- [Jed] You look very nice.
- Thank you.
(glasses clanging)
- Can I ask you a question?
- [Sherry] Of course.
- [Jed] Why me?
- That's a very good question.
I don't know.
Why are you with your wife?
I mean, why are any two people together?
All I know is that when I saw you,
I found you completely irresistible.
- That's very interesting,
very interesting.
- Are you hungry, can
I ring for some food?
- No, I'm sorry.
Under the given circumstances.
I don't think I could
enjoy a meal right now.
- Why, you're not comfortable?
- No, I'm, I'm not comfortable.
- Well, that's what the champagne is for.
It's to get you loose so we can
get to know each other, hmm?
- Cheers.
Tell you what.
You invited to me up
here to fuck you, right?
Well, this bar looks very sturdy.
Why don't you just climb
up here and let's fuck,
get it over with.
What do he say?
- I didn't say "fuck me."
I said spend the night with me.
And since I am paying,
I will decide what happens
when it happens, and how.
Now, sit down.
Figuring how desperate you seemed earlier.
I really think that you
could use another drink.
Hmm?
- Cheers.
How about another bottle then?
- Good idea.
- You're, you're a damn beautiful woman.
And I'll tell you what, if I
wasn't a happily married man,
I'd probably be enjoying myself right now.
- Well, if you weren't married,
then we wouldn't be doing it.
That's the whole point.
- What is?
- Turning you on when you
don't wanna be turned on?
That's what every woman
wants, to be irresistible.
You mentioned the sturdiness of this.
Well, I assure you it's a
multi-purpose piece of furniture.
(Sherry gasping)
Touch me.
- [Jed] I got it.
- Undo my dress.
- There you go.
Oh boy.
(door banging)
- [Stan] Sherry, it's me.
Sherry, open up the door.
Sherry, I'm gonna smash down
this door, now open it up.
- Come with me.
- [Stan] Sherry, I know you're in there.
Open up the door, now.
(door banging)
- Shh.
- Who hell is that.
- [Stan] Who's in there with you?
- Stan?
- Who the hell is Stan?
- He's the guy that you owe $30,000 to.
- What the hell is he doing here?
What's he doing here?
- I don't, I don't wanna talk about it.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Jed, make love to me.
- But.
- Just, just, make love to me, OK?
(smooth jazzy music)
(singer vocalizing)
♪ Beauty ♪
♪ A tantalizing tease ♪
♪ Desire ♪
♪ Is a dangerous disease ♪
♪ Searching for something
you cannot remember ♪
♪ The deal is made and you fade away ♪
♪ She's turned you inside out ♪
♪ You're no longer what
you're talkin' about ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ You're playin' with fire ♪
- Ow!
♪ And you're gonna burn ♪
- Sorry.
- [Jed] God, ow!
- Take your pants off.
♪ Moonlight ♪
- Take 'em off for me
♪ And you're gonna burn ♪
- [Receptionist] Front desk.
- My name is Sally Mills.
I was wondering if maybe my
husband left a message for me.
- [Receptionist] No, I'm sorry.
There are no messages.
- Thank you very much.
- Good morning.
- [Jed] What time is.
- Nearly noon.
- Oh shit, oh shit.
Oh shit, oh shit.
- Drank a lot last night.
- Oh man, I must have.
- You were wonderful.
- Thank you.
Look, it's well past,
whoa, it's well passed dawn here.
Can I get my money so I can go?
- That's fine.
- Oh, oh man.
I have to figure out what
I'm gonna tell my wife
where I got that $40,000 from.
- Who says you have to tell her the truth?
Why don't I just tell
you to talk to the bookie
and he says he's gonna let the bet slide.
- Because somehow I don't
think she's gonna believe that.
- She'd believe you.
Trust me.
- Well, that's because you're a good liar.
- Thanks.
- You can go to your room now.
Money's down in a safe.
I'll call you when I have it.
- Hey, thanks.
- You're welcome.
- No, I really means thanks.
I mean, you really saved me.
So,
had a good time last night.
It was fun.
- So did I.
- [Sally] Jed, where
the hell have you been?
- Hi honey.
- I've been so worried.
I'm sorry, I know I was
mad at you last night, but-
- It's OK, Honey.
I was just walking around and
you know everything's gonna be OK.
- What?
- Yeah, I was talking to
Chick and Chick said, he said,
I'll just take care of the bet for you.
- [Sally] How?
- Ah, he just said he was
gonna erase it outta the book.
I guess.
- I can't believe it, Just like that.
- Yeah. It's pretty amazing, huh?
So what I think we should do,
let's get are stuff all packed up.
Get ready to get the hell outta here
and just forget that this
damn thing ever happened, OK?
- Fine. Let's go right now.
- Oh, we have to wait cuz
he's supposed to call.
He's, he's gonna tell me like
if it's OK to go back to LA,
if it's safe.
(phone ringing)
- I bet that's him.
Hello?
- Hello Jed.
It's me, Sherry.
There's been a development,
we need to talk.
- I'm here with Sally.
Is there some kind of problem?
- I think it would be better
if we talk down here alone.
- Why?
- I'm right near the front desk.
I'll tell you when you get here.
(Jed sighing)
- What, what is it?
- I dunno, there's a problem,
Chick said, I got a call,
I got a call from an outside phone.
OK, what's going.
- I need to talk to you.
- Look, my wife is upstairs.
You're scared to hell outta
me, now what's going on?
- I was upstairs making some phone calls
and I spoke to Stan.
Evidently, he's on some sort
of rampage about the $30,000.
You still owe him?
- I told you I was gonna pay the guy.
- You don't understand it, do you?
Stan is crazy.
He doesn't like to be walked on.
- Whoa, what's that
got to do with a thing?
Like I told you I was
gonna pay the guy today.
I didn't walk on him.
- I know, I know.
- I told him that you were here,
here and you're going back to LA shortly
but he said it doesn't matter.
It's too late.
- Too late.
- And Chicks been hurt.
- How bad?
- I don't know.
And there's another thing.
He said that because you've been late
and you put him through so much trouble
that you now owe him $50,000.
- Jesus Christ.
How can he do that,
wow can he do that?
A bet is a bet.
I mean, you can't just go
change it a bet like that.
Christ sakes, I'm only two days late.
How can he do that?
- I think there's a way
that we can work this out.
- [Jed] How?
- I can just give you the $10,000
in addition to the $40,000
that I already owe you.
- You, you would do that for me.
- Of course.
If you'd spend the night with me again,
I'd give you the money.
- No, it's impossible.
Sally's upstairs, she's
alone, she's scared.
I can't leave her alone again.
- I think I've been pretty fair already.
So what's it gonna be?
It's just a night.
- Ah, OK, look, gimme a couple hours.
I gotta work out something with Sally.
- See you in my room.
- I'll call you, I'll call you.
Fuck.
(jazzy rock music)
- What happened?
- Well, let's go sit down.
Chick said I have to go meet his boss.
Remember that guy at the
horse race, the big guy, Stan?
- The real big scary guy.
- Yeah, that's the guy.
And Chick said he'll probably put me on
some kind of a payment plan,
but I have to meet the guy in person
and I'm supposed to meet
him in about 20 minutes.
- What? Where are you going?
- I don't know, Chick wouldn't say.
- Jed, I don't want you to
do this, it's dangerous.
- Honey, what choice do we have?
Look, I'll call you, let
you know what's happening.
OK, I'll, I'll be back,
I don't know, late tonight,
early tomorrow morning.
- No!
- Look, I'm just gonna go
talk to this guy, Stan,
and reason with the guy.
Chick said everything's gonna be OK.
- Oh, I can't believe it.
And you believe Chick?
- Yeah.
- Well, I can't take it.
I'm leaving.
You can do whatever you want.
- Sally, Sally,
would you just stick with me
a little while longer, honey.
OK, look, I swear to God after tonight,
everything is gonna be OK.
- Jed, I'm just really scared
that something's gonna happen to you.
- I know, everything's gonna be OK though.
I'll be fine, Honey, I love you.
- Jed.
- Look, I gotta go.
I'm really sorry about this.
- [Sally] OK?
- [Jed] I love you.
(pensive music)
- Things are gonna be a
bit different tonight, Jed.
I've got some excitement planned for us.
Would you get this?
- What?
- You want me to tell you now
or do you want it to be a surprise?
- I'd like you to tell me now.
- Well, you're a very handsome man.
So we're gonna go downstairs
and you're gonna seduce a
young lady of my choosing
and then you're gonna bring her up here
and make love to her while I watch.
How does that sound?
- It sounds like I'm not gonna do it.
- [Sherry] What?
- What?
What if Sally sees me?
And besides our agreement was
that I would spend the night
with you, not somebody else.
- I'll be there, Jed.
And our agreement doesn't
prohibit the company of others.
He wants you to invite your wife.
She's really very hot.
I know I'd like it.
- You can forget about it.
- I'm ready, let's go.
- Stop pretending you don't like it.
(sultry electronic music)
Wait, her.
- Her?
- Yeah, her.
(slot machine chiming)
- OK, so, so what do you wanna do?
You gonna walk up to her and say ,
"Hi, why don't you come
upstairs for a threesome?"
That's not gonna work, Sherry.
- Don't underestimate yourself, she's hot.
Just do it.
I'll be right over there,
if she agrees to it
I'll meet you up in my room. OK?
Just pretend I'm not there.
(sultry pensive music)
(slot machine chiming)
(date chuckling)
- There I was sitting on
the other side of the casino
and I saw you sitting there and
I thought, "What the hell?"
You know you are a very beautiful room.
- Thanks.
Wow, this is a really nice room.
- Should I give you the tour?
- Sure.
- OK.
We got the lovely spacious living room.
The baby grand piano, do you play?
- No I don't.
- The bar and the great
panoramic view of Las Vegas.
- Do you mind if I sit down here?
- I don't own the seat.
- Of course you don't.
Seven and Seven please.
- [Bartender] Coming up.
- The only reason I ask
is I don't wanna sit here
If it's gonna bother you.
- It doesn't bother me.
- What happened, did you lose your shirt?
- No, my husband.
- Excuse me.
- Nothing.
- Can I buy you a drink?
- [Date] This is really nice.
- [Jed] I've got a great
view over there of the city.
- [Date] Oh, this is a beautiful view.
- Yeah, it is.
It's, there's the, The Strip over there.
Oh, we got the bed over here too
if you would like to
bounce around a little bit.
- Maybe later.
(smooth jazzy music)
- Later's good.
♪ Alone in the darkness ♪
♪ I know your deepest fear ♪
♪ You cannot touch me ♪
♪ Still I am always near ♪
♪ I will make you pay ♪
♪ Pay for what I'm feelin' ♪
♪ I will have my way in time ♪
♪ Desperate ♪
♪ I'll play ♪
♪ I will have my way in ♪
♪ Desperate ♪
♪ I'll play on your blindness ♪
- So I seem to recall you
saying something earlier about a husband.
- Did I?
- Yes you did.
Are you married?
- Yeah, but I wish I wasn't.
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean to pry.
We can talk about something else.
So what do you do?
- I'm one in a million outta
work actresses in Los Angeles.
- Yeah.
I think it's gonna happen
for you sooner or later.
You strike me as a winner.
- Thanks.
I guess it doesn't mean much
since you've only known me
for half an hour, but thanks.
- No, it means a lot.
I know people, that's my job.
- What did you say you do again?
- I'm a filmmaker.
Not your kind of films though.
I'm a documentary filmmaker.
- So you shoot elephants in
the wild, stuff like that?
- No, no, no, I only shoot people.
They're what interests me.
I study interesting people.
And that's why I came
up and talked to you.
I've just about had it.
I won me $300 tonight.
So I'm want to go back up to my suite.
If you'd like to join me for a nightcap
you're more than welcome.
- I don't think so.
- OK, here's my card.
It has my number on it.
Give me a call sometime.
- You know, I think maybe I
will have that drink after all.
You really make me feel special.
- You are special.
Shall we go?
- OK.
(jazzy electronic music)
- OK, Laura, you can go now.
- That's it, that's all I have to do?
- Yeah, you were great.
- Whoa.
Do you two know each other?
- Yes, she was paid to be
here, much like you were.
I must admit it was amazing.
- [Laura] I'll see you Sherry.
Anytime you need me, I'm available.
And it was nice meeting you.
- Yeah.
Why'd you do that?
Did you think I'd be able to
pick up a woman on my own?
- I just wanted insurance
that my fantasy would be fulfilled.
Jed, I have some things
that I have to tell you.
- What.
- I lied to you about Stan.
(pensive music)
- About what?
- He never said you owed
him many more money.
I made that up.
- Why?
- When I want something, I make it happen.
Like with you.
I wanted you, so I made it happen.
I wanted you for another night
and then I made it happen.
And Chick is dead.
- Chick is dead?
- He didn't pay your debt on time.
- You're,
you're telling me that you
created this whole thing
for your own amusement?
- Yeah.
Wasn't it fun?
You know, the thing is, I want you again.
Huh?
- Get off me.
- Jed.
And I want my money, I want it now.
- It's in the drawer.
But you know what, Jed?
You can't resist me, you want me?
I just want you inside of me, come on.
- I want my money and I want it now.
- You can have your
money, it's right here.
- Get it for me!
Get it.
You can have it anytime you want.
(Sherry giggling)
Be rough with me, Jed, be rough.
- You'd like that?
- Yes, I do.
- You like that?
- You can have it.
You can have your money,
yes, you can have it.
- You want it?
- Oh god, just do it rough.
(Sherry exclaiming)
- I do.
- Yeah?
- You know what?
(Sherry gasping)
Let me tell you something.
This is all for my entertainment
because I don't like to be bored, Jed.
- Shut your mouth.
Shut up.
(jazzy electronic music)
(Sally chuckling)
- Why you being so nice?
- Oh, I guess I'm just a nice guy.
(Sally giggling)
- Really, I have no ulterior motives.
Otherwise, I would've
made a pass at you by now.
- That's not what I meant.
I can tell you're a perfect gentleman.
- So tell me about this husband.
He seems like a real mystery man.
- Lately, he is.
We got ourselves into a
bit of trouble recently.
- What kind of trouble?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
You know, sitting here
talking with you, John,
I'm beginning to remember
what it's like to just relax
and have a pleasant
conversation with someone.
(pensive music)
(jazzy electronic music)
♪ A bad thing ♪
♪ You did it again ♪
♪ You wanna come back but
you're caught in a flame ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ You're playing with
fire, playing with fire ♪
♪ It's turned me inside out ♪
♪ Inside out, but you're
caught in a flame ♪
♪ No, no, no, no ♪
♪ You're playing with fire ♪
♪ You're dark and did me again ♪
♪ Oh, did me again ♪
♪ You wanna turn back but
you're caught in a flame ♪
♪ Oh no, no, Oh no, no ♪
♪ You're playin' with fire ♪
♪ And you're gonna get burned ♪
♪ She's turned you inside out ♪
(Sherry moaning)
(pensive music)
(Sherry moaning and chuckling)
- What, what are you doing here?
You're supposed to be out.
- So Sally, it's not what it looks like.
I can explain.
Hi, Sally, wait!
Sally, wait!
Sally!
(Sherry laughing)
Wait up.
Sally wait.
- No, get away from me.
- Sally, would you wait?
- No!
- Goddammit, wait!
- Let go of me!
- You're gonna wake everybody up.
- I don't care, you have picked, Jed.
Let's go of me!
- Let explain what's going on.
- What possible explanation
could you have for that?
(Sherry chuckling)
- I saw an opportunity
and I took it to get us
out this god damn mess.
OK?
Now what the hell are
you doing in here anyway?
- I got a note telling me to come.
- Oh, that's, god damn bitch.
- It's not what this is about, Jed.
What scares me is it
if I hadn't found out,
you never would've told me.
You had no intention of ever telling me.
I can forgive you for cheating on me, Jed,
but I can't forgive you for lying to me.
I can't trust you, so what-
- Sally, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Sally.
OK, like I'm sorry.
- I'm going back to LA.
- No, where are you gonna go?
Where you gonna go?
- Go back to Florida.
Don't, Sally!
- Get away from me!
- Sally!
Ah, Sally!
(pensive music)
(Jed grunting)
Oh man.
- Were you able to patch things up?
- What do you think?
- I just wanted to see
how far I could take it.
How about now?
Would you consider getting in bed
and making mad, passionate love?
- Right now I wouldn't
even spit in your face.
- Well, I guess I've taken
it to the outer limits.
You did more for money
than I thought you would.
You know, I suppose when
you have a lot of money,
well you just forget how
desperate those without can be.
- Yeah, well, what I
did I did for my life.
That guy Stan might have
killed my wife and I.
- That's true, he very well might have.
That's only why you
agreed in the beginning.
I know men and I know that
when you were with me,
you enjoyed it.
I'd even bet that you were turned on
by the fact that you
were being paid for it.
- Yeah, maybe I was.
But still, you didn't have to
be so cruel to my wife, Sally.
- Look at it this way.
That's $20,000 more than
you thought you'd have.
I could even take it one step further.
Maybe I'll just call Stan and
he'll squelch the whole bet.
That'll be $50,000 all to yourself.
- No, forget about that, OK.
I'll tell you what,
I don't need any more favors from you.
I'll just take my $50,000
and I'll pay off my bet
and then I'm gonna go back
and buy back something
that I had to sell.
OK?
I'll tell you what, gimme
my money and I'm outta here.
- Good luck.
(doorbell buzzing)
- Sally, what's wrong?
- I need a ride back to LA.
Do you think you can gimme one?
- Of course.
Why don't you come in to
get a few hours sleep First.
I am very attracted to you, but.
Whoa, careful, careful.
I don't wanna do this
if it's gonna be something
you end up regretting.
- John, I won't regret it.
(reels booming)
(slot machines chiming)
(jazzy electronic music)
(Sally sighing)
- [Sally] Yeah.
(Sally moaning and panting)
(pensive music)
- Hey, I know it's been
more than two days,
but do you still have
the rings I left here?
- Yes I do.
- Oh, great.
I'd like to buy 'em back.
- However, I did have
an offer on those rings.
It's gonna cost you
$10,000 to get them back.
- How much?
- 10,000.
- 10,000 dol...
- Take it or leave it.
- What?
Bastard.
- Sally.
Sally.
Sally, you here?
Where the...
Shit.
Sally!
Wait!
Where the hell you going?
- I told you where I was going, Jed.
Leave me alone.
- Who the hell's this guy.
- It's John, my ride.
- Look, you're going back
to Los Angeles, Sally,
I'll give you a ride, OK?
- I don't want you to gimme a ride, Jed,
I want you to leave me alone.
Sounds like you found
your calling in life.
- Oh, don't be like that.
- Jed, I loved you so much.
I would've have done anything for you.
But that's it, it's over.
I don't want you in my life anymore.
- I got the rings back, look.
- I don't want it.
Stop it, Jed.
- Sally, I said I was sorry, OK?
- Sorry doesn't cut it.
John, let's go.
- Excuse me.
Hey, I think the lady's made
her feelings clear, don't you?
- No.
- Yeah, I think she has.
- [Jed] I don't think so.
- Hey.
- Whoa, hey, hey.
Take it easy, man.
I got your fuckin' money, all right.
Here, here.
Don't touch me, here's your 10,000 here.
Here, $30,000 , we're square.
- Thanks.
But you don't owe it to
me, you owe it to her.
- To Sherry?
- [Sherry] Jed, you don't look so good.
- Yeah, well my wife just left me.
Thank you.
- Well,
maybe it's for the best.
- What's this guy talking about?
- What, I didn't hear what he said.
- He says I don't owe him the
money, I owe the money to you.
- Oh that,
that was just one little thing
that I neglected to tell you
in my revelation to you last night.
Stan works for me.
I'm the one taking the bets.
Stan's just a collector.
- And what about the
other night in your room
when he was pounding on the goddamn door?
- I guess I'm a fairly decent actress.
(both laughing)
It's all a game.
High stakes bluff, I
guess you got bluffed.
- So you're telling me this
whole thing was a a setup.
You, you made this whole thing up.
- Yes, it was, all
constructed from my amusement.
Life is boring, Jed.
And I just hate to be bored.
- Excuse me, but I'll meet
you back at the office.
- [Sherry] So would you like
to have dinner with me tonight?
- Yeah, sure, why not?
- You mean to tell me
that you'd spend the
night with me for free?
- Yeah, well, I don't have
anything else to lose?
- You know what, I'm really
not interested anymore.
I thought it was fun when
you weren't interested in me.
But now that you are,
you seem so desperate.
- You know you are such a bitch.
- You see that couple
on the roulette wheel?
- Yeah.
- They've been losing
an awful lot of money.
- Yeah, so what?
- He is really quite attractive.
I wonder how bad it's gonna get for them.
Hmm, they lost again.
Too bad.
(pensive music)
- Hey Mister, you got a buck?
- How about a hundred?
- A hundred, you must be a millionaire.
- No, just a writer.
Got a great idea for a screenplay.
- All right, thanks a lot, man.
- No problemo.
- Excuse me.
- Sure, here, I'll get
that for you, Elvis.
- Thank you, thank you very much.
- My pleasure.
(jazzy electronic music)
Yeah!
(pensive music)
(sultry electronic music)
(jazzy electronic music)