[dramatic music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[plane humming]
[dramatic music]
[Williams] Charlie,
Roger, 031915, almost home.
[plane humming]
[Zuchowski] Charlie,
Roger, 040904,
coming in, tower,
I have no issues.
[plane humming]
[Bender] Adam, Tex 699543,
coming in, no problems.
[plane humming]
[McGee] E.T, that's
Easy, Tara, 0710992
coming in, no problems.
[plane humming]
Gentlemen, we're
under 10,000 feet.
They gave us hell for a
while, didn't they, Major?
[Cole] They sure did, Eddy.
How many of those German
rocket planes did you see?
Caught a glimpse of
one, moving really fast.
Hey, Joe!
[Joe] I'm here.
How many of those German
jets you see from back there?
[Joe] Two, I think.
They're so damn fast
you can barely see them.
What the hell is that?
[rocket humming]
Looks like a rocket.
Anti-aircraft?
[Cole] I don't think so.
One of those jets?
[Cole] It's too big.
Ain't never seen that before.
Definitely gotta report
this to Colonel Richards
when we get back to base.
[dramatic music]
So, how are things in Berlin?
The atmosphere is tense,
as you might expect.
What was the Fuhrer's
decision regarding my jets?
The resources are
staying with the V-2.
The Fuhrer feels that the
retribution program is the future
of the Third Reich.
Unless we have a
deterrent in the air,
all of this will not matter.
The problem is
personnel, Colonel.
Rockets require no pilots,
and the trajectories
towards the London area
have been very precise.
Your program requires an
extensive training of the pilots
that are available, and
that number is dwindling.
Since when do Jews get
their own offices here?
He works developing propulsion
systems under von Braun.
And he studied under Einstein.
You're not paying
him, are you?
Of course not.
All he cares about is
the safety of his family.
They are laborers here.
Difficult work, I imagine?
Extremely.
Sir.
Excuse me, General, I
have a nation to defend.
Good morning, gentlemen.
Are you here to represent
the fighter pilots?
Pretty much everyone
in our squadron, sir.
Okay, then, tell me,
what seems to be the beef?
Well, these orders
about cutting back
on radio communications
during the fight.
I don't see how that's
gonna work, sir.
That's what keeping
us alive up there, sir.
It ain't like the 17's.
They got their formation
and their rules.
That's right, and their
rule is absolute radio silence
until they turn around for home.
Because what they're doing
has order to it, Colonel.
That's right.
Point man drops his payload,
then all the others know to go.
Ain't the way it is for us.
When those bandits come
in, it's absolute chaos.
Exactly.
Have you ever been
up in the air, sir?
Couple of times last year.
But that was before
we had you, boys,
so please don't ever think
that we don't appreciate
you being up there with us.
So let me clarify.
The purpose of the orders
is not to prevent you
from alerting the
rest of your squadron
if they're in danger, or
if there's any danger.
The purpose of the orders
is to not alert the Germans
as to where we're at, what
we're doing, where we're going,
what our payload is, and so on.
You understand?
Okay, I understand.
So work with me on this.
Chatter all you want
only when it's necessary.
You gotta back off on
helping their intelligence.
Now, once all the
bombs are dropped,
it's no longer an issue.
Okay?
Okay, sir.
We'll make sure this
clarification gets around.
I would appreciate it.
Now, if you gentlemen
will excuse me,
I've got to address my bomber
crews in less than 30 minutes.
[dramatic music]
[bleeping]
My primary concern,
Herr Captain, is safety.
My last station was in a high
security bombproof facility
that is now in rubble.
We are impenetrable here.
The rockets are a prime
target for the British,
so they bomb, they
bomb, they bomb.
Down here we get
a little rumble.
Ah, this is Issac.
Rocket propulsion.
His is the next office.
So he is one of the
Reich's protected Jews?
He's quite brilliant, and
very important to our cause.
It's all right, Siegfried.
Delighted to make
your acquaintance.
Fraulein Falenburg.
Von Falenburg.
My apologies,
Fraulein Von Falenburg.
So when would you like
to begin your broadcast?
I start tonight after dinner.
And you will please ask the
cook to prepare some fish
for my Siegfried.
Ja, Liebehen, you would
like some fish, ja?
I know you do not like
to be next to the Jews.
- I do not like it either.
- Fucking cats!
Cole, I have to talk with
you about your brother.
[plane humming]
[Cole] What's
he done now, sir?
I'm not talking about
his practical jokes.
I'm afraid I'm gonna have
to pull him from your plane.
Why, sir?
Because he's you're
only brother, Cole.
It's just you and him, right?
No other brothers or sisters?
Yes, sir, that's right.
This has been shaping up ever
since those brothers
were lost in the Pacific.
I have nothing to do with this.
This is coming directly
from Headquarters Command.
I don't have any other choice.
I understand, sir.
Can I tell him myself?
Yeah.
See to it.
- After the briefing.
- Yes, sir.
Yes, sir, thank you.
Well, fellas, we got
the weather forecast.
It's not looking good.
They're calling for a clear sky
with very partial cloud
cover tomorrow morning.
Just remember how
lucky you are compared
to the crews last year.
They didn't have P-51's
to keep them company
all the way there and back.
They were on their own.
Let's hear it for
our little friends!
[applauding]
All right, all
right, knock it off.
Sir, how many planes are
on the mission tomorrow,
including escorts?
Between 700 and 800, Cole.
Sir, with a grid that big,
any bullet fired anywhere
in the sky's bound to
hit one of our planes.
Yeah, well, people
with more rank than me
want these factories taken out,
and they've decided that
this is the way to do it.
Besides, grids shouldn't
be that tight, anyway.
Someone above you
gets hit and falls,
you don't want him
falling on you.
More planes, fewer missions.
Makes sense.
More planes, more missions.
That's the way it goes.
We've got a job to do and
that's to win this damn war.
If it takes 1,000
planes every day,
then by God that's what we do.
What about these rocket
planes we've been seeing, sir?
Rumor has it they're twice
as fast as our newest 51's.
I'm gonna let Lt. Colonel
Thompson brief you in
on what he knows about that.
Rob.
Thank you, Colonel.
They're not rockets.
They're a twin jet design,
but they're not as fast
as everybody's crying about,
but they're certainly faster
than anything we've
got right now.
Why don't we have
something like that, sir?
Well, we will, we will.
How are the
Germans building them
when we're bombing the
crap out of them every day
and the Brits are
slamming them every night?
That's why we have to
keep bombing the crap out
of them every day.
The other day I saw
something on a mission.
And it wasn't a jet plane, it
was a rocket, sir, a big one.
Straight out of science fiction.
And it was moving
fast, very fast.
Anybody else see
anything like this?
All right, gentlemen, I
know you get it pounded
into your head every
day about keeping quiet
about classified information.
And it's critical, very
critical, in this case.
What these men have seen is
no longer science fiction.
These Nazis for a long time
have had these buzz bombs.
We can shoot them out of
the sky with fighters.
We can blow them out of the sky.
But they've got
something new now,
and they call it a
vengeance weapon.
It's a large rocket.
It travels at supersonic speeds,
and it's been terrorizing London
and the surrounding area
almost on a daily basis.
But that's about as much as
I can share with you now.
But when we get more information,
I'll pass it along to you.
Colonel, let's get on
with your briefing.
[Richards] Thanks, Rob.
[Cole] Hey, Joe.
Cole, what you thinking?
Well, everybody's afraid
of those rocket planes.
Well, they'll blow up and
burn down like the rest of them.
Right?
Yeah.
I Guess so.
Listen, Colonel
Richards came by,
and he says that I gotta
pull you off my bird.
You gotta go to another crate.
[plane humming]
For what reason?
Well, apparently they don't
want family members going down
in the same wreck.
Never bothered them before.
I know.
It's not my decision.
You sure about that?
Yeah, of course I'm sure.
Even though you're my brother,
you're the best tail gunner
in the whole theater.
I'm really not happy
about this, Joe.
All right.
Maybe I'll just tell you
what number I'm in up there.
You can pick me out.
That'll be the trick.
There's gonna be a lot of
metal in the sky tomorrow.
[plane humming]
Colonel Raiden, I do not feel
I have adequate
flying experience
to take the Me262 into combat.
I agree, Lieutenant,
but you have to understand
I need these jets in the air.
They are our last hope
for victory in this war.
My concern is their
lack of maneuverability.
Keep in mind, I'm used to
these more agile 190's.
I've seen you in
the 262, Lieutenant,
and you've done well.
Just remember,
gradual acceleration
and gradual
deceleration is the key.
Tricky in a combat situation.
I'll do my best to
remember that, sir.
[Raiden] Good boy.
Good boy, he's a good boy.
[planes humming]
Eddy, what's up?
It's the Dresden Doll, Major.
Lord have mercy,
not that bitch again.
Good evening.
This is the Dresden Doll
here in beautiful Germany.
And there you are, my
sweet young heroes,
soaring high in the
heavens on your missions,
certain that you are
fighting as honorably
as the knights of old.
But think for a moment,
what are you really doing?
You are dropping your bombs
on the women and the children.
They are innocent civilians
who cannot defend themselves.
That is the work of a
butcher, not a soldier.
You are destroying
homes and families,
homes and families just
like yours in America.
And I know you miss your
home and your family,
and especially your sweetheart.
She must be so lonely,
she misses you so much.
But how long can
she wait for you?
And will she still want
you if you come back...
I don't like that
- on my aircraft.
- Without an arm?
[planes humming]
[Pilot] Some kind
of body's gotta go
with that bedroom voice.
I'd like to meet her.
[Pilot] Yeah, I bet you would.
[planes humming]
[Joe] Captain Bender,
I might have something.
[Bender] What do you got, Joe?
[Joe] Not 100% sure, sir.
It's behind us and low.
[Bender] Willis,
you see anything?
[Willis] Nothing
but our boys, Captain.
All right,
everybody stay sharp.
[Pilot] Check the sun.
[Pilot] What about it?
[Pilot] Just below it.
Something.
[Pilot] I think you're
hallucinating again.
[Pilot] Don't think so.
[Pilot] Just the sun, dog.
I don't see anything.
[Pilot] It's too
sunny out here.
I want more cloud cover.
[Pilot] I second that.
[Pilot] How far to the target?
[Pilot] Cut the
chatter about the target.
[Pilot] Roger that.
[planes humming]
[Lucas] Skipper,
I got bandits below!
[Cole] Bandits where, Lucas?
[Lucas] Below
and to the right.
Four, maybe five o'clock.
[Cole] Joe, what you got?
Uh, sorry, tail gunner,
what do you see?
[planes humming]
[Pilot] What's
that at two o'clock?
[Pilot] Looks like
a flock of birds.
[Pilot] Some big birds.
[Pilot] This is trouble, boys.
[Pilot] What the hell?
[planes humming]
[Pilot] Oh, hell, bandits!
[Pilot] Good Lord!
[Pilot] Easy, men.
[Pilot] Do they
know we're here?
[Pilot] What the
hell are they doing?
[Pilot] Of course
they know we're here.
[Pilot] Are we supposed
to engage that whole group?
[planes humming]
[Pilot] What the hell kind
of Napoleonic tactic is this?
[dramatic music]
[planes humming]
[Joe] They're coming up
on the second grid, Captain.
[Bender] Get me closer, Joe.
[Willis] I can see something.
[Pilot] Don't shoot
points for this.
[Pilot] There they go!
[planes humming]
[Pilot] This is crazy!
[Pilot] Son of a bitch!
[Pilot] I can't
tell who's who!
[Pilot] One lane.
Brace it up out of here.
[Pilot] I see jets!
[planes humming]
[Pilot] Nine o'clock.
Nine!
[plane humming]
[Pilot] This pack of
birds is just a diversion.
[Pilot] Protect the 17's.
Remember the mission.
[planes humming]
[guns firing]
[Pilot] Farmer down.
Farmer down.
[Pilot] Another one!
[Pilot] Do your job, fellas!
[dramatic music]
[screaming]
[plane crashing]
[Willis] What happened?
[Bender] We have
no controls at all.
[plane humming]
[Willis] We're gonna die!
[Bender] We're going down!
Abandon ship!
- Willis, get your chute!
- I can't!
[plane humming]
A fine performance.
Thank you, Captain.
I have a favor to ask of you.
A public relations issue.
Yeah?
There is a girl here working
for us, one of the laborers.
She has become enraptured
with your performances
and would very much like to
meet you if you have a moment.
Certainly.
Hello, madam, are
you the Dresden Doll?
That is my radio persona, yes.
Oh, it is an
honor to meet you.
I listen to you every
night on the radio.
Do you?
And what is your name?
Anna.
Well, Anna, what
do you do here?
I am in assembly, but
when I am older I want
to be just like you.
How charming.
Uh...
[Von Falenburg]
Where is she from?
Poland, originally.
You may leave now, Anna.
I want her eliminated.
Excuse me?
Executed, as soon as possible.
[he sighs]
And how would you
like this accomplished?
Do I have to tell a
Schutzstaffel officer how
to do his job?
Just make sure that the last
thing she hears is my voice
on the radio.
Very well.
Colonel Raiden's dog has
not had to work for his meal
in quite some time.
I hope he likes Polish food.
[chuckles]
[plane humming]
[Cole] Has anyone seen Bender?
Has anyone seen Captain Bender?
Captain Bender's
plane, Fire Down Below,
has anyone seen him?
Ain't seen nobody
from Bender's plane.
[plane humming]
[Cole] Anyone
seen Joe Phillips?
I thought Joe was the tail
gunner on your plane, sir.
[Cole] Sergeant Phillips?
Anyone seen Joe?
He got moved to
Bender's plane?
[plane humming]
[Henderson] Major?
Yes?
I saw Bender's plane.
Where?
In a fight.
But it didn't make it back.
Bender's plane
went down, Major.
[plane humming]
It went down how?
It looked like
there was a collision.
A collision?
You saw this?
Yeah, looked like one
of those jets hit it.
Are you sure it
was Bender's plane?
It happened real fast,
sir, but that's what I saw.
Did you see any shoots?
Flamed out fast.
I didn't see anyone get out.
[plane humming]
Thank you, sergeant.
[dramatic music]
[knocking on door]
It's just us, sweetheart.
I'm sorry it's so late.
What's wrong, Mama?
Nothing's wrong.
Your father and I just need
to talk to you for a minute.
Gonna go to
Grandma's tomorrow.
Would you like that?
Can I help Grandma make some
of her homemade ice cream?
[Joe] I sure hope so.
I could absolutely
use some of it.
Is something the
matter with Grandma?
Oh, no, we just need
to get everyone together
so we can talk about your
father and your uncle.
Are you gonna be
a soldier, Daddy?
[Joe] Why, yes, yes, I am.
I knew it.
How did you know that, Emily?
A lot of kids already
had their daddies leave.
How do you think Grandma's
gonna feel about this?
Well, we've always
been very patriotic.
I'm sure she'll be
just fine with it.
I cannot believe this!
You all come in here like this
making me the last
person to know!
Shame on you!
Did he put you up to this?
No, Ma, we discussed it.
Well, you didn't
discuss it with me.
Can I talk to you in the other
room for a minute, please?
Yes, Ma.
Why is Grandma so mad?
She's just worried, Emily.
What were you thinking, Cole?
It wasn't me.
A lot of people are joining up.
Didn't you hear
the President, Ma?
I mean, we all have
to do our duty.
Everybody's gotta do their part.
Well, I imagine it was
the right thing to do.
Well, thank you.
- I -
- For you!
You've gone from here for 10
years, and I don't blame you.
This place is just a
tiny speck of a town
in the middle of nowhere.
And, Cole, you've always
had bigger and better ideas,
and I'm proud of you, son.
Thanks, Ma.
But Joe's different.
He stayed.
He has a family now.
He's got a wife and a
beautiful little girl.
Don't get me wrong, son,
I don't want to see
you get hurt either,
- but Joe's...
- Yeah?
Well, he doesn't have the
kind of common sense you have,
and he never has.
He's a grown man, and he
can take care of himself.
You know what I mean.
You've been taking care of
him since you all were little.
You kept him out of
trouble, you kept him safe.
I don't know the whys
or the wherefores,
but I've always appreciated it.
I made my decision
and he made his, Ma,
and we're going in.
It's our duty.
You promise me.
You promise me that you'll do
everything humanly possible
to look out for him and make
sure he doesn't get hurt.
You promise?
I will, Ma.
[dramatic music]
I'll take care of him.
Another.
Hello, Eddy.
What's going on?
[Eddy] I just
want to let you know
that I'm not the type of
guy to rat on a friend.
Okay.
[Eddy] I just wanted
to let you know that.
Here, have a seat.
[Eddy] Yes, sir.
What do you need
to tell me, Eddy?
It's Cole, sir.
Major Phillips.
I think he's gone AWOL.
AWOL?
Phillips?
That doesn't sound right.
I know, sir.
But this thing with
his brother and...
I mean, they were really close.
Well, when was the
last time you saw him?
Right after we got back.
He's just vanished.
That's been about
what, 12, 14 hours ago?
Yes, sir.
I'll tell you what, Eddy.
Get a jeep pulled
around in front for us.
- Yes, sir.
- All right.
Colonel, respectfully, I'd
rather not accompany you.
I don't want the Major thinking
I had any part of this, sir.
Very well, then, stay behind.
You have any idea where
Major Phillips might be?
Yes, sir.
I think he might be at
the pub, King's Pub.
Do you know where
that's located?
Yes, sir.
All right, well,
let the driver know.
Make sure he knows.
Sergeant Perry, do you
know where King's Pub is?
No.
It's about five
miles southwest down
the main road off base.
Is that the one with
the uh, thatched roof?
Serves the 90 shilling?
- Yes, Sergeant.
- Yes, I know where it is.
Thank you, Sergeant.
All right, we set?
[jeep engine starts up]
[people murmuring]
Cole?
Cole.
[Cole] Yes, sir?
Look at me.
What the hell are
you doing out here?
What's it look
like I'm doing, sir?
Getting drunk.
Why don't you come
on back with us?
Get some hot chow and
some hot coffee in you.
You'll feel much better.
I'm really sorry
about this, Colonel.
Looks like I've cut pretty
heavy into your sleep.
Ah, don't worry about it.
But I am gonna have to pull
you from the sky for a while.
I think a couple weeks of R
and R will get you straight.
I understand, sir.
Also, nothing about
this little hike
of yours is going
to be reported,
provided it does
not happen again.
You understand?
Yes, sir, I understand.
[sighs]
[people murmuring]
What do you think the chances
are for my brother Joe, sir?
Well, Cole, some of the
guys have made it back
through the lines.
The resistance has been
a big help with that,
but I'm not gonna
bullshit you, Major.
The chances are not good.
Well, Joe could survive, sir,
if he made it to
the ground alive.
He could survive in the woods.
It's obvious to
me that you two
were pretty darn
close growing up.
We did just about everything
together growing up.
Our Daddy died in the Great
War when we were young, sir.
Joe never met him.
He was a soldier?
[people murmuring]
Look, we don't have to talk
about this if you don't want to.
No, no, it's okay, sir.
He was a pilot too.
Really?
Yes, sir.
He was one of 20 shot down
by a young German ace.
You know, those German
planes could turn on a dime.
They were better than ours.
Wasn't the Red Baron, was it?
No, it wasn't
Baron von Richthofen.
But I did find out
who it was, sir.
You know how the army is,
they don't like to tell you
anything unless they have to.
Well, ain't that
the damn truth?
No, sir, his name was Raiden.
R-A-I-D-E-N.
I don't know much
else other than
that he stayed
flying after the war.
Knowing you, I'm surprised
you didn't stow away
on some transatlantic ship
just to try and find the guy.
Well, it had
crossed my mind, sir.
Anyway, during your time on
the ground I'd appreciate it
if you'd hang around the
rookie pilots a little bit,
you know, maybe give
them a few pointers.
Absolutely, sir, absolutely.
[Richards] All right, good.
[Von Falenburg] What are
you doing with my apparatus?!
I meant no harm.
It reminded me of the equipment
I used during the last war.
I was a communications officer.
[Von Falenburg] You know
this area is forbidden!
[Messner] Is there
a problem here?
Why was this Jew
meddling with my equipment?
Isaac, go back to your work.
I apologize.
Isaac has not been
himself today.
[panting]
He must be disciplined.
It is not that simple.
His wife and sons are
laborers at this facility.
The officer in
charge has determined
that they are too
weak to continue,
so they are being sent back
to the Mittelbau-Dora camp.
Why is this a concern?
These Jews are not even human.
It is a concern of mine.
We need Issac to be productive.
This intrusion will
not happen again.
You will make sure
that it does not.
So, Captain, will I
be able to see my wife
and sons before they
are transported?
[Messner sighs]
[Messner] I'm
afraid I won't be able
to help you with that.
[moaning]
[Isaac] Miriam.
Issac, compose yourself.
I need you to focus
on what I am saying.
The radio equipment
in the next room.
[Isaac] Ja.
Do you believe
you can operate it?
I am certain of it.
Good.
I must take leave of you now.
I am going to interrupt
Colonel Raiden's dinner.
Do I know of this man?
I don't think so.
He is one of the commanders
of the Me262 program.
Ah, ja, the jets.
I have heard of them.
Fascinating devices.
Yes, but the program is
having personnel issues.
What you are working on
is the wave of the future.
Remember that.
[knocking on door]
Come.
Ah, Captain Messner.
Colonel.
Sorry to interrupt your dinner.
I was already finished.
No problem.
So what do I owe this
visit from the SS?
No trouble, I hope.
Not at all.
I just wanted to finally
meet the heroic war hero
everyone is talking about.
Oh, please.
Just following orders.
[Messner] Nonsense!
27 kills in two months.
And with the new jet
fighter, no less.
It is truly an
amazing aircraft.
You should see her in action.
I would like to.
I imagine the
same as before, Rob.
Brandy?
You have an excellent
memory, Malcolm.
The intelligence
community does frown
upon those forgetful types,
if you know what I mean.
Do you miss your
offices at the RAF?
Oh, I suppose.
However, the man at the top
is not going anywhere soon.
So I thought it best for
me to make a lateral move.
Cheers!
[clinking]
Rob, I know you are
an extremely busy man.
I do appreciate the visit,
but, what actually brings
you all the way out here?
Malcolm, my boys are getting
spooked, just plain spooked,
by this German technology.
[Malcolm] You're
referring to the Me262.
And the rockets, the big ones.
Terrorist weapons.
Their sole purpose
is to spread fear
amongst a war-ravaged
civilian population
that has already endured and
suffered so so very much.
Yes, sir, you're
absolutely right, Malcolm.
But we're here now.
And we've got better bombers,
we got better ordinance,
we got better tactics than
we've ever had before.
But we need targets.
Precise targets are a
problem with the Me262.
They're being assembled
in abandoned tunnels,
bombed-out cathedrals, even
in forests under the trees.
And the rockets?
A little tougher to hide.
Ah, they require
very skilled assembly
and the fuel system
is quite volatile,
ethyl alcohol and liquid oxygen.
However, there is
one major facility
that assembles the Me262
and the V-2 rocket.
The Germans call
it The Kohnstein.
So, Colonel, tell me
about this amazing aircraft
I've heard so to much about.
You know, they are building
you up as the next Red Baron.
[chuckles]
Our propaganda office is
doing a fine job, aren't they?
I first entered our
squadron as night fighters
against the British.
That's why they are
mainly painted black,
which I hear strikes fear into
the heart of the Americans.
But how did you
achieve so many kills?
25 of the 27 were Mosquitos,
the twin-engine
workhorse of the RAF.
My jets have a top speed
that is 200 kilometers faster
than the Mosquitos.
They never knew what hit them.
The Kohnstein plant, I'm
sure it's been targeted
by your boys?
Of course.
We've bombed the
bloody hell out of it.
The problem is that it's
located in a former gypsum mine,
extraordinarily well-protected
by the Mother Earth herself.
So what kind of
targets can you give me?
Mobile airfields.
Our counterparts have
become quite adept
at moving major operations
in 12 to 18 hours time.
Right now I could give
you two, maybe three,
locations where
Me262's may be found.
Then how can you
give us locations
if they're moving
them around so fast?
Our intelligence is
first-class, my dear Colonel.
First-class.
So, from one interested
party to another,
perhaps you could tell to
me about this new rocket
I've been hearing about.
What have you heard?
That it may have
the capability
to reach the east coast
of the United States.
Pure speculation, of course,
but I have seen the plans.
Such a weapon could secure
the future of the Third Reich?
Such a weapon, Herr
Colonel, could signal the rise
of the Fourth Reich.
Malcolm, I'm gonna take
whatever you can give me
on the airfields.
But this Kohnstein thing,
this really intrigues me.
Be patient with
that one, Colonel.
Sometimes terrible empires can
be brought down from within.
Malcolm, do you have
someone on the inside?
I'm afraid at this
time I'm not at liberty
to discuss that.
Colonel Raiden,
your enthusiasm
for the Me262 program
is appreciated,
but your squadron is down
to two now, I believe?
Good pilots are
hard to come by,
and I have to change airfield
locations, feels like daily.
Yet you have time
to visit us here.
Parts.
I have a critical shortage
of parts, Captain.
As a matter of fact, I
have to round up two trucks
and take parts to Frankfurt.
Frankfurt?
Unusual that they
would want to move you
to such a large city.
[Raiden] They wouldn't.
The field is an hour
south and further inland.
Reporting as ordered, sir.
Good evening, Major.
Finished torturing
rookies for the week?
[chuckling]
I just tell them
like it is, sir.
Yeah, well, we both know
it probably puts the fear
of God into them and that's
probably a good thing.
- Yes, sir.
- Here, take a seat.
[Cole] Thank you, sir.
Cole, we got some intel
you might be interested in.
I see you got a new map, sir.
Mm-hm.
Well, we found the
location of some
of those rocket planes
you encountered.
Hm.
Yes, we've located
a mobile airbase.
It's deep in Germany, about an
hour southwest of Frankfurt,
and our on-ground re-con
folks tell us there are two
or three of the
jets on the field.
They're made by Messerschmidt.
The model number is 262.
They've been giving
our boys quite a fit.
Are you sending
the 17's in, sir?
Major, it's a real hornet's
nest, and, at any given time,
there could be fighter squadrons
on this mobile
airbase, 109's, 190's.
We don't want to
tangle with those.
And the 262's might
be in bunkers.
What would you like
me to do about it, sir?
For one thing, you've been
out of the sky for 30 days,
and I know you're
itching to get back up.
Yes, sir, I am.
Tell me, Cole, when's the
last time you flew a Mustang?
It was about a year ago, sir.
But it wasn't one
of the new models.
The new models are
faster and carry more.
Still fly about the same.
I still like my old
crate, sir, the Gunfighter.
The Gunfighter.
Well, the Gunfighter's
still on the airfields.
Yours if you want it.
This is strictly
volunteer, of course.
If you don't want do it, I'll
still put you up in the sky.
But it's gonna have to be
in one of the newer B-17's.
That hole in the side
of your old ship,
it put her out of
commission for a while.
Yes, sir, I saw her
down off the tarmac.
She looks kinda
lonely down there.
The other reason
is, I'm in a pickle.
The target is a mobile airfield,
and they can change
locations in six hours.
All of my P-51 pilots
are up on escort.
I'm not gonna send an
inexperienced pilot
on a mission like this.
I understand, sir.
What are the particulars
of the mission?
Well, Major, it's
gonna be a daylight raid.
There'll be two
fighters involved.
You'll be coming
in under the radar,
very low, very low over
some very rough terrain.
Sounds like a lotta fun, sir.
Well, we're gonna need someone
to fly the other
plane, the P-38.
You got any suggestions?
[Cole] How about
Eddy, my co-pilot, sir?
He's ready for the 38.
Ah, a twin engine man.
[Cole] Yes, sir.
Okay, get Eddy
in here tomorrow
after breakfast first thing,
and we'll go over the plans.
Is there anything else, sir?
Anything else?
What do you mean?
Well, you said there was
two reasons you wanted me
for this mission, sir.
Ah, yes.
Well, I don't want
you reading too much
into what I'm about to tell you.
[Cole] Is it about
my brother, sir?
No, no.
No, I wish.
I did some research on
this Colonel Raiden,
this German ace Colonel Raiden.
Colonel Raiden, sir?
Really?
Well, you're right
about him staying
in the service after the war.
He's been part of the Luftwaffe
ever since its beginning.
In regards to this
airfield, your target,
a Colonel Raiden comes into
play, we just don't know how.
Yeah, the ace from the previous
war, this Colonel Raiden,
was made the person
in charge of a portion
of this 262 program
back in 1942.
And he convinced the Luftwaffe
brass to use the aircraft
as a fighter, for
which it was designed.
You know, Hitler insist
on using it as a bomber.
- [chuckling]
- Yeah, go figure.
Anyway, I wouldn't get
your hopes up too high.
Your German ace just
might be at that airfield.
[dramatic music]
Colonel?
[Richards] Yes, Cole?
I'll take the assignment
on two conditions.
One is that I can
cut a savior pouch
into the backseat of my plane.
Hm, it's possible.
I'll have to get with
the mechanics on that.
Tell me, what's your
thinking behind this?
If Eddy doesn't make
it back in the 38,
it still gives us a chance to
get back to our lines, sir.
Keep in mind,
you're gonna be right
on the edge of effective range,
so if anyone uses the savior
pouch, it won't have a mask,
so altitude will
be very limited.
Yes, sir, I understand that,
but we're already gonna
be flying low anyway.
And I'd like to
arm the plane, sir.
Well, I figured you would.
[jeep engine humming]
[plane humming]
So how'd my name
come up for this?
I volunteered you.
So why'd you do that?
Because you like flying
these P-38's so much.
Yeah, I like to fly them.
I don't particularly
want to die on one.
Look, you'll do fine.
I've never even come
close to being in combat
in one of those.
What if I get into a dogfight?
Look, we're not gonna
be flying high enough
to get into a
dogfight, so relax.
Are you familiar with the
firepower on the 38 now?
Gun cluster up front.
Easy to aim.
Now the 51 is different.
Six MG's, three on either wing.
What happened to the cannon?
[Cole] The ammo was too
heavy, and it ran out too fast.
I liked the cannon.
Journey's End?
Yeah, I like Journey's End.
It's kind of poetic.
Yeah, well, poetic
if I make it back.
Otherwise pretty damn tragic.
[plane humming]
Eddy, no matter what happens,
I'm not gonna leave
you behind, okay?
Likewise.
Gentlemen, the German
planes, mostly 190's,
are gonna be in
this area spread out
around the control station.
Now, also we've been
told there may be
some anti-aircraft batteries
in the vicinity, of some kind.
We're not sure how many,
we're not sure of location,
but that's the intelligence
we have at this time.
Our primary targets, the
Me262's, should be here.
Now, they may be in protective
cover, it's hard to say.
Or you could get lucky and
they're out in the open,
either getting refueled
or waiting to take off.
The key is knocking out
those anti-aircraft
artillery guns first.
Yes, but you've got
to go in low and slow,
otherwise they're gonna
know you're coming.
Now, that's the case, it
may be over pretty quick
for you two.
Look, Eddy, we're gonna
split and hit both sides
of the field simultaneously.
Yes, sir.
Yes, and after
you hit the guns,
regardless of your success,
you've got to drop your payload
and make some great big
holes in the runway.
Otherwise you're gonna have a
swarm of 190's up in the air
on your butts
within five minutes.
I'm not buying that, sir.
[Richards] And
why do you say that?
Because the 190 is a field
plane, sir, it's agile.
They'll scoot right
around those holes,
take off and come
right after us.
So they'll be on us like a
hound dog on a pork chop,
just like that.
Okay, I see your point.
So what do you suggest?
Okay, what I'm thinking
is forget the bombs, sir,
that's a one-shot deal.
What we do is, we split.
Eddy hits the anti-aircraft
and I hit the fuel trucks.
That way they stay on the
ground for the entire time.
And think about it like
this: on our way back,
those bombs are gonna make the
difference between fuel, sir.
We might not make it back,
we'd have to splash
in the channel.
Okay.
Eddy, are you okay
with that plan?
I don't want a swarm
of 190's on my butt.
If Cole's plan stops that
from happening, I'm good.
Sir, we're gonna be light
on ammo on the way back.
Can you tell us anything
about these jet planes
in case one of them gets
up and starts chasing us?
Listen, let's pray
that doesn't happen.
But if, and I say if it does,
just remember these
jets are faster
but they don't have the range
or the maneuverability
that you have.
So why are we doing
this as a daylight raid?
Eddy, because most of the
planes on that airfield,
including the 262's,
won't be there at night.
Why?
Because they're gonna
be up in the sky
hurting our British friends.
I can hear the roar
of the engines now, sir.
[plane humming]
I don't like precision bombing,
it's not easy with
these machines.
That's why I'm a pilot,
not a bombardier!
What's that, you get
some butterflies?
Butterflies, maggots, worms.
All thanks to you.
Don't worry,
I'll be right there
with you the whole way, okay?
Let's get this
thing done, Major.
Come on, let's go!
[planes humming]
[dramatic music]
Hello, Isaac.
Herr Von Braun!
It is so good to see you!
I had no notice of your arrival.
Advanced communications
are not always best
at this time, Isaac.
I understand.
So tell me, what is new?
Well, for one thing, I noticed
that they have expanded
the trophy room.
Someone has been doing
a lot of hunting here.
Ja, that would be
General Stahkmann
and his officers from
the Mittelbau-Dora camp.
I see.
Is that where you
are housed, Isaac?
To them I am an important
part of the V-2 program.
Thanks to you.
However, my family has been
transferred back there.
And I fear for them.
I am not familiar with the
reputation of that facility.
It is notorious for
illness, beatings,
and intolerable
working conditions.
Unfortunately that
appears to be the norm
for all of these camps.
Isaac, the V-2 program is a
success, thanks to my work,
and, of course, thanks to you.
So tell me, how do
you define success?
Do you remember our days back
in Berlin at the Technicia?
Yes, I believe you
and I met in '31.
Something like that.
I was so young!
And my hair was
so much darker.
- [dramatic music]
- We talked so much
about space travel with
the rockets we would build.
We had such dreams
for the future.
Ja, so many dreams.
The rockets that hit
London worked perfectly,
except that they landed
on the wrong planet!
[Isaac laughs]
I overheard someone refer
to you as Professor Von Braun.
Is this correct?
It is correct,
but it is old news.
You must tell
me what happened.
When the V-2 was
still the A-4 program,
the Fuhrer was thrilled when
he saw a film we had made
of a successful
launch, so much so
that he personally insisted I
be awarded Professor status.
Good for you, Wehrner.
I am glad to see you
are on their good side.
Well, I don't know.
You know, sometimes I'm not
afraid to speak my mind.
I remember that got you
into some trouble at school.
The professors would discuss
your perceived arrogance
in the faculty lounge.
In February I was summoned
to Himmler's
headquarters in Prussia.
He was trying to
take control of all
of the armaments programs,
including the V-2.
Himmler and I did not
particularly get along.
Mostly because I
did not want to work
with the people he
wanted me to work with.
They were not good people?
It's just that they
weren't brilliant like you.
So, late last year
an engineer friend
and I visited a dentist.
This was a lady dentist who I
found out later was an SS spy.
She overheard us talking
about the rocket program,
how space travel is the reason
for our work, not warfare.
We may have also said something
about the war effort not
going well for Germany.
[Isaac sighs]
These remarks were,
of course, reported,
and I was detained in
March by the Gestapo.
I was a guest of
theirs for two weeks
in one of their cells
in western Poland.
I assume it was
not a posh resort.
It was isolation in a dungeon.
I truly did not think I
would make it out alive.
But I was released
when it was discovered
that they could not continue
the V-2 program without me.
So, now you too must
look over your shoulder.
Isaac, believe
me, no one is safe.
[dramatic music]
I will not spend another night
with these jets on the ground!
We have fueled the
262s except for yours.
And why isn't my
jet being refueled?
Well, sir, it is
the coupling, Colonel.
What coupling?
The coupling that
malfunctioned was replaced,
but the replacement failed.
How am I supposed to fly
without fuel and parts?!
[dramatic music]
[Eddy] Battery first.
Battery first.
[dramatic music]
Come on Eddy,
where's the battery?
There is no battery.
Eddy, if they're
there, take them out.
[plane humming]
Check the horizon!
Alarm!
[guns firing]
Take cover!
Shoot the twin-engine!
[guns firing]
[plane explodes]
[dramatic music]
[Cole] That's
the way it's done!
I'll take center from here.
[dramatic music]
[guns firing]
[plane explodes]
[dramatic music]
Only a guess, but I think
they just got refueled.
[guns firing]
[Eddy] Taking fire, Major.
[dramatic music]
[guns firing]
[Cole] All right.
One pass.
Surround them with your gun.
[guns firing]
[Eddy] Ammo's
gonna dry up quick
if we keep up this turkey shoot.
[guns firing]
[plane explodes]
Major.
Major, I got a problem here.
[Cole] Yeah, I see.
[plane humming]
Come with me.
[Cole] Go out the
same way you came in.
[planes humming]
Get a few miles out and then
take her down in a field.
Keep that Tommy Gun close.
[plane humming]
They won't be expecting that.
I'll pick you up
in a few minutes.
[Eddy] Where are you going?
[Cole] I'm gonna
make another pass.
Looks like they still have
planes they can fly out of here.
We can't have that.
[Eddy] Okay, Major,
I'm counting on you.
[planes humming]
[guns firing]
[plane explodes]
[planes humming]
[guns firing]
[plane engine humming]
[gun firing]
[groaning]
How bad are you hit, boy?
[Eddy] It hurts
like hell, Major.
I want to see what
we are up against.
These men possess
unimaginable courage.
They are the enemy, sir.
They are pilots.
With a squadron of these men,
I could turn the
outcome of the war.
Well, it ain't
supposed to feel good.
[Eddy groans]
It feels like it just
went straight through.
All right, listen, just keep
some pressure on it, all right?
Hold right there, we'll
get you to the aircraft.
[gun firing]
[groaning]
Come on, Eddy, this
ain't gonna be easy!
Beats walking home, skipper.
Come on!
What kind of
fresh hell is this?
Great.
Now you got me in a pine box.
[Cole] Colonel Raiden!
[dramatic music]
Do you know this man, sir?
No.
[dramatic music]
Ah, it is personal
with this American.
My father sends his regards.
[gun firing]
[plane humming]
[fire crackling]
I don't think
anything will fly here.
Yes, sir.
Here's what I want you to do.
Get my jet ready and make
sure it's fully armed.
[fire crackling]
Sir, need I remind you,
you're plane was not fueled
up before the attack.
I am aware of that.
[plane humming]
You out there, Joe?
You out there somewhere?
[dramatic music]
♪ Yankee doodle went to town ♪
♪ Riding on a pony ♪
[Cole chuckles]
Are you keeping it
together back there, Eddy?
[dramatic music]
I think I'm gonna
pass out, skipper.
Huh, hang in there.
[planes humming]
[dramatic music]
Oh, great.
[planes humming]
[gun firing]
[screams]
[planes humming]
[gun firing]
[screaming]
[planes humming]
What the hell's
goin on, Major?!
[planes humming]
[gun firing]
[screaming]
[planes humming]
Oh, I'm gonna get sick.
- [bleeping]
- Damn it!
[sighing]
[groaning]
Talk to me, Eddy.
Stay with me, kid.
Stay with me.
[planes humming]
[dramatic music]
We almost there, skipper?
Almost.
I didn't hear you
singing over the channel.
Acrobatics about did me in.
What do you think
happened to that jet?
Must have run out of gas.
He's still out there.
I appreciate the
ride home, Major.
Damn good work, Eddy.
Damn good.
[dramatic music]
Major Phillips.
- Yes, sir?
- Colonel Richards needs
to see you.
He needs a full debrief on this.
[Cole] Yes, sir, no problem.
Oh, and by the way,
your brother's back.
I'm sorry, what was that, sir?
[Thomson] You're brother, Joe.
Joe Phillips, right?
[plane humming]
Uh, yeah, tail
gunner Joe, sir?
He made it back
across the lines.
Your brother's back.
[plane humming]
Uh...
Where is he, sir?
He's, uh...
Well, I saw him over there,
he was over with the others.
Okay.
Well, don't forget now,
Colonel Richards needs to see you,
- he needs a full debriefing.
- Yes, sir.
Hey, soldier, soldier!
Have you seen...
Have you seen Joe Phillips?
Who?
Joe?
Phillips?
What is he, a pilot?
Gunner?
Tail gunner Joe.
No?
Yeah, thanks.
[plane humming]
Who you yapping
at now, you jerk?
[dramatic music]
You're mama's
gonna be real happy
you made it through this.
[Joe laughs]
Look at you, brother?
[laughing]
[Joe] Still a jackass.
Ugh!
- Tell me what happened.
- I will, I will.
How's Eddy?
Ah, he's not good, not good.
I'm gonna go check
on him in a few.
Yeah, I wish I could tell
your wife and kids about this.
They'll know soon enough.
Telegraphs go fast.
He made it back, Lillian.
Joe made it back.
He made it back.
My Daddy's coming home!
Yes, he is, sweetheart.
Yes, he is.
[Wilkins] Rob, I took the
liberty of pouring you a brandy.
I hope you don't mind.
Thank you very much,
Malcolm, I appreciate that.
They said your phone
call sounded urgent.
I got over here as
quickly as I could.
I heard about the
pain that a couple
of your boys put forth
on that German airfield
that we talked
about a while back.
Yeah, Malcolm, it
was one hell of a raid.
And we couldn't have done it,
though, without your help.
I trust both pilots
returned safely.
One of them took
a pretty bad hit,
but he's pulling through.
Good for him, good for him.
Young man's been
given a ticket home.
I'm not so sure.
He may still have some piss
and vinegar left in him.
But tell me about the Kohnstein.
What's with the Kohnstein plant?
It seems that the Germans
have more tricks
up their sleeves.
What do you mean,
beyond the V-2 rocket?
There's more?
[Wilkins chuckles]
In the deranged
mind of Adolf Hitler,
the V-2 rocket is considered
a retribution weapon,
or a vengeance weapon,
hence the letter V.
He considers this payback
on us English people
for all of our bombing raids.
It doesn't seem to matter
to that bloody bastard
that they bombed
us to start with.
Well, Malcolm, you know
what they say, "All's fair...
"In love and war," yes, yes.
The Kohnstein is still the
primary manufacturing facility
for the Me262.
It's also the primary
manufacturing facility
for the V-2 rocket, and
it's also home of research
and development
for a new project.
Is that using the
same V-2 technology?
Pretty much, just much larger.
The goal of this
is to hit targets
on the east coast of
the United States.
Do you actually believe
they can do that, Malcolm?
Had I not thought
they could do it,
I would not have called you.
They're building a
prototype as we speak.
This war needs to end.
Whatever we have to do,
we need to stop them.
This war must end.
[dramatic music]
Frauline von
Falenburg, I apologize
that I am just now
able to entertain you
with a proper dinner.
I hope your stay here so far
has not been too terrible.
No apologies needed.
Thank you for taking the time
out of your schedule for this.
Hopefully, conditions in
Berlin will improve soon
and you can return home.
The most important
thing is that I am able
to continue my support
of the war effort.
Germany must be victorious.
I completely agree.
I have heard many
of your broadcasts,
so I'm very familiar
with your persona.
However, I know very
little about you.
Tell me, Frauline, what
are you planning on doing
after the war?
You mean, after the triumph
of the Third Reich, general?
Of course, Frauline.
That's exactly what I mean.
I will do everything
in my power to make sure
that Germany is
the greatest empire
in the history of the world.
There are those who forget
that conquest can
be very difficult.
General, when I
see what we have done
in the last five years,
I can only imagine
what we can accomplish
in the next 20 years,
50 years, even 500 years.
Food for thought, Frauline.
We must do this again sometime.
It would be my
pleasure, general.
[dramatic music]
Is this everything on the V-3?
Everything that I am
responsible for, yes.
Do you really think that
this propulsion system
could take a rocket that is
larger than the V-2 all the way
to the east coast of
the United States?
[Isaac] I'm absolutely
certain of it.
All right, Isaac.
This is what I need you to do.
Go through all of your
plans and equations
and make them unworkable.
What?
But do not make it obvious
that you are doing this.
- Captain, are you a...
- Mr. Abromowicz,
I believe you are
a very clever man.
What is the mission, Captain?
The mission is the
destruction of this facility.
Can you verify that
my family is safe
and has been moved from here?
They have been relocated.
I put them on the train myself.
Very well.
Then I agree.
I need you to use the radio
equipment in the next room.
I need you to broadcast
a short message
at a very specific time.
Is this possible?
Yes, if her majesty Frau
Falenburg isn't around.
I'll see to it
that she is occupied.
Isaac, this will be
needed when the Me262's
and rockets are being removed
from this facility in two days.
What is the message?
It is, [clears throat],
"Now is the time
for all good men
"to come to the aid
of their country."
Repeated twice.
Captain, you make a
very convincing American.
Or, I make a very
convincing German.
[dramatic music]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull