Your grandmother's grandfather
came out here in 1873
after the Civil War.
Family lore has it
when he topped Johnson Mesa
and he looked down
at this valley
and saw buffalo and antelope
belly deep in a sea of grass,
with the Sangre de Christos
behind him,
he knew this was it.
Your people have
been here ever since.
Now me, I was born in Louisiana,
came out here after the war.
I was a wandering soul,
looking for a North Star.
And I found it right here in
this valley along this river.
To me, this is the Peace River.
I feel peace
every time I look at it.
Casey, what you want to
be when you grow up?
A cowboy, just like you, Pop.
Well, you come from
a long line of cowboys.
The cowboy loves big
sky and open range.
Works hard,
is a man of his word.
Loyal to his friends and family.
Treats everyone with respect,
especially women.
Is courageous,
fearing God and no man.
Don't ever forget
what's important.
Friendship with God.
Family. Friends.
Meaningful work
and one good horse.
Never make the mistake
of measuring wealth by money.
You do that,
and you'll be a rich man
and a good cowboy.
That's what I want to be.
I met your grandmother
on the spring round-up.
I loved her from
the first time I saw her.
The love of a good woman
can save your life.
When I came back from the war,
I had shrapnel in places
the doctors couldn't get to.
The doctor said
I better live well
because I probably
wouldn't live long.
Son, that was 40 years ago,
and I ain't dead yet.
Be thankful.
Always be thankful.
All right.
No peeking. No peeking.
You ready?
Yes, sir.
Well, what do you think?
He's beautiful.
Well, you know,
at the end of the day,
cowboy in' is teamwork.
Cowboy is only as good
as his horse.
So I've been looking for
your one for a while.
I think this may be the one.
Now, listen, he got
a lot of cow in him,
so don't you be trying
to teach him anything.
If you pay attention,
he'll teach you something.
Okay?
All right.
Go see what you think.
His name is Pecos.
Hey, Pecos.
I'm Casey.
And I'm gonna take
good care of you.
Casey, slow it down, buddy.
Okay, that's it.
Hey, you kids stick together.
No running!
Those kids were born running.
That'll be two bits.
Drop it in
Bo's jar on the way out.
Little Casey had a head start.
Two bits all the same.
- Hey, Casey.
- Oh, no.
I guess you Shanes will take
in any strays, even beaners.
You are so stupid.
That's funny,
coming from a fence jumper.
Mr. Shane, I appreciate
you coming in today.
Yesterday on the playground,
there was an altercation
with your grandson.
We have a zero tolerance
policy for fighting.
He needs to be suspended
for a day.
I don't understand.
What did I do wrong?
Well, Case,
you had good intentions
of defending Maria's
dignity and honor.
But the problem is,
you delivered the first blow.
There's only two blows a cowboy
ought to deliver for sure.
That's the second one
and the last one.
You know, if everybody responded
to every verbal provocation
in this world,
civilization would come unglued.
You okay?
Grandma, you reckon
he's still mad at me?
Heck, no, he ain't mad at you.
Casey, that man loves you
more than you can know.
He just wants you to be
a kind and a strong man.
Hey, little buddy.
What you looking at there?
What was my daddy like?
Man, your daddy
was something else.
Full of life and laughter.
As the cowboys would say,
he was a man
to ride the river with.
What a cowboy.
That boy could ride
the hair off a bull.
And you know,
when I look at you,
I often think
I'm looking at him.
Why did God let my daddy die?
Case, there are some things
in this life that
it's hard
to understand or explain.
We just have to...
trust in God.
I believe God is, and he's good
in all that he does.
I believe there's a heaven.
And someday you
and me and Grandma
and your mom will be
with your dad in heaven.
So, Lord, I thank You for Casey.
I pray that You give him
the dreams of God tonight.
We thank You for our loved ones
pray that
You watch over them all.
- In Jesus name, Amen.
- Amen.
All right, little man.
Get you some rest.
Morning comes early for cowboys.
Ooh! Not a bad
ride there by Dakota Shaw.
Let's give him a round
of applause, everybody,
and thank you for coming out
today for Cimarron's Youth...
Who are these parents
who let these kids ride bulls?
Up next in his debut ride,
Cimarron's own Casey Shane.
Did you do this?
I was just sitting
over here wondering,
who are these parents
who let these kids ride bulls?
Go, Casey!
Woo!
On his debut ride...
Casey Shane!
Out back.
Get lower.
I can't crawl as low as you.
Why not?
Do I need to draw
you a picture, dummy?
One of these days,
you'll be glad
I can't crawl as low as you.
Shoot the big buck on the right.
Shoot.
I missed him.
No.
No, you got him.
You shoot him, you skin him.
You are a cowgirl, aren't you?
I've loved you my whole life.
I could never love anyone
other than you.
I love you forever.
You know, Pop...
been thinking a little
more about it lately.
I think I might just join
the Army after graduation.
Casey, this family's
done enough military service
for several families.
You don't have to do that.
Pop, I know the family's
done enough,
but I ain't done enough.
What about college and rodeo?
See, I figure this way,
get the service out of the way,
before I got me a wife.
Couple grandkids for you, huh?
You know,
there's a little prerequisite
to that kid's deal.
You got anybody in mind?
Ah, I figured Maria
would do. Huh?
Boy, I sure do like that
little lady.
Case, it's a profound
and powerful thing
to stand on the wall
for your country.
Not something to be entered
into lightly.
The young men
we send into battle
are riding point
into the gates of hell.
You gotta be ready for it.
You gotta take
Almighty God with you.
It's a serious decision,
something you need
to be ready for.
Yes, sir.
You think you're ready?
I'm gonna tell you what:
I believe in you.
You know, you're a good man.
Whatever you decide,
I'm gonna support it.
Thanks, Pop.
I know.
- You know.
- I'm late.
Maria, I've been thinking.
Well, now, that's a scary thing.
No, it's about us
and the future.
Are you trying to propose to me?
More like wanting to know if
you're willing to wait for me.
Willing to wait for you
to do what?
I'm joining the Army
after graduation.
Maria, four generations
of Shane men have served
and I can't break that chain.
Casey, God doesn't want you
to do something for me.
He wants you to be the man
that he created you to be.
Would I wait?
I wouldn't like it.
But yes.
- Yes?
- I'd wait.
- You'll wait?
- Yeah.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen,
to the National
High School Finals Rodeo.
All right, Casey.
All the big
rodeo colleges are here
and they're talking
about you, son.
PBR's here too sniffing around,
looking for talent.
And you've drawn
a really good bull tonight
for this go round.
I want you to stick
your toes out, hang your spurs
in his hide and ride like
Old Freckles Brown on Tornado.
How are you feeling, Maria?
Good.
Little nervous.
There'd be something wrong
if you weren't just
a little bit nervous.
And as we go to our barrel race
here this evening,
the ladies barrel race
coming down the alley
for you right now,
the young lady has had an
outstanding year,
has been moving up
in the rankings
and the standings
each and every week.
We hope that it culminates
right here this week,
the National Finals rodeo
for these young men and women.
So, here we go, Maria Martinez,
the Mexico Cowgirl
and this first barrel.
Looking good,
six seconds right now.
We go to number two,
still standing.
Around it we go,
and it's a horse race
back to the house,
and in with... a 16:58.
Oh, look out, leader board,
that might change.
And as we go to the bucking
chutes for the next one,
it's gonna be Casey Shane,
the young man that we've been
talking about all week long.
This kid has exploded
here tonight.
Nods his head, and here we go.
Pulling it out.
Attaboy.
Perfect moves...
Casey, go!
Casey, go...
And here we go.
Look out, there's the horn...
Whoa!
So, what do you think,
ladies and gentlemen?
High 80s, low 90s?
You tell me
and the judges will tell us.
And let's go to that
little Mexico Cowgirl...
Maria Martinez,
through the first.
Looking good.
All right, to the bucking
chutes we go for the young man
who had an outstanding ride
in round number one.
Let's see if he can
back it up here tonight.
Got a good bull,
maybe not as good
as that first one he had,
but a good bull nonetheless.
Nods his head.
Bald-faced bull.
Yeah, a lot of buck.
A lot of buck.
Turning back right about there.
Into his hands. Oh, look out,
look out, look out.
Into the well he goes.
Go get him, boys.
Help him, help him.
Oh. All over him.
Let's see what happens.
We got to see what happened
on him right here.
He's holding
that arm a little bit.
I am getting confirmation,
though,
it was an 8-second ride.
I think we're in business.
So he's two up, two down,
two in the books.
But they got to check him out.
It's gonna be all right, Casey.
Hey, everybody.
Hey, Casey, got some bad news.
We got your results back.
You have a fracture
of the radius.
It's not all the way through,
but it's structurally
compromised.
You're not gonna be able
to ride in the finals.
Sorry.
Hey, Doc, what's the lightest
and strongest cast you got?
I know what you're thinking,
son, it's not a good idea.
Man, if you rebreak this arm,
you could have some
serious permanent damage.
No, but, look, hey.
I got another one
that looks just like it.
You're not ambidextrous,
are you?
Well, I wasn't until today.
So, come on, Doc,
give me the best you got.
Okay, Maria,
you've got your strategy
all worked out and settled
in your mind?
Well, yeah, but I don't
think I can take the lead
with a standard run.
I want to go for the win.
That's my girl.
All right,
let's go to the young lady
that is still in the hunt
for that aggregate title.
She came in close
in the second round.
Here she comes for number three.
Maria Martinez
through the first.
Around it, good.
Oh, this is looking good.
Headed to number two,
tight, best barrel
of the performance so far,
now the elusive number three,
it's the money barrel.
Oh, oh, oh no!
She didn't need that.
No, no, no. It's a penalty
of five seconds.
That's going to hurt her
in that average
and take her completely
out of this run.
Hey, girl.
Look, it's a sport
of inches and microseconds.
You did the right thing.
Hold your head up.
I'm so proud of you.
Now, ladies
and gentlemen, we just got
confirmation that Casey Shane
is the national High School
champion bull rider.
But he is going to go ahead
and get on this last bull.
So I guess it's true.
You can't keep
a good cowboy down.
New Mexico's own Casey Shane
glides up on the rope.
Nods his head, and here we go.
Looking good.
No, no, no.
Get on him, on him, on him.
Reach, grab, no.
Still the champ.
...is still your
National High School
bull riding champion.
How about it
for New Mexico Casey Shane?
Hey, we should go celebrate
tonight, what do you say?
I just need to go
the hotel and go to sleep.
You're not happy that I won?
Yes, for sure, but...
I'm also processing my loss.
I'm exhausted and I feel
upside-down inside.
And I don't know how to rejoice
and grieve at the same time.
All right. But there is
a ton of other girls
who would love to
go out with the guy
who won this
championship buckle.
Are you crazy?
That sounds like a threat.
Don't lose the best thing
you ever had.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Going to the
Maverick club tonight.
You won the
national championship, man.
Time to celebrate.
Hey, I don't drink,
though, so...
- Never did or quit?
- Never did.
Well, you got to try it
once in your life.
- One more! One more!
- Cowboy!
Maria.
Yeah?
There's been a lot of talk
around town that...
Casey two-timed you.
Are you sure?
I hate to be
the bearer of bad news,
but as your friend, I believe
that you should know.
Thanks.
Nobody wants to be played
for a fool.
I heard you went out
after we parted
the last night of the rodeo.
Yeah, I went out with
some of the guys.
You didn't have a late date?
Huh?
No.
I don't like what
I see behind those eyes.
Don't lie to me, Casey.
I'm not lying to you.
You don't think I can tell
when you're lying?
This is your fault.
My fault?
How is this...
You dirty two-faced
faithless liar!
Juan said Maria went
to Albuquerque this morning.
Is there something here
I need to know?
We had a little fight.
She'll get over it.
Well, that's comforting to know.
From the looks
of that strawberry,
I would have thought it was more
than just a little squabble.
Take a seat.
So I want to be special ops.
What do I gotta do
to be one of those guys?
Let's see if you can make it
through basic training first.
There you are.
Well, Pop...
It's time for me to go.
Well, I've been
saving something for you here.
This is the Bible
I gave to your dad
when he left for the service.
Left you a little memento
in there.
"Peace forever and never forget
your way back home."
Memory is the bank into which
we make deposits in good times
so that we can draw
from it in tough times.
She's never gonna
forgive me, Pop.
I don't know
if I can forgive myself.
No bridge too far for the Lord.
Trust in Him. Pray.
Do the right thing.
It'll work out in the end.
May the Lord bless you
and keep you.
May His light shine upon you,
and be gracious to you.
May He lift His countenance up
and bring you peace.
The Lord God is a fortress
and a shield.
And Lord,
today may You be Casey's.
- Amen.
- I love my people.
Please tell Maria
I love her, too.
Attention!
Private, what are you
wearing on your feet?
- Cowboy boots, sir.
- Do I look like a sir to you?
Do not address me as sir,
I work for a living.
You will address me
as drill sergeant.
Yes, drill sergeant.
What are you gonna do
with those roach killers?
Do you think you're Roy Rogers?
- No, drill sergeant!
- Do you think
you're actually gonna
ride a horse into combat?
I don't think so,
drill sergeant.
You don't think so?
We have landed
a man on the moon.
There hasn't been a cavalry
charge in over 100 years.
And if you ride a horse
into battle,
then I'm Peter Frikkin' Pan.
We're gonna get you
some righteous boots, soldier.
'Cause those feet are gonna
carry you into battle.
- Do you understand this?
- Yes, drill sergeant!
Yeah, I know, but have you
seen or heard from her?
We've not seen her
since she left last week.
She came by the ranch and...
she didn't have much
to say, but...
She cried like a baby
when she left.
Casey, you gotta trust
the Lord with these things.
You got to focus.
You're about to stand the wall.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
All right.
We love you, son.
Bye bye.
Good morning, gentlemen.
I'm Sergeant Major Spencer.
Welcome you to the fifth
Special Forces Group.
Congratulations.
You completed
qualification training,
made it through our
training pipeline.
A lot of people try it.
A lot of people
don't pull it off.
So you got that one
under your belt.
But let me tell you this:
you trained to get here.
You're gonna train to stay here,
every hour, every day.
We are training
and we are learning,
or we're not doing our jobs.
- Roger?
- Roger.
Here at Second Battalion,
we're going to emphasize
foreign internal defense
and unconventional warfare.
We are gonna become
masters at infiltration,
link up operations
with guerillas and
guerrilla chiefs,
learning from them,
building rapport,
using what we learn
to lead guerrilla forces
anywhere in our
area of operations.
That is the goal.
Roll him, roll him!
- Roll him over!
- Roll him!
Look to your left
and your right.
That is our most
important asset,
is the Special Forces soldier.
The man next to you.
You will be each
other's savior...
and ally at all times.
So, Staff Sergeant
Casey Shane...
meet your new guys.
Take care, gentlemen.
So, you mean to tell me
you're a cowboy?
- Like, a real cowboy?
- Yes, sir.
Boots, hat, horses...
That type of cowboy?
Or you playing football
in Dallas?
- No, I rode bulls.
- Okay.
Ohh.
How big is your ranch?
Uh, 50,000 acres.
50,000 acres?
Exactly how big is that?
It's twenty miles long,
four miles wide.
Wow. Okay.
How many people
live on your ranch?
We got seven.
Seven?
Seven people?
Dude, that's almost like
the size of Detroit,
and we got 700,000 people there.
Y'all got seven
people on the ranch?
Dude, I know you get lonely.
No, man, it's...
it's paradise.
Just come out
and see it some time
and you'll know
what I'm talking about.
I just might have to take you
up on that offer, man.
But first, is there
any Black people out there?
- We ain't got no Black people.
- What?
Man, you're telling me
you want me to come
to a place where
there's no Black folk,
a few white folk and a whole
lot of empty space?
Yeah, a'ight.
Why are there no Black people
out there, man?
You know, honestly,
I have no idea.
It's kind of funny
'cause Black cowboys
were some of the first people
to settle the West.
Well, look, man,
I'm definitely interested.
And I just may have to
take you up on that offer.
Maybe.
Gonna have to count us in.
What, they let the riffraff
in here this morning?
In? You guys are supposed
to be in 20 minutes ago, man.
Hey, government time.
Government time.
Tu, what you say, next game?
So, since we're all here,
what made you join
the military, Casey?
Oh, uh...
I don't know.
Family tradition, I guess.
Four generations have served.
My dad died
in the Beirut bombings.
Felt like something
I needed to do.
What about you?
Mine is, um, it's pretty simple.
Actually, very simple.
But to make a
long story short...
my daddy left my mom,
me and my little brother
like 12 years ago.
And my mom, she was working
two jobs back then.
And it was horrible
to see my mom, you know,
hustling like that,
trying to make ends meet.
My little brother was doing
horrible in school.
It was just all around bad, bro.
But thank God for the military.
You know, it really
changed our lives.
Now, my mom, she only works
40 hours a week.
You know, they don't
hear gunshots anymore.
Unfortunately, I do.
But, you know, it's a blessing
to have my family
out of that situation.
My little brother's following
right behind my footsteps.
And I just got married, guys.
So, my life is good.
I'm blessed.
Tu, what about you?
Well, um...
My parents made it
out of Vietnam on a boat
and they were out
on the South China Sea
when they were rescued
by the US Navy.
They became
commercial fishermen.
And they're the hardest
working people I know.
Luckily, I had the good
fortune of going to Harvard.
Some folks might say
you're wasting a high
powered education.
Yeah. But the military is
part of my master plan.
- Master plan, huh?
- Now, listen,
seven out of 43 presidents
have Harvard degrees.
31 out of 43
served in the military.
There's a method to my madness.
Okay.
My money's on the fisherman
from the bayou.
Well, John, how about you?
I'm from Highland Park, Texas.
My dad's in the oil business
up there.
You know, to tell you the truth,
he really wasn't excited
about me signing up.
But my grandfather
was a World War II hero,
and I admired him my whole life.
You can call it whatever
you want... rich white guilt.
But I just wasn't gonna sit
in the lap of luxury
- my whole life.
- What?
That sounds like
a comfortable lap to sit in.
So, Joe.
What's your story, bro?
I'm Lakota Sioux.
Lakotas were great warriors
for generations.
And at one time we were
one of the greatest
light cavalry in the world.
Native Americans have
the highest per cap it a
military service of any
ethnic group in America.
There have been
29 Medal of Honor recipients
from the Native Americans.
These warrior ways,
they run deep and die hard.
My man...
that's like you're working
for the same institution...
that oppressed your people.
Yeah, some would say
the same institution
that tried to enforce slavery.
But history is a river, guys.
You can't dam it up.
You can't back it up.
We can't change the past.
You can only alter its
downstream course, the future.
Because an eye for an eye
would leave this
whole world blind.
No cross, no crown.
No pains, no gains.
You know, Joe...
Always wanted a brother.
Now I got four
from all walks of life.
Leave it to
the US military, huh?
De oppresso liber.
To free the oppressed.
Whoa!
What's up, man?
How we doing?
Okay, boys.
We officially made it.
Graduation present.
We're going off to cowboy
paradise, but here's the deal.
I can only adopt one of y'all,
so there might be a fight
to death to earn that spot.
My bets are on John.
So Casey,
you're telling me in the age
of the Internet,
fast cars and airplanes,
you are still
talking about horses?
John, there's been five major
advances in man's ability
to transcend
space and time, okay,
and that has been the
domestication of the horse,
the sailing vessel,
the steam locomotive,
the car and the airplane, okay?
They all have a romantic
culture surrounding them,
but only one has
a dynamic relationship.
Oh, man.
You know, relationships,
I don't know.
You're talking about
an ignorant beast of burden.
What exactly do you mean,
relationship?
Okay, you can ask
millions of people,
millions of testimonies.
But there's a magical bond
between a man and his horse.
Going to have to sell me, man.
It sounds a little crazy.
Hey, laugh all you want.
Just telling you what it is.
White dude speak
with unified tongue.
Woo!
- Cowboy land, baby.
- Woohoo!
Hey.
Oh, wow.
All right, guys.
This is mom.
This is grandma and grandpa.
These are the guys.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, wow.
- Cowboy.
- Oh, wow.
Don't believe anything
she says, y'all.
Hey, boys. Jackpot.
Bull riding tomorrow.
You ain't gotta ride
unless you're feeling froggy.
But you're welcome to join.
Come watch, cool?
All right, turn in early.
You got a long day tomorrow.
Mr. Shane, this must be
Casey's dad.
Yep. That's him.
He was a... he was a great,
great man, served in Vietnam
and survived Vietnam
and died in an age of peace.
Beirut '83.
Casey told us about it.
Yeah.
Very sorry for your loss,
Mr. Shane.
Well, I appreciate that.
Pain fades,
but never goes away completely.
But Casey was a real blessing.
He was a clone of his dad.
Every time I look at him, I...
thought I was looking
at his dad.
But... he gave me
a second shot at fatherhood,
and it's been a great ride.
This country
never ceases to amaze me.
Right.
Greatness emerges
from every corner.
Amen.
Good Lord, what a surprise.
Look at you, man.
- Still one piece, one piece.
- All grown up, man.
- How's everything, man?
- Still alive.
- Still breathing, kicking.
- All right.
- Everything's good?
- Yeah.
All right, come on in, man.
Come on in.
Hey, Carla, you ain't gonna
believe who's here.
Carla.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, hon.
Sure is good to see you guys.
Yeah.
How's everybody doing?
Family, parents?
I heard Maria is still
riding in school?
How is she?
Fair.
Casey, whatever happened...
you broke her heart.
I messed up.
And I know that.
I'd do anything
to take it back, but I can't.
I just hope that you two
are able to forgive me someday.
Please, I just need
to talk to her.
Well, Casey...
she made me swear
I would not do that.
Please, Juan.
Sorry. We can't.
Yes, sir.
Well, I got our guests waiting.
It's been a long day,
I should probably head off.
Just wanted to stop by,
say hello,
see how everyone's doing.
Yeah.
Thinking about you over there.
Praying for you.
Come by again to have
some of those tortillas.
Yeah.
Could you give her this for me?
Just tell her I love her,
please.
I will.
But I think she's ready
to move on without you, Casey.
She sent all your letters
back to me unread.
Casey...
Take care of yourself.
I will. Promise.
Oh-ho-ho.
All right, let's go, boys, come
on, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Everybody, let's go, let's go,
come on, come on.
Burning daylight, here we go.
Yeah, let's go.
Good morning, how you doing?
Man, I'm from the hood,
you can't be barging in
like that.
Five minutes, Tu,
if you don't get
that scrawny butt
of yours up, boy.
Let's go.
I'll meet y'all out there.
Hustle up, boys.
Ready, boys?
All right, Poppy is gonna
show you how it's done.
You might want to listen up,
'cause I've seen you all
try and aim
a rifle before, so...
Good morning.
Welcome to New Mexico.
Hold your hands up.
How many fingers you got?
- Ten.
- Ten?
The objective is
to come away with ten
after you finish roping.
Roll that wrist.
All right, nothing to it.
All you gotta do
is think it there.
So, who wants to try it first?
All right.
Oh!
Hey!
Woo-hoo-hoo.
I just wanna shortstop
any cowboy and Indian jokes
from you chumps.
Maria.
We got to have a girl talk.
That sounds kind of serious.
Maria, I've bit my tongue
for months now,
and that's not fair
or right to you.
I'm going to read
the tea leaves for you.
Okay.
4.0 GPA, pre-vet, check.
Co-captain of the rodeo team.
Check.
Unofficial New Mexico State
record holder
for being asked out
by good-looking guys,
but never having more than
two dates with the same guy.
Now...
either Maria is highly
motivated and ambitious...
and has super high
standards or...
Maria is running from something.
Maria...
You might as well
be wearing a shirt
that says
"Trust issues. Beware."
Don't waste your time.
That obvious, huh?
Yes.
I don't know
what's wrong with me.
I feel like I can't move forward
and... I can't go back.
Back to what?
You're still in love
with Casey, aren't you?
Maybe.
Yeah, like maybe the sun
will rise tomorrow.
Did he ever reach out
to you after the breakup?
Yeah, he sent
several letters to my parents.
Did you respond?
No.
Well, that's a creative way
to catch a guy.
That's playing
hard to get on steroids.
Well, I...
I didn't think I could ever
get over the betrayal.
And then I got to the point
where I thought
I'd take him back
if he crawled on broken glass.
And then I got to
the point where I'd...
take him back
if he just walked in.
But... by then he was over
2,000 miles away.
You got to send him
a smoke signal, girl.
- Like, how?
- Like...
Like, how about
the old-fashioned way?
Write him a letter.
Express your true feelings.
Send it snail mail.
Spill some perfume on it.
I don't know if I could do that.
I haven't talked
to him in two years.
Hmm.
Well, you better
figure it out, and fairly soon.
Or you're gonna end up married
to that barrel horse of yours.
Well, at least we know
we wouldn't have
any trust issues there.
Hey, you all right, Pop?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
You know, I think Doc
may have picked up a rock.
Come on.
I'll check him.
You take him on down
to the spring and loop back.
Pick me up on the way back.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
I'll be all right.
Oh, boy, lookie here.
Lookie here.
That's a "Bonanza" shot
if ever there was one.
Warrior spirit still lives.
All right, so tell me what
you guys think?
- Beautiful.
- Unbelievable.
Man, it's amazing.
Tell you what,
you come out here...
imagination runs wild.
Dreams come true.
Worries don't even exist.
I'll tell you what,
I'm a believer.
I'm definitely a believer.
I wouldn't have
never dreamed it.
But I'm here and I can see it.
When I get out of the Army, bro,
I'm gonna come kick it
with you, for sure.
And you know I'm gonna take you
up on that, right,
put you to work?
Hey, man, just keep me out
of that truck, and we good.
Hey, you come back any time.
Reclaim the ancestor's
legacy, huh?
Thank you.
We saw Casey last week.
He came to the ranch with
some of his soldier fellows.
How was he?
I'd say he was good
and that he looked great.
He must have gained
ten or 15 pounds,
- and all muscle.
- Muscle.
I'd hate to tangle with the guy.
And he's got some great men
in his special operations unit.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I tell you,
those guys make me feel good
about America.
What was the bad?
Well, Casey came to see
your mother and me in private.
Never seen lover's remorse
like that.
- Mm.
- And I got to tell you, Maria,
I think this guy Casey
loves you more than he ever has.
He fessed up
that the breakup
was all his fault.
He expressed
his undying love for you.
And he said he was gonna
come back for you.
So, you better be thinking about
what you're going to say
when he shows up.
I don't know
if I can go back there.
Maria...
most young men
have to Fool's Hills
once or twice
before they grow up.
And the Lord knows I was
captain of the Fool's Brigade.
If there's no forgiveness...
there wouldn't be many men
standing in the end.
Mama, what did you think?
I saw a heartbroken man
deeply in love
with our daughter.
Would you trust him?
With my life.
So, what are you thinking?
Daddy, don't push me.
The heart has reasons
the mind knows nothing of.
- Fair enough.
- Mm-hmm.
Fair enough.
He asked me to give you this.
Dear Maria,
shame and grief have haunted
me since my stupidity,
arrogance and sin caused
the chasm in our relationship.
I think about you
a hundred times a day.
I would understand
if you choose to move on.
But if there's
a glimmer of chance
to put us back together again,
I believe I can persuade you
that I'm a changed man.
I love you
as much as I ever have.
I hope to hear from you.
Love forever, Casey.
Dear Casey,
thank you for your kind note.
I am not sure whether
the pieces of our mutual life
can be put back together,
but I am willing to get together
to see where the trail may lead.
I look forward to
hearing from you soon.
Love, Maria.
These are live pictures
for you right now,
a tragic accident
apparently has just happened
in New York City.
A plane has crashed right
into the World Trade Center.
You can see the smoke
and the flames
coming out of the
shattered windows.
Woo!
Appeared to bank sharply,
and smash directly,
perhaps purposefully into...
- Oh, my goodness.
- Oh, God.
There's another one.
Oh, my goodness,
there's another one.
This seems to be on purpose.
Oh, my goodness, now you...
- Is that a plane?
- Now it's obvious, I think.
Do you know where Casey is?
No.
I think we have a terror attack.
Obviously a suicide
terrorist attack
on the World Trade Center.
What we have been fearing...
What we have been fearing
for the longest time here
apparently has come to pass.
A disastrous terrorist...
Let's strap it on, boys.
We're going to war.
It's Casey.
Yeah, we're the first ones
going in.
We ship out in 48 hours.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
How long will you be gone?
Can't say.
Well, Casey, I wish to God
I could go in your place
or at least go with you.
There's nobody I would trust
more in defending my family
and my country than you.
Know that we... love you,
and hold you in our hearts
and pray for you every day.
We love you more than
you can know.
Forever and always.
I love...
I love my people, and...
I'll communicate as I'm able to.
Bye, Pop.
Got two minutes.
Contact alive, 50 meters.
Got a red chem light.
It's our guy, Case.
Ruck up.
All right, let's do this.
Hello.
Staff Sergeant Casey Shane.
All right, let's move.
This is General Daood.
Please.
Joe, Tu, take watch out front.
We are very grateful
you are here.
More Americans come
when the towers fall.
We prevail, we're very thankful.
The Taliban have ruined
our country.
Our men are very valiant.
We will fight the ground.
We need your air support.
Do your men ride horses?
All experts, sir.
Cars cannot climb mountains.
Elevation.
It is key in my country,
mobility for battle
effectiveness.
Huddle up on me.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed by thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done
on Earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
Lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
Blessed be the Lord.
My God, my rock, who prepareth
my hands for war,
and my fingers for battle.
Lord have mercy on every soul...
we're about to send to you.
Hey, they look like they're
about to make a cavalry charge.
They say anything about that?
Negative.
Not that I heard.
Mm-mm.
21st century cavalry charge,
Bo ain't gonna believe this.
Hey, I ain't missing
this, fellas.
You're not going without me.
Well, come on, brother.
What do you say, Chief?
Time to go kinetic.
Hey, guys, me and Tu
will stay behind,
calling in our CAS.
We'll rendezvous from here
straight down the wadi.
Nobody goes through the pass.
Nobody.
Guys, drop everything
but your arms and ammo.
- Let's do this.
- Hoi!
Ah!
Many Muslims say...
Americans are infidels.
It is strange you and I
be fighting together.
Different countries.
Different religions.
Many will cut my head
if they could.
But... I fight for my people.
Why you say you here?
We're here to kill the people
who attacked our country.
But we're also here
to help you and your people...
experience liberty.
Because that's a basic
human right.
See, God represents freedom,
and without freedom,
you can't have love.
So, although you and me
practice a different religion,
we're willing to risk our lives
to make sure it stays that way.
My country has been called
the Graveyard of Empires.
Alexander the Great
has been broken here.
The British, broken here.
Russians.
I pray to Allah...
that you not broken here.
I pray so, too.
We don't break.
We hear tales of cowboys
in America.
I saw John Wayne movie once.
You Americans don't disappoint.
I am proud to fight with you.
Sleep well, my friend.
Hey, I need you 203
over here in this corner.
You, cover one to three o-clock.
Take a knee, take a knee.
How's he doing?
Okay, good work.
I need another rifle up front.
All right, all right.
Hey. Griffin 99,
this is Sabre two zero.
In contact, 50 hostiles.
We are taking small arms fire
and heavy RPG.
I need immediate air support
and medevac, over.
I got two wounded, one critical.
Viper 61.10 minutes
out...
Griffin 99, Sabre two-zero.
Echo, tango, whiskey,
zulu 379248.
I need immediate air support
north of my position. Over.
Viper 61, tally target...
Hang in there.
All right, boys,
all right, boys, hey,
air support is 10 mikes out.
Our boy's 10 mikes out,
we gotta hold it, right?
Hold it down.
Put me in the fight!
All right,
how are we doing, guys?
Heads in the fight.
Viper 61, roger that.
We are the only structure
in this grid square.
I need 100 meters on
every corner. Expedite.
That's too tight...
Viper 61, I need 100 meters.
Danger close.
I repeat again, 100 meters.
Anybody see that girl?
Put me in the fight.
- I need cover.
- What?
No, what are you doing?
No!
Come on!
Lord, watch over our boys.
Casey, Quan,
Joe, Tu, John.
As a mighty man of old,
I pray, Lord,
that You'd protect them,
You'd watch over them,
and that You bring them home.
In Jesus' name, amen.
Engage.
CAP one, Angel one, wheels up.
Twenty mikes out, standby,
CAS evac...
We got five KIA, one crippled.
O positive, pushing blood now.
CAP one, angel one,
casualty in cardiac arrest.
Popping de-fib and CPR now.
Hello, Sergeant Shane,
I'm Major Rogers,
and this is Captain Jones.
We're so glad
you're gonna be okay.
I will be doing the post-op
on this mission.
How are my guys?
Casey, we regret to inform you
that all of your men
have been killed.
The QRF team found
a detonated suicide vest
in the house.
Little girl must have been
wired with a suicide vest.
I killed my...
I killed them.
No, Casey, you tried
to save a little girl
in an awful firefight.
I killed them.
Casey, you did not
kill those men.
You acted with great bravery
and compassion.
But it looks like everything
will heal up
except for your leg.
Casey, you need
to get some rest.
Push number two on that
telephone if you need me,
and I'll be checking up
on you periodically.
Major, that soldier's world
has just imploded.
I want a suicide watch placed
on Sergeant Shane immediately.
There's something
not right with that boy.
He hasn't left this ranch
in six weeks.
None of us have had
a significant
conversation with him.
He's isolated himself.
I smell liquor on him.
Only good thing
is he started riding again.
Case.
Johnny called and said
he and some of the buds
were getting together for a
game of cards in town tonight.
They'd sure like you
to join them.
Nah, I got some reading
to do tonight.
They really want you to come.
I think it'd be good for you.
Think about it.
Okay.
Hey, toots.
Jager bomb.
You just back
from the Middle East?
Good to see you, Casey.
How you guys been?
- Good.
- Yeah?
- Explain to me.
- Quench your thirst.
- Thank you, sir.
- You think those camel jockeys
give a rip about us
being over there?
Why would you join the military
and fight their war?
You know, it's been said
that patriotism...
is the last
refuge of scoundrels.
Whoever that chump was,
he'd have a different idea
if he knew my guys.
How much they pay you guys?
Enough.
Not to mention
Uncle Sam's gonna pay
for my college education
when I finish my tour.
Kind of makes you
a mercenary, doesn't it?
Look, buddy, you need
to watch your mouth.
Well, it does, doesn't it?
All right, ponytail,
that's enough.
Just apologize to that soldier
and call it a day, huh?
Hey, this ain't your affair.
- Yeah, I got it covered.
- Yeah, stand down.
Actually, it is my affair,
'cause you see, this man,
yeah, he could definitely
handle you,
but then he'd get
court martialed.
And I'd get kind of sad.
So, do the right thing.
Apologize.
Go home.
What happens if I don't?
Well, they're gonna have
to carry you out of here
horizontal and feet first.
Case, what are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
We've been friends for life.
Now I've got to take you in.
You're really
putting me in a bind here.
D.A. may classify you
as a lethal weapon,
and call this armed assault.
And you act like
you don't even care.
Yeah, maybe I don't.
Hmm.
All right, let's go.
Hey, Marshall.
It's good to see you.
Well, nothing like a night
in the slammer
to give you
a whole new perspective.
Casey...
I've been knowing you
ever since you were
just a glimmer
in your mama and daddy's eye.
I love you, son.
God knows I love you.
This whole community loves you.
But it's getting about past time
for you to tell somebody
what happened to you over there.
The only people I want to
talk to about that are dead.
That old boy
needed to be checked,
but you didn't need
to beat him half to death.
What say you?
Case, I don't
want to push too hard.
I realize some things take time.
But don't stay in
the wilderness too long.
Sometimes bad things
take root...
if you let them fester.
We'd love for you to go to
church with us in the morning.
Mean a lot to your mother
and grandmother.
So, Jesus' disciples came to him
with a very
interesting question.
They said, "Lord, who sinned?
"This man or his parents,
that he should be born blind?"
Jesus said neither.
It's what theologians
call the mystery of evil.
How can good and evil coexist
to bring about the glory of God?
Pop... did you fight
in the war like my daddy?
Yeah, it was
called World War II.
We fought a great evil...
and we won.
Many good men did not return.
Casey, you need to always
be thankful.
Thankful for the sacrifices
others have made for you.
Morning.
Where are you headed?
Gonna go see Maria.
Does she know you're coming?
No.
Don't you think
you should give her
a little prior notice
before just showing up?
See you when I'm back.
Hey, Maria.
Hello, Casey.
Was hoping we could
talk for a bit.
I'm sorry for what I did.
I forgive you.
Leaving in the middle
of the night
without telling me
where you're going
and not responding to my letters
sure didn't
feel like forgiveness.
You ignored my letter, too.
Never got a letter from you.
Well, I sent one
eight months ago,
and I never heard anything
back from you.
You know, forgiveness
is one thing.
But growing up
with another person
in a committed love
relationship for a lifetime...
that's even bigger.
Ideals are prickly things.
Without them, life
isn't worth much, and...
with them can come
disappointment.
I grew up believing
that cowboys were tried
and true to their word
and their people.
And especially their women.
I can fix it.
We can put it back together.
What we had was so special.
So unique.
I thought it was a one
in a million kind of thing.
I thought it was sacred.
But... you trashed it.
And if you would trash it
in the best of times,
how could I ever trust you
to be there when
the days go dark?
I... cannot.
And I will not live
with a man I cannot trust.
Some awfully hard words.
Sometimes life is hard.
Sometimes we make them hard
by our own actions.
Doesn't that tried and true
go both ways?
I'm in a bad place, Maria,
I thought my oldest and
best friend could help me out.
I know you're in
a bad place, Casey.
And that something bad must
have happened in Afghanistan.
But we have too much history.
We're too emotionally entangled.
And I'm trying to rebuild
my shattered dreams
and find a way forward.
And with God's help,
I'm gonna make it.
I know you're suffering.
And I want the Lord to heal you
and to restore you.
You have no idea what
happened to me over there.
You just throw me out?
And then you have the nerve
to preach to me about God,
- you selfish, sanctimonious...
- That's it.
Get out. Leave!
You have crushed
every dream I ever had.
Don't ever come see me again
unless God has changed you.
I can't go through
another crushing.
Sorry.
Hi, Mom.
Casey, Pop is sick.
We're at a hospital
in Albuquerque.
What's wrong with him?
That shrapnel from
the war has moved
and caused some damage
and he's developed an infection.
It's... it's not responding
to the antibiotics.
Casey, it's not good.
You need to get here
as soon as you can.
He's asking for you.
Yeah, I'm on my way.
Just tell him I'm on my way,
all right?
Okay.
Well, did you get the girl?
Uh... I'm working on that.
How are you doing?
I feel about like I look,
which ain't too good.
You look pretty amazing to me.
Well...
I believe the old thumper's
about to quit on me.
Man, I... I robbed
the Angel of Death
for several decades longer
than the doctors
thought I'd have.
So I got no complaints.
You ladies, give me and Casey
a little time alone
for a few minutes?
We'll be outside if you need us.
I know you're in trouble.
I know you know
you're in trouble.
The trouble you're in,
I've been there.
Casey, I don't know
what happened over there.
It's a world that'll break
a man in a thousand pieces.
And when it does,
there's only one architect
in the universe
that can put it together.
That's our Heavenly Father.
Case, he did it for me.
He can do it for you.
Pop, I killed my men.
I don't believe that, Case.
We were ambushed
by about 50 Taliban.
Went down the mountain,
Alamoed in an abandoned house.
Two wounded,
but we were fighting.
Called in CAS and evac.
And a little girl ran out into
the middle of the firefight.
So I went and got her.
Brought her back.
She was wired with explosives
and blew us all up.
If it wasn't for me,
my men would still be alive.
No, Case.
You've got this thing all
twisted up in your mind.
That was heroism
in its purest form.
That was self-sacrificing love.
No, Pop.
Those men were my best friends.
The best men I've ever known.
And I don't even have
the courage
to go talk to their families.
I can't even tell them
what happened.
Can't face 'em.
You can do this.
You've got to do this.
Those families, they deserve
to know how their sons died.
They deserve to know how brave
and valiant they were.
And you can relay that
to them, Case.
The cowboy way.
I lost Maria too, Pop.
She was supposed to be
my love of my life,
but I... betrayed her.
Broke her trust.
She told me she never
wanted to see me again.
Case...
I see you.
I see you through the eyes...
of our heavenly Father.
And I know what He has
planned for you.
And I know how He feels
about you.
Come talk with Him.
With me.
Oh, Lord God.
I thank You for Casey.
I thank You for the man he is.
I thank You
for the man he's gonna be.
I pray that You would bring
and put the pieces of
his life, his soul, his spirit,
that You put it back
together again.
Father, I know this man.
I know this man.
I know what he's made of.
I pray that You would open
the eyes of his heart.
The power of Your Holy Spirit
would come upon him,
You to heal him.
You'd put the
pieces of his soul,
of his spirit
back together again.
I pray, Lord, that You'd
give him the courage
to go see those families.
Lord, I pray that You'll
bring him the woman
of Your design.
And Lord, if it's okay with You,
I pray that it be Maria.
I thank You for Casey.
I love him with all that I am
and all that I have.
In Jesus' name, Amen.
I thought you might
slip in a little late.
Maria.
You were one of
Bo's favorite people
in the whole wide world.
I feel like an orphan.
I've abandoned those
most dear to me, and...
now, I have no opportunity
to make it right.
Some of the most
ominous words in the Bible
are "forgive us our sins
as we forgive others."
I think I know
a couple of young people
that are gonna have
to deal with that.
Bye, boy.
God!
Where are you?
You have taken everything
that I've dreamed and loved.
Jesus... Jesus... Jesus.
Please.
Please, please, please.
Case, don't ever forget
what's important in life.
Friendship with God.
Family. Friends.
Meaningful work.
One good horse.
Casey.
I know. I saw.
All your loved ones are with me.
Someday, you will understand.
But for now, you must trust me.
It's time to
come out of the darkness.
And walk with me.
God, is that you?
Casey...
We were worried sick about you.
I'm gonna be okay, Mom.
Well, that went all right.
Hey, Kel.
Is she here?
No.
Do you know where she's at?
Casey...
I know she loves you in
a profound and inescapable way.
Now I need to know...
are you gonna cowboy up?
With all my heart.
She's at her grandparents'
house in Lordsburg.
Go get her.
I'm pulling for you.
Kel...
Thank you.
Thank you, hon.
Oh, and that one, that sunset.
Isn't it beautiful?
Daddy, no.
I'll take care of this.
What are you doing here, Casey?
I don't want to lose you, Maria.
I've loved you my whole life.
I knew as a little boy
that I wanted to marry you.
Casey, that's mighty bold.
Do you think I can just
take your word for it?
How could I ever trust you?
Look into my eyes, Maria.
As God is my witness,
I'll be true to you.
God is healing me
and delivering me
from the darkness, and I will
not drag you down into it.
There's a lot of water passed
under the bridge, Casey.
A broken heart
is a complex thing.
I'll always love you, Maria.
I know with sin
comes consequences,
and I'll have to live with that.
I just want you to know
you're such a beautiful,
extraordinary woman,
truly Godly woman.
I just want the best for you...
even if that's not with me.
You deserve better than me.
You're gonna buck off that easy?
Never again.
What can I do for you?
- Mr. Shane?
- Yeah.
Isaiah Smith,
Kwan's little brother.
Man.
You got to be kidding me.
I didn't recognize you
all grown up.
What are you doing
all the way out here, huh?
A man you knew well,
and the best man I ever knew.
My best friend.
He told me about a place
where the wind blows free
and the sky meets the horizon.
A place my ancestors
helped settle.
He said he would bring me
here one day,
but in chance that he couldn't,
I was to come here alone
and meet you,
and you would give me
a job in his place.
Yeah, well,
he wasn't lying to you.
Oh, and he also said
you have a shortage
of Black folks out here.
Man, he wasn't lying
about that, either.
Welcome home.
All right, hop in.
You rode a horse before?
- No.
- Okay.
- You fix things?
- No.
All right.
- Got any boots?
- No.
No?
We'll figure it out.
All right, Bo.
So, what do you want to be
when you grow up?
Cowboy, just like you, Pop.
We come from
a long line of cowboys.
We love big sky, open range.
We work hard.
Man of our word.
Loyal to our friends and family.
Treat everyone with respect,
especially our women.
Courageous.
Fearing God and no man.
Don't forget the important
things in life, Bo.
Friendship with God.
Family, friends.
And a good horse.
If you do that,
you'll be a rich man...
and a good cowboy.
That's what I want to be.