♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Yeah-eh-eh ♪
♪ I like to wake up in the morning ♪
♪ But keep dreaming without waiting ♪
♪ The day is gone ♪
♪ And sometimes I take a walk ♪
♪ But I forget about the clock ♪
♪ I can't slow down ♪
♪ My friends all sittin' laughing ♪
♪ But I just keep on napping ♪
♪ They're knocking on my door ♪
♪ But I'm knocking them down ♪
♪ They say I'm acting crazy ♪
♪ But I just want to lie in the sun ♪
♪ Whoa, lie in the sun ♪
♪ Now I've been to many places ♪
♪ And won so many races ♪
♪ I was a child ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ But now my only when is now ♪
♪ And my only where is
when I'm by your side ♪
♪ My friends all sittin' laughing ♪
♪ But i just keep on napping ♪
♪ They're knocking on my door ♪
♪ But I'm knocking them down ♪
♪ They say I'm acting crazy ♪
♪ But I just want to lie in the sun ♪
- Another Instagram meal?
- Yeah, you know how many likes they get.
- I'm gonna lock up and head to bed.
- Okay, I'll be there in a minute.
- Don't stay up too late.
Expecting one of your friends?
- No.
- Hello?
Must be those kids again.
I'll make sure the alarm is on.
Can you double check
that the back is locked?
- Yeah.
Brad!
- What,
what happened?
- I saw someone.
There's someone in the-
- Where was he?
- Um, he was in the window.
He looked right at me.
- I don't see anything.
- He was right there.
He was looking right at me.
- Stay here.
Fuck.
Call 911.
Who's there?
- 911, what's your emergency?
- And my boyfriend,
he's out there um,
I saw someone outside
the window of my house.
- Okay, ma'am,
I need you to remain calm.
Where are you located in the house?
- My boyfriend, he's out there, and I,
I can't see him.
I think someone is here.
I saw someone in the window.
- We need you both to stay put
until the officers arrive.
- Please get here.
Please hurry.
I think I hear something.
- Can you call
him back into the room?
- Brad!
I have to do something.
- Ma'am, I
just need you to relax.
We have units on the way.
They will arrive in a few minutes.
- He's out by the door and I-
- Please calm down.
The officers are pulling up now.
- Please get here.
Please hurry.
- Stay where you are.
Do not leave the closet.
Let the officers handle the situation.
Ma'am?
Ma'am, are you still there?
Ma'am, please respond.
Please stay on the line.
Ma'am?
- So you heard a knock
on the front door there?
- Yeah, I answered, but nobody was there.
- And has this happened before?
- I mean, yeah, we live in a neighborhood
with a bunch of bored kids,
but never this late at night.
- So when you closed the
door, did you lock it?
- I could have sworn I did,
but it's possible that I forgot.
- If you left the door unlocked,
perhaps it set off the alarm.
So,
it's mighty windy out, it's possible.
- I guess that could have happened.
- But I saw someone at the back window
right after the knock.
- Okay, did you see someone as well?
- No, but I believe her.
- Okay well, you know, it's late at night.
There's a lot going on.
You look out the window.
I mean, we get calls all
the time from residents
spooked by shadows.
- It wasn't a shadow, I know what I saw.
- Okay, so assuming it wasn't a shadow,
perhaps, do you know anyone
who might be messing with you?
A jealous ex, something of that nature?
- No, I mean, not really.
Sunny has a pretty big
following on social media.
Those guys can get pretty weird.
- Of course.
So what we'll do is we'll
patrol the neighborhood,
keep an eye on the house, and
make sure everything's okay.
- Thank you, we really appreciate it.
- You know, maybe you
should go see some relatives
or friends, if you're
still feeling uneasy.
- I mean, both of our parents
live on the west coast.
- Well, how about you take a vacation?
You know, just get out
there on the open road,
away from the city.
- Yeah, I mean, maybe it is time for that.
- Getting anything?
- Trying.
How is there not even one bar?
- I don't know, but we'd better
figure out something soon.
I have no clue where this damn cabin is.
- Come on, stupid thing.
What are you doing?
- Will you reach into
the glove compartment
and hand me the map?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Okay.
So it looks like we make
a left in a few miles
and we'll run right into the cabin.
- You sure?
- No, but I guess we're gonna find out.
I mean, there's not many roads out here.
- And you told me you wanted
something off the grid.
- Yeah.
But something a little closer to the city
wouldn't have been terrible.
- I did my best for 24 hours of notice.
- I'm just giving you shit, Sunny.
All right.
Damn, good fucking work, Sunny.
This looks even better than the pictures.
- Yeah, it's perfect.
- Really?
We don't even have service out here.
- Say cheese!
- I thought the whole
reason we came out here
was to get away from that stuff.
- Oh, it's just a quick one.
- I mean, at least wait
until we're settled in.
- Hey guys, welcome back.
So I've got a huge surprise for you.
My wonderful boyfriend.
Say, Hi.
- Yo.
- Has surprised me with a weekend get away
to this crazy cabin,
but there's a catch.
So there's no internet.
And my phone is completely out-of-service.
I mean, we barely got here.
This is gonna be our last post
before we return to civilization.
So just be sure to stick
around and subscribe.
Bye, guys.
How was that?
- Really? It's fine.
Come on. Help me with your bags.
- I just think I rushed it a little bit.
I'm gonna do one more.
Hey, guys.
You, go ahead.
Oh man, this place is pretty cool.
- Yeah, this place is sick.
I'll put the suitcases in the back.
- Okay, you want a drink?
- Yeah, I need one.
Fucking finally.
- Oh, shit man, I'm sorry.
I didn't hear you.
I didn't think you were
coming until later.
- It's fine, I just know
anybody else was in here.
- I'm Joe, I run the cabins in this area.
- I'm Brad.
- Pleasure to meet you, man.
Let me, let me show you around.
- Sure.
- Hey.
- Oh Sunny, this is Joe.
He manages the properties in the area.
- Hey Joe.
- You're the one who booked it.
- Yeah, that's me.
This place is beautiful.
We're excited to be here.
- Yeah, it's real popular among folks
who want to get away from the
city, or reality for a bit.
- Well, that's exactly
what we're looking for.
- Let me show you around and
then I'll get out of your hair.
This here's the living
room area, not much.
TV over there.
We don't get cable or satellite,
but we do have a DVD
player with some movies.
So the fridge got a few snacks, not a lot.
- It's fine, we brought
most of our own food.
- Good, 'cause the nearest gas station,
it's about 45 miles out.
- Can you come out here
much if we need anything?
- Yeah.
I make my rounds to
each of the properties.
You know, stuff breaks down all the time,
so it's just a matter of
time before I'm out here.
Oh, and as you probably
already know cell phone service
is like shit out here, comes and goes.
You need to make a call,
I'd say jump on the A1A
and drive for a little bit
and usually you'll get some service.
- And if we need to contact you, like,
let's say if there's an emergency?
- Oh yeah, your best bet, that landline.
I put my home number, my cell number,
but remember, my cell reception
is probably not gonna work.
And I put the local police
station just in case.
Anything else?
- No, I think that's good.
Thanks for the tour, Joe.
- I'm gonna get on down
to my other properties.
You guys should have a quiet night.
There's not going to be
anybody here to bother you.
- How many people are out here?
- It's just you two
right now, but there's,
there's more coming tomorrow.
Most of the cabins are vacant right now.
They all belong to this one owner.
He's one of those prepper guys.
Hey, I just manage the place,
and he cuts me a check each month.
I haven't seen the guy in over two years.
- Prepper like?
- One of those crazy apocalypse guys.
- Oh.
- I don't know how crazy they are
with how things are going in the world.
- Yeah, I guess you have a point.
- Anyways, he rents out these cabins.
They're his bug-out spots.
- Like if the world ends?
- Yup, pretty much.
All the walls are
fortified and reinforced,
and check this out.
Bulletproof windows.
You guys don't have to worry
about any bears getting in here.
- Well, that's good to know.
- I'll be back to make
some repairs and oh,
if you guys want a suggestion,
I'd go ahead and take a hot now
before you settle in,
because the temperature is
quite nice as the sun sets.
- Thanks, yeah, we might try that.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- Finally, that guy can talk for hours.
- You want to start dinner?
- Actually, I was kind of thinking
we could take that hike we talked about.
- I'm kind of just ready to hang out.
- Come on.
It's so beautiful out.
I bet you can get some really
good content for your Insta.
- Think so?
- Yeah, come on.
Let's go before it gets too dark.
♪ It's the coldest hand ♪
♪ That run down this land ♪
♪ Where the ocean led ♪
♪ It's a soulless sound ♪
♪ But their smallest crowd ♪
♪ But their heart speaks loud ♪
♪ I'll push you back towards the fantasy ♪
♪ They're going down for
love and love is free ♪
♪ Stick with me and I will guarantee ♪
♪ You're never lost or
alone, come with me ♪
♪ Never lost or alone, come with me ♪
- How about here?
- Come on. Sunny.
You have enough content for weeks.
- Come on, please?
The lighting's perfect, please?
- All right, give me the phone.
- Okay, thank you.
- Does this look okay?
- It looks so good, you
might not even need a filter.
We're rolling.
- Hey guys, welcome back.
So I've got a quick update for you.
We've been out here like all day,
trying to find some waterfalls.
We were a little delayed,
but I promise we're going
to head back out tomorrow
and get you some really great footage.
So just stick around for more, bye guys.
How's that?
- You know, we've been hiking
for like 15 minutes, right?
- Yeah, but they don't know that.
Plus if we were hiking all day,
I'd get really gross and really sweaty.
And no one wants that.
Cool, it should work.
Wanna head back?
I'm getting kind of hungry.
- Actually, I was thinking
maybe you could head back.
I kind of want to hike a little
bit further down the trail.
- It's getting pretty late, I don't know.
- Come on, it's
like a 10 minute hike back.
I'll be in right behind you, I promise.
- Okay, but if I scream,
you better come rescue me.
- All right, deal.
- What the fuck?
Why the fuck are you following me, dude?
What a weirdo.
What the fuck was that?
It's okay.
You're okay, just a fucking redneck.
- You good?
You look like you just saw a ghost.
- No, yeah.
I'm good.
I heard a noise out there,
probably was an animal,
but wasn't sticking around to find out.
- I've had a pretty
long day, wanna head in?
Yeah.
Sounds good.
Let's go.
Another bottle?
- It's vacation, don't judge me.
- Hey, this is a judgment-free zone, okay?
So I got you a surprise.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah, I was going to
wait until your birthday,
but I figured you could use it.
Come on.
- Slow down.
- You stay right here, and I'll be back.
Okay?
Okay, close your eyes.
Close them.
- Okay.
- Okay, open them up.
- You didn't?
- I just figured you'd get
some good use out of it this weekend.
- Holy shit, how did you even afford this?
This thing is like super expensive.
- Just remember me when
you're Instagram famous, okay?
- Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
I love you.
- I love you too.
- But I do need one more thing.
- Here we go.
- Do you think you
could help me set it up?
- Oh yeah, I think I can manage that.
- Fuckin' creepy-ass woods.
- I'm so excited to shoot tomorrow.
It's gonna look so good.
- Yeah, it shoots in 4K.
What trail do you want to hike tomorrow?
- What are my options?
- Option A is five miles
and it's pretty easy.
Option B is nine miles, but
it's got the nicer views.
- Oh well, yeah probably the
one with the better view,
I would think.
- When's the last time you
hiked nine miles, ever?
- I'll be fine.
All right, well don't
say I didn't warn you.
- Seriously, I mean,
you came back from that walk
earlier covered in sweat.
Brad, did you see anyone
else out there on the trails?
- No, it's just you and me.
- Come here, look at this.
There, you see it?
- I don't see anything, Sunny.
- It's right there.
What is that?
- I mean, it's kind of
blurry, like a glitch.
If two images merged or something.
- No, look, it's in the other ones, too.
What the fuck?
You didn't see anyone else out there?
- Not at that time, it was just us.
It's probably just some
bored redneck kids, you know,
I wouldn't worry too much.
- This was 15 minutes later.
He had to be following us.
- I'm telling you,
I used to play in the woods
all the time when I was a kid.
It's nothing.
- And would you wear creepy
masks and follow people around?
- I mean, no.
- It makes no sense.
I mean, there shouldn't be
anyone else out here for miles.
- I wouldn't worry too much about it.
You know, I mean we're safe in here.
Come on, let's go to bed.
- You don't,
you don't think this has
to do with the other night?
- No, no, I don't.
That was 150 miles away.
Nobody even knows we're out here.
I think we're both
overworked and overstressed,
so let's not bring that stress
here and ruin our weekend.
- Okay.
- I promise, it's just a coincidence.
And if it's not, well,
I'll beat the shit out of him
and bury him in those hills over there.
There won't be any witnesses
as long as you don't snitch on me.
- Come on, I'm ready for bed.
- Yeah?
You know, I'm not really that tired.
Let me see this.
You know what we could do?
- Put that thing away right now.
- Come on, we gotta test it out.
- In your dreams.
- I mean, we could create
some killer content
that I know your fans will love.
- Yeah, the neck beards.
- I mean, this is a whole untapped market,
just waiting to be monetized.
- And only at the expense of my family.
- Is that such a bad thing?
- You are such an asshole.
If you don't put that away,
I'm gonna make you sleep
outside with the bears.
- All I'm saying,
how many followers does
Kim Kardashian have?
- Millions.
- I rest my case.
- Who's that?
- I don't know.
- It's pretty late.
- It's probably just Joe.
Probably left some tools or something.
- Who's there?
- There isn't anyone there.
Hello?
Who's out there?
Joe, is that you?
Hello?
Anyone?
- You heard it too though, right?
It wasn't just me?
- Yeah, no, I heard it too.
- I don't like this.
Look, I know it's weird,
but we're safe in here.
Everything's locked up.
We're fine.
What the fuck?
- Wait.
- God damn it.
Okay, who the fuck is out here?
This is private property
and you're trespassing.
This wasn't funny earlier
and it's not funny now.
You need to leave.
- What do you mean, earlier?
- When I was out there alone.
After you'd left,
saw that guy,
from the photos on your computer.
- And?
- And nothing, I yelled at him.
- Well, did they attack you?
Did they hurt you?
What happened?
- No, no.
He, he creeped me out.
That's all, and I told him to fuck off.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I didn't want to freak you out.
- I want to go home.
- Sunny, we can't leave.
I mean,
we've both been drinking
and I really don't feel like
driving four hours drunk,
with no cell service.
If we still feel unsettled
tomorrow, we can go back home.
- You promise?
- I promise.
Besides.
We're safe in here.
Fuck, even Joe said this place
was built to survive the apocalypse.
There's probably nobody
even out there right now.
Motherfuckers.
Listen here you motherfuck-
- Who are they?
- What the fuck?
- Brad get inside.
- What do you want?
- Get inside.
- I'm fucking talking to
you, what do you want?
- Just come in.
- Sunny, get inside, now.
I'm fucking talking to you.
This is private property and
you're fucking trespassing.
I will call the cops.
- Come on.
- I fucking warned you.
Get your fucking phone,
we're calling the cops.
- Okay.
Nothing.
- Fuck, where's my phone?
Fucking redneck forest,
fucking reception, fuck!
- The landline.
No dial tone.
- Let me see.
Son of a bitch.
- What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
What the fuck are they doing?
- We've got to do something.
You think they were at
the house the other night?
Do you think they've been watching?
- Must want something, maybe money.
Maybe if I give them cash,
they'll just leave us alone.
- You're not going back out there.
- They're not gonna do anything.
I mean, they're just standing there.
If I have to fucking pay them
to leave us the fuck alone, then I will!
I'm not having them
watch us sleep all night.
- Brad.
No.
- The cops are on their fucking way,
so you better get the
fuck out of here, now.
Wanna go to jail?
Fine, just fucking stand there.
Look, just tell me what you want,
so you'll leave us the fuck alone.
We're trying to enjoy our
vacation for Christ's sake.
You want money?
Your fuckin' PayPal, Venmo cash app.
You want fucking cash?
Just fucking tell me.
Go buy yourself some
fucking camo or some shit.
You want me to fuck you up?
Your last fucking warning.
- Can he get in here?
- I don't know.
We need to lock all the
windows and doors now.
Did you get 'em all?
- I don't know.
- You have to be sure,
they're moving around
the side of the cabin.
- I told you, I told
you not to go out there.
You pissed them off and now look at us.
- It's okay.
We're.
- Fucking okay?
These aren't kids, Brad, these are adults.
These are fucking adults.
- Look, they can't get in here, okay?
Even Joe said this place
is like a prepper fortress or some shit.
In the morning,
they'll either get bored,
or Joe will come and
he'll fix all of this.
- They came at us with knives.
- They didn't attack us though.
- Then they tried to get in here.
- All I'm saying is that
we're safe in here, okay?
We have everything we need.
They can't get in here
and we can wait 'em out.
Okay?
We're okay.
They cut the power.
- No, no.
No no no no.
- Read lights, get the candles.
It's okay.
We're okay.
We didn't even need power.
We'll get through this, all right?
We just have to wait it out, okay?
How did they even know we were here?
You didn't, you didn't
tell me you made a post.
- It was just one,
I know he said not to, but I just, I,
I thought that it'd be
fine, I just, I'm sorry.
- It's okay, all right?
It's fine, we're still safe in here.
I mean, they can't get in, all right?
- What the fuck do you want?
It's not like you can get in here.
If you don't want money, then what?
Just tell us what you want
and I'll give it to you.
Yes, tell me.
I'll give you anything,
just leave us alone.
Anything but that.
Anything but fucking that.
It's okay, I won't let them get you, okay?
I won't let them.
- What are they doing?
- I don't know, Sunny.
None of this makes any sense.
- We should have never come out here.
I should have just, I should
have chose somewhere else.
- Don't worry, it's not your fault.
Okay? It's not your fault.
- I just want to go home.
- Me too.
- It's Joe.
- Oh thank fucking God.
- He can help us.
- Wait, no no, Sunny, Sunny,
they're still out there.
Wait, just stay here.
Joe?
- He can't fucking hear us.
- I don't know what to do.
- Why can't he hear us?
- Should we try and just open up?
- No no, we can't
go out there, we can't.
- Where's he going?
- He's going back,
he's going back to the truck.
- I don't see him.
- I fucking lost him.
- You don't think?
- Do see the guys?
- He's not at his truck.
- He's not over here either.
It's okay, all right?
It's gonna be all right.
I'm sure that Joe's getting
them all three out of here.
- This is our only way out, Brad.
- I know but,
we're safe in here.
They can't get in, okay?
- Okay.
- I'm sure that Joe's out front.
Look, look.
- They fucking killed him.
They're gonna kill us.
They want to kill us.
They want to get in here
and they want to chop us the fuck up.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
We need to get this out.
I won't let them get you.
We're gonna be all right, okay?
I just need some time
to think this through.
Okay?
We need to go, okay?
We need to go, come on.
Okay.
We're still safe in here, all right?
They're outside and we're inside.
- For how long?
We don't have, we don't have any food.
We have no water.
No one's looking for us.
- Someone will come, okay?
Someone has to come, eventually.
- Who?
Hell, the closest police
station is like an hour away.
- When the new renters arrive.
And Joe doesn't show up,
they'll go get the police,
and they'll come find us.
I mean,
we fight.
I promise we can get through this.
All right?
We can wait this out.
We can wait them out.
Wait here.
You don't need to do this.
Look, I know you guys were
just trying to scare us.
Maybe it went too far.
I get you.
I understand.
You don't need to do this.
You're not murderers, or killers.
You just made a mistake.
Look, just let us sneak out the back,
go through the woods,
into our car.
Just drive.
We won't even go to the police.
Like this never even happened.
There's still time.
You can get out.
Okay?
You haven't done anything wrong, not yet.
Even if we went to the police,
I haven't seen your face.
It's not like we could identify you.
No, no don't please.
What are you gonna fucking do?
- Five minutes until what?
- Till nothing.
I'm not gonna do anything,
it's another fucking bluff.
- They're gonna burn down the cabin.
They're going to burn us alive.
- Sunny, Sunny.
Hey, look at me.
Look at me, I have a plan.
Okay?
- There's no way, there's no way.
- Look, we can get out of here.
You can get out of here.
- I can get out?
What about you, what do you mean?
- I need you to listen,
listen very carefully
to everything I'm about to tell you, okay?
- Brad, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no way, no way.
- Listen, all three masked
men are out front, okay?
I'm gonna distract them.
While I have their attention,
I need you to sneak out the back door.
They aren't gonna be expecting it.
- I don't want to, I can't.
We can come up with something else.
- No no, it's only 50 yards
from the back door to the car.
You turn and you run into the woods.
Once you get in the car,
you lock the doors and
you floor it to the cops.
This'll work, Sunny.
Okay, this has to work
- I'm not fast enough.
- Yes, you are.
You just need to run as
fast as you can, okay?
- I don't know if I can.
- No, look, I know you can do this.
I'm sure of it, all right.
You can do this, okay?
This is it, this is our last chance.
- What about, what about you?
What are you gonna do?
I can't leave you here.
I'm not leaving you.
- They want you.
For some reason they want you, Sunny.
So, if you can get away, well then,
they'll just let me go.
And if they don't, I can get out.
I can run into the woods and
I can hide and wait for you
to come back with the cops.
I promise, all right?
This will work, all right, but I need you,
I need you to run as fast
as you can, all right?
And don't look back.
Promise me.
- I promise.
I love you.
- I love you, too.
You gotta move quickly.
We need to move quickly,
we don't have much time.
Wait until I have all three
of them out front, okay?
Wait until I have their attention,
then you make your move.
Okay, ready?
All right you fucking
pussies, I'm coming out.
I want to make a deal.
You take me and you let Sunny go.
You let the girl go.
Come and get me, you pussies.
- Sunny, get the knife, the knife.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Are you hurt, did they hurt you?
- No, I'm okay, I'm fine.
I think, I'm sorry.
I tried, he was too fast.
I screwed it up, that was our only chance.
- We need a weapon.
We need, we need something.
We need something.
Sunny.
Get back.
Sunny, run.
Go, now.
East shit, smooth brain.
Get the fuck off me!
No please, no.
God damn it!
- I need help, I need, I
need someone to send help.
There are three masked men
in the cabin we've been staying at.
I just ran into the woods
and I, I don't know where,
where Brad is or I don't know.
I don't know if he's okay.
I ran out into the woods
and I'm hiding now.
And I don't know if
they're in here with me,
but if you see this
please, please send help.
I don't know if I'm gonna make it out.
So mom, mom and dad.
I love you.
- Hey guys, I just wanted to-
Hey guys,
I just wanted to make a quick
video and catch up with you.
As you can see, I am out of the hospital.
Yay.
These last few weeks
have been pretty crazy
and I really appreciate your
support and your patience,
but the worst is over
and I'm ready to head back
on the road to recovery.
I really can't thank you
enough for sharing my story.
We had over 4 million subscribers,
which is insane and more than
I could ever, ever imagine.
Everything's been going so
fast, I can hardly keep up.
I've got interviews with 60
minutes and CNN and Oprah.
Anyway, I think I'm going to take a break
from social media for a bit.
I don't know when I'll be back,
but I'm sure you'll seeing more of me.
Thank you guys.
Bye.