[birds chirping]
["Life Is Better Loud" playing]
♪ Woo-hoo-hoo, woo-hoo-hoo ♪
♪ Woo-hoo-hoo ♪
♪ Woke up just like any morning ♪
♪ New day, same sunlight pouring down ♪
♪ Woo-hoo-hoo ♪
♪ Danced on to the beat I'm drumming ♪
♪ High hopes pulled my feet
Off the ground ♪
♪ Woo-hoo-hoo ♪
♪ Heart stopped, didn't see you coming ♪
♪ Felt like you took my breath away ♪
♪ Woo-hoo-hoo ♪
♪ I knew this was the start of something ♪
♪ And I think I knew you felt the same ♪
♪ Woo-hoo-hoo ♪
♪ Time frozen, eyes opened ♪
♪ Spun my world around in motion ♪
♪ Just a step away ♪
♪ Just a slip of fate ♪
♪ Oh, you never know
How one simple interaction ♪
♪ Can lead you down a road
Where anything can always happen ♪
♪ The picture in our mind
Changes over time ♪
♪ Bigger than what we imagined ♪
♪ We wouldn't change
A thing about it now ♪
♪ Life is better loud ♪
[chuckles]
[laughing]
[exclaiming]
- [crash]
- [laughing]
♪ Woo-hoo-hoo ♪
[yawns]
[all] Aw!
♪ Woo-hoo-hoo ♪
[vocalizing]
[laughing]
- ♪ Ain't no stopping now ♪
- Whoo! Yeah!
- ♪ Life is better loud ♪
- [crying, laughing]
♪ Oh, it feels like home
No matter where we are together ♪
♪ Wish we'd always known
A bigger crowd was always better ♪
♪ We wouldn't change
A thing about it now ♪
♪ Life is better loud ♪
- ♪ Woo-hoo-hoo ♪
- ♪ Loud house ♪
- ♪ Woo-hoo-hoo, woo-hoo-hoo ♪
♪ Life is better loud ♪
♪ In the loud house, the loud house ♪
♪ Woo-hoo-hoo ♪
♪ Loud house! ♪
Movie!
[peaceful music playing]
[laughter]
Okay, Lily, I didn't wake you up
at 6:00 in the morning just to play.
It's time for another lesson
on how to survive in a big family.
Poo-poo.
Lesson number 374,
Breakfast Burrito Saturday.
Bawitotos!
Now that you have teeth,
you'll want one of Dad's famous
breakfast burritos all to yourself.
- [Lily] Lily!
- Just like your sisters.
Sisters.
Which means it's you against them
at the table.
- [gasps] Uh-oh.
- Don't worry!
Because your big brother
is the man with the plan.
- Patent pending.
- [giggles]
And today's plan
is to get to those burritos
before our sisters wake up.
[sniffs] I can smell them now.
Okay, Lily, it's go-time.
[splats]
Poo-poo.
So all you need to do
is just watch and learn
because around here,
no one outsmarts Lincoln...
Loud.
Nice try, Lincoln.
You're not the only one who remembered
it's burritos Saturday.
Yay! Burritos!
[all scream]
[Lori] Lincoln!
[laughs]
The key is to having a plan
is to always have a backup plan.
Backup plan.
♪ Hot burritos! ♪
♪ Hot, hot burritos, hey!
Do little a dance and move your feet-os! ♪
Hey! Morning, Lincoln! Hello, Lily.
Bawitoto.
That's right, sweetie. "Bawitotos." Mwah!
Hey, where're your sisters?
I thought I heard them.
Did you? Huh...
[clattering]
[all panting, groan]
- Uh-oh.
- [all shouting]
Burritos!
[sighs] Sorry, Lily.
So much for watching and learning.
Backup plan.
Oh-ho-ho!
The student has become the master.
[all clamoring]
[whistle blows]
Lola, we need to go
to make it to your recital on time.
- Don't forget my science fair.
- I have the Junior Morticians Death Match.
I'm working pit crew at the race track!
Soccer playoff.
- Joke-A-Palooza!
- Don't forget my shred-off.
[gasps] You all have activities today?
- [Leni] Not me.
- [sighs]
I just have my fashion show.
That's an activity, honey!
We're not prepared for this!
This is a ding dang disaster!
What do we do? Don't panic! Don't panic!
[screaming] Don't panic!
Relax, everybody. I got this.
Another lesson, Lily.
It's always more important
to help your family than outsmart them.
All right, Louds. Let's go, go, go!
- Lori, golf clubs.
- Thanks.
- Leni, measuring tape.
- Luna, guitar.
- Thanks!
- Lynn, soccer ball.
- Yeah!
Luan, rubber chicken.
- Lucy, black veil.
- Thanks.
- Lola, flaming baton.
- [Lola] Thanks.
- Lana, wrench set.
- Thanks, Linc.
- Lisa, ammonium di...
- Dichromate! Thank you, male sibling.
- All right, we got everything?
- Yup, we're good to go.
Mom, Dad, you forgot something!
[grumbles]
Oh, sorry, sweetie.
[groans]
Okay, where to first?
- Race track.
- Soccer field.
Dad, Lori's first. Take a right.
[upbeat music playing]
- Go, Lori!
- Hole in one!
Hole in one!
Can someone please hold this for a minute?
I got it.
Leni's next.
[Lincoln] Go left. I know a shortcut.
[cheers, applause]
Amazing!
Gotta go!
- Who's next?
- It's Luna time.
[upbeat electric guitar solo playing]
Go, Luna! [whistling]
- Yeah, Luna!
- [cheering]
Thanks, bro.
Go, go, go!
[grunting]
Why did the chicken cross the playground?
To get to the other slide!
[all laughing]
- [cheering]
- Woo-hoo!
- Hey, Lincoln.
- [Lincoln] I got it.
She shoots...
she scores!
- [cheering]
- Lincoln, catch.
Oof! Got it. Dang it.
Lincoln.
You're next, Lola.
- Uh-uh. Hands off.
- [Lincoln] Ow!
Come on, we gotta get to Lana's race.
Woo-hoo!
Lincoln will hold it.
Lisa, you're up.
- [cheering]
- Lisa! Lisa! Lisa!
♪ We are the Louds!
Loud and proud! ♪
♪ We are the Louds! ♪
[both sigh deeply]
Oh! We did it. Thank you, Lincoln.
You sure know how to keep
the old Loud fam' running smoothly, kiddo.
[gentle music playing]
♪ We are the Louds!
Loud and proud! ♪
♪ We are the Louds! ♪
Yeah, Loud and too loud!
[chatter]
Let's get a pic of the kids
for our Loud Wall of Fame.
Oh, great idea!
Everyone, hold up your trophies!
- Get my good side.
- I only have good sides.
- Yeah.
- Not sure I'll show up, but...
- Get my funny side.
- Whoa! Hey! Watch out!
- [grunts]
- [Mom] Okay, everyone, squeeze in.
Sisters!
Hey. Guys, wait for me.
- Look, it's the Loud sisters!
- Nobody tosses a baton like that one.
She embalmed my Uncle Jack!
I wish my family
was as talented as they are.
- [man] Selfie!
- [woman] Can I get an autograph?
Enough loudness. Scoots out.
Hey! You gotta pay
to ride this hog, sonny.
Wait! Hey? Hey, guys?
I want to be in the photo.
[poignant music playing]
Oh, you just must be
so proud of your girls.
- You're ding dang darn tootin'.
- They are very special.
[giggles]
No trophy, no photo. [laughs]
Loser!
- Guess! I'm gonna be in the newspaper!
- That lady wants to interview us on TV!
- [Lori] Most "likes" ever.
- Me too.
- [Dad] How cool is that?
- [sisters] Yeah!
[Dad] Let's go home
and put these trophies on display!
[sighs] I wish everyone thought
I was special.
♪ They say it doesn't matter ♪
♪ How you look or where you've been ♪
♪ So why do I need a thousand likes ♪
♪ To feel like I fit in? ♪
♪ I'd probably have it easy ♪
♪ If I were the only kid ♪
♪ But when you live with ten superstars ♪
♪ It's hard for you to win ♪
♪ I wish I could be ♪
♪ Someone extraordinary ♪
♪ But I'm just me ♪
♪ And that's too ordinary ♪
♪ Is there ever gonna be
A place in the spotlight just for me? ♪
♪ When the world can finally see
I'm special like my family ♪
♪ Will there be a time ♪
♪ When I really shine? ♪
♪ Am I always gonna be ♪
♪ Plain old ordinary me? ♪
♪ Ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Am I always gonna be ♪
♪ Plain old, regular, boring ♪
♪ Unremarkable, ordinary me? ♪
Ordinary? You're talking crazy.
You're just saying that
because you're my best friend.
Name one thing that makes me special.
How about three? You've read
every single Ace Savvy comic twice,
you're the fifth-best junior magician
in Royal Woods,
and that history report you wrote?
It was like I was at the signing
of the Declaration of Independence!
Oh! And you can sing! That's four!
Anyone can do those things.
[sighs] Admit it, Clyde. I'm always going
to be stuck in my sisters' shadows.
I know exactly what'll cheer you up.
My homemade cream puffs!
Or, as I like to call them, "dream puffs."
Mm.
Mm...
[sobbing]
What... What is it?
Too much cinnamon? Not enough cinnamon?
Actually, the recipe doesn't call
for cinnamon but I can add it...
No, Clyde, it's the best!
[sobbing]
It's just that you, my sisters,
everyone is good at something.
Except me.
[Clyde] Nice one, Clyde.
You just made it worse.
Well, I'm not that good at baking.
Then how do you explain this?
[Clyde] I'm just lucky.
- Baking runs in my family.
- What do you mean?
Remember when I took that trip
to France with my Nana Gayle?
That's where I met my great-Nana May,
- who owns a bakery in Paris.
- Bonjour.
[Clyde] She told me about
my great-great-Nana Collette,
- who ran a crepe shop in Calais.
- Bonjour.
And my great-great-great-great-great-Nana
Helene, who baked for French royal family.
Enchanté.
[Clyde] When I got home,
Nana Gayle showed me their recipe books
and I made cream puffs.
She said baking was in my genes,
just like Nana May,
Nana Colette, and Nana Helene.
- [gasps]
- Sorry, was that confusing?
- It was a lot of nanas.
- No!
You just gave me an awesome idea!
You're the best best friend ever!
[door opens]
Mm.
[door closes]
[Mom] Hey, kiddos, it's late.
Time to get ready for bed.
Last one has to take out the garbage...
for the rest of the month.
[both grunting]
Uh-oh.
A superb time to evacuate the premises.
- I get the mirror first!
- Not happening, dude!
You can't brush me off. [laughs]
Quickly, let's skedaddle!
[explosion]
Um, I'm literally trying
to brush my teeth here.
We all are, honey.
Shh, I'm trying to brush my hair
and you made me lose count.
Well, I'm plucking nose hairs
and I lost count too!
[clamoring]
Mom! Dad!
[laughs] Lincoln has
to take out the trash for a month!
I don't care. What part
of the world are we from?
- Who spit toothpaste on my arm?
- Clyde's family's from France.
Well, my family is from right here
in Royal Woods, honey.
I'm not sure where my family is
from originally. Why?
If we knew, we could take
a vacation and meet our relatives.
[all gasp]
- Vacation!
- Five-star hotel, please.
All we need to do is find out
where Dad's family is from.
[all talking at once]
- Okay, let's just slow down, everyone.
- Well, it can't hurt to find out.
All I will need, Father, is a DNA sample.
No needles. I hate needles!
Pshaw. Oh, Father.
Needles are for amateurs.
[exciting music playing]
[device powering up]
[Dad screaming]
I shoulda... picked the... needles!
Boy, I'm glad I know where I'm from.
[laughing] Please don't!
[groans, grunts]
You couldn't have just
made him spit in a cup?
There's a scientific word for that.
Boring.
[Dad groaning]
- Dad?
- No more tickles!
- There, there.
- Is it over?
Indeed. My test has determined
that we hail from a land
the Romans called...
Caledonia.
Uh, just give us the street name, Lis.
Street name, Scotland.
- Whoa!
- What?
- Scotland?
- We have family in Scotland?
- Cool.
- So exotic.
So international.
So expensive!
Thirteen of us traveling all that way?
I know, but we always do find a way
to make vacations work.
- And the kids always have so much fun.
- Please! Can we, please?
[whispering] Prove your love to us.
Scotland, here we come.
- Yeah!
- [cheering]
Let's check the old vacay coin jar!
This is just what we've been saving for.
Where'd all the coins go?
[stairs creak]
What? This winning smile
doesn't whiten itself, you know.
Oh!
No bucks, no luck, dudes.
- [all groan]
- Really?
Mom, Dad, we can make this work! Trust me.
We just gotta be...
a little adventurous.
♪ I packed up all my things
Now there's no looking back ♪
♪ I'm gonna leave it all behind ♪
♪ We might not get tomorrow
But we got today ♪
♪ We've got no time to waste
'Cause it's now or never ♪
♪ Now, now ♪
♪ It's now, it's now ♪
♪ It's now, now ♪
♪ It's now or never ♪
♪ Now, now ♪
♪ It's now, it's now ♪
♪ It's now, now
It's now or never ♪
[train horn blows]
[clock chimes]
♪ It's now or never ♪
♪ I wanna see the world ♪
♪ Wanna do something new ♪
♪ And who knows what we're gonna find? ♪
♪ It's now or never ♪
♪ Now, now ♪
♪ It's now, it's now ♪
♪ It's now, now ♪
♪ It's now or never ♪
♪ Now, now ♪
♪ It's now, it's now ♪
♪ It's now, now ♪
♪ It's now or never ♪
Loud family, welcome to Scotland.
- Whoa.
- Wow.
- You did it, Stinkin.
- Way to go, bro.
- Lincoln, you're the man.
- Totes awesome.
- [Dad] This is great, Lincoln.
- Scotland!
[Lola] It's like something
out of a fairy tale.
[uplifting music soaring]
- I can't wait to meet our relatives.
- Amazing.
I don't see a mall,
but it's still totes pretty.
It's so wonderful, I don't even mind
seeing it in the sunshine.
- [gasps]
- [shutter clicks]
[Scottish accent] Time fer
a wee dauber doon yonder.
- An accent already, Dad? Really?
- At least he's not wearing a kilt.
- Oh, yeah? Check it out.
- My eyes!
Sweet knees, Pops.
Oh! Bobby's not gonna believe I'm here.
Boo Boo Bear.
Boo Boo Bear. Boo Boo Bear. Boo Boo Bear...
- Owie!
- Boo Boo Bear.
Babe. I miss you so much!
Oh, Boo Boo Bear.
I hope you got my texts!
I sent one every hour
on the hour just like you asked.
- How's the vacay?
- It's amazing here.
What? Oh, I lost you there for a sec.
- I was saying how much I love Scotland.
- Babe.
Wait. You're breaking up.
I can't hear you.
Babe, I can't hear you.
- I love Scot...
- Babe.
Breaking up... you.
Wait. What?
Stupid phone.
Did Lori just break up with you?
She said she's in love with
some other guy!
Don't just stand there!
You can't let some other guy
be her Boo Boo Bear!
Heck no, I can't! There's only one
Boo Boo Bear and that's me!
Looks like I'm going to Scotland!
- Wait!
- Huh?
What was I thinking?
You can't ride a bike to Scotland...
[clattering]
...without a helmet.
[bicycle bell rings]
Okay, everyone.
So what do you say we meet some Louds?
[all cheering] Yes! Yeah!
Hmm. [gasps]
Let's ask that fisherman
where we can find them.
- Yes!
- Yeah!
[exclaims]
Excuse me. We've traveled halfway
around the world to meet our relatives.
- We're the Louds! Do you know where...
- Louds? Louds!
Louds! Louds!
- Think he's coming back?
- Don't worry, everyone.
I bet there are Louds this way. Follow me.
Let's do this!
Oh, yeah!
Whoa, cool!
[sheep bleating]
What the sheep?
Hmm. Quaint yet illogical.
Just like that door over there.
- Have a lovely day, my dear.
- [all gasp]
- Watch your step, Mrs. Turnberry.
- Thank you, Angus.
Someday, someone will help us
fix this silly town.
[Angus] One can only hope, ma'am.
Looks like someone failed Door-Making 101.
Hey, I bet those signs will tell us
where to look!
Or not.
Someone failed Sign Making 101 too.
[woman] How do I get out of here?
Dudes, look at that!
It's nine o'clock and all is well.
- [all laughing]
- Never seen that before.
Rita! They have a fish shop
and a chip shop.
- The fish goes on chips!
- No, the chips on fish!
Nobody likes cold fish.
- You're a cold fish!
- Well, you married me, didn't you?
This place is crazy town.
Talk about bonkers.
Who's running this show?
Have a nice day, Scott!
Hi, Scott! Hey, Scott!
- Why are you calling everyone Scott?
- Um, we're in Scott Land? Duh.
What's up, Scott? You must be... [grunts]
Scott.
Yeah. How did you know that?
Leni?
Uh, bye, Scott from Scott Land.
That was Scott.
[man] Could it be?
[villagers murmuring]
Hey, Angus, you're not going
to believe who's here. Look!
- [woman] Are those the Louds?
- [gasps]
Well, blow my bagpipes!
- Oh, hi.
- Hello.
Everyone is so friendly.
Pardon me. Are you really Louds?
[bleats]
Yes! We sure are!
[laughing]
Then welcome to Loch Loud!
- Loch Loud?
- That's right, lad!
This town was founded by your ancestors!
♪ You see, about 400 years ago
Our village rose to fame ♪
♪ By a family who founded all
I believe you know the name ♪
♪ But we lost our leaders, lost our way
We've never been the same ♪
♪ That family's name was Loud
And now you've come home again! ♪
♪ This town is named for you, yes
This town is named for you ♪
♪ It's hard to believe, crazy but true
♪ And 400 years we've waited
With a hope as strong as stone ♪
♪ For the Louds to come back home again
We've yearned ♪
♪ In this glorious castle on the hill
We've been awaiting you ♪
♪ My Louds, at last you've returned ♪
♪ Come on! ♪
♪ This town is named for you, yes
This town is named for you ♪
♪ It's hard to believe, crazy but true
♪ This town is named for you ♪
"For You" is a weird name for a town.
Uh, I'm sorry, but who are you?
Oh, ha!
Forgive me! I'm Angus,
the groundskeeper here at Loud Castle.
And I welcome you to your ancestral home!
[Louds gasps]
- Sweet!
- So fancy.
- This is more like it.
- Wowie, wow.
I can't believe Louds lived here.
We could fit 100 of our houses in here.
[whimsical music playing]
Oh me, oh my!
Do my eyes deceive me? Why, you're, um...
Louds!
Yes, I heard the song, Angus.
Everyone in Scotland heard the song.
Our dreams have come true, Morag!
Louds are back after 400 years.
Oh, my!
Put me down!
Oh! Sorry. Sorry.
Loud family, may I introduce Morag,
the castle caretaker.
Oh! Would you care to take my bag?
Lola! Sorry.
I can barely believe Louds have returned
to their rightful place.
Well, for a week.
A week? Not forevermore?
Oh, let's not pry, Angus.
The family is only here on holiday.
Yes, well, I do hope you enjoy your visit.
You'll find lovely accommodations
in the village.
Or they could stay here!
It's their family's castle after all.
- You mean it?
- We can stay?
[all cheering] Yes!
What a marvelous idea.
[cheering]
- I've never been so excited.
- Can we call you Aunty Morag?
- [gasps] Oi! Hands off the antiques.
- Oh!
- Oh, my.
- It was like that already.
- [crashing]
- [cat meows]
[chuckles] That one's on me.
Uh, Mr. Angus, sir,
what can you tell us about our ancestors?
Oh! A grander clan
this land has never seen!
- [Luna] Whoa!
- [Lola] No way!
Am I experiencing double vision?
It's old-timey us!
When did we pose for this?
[Lori] Ten girls and one boy.
Literally just like us.
That's amazing.
Yes!
Yeah. How about that?
Just a week. Only for a week.
Would you fancy a look
at the rest of the castle?
[all] Yes!
[Luan] Last one to their room
is a Scotch egg. Get it?
- [Leni] No, I don't.
- No touching!
[screams]
It's just impossible to find
good help these days.
- [Luan] Woo-hoo!
- Oh!
No roughhousing. Hey, you!
Hey, hands off the tapestries. Tapestries!
So, let me guess.
The sisters were all special, right?
Oh, aye! All were exceptional.
Our loch has never seen anything
quite like the Loud lassies!
Of course.
But there was also...
- Stinkin!
- Lincoln!
- Come here.
- Hurry!
- Chop, chop!
- Sorry, Angus, I gotta go.
What? What is it?
[Lori] You have to see this.
Wow! Look at this!
We all get our own rooms!
[sisters] Lincoln, come look.
I can jam in peace.
Cool.
I can rest in peace.
Spooky.
Whoa!
No more tea parties
ruined by Lana's burping.
Wanna bet?
- [belches loudly]
- [laughs]
My room has a hot tub.
Yeah, I noticed.
Whoa!
I've found my happy place.
- [explosion]
- Boom-boom!
Mine has a fashion runway!
[Lincoln] Styling!
- [mic feedback]
- Mine is big enough to be a comedy club.
[laughs] We each have our own bathroom!
[all] What?
I'm gonna take like 100 leaks a day.
- [toilet flushes]
- [screams]
- Ah, there you are, lad.
- [Lily giggles]
Before you were whisked away,
I tried to tell you
that the most special
of all your ancestors was the duke.
The duke?
Aye. And don't you know,
you'll be staying in his room.
[gasps]
Whoa!
Wait. The boy in the painting
was the duke?
- Aye.
- Hang on.
The boy in the painting
with the white hair was the duke?
Aye.
The boy in the painting
with the white hair that had ten sisters
and looked just like me was the duke?
The one and only!
He was the most special Loud
there ever was.
Yes!
[Angus] Far and wide people knew his name.
His deeds were noble. His heart was stout!
- Whoa!
Sweet digs, Stinkin.
The boy was the duke!
Whatever tugs your tonsils, bro.
Hey, Angus, what's the deal
with all the dragon stuff?
Ah, so you noticed!
If it's dragons you fancy,
there's something you should see.
- [Lana] Ha!
- [Angus] Come with me.
[gasps]
Whoa.
[noble music playing]
The reason why dragons are celebrated here
is that they are a part of our history.
I knew it! Dragons are for reals.
[imitates buzzer] Sounds like hooey to me!
Oh, they're as real
as the tartan in my kilt.
In fact, your ancestors
had their very own dragon.
And when the family left, so did she.
Whoa, a dragon cave!
Keep dreaming.
If it's proof you need,
take a gander at what
your ancestors' dragon left behind.
Whoa! Oh, man. I told you!
This is wack-a-doodle!
Miss Lynn, if you wouldn't mind
taking Miss Lily for a moment.
[giggles]
Just as we hoped
that someday Louds would return,
we hoped a dragon would too.
[gasps] It's hatched!
You mean there's a dragon
on the loose in here?
- Uh-oh.
- No sudden movements.
Easy does it. Remain calm!
[both] Angus!
Ah! Run for your lives!
[shouting]
[laughing]
- Aw, so cute.
- Puppy dragon.
Look at that little face.
- [chuckles]
- We gotta name this little pup.
Lela.
[Lana] Her name is Lela.
[Luan] I love her so much.
She's so cute.
Biologically improbable yet so adorable.
Can we keep her?
Okay. But I am not changing her diaper.
- Yes!
- Thanks, Mom.
[trumpet playing off-key]
Dude, pick a key.
[trumpet sputters]
[trumpet clatters]
[noble music playing]
Uh, what are you doing, honey?
Duke-ing.
Right in front of us?
You know we have our own bathrooms now.
[laughing]
[regal music playing]
Hmm?
Hmm.
[trumpet sputters]
[all laughing]
Nice toilet paper scarf.
Seriously? Pantaloons this time of year?
I think Lincoln's gone
a little panta-looney. Get it?
[exclaims] What the what?
At least someone knows royalty
when they see it.
The rest of you might wanna get on board.
'Cause this Loud is about to rule.
- Dinner is served.
- [Lincoln] I'm okay.
- I cooked everything in the castle.
- Whoa!
I ran out of garlic, so I used Gaelic.
[laughs] Good one, Dad.
- [all cheering]
- [Luan] I call the turkey!
Save some for me.
[Lana] Yay, burritos!
This is all your doing.
It was my pleasure.
[screams]
What a day!
The Louds are back and so is a dragon.
[laughs gleefully]
[Lily giggles]
Bawitotos.
[sniffs]
[whimpers]
[coos]
[giggles]
I'm so glad we did this.
[in Scottish accent] Aye, m'lady.
What a happy clan we have.
Thanks, Angus.
- Mmm.
- [Lily] Bawitos.
So, what's a guy got to do
to become the duke around here?
Come again?
I was thinking about it,
and the duke and I look alike,
we both have ten sisters, white hair,
a turkey tail, we're the same height...
Dragon.
[giggles]
- [stomach grumbles]
- [moans]
Whoa!
Holy moly, she grows fast.
Big girl!
[all laugh]
So the way I see it,
A plus B equals me being the new duke!
What do you think?
Lincoln, I'm afraid
it's not that simple, lad.
[sighs] Wisely spoken.
You should listen to Angus.
One can only become the duke
by making life better
for the people and our village.
I see.
Help the town and become the duke.
Piece of cake.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I've got work to do.
'Cause tomorrow, I'm gonna duke
this town up! Oh, yeah!
You fool! Blathering on
to that featherbrained boy
about becoming the duke!
Oh, the people would love a new duke.
[imitating Angus]
"Oh, the people would love a new duke.”
[normal voice] I don't care a jot
about those peasants!
They're not peasants, Morag.
They're our neighbors, friends.
Enough with your twaddle!
Thanks to you flapping your gob,
I'm stuck with these hooligans!
Crashing through the crowded halls,
dodging girls like...
- Ping pong balls?
- Just to reach the bathroom on time.
[chuckles] That's rather catchy.
Don't you get cheeky with me.
My ancestors have cared
for this castle in peace and quiet
ever since they drove away the...
I mean, ever since the, you know,
the first Louds sailed away forever.
Oh, I deserve better than
to be banished to your wretched hovel.
It's only for a week.
And you'll have oodles of quietness here
in my little castle.
Shall I give you the grand t... Oof.
Oh.
Good night, Morag.
[owl hooting]
[dreamy music playing]
Castle spirits, hear my plea.
I summon a Loud from my family.
On mystic winds, across Scottish moors,
send the girl
who once walked these floors.
[window creaks]
- [wind gusting]
- [laughter]
[crow caws]
[Lana yawns]
- What time is it?
- It's late.
I'm still parachute-lagged.
What's this about, Luce? I need my sleep.
My family from this world,
meet our family from another.
Lucille Loud.
Charmed, I'm sure.
- [all gasp]
- G-G-Ghost!
[grunting]
O-M-Ghost!
She's like a glow-in-the-dark Lucy.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
and to be home after 400 years.
[gasps] Dragons and ghosts?
- This place has everything.
- Whoa.
- She's literally floating.
- Love the see-through look.
- Wow!
- Honey?
- What?
We did take this trip to meet relatives.
Yeah, but not creepy ghosty ones.
- [gasps]
- I heard that.
[Dad screaming]
- [birds chirping]
- [rooster crows]
[groans]
- Good morning, Morag.
- Your athletic supporter, sir?
Not mine. [laughs]
[groans]
Dear Old Aggie,
you so cleverly drove away
those royal ruffians
to have peace and quiet.
How pained you'd be to hear
new Louds have returned!
Thank goodness it's only for a week.
- I wanna ride her!
- My turn!
Oh, you found it. Thanks, Morag.
[Morag] Ow.
Oh! Poor Aggie!
Look what those beasts did to you.
[screams]
- Say, "Ah."
- Ah.
Excellent.
[humming]
Is someone there?
- I...
- [continues humming]
[Morag screams]
[gasps]
[Lily] Poo-poo.
Only for a week.
[Angus] Good day, lad.
You got that right.
I'm about to become the new duke!
[gasps]
You might wanna tell Morag
to start polishing that crown.
I certainly will not be doing that.
♪ I used to feel like a nobody ♪
♪ 'Cause my sisters always
Steal the spotlight ♪
♪ But now I know that I can be somebody ♪
♪ The most special Loud in all the land ♪
♪ I'm gonna turn some heads around ♪
♪ Make everybody know my name ♪
♪ I'll bring a little loud
Into this quiet place ♪
♪ And no one's ever
Gonna steal my spotlight ♪
♪ I'll be the talk of the town ♪
♪ This comic book's gotta go
Ace Savvy's all you should know ♪
♪ Have a breakfast burrito on me ♪
♪ Step right up to my show
For some magic and gold ♪
♪ You can thank me later, 'cause ♪
♪ I'm gonna be the duke ♪
♪ It's my time, my turn to be ♪
♪ The new duke in history ♪
♪ Gonna show my family ♪
♪ I'm ready to rule ♪
♪ I'm gonna be the duke ♪
♪ When you help out other people
Don't just do it to be in the spotlight ♪
♪ Or be the talk of the town ♪
♪ Remember everything you do
It's about them and not you ♪
♪ That's how you live like a Loud ♪
♪ If you want to wear the crown
Go make this town a better place ♪
♪ Look into their hearts
And make some real change ♪
♪ 'Cause magic tricks and short-term fixes
Are not the answer ♪
♪ You've gotta do some good deeds ♪
♪ I hear you loud and clear
I have to act more sincere ♪
♪ That's the secret for me to win ♪
♪ 'Cause if I do this right
I'll be in the spotlight ♪
♪ You can thank me later, 'cause... ♪
♪ He's gonna be the duke ♪
♪ It's my time, my turn to be ♪
♪ The new duke in history ♪
♪ Gonna show my family ♪
♪ I'm ready to rule ♪
♪ He's gonna be the duke ♪
[villagers cheering]
So, did I make life better
around here or what?
[crowd cheers]
All right.
Then how do we make this official?
- We have a coronation.
- [chanting] Duke! Duke! Duke!
Oh, how glorious. Loch Loud will have
a new duke for a week.
Duke for a week?
Actually, six days, 11 hours,
23 minutes and four seconds.
But who's counting?
I burst into dance for a tourist?
- [man] Never mind.
- Whoa! [grunts]
Such a shame.
- Lincoln?
- [groaning]
Take heart, lad. The hard part is over.
Our people want you to be the duke.
Now all you need to do is convince
your family to move here, eh?
Easy peasy.
How do I look?
Oh! Brilliant, sir. But why a suit?
It's my blue convincing suit.
Patent pending.
I wear it whenever I need to talk
my family into something.
It's never let me down. Right, Lil?
Man with plan.
[Lincoln on video] Scotland! Where
the Loud clan first rose to prominence.
Our family came here on vacation
to find our ancestors.
We found so much more.
We found our town,
our castle, our history.
And most importantly, we found ourselves.
So true.
[Lincoln] But soon, our vacation will end.
[screams] No!
[Lincoln] Unless we seize the chance
of a lifetime and fulfill our destiny!
How, you may ask?
By moving to Scotland,
where the Louds can truly live loud!
[Lily on video] Loud and proud.
That last part always gets me. So?
[in Scottish accent] I'm in!
Scotland forever!
- [clears throat]
- This is all 'cause you wanna be the duke.
What? No. It has nothing to do...
- [Lynn] No, no!
- [Luna] Busted.
- No, no, no.
- Fat chance, Lincoln.
Yeah, okay.
So maybe that has a little to do with it.
But moving here would be
wonderful for all of us!
Sweetie, we're on vacation.
We have a life in Royal Woods.
- Not to mention schools.
- Friends.
Adoring fans.
We're not moving to Scotland.
[Lori] Yeah.
[sighs] Mom's right. Forget it.
We should just enjoy our vacation
and go back home...
to our house with one bathroom.
[all gasp]
- We're moving to Scotland.
- [all cheer]
[fanfare playing]
[bagpipe music playing]
[crowd cheers]
- Go, Lincoln!
- That's my brother.
Royalty runs in the family.
Oh, thank you.
Mwah! Mwah!
Oh!
[sighs]
[clears throat loudly]
For four centuries, our loch
has been without a duke,
ever since the first Louds
broke our hearts
and decided to sail away forever.
[crowd] Aw!
I cannot believe my ears.
From today on,
our village will be duke-less no more.
[crowd cheering]
Lincoln Albert Loud,
by the powers vested in me...
Ooh! Cool duke stick.
It's the royal scepter, sire.
- [clears throat]
- [gasps]
By the powers vested in me,
I dub thee
the...
I dub thee...
[groaning]
Duke of...
[continues groaning]
The Duke of Loch Loud.
Yes!
[crowd cheering]
[upbeat music playing]
♪ Shouting through the empty halls
Just to hear an echo call ♪
♪ Trying to find the bathroom on time ♪
♪ Hopscotch on the royal tiles
Corridors that run for miles ♪
♪ It's the perfect home
For the rest of our lives ♪
♪ Loud Castle, Loud Castle ♪
♪ Yell, stretch, spreading out
Even got our own town ♪
♪ Loud Castle, Loud Castle ♪
♪ All the room we'll ever need
It feels good to finally breathe ♪
♪ Loud! Castle! ♪
♪ Loud! Loud Castle! ♪
♪ It's all about me now
Spotlight on Lincoln Loud ♪
♪ Stepping out of the crowd
To really shine ♪
♪ Dub me the one and only ♪
♪ The spotlight is on me
And this time it's all mine ♪
♪ Loud Castle, Loud Castle ♪
♪ So much empty space
With no one in your face ♪
♪ Loud Castle, Loud Castle ♪
♪ Eleven kids, a zillion rooms
I guess it'll have to do ♪
♪ Loud Castle, Loud Castle ♪
♪ Home was sweet but so compact
Why would we return to that? ♪
♪ Loud! Castle! ♪
♪ Loud! Loud Castle! ♪
Loud Castle! [giggles]
[Angus hums]
[sighs] Isn't this awesome?
Us Louds, you two,
hanging at the castle just like old times.
[Morag chuckles sheepishly]
[chittering]
[bleating]
[frog ribbits]
[Morag screaming] I hate
the Louds!
[panting]
- [Lucy] What a wretched day.
- I wish we were out in it.
[both laughing]
But seriously, cousin,
we have an urgent matter to discuss.
Our bond of eternal sadness?
Nay, what I must say,
others may not want to hear.
Lucy, what Morag said
at the coronation is not true.
My family did return to Loch Loud.
On that fateful day,
our hearts were as full as our sails.
We longed to be home again.
I've missed me laboratory.
And my coffin.
And me Scott. He's from Scott Land.
We know.
Home is on the horizon. Land ho!
[Louds cheer]
Look, family! It's our Lolo.
She's come to escort us home.
- Lolo!
- That's our girl!
[growls]
[all screaming]
What's come over her?
She's turning us away.
- How are we to get home?
- We're not.
The dragon forbids it.
But why?
According to ancient lore,
the dragon is the protector of the loch
and a duke's truest friend,
until it deems the duke worthy no more.
Ding dang ancient lore!
I've done nothing to earn such a fate.
Lolo, I command thee to let us pass!
- [Lolo growls]
- [screams]
‘Tis no use, dear brother.
Our fate has been decided.
I shan't argue with that.
Mother, turn the ship around.
And to all,
bid your farewell to Loch Loud.
[screams] What now?
Uh... you must give the crown back.
Of course.
That's so sad.
Normally I like sad, but that's too much.
Why would Morag lie
about your family never returning?
[gasps] Our caretaker Old Aggie!
She kept a journal that chronicled
everything that happened in the castle.
Perhaps the answer lies within its pages.
I wonder where it may be?
[laughs maniacally]
My deviously brilliant,
wicked, dear Old Aggie.
Mwah! Ew. [spits]
You were the first to rid this loch
of hideous Louds!
[gasps]
[cackling]
[cackles]
[roars]
Well done,
you monstrous, pea-brained cretin.
[laughing maniacally]
You got rid of your duke
and I shall get rid of mine!
[cackles]
[sighs deeply]
- [cell phone rings]
- [gasps]
Hi, Lincoln!
How is the best bud that a best bud
could ever have enjoying his vacation?
You won't believe it, Clyde!
Turns out my family is royalty
- and I'm the new Duke of Loch Loud.
- [growls]
[Clyde] Holy dream puff! That's awesome!
I guess now that you're a duke,
you don't have to worry if you're special.
[Lincoln] Yup! No more being stuck
in my sisters' shadows.
- [Clyde] Yes!
- [Lincoln] All hail the duke!
Wait a minute. How are you gonna be
the Duke of Loch Loud in Royal Woods?
Do they have, like, an exchange program?
Um, not exactly, which is why...
we moved to Scotland.
Clyde?
Lincoln, this is the coolest news!
It is? That's such a relief.
I can't wait for you to come visit.
Me too! I'd love to visit Scotland!
Hey, I gotta go.
But call me later, 'cause I wanna hear
all about your new amazing life!
[phone beeps]
[sobbing]
Needs more cinnamon.
[continues sobbing]
Ah, what a friend.
The sisters! Yes, that's it.
[laughs]
♪ The time has come to play pretend ♪
♪ And I'll trick Lincoln
Into thinking I'm his friend ♪
♪ And I'll humiliate the boy, you'll see
And drive the Louds away from me ♪
♪ For good ♪
♪ No, no, no, no! ♪
♪ I must do more! ♪
♪ So other Louds never set foot
Upon this shore ♪
♪ To stop them coming after me ♪
♪ I'll need the crown's authority
For all to see ♪
♪ The duchess I must be ♪
♪ It's what you started ♪
♪ I vow to finish ♪
♪ The reign of Louds
Over this castle will diminish ♪
♪ 'Cause if I want tranquility ♪
♪ The duchess I must be ♪
[laughing]
♪ This foolish town adores that boy ♪
♪ But I will break their little hearts
Oh, what a joy! ♪
♪ And with the dragon on my side
I'll take the duke for a royal ride ♪
♪ What an embarrassing turn of events ♪
♪ It's what you started ♪
♪ I vow to finish ♪
♪ The reign of Louds
Over this castle will diminish ♪
♪ 'Cause if I want tranquility ♪
♪ The duchess I must be ♪
♪ Is it wrong to long for quiet? ♪
♪ Should I just let this family be? ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ The Louds will sail across the sea ♪
♪ And then this town belongs to me ♪
♪ The duchess I will be ♪
[cackling]
- Morag.
- Ah!
- [crow caws]
- [gasps]
You... You're a ghost!
You told the people that my family
sailed away forever. 'Tis not true.
I was there.
I know only what
my ancestors passed down to me.
I want to see for myself.
- Old Aggie's journal. Where might it be?
- A journal?
I didn't know she kept a journal.
[both] We've got our eyes on you.
[bagpipe playing]
[breathes deep]
[bagpipe sound distorting]
[clapping]
Bravo, Miss Luna. Bravo.
Aw, thanks, Morag, dude. Rock on!
Indeed. Heh.
May... May I ask? Why hide
your musical light under a bushel?
I'd tell you if I knew what that meant.
The village has not heard
such stunning bagpipery
since the golden age of your ancestors.
Whoa! I had no idea
my oldies liked to rock.
Yes, they excelled in many things.
Music, fashion, sport, wise-crackery.
[laughter]
It was they who put the loud in Loch Loud.
Whoa.
Oh, how the people would love
for that golden age to return
with you lassies.
I'm snacking what you're packing.
Uh... come again?
I'm in, dude!
I'll go tell the other lassies.
[rock music playing]
Ooh, a letter! Say thanks to Lisa,
big metal bee.
[laughs]
[squeals] I'm supes excited!
My sisters and I are gonna perform
in the village.
And you'll look smashing
in this new dress.
- [chuckles]
- Oopsie.
- [both chuckle]
[laughs] Quite funny.
[both laughing]
[Lincoln] For my next
spellbinding act of magic,
I need one crown.
Voila!
Oh, dear.
Royal crown, I see thee so.
But this duke is hungry,
and he wants a burrito!
Ta-da!
[sighs] My bad, Lil. I didn't give you
enough time for the switcheroo.
Oh, no, sire!
It was jolly good enchantment!
[sighs]
Now, Sir Duke, I believe it's time
for you to seize the royal day
and go to the village,
and serve your people!
Um, I think me and Lil will stay here
and work on our trick.
But, sire,
the people have been waiting 400 years
for their duke to make
their loch a finer place.
Well, when you put it that way...
Lil, your big bro's got
some important duke business to do.
[coughing]
A banner job, sire.
Our chimneys have needed
a keen spiffying for centuries.
Uh-huh. How many more?
One down. Just 432 to go.
[groans]
[cheering in distance]
Well, it's worth it
if the people are happy.
Sire, I'm not certain
where that's coming from.
What? Not again!
Lincoln? Is everything all right?
[crowd chanting] Luna! Luna!
When is a piece of wood like a king?
When it's a ruler.
[laughter]
Here's Leni Loud.
She's the talk of the Highlands.
This is what talent looks like, people.
Yeah!
[woman] Look at that sister skating!
Oh, yeah. Drink in the talent.
Loud sisters hoo! Loud sisters ha!
Loud sisters ho, ho, ho!
[Morag] Oh, poor, poor duke.
It's not fair. I'm the duke!
I'm supposed to be
the most special Loud of all.
Not stuck in your sisters' shadows.
That's what I always say.
Is it now? Hmm.
There must be something we could do
to put a proper spotlight
on our dear duke.
Yeah.
[clears throat]
Ooh. What about that?
- What about what, sire?
- That!
I could ride the dragon
just like my ancestor.
[gasps] Brilliant idea, sire!
I can just picture it.
The people watch you soar overhead,
then break into cheers,
more certain than ever that you are
the most special Loud there ever was.
This is gonna be so awesome!
Oh, yes.
More than you could ever imagine.
[sinister music playing]
[laughs menacingly]
[crowd cheering, whistling]
[Lincoln] Hello, my people!
- [gasping]
- Oh, look at that!
Lincoln?
Go, Lela!
- [Lela roars]
- [Lincoln] Woo-hoo! Yeah!
[Lincoln laughs]
Woo-hoo!
This is amazing.
[crowd gasps]
[ringing]
- [gasping]
- [Lincoln laughs]
[Lincoln] Duked it.
No one's ridden a dragon here
in centuries.
[man] He drew his own face!
Hey! Adoring fans?
[laughs] Yes!
Time for the real spectacle.
[growls]
Lela, what are you doing?
- [crowd shouting]
- [Lincoln screams]
- Lincoln!
- My baby bro.
Why... can't... I steer you?
- Lincoln.
- [Dad] This way!
[Lincoln screaming]
- [Dad] Come on.
- There he is!
- Lincoln!
- Stop!
Ah! Get out of the way!
Look out!
[all screaming]
- Ah!
- Whoa!
Oh, no! We're in-tuh-rubble. Get it?
- [villagers screaming]
- [laughs]
- [shouting]
- [villagers gasp]
- Help!
- Lad, grab on!
Och, steady now, I've got you!
There you go.
[Lincoln screaming]
- [crowd gasping, screaming]
- [Lincoln grunts]
[groans, gasps]
Oh, no.
Don't worry. I can fix everything.
I'm the duke, remember? Here, watch.
[grunts]
See? Good as new.
[chuckles]
- [crowd gasps]
- Oh, no!
It's okay. You still have the fish shop.
That's a relief.
- [shouting]
- [woman] How could you?
- We trusted you.
- I loved that chippie!
How dare he?
[crowd shouting indistinctly]
Lincoln!
[Lincoln sobbing]
- What a mess.
- [Leni] It's a disaster.
- [Lana] This place is trashed.
- [Luna] Total bummer.
[laughing]
[grumbles]
[laughs]
[sighing]
Oh, don't be sad.
Lela did precisely what
she was asked to do.
That's it.
[swallows]
Good girl! Morag needs you
to be big and strong.
- [roars]
- [chuckling]
[ominous music playing]
Even dukes have bad days, sire.
[Lincoln] Bad day? Try "worst day ever."
From the worst duke ever.
[gasps]
It hurts me to hear you say such a thing.
The people need you now more than ever.
[sisters] Lincoln? Lincoln?
Hey, everyone! I found him!
- [Lori gasps]
- [all clamoring]
- Are you all right?
- How you doing, buddy?
- We were worried about you, honey.
- Yeah, you really bombed out there.
- Lola!
- Not funny.
Totally uncool, dude.
If you'll let me finish!
We all blow it sometimes.
[whispering] Even me.
We want you to know
that we talked about it,
and tomorrow,
we're gonna help you rebuild the town.
Really? Aw, you guys are the best.
Well, of course they are! They're Louds!
Do you think the people will forgive me?
If there's one thing about our people,
it's that they don't keep a grudge.
[villagers chanting outside]
Go home, Duke!
Go home, Duke! Go home, Duke!
- We've lost everything!
- Out with you!
Leave our loch!
They're just blowing off some steam.
- Oh, they'll come around.
- Just give 'em time, bro.
No, they're right.
Sire, no. I beg of you.
I don't deserve to be the duke.
Can we go home now?
Toodle pip. Bye-bye!
[laughs gleefully]
I wouldn't want this
to be seen by the wrong eyes.
[chuckles]
Now, dear Aggie,
it's time I fulfilled my destiny.
Gasp. It cannot be. Old Aggie betrayed us!
My dearest friends, thanks to you,
the Louds will be gone forevermore!
- [cheering]
- Great job!
Glad that's over. Back home we go.
Oh, sorry, almost forgot to mention.
Before the Louds skedaddled off,
they requested that I be crowned duchess!
I was like, "Me? What?"
They were like,
"Yeah, totally, you're the best.”
It was so embarrassing.
But how could I say no?
[crowd gasping]
So let's get on with it.
Trumpets, robe, adoration.
[fanfare playing]
Morag, this is not...
By the power vested in me,
blahddy blah blah,
Angus dubs me the Duchess of Loch Loud!
You can't do this.
Silence, you ninny.
Oh, for argyle's sake.
[laughs menacingly]
[crowd chanting] Duchess!
Duchess! Duchess!
[fanfare playing]
No!
- [gasping]
- [trumpets sputter]
The Louds did no such thing.
I was there.
They never gave you the crown!
- [groans]
- Angus is as honest as the day is long.
Is it true, Morag?
You know what? I could lie.
But why bother?
Guilty as accused!
[crowd gasps]
Our people deserve better
than a liar and a thief!
We willnae stand for it! Imposter!
Very well.
I tried doing this the nice way.
Now I'll do it my way.
Huh?
[Lela roars]
We've been run out of lots
of malls before,
but never a whole country.
I didn't get to say goodbye to Scott!
- [sobbing]
- Lela!
Or Lucille.
- Yo, Luce, looks like you'll get a chance.
- [Lucy] Gasp!
Cousins! Cousins!
Lucille.
I come with grave news.
The best kind.
Not this time, Lucy.
Morag has stolen the crown
from our family and made herself duchess.
- Rude!
- What?
That's nefarious.
She can't do that.
We knew Morag couldn't be trusted.
But I did trust her.
- [Lucille] I fear it gets worse.
- Of course it does.
Morag is using the dragon
to chase away the people of Loch Loud.
- What?
- How?
With the ancient dragon stone.
It can turn a good dragon evil.
Wait. My dragon ride.
That's why I couldn't control Lela!
She was under Morag's power.
Translation, Morag wrecked
the village, not you.
It's still my fault.
I wanted to be the duke so badly,
I let Morag trick me.
Now those people will lose their homes.
I've gotta do something about this.
No, we all do.
You're always helping us.
This time, we're helping you.
[uplifting music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Angus] Careful now.
Hurry. Come on, this way.
- [Lincoln] Angus.
- Blow me bagpipes!
Sire! Sisters!
You're back! But I'm afraid
Morag is mad as a March hare!
We know. We've got a plan
to get that scepter and save the village.
[Morag laughs]
I'd say day one as the duchess
has been a smashing success!
[sighs] Peace and quiet at last.
[Lincoln on PA] Testing one, two, three.
- What?
- Let's start the show.
The Louds!
- I don't ding-dang get it.
- A boat, a crown, a muscle-arm?
And a smiley-face poop?
What is Leni trying to tell us?
[Lily giggling]
Boat go bye-bye.
- [both scream]
- Kids!
- [Dad] Starboard!
- [Mom] What does that mean?
[Dad] I don't know!
[Lela growls]
I thought I was done with you!
Show yourselves,
you deplorable, knee-high plonkers.
- [cheers, applause]
- Ah!
Okay, girls!
Operation "Get The Scepter From Morag
And Save The Village Before It's Too Late
And Also Think Of A Shorter Name
For This Operation" is a go!
Luan, you're up.
There once was a duchess named Morag
Whose hair smelled like a floor rag
When she stole the crown
Everyone frowned
'Cause now their ruler was a poo-bag
[laughs]
Come on, feel the noise!
[loud guitar distortion playing]
Fore!
Leni, go!
Yay!
Ah! My eyes!
That teeth whitening was worth it.
Oops. Sorry.
- Lucy, you know what to do.
- Morag, catch me if you can.
Gotcha.
I was almost a goner. Maybe next time.
Fire!
Angus! What is going on?
- My dear Louds, it's madness!
- Where are the kids?
Oh, you know, just battling
a fire-breathing dragon.
- This way.
- Wait! I'm not ready.
- [in Scottish accent] Now I'm ready.
- Blow me bagpipes!
That's it, Luce! Keep coming!
Here we go. It's my turn. I can do this.
[grunts]
Yes! I'm on the dragon.
Ah! I'm on the dragon!
Easy now.
[exclaims]
Phew.
[gasps]
Fire!
[roaring]
- [grunts]
- [both scream]
- [gasps] You!
- I won't let you get away with this!
- Let go!
- Never.
- [Lincoln] You stole it.
- It's mine!
Lincoln needs our help.
We have to get the others.
[roaring]
I command you to let go!
Command?
Is that what this is all about? Power?
Ha! No, this crown will guarantee
no Louds ever bother me again!
[gasps] Hate to bother you, but...
[screaming]
[screams]
Ah! [grunts]
[Luna] Lincoln!
[Lola] We're coming!
- [gasps]
- Holy moly!
- Ah! There he is!
- [Mom] My baby!
[Luan] We're here, brother. Don't worry.
- [all scream]
- No, Lela!
[Morag cackles] Oh, you really bungled it.
You should have sailed away
while you had the chance!
[gasps, grunts]
Now prepare to be loud no more!
[whimpering]
Fire!
No!
Stop!
- [gasps]
- Lincoln!
You want the crown so bad?
Come and get it!
- Lincoln!
- Don't do this!
Lela.
- Lincoln!
- What do we do now?
[Dad] Just don't panic. Don't panic!
Don't panic! Don't panic!
Oh, what a pity. Nowhere to run.
This isn't the way to get what you want.
Maybe you can tell everyone you're sorry.
Why, yes, I could...
if I were a hare-brained fool!
Now give me the crown!
[gasps]
Never, Morag.
It's "Duchess" to you.
You can have all the crowns in the world,
but you'll never be the duchess.
You will never be special!
Just plain, boring Lincoln Loud.
Always in your sisters' shadows,
just where you belong.
You're wrong.
I'm the fifth-best junior magician
in Royal Woods.
What?
What enchantment is this?
Enough!
No more tricks!
Except one! Presto!
Dragon, obliterate this ninny
and bring me the crown!
What?
Oh, dear.
[triumphant music playing]
Ta-da! Lela!
No!
[gasps]
Backup plan. [laughing]
We did it! Way to go, Lily! [laughs]
All I wanted was my peace and quiet.
- And I will have it! Give me the crown!
- Let go!
[all screaming]
Lincoln!
Gotcha, Lil!
[thump]
Wait. What?
[triumphant music soaring]
Lela!
Good girl.
Slow down, Rita!
- Careful, sweetie.
- Ow!
[gasps]
Lily flying dragon!
- [cheering]
- [giggling]
Let me go, you horrid beast!
- That was awesome!
- Way to go, Linc and Lily!
My babies!
Oh, Lela, we can't thank you enough.
Way to go, Lincoln.
We love you, Lela.
Who's a good dragon?
To the Louds! For saving our home!
To Lincoln, whom history will remember
as the loudest of the Louds!
[all cheering]
I'm sorry we doubted you.
[growls]
Duke Loud hoo! Duke Loud ha!
Duke Loud ho, ho, ho!
Our duke is back!
[all cheering]
What you waiting for, Linc?
Put that baby on.
If you don't, I will.
Ever since we came here,
I wanted this crown more than anything.
I thought if I had it,
I'd finally be special like my sisters.
When I wore it,
all I cared about
was what it would do for me,
not what I could do for you.
I'm sorry for being selfish.
The thing is,
someone kept trying to tell me
what it really means to wear the crown,
but I wouldn't listen.
I'm sorry for that too.
That's why there's only one person
who deserves to wear this crown.
- Angus, with the power vested in me...
- Lad, no.
- By the royal Loud family...
- I can't.
I dub thee the Duke of Loch Loud!
No, no, I'm just a simple groundskeeper.
- Oh, you're so much more.
- You're like family.
You've always been there for us.
[boy] The people have spoken, Angus.
- [gasping]
- The duke!
[warm music playing]
- Astonishing.
- It's our family.
Yo, cuz!
Twelve more ghosts. [laughs]
That's fine. I'm totally fi...
A more worthy duke
I've never laid eyes upon.
For you are the true caretaker
of our home and us all.
Thank you, Your Dukeship.
Well, blow my bagpipes.
- [cheering]
- [roars]
[coughs] Oh!
- So, Duke, what about me fish shop?
- What about my chip shop?
What about her?
Oh, dear.
Unhand me, beast!
The dragon is the true guardian
of the loch.
She shall decide Morag's fate.
[laughs]
The joke's on you,
you scaly, putrid lummox!
You gave me my peace and quiet.
[seals barking]
What? No. No!
No!
Lincoln, you giving the crown
to Angus was the coolest!
You're a good dude, dude.
Yes!
But all that stuff
about you not feeling special...
What was that?
[sighs]
You're all so good at everything.
You win trophies,
get your pictures taken, and...
I wanted to be special too.
Lincoln, you are special.
I am?
Yeah. Just like how Angus
takes care of everyone in Loch Loud.
You take care of us.
Every day, bro.
For reals.
That's why you're
the most special brother ever.
- Literally.
- That's right.
- I'll say.
- Indubitably.
Hmm.
I'm good with that.
I love you, Lincoln.
[all] Aww!
Warm feelings.
♪ I've been searching high and low ♪
♪ Looking for that place where I belong ♪
♪ Trying to find my way back home ♪
♪ To the land
Where I can sing my own song ♪
♪ Overlooked and overshadowed ♪
♪ How will I stand out? ♪
♪ Maybe now I can be
Here on this side of the sea ♪
♪ With all my family standing beside me ♪
♪ They just might be the key ♪
♪ Can I find my kind of connection ♪
♪ And a whole new direction
To call my own? ♪
♪ Staring back at my own reflection ♪
♪ With a love and affection ♪
♪ Now I know ♪
♪ I'll always find my way back home ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- Get my good side.
- The brain belongs...
[song continues playing]
[song ends]
I'll miss you, lad.
If you ever need any duke advice,
you can call me.
Deal. You are, after all,
the man with the plan.
- [both] Patent pending.
- [laughs]
- Thank you!
- Bye! We'll be sure to write!
[villagers] Goodbye!
Ah, that was one vacation
we'll never forget.
- That's right.
- Literally.
[Lola] So long, adoring fans!
Try not to miss me too much!
Scotland! Finally!
[screaming] Whoa!
Excuse me, I'm looking
for a girl named Lori Loud.
Can you tell me where she is?
No!
[upbeat music playing]
- Welcome home, buddy.
- Thanks, Clyde.
- Mm-mm-mmm.
- Huh?
- Just the right amount of cinnamon.
- [gasps]
♪ Hey! Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Let's get lost ♪
♪ And find out what's inside of us ♪
♪ Let's get lost together
Let's get lost ♪
♪ Sometimes things don't go
The way you plan ♪
♪ But good things happen
When we take a chance ♪
♪ And I don't want to waste my time
Performing in the front of the line ♪
♪ You never know what you might find ♪
♪ Hey! Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Let's get lost ♪
♪ And find out what's inside of us ♪
♪ Let's get lost together
Let's get lost ♪
Let's get lost! ♪
[traditional Scottish music playing]