Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(CAMERA WHIRRING)
Well, let's see, he was in
charge of me,
my life, me.
But he comes up every once in a
while
just in my mind.
The name is very clear.
Sator, it was Sator, who
was in charge of everything.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(GLASSES CLACK)
(PENS CLATTER)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(PEN SCRAPING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(DISTORTED WHISPERING IN FOREIGN
LANGUAGE)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(DISTORTED WHISPERING IN FOREIGN
LANGUAGE)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
(PEN SCRAPING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(GASOLINE TRICKLING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(FIRE ROARING)
(PEN SCRAPING)
(WATER FLOWING)
(CLATTERING)
(MOSQUITO BUZZES)
(GUN FIRES)
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
(SHELLS CLINK)
(SHELL CLICKS)
(RIFLE CLACKS)
(MOSQUITOES BUZZING)
(GUN FIRES)
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
(LEAVES AND BRANCHES CRACKING)
(WATER FLOWING)
(MOSQUITO BUZZES)
(LEAVES AND BRANCHES CRACKING)
(CALLER SHRIEKING)
(DOG WHINING)
(DOG SNORTS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(TAPE MACHINE CLACKS)
MOTHER ON TAPE: All upon
the face of the forest,
shall tremble at his presence.
And the mountains shall be
thrown down.
For Sator's eyes are in every
place
on those who fear him,
On those who hope for his
kindness.
his acceptance.
Every beast of the forest,
(FOOD SIZZLING)
everything that moves is his.
Sator has made a covenant of
peace,
illuminating all harmful
beasts from this land.
And uses their flesh
(CAN CLACKS)
to cloak his disciples,
so that we may all live
securely in the wilderness
and sleep soundly in the woods.
We find you stranded
in a howling waste of a
wilderness.
We observe you.
We learn all about your ways.
And when the sun rises,
we withdraw and lie down in our
dens.
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(DOG SLURPING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
(DOG SNARLING)
(DOG BARKING)
(DOG WHINING)
(DOG SNARLING)
(DOG LICKING)
(CALLER SHRIEKING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(BRANCHES RUSTLING)
(PAWS PATTERING)
(DOG PANTING)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(METAL CLINKING)
(TRAIL CAM CLATTERING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(CLANKING)
(FOOTSTEPS BANGING)
Hmm.
(BOTTLES CLINK)
(PAN SCRAPES)
(LID SCRAPES)
(PETE SNIFFS)
Hmm.
(PETE GULPS)
(PETE SIGHS)
(JAR CLATTERING)
(LIQUID TRICKLING)
(LID SCRAPING)
What?
Hmm.
(JAR CLACKING)
(FLASK TAPS)
(PETE SIGHS)
PETE: Get out of my head.
(CLATTERING)
(COMPUTER CLICKS)
(COMPUTER WHIRRING)
(ANTLER TAPPING)
(TRAIL CAM CLATTERING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
I bet the card's messed up.
Who's cam is this?
Grandpa Jim's?
Yeah.
Hmm.
(TRAIL CAM CLACKING)
(DOG SNORTS)
You hunting deer?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Mm.
You know grandpa kept a lot of
gear
at the main house, right?
Probably had another one of
these.
Some beer too.
Wanna stop by?
(CLATTERING)
I would have put a shotgun
in my mouth by now,
if this is where I thought I'd
end up.
Fuckin' Deborah.
(PETE BELCHES)
She could have fought a little
harder
for you to be where I'm at.
(PETE GULPS AND SIGHS)
(PETE COUGHS)
(PETE HUMMING)
(SIGHS) I'm telling ya, man,
if you would have just talked
about Sator,
I guarantee the home
would have accepted your ass.
(WATER FLOWING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(CLICKING)
(FOOTSTEPS TAPPING)
(CROW CAWING)
(CROWS CAWING)
(PATTERING)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC)
(NANI CHUCKLES)
all kind of places.
(SCRAPING)
Well I'm not anyone who
gets up to anything anymore.
Not up to anything?
No, I sit in this spot here.
But my brain's dead.
- Mine too.
- Oh.
(LAUGHS) Welcome to the crowd.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- Yeah.
- No, I don't know, I,
memory is something I lose.
I pick up something in the
house,
take it around and put it down,
and then I can't find it again.
- I forgot where I put it.
- Yeah.
Ha, I wasn't lucky when Jim
died,
but when he did,
they still let me stay on here.
I've just been here ever since
then.
I don't know how many
years since Jim died.
I miss him every day.
(CROWS CAWING)
(CONTAINER OPENS)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(LID CLANKS)
(SEEDS RATTLING)
(CROWS CAWING)
So distracted down here.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(CROWS CAWING)
Forget to look up sometimes.
(SEEDS RATTLING)
(LID CLANKS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(CROWS CAWING)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
I'm Evie.
Can I help you look for
anything?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(CROWS CAWING)
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
PETE: Don't drink all of
these.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(BOTTLES CLINKING)
(CARD RUSTLING)
(CONTAINER CLICKS)
(TRAIL CAM CLATTERING)
(CALLER SHRIEKING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(SHRIEKING)
(BOTTLE BANGS)
(LID CLATTERS)
(LID CLINKS)
(TAPE MACHINE CLACKS)
MOTHER ON TAPE: When you
summon Sator,
he will turn his attention to
you.
(CAN LID CLACKS)
Submit yourself
to him, trust in him completely.
And do not lean on your own
understanding.
(DOG SNORTS)
You will be tested by affliction
(KNIFE SCRAPING)
for he is
a consuming fire.
And after you have
suffered a little while,
he will refine you.
(DOG SNORTS)
He will
make you pure.
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(TAPPING AND RUSTLING)
(CLATTERING)
(FLASHLIGHT CLICKS)
(CREAKING)
(LAMP CLATTERING)
(CAN CLINKING)
(THUDDING)
(DOG BARKING)
(DOG WHINING)
(PAWS PATTERING)
(CLATTERING)
(DOG GROWLING)
(DOG WHINING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(PAWS PATTERING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(DISTORTED WHISPERING IN FOREIGN
LANGUAGE)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(ADAM GASPING)
(RUSTLING)
(CREAKING)
(ADAM WHISTLING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(CLATTERING)
(ADAM WHISTLING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(BRANCH SNAPS)
(CLACKING)
(ADAM WHISTLING)
(PATTERING)
(CARD CLATTERING)
(COMPUTER WHIRRING)
(FINGER TAPPING)
(CROWS CAWING)
(CONTAINER CLATTERING)
- Hi, Nani.
- Oh,
hi there.
PETE: How are you?
How come you my name and
I don't know who you are?
Oh, hello.
- Hi.
Good to see you.
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC)
Fred, Jack, Joe? (CHUCKLES)
You know, you know me.
- No, I don't.
- You know.
I don't recognize you. Why is
that?
I don't know.
- It'll come to you.
- Oh, I don't know why.
I just don't recognize
you for some reason.
PETE: I'm your grandson.
Well I thought so, but
you got a beard, you've grown
considerably since I last saw
you.
I was just here yesterday.
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC)
- Yesterday?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
We had a good talk yesterday.
- Who did?
- Me and you.
How you've been sensing spirits.
NANI: I don't remember
yesterday.
PETE: Oh, that's okay.
What kind of things did...
What kind of things happen
around here
that are peculiar?
You sure that was yesterday?
PETE: I'm pretty
sure that was yesterday.
MANI: Well occasionally,
something happens.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
NANI: Things are,
they'll be moved somewhere
- from one place to another.
- Yeah.
(CAMERA WHIRRING)
You put something somewhere-
- NANI: Yeah, and you know darn
well
- you didn't do it yourself.
- Mm-hmm.
(CAMERA WHIRRING)
(GENTLE MUSIC)
(BOX SCRAPES)
Hey, where are you?
Are you in here?
Come on, where are you?
Oh, there you are.
What are you doing?
What's going on with you?
You playing hide and go seek?
- Who are you?
- Okay.
Oh, my God.
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC)
I used to do automatic writing,
and I was told what to write by
spirit.
PETE: It's implanted in your
brain?
- Yeah.
- And you just transfer it
from some other entity
that's telling you what
to write down
Yeah, it's that sort of thing.
Like my guardian
I have a guardian
that I, he, he's always there.
I always, he's gonna
just let me know something is
not right.
- Mm-hmm.
- If it's going to
be a good thing or something
I...
Sator is like a human being
that lives around here
somewhere.
Somebody who manages to get into
my brain
and talk to me. Knew everybody,
what they were saying and doing.
And he was aware of
everything that was done
and what should be done
and what has to be done,
what wasn't done.
How you people are this and
that.
Sator would help me, was
teaching me,
training me to be a person.
Every once in a while,
I just wake up in bed
and he's there.
He talks to me.
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC)
It's interesting to have that
kind
of care. The talking in my head.
I have nothing to do with it.
It just starts, and I listen,
and if I'm supposed
to write it down.
I write it down or whatever.
I don't know.
People think you're nuts
if you tell them that.
PETE: Well I don't think
you're nuts.
Oh good, I hope not. (LAUGHS)
(CAMERA WHIRRING)
Although, when I feel
like wanting something
that I want to know about
(DOOR CREAKING)
or think about
or something, I just think about
it
and he comes in my brain,
(CLATTERING)
or (LAUGHS) he manages to
(DOOR CREAKING)
make me aware of him,
talks to me and do, you know,
make me do some things and
stuff.
That was just a period of time.
- Mm-hmm.
- Then I went off
on my own way, I'd guess you'd
say.
I still wrote stuff.
What's that for?
NANI: I would hear
from him occasionally,
have something written to me.
When I've taken something
- and tried to write on it,
- Come on.
NANI: he gets in there
and telling me I should not be
saying
and doing what I was doing and
saying.
My dog ran off.
I'm sorry.
NANI: Things got so
complicated
and too many people involved.
- Think something hurt him?
- NANI: He still gets
a word in every once in a while
that I'm aware of.
Although he did, he talked to
James. Jimmy.
I'll keep an eye out.
NANI: I don't know any more.
Time has swallowed it all up.
PETE: Well that's
very interesting, Nani.
(NANI LAUGHS)
- (WHIRRING)
- I had voices.
I get messages,
and I still do in a sense.
And he comes to the house.
He comes here,
Sator does, often.
And just not in this particular
area
but out there where he
comes and stands around
and (LAUGHS) and just
watches what I'm doing
or whoever else is there, you
know,
he watches them.
And it still happens.
I still get messages from Sator.
PETE: Ugh, Sator can fuck
off, dude!
ADAM: I don't know
what else to do, dude,
and like, he's holding
Ma hostage somewhere
and doesn't want her to fucking
remember.
Goddammit.
(TRUCK WHIRRING)
I don't know, maybe, I think
I need a cigarette right now.
Seriously though, Brother.
trips me the fuck out what the
brain chooses
to hold on to.
(CLATTERING)
PETE: Like helping
Grandpa Jim build his cabin.
(CLATTERING)
I have this image really
fucking clear in my mind.
But then I found a photograph of
this,
and that's what I'm actually
seeing
is a damn photograph.
(CLATTERING)
I don't remember that day at
all.
It's the same shit with Evie.
I have all these photographs,
but I can't remember her or the
accident.
And that shit was recent.
But we were fucked up
most of the time together.
So I guess that's different.
(COMPUTER WHIRRING)
(TAPE CLACKING)
MOTHER ON TAPE: This is
Sator.
Your path to purification
(SHELLS CLATTERING)
will be tried with fire,
(SHELLS CLACKING)
only then will I make you in my
image.
But first, I will send a
messenger to your temple.
(THUDDING AND RUSTLING)
One who shall prepare the way
before you.
(CLATTERING)
DEBORAH: Are you fucking
kidding?
What the fuck?
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
For this messenger will
be like a refiner's fire,
and will sit as a refiner.
Are you ready
to have dominion
(HAMMERS CLICK)
over every creeping thing that
creeps?
Ready to cleansed
(THUDDING)
and purified.
To join Sator as one of his
disciples.
I am now waiting
for your burnt offering.
I delight in burnt
offerings and sacrifices
just as much as you,
(DOOR CREAKING)
obeying my voice.
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
EVIE: Hi, Adam.
Your dog ever come back?
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
I brought you something.
It was hidden at your
grandmother's.
I didn't know when you would be
back,
so I thought you might wanna
have it.
(DOOR CREAKING)
(BOTTLES CLINK)
(DOOR CREAKS AND CLOSES)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(FAUCET FLOWING)
(TAPPING)
(BOTTLE BANGS)
(LID CLATTERS)
(SCRAPING)
It was with Pete in that
accident.
Glad he made it out okay.
(FOOTSTEPS SHUFFLING)
(BOTTLE TAPS AND SCRAPES)
Thought that'd be a nice memory
to have.
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
Sorry about your mom.
Was anybody able to find her?
I was in a similar situation,
and Pete was the only
person I had to go to.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
I think you're lucky to
have someone like Deborah.
(DISTORTED WHISPERING IN FOREIGN
LANGUAGE)
She really kept it together
for the both of you.
(DISTORTED WHISPERING IN FOREIGN
LANGUAGE)
I hope one day the three
of you can come together.
(DISTORTED WHISPERING IN FOREIGN
LANGUAGE DROWNS OUT VOICE)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(DISTORTED VOICES IN FOREIGN
LANGUAGE INTENSIFIES)
(MATCH STRIKES)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(LANTERN CLATTERING)
(GAS SLOSHING)
(LANTERN HANDLE CLINKING)
(ADAM SCREAMS)
(BODY THUDS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(ADAM BREATHES HEAVILY)
(FOOTSTEPS TAPPING)
(STATIC BUZZING)
MOTHER ON TAPE: Sator has
searched you and he knows you.
He knows when you rest and when
you rise.
He perceives your thoughts from
afar.
He observes you're going out
and is familiar with all your
ways.
When you lay your hand upon
Sator,
such knowledge will be too
wonderful,
too high for you to attain.
(CHAIR CLACKS)
(ADAM GASPS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(FOOTSTEPS SHUFFLING)
(ANTLERS SCRAPING)
(FOOTSTEPS TAPPING)
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(STATIC BUZZING)
There is nothing covered up
that will not be revealed,
and secrets that will not be
known.
He who reveals the
profound and the hidden,
will know what is in the
darkness.
(PICTURE SCRAPES)
What can't be seen in the dark,
can be shown in the light.
(FLAME FLUTTERS)
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(WIND HOWLING)
(BRANCHES RUSTLING)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(GUN FIRES)
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
(PETE WHISTLING)
PETE: Well, I don't know what
to fucking tell you, Brother.
Your dog's gone.
(BOTTLES CLINK)
Should have held it
together for Deborah.
So fucked, this was all put on
her.
(CIGARETTE PACK RUSTLING)
Shouldn't have to put
up with all our bullshit.
(FLAME CRACKLING)
(PETE EXHALES)
(POCKET ZIPPING)
I still think grandpa
Jim sacrificed himself.
So Ma could be with Sator.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You know there was a lot of
weird shit going on there.
I don't think Mom could have
fucking done that herself.
Bet Nani was in on it too.
(PETE EXHALES)
(INDISTINCT)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
Sorry we couldn't find your dog,
dude
What's going on with you,
Brother?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(PAPER CRINKLING)
(LEVER CLANKS)
(MATCH STRIKES)
(MATCH CLINKS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(CAMERA WHIRRING)
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
(DISTORTED PIANO MUSIC)
(BUZZING)
(ADAM BLOWING)
ALL: We want cake!
We want cake!
(SOFT MUSIC)
(PETE CHUCKLES)
- What is this thing?
- Ooh!
(NANI LAUGHS)
NANI: Got in there, an atomic
bomb?
(NANI LAUGHS)
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC)
What?
Shouldn't Ma be here for this?
DEBORAH: You really
think you're gonna get her
- to come out here?
- I'm not going
back there, Deborah.
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC)
(GROUP CHATTERING)
(CAMERA WHIRRING)
MOTHER: First I will send a
messenger
to your temple.
One who shall prepare the way
before you.
(DEBORAH GASPS)
DEBORAH: Are you fucking
kidding me?
What the fuck?
(DOOR SLAMS)
(STATIC BUZZING)
(CAN RATTLING)
(CROWS CAWING)
(CAN CLACKS)
DEBORAH: Go back there.
We need to burn those fucking
writings.
DEBORAH: I wanna get
Adam out of this place.
You wanna take him to
Midground and go see Evie?
Or not.
DEBORAH: Do you think that's
smart?
Hmm?
Having him around that many
people?
(CAMERA WHIRRING)
Adam?
Hey?
Did I hurt you?
DEBORAH: Where do
you go when you do that?
Anyone talking to you?
Like with Nani and Mom?
Is it Sator?
(CROW CAWS)
(STATIC BUZZING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(CLATTERING)
(CLINKING)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(TAPPING)
(OBJECT BANGS LOUDLY)
(CLATTERING)
(CLINKING)
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(CLATTERING)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(THUDDING)
(BANGING)
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(FOOTSTEPS TAPPING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(ADAM BREATHES HEAVILY)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(ADAM BREATHES HEAVILY)
(ROPE RUSTLING)
(EVIE MOANS)
(EVIE WHIMPERING)
(EVIE GASPING)
(EVIE CHOKING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(EVIE GASPING)
(EVIE SCREAMING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(BRANCHES RUSTLING)
(SHRIEKING)
(BRANCH SNAPS)
(ADAM GASPS)
(CREATURE SHRIEKING)
(ADAM SCREAMS)
(WIND HOWLING)
(BRANCHES RUSTLING)
(GUN CLACKS)
(ADAM GRUNTS)
(LIGHT SWITCH CLICKING)
(BAG RUSTLING)
(CANDLES CLINK)
(CANDLES TAPPING)
(PAPER CRINKLING)
(CHAIR CREAKING)
(COMPUTER WHIRRING)
(CURSOR CLICKING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(ADAM GASPS)
(CHAIR CREAKS)
(COMPUTER WHIRRING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(BANGING)
(FOOTSTEPS SHUFFLING)
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(WAX DRIPPING)
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(LANTERN CLATTERING)
(FOOTSTEPS TAPPING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(WATER RUNNING)
(LANTERN CLINKING)
(WATER SPLASHING)
(CREATURES SHRIEKING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(ADAM GROANING)
(WATER RUNNING)
(LANTERN CLINKING)
(BRANCHES RUSTLING)
Uhhhahh!!
(LANTERN CLATTERS)
(WATER RUNNING)
(ADAM BREATHES HEAVILY)
(WATER CASCADING)
(HAUNTING MUSIC SLOWLY FADES IN)
(DISTORTED WHISPERING IN FOREIGN
LANGUAGE)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(LIGHT WIND)
(WATER RUNNING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
(BOX SCRAPES)
(LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS)
(SOFT MUSIC)
DEBORAH: Do you know what
these are?
NANI: It's my handwriting,
but I, it,
I can't read it anymore here.
DEBORAH: They're
your automatic writings.
Yeah. Oh.
- You'd get in trances and
- Yeah.
- spirits would write for you.
- Yeah, well somewhere
along the lines there,
I wanted to have something
going on in my life.
The next thing I found
out was that in my head,
I was being told about things.
For a long time there,
I was writing down stuff
that was given to me,
like people talking to me.
(SOFT MUSIC)
So I would listen, just listen,
and write down what was
being said in my head.
You know, I had access to them.
Even now I can see them.
The people hopping around
in my head. (LAUGHS)
DEBORAH: Did you know mom
was also able to hear them?
NANI: Your mother you're
talking about?
- Mm-hmm.
- No.
DEBORAH: I think she
was trying to join them.
- Well, it's a good possibility.
- Yeah.
Look at this one.
"They've chosen you from
the furnace of affliction.
You may now present an offering
by fire before purification
as a soothing aroma to Sator."
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC)
Hmm.
Do you remember the day
that Grandpa Jim died?
Yes. That was sad.
(SOFT MUSIC)
He seemed to be involved
in it quite a lot,
and we had discussed his
dying somewhere before,
that this is what he is
intending to do.
And he walked out of the house
and went out laid down in the
grass and
and we found him, and he died
there.
That's all I remember at this
time.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause he died.
(SOFT MUSIC)
DEBORAH: Mm-hmm.
Um...
His death
caused Pete to get into
- a lot of trouble with Evie.
- Oh my, yeah.
He's been in a home now for a
while.
He gets out today.
- Oh.
- I get to pick him up.
Oh.
We have to show him how proud
we are of him.
For all the progress he's
been making to get better.
NANI: Yes, yes,
that's important to him.
DEBORAH: Do you think
that you can help me
- with that, Nani?
- Sure, yeah.
I can try. (LAUGHS)
DEBORAH: Thanks.
(WATER FLOWING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC)
Think it's genetic?
What, dementia?
The voices.
Well if it is, I'm glad
Nani never hurt anybody.
Ma didn't either.
DEBORAH: If you still think
Sator killed Grandpa Jim,
we can send you back there right
now.
I have no problem with that.
What about Adam?
- What about him?
- Can we visit him?
No.
I feel bad for just
leaving them up there.
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC)
Excuse me?
You feel bad because
you left him up there?
Did you even see how
it wasn't exactly safe
for him to be around us?
'Cause I don't remember
you making the decision
to isolate him from
everyone because you didn't.
I left him out there.
Give me a goddamn break, Pete.
Mm.
It's been nice talking
to a friendly face,
but I must find my brother and
get home.
I have a long road ahead of me,
and I can't waste any more time.
(CHANNEL CLICKS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Mm.
(CHANNEL CLICKS)
Right at home
(SOFT MUSIC)
with the people, the
beaches, the cool waves.
Welcome to Midground.
A perfect family vacation.
Come stay in the Blaze Inn
Hotel,
with breathtaking views
of Younglove Island.
Take leisurely strolls...
(REMOTE CLICKS)
(PETE SIGHS)
(FAUCET RUNNING)
(CIGARETTE PACK RUSTLES)
Mm.
You want company?
I'm all right.
Mm.
(DOOR OPENS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(TRUCK APPROACHING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
Adam?
Hmm.
(LID CLINKING)
(JAR CLACKING)
(LIQUID SLOSHES)
(LID SCRAPING)
(PETE SNIFFING)
(LID CLACKS)
(JAR CLACKS)
(LID CLINKS)
(WIND WHISTLING)
Ehh.
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(PETE SIGHS)
(THUDDING)
(PETE GROANING)
(FLESH SQUELCHING)
(BLOOD SPURTING)
(PETE GASPING)
(FLESH SIZZLING)
(PETE GROANING)
(PETE SCREAMING)
(FIRE ROARING)
(FLESH SIZZLING)
(PETE GASPING)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(FLESH SIZZLING)
(WATER RUNNING)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(NANI LAUGHING)
Ah.
You going to get ready for
bed, Nani?
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(WALKER THUDDING)
(WATER FLOWING)
(WATER TRICKLING)
Hey, Nani?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Nani?
(LANTERN CLINKS)
(FLAME POPS)
(LANTERN HISSING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(LANTERN CLINKING)
(LANTERN HISSING)
Nani?
(DEBORAH GASPS)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(DEBORAH WHIMPERING)
(DEBORAH CHOKING)
(GAS POURING)
(DEBORAH GASPS)
(MATCH STRIKES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(FIRE ROARING)
(DEBORAH GASPING)
(DEBORAH GROANING HYSTERICALLY)
No!
(DEBORAH SCREAMING)
(FIRE ROARING)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(FOOTSTEPS TAPPING)
(STATIC BUZZING)
Doesn't anyone talk
to you in your head. (LAUGHS)
I don't know how to explain it.
It's just, it's been given to
me.
Sator will send messages
that land in my head.
And so do the other
people who if they want to
will just talk to me.
Right here, talking to me.
Like you now...
What is it that you need?
(NANI LAUGHS)
What do you want to know for
sure?
That Sator loves you?
That he cares about you?
That you're being good?
That you're not being good
about some things,
a little antagonistic,
at times.
Well, I don't know where this
comes from.
I find you quite well organized,
and take good care of me and
what's here.
And I get this voice saying,
and does what we tell you to.
Okay, your turn.
Any messages coming?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull