(police siren wails)
- Dr. Langdon.
Are you familiar with the
statistics of violence
in the United States?
There's a violent crime
committed every 17 seconds.
Forcible rape every five minutes.
Robbery every 46 seconds.
Murder every 21 minutes.
The fact that I find it
hard to ignore the staggering statistics,
is what my husband calls paranoia.
I'm sure he's mentioned it.
- [Doctor] Would you like some
coffee or a glass of water?
- Water would be nice.
Thank you.
Jack thinks that we're all immortal,
and that the pain and
the suffering happens
on some distant planet.
He doesn't realize
that the violence is
happening right outside,
and that the statistics
have faces and families,
and spouses.
- Like yourself.
- I'm a woman living in a volatile city.
My husband leaves me alone for
days on end in a big house.
Every night after work,
I have to walk through
a dark parking garage
to get to my car.
Yeah, I think I'd sum myself
up as a walking target.
- And you don't think you can survive.
- I'm not afraid of dying if
that's what you're asking.
Death I could take.
- [Doctor] And what are you afraid of?
- Just look at the news.
There's sick, sick, torturous
things going on out there.
And I can't get Jack to see it.
- But your husband feels that
you're being a bit obsessive.
- I don't know what else I can do.
- You know, you could confront your fears
instead of running from it.
Are you familiar with
the term virtual reality?
- I think so yes.
- We've developed a new treatment
to help people conquer phobias
that goes beyond virtual
reality or hypnosis.
It involves a total mind immersion
which allows us to go far
into the human psyche.
It gives us a great deal more information
about the human mind for short.
I think this will be a
very great help to you.
- This certainly is not what
I expected when I came here.
- I know it all sounds a bit ominous.
But it's quite safe.
You see, we need to know
how much fear is necessary
to differentiate between a real threat
and what is not a real threat.
Just look at the light and relax.
(suspenseful music)
- I'm sorry, Doctor Langdon.
But I'm just not sure.
- I know this is an awful
lot to digest at one time.
Maybe you'd like to come back another day.
We can try it again.
- Okay, I'll think about it.
(suspenseful music)
(soft music)
- [Reporter] Mayor McMillan's speech
at tonight's charity
benefit was interrupted
just minutes ago with a tragic
news of the mayor's daughter
22-year old Natalie McMillan
and four others were involved
in a drug-related one-car accident.
(dramatic music)
And in local news, Malibu
authorities are on the lookout
for the culprit in a series
of dog and cat mutilations
that has residents crying wolf.
More than 20 household
pets have disappeared
over the past two weeks
in the Malibu hillsides.
(soft music)
- Hi, Mrs. Porter.
Lovely day today, isn't it?
Beautiful.
Beautiful day.
(dramatic music)
(fountain pouring)
- [Alarm Voice] Door is ajar.
You have 10 seconds to disengage
or reactivate the alarm.
Alarm activated, thank you.
- Jack?
Jack!
Jack?
Jack.
- I don't care what the report says.
You can't run a business based around
some bullshit audit figures.
Yeah listen, I got to finish packing.
Yeah, we'll talk about it on the plane.
See you then.
- You're leaving?
- I don't have any choice.
The auditors are trying to
write off some of our assets.
Tim and I are going to
New York for three days
to try to straighten it out.
- Three days.
- Did you see Dr. Langdon?
- [Jenny] Yes.
- Well?
- You know I heard on the news today
that there's been a rash of
cats and dogs missing lately.
What do you suppose is causing it?
- Road kills probably.
- Well, Mrs. Horton never found out
what killed her labrador.
She thought it might be
some kind of a wild animal
or something.
- Jenny, what am I
supposed to say to that?
- That you won't go.
That you won't leave me
here like this again.
- What did the doctor say?
- Not much.
- What am I supposed to do?
Let the company fall to pieces
because my wife is
terrified of her own shadow?
- Jack, her dog was ripped to pieces.
- The vet told Mrs. Horton it
was a roadkill, an accident.
And even if it was a wild animal,
a whole pack of them for that matter,
how the hell they going to get
in here for Christ's sakes?
This place is like Fort Knox.
I've installed a top security system,
closed circuit cameras,
the windows are like steel.
There's three deadbolts on each door.
I'm even building a brick wall outside.
I mean, what else can I do?
Stay with you every hour of every day?
Jenny, you got to stop this.
You won't even let me
open a window anymore.
- I'm sorry.
- We're becoming prisoners.
- I'm sorry, Jack.
Damn it, I just can't help it.
- You're gonna be fine.
- Do you love me?
- What do you think?
(soft music)
- [Alarm Voice] Alarm disengaged.
- I'll call you when I arrive
in New York to check on you.
- Okay.
- It's gonna be late.
- That's okay, call me.
- I love you.
Bye honey.
(suspenseful music)
(ominous whispering)
(dog barking)
(suspenseful music)
- [Alarm Voice] Alarm activated.
(doors locking)
Thank you.
- Hi, Theresa?
This is Jenny.
Jenny Porter.
How have you been?
Yeah, it has, hasn't it?
Hey, but we should get together sometime.
Yeah.
Hey you know what, what about now?
You could come over for dinner
and you could even stay the
whole night if you want.
Jack's out of town and, you're kidding.
Oh my God, I didn't even
know you had a baby.
He's 14 months old.
Oh wow Theresa.
Has it really been that long?
Oh listen, no problem.
We'll talk tomorrow then.
Okay, all right.
Okay bye-bye.
Oh, idiot.
(suspenseful music)
- [Reporter] So we can
count on more of the same,
sunny and 72.
Thanks Tony.
Coming up next, record
highs on Wall Street.
We'll be right back.
(dramatic music)
(ominous whispering)
(suspenseful music)
(crickets chirping)
(cat meows)
(suspenseful music)
- You hush, you're staying here with me.
- [Reporter] The House of
Representatives debated today
over the President's
controversial Crime Bill.
The reform package
includes drastic measures
to increase the number of
policemen on the streets
of our city.
As well as legislators...
(suspenseful music)
In a related matter, the President...
(flashlight clicks)
Their constitutional right to bear arms.
And the President is expected
to sign that bill into law tomorrow.
Officials in Congress are optimistic
that the Navy's new proposed high-tech
satellite detection system will result
in positive identification
that the body of the 28-year old woman
who was found mauled to
death today by wolves
in the Malibu hillside
was indeed Jenny Porter.
Authorities found traces
of Miss Porter's body
strewn throughout the Point Dune region,
where the Navy completed
its second of the successful
satellite matrix system launches.
Pentagon officials were
pleased with the results
and look forward to two more attacks.
- Get a grip.
- Get the US out of the
UN was the cry today
in New York where the
President presided over
the historic Middle East Peace Conference.
The first time in over a
decade that representatives
of the Palestinian
Liberation Organization...
(growling)
(suspenseful music)
(dog growls)
(scratching on door)
(dramatic music)
- Oh my God.
(door shakes)
(suspenseful music)
Let me in, let me in.
Please open this door.
(shotgun fires)
(dramatic music)
(dog growls)
(Jenny screams)
(crickets chirp)
- I'm sorry, baby.
I'm sorry.
Lay down.
Come on, lay down.
(dog panting)
(dog whining)
(men screaming)
- I'm gonna kill it, I'm gonna kill it.
(dog squealing)
(suspenseful music)
- Do you ever fantasize
about being killed?
- Never.
- Do you ever wonder about all
the different ways of dying?
You know, violently.
- Jesus.
Are you hungry?
Want something to eat?
Come on, let's go.
(soft music)
Are you hungry?
Come here, honey.
Hey sweety.
Wanna eat, come on?
- [Girl] Help me.
(suspenseful music)
(glass breaks)
(Jenny grunts)
(scratching on door)
(suspenseful music)
(door opens)
(light switch clicks)
(suspenseful music)
(Jenny screams)
Bengolt, get away from that window.
Go on, get.
(water dripping)
(cat meows)
(dog growls)
(cat screeches)
Bengolt, Bengolt get out of here.
You're driving me crazy.
Get away from that window.
(Jenny gasps)
(suspenseful music)
(phone rings)
Holly.
Holly!
(suspenseful music)
Holly, Holly.
- [Alarm Voice] Door is ajar.
You have 10 seconds to disengage
or reactivate the alarm.
- Damn!
- [Alarm Voice] Five seconds.
- Holly, come here.
- [Alarm Voice] Four, three, two, one.
Sequencing complete.
Initiating automatic lockdown.
(window sliding)
Alarm activated, thank you.
(suspenseful music)
- Holly!
Holly!
(suspenseful music)
(dog growls)
(cat meows)
(dog barks)
(cat screeches)
Holly.
Holly?
(suspenseful music)
(dog growls)
(Jenny screams)
(Jenny panting)
(suspenseful music)
(Jenny screaming)
(dogs barking)
(suspenseful music)
(Jenny screams)
(dogs growling)
(suspenseful music)
(dogs barking)
(phone ringing)
(dogs growling)
- No answer.
- She's probably sound asleep by now.
- Yeah, she's safe.
(dogs growling)
(suspenseful music)
- Help me, somebody help me.
(banging on window)
(suspenseful music)
(dogs growl)
(Jenny yelling)
(suspenseful music)
(branch breaks)
(Jenny screams)
(dogs growl)
(suspenseful music)
- Sparky?
- Hi, Mrs. Porter.
Are you playing with Sparky, huh?
I'm gonna take him home,
I think he likes you.
Good boy!
Mrs. Porter, are you all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
It was just Sparky.
- [Doctor] Jenny.
- What was that?
- [Jenny] Doctor Langdon?
- Our time is up.
I'm afraid I'm going to
have to take you out now.
I'll count back to one and you'll awaken.
Three.
Two.
One.
(Jenny gasps)
Welcome back.
- Oh my God.
I thought I left the office.
- That's the beauty of it.
How do you feel?
- Okay.
- I think it was necessary for you to see
how much fear can feed upon itself.
- I was so terrified.
- I merely planted the
seed of a German shepherd.
And you did the rest.
- My mind turned Sparky
into a pack of wolves?
- Yes.
- Good Lord, maybe I should be in therapy.
- At least until you get
a better perspective.
- Excuse me, hello?
- Oh, Mr. Robinson, how are you today?
- Oh, I'm not that great.
- Doctor Langdon will be right out
and he'll have you smiling in no time.
By the way, did you change
insurance companies?
We've had a problem getting
paid the last couple of visits.
- Oh yeah.
I mean, no.
I mean I meant to get a
new insurance company,
but the others guys are real
sticklers about payments.
- Let me know when you can please.
- I will.
- [Doctor] Come on in, George.
- Oh, hi doc.
- Yeah, go on.
- What is your problem
that you had the see me
three days early?
- Oh, it's pretty much the same problem.
Only worse.
I, I got an eviction notice.
- Didn't you pay the rent as we discussed?
- Yeah, I meant to.
But I, I guess I got carried
away at the Price Club again.
- George, what good is it to save money
on 10 cases of fish food,
when you can't even
afford to pay your rent?
- It seemed like a great buy at the time.
- You've gotta be more responsible
when it comes to your financial matters.
- I know.
- All right, let's get started.
I want you to relax and tell
me exactly what you're feeling.
- What am I feeling?
I'm feeling like it's all
dog eat dog out there.
Or better yet, it's cat
eat bird, dog eat cat,
and so on and so forth.
Until I'm the one that's being eaten.
(mouse squeaks)
(suspenseful music)
(hawk screeches)
(cat meows)
(dog growls)
(suspenseful music)
(staple gun fires)
(paper rips)
- I think I'll go with Lana.
Oh, we're late!
(students chattering)
(dramatic music)
(students chatter)
(typing)
(cards falling)
(suspenseful music)
(lights flickering)
(man groans)
- Damn, I must've overslept again.
Last guy that fell asleep on the job,
he got tagged and they took
him to the crematorium.
When he woke up, ashes to ashes.
Dust to dust.
Anderson, number two.
Riding lawnmower accident.
You're gonna have to
improvise something there.
Cut off all his toes.
Nasty.
Very nasty.
- What a horrible way to die.
- George, it's not the how or why.
How many times do I have to tell you?
You can't choose your own death.
Death chooses you.
Oh, that's good.
That's very good.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- [Vince] Yeah, is the
room still for rent?
- Yes, yes it is.
Would you like to come over and see it?
(dial tone)
Let's see, what do we have here?
Original, tomato.
Fish food, great.
Petey, chow time.
(knocking on door)
Are you the one that called?
- Yep, that's me.
(police siren blares)
- What was your name again?
- Vince.
Vince Powers.
(dog barking)
- Well, the room's right this way.
(water splashes)
Well this is...
- A little sparse for $300 a month.
- Well, the ad did say this
was an unfurnished room.
- Unfurnished.
The ad said furnished.
- Oh no, that's impossible.
I distinctly remember
filling out the card.
- There it is in black and white.
One furnished room, $300.
- Looks like somebody altered the card.
- Really?
Gosh, I hadn't noticed.
Geez, that's awful.
The world today.
So how about it Georgie?
- How'd you know my name?
- So what are we going to
do about our little problem?
- What problem?
- We seem to have a
disagreement on the room.
- I wouldn't call it a disagreement.
It's more of misunderstanding,
don't you think?
- What do I think?
I think you should make good on your end.
- You're right.
You're absolutely right.
I can lend you a few of my things.
I don't have much.
- That's okay, Georgie,
Cause I don't need very much.
- Anything else, Vince?
- Yeah, a little more to the right.
Ho, perfect.
- Well, if there's nothing else,
- Hey, how about dinner?
- I'm not hungry.
- Not for you, for me.
Bed and board, pal.
Says so right here.
- Where?
Meals provided.
- There, see.
Would I lie to you about
something like that?
Hey, you're probably tired
from all the moving, right?
Want to hit the sack right away?
- Yeah, I'm real tired.
- There see, I knew it.
I'm not such a bad guy.
Tell you what?
Just give me 10 bucks
and we'll call it even.
- Ten dollars.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I need the rent money from you,
- But I haven't even
slept here yet, Georgie.
I may not like your bed.
I may not like this room.
I may not like you, and then what?
I've just given my life savings
to sleep in an uncomfortable bed
in a lousy apartment
leased by a total creep.
I ask you, is that fair?
- Well, I suppose not,
but I don't...
- Tell you what.
I'll go to the bank tomorrow
if it'll make you feel any better.
In the meantime, how about that 10 bucks?
- That's fifty dollars.
- Look on the bright side, Georgie.
You won't have to cook
for me for five days.
- Is there anything else
you'll be needing, Vince?
- Georgie believe me, if I do,
you'll be the first to know.
(winding clock)
(door opens)
Pleasant dreams, Georgie.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
Good morning, Wells.
What are you doing up so early?
I'm late?
Late!
(dramatic music)
(water dripping)
I can't vouch for you, Vince,
but I was not raised in a barn.
Rule number two, do not,
I repeat, do not use my toiletries.
If you do, you're a dead man, understand?
Without order, there is chaos.
What's that?
You say something, Vince?
I didn't think you did.
(suspenseful music)
(door closes)
(girl laughing)
- How's the view from down there, Georgie?
- View?
Vince, I wasn't looking.
- Sure, and the check is in
the mail and I love you...
- Do you have the rent check?
- I promise to pay the rent on time.
Georgie, I promised you I'd go
to the bank today, didn't I?
It's not the first time
I've broken my promise.
- You don't have it?
- No.
- You know Vince, without
order there is chaos.
(slams door)
- Georgie, are you trying to insinuate
that I'm taking advantage of you?
Gosh, next thing you know,
you'll be giving me a
list of rules to live by.
I suppose this attitude
you're flexing here,
stems from this morning's events.
I suppose you think I left
that mess for you to clean.
Right?
What do you think, that
I was raised in a barn?
Well, I saw what you did to
the kitchen and the bathroom,
cleaning it up for me,
thinking I would be so inconsiderate
to not clean up my own mess.
Well it just so happens that I
was at the bank this morning.
When I remembered how
I'd left the room a mess.
So I got out of my place,
in the front of the line,
and walked all the way
home just to clean it up.
Well imagine my shock and surprise,
when I found out that you
had already done it for me.
Trying in essence to show me up.
- I wasn't trying to show you up.
- Georgie, I think you owe me an apology.
- All right Vince, I'm sorry.
- Jesus Georgie, don't apologize.
It's too late for that.
And I'll tell you what.
You want your rent so badly?
I'll just go and get it for you.
Oh yeah, I know a place that's open.
I guess I'll just have
to be rude to my guest
and leave her here alone with you.
- Oh Vince really, it
can wait till tomorrow.
- Car keys.
- What?
- Well, I can't very
well walk the 20 miles,
now can I, Georgie?
I'd be gone all night.
Car keys.
I just hope you're satisfied.
(knocking on door)
- Come in.
- Hi, I'm Georgie.
You have lovely toes.
- Thanks.
- I'm an expert on toes.
You might say toes are my life.
- My ex-boyfriend gave it to me.
It's a symbol of his
love and kind devotion.
- It's sweet.
What does it say?
- Satan's slut.
I think he was a little
wasted when he picked it.
- Well, it's the thought that counts.
- All done.
How do they look?
Like the color?
- Yes, yes.
- Don't worry, Georgie.
It won't bite.
Oh, I thought you said
toes were your life.
- Yes, dead ones.
- Hey you little weirdo. (laughs)
(men shouting)
- Hey buddy, lock yourself out?
- My car.
What did you do to it?
- What are you getting
so upset about Georgie?
I went out to get your rent last night,
and on the way home, I don't know,
I must've taken a wrong turn and bam.
Ended up in a homecoming parade.
Hey, a simple mistake.
It could happen to anybody.
- But it's my car, Vince.
- Georgie, you're right.
So I guess this belongs to you.
Congratulations, Georgie.
First place for the best decorated car.
Ho, and if that weren't enough,
I got the rent money too.
Just like I promised.
- What am I supposed to do with these?
- Oh, now I suppose
you're going to tell me
you wanted cash.
You know Georgie, you are
one hard-to-please guy.
Besides I was late, I was in a hurry.
(dramatic music)
(brakes screech)
- What does he want from me?
All I want is a little peace.
What do I have to do
to get a little peace?
- [Reporter] Last night, a
bizarre robbery took place
downtown when a lone unidentified burglar
broke into a video arcade,
getting away with hundreds
of dollars in quarters.
After police gave chase
and shots were fired,
the suspect eluded police
by ducking in a lengthy parade route.
Police are still searching for the car.
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
- Nice car friend.
You know how to read?
You know what this says?
- S-A-M?
- Beautiful, what's this read?
- S-A-M sucks.
- Next time you're
gonna decorate your car,
you should call us.
We'd love to help.
(banging on car)
(glass breaks)
- Little shit!
(window breaks)
(frat boys shouting)
- Cornell, snap to it.
I need a tag right away for this one.
Cops are on their way
down right now, Kafka.
- Well, we're all out of room I'm afraid.
- Nonsense, Georgie.
This is the revolving
door of life and death.
Someone's always coming in.
Someone's always going out.
So we are here for pickup as well.
- Who?
- Number 15, Brewster
The magician's assistant.
Poof, you're dead.
Hurry up with that tag,
they'll be here any minute.
(suspenseful music)
- What do we got here?
- Murder victim, decapitation.
- I haven't seen one of
those in a long time.
- Sorry about the wait.
- No hurry.
- She's not going anywhere. (laughs)
Nice clean cut.
- [Assistant] Yeah, it's
a good follow-through.
- [Detective] She got a name?
- Satan's slut!
- You sure that's not just
some sort of stage name?
- Excuse me.
- What's that kid's name?
(tires screech)
(suspenseful music)
(hatchet bangs)
(dog barking)
(kicks can)
(suspenseful music)
(garbage truck approaches)
(Georgie yelling)
- Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, I, I know this must look bad for me,
but it's not me.
You got to believe me, it's not me.
It's my roommate.
He's been driving me crazy.
- You look like shit.
You've either got the worst
table manners in the world
or you're too stupid to clean
up after you cut up a body.
- Cut up, me?
I had nothing to do with it.
I'll prove it to you.
- Hey, what do you think you're doing?
- I'm going to show you her ass.
- You little pervert.
- She has a tattoo there.
- How do you know?
- She showed it to me.
- She showed it to you?
- Was that before or after
you killed her, Georgie?
- What?
- Get him.
(playful music)
- I got him.
I got him, I got him.
(assistant screams)
(playful music)
- You're fired!
- I would like to purchase a
very powerful handgun, please.
- How much you got to spend?
- What will this buy me?
- For the price you're paying,
that's the best home
defense weapon money'll buy.
- Bullets, I need bullets.
- Well, we have several types.
Wad cutters, dumb dumbs.
It would help if I knew
what you were shooting at.
- My roommate.
I want to blow his head off.
- In that case, I recommend hollow points.
They're the best for close range targets.
Sign here.
That'll be 48 hours before
you can have the weapon.
State regulation.
- I don't have 48 hours.
- Hey!
(brakes screech)
- What's up, Georgie?
(dramatic music)
Hey wow, man.
Rent's not due for another three weeks.
- Well, I'm speeding
up your 30-day notice.
- Can we discuss this?
- Out of my apartment, out of my life.
- Hey, take a coffee break pal, will ya?
Uh listen, there's
something you ought to know.
- No, this is my apartment.
I make the rules, I make the decisions.
Without order, there is chaos.
I'm ordering you to disappear.
- Hold it, punk.
(gun fires)
(monitor beeping)
- How is he?
- He'll recover.
He's a lucky boy, very lucky boy.
(George gasps)
- Boy oh boy, Georgie.
You've really done it this time.
And if things weren't bad enough,
we lost the lease on our apartment.
You know Georgie, I
can't help but feel that,
that I'm to blame for your misfortunes.
So I've decided that the only
proper thing to really do
is for me to spend all my
free time here with you.
By your side.
(George grunting)
(alarm beeping)
(dramatic music)
Goodbye Georgie.
- He's recovering just fine.
He'll be up and around in no time at all.
His heart stopped.
Looks like a massive coronary.
(mother gasps)
I've never seen anything like this before.
- You were with him till the end?
- Yes.
- Did he say anything?
He wanted me to tell you
that he loved you very much.
And above all else, he wanted to make sure
that I got my security deposit back.
(dramatic music)
(George shouting)
- No, no, no.
He'll be all right.
All right, George.
We certainly didn't make
much progress today, did we?
- I was so angry.
I didn't know how else to respond.
- Yeah.
Well, we'll see you next Friday, George,
at your regular time.
- Okay.
- No, no, no.
That's not what we do.
Look, let me give you someone
that can tell you more about it.
Dr. Dempsey, could you
speak to Mr. Isaacs?
He's seen the report on "60 Minutes"
and wants to cancel his appointment.
- Damn it.
Hello, Mr. Isaacs.
This is Dr. Dempsey.
What can I do for you?
No, that's not accurate.
No, she did not have her brain fried.
No, no damage at all.
You know we're suing for that.
Yes, yes, I am aware of
the cats in the microwave.
But just be rest assured.
Our equipment is very safe.
You will not explode.
No, that's not true.
We have very few deaths here.
Well, that was several months ago
and those kids were just college students.
We adjusted the emissions
and we gave him a very nice memorial fund
for their whole family.
Let me put you on hold for a second.
I'll transfer you to the other phone.
He hung up.
(phone beeps)
- [Receptionist] Shall I
send in your 11 o'clock?
- Send him in.
Shall we begin?
- Well, actually Dr. Langdon,
I have to tell you,
I'm a little concerned.
- About what?
- Well sir, you did say
the procedure was new
and I did just hear
the last guy screaming.
- Steve, I'm a professional
and I'm here to help you.
Do you really think I'd put you in danger?
- No, I mean, yes.
I hope not.
- Why don't you have a seat?
(static charges)
(Hawaiian music)
(flash explodes)
- Hello?
- Forest.
- Marshall, can you
tell me what's going on?
- You're having a near death experience.
- You mean I'm dead?
- Yes.
- What did I do?
- You don't remember?
- I remember olives.
(jazz music)
- Hey, here's one for you.
What's going on with those shots of me
and my skydiving set?
- I still have a few more to print.
- You gonna come up with me sometime?
- What if you're up there
and the thing doesn't open?
- The chute?
- Yeah.
- You can forget about it.
- Yeah thanks, I think I will.
- Oh come on, Steven, that's half the fun.
- What, half the fun is dying?
Since when is dying half the fun?
- Marshall.
- [Marshall] How you doing, Fred?
This is Steven Forest.
- Marshall tells me good things.
- He does?
- Fred's the editor of
California Magazine.
I showed him some of your stuff.
- Steve, I thought it was tremendous.
Really.
Flight leaves Tuesday morning.
You'll get in say nine-ish.
We'll get to work by eleven.
We'll have you back the next day.
- Wait, back from where?
- A photo shoot for the magazine.
- Call my office, we'll
give you the rundown.
I got to see some people.
I just wanted to meet you.
It was a pleasure.
You guys go crazy.
Dinner's on me.
Hey Dave!
- You should have been
doing this a long time ago.
Get the hell on that passport once.
Okay, that's the one.
Ask her to dance.
- Oh no.
- Oh come on Steve, this is your night.
You're on a roll, celebrate.
- I don't.
- Why, why not?
- I don't dance.
- Jesus, Forest.
You don't dance, you don't
jump out of airplanes.
- I don't know.
(Marshall choking)
(banging on table)
- It was awful, wasn't it?
I think it affected you worse than me.
- He looked so young.
God, I hate these things.
Don't you hate these things?
- Yeah.
I hate these things.
- So what are you telling me?
He died, choking on an olive?
- It's just like that guy.
Did you hear about that guy?
- What guy?
- He was having lunch with his wife.
It was a tuna salad sandwich.
An hour later, he's dead.
- What the hell are you
talking about, he's dead?
- Bad tuna.
Same thing with chicken.
Salmonella, people die.
- You heard about this guy.
He was killed walking by
the Empire State Building.
Somebody dropped a penny.
- Oh, come on.
- No, he's right, they got a law now.
- I'm Paula.
- Steven Forest.
- Oh, wow.
You're his friend from high school.
The photographer guy, huh?
Did you do this one?
- Yeah.
- It's really good.
- Steve-O.
I'm sorry.
I know you guys were tight.
Listen, about Tuesday.
My guy will pick you up about eight.
- Tuesday?
- The shoot.
- Oh right, right.
- Great.
- Did you tell him?
- You got to tell him that story.
- Some guy in Georgia, what?
- Yeah, you didn't hear about this?
In Atlanta?
This guy's walking down
the street one day.
He exploded.
Nothing left but his shoes.
Apparently this happens.
- I've got to go.
- Are you okay?
(phone beeps)
- Yo, right.
June-ish.
(police radio blares)
(siren wails)
- Was it a heart attack?
- Steven, what are you afraid of?
- This morning, I was taking a shower
and suddenly I start thinking,
what if I slip and fall and
smash my nose into the tile?
Cartilege gets jammed up into my brain.
- God!
- A week ago, my bathroom
was just a bathroom.
Now it's a gauntlet.
Last night, I moved my alarm
clock away from the bed
because I read in the Times,
it gives out magnetic
fields that cause cancer.
- I saw that too.
- This morning, it didn't even wake me up.
I didn't even hear it.
What is that?
- It's a macadamia nut.
- How did you know, Marshall?
- I met him at Sky High.
- You jump out of airplanes?
- No, God no.
I was there for two weeks
helping set up their computers.
That's what I do.
I took one of those courses you see on TV
at three in the morning.
- Computers, computers.
Aren't you afraid of
repetitive motion sickness?
- With me it's birds.
- What?
- I'm afraid they're
gonna peck my eyes out.
Like in that movie.
Did you ever have that?
- No, but I think I
know what you're saying,
like pecking into your eyeballs,
so there's blood coming down.
- Nasty.
It's nuts.
- It's ridiculous.
- We're completely stupid.
- I know.
(romantic music)
I feel like he's watching us.
- Apparently, there are these cases
where people get phone calls
in the middle of the night
from an old friend or something
and they talk a little while,
and the friend warns them
about something horrible
that's gonna happen.
And then later it turns out
the old friend was killed or something,
before the phone call.
- Why are you telling me this?
- Isn't it scary?
Dead people on the telephone.
- No, I mean don't tell me this.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Still here.
- You cheered me up.
- Me too.
Good luck on your photo thing.
- Oh, thanks.
- Do you have a business
card or something?
- Sure.
- Just in case.
Maybe we could.
- Definitely.
- All right then.
- Drive carefully.
- Bye.
(phone rings)
(suspenseful music)
- Marshall?
(dial tone)
- Was that you?
- Was what me?
- Nothing.
I thought maybe you
were trying to warn me.
- About what?
- A trip.
Oh, that's it, isn't it?
Something happened on the trip.
This never would've happened
if you hadn't interfered.
- Oh, now it's my fault.
- You were always pushing me.
(flash explodes)
- [Model] How do I look?
- [Steven] Great, where are you off to?
- Spain.
- [Steven] Oh, that's great.
- Yeah, you been there?
- [Steven] No, never been to Spain.
Can you look at my finger?
- Okay.
- [Steven] So where are you off to?
- London.
- [Steven] Oh, you'll have a great time.
- Really, you've been there?
- [Steven] No, never been to London.
Can you look at my finger?
- Oh, wait, wait.
Is my hair good?
- [Steven] So where are you off to?
- Italy.
Great grandmother's going to be 90.
- [Steven] Oh, flying?
- Oh yeah.
You ever worry about it, to fly?
- Well you know it's like they say,
you have a better chance of
dying in your own bathroom
or your car.
Planes are very safe.
Safest way to travel.
I'm sure every now and
again, something happens.
(jet engine falling)
(flash explodes)
(male model screams)
- [Fred] Steve-O, this is Fred.
Driver will be there to
pick you up around 7:30.
That's me, gotta go.
- [Mom] Hi Steve, it's Mom.
Dad and I were calling to
see how the funeral was.
Love you.
- [Paula] Hi Steven, it's Paula.
I was just calling to see if you wanted to
maybe go get a drink or something
before you leave on your trip for luck.
(piano plays)
- You okay?
(crowd applauds)
(siren wails)
- [Radio DJ] Most insurance plans.
Call toll free 1-800-888-NEED.
That's 1-800-888-5633.
KBN in the Sin Barney
timeline, good morning to you.
Up with me this hour
as part of Earthquake Preparedness Week,
we've got professor Mark Campmann
from the University of Arkansas.
- [Mark] Hi, how are you?
- [Radio DJ] Professor Campmann predicts
that the LA area will be hit
with a 9.5 magnitude earthquake
this Tuesday.
- [Mark] That's correct.
- [Radio DJ] Professor,
what exactly can we expect
from a tremor of that size?
- [Mark] Total devastation.
- [Radio DJ] And we'll be right back.
- [Commercial] And when you
don't get enough exercise...
(doorbell buzzes)
- Am I too early?
So where are you off to?
- San Francisco.
- [Driver] I guess
you're getting out of LA
at just the right time.
- What do you mean?
- [Driver] Well you know,
all this earthquake business.
But I guess there's no ban on
earthquakes in Frisco either.
- No, I guess not.
- [Driver] Well, what are you gonna do?
You know, apparently it's not the shaking
that's the problem.
It's the stuff that falls on you.
That's the killer.
Massive spillage, head trauma.
(explosion)
- What's that?
- [Driver] That and the fire, gas lines.
Stuff burns.
- What is that?
(classical dirge plays)
Stop!
(tires screech)
- [Driver] What the hell are you doing?
- I don't understand.
- That was the driver.
Forest didn't get off the plane.
- What?
- It wasn't the trip, you didn't even go.
(doorbell rings)
- The earthquake.
You remember you had
that hat with the light?
- What happened?
- It was like a mining hat.
- The one with the light.
- Yeah.
- What about it?
- I need it.
- You need my mining hat?
- [Mom] Who is it, Lou?
- It's Steven, he wants my mining hat.
- Hi Ma.
- You're digging a hole or something?
You look terrible.
- Hi honey, how was the funeral?
- It was great.
- Your father and I are
baking some pancakes.
- No, thanks Ma.
I don't think we'll have time.
- Oh, Steven, you really
should call your Auntie Carla.
She's about to have that ear operation.
Call her, while she can still hear you.
- Okay Ma.
- You want to tell me what's going on?
- What?
- I don't know.
- Look, this guy on the radio mentioned
there might be an earthquake.
- And you want my hat just in case?
- Just want to be prepared.
You guys should too.
Maybe you want to keep the hat.
- No, no.
What if it hits while
you're in the shower.
Are you gonna wear the hat in the shower?
- I don't know, no.
- Maybe you're just gonna
stop taking showers?
- What are you saying?
- I'm not saying anything.
I'm just wondering if you're
gonna stop taking showers.
- Of course not.
That's ridiculous.
- Yeah, it is.
(phone rings)
- [Mom] I got it.
(dramatic music)
- Dad, I got a job, a photoshoot.
- That's great.
- I know it's great, it's really great.
But I couldn't get on the airplane.
Why am I doing this?
- I'm just not sure you know
what you're reacting to.
When you get to be my age,
you begin to realize that
death is just another part of life.
You're not happy about
it, but you accept it.
You take your Auntie Carla for instance.
She's getting on, she
could go at any minute.
But she's had a full life
and when the time comes,
I'll be ready for it.
I'll accept it and I'll
keep right on living.
Everything's going to be okay.
- Really?
- That was Leah.
- [Dad] Yeah?
- Auntie Carla died.
- What?
- She didn't make it
through the ear operation.
- Oh my God!
Oh my God, oh my God.
(Dad shouting)
(suspenseful music)
- Why can't I remember?
- [Marshall] Maybe you
never saw it coming,
- But I was being so careful.
- Hi there, cookie.
- Auntie Carla?
- How are you, sweetheart?
- I wish I knew.
How are you?
- I'm dead.
- Oh yeah I heard.
Dad was real upset.
- I know, I'm going to give him a call.
(dial tone)
(busy signal sounds)
- [Man] Who is this?
- [Radio Voice] Here
is the latest forecast
for Los Angeles and vicinity.
The synapses have brought a level trop
over California today,
with a strong Western wind...
(knocking on door)
Over Southern California.
This trop will move east of
the Southern California...
(mug shaking)
- Paula, cover your head.
- Why?
Hi!
- Come on, come on.
- What?
- Under the table.
- What's the matter?
- Earthquake.
(helicopter flying)
- That's a helicopter.
- Oh, but there's gonna be an earthquake.
- Oh my God.
- I know.
- No, your forehead's bleeding.
- Oh I guess I, a lot.
- Oh let me see.
What have you been doing?
- Nothing.
Did you go out with her?
- [Marshall] A couple times.
- Did you kiss her?
(clock ticking)
- Do you like Fred Astaire?
- What?
- They're having a thing with Fred Astaire
at the county museum.
I got two tickets.
Do you like Fred Astaire?
- Fred Astaire, not really.
I mean he's okay.
The dancing.
- Yeah, that's what I like, the dancing.
So do you want to go?
- Yes.
Where are you going?
- I thought we're going to the movie.
- What now?
- You don't want to go?
- No, I do.
It's just the earthquake.
(siren wails)
- Are you kidding?
Steven, that's ridiculous.
You're being ridiculous.
- [Steven] I just want to wait
until it's a little safer.
(police radio blares)
(monitor beeps)
- Paula!
Paula!
Paula.
(car starts)
(Hawaiian music plays)
(tires screeching)
Damn, I knew the minute
I did something stupid,
this was going to happen.
- All you did was cross the street.
What are you gonna do,
spend your entire life
stuck on one city block?
- I didn't have to run like an idiot
into moving traffic.
I should have crossed when it was safe.
- Steven, when is it ever safe?
- So you admit it, I was right.
It's never safe.
- Nothing is ever safe,
so what's your point?
Hey, Marshall.
- Fred, what are you doing here?
- Some schmuck dropped a
light on my head at the shoot.
And what the hell are you doing here?
You're supposed to be up in San Francisco.
- I couldn't get up the
nerve to get on the plane.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
Right.
Sorry guys, gotta go.
Looks like I'm going to pull through.
Just a concussion.
Hey Steve-o, if you
live, will you call me?
- Really?
- Hey, Phil.
(Marshall choking)
- Would you stop that?
What are you crazy,
those things killed you.
- [Medic] I think we're getting something.
- What's your point?
- [Medic] Getting a pulse.
- If you hadn't eaten that
olive, you'd still be alive.
- [Medic] Breathe!
- Yeah, but Steven, I love olives.
(Hawaiian music)
(flash explodes)
- [Medic] We got him.
- Jesus.
That's incredible.
- Perhaps you should come back next week.
- Sorry, I think I
understand everything now.
I don't think I have a problem anymore.
(door closes)
- Dr. Langdon.
- Thank you.
- Hello Brandon.
(machine beeps)
(intercom buzzes)
- [Receptionist] Mrs. Dalton is here.
Mrs. Dalton is here.
(static discharges)
It's her usual time.
Mrs. Dalton is here.
I'm sending her in now.
Mrs. Dalton, Mrs. Dalton, Mrs. Dalton.
(electronic music)
No one likes to be frozen
It's not safe to go outside
Take a good look at the mess you're in
Don't it make you wanna cry
Everybody reaching for something
The thing they never had
Can't you feel this is frozen
Try to make one sad
Open your eyes
The power's in mine
Future shock
What's hazy is not for them
Do what you got
Future shock
Love is really that important
But that ain't all we need
Work a little harder for what you want
Maybe one day you'll succeed
There's no need to be treated
There's more than enough to go around
Just remember the meaning
If the spirit knocks you down
Open your eyes
The power's in mine
Future shock
What's hazy is not
Gotta do what you got
Future shock