- Look, do whatever you have to do to find it.
When you do, give me a call.
All right, later.
Look, as I was saying, I don't give a fuck.
Understand?
I don't give a fuck.
You wanted in, now you got.
Now you got a job to do just like everybody else.
Now handle your shit
or get handled.
(soft reflective music)
(upbeat hip hop music)
♪ And one ♪
♪ Welcome to the streets ♪
♪ Of Iladelph ♪
♪ All you got is yourself ♪
♪ And nothing else in the streets of Iladelph ♪
♪ So if you got a brain ♪
♪ Use it ♪
♪ Don't abuse it ♪
♪ Welcome to the streets of Iladelph ♪
♪ All you got is yourself ♪
♪ And nothing else ♪
♪ In the streets of Iladelph ♪
♪ If you got a brain ♪
♪ Use it ♪
♪ Don't abuse it ♪
♪ Check this right ♪
♪ I and my soul unfold ♪
♪ To uphold in Iladelph ♪
♪ The city of brothers love ♪
♪ Took over self ♪
♪ So remember top shelf ♪
♪ And nothing else ♪
♪ No appetite or taste whatsoever ♪
♪ For any type of wealth ♪
♪ No energy no time ♪
♪ To grit and grind ♪
♪ Confined behind enemy lines ♪
♪ Trying to get mine ♪
♪ Seeing through darkness ♪
♪ Tripping every step I take ♪
♪ Never wasting a day ♪
♪ No learning from my mistakes ♪
♪ At times ache from stab wounds ♪
♪ From simply dipping and dapping ♪
♪ No longer am I listening ♪
♪ Put my heart out there ♪
♪ There my heart was took ♪
♪ Shake shuffle and shook ♪
♪ Give in a bloody hook ♪
♪ Like me in the heat of passion ♪
♪ Thoughtless is for prepared ♪
♪ For my be ashing ♪
♪ contraction ♪
♪ Our heart souls ♪
♪ Bodys and even minds ♪
♪ What's to stop at Judah ♪
♪ Must continue to blood ♪
♪ Welcome to the streets of Illadelph ♪
♪ All you got yourself ♪
♪ And nothing else ♪
♪ In the streets of Illadelph ♪
♪ So if you got a brain ♪
♪ Use it ♪
♪ Don't abuse it ♪
♪ Welcome to the streets of Illadelph ♪
♪ All you got is yourself ♪
♪ And nothing ese ♪
♪ In the streets of Illadelph ♪
♪ So if you got a brain ♪
♪ Use it ♪
♪ Don't abuse it ♪
♪ Word ♪
♪ Welcome to the streets of Illadelph ♪
♪ All you got is yourself ♪
♪ And nothing else ♪
♪ In the streets of Illadelph ♪
♪ So if you got a brain ♪
♪ Use it ♪
♪ Don't abuse it ♪
♪ What what ♪
♪ Welcome to streets of Illadelph ♪
♪ All you got is yourself ♪
♪ and nothing else ♪
♪ In the streets of Illadelph ♪
♪ So if you got a brain ♪
♪ Use it ♪
♪ don't abuse it ♪
♪ What what ♪
♪ Word ♪
♪ Keep your eyes open ♪
♪ Walk lightly ♪
♪ Look both ways ♪
- [Ninea Voiceover] It's not easy running things alone.
A black woman in the 90s.
Young, smart.
Thugs always trying to get next to you.
They wanna ask me out.
(soft tense music)
I need protection everywhere I go.
There's always someone with me,
watching me, guarding me.
I grew up in southwest Philly.
When I was 17, my boyfriend took me to my first drug buy.
He gave me the gun,
said they wouldn't frisk me.
So, we sitting down, he checking out the shit.
All of a sudden, this fool come rushing out the hall,
trying to jam us up.
(gunshot)
That turned out to be my first homicide.
I remember how I felt then,
hysterical, crying and screaming
as he dragged me out the spot.
I miss that feeling.
I wish I could go back.
Back to when I was soft and innocent.
We came up after that.
But eventually the cops caught him.
He left his fingerprints on the table.
I served one year for the drugs they found
when they served the warrant.
He pleaded guilty to homicide for me.
Said he felt responsible.
I really think he loved me.
He served nine months of a eight sentence in Rockview.
He was killed there a short time after.
When I got out, I went to the house we used
to live in to get our stash.
It was right where we left it.
It wasn't much, but it was enough
to get me on my feet, though.
For one year in prison, I barely talked
but I listened to everything that was said.
Every story that was told.
By the time I got out,
I was ready for the street.
I knew what I wanted to do
and I knew how to do it.
I did whatever it took to build a nice lay.
I even killed for it.
(gunshot)
Now, don't get it twisted, I'm far from rich
and I used to know how to make myself happy.
If I learned one thing in this business,
it's once you get on top. (phone ringing)
The fight to stay up there
is just as difficult as what you did
to get there in the first place.
- Yo.
(soft hip hop music)
(reggae rapping)
♪ It's time to get paid ♪
♪ Confiscating bread y'all ♪
♪ Yo here's the plot the plan ♪
♪ The blueprints in my hand ♪
♪ Say we take the west ♪
♪ Through the vent ♪
♪ One attempt ♪
♪ We in the trunk ♪
♪ Select you ♪
♪ He grab the set ♪
♪ Pull yes in the yeyo ♪
♪ 'cause shots when I say so ♪
♪ First car in sight ♪
♪ Make 'em strip ♪
♪ Till his dick hanging ♪
♪ Cut his throat ♪
♪ Till his tongue swing ♪
- Wake that pussy up.
- What the fuck, man?
Oh damn.
Fuck, man.
Who the fuck are you?
Oh shit.
(tense music)
Oh!
Damn.
Now what the fuck did I do now?
- Don't play stupid with me, motherfucker.
You know how many people I got working in your area?
Huh? - Five.
I count five.
- What you didn't think I'd find out
about you jamming up one of my workers?
- Ninea, it's just a little misunderstanding.
I aint know he work for you.
- You know what, Sammy?
This is one mistake you're not gonna walk away from.
(tense music)
- [Sammy] Look.
Come on now, we can work this out.
- Fuck that.
You had your chance.
- [Sammy] Come on now.
We can straighten this out.
- Uh uh.
- [Sammy] We can straighten this out.
Come on now, I'll stay out of the way with it.
- Oh you gonna stay out of it, all right.
- Come on, Ninea.
We can work this out.
Just like I said, I'll stay out of your neighborhood.
- [Ninea] Spare me the human emotions, nigga.
You asked for this shit.
- You know what?
I know how the fuck you are.
So you know what, fuck you.
I don't give a fuck.
I'ma die anyway 'cause I know how stupid your ass is
and I know how your mind is
'cause you know just as crazy as I am
'cause if I get out of this shit,
I will fucking kill you.
So you better kill me now
before I do it the fuck to you.
- All right. - So kill me.
Do it.
(gunshot)
(tense music)
(bell tolling)
- Yo.
Who Dion meeting here, man?
It's hotter than shit out here.
- Some simple minded motherfucker named Durango.
- Durango?
Oh shit, I know this motherfucker.
Oh my fucking God.
- Oh now I know what to do
to make you sweat like a bitch.
- Man fuck you, nigga.
Look, he aint get the name Quiet Coup for nothing.
Man he earned that shit.
Straight the fuck up.
- Yeah, you right.
Should of held this meeting in a more public place,
you know what I'm saying?
- Why, you think some gunplay gonna jump off?
- I don't really care about that.
But just in case,
it will be nice to have some innocent bystanders
to hide behind, you know what I'm saying?
- [Man] Oh yeah, yeah.
You know what's up.
- Yo, Razor.
(tense hip hop)
♪ Fucking with them north side crews ♪
♪ You lose ♪
♪ Fucking with them west side crews ♪
♪ Fucking with them southwest crews ♪
♪ You lose ♪
♪ Fucking with them south side crews ♪
♪ you lose ♪
♪ Fucking with them north side crews ♪
♪ You lose ♪
♪ Fucking with them west side crews ♪
♪ Fucking with them southwest crews ♪
♪ You lose ♪
♪ Fucking with them south side crews ♪
♪ Yo hey yo ♪
♪ Philly filled with criminal cats ♪
♪ That slang crack and pack gats ♪
♪ With the clap rat ♪
♪ For fat stacks ♪
♪ Pass rap ♪
♪ Niggas lets put the blow back ♪
♪ With the black mack ♪
You must of lost your fucking mind.
Buying for Ninea.
That fucking cheap bitch trying to move in my shit
and you fucking helping her.
Durango, I know you hear me, man.
Yo!
(glass shattering)
(tense hip hop)
- Yo, Dion.
Don't take this personal.
Ninea offered me a better deal.
Saves me a fortune.
So fuck you.
(tense hip hop)
- Fuck!
I'm gonna have to do something about this.
♪ When you roll singular ♪
♪ Dead on impact ♪
♪ I wouldn't wanna be ya ♪
♪ Your girl complains she don't see ya ♪
♪ 'Cause now missing ♪
♪ If I don't trust you ♪
♪ Then my hollow ♪
- Motherfucker.
Shit.
You won't fuck up again, motherfucker.
(phone ringing)
Shit.
Fucking meat.
(phone ringing)
Yeah, who is this?
- [Joyce] Jimmy.
It's Joyce, Ninea's girl.
- Hey, what's up, Joyce?
- Yo, Ninea said she was gonna beat me.
What the hell are you doing?
- Yeah well what do you think I'm doing?
I'm working.
- I'm a little nervous about tomorrow night.
I think we should get together first.
- [Man] Uh huh.
- But I think I'm finally ready now.
- Yeah, well that's good.
That's good.
It's about time. - This is important.
You need to make time for this.
- Uh huh.
All right, all right.
I tell you what.
Look, I got, look I tell you what.
I'll meet you at Nifty Fifty's at four o'clock.
- Nifty Fifty's. - Uh huh.
- Four o'clock in the afternoon.
- Right and yeah, milkshake on me.
- I'll tell Ninea you said what's up.
- Yeah, give Ninea my best.
- [Joyce] All right.
- Yeah, later.
I'm gonna have to get a fucking sharper knife.
All right, here we go again.
Come on, motherfucker.
(tense hip hop)
♪ All stoned in blood ♪
♪ Can't ♪
♪ The order of my doom ♪
♪ Round out the 12 ♪
♪ Judah bring 'em hell ♪
♪ Fire brimstone ♪
♪ Shank your nervous ♪
♪ With the megahertz ♪
♪ At the sinner great they tempt ♪
♪ It's life worth ♪
♪ The empty on my plenty ♪
♪ My only sin on them ♪
♪ Is I'm bringing many ♪
♪ They never heard I'm one third in the closet ♪
♪ Coming for me ♪
♪ God only vice ♪
♪ Surprise ♪
♪ Don't catch her off guard ♪
- You get it?
What's up?
Who dented up the E Class?
- I did.
I was leaving the city
and some old bitty caught me from the tail end.
- What you do about it?
- [Woman] I didn't do anything.
I was dirty.
- Yeah, well get that fixed, man.
Looks like shit.
- Ninea, I hate to bug you
but did you figure out what you gonna do
abut that court case, yet?
- Yeah, I tried to have Penn paid off
but Dion got to him first.
So I'm just gonna take the money
I was gonna get out of him,
tell one of the girls to take care of him.
- Oh, okay.
Well who you gonna give the work to?
- Joyce.
- Joyce?
She's never been on her own before.
- Yeah, I know.
This her chance to earn her stripes.
- I don't think she can do it.
I don't think she's ready.
- Man, stop fucking defending her.
Penn's a piece of shit
and I want him stuck before the sun come up
or I'ma kill both of 'em.
- Well.
You're the boss.
♪ Yeah wish y'all remove my habit ♪
♪ I was tragic ♪
♪ For he saw he saw ♪
♪ Creeping in the midst ♪
♪ With the competence ♪
♪ And high risk ♪
♪ And Satan's pissed off ♪
♪ Despise my cloth ♪
♪ Slashed by the wrath ♪
♪ As he burns in ♪
(soft reflective music)
- Ninea.
I got you something when I was in the city.
- Just like my baby.
(storm raging)
- I'm gonna turn in.
You want something before I go?
- Yeah.
Call the escort service.
I feel like some entertainment tonight.
- Okay.
Oh, do you want anybody in particular?
- Yeah, see if Derek's in.
He's six four.
What?
- You are so fucking crazy.
- [Ninea] I'm so fucking horny.
(storm raging)
- Here, take these.
That's for the fingerprints and the powder burns.
You need the gloves.
They're pretty colorful, too, huh?
Yeah, just remember what Ninea told you.
All right, everything will be aight.
I'm here to back you up.
- All right.
- You know what I'm saying?
I know this is your first one.
You aint gonna have no problems.
- All right.
(tense hip hop)
- [Ninea Voiceover] Now, when everything is cool,
he's gonna give you the signal.
(tense hip hop)
Now, when you knock on the door, back up.
'Cause when you blast his ass,
blood is gonna spray
and you don't want it.
And make you sure you tell him it's from me.
- What's up?
What the fuck you want?
I know you aint for me.
- I don't want shit.
- What the fuck you knock on my door for?
- I knocked for Ninea.
Ninea wants you dead.
(gunshot)
- [Ninea Voiceover] When you blast his ass,
make sure he's dead.
You go up in the crib and put two in his back.
(tense hip hop)
(man groaning)
He's a slimy bitch.
So if he lives, I don't want him walking or talking.
(tense hip hop)
(gunshots in distance)
Now remember, when you leave, walk.
Don't run.
And when you pull off,
tell Jimmy don't be screeching.
Pull of casually.
(tires screeching)
Call me when the jobs done.
(knocking at door)
(soft music)
- Why me, woman?
You got Mustang, Star, Diamond,
all them other fellas.
And Ninea, whatever your name is, woman,
just pay me my money, me be out of here, all right?
I want no kinky stuff.
I want none of that kinky thing, all right?
So we just do that and be out of here.
No problems.
See?
Cool.
♪ Hey it gotta be the money ♪
♪ Pussy and rapping ♪
♪ That keep me going ♪
♪ Before I do ♪
♪ Trying to see millions ♪
Bitch!
- [Ninea] Say it again.
- [Derek] Fuck bitch.
Say it again. (phone ringing)
- [Derek] Bitch!
♪ Screaming RTX till I die ♪
♪ we stuck up a club ♪
♪ Survive then blow up a five ♪
♪ We the killer kind ♪
- [Voicemail] Ninea, this is Joyce.
I just granted you a continuous on your court case.
I guess I'll catch up with you later, peace.
♪ Rock it down ♪
♪ Take a stripper lock it down ♪
♪ This around when niggas hit the crown ♪
♪ Niggas can't fuck with us ♪
(Derek shouting)
♪ They mess they fate ♪
♪ They going out with a bang ♪
- Yeah, I heard about it.
Oh yeah, I'm gonna do something about it.
Me and my boys, we on this one.
No way, she will not get away with this.
That's right.
No problem.
We'll take care of it.
Well look, I gotta go.
My boys are walking up.
All right, I'll get back with you on it.
Later.
- Yo, what up, D?
- Yo.
Check it.
- What's going on, D?
- All right, man.
- Hey, feel.
- How you feeling, buddy?
All right.
Yeah, good.
- Nigga, what the fuck is you doing?
Get the fuck up off my swing.
- Man, you crazy as shit, motherfucker.
Crazy as shit.
- Nasty ass motherfucker.
Shit.
What's going on, D?
- Yo, check this out, read this.
- What the fuck is this?
Last night a man was shot once in the head
and twice in the back as he answered his front door.
So the fuck what?
- Read on.
- I don't read this shit.
Aint a school.
Man has been identified as 24 year old Pat Lewis.
Neighbors say they heard the shots
and ran to the door to find Lewis dead in the hallway
and a car speeding away.
Police say this mafia style hit
was the work of a professional.
Several neighbors reported hearing the shots
but could not shed any light
on who have committed this gruesome crime.
So what?
- That was Penn, asshole.
- Shit.
I aint know that motherfucker real name.
- Get the fuck outta here.
- Nigga, what the fuck is you doing?
Just take the fucking paper.
- Nigga, I wanna see, too.
Fuck you, motherfucker.
- Damn.
Ignorant ass reading over motherfucker's shoulders.
What the fuck he do, piss off the mob or something?
- [Dion] Something like that.
He pissed of Ninea Ranks.
He was gonna testify against her in court.
So she had him killed.
Stupid motherfucker!
I told him to lay low.
Dummy.
Well, you know what this means, don't you?
We definitely gonna have to do something about this shit.
So this is what I want you two to do.
I want you to follow her, keep tabs on her.
Where she spends her money,
who she sleeps with, everything.
I'm getting tired of this shit.
This shit comes to a halt soon as possible.
You understand me?
And that's the way it is.
I'm out.
- That motherfucker tense.
We need to get that motherfucker laid.
Fart or something.
That motherfucker constipated or something.
I don't know what the fuck wrong with him.
Come on with your ignorant ass.
You know you can't read no fucking paper.
- Fuck you, nigga.
Black ass.
(soft upbeat hip hop)
♪ It takes a lot to be down ♪
♪ Can't keep control ♪
♪ You gotta cool yourself ♪
♪ A thousand gats ringing out ♪
♪ 1,000 cats ready to die ♪
♪ 1,000 niggas in the club ♪
♪ I spy smoke lock ♪
♪ Online ♪
♪ Et cetera et cetera ♪
♪ Blast with the nine ♪
♪ Silence that kid ♪
♪ Better use a silencer ♪
♪ Big game know you there ♪
♪ Rank and style ♪
♪ Run them jewels ♪
♪ Aint no reason to cry ♪
♪ I'm just fooling ♪
♪ Cooling off ♪
♪ If I wanted ♪
♪ You'd be knocked off already ♪
♪ I got a job ♪
♪ You ready ♪
♪ You got boss for who you grinding ♪
♪ Take the C4 ♪
♪ And its typical ♪
♪ Laid in with mine ♪
♪ Trying to move in ♪
♪ Any means necessary ♪
♪ This is real now ♪
♪ I bet you aint ready ♪
- What's up?
- What's that shit?
- Oh that.
It's nothing for you to worry about.
- Ninea, I told you a thousand times.
You're not my only client.
Now what you did, it jeopardized my whole career
and I don't like it.
Now don't me wrong, sister,
the money you pay me, it's good
but you cannot afford to buy me a new career.
- [Woman] Hi, Julie.
- Carla, hi.
The 16th, 10 am, my office.
The light cupcakes. - Okay.
- Fucking your shit up was a chance I had to take.
I had to send Dion a message.
Now if you as good as you think you are,
that shouldn't be no thing, right?
- Ninea, we had this case beat.
You can't just go around killing everybody.
The DA, they know who you are
and what you do.
And so do I.
(tense hip hop)
- It's still early.
I'ma give you a minute to check the tone of your voice.
(tense hip hop)
(phone ringing)
Yeah?
What's in it for me?
I don't know, man.
All right, well I really can't talk right now.
I'm with my lawyer.
I'll swing by the crib later, aight?
All right, later.
(tense hip hop)
Look, I knew the case was beat
but I also knew that Dion was behind this whole thing
in the first place.
And like you said, I pay you good
to handle my problems.
I got a problem.
So handle it.
♪ Got the jewel ♪
♪ Got it ♪
(tense hip hop)
♪ We did it ♪
♪ We got it ♪
♪ We made it ♪
- Hey, Julia, why are you still here?
As a bit of advice.
You should chose your clients better.
- Fucking bitch.
(tense hip hop music)
♪ Yo it's a cold world ♪
♪ So get yours ♪
♪ Money you start wars ♪
♪ Roll with four fours ♪
♪ Get knocked down for sure ♪
♪ We catching bodies ♪
♪ We all hunger for pays ♪
♪ If you get shot or knocked ♪
♪ You aint got what it takes ♪
♪ Yo it's a cold world ♪
♪ So get yours ♪
♪ Money to start wars ♪
♪ Roll with four fours ♪
♪ Get knocked down for sure ♪
♪ We catching bodies ♪
♪ We all hunger for pays ♪
♪ If you get shot or knocked ♪
♪ You aint got what it takes ♪
♪ Wide bodies six ♪
♪ Infinity bricks ♪
♪ Guns to spit ♪
♪ Slumlord of crack spots ♪
♪ Watch it flip ♪
♪ To get my cash back ♪
♪ Watch my stash stack to multi mils ♪
♪ Real dogs ♪
♪ They fucking suitcase ♪
♪ Care my bills ♪
- Yo, can't you at least talk to her for me?
- I'll think about.
I'm letting you now right now,
she doesn't have a point man.
She has no use for him.
- But you still gonna talk to her, right?
- I'll think about it.
- Nah, straight biz.
I want you to talk to her for me.
- I said I'll think about it.
- Aight.
Don't forget about all that.
What you doing later on tonight?
- What am I doing tonight?
♪ I'm into the heavy guns ♪
♪ AKs spread through cars ♪
♪ Murdering anyone ♪
♪ Been at you with thugs ♪
♪ That could place hands on any gun ♪
♪ I done seen niggas rise ♪
♪ I done seen 'em fall ♪
♪ From the streets to ♪
- [Ninea Voiceover] T, play nice.
Don't hurt him.
♪ Step in turn forever with me ♪
♪ One by one ♪
♪ Niggas I roll with is getting shifty ♪
♪ Quickly ♪
♪ Double the rock so we can double the stock ♪
♪ Cribs on the outskirts ♪
♪ 'cause we double the knots ♪
♪ Sipping bubble with scotch ♪
♪ While we hustle on blocks ♪
♪ All you faggot niggas thinking that you tough ♪
♪ When you not ♪
♪ Sounding like KISS ♪
♪ Sounding like NAS ♪
♪ Sounding like P ♪
♪ Next thing you know ♪
♪ Niggas gonna sounding like me ♪
♪ That's I keep it real no matter the cost ♪
♪ Shatter you all ♪
♪ I'm hungry ♪
♪ That's why my shit is fatter than y'all ♪
♪ Keep you heated all the time ♪
- Slow down, Deja.
Look, shut the fuck up and hold on, all right?
- Did you see that shit? - Hold on.
- This motherfucker is bad!
And I'm like.
What part of--
- Excuse me.
If I gotta end my conversation
to deal with your ass I'ma blacken your motherfucking eye.
- What?
♪ Start wars ♪
♪ Roll with four fours ♪
♪ Get knocked down for sure ♪
♪ We catching bodies ♪
♪ We all hunger for pays ♪
♪ If you get shot or not ♪
♪ You aint got what it take ♪
♪ This to my thugs and my bitches ♪
♪ Trying to stack Gs regardless ♪
♪ Ready to spark shit ♪
♪ That's with these cartridge ♪
♪ Robbing your guys ♪
♪ We later we splitting ♪
- Fuck it, just kick it in.
♪ On billboards ♪
♪ Niggas I eat what I kill for ♪
♪ I'ma get more ♪
♪ Y'all dudes better get yours ♪
♪ I'ma flip ♪
Not bad.
♪ On Pit bull shit ♪
♪ Them bulls heartless there ♪
There aint nothing in there but clothes and nothing?
- Nothing.
♪ Street lights get dim ♪
♪ After smoking a dub ♪
♪ Back in that shit ♪
♪ Rolled in a dutch ♪
♪ Bottomed with dust ♪
♪ You and your mans end up getting touched ♪
♪ You pack two gats in the Lex ♪
♪ Don't have to take the bus ♪
♪ I roll with big guys ♪
♪ That dedicate their wrists to cuffs ♪
- Seeing as how you just got out of jail,
we're gonna start you off small.
Pick up, deliveries.
Nothing major.
Nothing to get you sent back.
Now your brother, he's a good friend,
I expect that same loyalty out of you.
You fuck with me, you end up in a grave.
It's nothing personal, it's just business.
♪ Clips they fill with hollows ♪
♪ If not the rhinos ♪
♪ Between me and you ♪
♪ Aint no comparison ♪
♪ Cause when it come to beef ♪
♪ I'm a vegetarian ♪
♪ Don't you see this heat I'm carrying ♪
♪ Take key from the deceased ♪
♪ I'm burying ♪
♪ For Cs I'm averaging ♪
♪ I squeeze no matter when ♪
♪ A quarter then ♪
♪ Out number one to ten ♪
♪ My pockets fat ♪
♪ Your pockets thin ♪
♪ Now you tell me you saved us then ♪
♪ When it come to Benjamins ♪
♪ And Jamal man ♪
♪ Rapping over instruments ♪
♪ While y'all pretend. ♪
- Yo, T, what's up?
How's pop?
Oh that's good, that's good.
Tell him I said hi.
It's hot.
Hot here.
How's the weather in Madrid?
Yeah, they've been asking about you.
All right, I'll tell 'em.
Been quiet.
No problems.
We did get a new girl, though.
Yeah, I don't know how she gonna work out yet.
We'll see.
When you get back, we'll put you on her.
All right.
Well what time your plane come in?
What gate?
All right, well I'll be there to pick you up.
Yeah.
All right.
I'll see you when you get here.
Later.
(soft hip hop)
- So let me get this straight.
While I was out of town,
you called Ninea from jail?
- No.
- So how'd you get in touch with Ninea?
- My brother called her for me.
- So how'd your brother get Ninea's number?
- [Woman] My brother know Durango.
- So.
So let me get this straight.
Your brother called Ninea
to get you out of jail for what,
so you can put in some work?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Okay.
So um, what you know about drugs?
- I used to sell for this girl on north side.
I got popped once.
I used to sell for her.
She was all that.
She was the only girl I know who was slinging.
All the other girls and shit,
they worked for men.
- [Woman] So what happened to her?
- Man.
She got, she got killed in a car accident.
- Gotta love it.
So, what was you in jail for?
- Me and my nigga was tearing it up.
I kicked his ass.
- Word.
So, is that how you got that black eye?
(low tense music)
(tense music)
- So what's up?
- We got a problem.
- We don't have a problem.
You seem to be the only one with a problem here.
- Yeah well why don't you take your shit down south?
I heard the business is great down there.
- Well if business so great down there,
why don't you take your bloated ass?
- Dog, why you asking these stupid questions?
Ask her why she always wearing those fucked up wigs.
- Well you aint going nowhere
and I aint go nowhere.
So what we gonna do about it?
- Well, I don't know about you.
But I'm fitting to blast my way out this motherfucker.
(door creaking)
- Hey, get up.
I wanna buy something.
(tense music)
- Some other time.
♪ I'm lighting up one ♪
♪ Then we heading to the crib ♪
♪ So we can tighten up some ♪
- Alright, so you got a little bit of heart.
So, you not worried about that nigga coming back for you?
- Hey, T.
- [T] What's up?
- I finished doing what you wanted me to do.
- You ate everything?
- [Woman] Yeah, everything.
- [T] Moneys on the table.
I'll give you a call later.
- Bye.
(soft hip hop)
- So, like I was saying.
You aint worried about that nigga coming after you?
- Hell yeah I worry about him coming after my ass.
I mean, I know the first thing he do
right after he get out of the hospital
is come straight for me.
That's why I'm here for Ninea's protection.
- Okay, well.
So let me tell you something.
I take care of all the girls here.
It's my job to make sure you doing your job.
You do what you're told,
we won't have any problems.
Now, all we sell is weight.
If I catch you on the cornering pimping dime bags,
there's your ass.
- All right.
Can I ask you a question?
- [T] What?
- Is Ninea gay?
- Why?
You got a problem with gay people?
- I was just wondering because I haven't seen
no men up in here.
Only thing I see was women.
- [T] No, Ninea is not gay.
She doesn't trust men, though.
- Are you gay?
- Why, you interested?
- Uh.
- [T] Well, anyway.
I have a favor to ask you.
I want you to snort a line of some blow right here.
- Nah, that's all right.
I'm cool.
- [T] Oh you cool?
- I'm all right.
(tense music)
(woman gasping)
What you doing?
- When I tell you to do something,
you fucking do it.
I run this fucking shit.
You do what I tell you to do when I say.
Or I will cut you up into fucking pieces
and throw you down the motherfucking sewer.
Now you snort that blow.
You hear me?
Snort the blow!
(woman coughing)
- Oh god.
(bell tolling)
- We don't know why he did it.
All we wanted to do was come in and question him, you know?
The guy said he had to pee.
He went to the bathroom and he blew his fucking brains out.
- [Woman] What?
You mean to tell me he blew his brains out
while you two was still in the house?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
Do you know if he ever killed that girl or not?
- We never got a chance to ask him.
Apparently someone tipped us off and led us to him.
Obviously, he was doing something that we didn't know about.
We tore the house apart
and we found nothing.
- Guy did something
and he panicked and he blew his head off.
- Wow.
This is so fucking bizarre.
I don't think I can live in your world.
You two got preps blowing their brains out
just because they're under suspicion.
- Hey, you should of been there when we told the captain.
I thought his head was gonna fucking explode.
- I gotta go.
By y'all.
- Look.
- What?
- Shooting star.
- Ninea.
- Ranks?
- Yeah.
♪ Where were you last night ♪
(tires screeching)
(siren wailing)
(soft R&B music)
- Oh shit, Ninea.
It's the 5-0.
- Man go over to that shopping center
and stash the gun.
(soft R&B music)
♪ Where were you last night ♪
♪ It was all just a dream to me ♪
♪ Where were you ♪
- Ninea Ranks.
- [Ninea] I want my lawyer.
- What?
I haven't even asked you a goddamn question yet.
- [Ninea] I know but you will
and I want my lawyer.
- Just relax, Ninea.
Stop acting like one of the fucking Ramseys
and get out of the car.
So, it's been awhile.
How was your vacation?
- [Cop] You got identification?
- Would you like to have another one?
- Hands behind your back.
- Let's see.
Been three years since I was on the narcotics squad.
I remember arresting your mother
with an eight ball.
- Stay right here.
- And speaking of law abiding citizens,
how is your dear old lady?
- She's dead.
- Damn.
And she was a fucking contribution
to your sad ass environment.
- Look, I got somewhere to be at.
- Oh I know.
I know.
You gotta, you know, keep your little bitches
in check, right?
Look.
I play pokers with the boys in Vice.
You take care of me and I guarantee
that you won't have to spend another time in jail.
- [Ninea] What about your partner?
- He knows the rules.
He knows how to play the game.
So, do we have a deal or what?
- Yeah.
- That's good.
Well, you know what.
I think you need to hibernate for today.
I'm sick of looking at ya.
- Bitch.
(soft tense music)
- Yo man, why your face all twisted the fuck up?
Yo, Penn, what the fuck you keep looking over here for
before I blast your fucking ass.
What what what what?
Yeah, go ahead.
Fucking bitch ass nigga.
See, that's what I'm talking about, man.
That's how you gotta do these motherfuckers out here.
Straight the fuck up.
You gotta let these motherfuckers know
at any time, bang, you know what I'm saying?
Better pay attention to this shit man,
that's how you do that shit.
Fuck the motherfuckers.
- Yo, man, let me ask you a question.
How come we never seen Ninea and her bitches
out on the fucking corner clocking bags?
- I don't know.
And one thing, them bitches don't be where we be at.
- But that's just it, yo.
I be around they motherfucking way.
They don't be on the fucking corner.
How the fuck do they be making they money?
- Keisha.
What ups, girl?
Come here, come here for a minute.
Let me rap at you for a minute.
I'm saying, what I can't get a fucking minute?
Go away, go away.
Fucking chicken head, man.
Yo man, she must be selling weight, though.
Yo, wouldn't it be funny
if Dion bought his stash through Ninea
from two different people?
That shit would be fucked up.
- You know that would be funny.
That means Dion basically working for Ninea.
(laughing)
- Like Lawrence.
- Speaking of Dion, our boss,
fucking boss.
How the fuck did he get to be our boss, yo?
- Man stop asking stupid ass fucking questions.
That motherfucker got the coke,
he got the money, and he got the fucking power.
- Nigga, I'ma put it to you like this.
The money we could take.
- Right.
- The coke we could purchase
and the power,
nigga the power, that remains to be seen
who the fuck got the power.
Let's keep it real, aight?
- Aight, true that.
- Have you ever seen that motherfucker packing heat?
- Nah.
I'm being straight up, nah.
- Okay, keep it real.
Have you ever seen that motherfucker throw a punch?
- See, he don't have to do that shit
because that's why we here.
You know what I'm saying?
We the muscle in this bitch.
- Oh like the mob, right?
Like Dion fucking mob connections.
- So what you saying?
- What I'm saying.
What I'm saying, what I'm saying, what I'm saying.
Nigga, what I'm saying is Dion's a fucking bitch.
I'm saying.
We already know Ninea done killed one person already
and who the fuck knows who else she tapped the fuck out.
We saw this bitch in the fucking store,
I'ma tell you like this,
that bitch is fucking 'bout it.
She ready to go, she making power moves and shit.
We still doing this penny ante bullshit.
Dean, fuck Dion. - You know what though?
You know what though,
Dion told me about that situation
at the grocery store, right?
But he aint fucking tell it to me like that.
He made it seem like he handled that shit
like a fucking man.
And you telling me this, he bitched the fuck out.
What the fuck, what the fuck is up with that shit?
- Nigga.
- I'm saying, so now what?
- Nigga, if he handle his shit,
Ninea and everybody in that motherfucking store
would be dead right now
and we wouldn't be going through this shit.
If he handled his shit.
He got mob connections.
He aint supposed to be scared of shit.
He a fucking bitch.
- So-- - You ask me now what?
- So now what?
- I'ma tell you like this.
- What now, nigga?
- I'm ready to cap this motherfucker.
I'm ready to pull his motherfucking chain
and see what the fuck fall out.
Fuck Dion.
Tired of this shit!
- Man, here the fuck you go with
that fucking bullshit again.
Man, I, you aint take your fucking medicine, did you?
I can't believe your fucking ass, man.
What the fuck is wrong with you, nigga?
You know, it would take a stupid nigga like you
to say some shit like that
come out your fucking mouth.
Man what the.
Little fucking Timmy aint here now
'cause he tried to pull a fucking stunt like that
and they gutted him like a fucking fish.
Man fuck you, nigga.
You bump your fucking head?
You must have.
- I'm calm now.
I'm calm, I'm cool.
But, nigga.
If Dion aint got no mob connections,
we aint got nothing to worry about, baby.
Right?
- All right, okay, now what if he do?
What if he got some fucking mob connections?
You want them fucking mob Corleone motherfuckers
running around chasing you?
Man, look, let me tell you something, man.
Running from the cops is one thing.
I can handle that shit.
But fucking, yo, man I'm human, man.
My shit aint constructed out of fucking Teflon.
Man them motherfuckers will find you
wherever the fuck you go.
They will hunt you the fuck down.
That's what the fuck they do.
Understand what I'm saying.
Look, man, don't get it twisted man.
You know you my road dog and we gonna do whatever.
I'm to the death, you know what I'm saying, whatever.
But if you fucking wrong, though,
man, you ready to take that chance?
- Yeah.
I'm ready to take that fucking chance.
- Then I'm with that.
Fuck it.
Only if you take your fucking medicine.
- Fuck you, man.
Hot as shit out this motherfucker.
- You need some fucking fruit,
that's what you fucking need.
Thugs gotta eat healthy, too, baby.
Here.
- Get that fucking shit out my fucking,
need some fucking fried chicken, motherfucker.
- See, that's your problem.
- I need some grease, some shit that had parents.
- You gotta keep it cool, baby.
You gotta have some of this shit
and you can deal with that shit in the world.
You know what I'm saying?
- Where's my fucking medicine at?
- Yo, we gonna do this right, baby?
We gonna do this?
We gonna do this shit?
- You with me, motherfucker?
- You know I'm with you to the death, nigga.
- That's what's up.
- You know how we do.
- Trying to make this fucking money for real.
Fuck Dion.
- It's never too hot for this shit.
- Fucking ants!
Fucking ants.
- You sure you aint chucking that shit between your teeth?
You gotta swallow all them fucking pills.
Fucking wrong with you.
Aint this some shit.
♪ Get the fuck out ♪
- Oh my god.
I know.
I know but.
♪ Make my titties jiggle ♪
♪ One in the front ♪
♪ One in the back ♪
♪ And I'm in the middle ♪
♪ Hands in the air ♪
♪ Pop my twat ♪
♪ Let me keep a little ♪
Mom, Jean, listen.
Can you just listen to me?
Look, I don't want nothing from you.
All just want you to do
is tell him to leave me alone
and give me my stuff back.
♪ We in the club ♪
♪ What the fuck ♪
♪ I come to check with you ♪
♪ Get the fuck ♪
♪ What's up ♪
How is that my fault?
♪ Y'all really want to get buck ♪
♪ Get bucked ♪
♪ Till my brothers playing in the cut ♪
♪ In the cut ♪
♪ T it up ♪
♪ Get it up ♪
♪ Rip it up ♪
♪ What the fuck ♪
♪ Get the fuck up ♪
♪ What's up ♪
♪ Do y'all really wanna get buck ♪
♪ Get bucked till my follows playing in the cut ♪
♪ In the cut ♪
I was protecting myself.
Well I mean, what was I supposed to?
He was going to kill me.
♪ Cat scratch as he trying to get on top of me ♪
♪ How you buying me ♪
Okay.
He's dead.
He comes around me, he's dead.
Gosh.
- Look, bitch.
You better keep your punk ass son in his cradle
'cause if he come around here fucking
with any of my girls, I'ma trade that cradle in
for a coffin and then I'm coming after you.
Can't you just see the fucking headlines?
Woman kills her son then turns the gun on herself.
You goddamn right I mean it.
You goddamn right.
What the fuck did you call there for?
That was stupid.
Downright dumb.
Go drop 60th street.
Hold up, come back for a second.
You bring heat on my spot, you fucking with my fiances.
I don't tolerate that shit.
Okay?
- [Woman] Okay.
- Yeah.
Make sure you remember it.
Go ahead, go ahead.
♪ Bust and you miss ♪
♪ I gotta hit you up with the fifth ♪
♪ It's only right though ♪
♪ Till your neck is where the pipe go ♪
♪ Let the gat blow ♪
♪ Till your eyes close ♪
♪ And arms fold ♪
♪ Had enough of these fake dudes ♪
♪ That fake moves ♪
♪ Put they gun out ♪
♪ I smoke dust to black my lungs out ♪
♪ Acting is over ♪
♪ Niggas all screaming in they rhyme ♪
♪ They taking over ♪
♪ Bagging them trays off of corners ♪
♪ You need to dig that ♪
♪ 24 is where I lay my head at ♪
♪ Me and my dogs batting G stacks ♪
- Yo, Razor.
You sure this aint some kind of set up or some shit?
- No man, like I told you.
Said she would call if she wanted
to discuss some kind of peace shit between us.
Maybe the shit that happened in the store got her scared.
I don't know.
♪ Acting like a serious bitch ♪
♪ Gun to your lips ♪
♪ Talking 'bout me and my clique ♪
♪ But you the type of dog ♪
♪ That be scared to walk on my strip ♪
♪ Put 'em to sleep like the turned out pit ♪
♪ You useless ♪
♪ Sends gs out wouldn't do it. ♪
- I don't know, man.
I don't trust that bitch.
You load the shotgun in the trunk?
- Yeah the shotgun in the trunk.
Shit I don't go unprepared.
I don't trust the evil.
- All right, pop it.
♪ Stacking your riches ♪
♪ Fighting for these bitches in cars ♪
♪ Hoping that you see tomorrow ♪
♪ Your path looking narrow ♪
♪ Adding numbers in front of my zeros ♪
♪ Increase my payroll ♪
♪ Fatty stack ♪
♪ I take my stack ♪
♪ A rose petal ♪
♪ I got my face on cream ♪
♪ And my name Hakeem ♪
♪ I aint settling for bridge ♪
♪ I'm a king that always stay bent ♪
♪ From Africa ♪
♪ But I'm coming to America ♪
- [Dion] What the fuck?
♪ Beware of my area ♪
- Get the fuck in the trunk.
Get the fuck in the trunk, motherfucker!
Get the fuck, get the fuck in the trunk.
♪ With this bitch named Priscilla ♪
♪ My army of killers ♪
♪ Music wise ♪
♪ I know you feel us ♪
♪ Clip filling spit shit ♪
♪ And drill ya ♪
♪ I cop a DS ♪
♪ For platinum not silver ♪
♪ Without being a drug dealer ♪
♪ My microphone my block ♪
♪ My voice ♪
How you like me know, motherfucker?
(gunshot)
♪ Killing all you niggas ♪
♪ We possess manners ♪
♪ When it comes to the riches ♪
♪ We want the money tree ♪
♪ So fuck the golden wishes ♪
♪ My microphone my block ♪
♪ My voice is my trigger ♪
♪ Lyrics all the bullets ♪
♪ So we killing all you niggas ♪
♪ See we possess manners ♪
♪ When it comes to the riches ♪
Checked it before you left the city, right?
- No doubt, baby.
It's all there.
- Oh baby.
You see that bitch all raised up in there?
- You know I ran through that piece, man,
you know it's only right.
- God man, what I been telling you?
Leave that bitch alone,
she's fucking crazy.
- Whatever, dog. - She's fucking loony.
- Shit man.
Why the fuck is we in this fucking bathroom?
Where the fuck is Dion?
He aint supposed to be fucking be here?
- Man, shut the fuck up.
Look, that Dion shit, I took care of that shit.
I told you.
- Man what the fuck you mean?
- I said I took care of that shit.
I said I was gonna take care of that shit.
I took care of it.
- Whoa, whoa.
- Look man, we running this shit now.
If you aint with me, you let me know right now.
- Hold up, man, you know I'm your fucking dog.
You know.
- I know you my motherfucking dog.
Cut the fucking words.
If you with me, you with me.
- Man what the fuck?
I aint think you were gonna do that shit, dog, for real,
straight up.
- I'm a man of my motherfucking word.
I say I'm do something, I'm a do it.
You should know me by now.
- I thought you was joking.
- Come on, I gotta call this bitch, yo.
- Fuck man.
- [Razor] Come on, man.
- Happy birthday, boo.
(tense music)
- Ninea?
- Darien?
- What's up, girl?
- What's happening.
- Heard you got smoked.
Back in my area.
- Nah, I'm still here.
- I see.
Looking good.
I mean.
Not to disrespect you in front of my brother's grave
and all that, I'm just saying,
you look like you've been taking care of yourself.
How you been?
- It was a little rough when I first got out.
I'm straight now.
- That's good.
That's good.
Damn, I miss my brother, man.
- You never did find out who did it, did you?
- Nah, nah.
Prison said it was drug related.
(somber music)
At least that's what the papers say.
That's some fucking bullshit, man.
- I hear that.
It was nice seeing you again.
But I gotta go.
- Ninea.
Ninea, wait.
Why don't you give me your number
so we can hook up later on.
- Nah, that's a bad idea.
I'm not the same person you knew.
- I'm not the same person neither.
- It's just that right now, I got a lot
of drama happening in my life.
Just being around me is bad for your health.
- Aight.
Whatever.
- Ninea, everything all right?
- Well if it wasn't, you'd be a little late right now,
wouldn't you?
- I was up all night with that Jimmy thing.
(phone ringing)
- Hello.
- [Razor] Hey.
- Who's this?
- [Razor] Razor.
- How the fuck you get my number?
- Look, don't worry about how I got your fucking number.
Look, that beef you had with Dion,
that shit don't exist no more, I took care of that.
- And what?
You called me just to brag.
- Look, bitch.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry I don't mean to disrespect you.
But look, now that Dion no longer in the picture,
I'm saying we squash this beef and come together
and work together, you know what I'm saying?
Lock this city down.
So what's up?
- Oh, I get it.
If I'm not with you I'm against you, right?
- Yeah.
Hello?
Ninea?
- You used to like talking to me back in the day.
It's not your fault.
It was his time, Ninea.
- Fucking bitch.
That fucking bitch hung up on me.
- What happened, bro.
What happened, what happened?
She call you?
What she say?
- That bitch hung up the phone.
I don't believe that shit.
It's time to send this bitch a fucking message, man.
- What the fuck she say?
- Fuck.
- Man, you aight?
What the fuck she say?
- [Razor] Come on man, let's go.
(door creaking)
(tense music)
- Look.
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- My girls fellas don't need no man power.
I really don't want you here
but Razor got 'em all nervous and what not.
So you have to prove yourself to me.
- Really?
- You ready to get a little blood on your hands?
- Whatever.
- Come on.
(tense music)
You see this little hussy right here?
- Yeah.
- She stole $200 worth of my product.
- Word?
- And she's been down here two days.
Till I find out what I'm gonna do with her.
She only 14.
And her mommy left her with her step daddy
and he likes to play daddy.
So brother, you'd be doing her a favor.
Ah, look at her.
She's so scared.
Heart beating like thunder.
(tense music)
Fully loaded.
Kill her.
- What about the noise?
- Don't worry about the noise,
you just point and shoot when I tell you to.
(tense music)
Shoot.
(gun clicking empty)
- What's up with the gun?
- No firing pin.
- How am I supposed to bust a cap
without a firing pin?
- You don't.
Look, if you...
My girls are off limit to you, okay?
Call me tomorrow.
On Saturday.
- What's up with your girl?
- She pissed off.
We had a $200 bet.
She bet that you wouldn't do it.
- You were gonna shoot me, weren't you?
- Business.
Sure is a feisty one, aint she.
(tense music)
(gunshot)
- Come on, you want some more?
(tense dramatic music)
(somber music)
- [T Voiceover] I take care of the girls here.
I got you something.
(echoing indistinct voiceovers)
(gunshots)
(somber music)
- So what you wanna do?
- I'm gonna kill that motherfucker,
that's what I'm gonna do.
- I don't think you should do that.
I think you should wait things out.
- Look, I don't,
I don't pay you to think.
I'm gonna kill that motherfucker.
- Hold on, hold on.
Catch the next elevator.
Back up, man.
Come on, Ninea.
Let's think things out.
- I'm gonna kill him.
I done thought about it.
What is there, what?
- What, then what?
Kill one of theirs, they kill one of ours
and then what?
Just keep going back and forth?
- Then everybody's got to die, okay?
- Oh now everybody's got to die?
- Everybody gotta die.
Whoever don't want to die
just don't be there.
- Listen, I don't want to tell you how to run your shit,
Ninea, but, it aint gonna work out that way.
(somber music)
- [Man Voiceover] You know when I got back
from the hospital,
you know how I sound when those fuckers tore me up.
You know what I did to those guys?
(somber music)
So you got no choice.
You got to take care of Holly.
If you don't.
You know how you gonna wind up.
(somber music)
You're looking at it.
- Get your coat.
We gonna take care of this shit tonight.
(upbeat hip hop music)
♪ My life ♪
(knocking at door)
♪ My niggas ♪
♪ They my life ♪
- Get the door, yo.
♪ My life ♪
♪ My niggas my life ♪
♪ We might die ♪
♪ Spit the heat like ♪
What the fuck?
(tense hip hop)
- Which one of you motherfuckers killed my sister?
- I see you got my message.
- Oh yeah, I got your message.
Snake ass motherfuckers.
You know you gonna pay for what you did to my sister.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whatever, bitch.
What the fuck you gonna do?
You outnumbered, you out gunned.
You think I give a fuck about him?
Only been here a week.
Fuck him.
One word from me,
my boys gonna twist your wig and his.
So you say what you gotta say
then you get the fuck outta here.
(tense hip hop)
- What's your name, lips?
- Curtis.
What's the most amount of cash
you ever had in your hand at one time?
- I don't know, a grand maybe.
- A grand?
I got nine in this bag right here.
Three for everybody that turns their gun on him,
plus whatever he got laying around here.
(tense hip hop)
What you gonna do?
- Stupid bitch, what the fuck?
Gonna walk in here with nine grand in the Christmas bag?
My boys supposed to take it?
He's my crew.
Fuck you.
♪ We wild life ♪
♪ We might die tonight ♪
- [Man] Shit, it look like nine Gs in here to me, dog.
- [Man] Fuck that.
♪ Playing God tonight ♪
♪ We wild life baby ♪
♪ wild life baby ♪
♪ wild life ♪
- Never underestimate the power of money.
Come on.
You a big dog, you a criminal.
Make a run for it.
Jimmy Walker looking motherfucker.
Make a run for me
so you don't die like the bitch you are.
Come on.
(tense hip hop)
♪ We wild life ♪
♪ We may die tonight ♪
(gunfire)
(man laughing)
- [Curtis] Told ya I was with you to the death, nigga.
(soft tense music)
(gunshot)
(tense hip hop)
♪ Not on that fake shit ♪
♪ Word up ♪
♪ When you see me ♪
♪ Nigga we here ♪
♪ Yo hey yo we gotta be the money ♪
♪ Pussy and rapping ♪
♪ That keep me going ♪
♪ Before I die ♪
♪ I'm trying to see millions off the flow ♪
♪ And it never stop ♪
♪ Take drug money invest in stock ♪
♪ Bury a cop ♪
♪ Blow and bribe a block ♪
♪ It's J street niggas ♪
♪ Screaming RTX till I die ♪
♪ We stick up a club ♪
♪ Survive then blow up a five ♪
♪ We the killer kind ♪
♪ That love to stay on our grind ♪
♪ Popping wheelies on the nine ♪
♪ And summertime up till nine ♪
♪ However you want ♪
♪ However that is we got it ♪
♪ Cock a Glock and pop it ♪
♪ Cop a brick and chop it ♪
♪ Cop a roadie rocking down ♪
♪ Take a stripper lock it down ♪
♪ The sound of running ♪
♪ When niggas hit the ground ♪
♪ Niggas can't fuck with us ♪
♪ Can't mess they fate ♪
♪ They going out ♪
♪ In the bang ♪
♪ When they slow some weight ♪
♪ Y'all niggas don't really know me ♪
♪ I keep my brain smoking ♪
♪ Turn into a Glock and have rock ♪
♪ I got low ♪
♪ Used to be my man ♪
♪ Until you got some old fail shit ♪
♪ Smoking down ♪
♪ You was about it ♪
♪ All time it was as set up ♪
♪ Let your dogs leave me ♪
♪ Right up from the neck up ♪
♪ But guess what ♪
♪ It aint happen ♪
♪ And we smashing and clapping ♪
♪ And blasting if we gotta ♪
♪ I see y'all fake niggas try to touch ours ♪
♪ You get rained on like showers ♪
♪ With nine millimeters ♪
♪ And then leave your body there ♪
♪ For the rats to feast on ♪
♪ Pull out in a Nissan ♪
♪ With my bleep on ♪
♪ Shorty keep on asking me ♪
♪ Yo why the heat warm ♪
♪ Shut up and keep going ♪
♪ I'm tired of this ♪
♪ Pull out a little Chris for 'em ♪
♪ Niggas start taking shit ♪
♪ I put the fifth on 'em ♪
♪ You aint got a chance to set me up ♪
♪ Niggas wet me up ♪
♪ While you're bleeding from the gut ♪
♪ I'm sipping on Hen out the cup ♪
♪ Getting my dick licked ♪
♪ By a chick you used to fuck with ♪
♪ She gave me a ♪
♪ Two point of niggas ♪
♪ That you used to fuck with ♪
♪ A chance to kill dames ♪
♪ I aint saying no names ♪
♪ I'm squeezing them things ♪
♪ Must be the weed in my veins ♪
♪ Niggas go against the grain ♪
♪ But who's to blame ♪
♪ I gotta maintain and do my thing ♪
♪ To stay on top of the game ♪
♪ I'ma pull a gat ♪
♪ Cock it back ♪
♪ Real live niggas ♪
♪ Take a stack to the track ♪
♪ Ready to die niggas ♪
♪ Smoke a ho fuck a ho ♪
♪ Stay high niggas ♪
♪ Do for niggas ♪
♪ J-A-Y niggas ♪
♪ This is for all the pull a gat ♪
♪ Cock it back ♪
♪ Real live niggas ♪
♪ Take a stack to the track ♪
♪ Ready to die niggas ♪
♪ Smoke a ho fuck a hoe ♪
♪ Stay high niggas ♪
♪ Two four niggas ♪
♪ J-A-Y niggas ♪
♪ I stay fit ♪
♪ The pussy lickers on the bill for real ♪
♪ Bust a nut ♪
♪ Impregnate with the shit that I spill ♪
♪ Catch me chilling ♪
♪ Smoked out dealing with villains ♪
♪ I turn the world upside ♪
♪ And put your brains on the ceiling ♪
♪ Real niggas do real shit ♪
♪ Ill niggas fill ill shit ♪
♪ Lunatics like me kill quick ♪
♪ I hate a bitch with an attitude ♪
♪ The bitch sucked my dick for gratitude ♪
♪ I confess but its rather rude ♪
♪ I'm on some other shit ♪
♪ Handcuffs and badges ♪
♪ Real spot rushing ♪
♪ Nigga fuck you the matching ♪
♪ Pit boss my nickname for slugs ♪
♪ And my clips for you ♪
♪ We draw ♪
♪ If not get hit ♪
♪ With some shit ♪
♪ On timberlands ♪
♪ On the feet of the realest then ♪
♪ Don't make me have to black out ♪
♪ And kill again ♪
♪ Niggas hate us 'cause we Gs for em ♪
♪ If you got brains ♪
♪ Use it ♪
♪ Don't abuse it ♪
♪ Check this right ♪
♪ I am my soul unfold ♪
♪ To uphold in Illadelph ♪
♪ City of brother's love ♪
♪ Took over self ♪
♪ So remember top shelf ♪
♪ And nothing else ♪
♪ No appetite or taste whatsoever ♪
♪ For any type of wealth ♪
♪ No energy ♪
♪ No time to grit and grind ♪
♪ Confined behind the enemy lines ♪
♪ Trying to get ♪
♪ I'm think I'm gonna run from your house ♪
♪ Them set them apart ♪
♪ High high ♪
♪ My life ♪
♪ My niggas my life ♪
♪ We wild life ♪
♪ We might die ♪
♪ So I wanna ♪
♪ Spit the heat like a sauna ♪
♪ Y'all niggas gonna ♪
♪ Big snake in the corner ♪
♪ But niggas wild life ♪
♪ Gotta prove yourself ♪
♪ Thousand cats bringing out ♪
♪ 1,000 gats ready to die ♪
♪ 1,000 niggas in the club ♪
♪ Know why ♪
♪ I spot smoke block ♪
♪ Online ♪
♪ Et cetera et cetera ♪
♪ Blasting the nine ♪
♪ Silence that kid ♪
♪ Better use a silencer ♪
♪ My voice is my trigger ♪
♪ Lyrics are bullets ♪
♪ So we killing all you niggas ♪
♪ We possess manners ♪
♪ When it come to riches ♪
♪ We want the money tree ♪
♪ So fuck them other bushes ♪
♪ What's rocking blow ♪
♪ Aint nobody fucking with this ♪
♪ Bust and you miss ♪
♪ I gotta hit you up with the fifth ♪
♪ It's only quiet though ♪
♪ Until your neck is where the pipe go ♪
♪ We catching bodies ♪
♪ We all hunger for pays ♪
♪ If you get shot or not ♪
♪ You aint got what it takes ♪
♪ While a body six ♪
♪ Infinity bricks ♪
♪ Guns to spit ♪
♪ Slumlord over crack spots ♪
♪ Watch it flip ♪
♪ To get my cash back ♪
♪ Watch my stash stack to multi mils ♪
♪ Real dogs they fucking suitcase ♪
♪ Carry my bills ♪
♪ Spinning on four wheels ♪
♪ Chrome keep 'em shining ♪
♪ Freak hoes rubbing my chest ♪
♪ Clothes designing ♪
♪ My whole frame flooded ♪
♪ And ice life it's nice ♪
♪ Casino bets chasing snake eyes ♪
♪ Rolling the dice ♪
♪ That's money on the race track ♪
♪ Living like crack. ♪
♪ You see how much ♪
(soft R&B music)
♪ I've been up since midnight ♪
♪ Waiting by the telephone ♪
♪ I kept calling and calling ♪
♪ But you never made it home ♪
♪ Now I'm searching for an answer ♪
♪ Yo we ball 'em ♪
♪ You know we ball balling ♪
♪ Pet niggas with holes ♪
♪ Mixed up ♪
♪ Turn 'em old ♪
♪ We know how we go ♪
♪ I'm lady ♪
♪ This our time to blow ♪
♪ Let me hear you say whoa ♪
♪ We get the dough ♪
♪ But balling ♪
♪ Pet niggas with holes ♪
♪ Make thugs ♪
♪ Turn 'em old ♪
♪ Y'all know how we go ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Ladies it's our time to blow ♪
♪ Let me hear you say whoa ♪
♪ We gotta go ♪
♪ Call me a freaky ass bitch ♪
♪ 'cause I'm balling 'em all ♪
♪ Then when we talk ♪
♪ 'Cause you're never gonna see me fall ♪
♪ Uh huh ♪
♪ Thinking I'm wrong ♪
♪ Catch me up with some songs ♪
♪ Leaving them numb ♪
♪ Get hard ♪
♪ Talk shit till they come ♪
♪ It's me ♪
♪ Lady to the ♪
♪ Got no respect ♪
♪ Fuck the man bitch ♪
♪ Where you rest at ♪
♪ Got that ♪
♪ Wifey ♪
♪ I don't know what that mean ♪
♪ Fuck a ring ♪
♪ 'cause that shit to me ♪
♪ Really don't mean a thing ♪
♪ Saying you got bling ♪
♪ But he gives me everything ♪
♪ I ride around in your whip ♪
♪ And your dough ♪
♪ He gives to me ♪
♪ Let him come home to you boo ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ You may be claiming him now ♪
♪ But we still fucking tonight ♪
♪ Right ♪
♪ We keep on balling ♪
♪ Pet niggas with hoes ♪
♪ Make thugs ♪
♪ Turn 'em old ♪
♪ Y'all know how we blow ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Ladies this our time to blow ♪
♪ Let me hear you say whoa ♪
♪ We getting dough ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Uh huh ♪
♪ Ball balling ♪
(upbeat music)
(gunshot)