(MultiCom Jingle)
(cheerful music)
(horn blares)
(smacks)
- Have you got that rat with you?
Have you?
If you brought that rat with you,
the captain's gonna turn
this boat right around
and no one'll be going anywhere.
You understand?
Be a nice start to a
vacation, now wouldn't it?
Let me see the other pocket.
- Hi, Mom.
(dramatic music)
- [Captain] On behalf of Catalina Cruises,
this is your captain.
- Seasick?
- [Captain] As promised,
it's been a smooth crossing.
We're only a few minutes
away from Catalina Island,
here in the sunny southern California.
Thank you, have a good
visit on the island.
- Hi, how are you doing?
Are you going to Catalina too?
I'm going to see my dad.
He lives there.
- Billy, who are you talking to?
- No one.
- Right, thank you.
We need to have a little talk.
You wanna live with your father, fine,
but you're gonna have to grow up.
One of you will have to.
Every toddler talks to their toys.
You're still doing it.
(laughs)
- Mom.
- Broccoli can't talk.
Nor can trees, frogs,
caterpillars, white mice, rats,
snakes, cats, or dogs.
- I know.
- What do you think?
(dog whines)
Yeah, me too.
(sighs)
15 across.
Over your head and on top of your mouth.
Must be an American word like
popsicle or Ranch dressing.
- Roof.
- Roof?
Roof!
Over your head and the roof of your mouth.
Okay.
12 down, where you get tied up.
- Wharf.
- Wharf?
Wharf!
Where you tie up boats.
No, wharf doesn't fit.
- How many letters, huh?
- How many letters?
Four.
- Okay, fort, pier, dock.
(whirring)
- William dear, could you
get me some dog food, please?
- Of course, no problem.
(dramatic music)
- There you are.
So, welcome to Catalina.
- What's with the golf carts?
- It's a way small island.
- We patrol in golf carts?
- No way.
Hey, golf carts are the best.
Way less pollution,
cheap, no traffic jams.
- What's with your foot?
- Golf cart.
- Mrs. Bent--
Mrs. Bentley!
Look out!
Mrs. Bentley, behind you!
Stop, stop, stop that thing!
Stop that!
(crashes)
(grunts)
- What's the cop doing?
- He's getting in the truck.
- What's that dog doing?
- He's sitting on the ground.
- [Man In Black Shirt]
Man, I hate police dogs.
- Come on.
- Come on, come on.
- Now you're talking.
- [Mike] Let's go check out the ferry.
They have to be getting the
drugs onto the island somehow.
Hey, what's going on?
Let us out!
I'm a police officer!
Hey!
Get up there.
(mumbles), what can you see?
- What do you think?
Houses.
- [Mike] Now what can you see?
- More houses.
Oh!
- [Mike] Sherlock?
Sherlock!
(grunts)
(groans)
(gasps)
(screams)
- There's rats out there!
(groans)
(horn blares)
(gagging)
(sirens)
- I don't know what happened.
I don't want to know.
I just know it's always something.
Here.
Towards food.
- Oh no, thanks.
I'm fine.
I got a part time job here.
- [Announcer] We are now
boarding Catalina Island,
return to Los Angeles.
We apologize for the delay.
We remind you again, no pets on board.
And please use extra care
when walking on the dock.
- Love you.
- [Announcer] It may still
be a little slippery.
Thank you.
- Oh, I'm cooking lunch!
Sausages.
(gagging)
- How's the Turt?
- Turt's good.
I think I've got all the glitches out.
Billy, you know this
is just a trial visit.
- I know.
But you're gonna sell the Turt
and you're gonna have lots of money
and I can come live with you.
- But your mom has to agree.
She thinks I'm a bad influence.
- I don't think so.
(calm music)
- So, what happened on the ferry?
- Stuff.
What happened to the car?
- Oh, whoa!
- Oh!
(groans)
(dogs barking)
- Doctor.
- (mumbles) that end.
Are you okay?
- Oh, no, I'm fine.
- Is he yours?
- We were just coming back from the ferry.
- [Sally] Thanks for bringing him in.
Most drivers don't.
- Is he gonna die?
- Looks like a survivor to me.
No license tag.
- Is that bad?
- Means he's probably a stray.
Means I won't get paid for treating him.
And it means he'll end up in the pound.
- Then what?
- No one claims him or adopts
him, he's put to sleep.
(whines)
- Mom, Mom!
It was so gross, there's vomit everywhere.
They had to hose down the whole dock.
- My daughter.
- This mutant moron was talking
to his rat on the ferry.
- [Sally] Mutant moron?
- Mom, talking to a rat?
The kid's special ed.
Oh, hi.
- I don't think anything's broken.
This'll make him sleepy.
I'll take him in there and X-ray him,
and I'll put a couple of
stitches in that wound.
- [Man] Excuse me, Doctor?
- Right.
There.
(kisses)
While we're waiting for this to work,
maybe Emma could fix you something?
- Peanut butter and jelly shake?
- Ah.
Can I help?
(gentle music)
- Hey, let's see him.
- Who?
- The rat.
- Oh, he ran away.
- Maybe you said something he didn't like.
- [Sherlock Bones] Psst, psst.
- Go away.
- Hey buddy, go get the telephone.
Go on, lad, I've got to make a phone call.
Hurry, before the injection kicks in.
Go on, lad, fetch, fetch.
- Dad, Dad, Dad!
Dad, he can talk!
He can talk!
- Billy, I thought the place was on fire.
- He can talk!
- Who can talk?
- He can.
He just talked to me.
- The dog?
- Go on, this is my dad.
Go on, say something.
- Billy.
- He can talk.
He has a funny accent and everything.
Say something.
Tell him to go get the phone.
- Billy.
- I'd better get back.
- Quick.
- [Billy] Why'd you do that?
- I no talk to people, lad, okay?
- I no what?
- I do not talk to people.
- You talked to me.
- You're a kid.
- So?
- So no one believes you.
This is urgent.
Go get the phone.
Come on, the injection's
making me very sleepy.
- You're gonna make a phone call?
- No, I'm going to eat it.
911.
- That's the police.
- [Sherlock Bones] Dial.
- 911.
- Come on, come on.
Code 38, code 38.
Police officer kidnapped.
- [Operator] Hello, hello?
Hello?
- Hi.
This is Billy.
I think he said a police
officer had been kidnapped.
He's sort of a friend.
I'm 10.
Come on, come on.
Say something.
Please.
- I hope that's not long distance.
Mom hates it when dogs
run up big phone bills.
(shouts)
- I'm sorry, I'll have it towed.
- Whoa, Waynester.
Neighbor's cat got caught up a tree.
Let's go, dude.
- Excuse me, sir!
- What?
- Has anybody been kidnapped?
- I think your police
officer's been kidnapped.
- Go away.
- Like yesterday, or today.
- [Wayne] Go away.
- Mom's got a car phone if he needs it.
- Who?
- The dog.
- Shut up.
- What's your dad doing?
- He designs toys.
- What kind of toys?
- Well, this is one of them.
It's a Turt.
- A turd?
- Emma.
- Sorry.
- Turt.
Totally Underwater Robotic Turtle.
- What's it do?
- Teaches kids to swim.
And Dad's gonna sell it
to a big toy company.
- Dad's gonna try and sell
it to a big toy company.
Excuse me just a moment.
Mrs. Bentley.
Mrs...
Mrs., Mrs. Bentley.
I forgot to get your dog--
- After any kind of shock,
animals and people can
get very dehydrated.
Do you know what dehydration is?
Give him lots of water when he wakes up
and keep an eye on him.
If he starts to bite off the splint,
you'll have to distract him, talk to him.
- Talk to him?
- Oh, yes, right.
You see, there's talking to animals
and then there's talking to--
- Neat house.
What are these for?
- They're spare eyeballs for the Turt.
- Alright!
Mom, can we stay for dinner?
- Oh, I didn't know we'd been invited.
- We haven't yet.
Can we stay for dinner?
- Dinner?
Dinner!
Oh, yes.
Right.
- [Emma] Come on, I'm starved.
- Emma.
For some reason or other,
we're not invited out often.
Try not to blow it.
- Okay.
I'll bet you're a terrible cook.
- Don't get too attached.
He may belong to someone.
- Um.
Could he be a policeman's dog?
- Yeah.
The police use Airedales a
lot, especially the British.
It's a Scottish breed.
- Scottish?
- Like my grandfather.
Aye, lass, I don't think
you're gettin' any bigger.
- Can you talk to people?
- Where'd you learn Scots?
- Oh.
Um, from TV.
- Did you know that you can cook food
by passing electric current through it?
- (mumbles) of course.
If you want to stay,
you should wear these.
- Ah.
Maybe I should have my calls forwarded.
Can I use your phone?
- Of course.
Everyone like corn?
(shouts)
- Got it.
- [William] Over there.
Good!
- Dad took it apart to make this one.
It's for kids' use.
It's unbreakable.
- That's a phone?
- Yeah.
You have to kinda dribble.
Like that.
- [Operator] Good evening.
At the tone, Pacific
daylight time, 6:57 exactly.
And that's how you hang it up.
Okay?
- Oh.
- [William] There's one!
Over there, on the brick!
No, no the other one.
- Got it.
- Yeah, that's it.
No.
Over here.
You get those over there.
I got this one here.
Yeah, on the right.
- Do you think there
are any animals that...
- Any animals that what?
- Talk?
- You know the main difference
between animals and people?
There isn't one.
Different species are
better at different things.
Humans do certain kinds
of thinking better.
- [Emma] I got it!
- But--
- [Emma] Keep going, keep going!
- The animals do communicate.
(glass breaking)
- Stop.
Dinner's ready.
- The theory behind
plug in food isn't new,
it's making it work.
- No, no, no, they taste fine.
You been on the island long?
- Oh, it's my second year.
It's a great place to work.
How about you?
- Oh, I was born here.
I went away to school but I was born here.
- Then when she knew she was
gonna have me, she came back
so I could be an islander too.
- A shock the island
may never recover from.
- Because she wasn't married.
I'm illegitimate.
Neat, huh?
- Emma belongs to the hit them
over the head with a brick
school of chit chat.
- Dad, can we try the Turt?
- Sure.
Tomorrow's the big day.
- You try to sell it?
- Right.
- Then I can come live with him.
- That's the plan.
- I think the gearing's broken again.
- It's just a loose screw.
- So, does it have a temperature?
- Coffee?
- That'd be great.
Here, let me give you a hand with this.
- Oh, no, no!
We've got a system.
- Alright!
(laughs)
- Billy, did that plant just move?
- Yeah.
They're on a turntable, so
that the sun gets to all sides.
- You suppose your dad
has any wine glasses left?
(glasses whistling)
(laughing)
(whines)
(ominous music)
(dog barking)
(calm music)
- Hey, wake up.
Wake up, come on, talk to me.
(rattling)
- [Man] Hello, hello?
What kind of pizza you want?
Hello, hello, hello?
Come on, I don't got all day, I'm busy.
What kind of pizza you want?
- What are you doing?
You were calling the
police again, weren't you?
(moaning)
What's the matter?
Don't you talk anymore?
- Billy.
- Oh.
- This is Sergeant
Turner and Officer Quail.
You didn't call 911 yesterday, did you?
I'm really sorry, will
you let me talk to him?
- Go for it, dad.
- Why did you think a
policeman had been kidnapped?
Did someone tell you to call the police?
So you were playing a game.
(whines)
- I'm sorry.
- Billy, I keep trying to
remember what being 10 was like.
- I know, I know.
I promise not to do it again.
- I have to go to work.
First day.
Mrs. Bentley's gonna fix you lunch.
You're gonna be okay for
a couple hours, right?
Okay.
We'll talk later.
Bye.
- Mmhm.
Right then, dad's gone.
Get dialing.
- No.
- [Sherlock Bones] No?
- I promised Dad I wouldn't
call the police again.
Well, maybe if you'd talk to Dad.
- No.
- Why not?
- I no talk to people.
Keep telling them.
- Hey, where are you going?
- [Sherlock Bones] Down to the harbor.
- Hey!
Hey.
- What?
- I'll help you.
So, what's your name?
- What?
- What's your name?
I'm not gonna help you if
you don't tell me your name.
- Sherlock.
Sherlock what?
- You're a pedantic wee--
- Sherlock what?
- Bones.
- Sherlock Bones.
That's neat.
- Don't push it.
- What do you smell?
- Drugs.
- Drugs?
How do you know?
Oh yeah, that's right.
You're a police dog.
It must be great to be able to do that.
- [Sherlock Bones] No, it's not.
- [Billy] Why not?
- There's a lot of very
nasty things on sidewalks.
- Billy?
(crashes)
- Come on, come on.
- Where are we going?
- [Sherlock Bones] I've sniffed out Mike.
- And now, if you will
look up and to your left,
you'll be enthralled by
a rare and unique example
of Catalina tile.
Catalina tile is tile
made out of Catalina.
- Sorry, tour's full.
- The Avalon Casino,
which is a registered historic monument,
only has two floors because
they have very high ceilings.
- Sherlock.
- [Emma] Downstairs is
the famous Casino Theater
and upstairs is the
famous Casino Ballroom.
- Come on.
- The Avalon Casino, which is
almost completely circular,
was built by William Raven,
who was famous for chewing gum.
He started building it in 1928
and didn't finish it until 1929.
Because he had to remove a mountain first.
- Excuse me.
But if there's no gambling,
why is it called a casino?
- Beats me.
And now, before we go upstairs
to the spacious Casino Ballroom,
we'll have a few minutes to buy some
of the very modestly
priced, tacky souvenirs
at the other end of the foyer.
No dogs allowed.
- But we're looking for Mike.
- Mike?
- The police officer that was kidnapped.
- What police officer?
- Sherlock Bones.
This is Sherlock Bones.
He sniffs out drugs.
Except his handler, Mike, was kidnapped
by the two drug smugglers
and now we've gotta find him.
- How do you know all this?
Let me guess, the dog told you.
I thought you were gonna be fun.
Grow up.
- Sherlock, say something to her.
Please, she's a kid too!
- What?
- I said I wouldn't kid you.
- Ha.
- No, no, it wasn't the dog.
I overheard this man.
- A man?
What man?
Talking to himself?
- Yes.
No.
Two men, talking to each other.
- I don't believe you.
- No, really.
One was fat, had a beard, and a limp.
And the other one, well, he didn't.
They were on the ferry yesterday
and I overheard them talking
about how they were keeping
this policeman prisoner.
- Prisoner?
Where?
- Um...
In the casino.
- Here?
Where, in a trash can?
(grunts)
- No.
Uh, upstairs.
- That dog's got ear mites.
- And Sherlock Bones is gonna
track him down upstairs.
- They're never gonna let a dog upstairs.
Quick, I've got an idea.
(playful music)
Sorry, I'm sorry!
Come on, follow me.
Follow me, come on.
Up here, come on.
This way, this way.
Come on, hurry up.
On our way upstairs to
the spacious ballroom,
you'll notice that there are no stairs.
(gasps)
The ballroom was used
extensively by the big bands
in the 30s and the 40s.
- Excuse me.
What kind of music did they play?
- Sorry, you're only allowed one question.
These ramps were specially designed
to help move the large
groups of dance goers
and avoid people being trampled.
The ballroom dance floor is
also almost completely circular,
180 feet wide.
- Stop staring.
- Why?
He can't see me.
- If you'll all pass through
the doors onto the balcony
you'll be treated to a
breathtaking view of Avalon Harbor.
- Aha.
- Where are we going?
- Come on, lad.
- Sherlock.
- Over here, over here.
- Ow, oh, ow, oh, ow, oh, uh, oh, ow, oh!
- Come on, lad.
Come on, come on, you weigh a ton.
Come on, try to keep up.
(shouts)
- Are you really blind?
(barks)
- Uh, Miss, that's not
a real seeing eye dog.
- Shh, he doesn't know that.
And now if you'll all step
outside onto the balcony,
you'll be treated to yet
another breathtaking...
(shouts)
- Right, bingo, here we are.
Come on, stop lying around.
Yes, yes, yes.
- What can you smell?
- Beer, pizza, anchovies,
old socks, dead rats.
Hey!
- Oh, sorry.
There's a door back here.
- Can you see anything?
- [Billy] There's someone in there.
- [Sherlock Bones] And?
- [Billy] And he's tied up with a rope.
- [Sherlock Bones] Does he have any hair?
- [Billy] No.
- [Sherlock Bones] That's Mike.
Go on, lad, now, would you?
- [Billy] He's got something.
- [Sherlock Bones] And?
And?
- [Billy] And he's
pushing it under the door.
(grunts)
- [Sherlock Bones] Right on my head.
Get it, get it.
- Got it.
It says Scotland Yard.
It's his police ID.
- Look out, lad, over there.
See the man with no neck?
- Who's that?
- One of the drug smugglers
who kidnapped Mike and me.
Get ready, get ready, go!
(squeaks)
- Hey!
(shouts)
(screams)
- The rat boy!
- No, no, I'm fine.
I've got it under control.
It's okay, it's okay.
(crashes)
Billy?
- Excuse me, sir, but
there's a policeman locked up
in the casino.
He's a police officer
and they've locked him up
behind where the band floor is.
- What?
- Mike.
- What Mike?
There's only two officers
on this stupid island,
Tom and Wayne.
- He gave me his police ID.
- He gave you his police ID?
Okay.
- It fell into the water.
Honest, I saw it.
And he's all tied up
with tape over his mouth
so that he can't call out.
- Billy.
- Tape over his mouth?
How'd he tell you this,
sign language with his toes?
- Smugglers have been using
Catalina for 200 years.
Shouldn't we take a look?
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Excuse me, wait a minute, please.
Excuse me, oh, wait a second, excuse me.
- It's okay, they're a group.
(dramatic music)
- [Wayne] 1912-11, 7F,
causing a disturbance in a public place.
- That was on the Catalina Ferry.
- Creating a panic, 19, 12-11-688,
causing a disturbance in a public place.
- That was in the restaurant.
- Creating a panic.
172-14, making a false
report to a police officer
concerning two nonexistent
men overheard on the ferry.
- Restaurant again.
- Creating a panic, 173-16,
sub-paragraph three,
making a false 911 call.
- Oh yes, well, we talked about that one.
- Didn't do much good, did it?
- Emma, why don't you
wait for me at the Jeep?
Tom.
- Come on, Wayne.
(calm music)
- Dad, I swear.
There was a man locked up in that room
and he gave me this, like,
wallet with a heavy metal badge
and it said Detective, honest.
- What about the two men you overheard?
The two men on the ferry?
- Well, I made them up.
- If I sell the Turt today,
things will be different.
We'll have money.
How can I tell your mom
you should live here
if you don't know the
difference between playing
and imagining?
- Dad, if I told you the truth...
- Try me.
- You wouldn't believe me.
- Why don't the kids come up to the house?
We've got a pool, the housekeeper's there,
and at least they could swim.
- Mom.
- [William] Very kind, thanks.
- But what about Sherlock Bones?
- Who?
- The dog.
- It's a very small island,
I'm sure someone will spot him.
- But only if you promise
not to go off again.
Wanna hear you say it.
- I promise I won't go anywhere.
- Billy, it's when you
wander off by yourself.
I want you to promise not
to go anywhere without Emma
for the rest of the day.
- Promise not to go anywhere without Emma
(gentle music)
- [Emma] You coming in or not?
- I can't swim.
Look, the most have moved Mike somewhere
when they saw Sherlock Bones and me.
- You can't swim?
- No.
If we go together, we
can find Sherlock Bones
and he'll find Mike.
- Why can't you swim?
- I don't know.
- Don't believe you.
Everyone can swim.
I'm gonna talk to your dad.
- If we got Mike's ID
back out of the harbor.
- Psst.
Psst.
Over here.
- What are you doing over there?
- [Sherlock Bones] Trying to get down.
- Where have you been?
- Where?
The harbor.
- What were you doing there?
- Tracking Mike down.
- You found him?
- [Sherlock Bones] I'm a police dog.
Stop lying around.
- Where are we going?
- To rescue Mike.
We've got to get back to the harbor.
- Sherlock, wait, I can't.
- Come on, lad.
Nothing but excuses, excuses, excuses.
- I promised Dad I wouldn't
go anywhere without Emma.
You've got to ask her to come too!
Sherlock, please.
If you just talk to Emma,
then she'd believe me
and we can all go and
look for Mike together.
Please.
- I don't talk to people.
- You talk to me and I'm a person.
- Barely.
Come on, lad.
- Whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
- I called your dad at the restaurant.
You're right, you can't swim.
What are you doing?
- Emma, you've got to swear
not to tell a living soul.
- You've just discovered
you're from outer space, right?
Don't you hate it when that happens?
- Swear!
- Is this gonna be
something really retarded?
- Swear!
- Okay, okay.
On my mother's grave.
- But your mother's not dead.
- Get on with it!
- Right.
Well...
Sherlock Bones has something
he wants to say to you.
Okay?
- Oh well, okay.
- See, see, see?
Go on.
- To be or not to be,
that is the question.
(smacks)
- Ow.
- My uncle does that at parties.
- What?
- Talks without moving his lips.
- Ah, but can he do the complete speech?
- See?
You can see his lips moving.
- Dogs don't have lips.
- Oh, I find that very, very hurtful.
- Go on, say something, please.
♪ Oh say can you see by
the dawn's early light ♪
♪ What so proudly we hailed at
the twilight's last gleaming ♪
- Wow.
♪ Whose broad stripes and bright stars ♪
♪ Through the perilous night ♪
- Wow!
♪ While o'er ramparts we watched ♪
♪ And the liars were squealing ♪
- [Sherlock Bones] Or
words to that effect.
I don't think that's right.
Oh, never mind.
Let's go kick some American butt.
Come on, lads!
(whirring)
- Mom says animals talking
is theoretically possible
because we've all got language
centers in our brains,
even animals.
- Hey!
- Sorry.
Ours are on the left except
in left-handed people,
they're on the right.
But everyone's got a language center.
- Oh, you probably have two or three.
- Whoa.
- Yo kid, got your dad's wheels here.
- [Sherlock Bones] Oh, you
can just leave it outside.
- Sherlock, what are you doing?
- Oh yeah, you sure?
- Aye, my dad will be right back.
- Okay, here.
Take the page for me, will ya?
Dog friendly?
- Uh huh.
- Yeah?
Where's your accent from, kid?
- Scotland.
- Oh yeah?
Watch them play soccer on TV.
What a bunch of bozos!
(growls)
Thought you said your dog was friendly!
- This isn't my dog.
- Sherlock.
What are you doing?
- Get in.
- Sherlock!
- I'm driving.
- It's against the law!
- Billy, there's no law against
dogs driving golf carts.
How old are you?
- 47.
- See?
- Come on.
Right.
- Sherlock!
- What, what?
- [Emma] Your legs are too short.
How are you gonna reach the pedal?
- I'm not, you are.
Go on, lass.
- Alright!
- Oh no!
- Put the pedal to the metal, lass, go.
Oh, this is fun.
Relax.
Enjoy yourselves.
That's a bonny good view from up here.
- Left, left, turn left!
(honks)
- Mellow out.
- Watch out!
(screams)
(honks)
Whoa!
Okay, no, stop!
- [Sherlock Bones] Relax,
I got it under control.
Now which one's the brake?
- All of 'em.
(honks)
- Hello.
- Right turn, right!
(screams)
- Right, everyone out.
- Go, go!
Go, go, go away, go, go, go, go away, go.
Get out of here, get out of here.
(groans)
(screams)
(slaps)
- Mr. William Anderson,
I'm here to see your
remote control turtle.
- Oh!
(groans)
(dramatic music)
- That's the dog.
Keeps finding us.
- It's a police dog.
That's what he's supposed to do.
Go back to the boat.
- You found Mike?
- [Sherlock Bones] Aye.
- [Billy] You can smell Mike from here?
- Wow!
Which boat is he on?
- No idea.
- Great.
- Oh, get down!
- Ow!
(gentle music)
- But how are we gonna get past Dad?
Ow!
- Another idea.
Alright, he didn't see us.
Billy.
Lighten up.
- I feel stupid.
- Billy!
There are people around.
(sighs)
- Ha, to think you look stupid.
♪ Row, row, row your boat
gently down the stream ♪
♪ Merrily, merrily, merrily ♪
- Can you smell anything yet?
- Hey, keep rowing!
(humming)
- Look, it's the man in the casino.
Ow!
(dramatic music)
(squirts)
Ow!
- Shh.
And let me tell the police.
No one believes you.
- Hey!
- Hey, hey, what are you doing?
He's not yours!
- He is now.
- Let him go!
- Get out of here, kid,
before I have you arrested.
- Hey, let him go!
Come back.
Let him go!
No!
Hey, come back!
We need help!
Can you come right away, please?
He's kidnapping my dog!
- Sorry, boys, he got off the boat.
- That's not his dog!
- He's a good guard dog but
he's not real fond of kids.
- I know how he feels.
- Captain Gavin Keene, Ice Breaker,
Marina Del Rey, Los Angeles.
- I'll see he doesn't get loose again.
(whines)
- Dad, Dad!
They kidnapped Sherlock Bones.
Now they have Sherlock and Mike.
- Billy.
- No, really, they took him over there.
- Where's the Turt?
- Out there somewhere.
- Okay.
- Dad, this man had a rope
and he lassoed Sherlock Bones
and he put on this fake
collar with this fake name.
- What do you mean fake name?
How do you know it wasn't his dog?
The dog slipped his collar and ran away
and his owner caught him and
put his collar back on again.
- He didn't.
- How do you know?
If you told me, I wouldn't believe you?
Emma!
He must have bumped into a
rock and turned himself off.
- How do you know it's a he?
- Well...
- You tell him?
- He thinks I'm a liar.
- Billy.
- What part's he having a problem with?
- Well...
- The policeman tied up in the casino?
- Well.
- The dog talking, right?
- How about the time the
policeman gave him his ID
and he dropped it in the sea?
- Well.
- Be right back.
- Billy, you can still
come here for vacations.
Your mom is right.
Maybe I am a bad influence.
- I had a first grade teacher like that.
- Oh!
- What are they saying?
- Warm up the engines.
(mumbles)
Got to go forwards and
sideways to get out to sea.
The dog?
Oh, the dog.
- They're leaving and they're
gonna throw the dog overboard.
- But how does he know?
- Gunter can lip read.
- I bet they're gonna
drown the policeman too.
- Come on.
- So what do you have here?
- Well, I got this for you.
It's a dog leash.
It's a really nice one.
I bought one for my great aunt Dorothy.
Just clip that on there.
- Right.
- And then there's this cord
and it's got this button.
- Oh, you're going to
have such a good time.
Go, Caesar, off you go.
Wonderful.
- You don't wanna do that.
Push the, you gotta hold the button--
(honking)
- Hey.
Hey!
What do I do with these things, huh?
- Alright, I see, alright, alright.
Oh, oh, there he goes, Caesar.
Oh no, no.
Caesar!
- Officer, quick!
We need your help.
(thuds)
- Come on.
Excuse me, but I think you should know
we have called the police
and you should save
yourself a lot of trouble
by letting the policeman and the dog go
and giving yourself up.
(smacks)
Ow!
- Sorry.
- I'll be fine.
I'll just look after Caesar.
- Dad, how far does the
Turt work underwater?
- 100 feet?
Why?
I think I get it!
- Yeah.
- Hey!
- Oh, sorry.
Come on!
- Men.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
(dramatic music)
- [Captain] Good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen...
(gasps)
- See, you're not really blind!
- No, that was my twin brother.
- Did you know I used to be
a professional ice skater?
- Yes, I think I did.
- It's all balance.
- Can you drive a--
(barking)
- I don't know what does what.
- Forward, to the head.
(barks)
(growls)
- Hey, dog!
- Ow!
- Shh.
- I think I'm getting the hang of it!
- Just hang on.
- Turn, turn!
- Uh, turning!
Hold on!
- Shh.
(panting)
- Hey, hey!
(shouts)
(laughs)
- Alright, keep going!
- Behind you!
- Come on, come on.
Grab the rope.
Hold it steady.
Mind now, here I come.
Give me the oars.
Row, row.
- I can't!
We'll go round in circles.
- Well...
Wait.
(shouts)
(beeping)
- Row, row, quick, he's getting closer.
Row!
- If this is as fast as you
can go, we're dead doo-doo.
- [Mike] Yeah, well, I
don't see you rowing.
- [Sherlock Bones] Come on, come on!
- Row, row!
Help!
(scrapes)
Sherlock!
Over here!
(calm music)
- Yeah, alright, we did it, yeah!
- Hey!
Yay!
- You did great, you got him, Dad!
You did great!
We did it!
(shouts)
- Mom, Mom.
Over here, Mom.
- Hang on, I'm coming.
Give you a hand.
I'm so proud of you guys.
You were great.
- Where's Sherlock?
Come on, come on.
Come on, buddy.
That's it.
There we are.
There we go.
(coughing)
- Can he swim?
- Probably not.
- Who's that?
- Mom.
- But who's that, Dad?
- [Emma] Not yet.
(dog barking)
- Just thought I'd say thanks very much.
Thought I was a goner there for a minute.
Ow!
Sherlock!
He doesn't like all that
sensitive emotional stuff.
Well...
Ta-ra.
Bye.
Thanks.
Cheers.
Come on, mate.
- Hey.
Are you not going to say goodbye?
Well?
- Bye, Sherlock.
(gentle music)
(MultiCom Jingle)