I'm alone, as agreed.
And the money?
It's all here.
Your theft has caused something
of an international incident.
The Japanese government
is blaming the British.
Good.
And of course you have your own
personal deal with our Japanese friend.
The hell with him.
I believe in rewarding the
highest bidder, Mr. King.
Any problem in customs?
They never better than I.
So beautiful.
No wonder people have killed for it.
Don't mind, I'm in a bit of a hurry.
Move and you're a dead man.
Lay it flat.
A knife.
You're going to clean some fish.
You could have handle that better.
Get my money.
Get it.
- Hurry.
- Filthy.
Okay Doe, let's see you got change for 20?
You don't change for 20.
Come on lady.
We'Re close.
I just need a second.
I've just arrived in town and I'm
here to make you a lot of money.
I'm a photographer and I have
worked all over the country.
I don't think we're going to.
I can easily clear 500 night
that is at the place of crowded
which looks like a pretty
happening place to me.
Your 25% of five isn't really that bad.
I don't think it's going
to really work out.
- 35.
- We're not really interested.
Ok, 50.
Come on, it's not a girl's got.
To make a living.
Lady. We're not interested.
Nowhere closed.
Sebastian.
Do you work here?
I could really use some help.
Cameron King.
Catherine, Tracy,
Katie to everyone of my third
grade teacher and me.
Catherine's a beautiful name.
Tourists really like those.
So what do you think?
Well, I think we could use
another pretty face around here.
Why don't you come back
in a couple of hours?
- We'll be open.
- Great.
You guys have changed parts.
Near the back door.
Down there.
What are you doing?
She's just what we need.
Joe, there you are.
Aren't you going to congratulate me?
I just got a job.
My day is made. Where's my money?
Give me cheap places for money.
Are you sure about your information?
Yes.
My source is very close to King
and the casinos.
On the third floor, the entire
third floor is a secret club.
Casino girls, private rooms.
Where's the entrance?
Behind that door there's an elevator.
Goes from the ground to the second floor.
Casino guests are given
special poker chips.
Show a chip and suddenly
there's a third floor.
Exactly.
Can we get a chip?
No way.
King hands them out himself.
Well, then we'll start by getting
into the nightclub, tomorrow night
and we're something stylish.
You do don't have change for 20?
I'll be right back.
Hi. Do you change for 20?
No, it's okay, really.
I worked here.
Yeah, right. Back of the line.
- No, I really do.
- Back at the line.
Look, I'm a photographer.
I spoke with Mr.
King just this afternoon
and he hired me on a spot.
Can you believe it?
I don't think it's of my talent.
I think the guy like me.
Although it kind of always happens to me.
My mother used to always tell me,
look, kind people like you.
There's no reason not
to take advantage of it.
You have this huge gift
and you should use it.
All right, you can go in.
Just please shut up.
Take her in.
Can I sit up here?
Sure.
- First night?
- Yes.
Can I have anything without an umbrella?
Turn it on.
The job, huh?
All right.
Do a club soda with an olive wave.
You're really cute.
What's your name?
Catherine. Katie.
To anybody I like.
Yeah.
So what do I call you?
Well, we'll see. And you?
What's your name?
Spencer.
Or Spence.
To anyone who likes me.
Well, see around, Spencer.
Great crowd. What's that?
I said, great crowd.
We're not interested, Manhurt.
Don't be rude, Leonard.
Don't be so rude.
We're still not interested.
Come on, Leonard. You don't
have to...
You don't have to take it.
Stay quiet and lay flat.
You'll be fine.
Can you keep a secret?
I hope so, because I
have a wonderful secret.
I'm going to let you look,
but you have to promise
me not to tell anybody.
What do you want?
Your expertise.
I want you to examine it again.
I want you to be absolutely sure.
I'm sure.
Thank you.
You are fortunate to have
done such rap beauty.
God.
Straight up.
Mr. King. Have some time
tonight. I'd like to meet with him.
- What for?
- Have a proposition for me.
What kind of a proposition?
Well, I'd really like to share it with
you, but I'd rather tell him directly.
Look, he's a busy man.
Anything you tell him comes to me.
Anyway, don't worry about it.
I'll flag him down later.
Do and it'll be your job.
You go through me.
So how are you doing this evening?
Nothing for me.
He's a little deaf.
So would you guys come here a lot?
No, thank you.
Nothing for me either.
What about her?
Who is she?
Takes photographs.
Customers.
Selfish tacky keychain.
Now, how could she help the case?
Evidence for warrant
photographs could do the trick.
The pearls. Rightfully mine.
I arranged its acquisition.
Or perhaps you should have
been more generous with Kern.
A million dollars is a pretty good profit.
Due to mr.
Kern's, unfortunately, is drowning.
The profit is all for you.
The pearl is going to be auctioned
off to the highest bidder.
I'm here to invite you
to that auction, nothing more.
This is an artifact of my people.
It is rightfully mine.
- 4 million.
- What?
4 million will get you a private auction.
That is absurd.
Let's see with the auction.
Lieutenant Victor Martinez.
- Detective George Williams, Spy Squad.
- Yes.
You work at one Lombard.
- Yeah.
- Seems there's been some complaints.
Someone working there hasn't
been paying their cab fares.
Oh, you're nervous.
I thought you were my man, George.
On these walls.
Yeah.
We could forget this
whole cavity complaint.
Or a little help from you.
Can you take your corner and just
put it like, over there?
We have an inside source that tells us
that there is illegal gambling
going on the third floor.
I didn't know there was a third floor.
Miss Tracy, we need your help.
How much does it pay?
Can you do less?
We were hoping you do it because
it is the right thing to do.
Well, what exactly is it I have to do?
In order to get a warrant.
In order to get a warrant,
we need physical evidence.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
My photograph.
Photograph?
So why don't you guys use
your own inside guy for this?
He's afraid to get too involved.
We protect our informants.
Yeah, but do you pay them?
Well, we can offer $200.
Oh, that's a little cheap,
don't you think, guys?
$200 on delivery of the photographs.
Will you do it?
I don't think I can get into this
whole Nancy Drew shtick.
This isn't a game as Tracy,
Cameron King is a very ruthless man,
and he won't take too kindly to someone
trying to get evidence on him.
I think I can handle Cameron King.
So what do I have to do?
- Why are you there?
- A little further.
Aren't you just so it
comes with my criminal.
Come on.
I'll take you up.
This place always puts me behind.
Yeah.
You're new, aren't you?
Is this elevator always this slow?
You've never been up here before?
Of course I have.
Normally a little close.
She told me it was okay.
No, I was just trying to help fast.
How did you get up here so fast?
Terribly more but color skin.
- Hey, babe. How's it going?
- Better.
I'm off at three people.
No.
I can't help but think you could
be doing something work related.
Nothing wrong with bettering one's
relationship with coworker, Sebastian.
In fact, I think this is a good time.
It's no camp cam come here often?
Well, hello there.
I'm sorry, sir.
That's okay, Sebastian.
I could use an escort this evening.
So what is it that you want?
What do you mean?
Catherine, I built a career on knowing
people, and you want something.
And you obviously hired me for reasons
other than my photograph skills, right?
Yes. You may have made a career out
of it, Cameron, but I had installed a birth.
It's called women's intuition.
Well, it doesn't take a genius
to understand my motives.
Meaning what?
But you're attracted to me now.
Why couldn't my mother be this man?
Somehow I don't believe
they're that simple.
I'm not as complicated as you may think.
You.
Perhaps not,
but I still haven't figured you out yet.
Nor are you.
But I will.
- Hey, Johnny, can you give me a hand?
- What's up?
I think I pulled my back.
You didn't get that case
of absolute backup for me?
Absolutely.
Did you get it?
Yeah.
Can you just put it
on the bar there for me?
Sure.
Man. I really appreciate it.
Thanks.
Oh, it's an absolute pleasure.
¿Más cartas señor King?
Una más.
¿Qué haces aquí?
Quiero hablar con el señor King.
Hablarás, no te preocupes.
Mr. King.
Up now. Sebastian.
What?
I found the new bartender up here.
How'd you get up here?
I don't know how it happens.
I must have dropped my keys.
- No, I stole them.
- Why?
Because I wanted to meet with you.
I want to be a dealer.
And Sebastian wouldn't
arrange a meeting for us.
How did you know about my little facility?
Good dealer knows where the games are.
How good are you?
Good enough to know who's counting
cards in your group over there.
Yeah. Who?
Do I get to be a dealer?
Who the guy in the end of the blue suit?
Well, he's not very good.
He's $2,000 in the hole.
Exactly.
He gets close, but he never hits.
Throws suspicion off.
What's the point?
The point is he's got a partner.
I didn't see enough to
I didn't see enough to know exactly who it
is, but it's someone who's
probably making stupid bets.
Some miss.
No one takes them seriously,
but then he hits.
And when he hits, he hits big.
And everybody thinks he's lucky.
- How do they communicate?
- His chips.
He ranges his chips.
- Johnny, take...
- Spence.
Spence, downstairs.
I'll talk to you tomorrow
when you come to work.
Thanks.
Sorry about the keys. Shut up.
That little stunt you pulled it in.
Made me look like a jerk.
I had to see him. What?
Would you just shut up?
You're not still mad at me?
I'll just head up for you.
All right.
Come on.
I want the pearl.
Is he going?
Well, apparently your boss's
calendar was inaccurate.
Remind him that the auction is Friday.
Get him out of here.
You have promise.
What do you want?
- I'm here to pick you up.
- For?
I don't know. Mr. King
wants to take you on a picnic.
I'll be right out.
Don't.
Hi.
So, what are we doing?
I thought it was a good opportunity for
you to know me outside of the workplace.
Any objection?
Well, why don't you ask me
again in about an hour?
Why then?
Because I know you better then.
Like it.
Yeah.
But what?
It just doesn't seem like you can.
This park actually has a lot
of personal memories for me.
You see the house here?
I grew up in that house.
And.
I only bring special people here.
Oh, good. I'm famous.
I love this park.
When I was a kid,
I used to come here and daydream all
the time about what I was
going to do with my life.
There aren't any sandwiches?
Sandwiches?
Oh, I don't mean to be picky or anything,
can, but there doesn't seem to be
anything in this basket resembling lunch.
Well, I did tell Sebastian
to pack something romantic.
So this place reminds you of your boyhood?
Yeah, it does.
In fact, it almost looks exactly
like it did when I was a kid.
Except for the statue.
It's lovely.
It's really pretty.
That's st. Michael, the Archangel.
I gave it to the city.
Kim, you don't seem like the kind of guy
that would donate a saint to the city.
I don't?
Well, maybe it was because I
was educated by the Jesuits.
I bet you look really cute in the outfit.
Didn't those nuns ever teach you the
importance of the basic four food groups?
Well, I'm sorry about the sandwiches.
It's not like Sebastian
to disappoint me like this.
Sebastian?
What's the deal with you two, anyway?
Well, he makes sure that I get
whatever I want.
Well, that must be nice.
Whatever you want.
Yes.
Whatever I want.
What do you want, Catherine?
How about a cheeseburger?
How are things progressing?
Just fine.
I have them wrapped
around my little finger.
What do you mean?
I mean I think he's going
to take me upstairs tonight.
Really?
How do you know?
Because he asked me or told me to dress up
tonight and that he wanted
to show me something.
This could be it.
Are you ready?
How does it work?
Aim like this, press like that, and voila.
You have evidence.
Sit for a judge.
Now, you better move along.
I have to look my best.
And be careful.
I mean it's.
Formation has just arrived from Berlin.
Oh, excellent.
Excellent.
Now our slate is filled.
Everything going okay with the woman?
Catherine?
I find her refreshing.
But this isn't going to last long.
In the meantime,
I'm going to enjoy the sport.
We have a little problem.
What's that?
Our friends in Cairo are having second
thoughts about bringing
cash to the auction.
Well, that's been the arrangement
since the beginning.
Yes, sir, that is what I told.
¿And?
It seems that your decision,
the current incident, has cast some doubt
on our reputation.
Damage, sebastian. Well, maybe the
body shouldn't have been found so easily.
Yes, sir.
- Arrange a meeting with him.
- What?
As soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
And let's not let it go as bad as we
did with her Japanese friend Died.
Yes, sir.
Don't worry especially.
By Friday night,
you're going to be a rich man.
Okay, boys, clean it up.
A lady's present.
Good evening, Ms.
Tracy.
Apparently the shopping went well.
Yes.
Can you guys kind of be careful
with this wiring thing?
I have to return it in the morning.
You should have a code word
in case something goes wrong.
How about help?
I don't think so.
How about money?
You should have no trouble working
that into the conversation.
What are my favorite topics?
We need you to zip your gallons.
I don't have a zipper.
Yeah. Places.
Single? Dancing.
You're late.
No, I'm right on time.
Actually, sebastian, could you be
a deer and run and go find Cam?
He's kind of expecting me.
Don't push your luck. Mr.
King.
Sebastian....
You get more beautiful
every time I see you.
Thank you.
You've made it sound so important.
I wanted to look my best.
Come with me.
I thought I would show
you a part of my world.
What is it?
That's what gives me the power
to live life as I chose.
Do you run a bordello?
Not quite.
So, what do you think?
It's wonderful.
If you like it.
It must be a gold mine.
Catherine, you're a woman
after my own heart.
It really is amazing.
I'm glad you think that.
I was afraid you might react differently.
That you might even turn me in.
It's fabulous.
So how much do you pull in cash?
She mentioned money?
No, she said cash.
Did we specifically say money,
or do you think she means any
reference to legal tender?
Money.
The word is money.
We've become quite well known now among
the world's so called rich and famous.
And we're practically
impervious to any legal action.
Really?
Sir, may I have a word with you, please?
Catherine, could you give
us a moment, please?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
You're making the bucks, huh?
Bucks?
You haven't done much of this, have you?
What's happening?
What's going on?
Shit. It's got her.
You're the one prepared to move in?
Lady's a born gambler, not me.
I don't like games of chance.
By majoring sailor.
I hate this job.
Was bringing you the final telegram and I
noticed that it's very
beautiful, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Beauty is a dangerous thing.
Can lead one to make unwise decisions.
Does that advice apply
to the girl as well, too?
Shame.
But I have that situation under control.
Naturally.
So, how'd they turn out?
Come on in.
See if you thought.
Nice.
Very nice.
I'd say those are worth $200.
I'd say it's a good start.
I don't like the sounds of that.
What Lieutenant Martinez
was saying, Miss Tracy?
That we'd have a much
better case if we had more.
Meaning. I don't get my $200?
No.
Which means that there's
more where that came from.
Subject has just left building
and is heading west along the wharf.
Follow that car.
What?
I've been trying to say
that my whole life.
Okay.
Subject is now heading north on Lombard.
He is completely oblivious to my presence.
- You're losing them.
- I am naughty.
- He's right there.
- You're obviously new with this, aren't you?
Lady, I've been driving cab
long and you've been alive.
And you're still so sweet.
Fred.
No, no. Hold on, Fred.
- Meat is running.
- Okay, I just want to watch for 1 minute
Special people.
What's that?
Nothing, Fred.
Just quartering the line.
I heard once.
So you private Dick or something?
No, Fred, I work for the police.
Undercover.
I had a cousin once who was an informant.
Made plenty of money, too.
Till Tony the Torch put
one through his ear.
No, it's now going to be an auction.
Bidding starts at 1 million, cash.
You told my employer that he would
have exclusive bidding privileges.
Well, the situation changed once I heard
there was so much widespread interest.
You will not be pleased.
Then you don't have to come.
This gives you a spot at the table.
What are they doing here?
Who is this guy, Mob?
I don't know yet, Fred.
I don't know.
Hey, he's leaving.
You want us to follow?
What's the damage so far, Fred?
375.
Can you break a 20?
Exact change only. Perfect.
Keep driving.
Come on, lady.
3 bolws for a buck.
What do you got to lose?
A buck?
Come on, lady, I ain't got any business.
Three for $0.50.
How much for one ball?
A quarter?
Now, look, aim low.
Your center of gravity is
kind of right about here.
Summer job, coney island.
She didn't pay me.
Well, what do you got?
Well, good evening to you, too.
Sorry.
Well, I followed him around today.
Didn't get much.
But I did see something
kind of suspicious.
What?
I saw them at the club first,
and then today they were falling King.
- What else?
- Do you recognize them?
Well, that's it.
You called us out here for that?
Well, I thought you might want
to pull them in for questioning.
The photos did the trick.
We're going to get our warrant.
Will you be going upstairs by the
elevator or the secret entrance?
Secret entrance?
The day I tried to sneak upstairs in the
elevator, Sebastian beat me upstairs.
Now, how could that be?
Unless there's another entrance
and you know where it is?
No, but I do have a pretty good idea.
And with a little incentive.
Unless your inside man can handle it.
All right, 200.
Deal.
Bye.
She's lying.
What's rhe secret entrance crap.?
There is no secret entrance.
She's just trying to soak
a few more dollars out of you.
I knew it.
I haven't got much time.
The raid must happen this Friday.
We can swing that.
We have enough for a warrant.
Why Friday?
He's planning on leaving the country.
That's all I can say.
Good evening, Joe.
You just hold off on celebrating.
Excuse me.
Have you seen Mr.
Kim or Sebastian?
No.
Hold it.
You told me that I would
have your check today.
Well, that's too late.
I leave the country today after the wall.
If you want this club,
you will get that check here today.
Oh, Sebastian.
You scared me.
Did you know that there's
an old stairway back there?
How far did you go?
Well, I didn't.
I just kind of stepped in.
It's too creepy for me.
How did you find it?
Well, I was reaching in to get something
and my sleep got caught on this insigna
right here and just
clicked open like that.
Do you know what's back there?
What are you doing here this early?
I had to pick up some
films to get developed.
Am I doing something wrong?
This little act may work with Mr.
King, but not with me.
I've seen through your charade
from the beginning and it's time
to put a stop to it right now.
Sebastian, wait.
Look, I know we got off
under the wrong foot.
Look, it's my fault, okay?
Shut up.
Can we just bury the hatches, so to speak?
Just shut up.
Slick little manipulations.
I got to straddle the breath
out of you right now.
Squeeze.
You and your devious schemes don't exist.
Sebastian.
What?
We're at a sour mix.
I'll take care of it in a minute.
I have something else to do first.
Thank you.
Too early.
We have to talk.
What is it now, Sebastian?
Why is she still here?
- Her job is finished.
- Calm down.
-What's the problem?
- Calm down?
She's snooping around.
She can ruin everything.
She's inquisitive.
You really can't be serious.
She's fun. I like her.
It's as simple as that.
You think she feels
the same way about you?
She turned. She went to
the police, for crying out loud.
Well, that's probably why I like her.
She's got a bit of larceny in her heart.
Let's stick to the plan.
It's time to get rid of her.
Sebastian, I'll be needing an extra ticket
for the plane flight tomorrow night.
Or maybe I should just give her yours.
Catherine?
You're alone?
Do you know what your Lurch did to me?
Well, Sebastian can be
a little hot headed.
He tried to kill me.
No, he tried to scare you.
Did a really good job.
Why do you keep him around anyway?
Because he knows how to scare people.
Do you have a passport?
Why?
Do you hungry?
Yeah.
Pretty fancy place.
Yes, it is.
You haven't traveled around much ever?
Yes, I outdroke tears on the back.
You did.
I'm leaving the country tomorrow night
and I'd like you to go with me.
Where are you going?
Where do you want?
Europe, asia?
Wherever you'd like.
Oh... Cameron.
I don't think you'd be very happy with me.
I'm not the sophisticated worldly type.
Well, that's exactly why I like you.
You need someone more like you.
You are like me, Catherine.
You're exactly like me.
You grab everything
the world has to offer.
Which I like.
Well, yes, we do have summer techniques
and I do enjoy
using the one a connoisseur.
Well, thank you.
I want you to think about it seriously.
I think I'm very flattered.
You got it. Yeah.
The auction is at eleven.
Vice will probably bust
in sometime after that.
I can't wait to see
the look on King's mug.
Let's not get cocky yet.
That guy is a slippery one.
Anything else?
No, but I probably won't
see you beforehand.
So wish everyone good luck for me.
Will do. And Mick.
- Yeah.
- Be careful.
Your weekly rent due. Hi.
Listen, I was going to stop
and tell you that I'm moving out.
Well, maybe I should make an inspection.
What's that? Shit?
Oh, I took a livery of kind
of spruce enough place a bit.
What was wrong with it?
- Well, nothing, but...
- That'll cost you.
What?
Because of me, now you can turn around and
rewrite this dump for twice as much money.
I should bill you.
You just kissed your
security deposit goodbye.
You didn't clean the kitchen.
When everything is clear,
I'll knock on the panel.
Are you fully prepared?
I'm always fully prepared.
Well, that's the way it should be.
Give me the key to the elevator
and you know where
to receive your payment?
Sure do, if Sebastian does his job.
Yeah.
Right this way.
All right, we're going through the front.
The first team will work
on empty in the nightclub.
At the same time,
the second team hits the casino on the
third floor through the fire escape.
Any questions? Yeah.
What do I do?
What the hell are you doing here?
Don't you guys want to know
about the secret passage?
Our source says there isn't one.
And he should know better than you.
You better get her out of here.
Yeah, you better get out of here.
Good luck, fella.
Welcome.
Perhaps you know your fellow bitters.
May I offer you some champagne?
No, thank you.
Can we begin now?
We're waiting for one more.
The flight from Marrakash has
been delayed due to a rainstorm.
How long our car is going to pick him up?
He'll be here within a half hour.
We have a slight delay.
You are explicit.
The auction begins precisely at eleven.
Well, he can't be held responsible
for a thunderstorm, can he?
He should have considered
that when he arranged his flight.
We'll wait until 1130
and the auction will begin.
Whether he has arrived or not.
I do not like this one.
Beat, instruct the cashier to give each
of our guests $1,000 worth of chips.
Yes, sir.
I did not come here to play casino games.
I agree.
This is becoming
a monumental waste of time.
That's a goal.
Just a moment.
You should at least hold
it before you leave.
Hey, babe.
Cole.
She likes me. Oh, hey.
We got a winner.
14 red.
14 red. No.
Sorry.
Welcome to Kings.
Ransom table closed.
Sit down.
What are you looking at?
Your head.
How'd you get it to go back like that?
It's a combination of brokering,
mousse and pure virgin olive oil.
My cousin Joey Palucci invented it.
- Joey Palucci?
- Yeah.
You mean Potato Head paluchi.
- You know him?
- Know?
We both did a hit on the same guy once.
I heard about that.
Tony Rocko, right? Yeah.
Lucky for your cousin, I was there.
That ain't what he told me.
Jason One, this is Tango Seven.
We're at the location.
Stand by for instruction.
What are you doing in here?
Looking for Cam.
In his desk?
You know, you're right.
Cam's much bigger than that.
I didn't know that's.
Just a casino.
I don't think so.
You're coming with me.
Black Four.
Close, but no cigar.
I'll check with Sebastian
about our late arrival.
You take over for a while.
I'm dual breaking.
If I don't take a break now,
I'm going to fill my socks.
Thank you very much.
It is very funny that you would
mention imani was having one up.
I had a similar experience in Wagadougu.
No shit.
Yes, shit.
Johnny, I need you in my office.
Yes, sir.
Police Department.
Everyone, please move to the nearest
exit in an orderly fashion.
Open the fire escape. Come on.
I know. I wait there for rage.
You better clear out.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford one, one will
be appointed by the state officers.
Stay with your groups. Let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Stay back. Can you move them
back? Let's make some room here.
Let's go, please.
Quickly.
Is king here. No.
Have you seen King?
No, he's not here.
He's not here. Please.
Is king in here?
Has anyone seen King?
- Yeah, someone said he was downstairs.
- Well, let's go.
Go ahead.
I'm going to finish up here.
They need you downstairs,
so I'll take care of this.
I don't think Mr.
King would like to know he's
dealing with a common thiefman.
I just thought I'd
take my money while it's here.
You'll get it precisely
when we said you'd get it.
When we are free and clear.
Now, let's stick to the plan.
Okay?
Looks like the boss got away.
He'll turn up.
I'm going to head back to the precinct.
Can you finish up in there?
Sure.
Everything is clear.
Find it there.
Sorry, Johnny.
Sebastian.
I thought we had a better relationship.
You've been treating me like dirt.
What did you expect?
I never expect too much from anyone.
Don't move.
- What the hell are you doing?
- FBI.
Put your hands behind your head.
You got to be kidding.
You're under arrest for the theft
of the Emperor's pearl,
for the murder of Tommy Kern,
and now for Sebastian Antonelli.
I don't suppose you'd be good enough
to tell us where the Emperor's pearl is.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Thank you.
He's gone.
Looks like we're in the clear.
Yeah.
All right, all right.
Let's not take any chances. Hurry up. Search
the room. He couldn't have gotten far.
Where's Bird?
Right here.
Oh, what happened?
All all right.
Right. Don't worry about it.
Come on, come on.
All right, let's get going.
So where's the pearl?
We have to leave without it.
What?
Not in your life.
Come on, hon.
We've got nearly 10 million here in cash.
Let's not push our luck.
Honey, the whole reason why I want
to pull it off is because of the pearl.
Okay, a few more minutes,
but then we're leaving.
Where are you going with him?
Hey, I set this bust up.
We have it.
You handle a crowd.
Handled crowd?
Serious shit, man.
No silent shit.
All right, that's it.
Round the guys up.
Let's get out of here. Let's get going.
I'm not going anywhere without that pearl.
No, we're out of time.
Okay, you guys go pack up and I'll
meet you by the car, okay?
All right. But you've got 5 minutes.
Otherwise, we're leaving with or without you.
Deal.
Come here.
Mark, are you all right?
Come on.
What happened?
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's coming around.
Smart. Very smart.
See, Catherine?
We are alike.
You take what you want.
But that's not your name, is it?
No, it's Bert.
Robert Chase.
Catherine Tracy Spencer headburn.
How cute.
I can't believe I was
fooled by a stupid girl.
I can't believe you're going
to shoot me over a little money.
I don't like to be toyed with.
Don't be so innocent, Cameron.
You used me as much as I did you.
Know what's really amazing?
I actually liked you.
My mommy stuff.
I don't give a damn about your mother.
I want my pearl.
Put it in the bag.
Goodbye Catherine.
Island is really paying off.
Hold it.
Turn around. Catherine.
Look, like I told you before, Cam,
I didn't mean to hurt any well,
just got a little out of here.
Turn around.
Twice in one night?
Come on, Mrs.
Chase.
The pearl.
Hold it Cameron.
I'll shoot it.
You won't shoot me.
Oh, yeah?
That's where you're rolling.
Wait a minute.
Hi, I'm Catherine Tracy.
And I liked a little gift
for Lieutenant Martinez in the alley.
Could you make sure he gets that?
Thank you, guys.
Come on, boys and girls.
We got ourselves the King's ransom.
Best one yet.
- What's next?
- Whoa.
Not so fast.
You must enjoy the food of your labor first.
14 or twelve well what?
Well, aren't you going
to critique my performance?
You always do.
As a matter of fact you did make it a lot
more complicated than it needed to be.
Just like the royal jewels in Banca.
I just wanted to make a simple switch.
Like it was my fault the prince
wanted me for his fifth wife.
People like me, they always have you.
Interpol.
- Oh, for heaven's sake,
- where's the Emperor's pearl?
Excuse me, but I don't understand what...
Well, I have it right here.
We were hoping to return
it for the reward.
That's the property of the Royal Museum.
There's no reward.
Well, here, take it.
Really, we don't want any problems.
We have a plane to catch.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
- You still don't remember them, do you?
- No.
Who the hell are they?
They were that nice couple who tried to
outcon us in Amsterdam in 1985, I think.
Remember.
The Golden Tulip?
Right, the roulette ball.
The Golden Tulip.
- You were a flirt on that one too?
- I'm sorry, Mr. ambassador.
- A flirt?
- Yeah.
I use what I have to my advantage.
So I've learned to do
with the bad yourself.
You learn to use what I've done.