[ Computer Voice ]
LOCK SYNC, SECTOR 43.
ALL PRISONERS RETURN TO CELLS.
PREPARE FOR LOCK-DOWN.
EARTH DATE: 1/1 2065.
YEAH. HAPPY NEW YEAR.
SHIFT'S OVER.
LOCK 'EM AND LEAVE 'EM.
SEE YOU BACK
IN 16 HOURS.
[ Footsteps ]
[ Mumbling Voices ]
[ Footsteps Continue ]
SO LONG, SCREW.
[ Gagging, Groaning ]
OH !
- IT'S TIME.
- LET'S GO THEN.
KNOWLEDGE.
STRENGTH.
JUDGMENT DAY
NEEDS SEVEN ANGELS.
COVER HIM UP.
[ Beeping ]
[ Inhaling, Exhaling ]
[ Computer Voice ]
ALL LEVELS HAVE CONFIRMED
FINAL WASTE DISCHARGE...
INTO REFUSE CHAMBER.
SEALING ALL GARBAGE CHUTES
FROM PRISON INTERIOR.
L4 REFUSE TRANSPORT...
AT 94.3 PERCENT CAPACITY.
SCHEDULE JETTISON
IN T-MINUS TEN MINUTES.
[ Beeping ]
YOU OFF YET ?
NO. I GOTTA LAUNCH
THIS LOAD. YOU ?
YEAH. GOT A DATE
WITH A DREAM GIRL.
HOW MUCH ?
ZERO PERCENT DOWN,
NO PAYMENTS TILL MIDYEAR.
- [ Sighs ]
- SHE IS STATE OF THE ART.
THINK LIKE, UH,
I COULD BORROW HER NEXT WEEK ?
YOU GOT A CIGARETTE ?
HEY, MAN, A PACK OF THOSE
WILL GET YOU FIVE YEARS...
BACK ON EARTH.OH, WELL.
LIKE, WHAT ARE THEY
GONNA DO, MAN ?
SEND US TO PRISON ?
[ Laughing ]
[ Computer Voice ]
NAVIGATIONAL SIGNAL FROM
MOONBASE RELAY STATION...
LOCKED ON.
INITIATING
PRE-LAUNCH SEQUENCE.[ Beeping ]
SOMEDAY THESE THINGS
ARE GONNA KILL ME.
WHAT THE--
[ Computer Voice ]
L4 REFUSE TRANSPORT
READY FOR LAUNCH.
LAUNCH SEQUENCE ENGAGED.
CLOSING POD DOORS.
OKAY, I'M COMIN'.
TRANSMITTING
TRAJECTORY COORDINATES.
POD IS SEALED FOR TRANSPORT.
LAUNCH IN T-MINUS THREE,
TWO, ONE.
GOOD-BYE.
[ Breathing Sound ]
[ Woman's Whispering Voice ]
JOHN.
[ Computer Voice ]
OXYGEN LEVEL CRITICAL.
RETURN TO BASE.
LIFE-SUPPORT FAILURE
IN 15 SECONDS.[ Hyperventilating ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Computer Voice ]
MOONBASE COORDINATES RELAYED...
TO L4 PENITENTIARY
REFUSE TRANSPORT.
CONFIRMATION
OF POD LAUNCH RECEIVED.
ESTIMATED TIME TO ARRIVAL:
26 HOURS AND 13 MINUTES.
BEAUTIFUL.
HEY, DECKERT.
GET THE CREW TOGETHER.
WE GOTTA FINISH CLEARIN'
OUT THAT DROP ZONE.
WE'RE OFF TODAY.
WELL, NOT ANYMORE.
L4'S GOT A DUMP
TOMORROW MORNING.
WE JUST GOT AN
EARTH DROP YESTERDAY.
THIS WAS OUR DAY OFF.
I KNOW, BUT THEY
CHANGED THE SCHEDULE.
WHAT CAN I DO ?
CORPORATE PROMISED THAT WHEN
THEY AUTOMATED THE DROPS,
IT WOULD EASE OUR WORKLOAD.
THIS IS NOT FAIR.LIFE'S NOT FAIR,
DECKERT.
YEAH, YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT
MY TRANSFER REQUEST ?
NOTHING YET.WHAT'S THE HOLDUP ?
I'VE SPENT THREE YEARS
DOING THIS MONKEY WORK.
THE COMPANY OWES ME.
DID YOU MENTION HOW WELL YOU
GET ALONG WITH YOUR CO-WORKERS ?
GOOD MORNING TO YOU TOO.
BEAUTIFUL.
WHAT'D YOU GET ?
IT SAYS,
"EGGS, SUNNY SIDE UP."
TRADE YOU SOME BACON.
ALL RIGHT.
IS IT ME, OR DOES THIS STUFF
TASTE WORSE EVERY DAY ?
[ Bag Crinkling, Ripping ]
I HAVE NEVER EVEN
SEEN THIS COLOR.
HE EXPECTS THE GOOD FOLKS
DOWN AT WTI TO SEND UP SOME
REAL EGGS AT 40 BUCKS A DOZEN.
NO. THE ONLY THING I EXPECT OUT
OF THOSE TIGHTWADS AT CORPORATE
IS A TICKET OUT OF HERE.
SCARF IT DOWN AND SUIT UP.
WE HIT THE SURFACE IN AN HOUR.
- WHAT ?
- YEAH.
THE GOOD FOLKS AT WTI
SLID OUR SCHEDULE AGAIN.
CAN THEY JUST DO THAT ?IT HAPPENS.
TOO MUCH.
DON'T PAY ANY
ATTENTION TO HIM.
HE HASN'T GOT LAID SINCE
SONNY BONO WAS PRESIDENT.
MAKES HIM CRANKY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S WRAP THIS UP
AND GET TO WORK.
LET'S GO.
ARE YOU COMIN' OUT ?
HE'S STILL A LITTLE GREEN, JOHN.
HOW ABOUT I TAKE HIM OUT
AND SHOW HIM THE ROPES ?
NO, WILL.
YOU'RE WITH ME.
JUST STICK WITH MASANI.
HE'S A REAL PRO.
WHERE IS MASANI,
ANYWAY ?
♪♪ [ Rock ]
ARE YOU READY
FOR ME, BABY ?OH, YEAH.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
LOOK AT ME.
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
MY BODY.
MMM.
OHH.
♪♪ [ Rock Continues ]
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
BIG BOY ?
YOU'RE SO BIG AND HARD.
YOU MAKE MY MOUTH WATER.
HEY !
YOU MIND ?
- THEY'RE WAITING FOR YOU
DOWN AT THE LOCK.
- IT'S OUR DAY OFF !
WHAT'S IT GONNA BE, SUGAR ?
HIPS OR LIPS ?
♪♪ [ Rock Continues ]
HEY.
HEY, HOW DID YOU GET BY
BEFORE YOU SNAGGED
THIS PIECE OF HARDWARE ?
YOU KNOW, NORMAL STUFF.
WAIT TILL EVERYBODY FALLS
ASLEEP, SNEAK INTO THEIR CLOSETS
AND JERK OFF IN THEIR BOOTS.
THAT'S A SIZE 11, RIGHT ?
I GOTTA GET OFF THIS ROCK.
HEY, CALL ME OLD-FASHIONED,
BUT I LIKE A WOMAN
WITH A CENTRAL NERVOUS SYSTEM.
YOU'RE JEALOUS.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY !
BE GOOD TO YOUR SUIT, LUCAS,
IT'LL BE GOOD TO YOU.THANKS.
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
PUT DECKERT'S BOOTS ON
BY MISTAKE.
HEY, JUST RELAX OUT THERE.
YOU'RE GONNA HYPERVENTILATE.
GONNA SCREW UP YOUR "O" MIX.
WHAT IF THAT HAPPENS ?BRAIN BURN.
YOU PASS OUT AND DIE.
NO BIG DEAL.
ASK JOHN RUSSELL ABOUT THAT.
HE'S THE EXPERT.
LET'S CUT THE CHATTER,
FOLKS, AND GET INTO
THE LOCK.
OPENING THE INNER HATCH. [ Beeping ]
[ Alarm Buzzes,
Machinery Groans ]
[ Groans Again ]
WTI SKIMPS AGAIN.
YOU KNOW, THIS WHOLE PLACE
IS FALLING APART.
[ Alarm Buzzes ]
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
HANG ON. ALLOW ME.
[ Alarm Stops ]
[ Beeping ]
YOU GOTTA FINESSE IT.
[ Engine Revving ]
HEY, IT'S A BALMY
110 DEGREES...
THIS MORNING
ON THE BIG CHEESE.
THAT'S ABOUT 260...
FOR YOU FAHRENHEIT
OLD-TIMERS, WILL.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY...
LET'S HAUL SOME TRASH...
AND GIVE NEW MEANING
TO THE TERM "FULL MOON" ?
THIS IS GREAT !
I COULD LIFT
FIVE OF THESE !
SIXTEEN PERCENT
OF EARTH G.
YEAH, THE PERKS FROM WORKIN'
ON THE MOON NEVER END.
I COULD SHOT PUT
YOUR MOMMA !
YEAH.
MAYBE EVEN MASANI'S.
I HEARD THAT, DECKERT.
[ Will ]
WILL YOU TWO LUNATICS
BUCKLE DOWN TO WORK ?
[ Lucas ]
WHAT IS THIS STUFF, ANYWAYS ?
WILL, WE GOT SOME
CHEMICAL WASTE HERE.
GONNA TAKE IT OVER TO B-TRENCH.
[ John ]
CHEMICAL ? WHAT ARE THEY
DUMPIN' ON US NOW ?
"ARTI-ZONE."
ARTIFICIAL OZONE.
THEY USED TO USE IT
TO SATELLITE-DUST THE ATMOSPHERE
BACK WHEN I WAS A KID,
BACK BEFORE THE UV SKYGRID
WAS INSTALLED.
[ Lucas ]
DID IT WORK ?
GIVE YOU AN EXTRA FIVE MINUTES
OUTDOORS BEFORE YOUR SKIN
STARTED TO BUBBLE.
HOW LONG YOU BEEN UP HERE ?
THAT WAS EONS AGO.
THEY EVEN HAVE
BLUE SKY AGAIN.I'D LIKE TO SEE THAT SOMEDAY.
LOAD 'EM IN B-TRENCH,
SECTOR 29. YOU COPY ?
YEAH.
TEN-FOUR, GOOD BUDDY.
AH ! AH !
HEY !
AAH ! AAH !
-WHAT HAPPENED ?
-[ Masani ] LUCAS GOT SPLASHED.
AAH !OKAY, OKAY !
RELAX, MAN !
- I'LL BRING HIM BACK
FOR A SCRUB.
- I'LL MEET HIM AT THE LOCK.
[ Will ]
THAT HATCH IS THREE-O AGAIN. [ John ] THE STUFF'S NOT HOT.
HE CAN WAIT TILL YOU COME IN.
I NEED THAT DROP ZONE CLEAR.
[ Masani ]
ARE YOU SURE ?WE'RE ALREADY BEHIND SCHEDULE.
[ Deckert ]
THERE'S A SURPRISE.
IF CORPORATE STOPPED SLIDING--
SAVE YOUR OXYGEN, DECKERT.
IT'S GONNA BE A LONG DAY.
SPEAK OF THE DEVIL.
WE GOT A CALL FROM CORPORATE
AT THE RELAY STATION.
- MAYBE IT'S ABOUT MY TRANSFER--
- NOT NOW, DECKERT.
[ Will ]
COMING THROUGH.
[ Static, Beeping ]
JOHN, GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
YOU'RE LOOKING WELL.
MURDOCH.
I KNOW HOW BUSY YOU ARE, JOHN,
SO I'LL GET RIGHT TO THE POINT.
THIS IS LIEUTENANT COLONEL
CALDECOTT...
FROM THE PENTAGON'S
SPECIAL OPERATIONS DIVISION.
MR. RUSSELL.
[ Murdoch ]
THE COLONEL IS HEADING UP TO
THE COMPOUND FOR AN INSPECTION.
HIS SHUTTLE LEAVES
WITHIN THE HOUR.
I'M SENDING KRUTCHFIELD
ALONG TO ASSIST.
- WHEN DID THE MILITARY START
INSPECTING GARBAGE DUMPS ?
- WE DON'T.
S.O.D.'S HANDLING THIS
AT THE REQUEST OF THE SENATE
APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE.
WHY'S THAT ?
JOHN, JUST BE A SPORT
AND GO ALONG WITH IT, OKAY ?
NOW, I KNOW
YOU CAN DO THAT.
WE'LL BE GOING DARK
UP HERE PRETTY SOON.
YOU MIGHT WANNA WAIT
FOR NEXT DAYLIGHT.
[ Caldecott ]
WHEN'S THAT ?
NEXT LIGHT IS IN 14 DAYS.
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
WE'LL PROCEED AS PLANNED.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.WE'LL BE
WAITING FOR YOU.
FINE, FINE. NOW JOHN,
IF THERE'S NOTHING ELSE--
COME ON !
ASK ABOUT MY TRANSFER.[ Whispering ]
DECKERT.
UH, YEAH, WE HAVE
A TRANSFER REQUEST PENDING.
NAME IS DECKERT.
OH, YES.
MR. DECKERT'S REQUEST
HAS BEEN DENIED.
WHY'S THAT ?
OH, WE FEEL HE'S DOING FINE
JUST WHERE HE IS.
GOOD-BYE, JOHN.
WHAT ?
ALL RIGHT, YOU TELL THAT MURDOCH
HE CAN COME UP HERE
AND KISS MY LUNAR BUTT !
THIS IS BULL !
TOOK THAT WELL.
DANA LOOKED GOOD.
I DIDN'T NOTICE.
YEAH, I NOTICED
HOW YOU DIDN'T NOTICE.
IT'S IN THE PAST.
LET'S JUST LEAVE IT.
LAST TIME YOU LOOKED
THAT STUNNED WAS WHEN I DRUG YOU
IN OFF THE SURFACE HALF DEAD.
DON'T START
WITH ME, WILL.
HOW CAN I START WITH YOU ?
YOU STILL HAVEN'T
FINISHED WITH HER.
YOU'RE SURE JOHN RUSSELL'S
PRESENCE WON'T CAUSE
ANY COMPLICATIONS ?
JOHN KNOWS
HOW THE GAME IS PLAYED.
HE WON'T GET
IN YOUR WAY.YOU'RE SURE ?
COLONEL, I KNOW HOW
TO PLAY JOHN RUSSELL.
HE'LL KEEP TO HIMSELF.
TRUST ME, JOHN KNOWS THE SCORE.
HE WON'T BE A PROBLEM.
MAYBE. HE'S HAD QUITE SOME TIME
TO RECONSIDER HIS POSITION.
HE MAY HAVE FORGOTTEN
WHAT PUT HIM UP THERE.
WELL, THEN MAYBE
HE NEEDS A REMINDER.
MISS MORGAN, I'VE READ
YOUR BACKGROUND.
I'M IMPRESSED.
I'VE READ YOURS AND I'M NOT.IT WASN'T MEANT
TO IMPRESS YOU.
OR INFORM ME.IT'S A SENSITIVE
SITUATION.
THE DISKS WERE MARKED FOR
DESTRUCTION, NOT DISPOSAL.
YOU DON'T NEED TO KNOW
WHAT'S ON THEM. YOU JUST
NEED TO HELP ME FIND THEM.
EXCUSE ME ?THERE'S BEEN
A CHANGE IN PLANS.
YOU'LL BE ACCOMPANYING ME
ON THE SHUTTLE.MURDOCH ASSIGNED KRUTCHFIELD.
AND I REQUESTED
YOU INSTEAD.
YOU CO-DESIGNED THE
COMPOUND'S COMPUTER SYSTEM,
AND I BELIEVE YOUR
PAST ASSOCIATION WITH
JOHN RUSSELL COULD BE USEFUL.
PAST ASSOCIATION ?ON THE TEAM THAT OVERSAW
WTI'S ARCTIC PLANT.
THAT WAS OVER FIVE YEARS AGO.
IT WASN'T EXACTLY A SUCCESS.
BUT YOU SURVIVED
THE CORPORATE AFTERMATH.
I WAS ASSURED
YOU WERE A TEAM PLAYER.
THE CHOICE, OF COURSE,
IS YOURS.
FINE.
WE LEAVE TONIGHT
AT 1800 HOURS.
WHO KNOWS ?
YOU MIGHT EVEN HAVE FUN.
[ Woman ]
ARE YOU READY FOR ME, BABY ?
I'VE MISSED YOU,
SWEETIE.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
LOOK AT ME.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU MY BODY.
WHAT THE HELL ?
MOM ?
MMM. YOU'RE SO
BIG AND HARD.
YOU MAKE MY MOUTH WATER.
OH !
DECKERT !
- YOU SCANNED HER IN.
- WHAT'S IT GONNA BE, SUGAR ?
HIPS... OR LIPS ?
NO !
[ Masani's Shout Echoes ]
[ Breathing Sound ]
[ Man's Voice ]
THE DAMAGE TOLL
CONTINUES TO RISE...
IN LAST WEEK'S
WASTE CONVERSION
PLANT DISASTER.
IT'S NOW ESTIMATED THAT AS MANY
AS ONE MILLION ACRES OF ARCTIC
WILDLIFE HAVE BEEN DESTROYED...
IN WHAT IS BEING CALLED
AN ECOLOGICAL CATASTROPHE.
[ Woman's Whispering Voice ]
JOHN.
[ Sighs ]
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, LUCAS.
THE FIRST TIME ON THE MOON
CAN SHAKE THE BEST OF US UP.
YEAH ? SURE.
NEIL ARMSTRONG.
I BET YOU CAN'T TELL ME
WHAT HIS FIRST WORDS WERE
WHEN HE STEPPED ON THIS ROCK.
[ Lucas ]
YEAH. "ONE SMALL
STEP FOR MAN."
HIS VERY FIRST WORDS WERE,
"CONGRATULATIONS, MR. GORSKY."
WHO'S MR. GORSKY ?EXACTLY.
NASA DIDN'T LIKE THE SOUND
OF IT, SO THEY DELETED IT
FROM THE TRANSMISSION--
WILL. IF I HAVE TO LISTEN
TO THIS STORY ONE MORE TIME,
I SWEAR I'M GONNA GO NUTS !
THE ARMSTRONG
STORY ?
IT'S MY BEST ONE.
SO, WHAT'S THE PROBLEM ?
NOTHIN', REALLY.
I HAD A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP.
HE'S GOT THE SHAKES.
ARTI-ZONE MUST'VE
DRIED ON HIS SUIT.
I'M OKAY, REALLY.
WE'RE SLIPPIN'
INTO LUNAR NIGHT.
IT SHOULD GET PRETTY COLD.
IT'S GOIN' DOWN
TO ABOUT 150 BELOW.
MAYBE YOU'D BETTER
KEEP HIM IN.
IT'S UP TO HIM.
HE SAYS HE'S OKAY.
THE LOAD FROM L4 PASSES OVER
THE DROP ZONE IN 45 MINUTES.
LET'S GET READY
TO ROLL OUT.
[ Masani ]
DROP ZONE IS CLEAR.
WE ARE READY FOR DUMP.
[ John ]
READY ON THE TUG, DECKERT.
[ Will ]
OPENING POD DOOR.
BRING IT DOWN NICE AND EASY.
[ Engine Revving ]
[ Deckert ]
THERE ONCE WAS A MAN FROM VENUS,
WHO HAD SEVEN WARTS ON HIS--
[ Masani ]
DECKERT, SHUT UP.
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
AND LEAVE MY MOTHER
OUT OF YOUR JOKES.
YOUR MOM HAS
SEVEN WARTS ON HER--SHUT UP !
DON'T JUST SAY,
"SHUT UP."
I'LL YANK
YOUR HOSE OUT.OOH, THAT'S COLD.
NO, MAN,
150 DEGREES BELOW IS COLD.
THERE ONCE WAS A GIRL
FROM URANUS, WHO HAD--SHUT UP.
[ Will ]
WILL YOU TWO
PIPE DOWN OUT THERE,
AND LEAVE THE LUNAR CHITCHAT
TO AN OLD PRO LIKE ME ?
HA !
[ Engine Revving ]
[ Will ]
HEY, LUCAS, HOW YA DOIN' ?
ALL RIGHT, I GUESS. JUST SETTLE DOWN
AND RELAX...
WHILE I FINISH TELLING YOU
THE ARMSTRONG STORY.
OKAY.HIS FIRST WORDS WERE,
"CONGRATULATIONS, MR. GORSKY."
RIGHT.A LOT OF THEORIES POPPED UP
ABOUT WHAT ARMSTRONG MEANT,
LIKE MAYBE HE SAW SOMETHING
UP HERE THAT PROVED
THE RUSSIANS MADE IT FIRST,
OR THAT HE WAS
SOME KIND OF DOUBLE AGENT
SIGNALLIN' MOSCOW.
FINALLY HE GETS SICK OF
HEARIN' ABOUT IT, SO HE DECIDES
TO SET THE RECORD STRAIGHT.
IT TURNS OUT
WHEN HE WAS A KID,
ARMSTRONG LIVED NEXT DOOR
TO AN OLDER COUPLE
NAMED GORSKY.
SO ONE DAY
HE WENT OVER THEIR YARD
TO GET A STRAY BASEBALL,
AND HE HEARD A NOISE,
AND THEN HE LOOKED
IN THE WINDOW,
AND THERE WERE THE GORSKYS
GOING AT IT ON THE BED.
[ Chuckles ]
AND SUDDENLY MR. GORSKY STOPPED
AND SAID TO HIS WIFE,
AFTER 30 YEARS OF GOOD LOVIN',
HE WANTED TO TRY
SOMETHIN' DIFFERENT.
[ Chuckles ]
WELL, MRS. GORSKY WAS SHOCKED.
HOW DARE HIM ASK HER
TO DO SUCH A THING ?
"DREAM ON,"
SHE SAID TO HIM.
"THE DAY I PUT THAT THING
IN MY MOUTH IS THE DAY
THAT LITTLE ARMSTRONG BOY
NEXT DOOR...
- [ Masani, Russell
Deckert Join In ]
- WALKS ON THE MOON."
[ Thumping Sound ]
- WAIT ! NO !
- WHAT ?
- [ Groaning ]
- LUCAS !
WHERE IS HE ?B-TRENCH, OUT OF
ROVER 2 CAMERA RANGE.
LUCAS, RESPOND.
ANYONE NEAR B-TRENCH ?
[ Masani ]
HANG ON.
I'M ON MY WAY.
LUCAS !
- HE'S DEAD.
- WHAT ?
- HE'S ALL TORN UP,
LIKE SOMETHING--
- [ Deckert ] TORN UP ?
EVERYONE BACK
TO THE LOCK, NOW !
[ Alarm Buzzes ]
WHO ARE YOU ?
I'M THE WHITE HORSE
OF THE APOCALYPSE.
AND WHO ARE YOU ?
I'M IN CHARGE HERE.
NOT ANYMORE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ?WHAT'S TO THINK ?
WE'RE SCREWED.
TAKE IT EASY.
WE'LL JUST GIVE 'EM
WHATEVER THEY WANT.
FILET MIGNON.
WHAT A TREAT.
KARL, WE'RE SURROUNDED
BY IDIOTS.
DID WE HAVE TO
BRING THEM ALL ?PATIENCE, MINA.
EVERYONE HAS
THEIR PURPOSE...
AND EVERYONE
THEIR TIME.
EXCUSE ME, UH,
MR. APOCALYPSE ?
HI. UH, YOU THINK
YOU COULD FILL US IN HERE ?
I'M SURE WE COULD
WORK SOMETHIN' OUT.
[ Clears Throat ]
OKAY, MAYBE NOT.
CAN'T WE JUST
GET ALONG ?
ALL I WANT IS TO GET BACK HOME.
I HAVE NO INTEREST
IN SEEING YOU DIE.
- WHAT ABOUT LUCAS ?
- WELL, I'M NOT PERFECT, EITHER.
SO SIT QUIETLY,
AND BY THIS TIME TOMORROW,
THIS WILL ALL BE
JUST A FOND MEMORY.
WHAT'S TOMORROW ?OUR DAY OFF.
SHUT UP.
COME NOW. YOU DON'T THINK
I WOULD HAVE COME TO THE MOON...
IF I DIDN'T KNOW WHEN
I COULD CATCH THE NEXT
REFUSE TRANSPORT HOME ?
WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM ?
ACTUALLY,
IT'S YOUR PLAN'S PROBLEM.
REALLY ?
ALL DROPS WERE AUTOMATED
SIX MONTHS AGO.
GARBAGE SHUTTLES FROM EARTH
DON'T LAND ANYMORE.
[ Will ]
AND EVEN IF THEY DID,
WE GOT OUR EARTH LOAD
TWO DAYS AGO.
WON'T GET ANOTHER
TILL NEXT WEEK.
THEY'RE LYIN'.
WE KNOW THE SCHEDULE.
WELL,
THEY CHANGED IT.
SURPRISE, SURPRISE.
I TOOK YOU ALONG
IN RETURN FOR SOME...
INFORMATION YOU PROVIDED,
CORRECT ?
THAT INFORMATION
IS OBSOLETE.
[ Chuckles ]
AND SO ARE YOU.
[ Gagging ]
[ Grunts ]
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
IN APPROXIMATELY
16 HOURS,
OUR ABSENCE FROM L4
WILL BE DISCOVERED,
AS WILL OUR
ESCAPE ROUTE.
A GUARD TRANSPORT
WILL BE SENT.
IF I'M STILL HERE
WHEN THAT HAPPENS,
I WILL BE VERY UPSET.
SO, A COMMON GOAL:
GET ME OUT OF THIS.
ANY IDEAS ?
THERE'S AN INSPECTION SHUTTLE
ON ITS WAY.
[ Man ]
MOONBASE CONTROL,
THIS IS THE SHUTTLELIBERTY.
WE ARE AT FIVE KILOMETERS
AND CLOSING.
[ John ]
ROGER,LIBERTY.
OPENING SHUTTLE BAY DOORS.
SEE YOU INSIDE.
THEY WALK OUT,
YOU WALK IN.I'M A MAN OF MY WORD.
[ Computer Voice ]
SHUTTLE BAY PRESSURIZATION
COMPLETE.
[ Alarm Buzzes ]
OF COURSE,
WE WILL NEED THE PILOT.
AFTER YOU.
NO HEROICS.
IT'S NOT MY STYLE.
- JOHN RUSSELL ?
- COLONEL.
I BELIEVE YOU KNOW
DANA MORGAN.
WHAT THE HELL
IS SHE DOIN' HERE ?
NICE TO SEE YOU, TOO.
WELCOME. I'M KARL.
GLAD YOU COULD COME.
ARE YOU THE PILOT ?
THIS ISN'T A SOCIAL CALL,
GENTLEMEN.
I'D LIKE TO GET TO WORK.
I AGREE.
LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
THIS IS MY TEAM.
LET'S GET STARTED.
HEY, WILL,
WHY DON'T YOU TELL HIM
ONE OF YOUR STORIES ?
MAYBE YOU'LL
PUT HIM TO SLEEP.
THEY'RE GONNA
LEAVE YOU BEHIND, SON.
YOU KNOW THAT,
DON'T YOU ?
WHY, THEY'RE PROBABLY
TAKIN' OFF RIGHT NOW.
OH, GREAT PLAN, WILL.
MAKE THIS PSYCHO KILLER
PARANOID.
WHY DIDN'T I
THINK OF THAT ?
YOU COME HERE OFTEN ?
PULL UP THE GRID
FOR B-TRENCH.
B-TRENCH ?
ARE YOU SURE ?
JUST DO IT.
[ Beeping ]
[ Beeping Continues ]
[ Keyboard Clicking ]
TRY ANYTHING
AND THE WOMAN DIES...
FIRST.
[ Beeping ]
TURN IT OFF.
- [ Beeping ]
- COM.
[ Beeping ]
[ Computer Voice ]
ALL POINTS BULLETIN
FROM L4 PENITENTIARY...
TO ALL FACILITIES AND CRAFT
IN THE OFF WORLD SECTOR.
THE FOLLOWING FUGITIVES
ARE BELIEVED TO BE
EN ROUTE TO EARTH.
THEY ARE ARMED
AND EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
ANY CONTACT SHOULD BE REPORTED
TO L4 PENITENTIARY.
BE GOOD NOW.
- [ Grunting ]
- [ Groaning ]
[ Gunfire ]
- [ Screaming ]
- [ Groaning ]
[ Gunfire ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Mumbling ]
SOPHIE !
MOVE !
[ Gunshot ]
SO YOU JUST LET 'EM
WALTZ IN AND TAKE OVER ?
THEY WANTED A SHUTTLE.HOW ACCOMMODATING.
I'M NOT A HERO !NO, YOU'RE
A DOWNRIGHT COWARD !
GET L4 ON THE COM.
LET 'EM KNOW
THEIR FUGITIVES ARE HERE.
[ Electronic Static ]I WOULD IF I COULD,
BUT THE TRANSMITTER TOOK A HIT.
LOOKS LIKE IT OVERLOADED
THE RELAY STATION,
TOOK IT OFF-LINE.
- MEANING ?
- WE CAN'T TRANSMIT TO ANYONE.
WE DON'T HAVE A DIRECT LINE
TO EARTH. L4 IS OUT OF RANGE
WITHOUT A STRONGER SIGNAL.
HOW LONG BEFORE
IT'S BACK ON-LINE ?SEVEN HOURS.
I WANT YOU
SURFACE-READY IN ONE.
UH, WAIT A MINUTE THERE,
TANK-BOY.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY
INTO THE SHUTTLE BAY.
THEY'RE GONNA BE BACK.
LOOK HERE.
IF THEY COME BACK,
AIM FOR THE GUT.
WE'RE NOT SOLDIERS.YOU WALK US INTO AN AMBUSH,
AND NOW YOU WANT OUR HELP ?
I SAVED MY NECK !PUT MINE ON THE BLOCK !
BETTER YOU THAN ME !I'D FORGOTTEN WHAT
A CHARMING GUY YOU WERE.
STAY OUT OF THIS.BELIEVE ME,
I'VE TRIED.
MISS MORGAN,
YOU'LL DIRECT OUR
SURFACE MOVEMENT FROM HERE.
WE'LL SUIT UP AND HEAD OUT
DOWN AT THE MAIN LOCK.
KEEP THE CONTROL ACCESS DOOR
AND THE AUXILIARY AIR-LOCK
AND THE SHUTTLE BAY SEALED,
AND THERE'S NO WAY
THEY'LL BE ABLE TO GET
TO YOU OR THE SHUTTLE.
- OUR MISSION PROCEEDS
AS PLANNED.
- OH, YOU THINK SO ?
- WHAT ?
- I HAVE A BRAIN,
LIEUTENANT COLONEL.
IT'S ABOUT A FOOT AND A HALF
ABOVE MY BREASTS,
IN CASE YOU'RE INTERESTED.
B-TRENCH IS FOR NUCLEAR WASTE.
THIS ISN'T AN INSPECTION, AND
YOU'RE NOT LOOKING FOR DISKS.
WHAT WE'RE LOOKING FOR
IS CLASSIFIED.
FINE.
B-TRENCH COVERS ABOUT
74 SQUARE KILOMETERS.
HAPPY HUNTING.
CAN EITHER OF YOU TWO
WORK THE SYSTEM ?
[ Caldecott ] WERTMAN-TOBASHI
ASSURED ME YOU'D COOPERATE.
IT'S YOUR DUTY.
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO HABLO INGLES.
[ Caldecott ]
ALL RIGHT, MISS MORGAN, YOU WIN.
POSITRONIC PULSE WARHEADS.
- WHAT THE HELL IS THAT ?
- [ Will ] SOUNDS NASTY.
AS NASTY AS THEY COME.
THE PROTOTYPE WE TESTED
BEFORE THE GLOBAL SUBATOMIC
WEAPONS BAN TOOK EFFECT...
WIPED OUT OUR TARGET SITE,
AND PART OF CUBA
ALONG WITH IT.
- WIPED OUT ?
- CHECK A MAP.
IT'S NOT THERE ANYMORE.
SO YOU STOWED 'EM UP HERE
FOR A RAINY DAY.
THE PENTAGON CONTRACTED
WERTMAN-TOBASHI FOR
TEMPORARY STORAGE.
- ANOTHER SWEETHEART DEAL
FOR MARVIN MURDOCH.
- ANOTHER ?
AND B-TRENCH IS A PERFECT PLACE
TO HIDE 'EM. IF ANYONE
DOES A SATELLITE SCAN--
THEY'D ASSUME THE READINGS
WERE FROM RADIOACTIVE WASTE.
BUT THERE'S BEEN
A SECURITY LEAK.
YOU'RE AFRAID SOMEONE'S
GONNA STEAL YOUR TOYS ?
THIS HARDWARE'S WORTH
A HELL OF A LOT
ON THE BLACK MARKET.
INSTANT SUPERPOWER STATUS
TO THE HIGHEST BIDDER.
NOW, MISS MORGAN, I'LL SEND
TWO OF MY MEN ON A SWEEP THROUGH
THE BASE, SEARCH AND DESTROY.
I'M TAKING THE OTHER THREE
TO THE SURFACE,
AND I WOULD APPRECIATE
YOUR FULL COOPERATION
FROM THIS POINT ON.
FAIR ENOUGH ?
MOVE 'EM OUT.
THIS ROOM IS
A SAFEGUARD CHAMBER.
LOCK YOURSELVES IN AND
SIT TIGHT TILL WE GET BACK.
THINK YOU CAN HANDLE THAT ?
MAN, THAT GUY'S GOT
A SERIOUS ATTITUDE PROBLEM.
[ Caldecott ]
CONTROL, WE ARE "GO"
FOR SURFACE ACCESS.
COPY THAT.
OPENING THE INNER HATCH.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW ?WE WAIT.
[ Caldecott ] REPEAT:
WE ARE "GO" FOR ACCESS.
HOW ABOUT THAT HATCH ?
COLONEL, DO YOU MIND GIVIN' THAT
DOOR CONTROL PANEL DOWN THERE
A LITTLE WHACK ON THE SIDE ?
COLONEL ? ROGER THAT,
CONTROL.
A "WHACK ON THE SIDE."
[ Engine Revving ]
SO, WHERE EXACTLY
IN B-TRENCH
ARE THEY HEADING ?
THE UNDERGROUND BUNKER
SHOULD BE IN SECTOR 56.
HMM.
FIFTY-SIX.
WHAT DID YOU MEAN, "ANOTHER"
SWEETHEART DEAL FOR MURDOCH ?
NOTHIN'.
JOHN, YOU NEVER MEAN NOTHING
WHEN YOU SAY SOMETHING.
YEAH, WELL,
PEOPLE CHANGE.
WHAT ARE YOU HIDING ?
EVIDENTLY,
POSITRONIC PULSE WARHEADS.
IS HE ALWAYS
THIS CHEERY ?
ONLY ON
HIS GOOD DAYS.
[ Engine Revving ]
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
A BLUE SECTOR MARKER.
THE WARHEAD BUNKER
SHOULD BE 20 METERS FROM IT.
[ Dana ]
COORDINATES 156
AT 34 DEGREES.
IT MUST BE COVERED.
WHO'S THE GENIUS WHO
FILLED THIS PLACE UP ?
WELL, COLONEL,
IT IS A DUMP, AFTER ALL.
[ Caldecott ]
THIS IS GONNA TAKE TIME.HOW MUCH TIME ?
LONG ENOUGH TO GET SCREWED,
LIKE LUCAS AND SOPHIE.
THOSE GUYS
ARE STILL OUT THERE.
LOOK, WE'LL BE FINE
IF WE JUST STAY PUT.
I'M TOO OLD
TO STAY PUT.WILL--
WE GOTTA GET OFF OUR BUTTS.
WE GOTTA GET A DISTRESS
SIGNAL OUTTA HERE.
NOW YOU'RE TALKIN' !THERE'S A PLAN.
BUT WE CAN'T. WE'RE ON
THE FAR SIDE OF THE MOON.
WITH THE RELAY STATION OFF-LINE,
THERE'S NO WAY TO BOUNCE
AND BOOST A SIGNAL TO EARTH.
SO WE CAN'T SEND A SIGNAL
AROUND THE MOON,
BUT WE CAN TRANSMIT
TO THE PRISON.
WE HAVE A STRAIGHT LINE
TO THEM.
THEN ALL WE NEED TO DO
IS AMPLIFY OUR SIGNAL
FROM IN HERE.
AND WHERE ARE WE GONNA
FIND AN AMP--
OH, NO, NO, NO.
NOT MY STEREO, MAN.
I SPENT THREE MONTHS' SALARY
ON THAT SYSTEM.
WILL, IT'S NOT SAFE OUT THERE.
IT'S NOT WORTH THE RISK.
- THAT TOO.
- I'LL GO.
SOMETIMES, JOHN, YOU GOTTA
LEARN TO TAKE THE RISK.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN ?
LET'S DO IT.
I'M RIGHT
BEHIND YOU.
HEY, HOW COME
YOU GET THE GUN ?
BECAUSE I'M OLDER AND WISER.
YOU COULD GET HURT.
HERE.
HEY, WAIT UP !
AND GIVE ME THOSE THINGS, MAN.
I CAN'T HAVE YOU AMATEURS
HACKIN' UP MY SYSTEM.
COME ON.
[ Unintelligible Dialogue ]
THEY GOTTA BE
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
BUNKER.
CODE ALPHA INPUT.
[ Beeping ]
THIS IS IT.
LET'S PACK 'EM UP.
[ Caldecott ]
WE'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE
AND BE BACK WITHIN THE HOUR.
UNDERSTOOD.
SO,
YOU LOOK GOOD.
I WISH I COULD SAY
THE SAME ABOUT YOU.
WELL, FIVE YEARS ON
THE FAR SIDE TAKES ITS TOLL.
BUT YOU HAVE TO ADMIT,
THE PLACE DOES HAVE ITS CHARM.
OH, YEAH.
IT'S A REAL
VACATION PARADISE.
I CAN SEE WHY YOU
REQUESTED THE TRANSFER.
I WASN'T GIVEN
MUCH OF A CHOICE.
BUT I GUESS YOU WOULDN'T
UNDERSTAND THAT.
YOU KNOW, EVERYTHING
WORKED OUT OKAY, THOUGH.
IT'S FOR THE BEST.
I MEAN, YOU MOVED UP
THE CORPORATE LADDER.
IT'S JUST, MY LADDER WENT
A LITTLE HIGHER THAN YOURS.
YOU LANDED YOURSELF HERE, JOHN.
I WORKED HARD
TO GET WHERE I'M AT.
I KNOW THAT.
THAT'S WHY--
WHAT'S THE BIG SECRET,
JOHN ?
THERE'S NO SECRET.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
AND YOU KNOW WHOSE FAULT IT WAS.
I MEAN, IT'S ALWAYS EASY
TO PICK OUT THE BAD GUY.
[ Masani ]
WE SHOULD PUT IN
FOR HAZARD PAY.
A BUNCH OF ARMED PSYCHOS
RUNNIN' AROUND
A NUCLEAR ARSENAL.
YEAH, I'D SAY
THAT'S HAZARDOUS.
DON'T TOUCH.
I'VE GOT THIS BABY
CHERRIED JUST SO.
I CAN'T HAVE YOU GUYS
YANKIN' WIRES OUT.
YOU REALLY THINK YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TIME FOR HER ?
JUST CAN'T LEAVE HER HERE
ALL ALONE.
WILL.
I'LL STEP OUTSIDE,
KEEP AN EYE OUT. GOOD IDEA.
KIND OF COLD
IN HERE.
YOU SHOULD TRY LUNAR NIGHT
ON THE SURFACE.
YOU SHOULD TRY
CORPORATE HEADQUARTERS.
ENOUGH TO
CHILL YOUR SPINE.
HOW LONG ARE YOU PLANNING
TO STAY UP HERE ?
LONG ENOUGH.
IT SUITS ME,
DON'T YOU THINK ?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO THINK ANYMORE.
I KNOW WHAT I SEE,
I KNOW WHAT I'VE BEEN TOLD,
BUT I GET THE SENSE
THERE'S MORE TO THE TRUTH.
THAT DEPENDS
ON WHO TELLS IT.
NO. IT DEPENDS
ON WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
WELL, YOU SAW WHAT
REALLY HAPPENED, DANA.
BIOLOGICAL CONTAMINANTS
WIPED OUT HALF
THE ARCTIC COAST...
AFTER I FUDGED
THE PLANT SAFETY SPECS.
- END OF STORY.
- AND THAT'S THE TRUTH ?
THE TRUTH IS WHATEVER
GETS THE JOB DONE.
DANA, DON'T WASTE
YOUR TIME WONDERING.
YOU'RE SMART.
LOOK OUT FOR
YOURSELF DOWN THERE.
WATCH YOUR OWN BACK.
THAT'S HOW YOU SURVIVE.
NO. THAT'S HOW YOU DIE.
IF ALL YOU CARE ABOUT
IS YOURSELF,
THAT'S ALL YOU'LL EVER HAVE.
HEY, THIS IS MY ROCK
IN THE UNIVERSE.
I DIDN'T MOVE UP
ALL THE WAY TO THE
FAR SIDE OF THE MOON...
HOPING YOU'D STOP BY
TO LECTURE ME.
OH, I SEE.
YOU TRANSFERRED TO THE MOON
TO GET AWAY FROM ME.
HOW ROMANTIC.
[ Caldecott ]
BASE TEAM, WRAP UP YOUR SWEEP.
ORDNANCE IS SECURE.
CONTROL, STAND BY
ON THE LOCK HATCH.
[ Dana ]
WE ARE STANDING BY.
[ Unintelligible Dialogue
From Headset ]
LOOKS LIKE A LITTLE SHEEP
HAS STRAYED FROM ITS FOLD.
[ Imitates Wolf ]
WAIT. DON'T KILL ME.I AM TIRED
OF WAITIN'.
I'VE BEEN WAITIN'
FOR THE PAST
FIVE YEARS NOW.
BUT I CAN
GET YOU HOME...
AND MAKE YOU RICH.
DESPERATE WORDS
FROM A DESPERATE MAN.
WHY SHOULD I
BELIEVE YOU ?
HEY, TAKE IT EASY
THERE ! GEEZ.
[ Man Screaming,
Distant ]
DECKERT !
[ Flesh Tearing ] [ Man Grunting ]
THEY'RE COMIN'
THIS WAY. FIRE !
[ Gunshot ][ Grunts ]
WILL !
COME ON. I'LL GET THE GUNS.
LET'S GET BACK TO CONTROL.
[ Caldecott ]
EASY.
[ Man Screaming ]
[ Dana ]
CALDECOTT ? CALDECOTT ?
SOMEBODY TALK TO ME. [ Beeping ]
[ Caldecott ]
SWEEP THE SITE.
[ Caldecott ] LOOK !
WATCH YOUR BACK ! WATCH
YOUR BACK ! CLEAN 'EM OUT.
- [ Groaning ]
- [ Dana ] GET OUT OF THERE !
- [ Caldecott ] FALL BACK !
- [ Yells ]
- [ Man Grunting ]
- [ Caldecott ] MISSION ABORT !
MISSION ABORT !
[ Man ]
GET OUT ! GET OUT !
[ Punching Keypad ]
[ Caldecott Gasps ]
WAIT, DON'T. THIS IS--
[ Gunshot ][ Yells ]
[ Groaning ]
SEAL THE LOCK.YEAH.
[ Continues Groaning,
Panting ][ Hissing ]
[ Alarm Sounding ]NOT NOW.
WHAT'S WRONG ?
THE HATCH ISN'T WORKING.
I'VE GOTTA SEAL IT
BY HAND.
[ Grunts ]
[ Panting ]
WHERE'S JOHN ?
HE WENT TO SEAL THE LOCK
MANUALLY. CALDECOTT'S DEAD.
STARK'S ON HIS WAY BACK.
[ Alarm Buzzing ]
[ Panting ]
[ Alarm Stops,
Beep ]
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Man ] HOLD IT.
[ Yells ]
GET OUT OF HERE,
JOHN. NOW !
[ Reloading Noise ]
GET DOWN.
[ Gunshots ]
[ Gunshots Continue ][ Electronic Tone ]
THEY'RE INSIDE.[ Masani ]
OH, YOU THINK ?
WHERE'S JOHN ?HE GOT AWAY
DOWN THE AUXILIARY CORRIDOR.
JOHN ?HE'S ALL RIGHT.
HE KNOWS THIS PLACE INSIDE OUT.
IF HE WANTS
TO DISAPPEAR, HE WILL.
[ Breathing Heavily ] [ Dana On Intercom ]
JOHN ?
THIS IS NOT GOING
AS PLANNED.
[ Mina Chuckles ]
HUH, YOU HUNGRY ?
[ Moaning, Spitting ]
DID YOU GET
THE WARHEADS ?YES.
GREAT. NOW, ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS GET US INTO THE SHUTTLE,
AND WE'RE HOME FREE.
WHO'S GOING TO FLY IT ?
THIS WAS MY BACKUP PILOT.
NO PROBLEM. WOULD YOU
TRUST ME ? I WILL GET US
OUT OF THIS DUMP.
HOW'S IT COMING ?
GIVE ME TEN MINUTES.YOU'VE GOT FIVE.
I TIED INTO THE SHUTTLE
MAIN COMPUTER. WE CAN REROUTE
COMMAND FUNCTION THERE.
I SAY WE BLAST OFF AND
GET OUR BUTTS OUTTA HERE.HOW ?
FLICK ON THE AUTO PILOT.
YOU CAN DO THAT, CAN'T YOU ?
NOT WITHOUT A NAVIGATIONAL
SIGNAL LOCK. HOW LONG TILL THE
RELAY STATION'S BACK ON-LINE ?
- [ Will ]
THREE AND A HALF HOURS.
- [ Gunshots ]
HOW DO WE GET IN ?YOU NEED
THE ACCESS CODE.
SO GIVE IT TO US.I DON'T HAVE IT.
YOU'LL NEVER GET IT
OUT OF WILL.
THAT'S VERY
DISAPPOINTING.
BUT YOU COULD TRY
JOHN RUSSELL.
[ Stark On Intercom ]
JOHN, I KNOW YOU'RE THERE.
WE SHOULD DISCUSS
THE SITUATION,
DON'T YOU THINK ?
COME, NOW.
DON'T BE RUDE.
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND ?
- THOUGHTS YOU CAN'T
EVEN IMAGINE.
- JOHN ?
THIS IS A PRIVATE
CONVERSATION, MISS MORGAN.
AND A PRIVATE OFFER
TO MR. JOHN RUSSELL.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ?
IT'S NOT WHAT I WANT.
IT'S WHAT I CAN GIVE YOU.
- WHAT'S THAT ?
- YOUR LIFE, IN EXCHANGE
FOR THE SHUTTLE.
GIVE ME THE ACCESS CODE
TO THE CONTROL CENTER DOOR,
AND I'LL BE ON MY WAY.
WHAT ABOUT MY CREW
IN THERE ?
THAT SHOULDN'T
CONCERN YOU.
I'M OFFERING YOU
YOUR LIFE, NOT THEIRS.
IT'S SIMPLE REALLY.
GIVE ME MY FREEDOM,
AND YOU LIVE.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO SACRIFICE YOURSELF.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO LIVE IN A CAGE, JOHN ?
IT'S INVARIABLE.
YOU WAKE UP TO THE SAME BARS,
EAT THE SAME FOOD,
TAKE THE SAME CRAP
AT EXACTLY THE SAME TIME,
DAY AFTER DAY.
EVERY DAY.
THE THING IS,
IT'S NOT PAINFUL
MOMENT TO MOMENT.
IT'S ALL THE TOMORROWS
THAT WILL KILL YOU.
BUT YOU ALREADY KNOW THAT,
DON'T YOU, JOHN ?
WE'RE THE SAME,
YOU AND I.
TWO SOCIAL OUTCASTS
SENT AWAY TO LIVE...
AMONGST THE WORLD'S
REFUSE.
BUT TELL ME, JOHN.
WHO IS THE REAL PRISONER ?
I BROKE OUT
OF MY CELL.
WE CAN FIX THAT.
THE ACCESS CODE, JOHN.
I WANT IT NOW.
[ Man On Radio ]
MOONBASE STATION, THIS IS
L4 PRISON TRANSPORT. RESPOND.
L4, L4, WE READ YOU.
GO AHEAD.
WE ARE APPROACHING OUTER ORBIT
WITH A FULL-ARMED CONTINGENT,
TRACKING AN L4 PRISON BREAK.
HERE. HERE.
WELL, YOU FOUND THEM.
THEY'RE DOWN HERE.
ROGER THAT. REQUESTING
CLEARANCE. ETA TO SURFACE
TOUCHDOWN, 20 MINUTES.
CLEARANCE GRANTED.
YEAH !
JOHN ?
IT'S OVER.
SORRY, STARK.
MAYBE NEXT TIME.
YEAH !
L4.
THERE ARE SOME
UNWELCOME GUESTS
COMING TO CALL.
CAN YOU ARRANGE
FOR A PROPER RECEPTION ?
ABSOLUTELY.
NO PROBLEM.
CONSIDER IT DONE.
PARTNER.
YOU KNOW,
I'M DOING ALL THE WORK
AROUND HERE.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO RENEGOTIATE
OUR ARRANGEMENT.
OH, DON'T WORRY.
WE WILL.
[ Sighs ]
YOU LOOK TROUBLED.
I'M TIRED, KARL.
I WANNA GO HOME.
IT'S GOING TO BE
A DIFFERENT WORLD, MINA.
LET'S GO HOME
IN STYLE.
[ Man On Radio ]
NAV RELAY IS OFF-LINE.
PROCEEDING WITH MANUAL APPROACH.
MAINTAIN VISUAL TO BASE.
CONTROL, PLEASE ADVISE AS TO
THE STATUS OF THE ESCAPEES.
UH, THE ESCAPEES ARE MAKIN'
IN THEIR PANTS ABOUT NOW.
COME ON DOWN AND WIPE 'EM
UP. HEY, HEY.
BE ADVISED, THE PRISONERS
ARE ARMED AND LOOSE
IN THE COMPOUND.
ROGER THAT, MOONBASE.
REMAIN IN SAFEGUARD CHAMBER.
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
[ Dana ]
JOHN, ARE YOU OKAY
OUT THERE ?
YEAH, I'M OKAY.
WHEN THIS IS ALL OVER WITH,
I'M PUTTIN' IN FOR
A THREE-WEEK VACATION.
FORGET VACATION.
EARLY RETIREMENT
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, WILL ?
TOO MUCH EXCITEMENT FOR YOU ?
AT MY AGE, A SOLID STOOL
IS TOO MUCH EXCITEMENT.
BUT I THINK I'LL TRY
MY CHARM ON DANA HERE,
AND SEE IF I CAN'T GET
ONE OF THOSE CUSHY CORNER
OFFICE JOBS AT CORPORATE.
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
PUT IN YOUR TRANSFER REQUEST
RIGHT AWAY.
[ Will Laughs ][ Whispered ]
DECKERT !
[ John ]
WILL, WHERE'S DECKERT ?
UH, WE LOST DECKERT,
JOHN.
HE WAS STANDING GUARD
FOR ME AND MASANI, AND--
[ Alarm Buzzing ]WHAT IS IT ?
WE'VE GOT A POWER SURGE
IN THE TRACTOR BEAM COIL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT--
LOOK !
[ Will ]
JOHN, WE HAVE A PROBLEM.DECKERT.
HE'S GONNA CRASH
THE SHIP.WHAT ?
[ Electronic Blast ]
[ Electronic Pulses, Beeps ]I CAN'T OVERRIDE THE UNIT !
WE'RE LOCKED OUT.
HE MUST HAVE HIS OWN
ENCRYPTION CODE.
WILL ? WILL ?
GET THAT TRANSPORT
OUT OF THERE, NOW !
- L4, GET OUT OF THERE !
- [ Electrical Pulses,
Explosions ]
[ Crashing, Explosions ]
[ Electronic Beeping ]
GOOD NEWS, JOHN.
IT LOOKS LIKE I WON'T
BE GOING BACK TO PRISON.
HI, THERE.
HMM, DID YOU FEEL THAT ?
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE, HUH ?
JOHN, HOW GOOD OF YOU
TO STOP BY.
- JOHN, I DIDN'T MEAN TO--
- YOU GOT YOUR TRANSFER, HUH ?
- [ Punching Noise, Grunt ]
- [ Man ] HEY, HEY !
HE'S USING YOU,
DECKERT !
EVERYBODY USES EVERYBODY,
JOHN.
IT'S THE WERTMAN-TOBASHI
MOTTO.
BESIDES, IF WE BOTH
GET WHAT WE WANT,
WHO CARES ?
- [ Snorts ]
- TEMPER, TEMPER.
ALL RIGHT.
LEAVE THE WARHEADS BEHIND,
I'LL GIVE YOU THE SHUTTLE.
NO. I'VE GROWN RATHER FOND
OF THEM.
THEN YOU'RE NEVER GONNA
GET OFF THIS ROCK.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ME.
JOHN, NOW WHY DON'T YOU
WANNA HELP US OUT, HUH ?
WE'RE JUST TRYING TO GET HOME.
THAT ISN'T SUCH A BAD THING,
NOW, IS IT ?
[ John ]
YEAH, YOU BETTER CHECK
WITH YOUR BOYFRIEND.
I THINK HE'S GOT
SOMETHING GRANDER IN MIND.
AW, WHAT DO YOU WANT, HMM ?
WHY DON'T YOU COME WITH US ?
I COULD SHOW YOU THINGS
THAT YOU COULD ONLY DREAM OF.
[ John ]
THAT'S OKAY. MY DREAMS
AREN'T THAT GREAT ANYWAY.
I NEED YOU TO HELP ME.
I'LL GIVE YOU
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
[ John ]
ANYTHING ?
UH-HUH.
CAN I HAVE
YOUR GUN ?
MOVE.
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
- THEY'LL GET THE DOOR ACCESS
CODE OUT OF HIM.
- NO, JOHN WON'T GIVE US UP.
-HE'D DIE FIRST.
-DO YOU KNOW SOMETHING I DON'T ?
'CAUSE HE'S NEVER STUCK
HIS NECK OUT FOR US BEFORE.SURE, HE HAS.
THE MILITARY HAD
A BIOLOGICAL WEAPON DEPOT
AT WTI'S ARCTIC PLANT.
THERE WAS A CONTAINMENT LEAK.
JOHN TOOK THE BLAME
FOR MURDOCH.
FOR YOU. MURDOCH FIGURED
YOU WERE EXPENDABLE.
-HE SET YOU UP TO TAKE THE FALL.
-SO JOHN STEPPED FORWARD ?
AND BEAT MURDOCH
TO THE PUNCH.
AND HE'S BEEN
BEATIN' HIMSELF UP OVER IT
FOR THE PAST FIVE YEARS.
FORGET ABOUT WHO HE'S BEEN.
I KNOW WHO HE IS.
[ Electronic Beeps ]
[ Two Beeps ]COMMAND FUNCTIONS
ARE REROUTED TO THE SHUTTLE.
WE'LL RETREAT BACK TO THE BAY
AFTER WE GET JOHN BACK.
OH.
GREAT.
LET'S TRY THIS
ONE LAST TIME, SHALL WE ?
THE ACCESS CODE,
OR YOU DIE.
[ Cartridge Clicks ]
[ Laughs ]
WHICH PART OF THAT
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND ?
[ Deckert ]
COME ON, JOHN.
GIVE IT UP, WILL YA ?
WE'LL GET IN EVENTUALLY
WITH OR WITHOUT YOU.
THIS WAY,
YOU GET TO LIVE.
DON'T KID YOURSELF, DECKERT.
WE'RE BOTH DEAD.
EVERYONE HAS THEIR PURPOSE
AND TIME, ISN'T THAT RIGHT ?
VERY GOOD.
- I GUESS IT'S YOUR TIME, THEN.
- [ Beep ]
[ Will ]
TIME TO GO, JOHN.
[ Deckert ]
DON'T SHOOT ! DON'T SHOOT !
- [ Dana ] COME ON !
- [ Yells ]
- [ Dana ] NO !
- WILL !
[ Yell Echoing ]
[ Dana ]
JOHN !
[ Masani ] WE GOTTA
SEAL THE DOOR !
[ Echoing ]
WILL--
[ Yelling ]
- [ Dana ] COME ON !
- [ Masani ]
WE GOTTA SEAL THE DOOR !
CAN WE LOCK THIS
FROM OUT HERE ?
IT'S LOCKED.LET'S GET TO THE SHUTTLE.
COME ON.
[ Buzzing ]
I THOUGHT YOU SAID ONCE
WE WERE IN HERE, YOU COULD
CONTROL THE SHUTTLE ?
- YEAH, I--
- [ Beeping ]
WE'RE LOCKED OUT.
THEY REROUTED EVERYTHING THROUGH
THE SHUTTLE ONBOARD COMPUTER.
THEY'VE GOT CONTROL.GET IT BACK !
I CAN'T.
[ Computer Beeping,
Electronic Whirring ]
EITHER I GET OFF THIS ROCK,
OR NO ONE DOES.
LET'S GO.
OH, WE CAN'T YET.
RELAY STATION'S
STILL OFF-LINE.
- TWENTY-SIX MINUTES.
- CAN'T WE JUST BLAST OFF ?
NO, THE COMPUTER CAN'T FLY
THIS THING BLIND.
WE NEED HEADING COORDINATES
AND TRAJECTORY DATA FROM THE
NAVIGATIONAL BEACON ON EARTH.
WHAT ? NO WAY.
WE GOTTA GO NOW.
YOU WANNA FLY THIS THING ?
- TWENTY-SIX MINUTES ?
- [ Deckert ]
RUSSELL, ARE YOU THERE ?
DECKERT, I'M GONNA RIP
YOUR HEAD OFF
IF I EVER GET--
HE CAN'T HEAR YOU.
DECKERT, I'M GONNA RIP
YOUR HEAD OFF IF I EVER
GET MY HANDS ON YOU.
YEAH, YEAH, LET'S SKIP
THE TEARFUL REUNION.
LOOK, RUSSELL,
WE KNOW YOU GOTTA WAIT
ANOTHER 25 MINUTES,
SO WHY DON'T WE TRY
TO WORK THINGS OUT ?
I GET THE SENSE THESE GUYS
ARE REALLY MOTIVATED.
YOU STILL DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU, DECKERT ?
THESE GUYS DON'T WANT TO DEAL.
AS SOON AS THEY'RE ON THIS
SHUTTLE, AND THE AUTOPILOT'S
LOCKED ON EARTH,
YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT SPACE TRASH TO THEM.
FULLY AUTOMATED FLIGHT.
THE WONDERS NEVER CEASE.
WELL, I-IT'S NOT
COMPLETELY AUTOMATED.
I MEAN, THERE ARE A FEW
KINKS IN THE SYSTEM.
YOU KNOW, COMPUTATION
OF ATMOSPHERIC RE-ENTRY ANGLES,
STUFF LIKE THAT.
AH, YES.
I SEE YOUR POINT.
[ Laughs ]
MY FRIENDS. LET ME MOVE
DIRECTLY TO THE POINT.
YOU'LL NEVER GUESS
WHAT I'M HOLDING IN MY HANDS
AT THIS VERY MOMENT.
A POSITRONIC PULSE WARHEAD.
REVERSE-SPIN ELECTRONS.
TOTAL MOLECULAR ARMAGEDDON.
I SET THE DETONATION
OF THIS DEVICE TO COINCIDE
WITH THE EXACT MOMENT...
THAT YOUR RELAY STATION
COMES BACK ON-LINE.
[ Beeping ]
IT'S REALLY UNBELIEVABLE.
NOT ONE LABEL TO EXPLAIN THAT
MOLECULAR ANNIHILATION...
COULD BE HAZARDOUS
TO YOUR HEALTH.
ONLY STEP-BY-STEP
ARMING PROCEDURES.
THEN YOU JUST
KILLED YOURSELF, STARK.
AGAIN, YOU UNDERESTIMATE ME,
AND ONCE AGAIN,
THE CHOICE IS YOURS.
WAIT, WAIT ! Y-YOU NEED ME.
MANNING THE SHUTTLE
IS COMPLICATED.
TELL HIM, RUSSELL.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S
THE GARBAGE TRANSPORT FROM L4.
- L4, THAT'S IT.
DECKERT JUST SAVED US.
- WHAT ?
WE STILL GOT A DIRECT LINE
TO THE PRISON, RIGHT ?
WE DON'T NEED THE RELAY STATION
IF WE CAN PIGGYBACK
THE NAVIGATIONAL INFO...
ON OUR COM SIGNAL.
NOT ENOUGH SIGNAL STRENGTH.
WE FORGOT TO REROUTE
YOUR AMP POWER.
[ John ]
STARK, WAIT. DECKERT'S RIGHT.
HE IS THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN GET US
OFF THE SURFACE.
BUT IF YOU KILL HIM,
WE'RE ALL DEAD.
NOW, IT'S UP TO YOU.
IT'S YOUR CHOICE.
WE DON'T HAVE THE POWER
TO DO ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
- [ Clicking ]
- [ Stark ]
A VERY NOBLE ATTEMPT, JOHN.
EVEN AFTER EVERYTHING
THIS TRAITOR'S DONE,
YOU STILL HOPE TO SAVE HIM.
BUT HE'S MY PARTNER NOW,
NOT YOURS.
CONSIDER OUR ARRANGEMENT
RENEGOTIATED.
[ Gunshot, Signal Buzzing ]
[ Beep ]HE DID IT !
DE-PRESSURIZE THE BAY
AND OPEN THE SHUTTLE BAY DOORS.
[ Masani ]
WE ARE OUT OF HERE !WE HAVE SIGNAL LOCK WITH L4.
[ Beeping ]PROBLEM.
I KNEW IT WAS
TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE.THE BAY DOORS WON'T OPEN.
DECKERT MUST HAVE SIPHONED POWER
FROM THE BASE GENERATOR...
WHEN HE CRASHED
THE TRANSPORT SHIP.WE'RE SCREWED.
NO, NO, NO. WE JUST NEED
TO REDIRECT THE TRACTOR BEAM
POWER TO THE BAY DOORS.
BUT THAT WOULD HAVE TO BE DONE
FROM THE CONTROL BOX
ON THE SURFACE.
HA, NO-NO-NO, MAN.
NO WAY I'M GOING
OUT THERE.
TWENTY MINUTES.
I'M GOING.YOU ?
YOU CAN'T. YOU'LL NEVER
MAKE IT THERE AND BACK
IN TIME.
RIGHT.
JOHN ! JOHN !DON'T.
EVERY TIME I THINK
I KNOW YOU--YOU DO KNOW ME, DANA.
YOU ALWAYS HAVE. YOU JUST
LOST SIGHT OF ME UP HERE.
I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
WILL.
YOU COULD HAVE TOLD ME,
YOU KNOW. YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO RUN AWAY TO THE MOON.
YES, I DID.
MOONBASE WAS THE DEAL.
PERMANENT TRANSFER.
I DIDN'T LIKE THE OTHER OPTION.
IF IT CAME DOWN TO IT, FOR YOU--
I'D DO IT ALL AGAIN.
YOU'LL MAKE IT BACK.DON'T WAIT. YOU GET THE
SHUTTLE OUT OF HERE, OKAY ?
HEAR THAT, MASANI ? [ Door Opening ]
[ Breathing Heavily ]
RUSSELL.
[ Beeping ]
[ Rapid Beeping ]STARK'S IN THE BAY.
WHAT ?
SEAL THE BACK HATCH.AH--
COME ON, JOHN.
WE NEED SOME STARLIGHT
IN HERE.
[ Grunts ]
[ Rapid Beeping ]
[ Mechanical Whirring ]
MINA !
[ Electrical Zap ][ Grunts ]
- [ Accelerating Beeps ]
- [ Popping ]
[ Alarm Buzzing ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Continues Yelling ]
[ Screams, Echoes
Through Space ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Yells ]
- [ Yells ]
- [ Hissing ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Breathing Heavily ]
[ Wheezing ]
IT'S JOHN.
HE MADE IT BACK.
YEAH, BUT HE'LL NEVER
MAKE IT PAST STARK.
YOU.
YOU ARE QUITE THE WORTHY
OPPONENT, JOHN RUSSELL.
UNFORTUNATELY,
WE ARE BOTH DOOMED,
BOTH OF US PRISONERS
OF ONE KIND OR ANOTHER.
NO FINAL WORDS ?
[ Woman's Voice ]
WHAT'S IT GONNA BE, SUGAR ?
HIPS OR LIPS ?
WHAT ?
[ John ] GOOD NEWS, STARK.
LOOKS LIKE YOU WON'T BE GOING
BACK TO PRISON.
[ Electrical Surging,
Shorting ]
[ Computer Voice ]
CLOSING COMPUTER LINK WITH
ROVER 1 SURFACE VIDEO CAMERA.
COORDINATES RECEIVED
FROM L4 PENITENTIARY.[ Beeps ]
AUTOPILOT SEQUENCE ENGAGED.
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
MASANI ?
I SAY
LET'S BLOW THIS ROCK.
[ Bump, Disengaging Noise ]
[ Rocket Boosters Sounding ]
FINISHED.
BEAUTIFUL.
SO MUCH FOR MY FIRST TRIP
TO THE MOON.
- NOT EXACTLY WHAT YOU HAD
IN MIND, HUH ? SORRY.
- DON'T BE.
[ Dana ]
I ALWAYS KNEW YOU WERE
HIGH-MAINTENANCE.
CLOSED-CAPTIONED BY
CAPTIONS, INC. LOS ANGELES