The following film
is based on court records, interviews,
and the book False Arrest.
Some names, characters, and
scenes have been changed.
Hey.
We missed you, baby.
Whatcha got?
Shut up.
Guns.
I don't like guns.
That's okay, baby.
We'll just use a knife then, eh?
You really have to push these guys.
I don't care what the
competition is bidding.
Hold on a second, Jason turn that down.
Jason, Eden.
Yeah, Mom.
Honey, turn Jason's
TV down, I can't hear.
Let me turn this down.
Hey, don't touch that!
Stop it, just a little bit.
I'm watching that!
- Why don't we with Fidelity.
- Stop!
In January.
Come on, Jason.
We can work
this out, we're free.
- Your mother can't hear.
- Ron!
Your news makes noise, too!
That's my show.
That's his favorite show, Ron.
- Much worse.
- Okay, okay.
Just tryin' to help.
Look, why don't we talk about this
when I get to the office?
All right, I'll see you in a bit.
Bye bye.
Jason.
What is that?
Good morning to you, too.
And what time did you roll in last night?
Always such a mother.
Honey.
Push your hair back.
I don't like it when it's
in your eyes like that.
Have some orange juice, Eric.
How's the band coming?
When do we get to hear you guys play?
I don't know.
It's not your kind of music anyway, Ron.
Not my kind of music, huh?
What is my kind of music?
Beats me.
- Oh, Toni.
- Yes.
Will you make a tuna casserole
for the kids tonight?
Tuna again?
I know, it's New Year's,
but that's what they want.
And don't forget a salad.
Do I ever forget salad?
Never, bye.
I'm trying, Joyce, I'm really trying.
The kid hates my guts.
He's just being careful.
Give him time.
Sure, like maybe another five years?
Maybe after 10 years, he
could work up to a hello
or a good morning.
You're making a big deal out of nothing.
The kids love you.
I love you.
I'm trying.
I know you are.
And you're doing a great job.
Is that all I get?
Mm.
Don't forget the party tonight.
I'm gonna start early.
One for Kathy and one for Arthur.
Where you going?
Nowhere.
Hey, how about my 50 bucks?
We'll be back.
Okay, put your shirt back on,
and Susie will give you the forms to sign.
Well, it's right on this chart.
I had it before.
Morning.
Early in the day for that.
One for you, Happy New Year.
- Thank you.
- And for my darling brother.
Hey, you want some good news?
Madison?
200 physicals minimum guaranteed.
Oh, all right!
Oh, thank god, I was about
to offer them your body.
My body, thank you very much.
Oh, also, Arizona is putting
out a new contract for bids,
physicals for state-owned daycare centers.
Oh, I'll get on that right away.
As soon as I run this over to Arthur.
Hey partner.
Partner!
- Hey!
- Hi, honey.
- How are you?
- Happy New Year!
- Is this for me?
- Yes, it is.
Oh, you're such a sweetheart.
- Thank you.
- Hi, Bobby.
- Thank you, honey.
- Hey, Joycie.
When's that husband of yours
gonna let me make him a millionaire?
We're workin' on it, Bobby.
Hey, I got investors
lining up around the block.
Happy New Year to you and your family.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Bobby.
We'll see ya.
Guess what?
What?
We landed the
Madison Insurance account.
I love it!
My sister, the tycoon!
- Yep!
- Ah, so?
What?
The loan will be repaid on schedule?
Oh, what are you putting
the muscle on your own sister?
Business is business.
And we are going
after a state contract next.
- You're on a roll.
- Mm-hm.
You're gonna be proud of me.
I'm already very proud of you.
Hey Arnie!
Eh, what do you think?
This is what you brought
me here for, Bobby?
Rugs?
Carpets, Arnie.
Genuine Persian carpets.
They go for 6,500 a piece.
Carpets, rugs, what the
hell is the difference?
They're old.
Sure they're old, that's
the way they like 'em.
And I want you to peddle 'em for me.
Oh yeah, no problem.
A lot of my friends pay 65 for an old rug.
Excuse me, carpet.
Arnie, I'm gonna give you
the names of some buyers.
It'll be no problem.
Joycie, baby, ooh,
you're lookin' good mama.
You are lookin' good.
Oh, Arnie.
I thought maybe you and
I could go out for a drink
after work, how's that sound?
Arnie, it's New Year's Eve.
You know, family, friends, Guy Lombardo,
any of that ring a bell?
I was thinkin' of
another New Year's Eve.
We didn't need no Guy Lombardo, eh?
Arnie, don't touch me!
She's crazy about me, eh?
We used to be an item, Joyce and me.
Once, we had one date once
when we were 17 years old.
He's still 17.
Oh, you don't know what
you're missin', Joycie babe.
I think I do.
Oh.
Ha!
Good.
He crazy, you know that?
Hey!
Everyone.
Everyone, come on over.
Pat, come on up here.
Pat and I wanna thank
each and every one of you
for making this the most successful year
in the history of Graphics Dimension.
We're the fastest growing printing company
in the Southwest, and you've
done one hell of a job.
Hi, Sherry.
We are solid, we are stable,
we have formed a firm
foundation for the future.
And the best is yet to come, cheers!
Hi, honey.
- Let me get you a glass.
- Okay.
Looks like a good party.
- Marilyn.
- Hi.
Champagne?
Yes, thank you.
- Excuse me.
- Okay.
Oh, that's a gorgeous outfit, Joyce.
You look trim.
Thank you, you look wonderful, too.
Hey, Wally.
Hey, Joycie.
Happy New Year.
Do you believe it?
1991.
You know what, Wally?
You are the best designer I know.
Thank you.
I just can't help thinking
how much better you'd be
if you didn't fry your
brains on this stuff.
Hey, Joyce, it's a party.
Don't you see how big this is?
Opportunity doesn't come along this often.
And this deal could
change our whole lives.
Look, hype our clients all
you want, don't do it to me.
I'm offering you half the
chips in the biggest game
you ever had a chance
to sit in in your life.
The chance for big money.
Seven figures.
Were those Vegas guys holding the cards?
I don't like that game, Ronnie.
If we something wrong,
they don't take us to court and sue us.
They call in the Louisville Slugger
and they break our knees.
Why do you wanna pass up
an opportunity like this?
Pat, trust me.
I've always done right by you.
This is the time to take the next step.
Come on, let's have some champagne.
Come on.
No, I gotta think
about this, you guys go.
What are you guys gonna do?
Don't ask questions.
I don't like this.
20 minutes, let's move.
Just put on somethin' sexy.
We're gonna be wanting to
party when we get back.
You gotta trust your instincts, honey.
If it doesn't feel right to you,
you shouldn't take a chance on it.
Ron has done a great job.
The business is taking off,
I can't fault him for wanting to be rich.
I'm happy with the way we live now.
Who needs the aggravation?
Did you get the cards ready?
I laid 'em out, Mom.
Ooh, I better get some quarters.
I'll get it.
Oh, napkins, napkins, napkins.
Good evening, sir.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Ooh.
Uh, anything wrong, officer?
Well, we're doing some
checking on a person
that has been seen in this neighborhood.
We were wondering if you
might've noticed something
that could be of help to us.
Whatever you need.
May I come in?
What did this person do?
If I could just come in, sir.
Sure, come on in.
Don't say a word.
Oh, dear.
You call your wife.
Like hell I will.
You call her, or
we'll get her ourselves.
- Marilyn.
- Yeah?
Come in here.
Come on, lady.
It's all right.
Who else is here?
Uh, just her mother.
She's in the den.
Get her.
Move, damn it.
Hey, come on.
Take her.
Hands behind your back.
Just take it easy.
Stay back there, lady.
Mother,
Mother, we're being robbed.
Mother please, do what they say.
- Pat!
- What do you guys want?
Cash and jewelry, where is it?
I've bot a couple
hundred bucks in my wallet.
It's in the bedroom, I'll show you.
Move, move.
- What do you want?
- Let's go, go, go.
Here, here, please, please,
take my earrings.
Take my ear...
Come on, gimme the bracelet.
- Give the bracelet.
- My keys are on the string.
Get in there, get on the floor.
- Please don't hurt me,
- Get down, on you knees!
Do it, do it.
- Don't hurt us, please.
- Head down.
You say there's cash, where is it?
It's in the drawer there.
It's on the left-hand side.
Hey, you people are supposed to be rich.
Where's the gold?
- Here, there's my diamond.
- Say there's money,
we know you got money, where's the safe?
We don't have a safe.
We were robbed about two years ago.
We have a safety deposit box in the bank.
Please take my diamond ring.
Man, this stuff is garbage.
Look, we don't need these people no more.
No, no, don't!
Hello?
Yes?
Oh my god.
What is it?
How, what happened?
Who is it, what's going on?
We'll be right there.
Ron Lukezic, we're
friends of the family.
It's all right.
Mr. and Mrs. Lukezic, I'm Lt. Martinson.
All they would tell me on the phone
was that an emergency, what happened?
There was a break in.
What about Pat and
Marilyn, are they all right?
No, they aren't.
I'm sorry to say.
Mr. Redmond and Mrs.
Redmond's mother are dead.
Oh my god.
I can't believe this.
We were just with them this afternoon.
What about Marilyn?
Is she all right?
Mrs. Redmond's in the hospital.
We don't know if she's
gonna make it or not.
Carry this outta here.
Oh look, look.
Was she raped?
Was it a ritual killing?
I can't
give you any answers now.
- Who's this?
- She's nobody.
Who is the
lady there, the woman?
Leave her alone, please.
Thank you, thank you.
Answer his questions.
Wait, there
was one shot, Lieutenant.
Dr. Samuels, line three.
Comin' through.
Redmond's son just flew in from Ohio,
he's in there with her now.
Oh Joyce.
Mike.
Oh god.
Hey, you come and stay with us, all right?
Okay.
They operated all night.
She's been in and out.
If the bullet had been a fraction
of an inch to either side,
she wouldn't be alive.
Hi.
It's Joyce.
I'm so sorry.
They hurt me.
I know.
Oh, Pat.
Oh, my god Pat.
- Pat's dead.
- Shh, Marilyn.
Go to sleep.
This is one of the
biggest police operations
in our city's history.
The people responsible
will be brought to justice,
I promise you.
It's a bad killing, Joe.
The mayor's on the hot seat.
Well, it won't get any better
with you guys snapping at my heels.
You've got to get those killers.
This is no pool room shooting.
We're talking about two murders
in a home in Scottsdale.
The whole town is running scared.
Four days, Joe,
and your detectives haven't
turn up as much as a footprint.
Now just a minute, I've got
every available man and woman
working on this case.
I wanna get these guys
just as much as you do.
We know that, Joe,
but you've seen the television
coverage, it's killing us.
What am I supposed to do?
All I can do is my job.
Dan?
This is my best man.
Come on in, Dan.
You all know Dan Ryan,
my chief investigator.
Anything break yet?
Not in the half hour
I've been sitting out there
waiting for you.
Wise guy, huh?
No sir, I just hate wasting time.
You have something for us, Ryan?
I have Mrs. Redmond's
description of the killers.
Now I'm thinking maybe this
is an armed robbery gone sour?
Thieves don't usually put a bullet
in the back of your head
and then slash your throat.
What if they were high?
There's no evidence of drugs, nope.
What you've got here is a
bonafide contract killing.
With these people?
The Redmonds are the people next door.
So where's the motive?
These clowns are hired guns, understand?
We find them, we find whoever
it is that set up the hit.
Is this all right?
It's the only black dress I have.
You're wearing a gun to the funeral?
I'm scared, Joyce.
Why was Pat killed?
Maybe it had something
to do with the business.
What are you saying?
You think you could be next?
I don't know what to think.
The Redmond murder case
continues to baffle police tonight.
It has been five days
since the brutal killings
of Patrick Redmond and his
mother-in-law, Helen Phelps.
Now this just into the newsroom.
Composite drawings of
the three murder suspects
have just been released
by the police department.
They were assembled by descriptions
provided by Mrs. Redmond,
who miraculously survived
being shot in the head.
Assistant D.A. Joseph
Brownley has asked the public
for their help in the
identification and apprehension
of the Redmond killers.
Martinson.
Who?
Oh yeah?
Take it easy.
They was at my place New
Year's Eve, three of 'em.
They was drinkin'.
I got three, I got three, one of 'em said.
He kept sayin' I got three.
Slow down, okay?
Look, I'm scared, I'm on probation,
I can't afford to mess up.
We'll take care of it.
Do you know where they are?
Yeah.
Chicago.
Get somebody
'round the back of this place.
All right, I got it, I got it.
Get out of the way, move it!
Come with me, Johnson!
Hey, hey, hold
it, police are here.
Move it, move
it, get outta the way!
Police officers coming through.
- Come on, come on.
- Police, open up!
Take it, take it!
- Get in there, get in there.
- Freeze, freeze!
Hold it right there!
- You, up against the wall!
- Don't move! Onto the ground!
- Don't move, don't move!
- Quiet!
- Oh my god!
- Hold it, hold it!
Get her, stop her,
stop right there, come here,
come here, come here, come here.
Hold it, hold it, right
there, right there,
come on baby, come on!
Freeze!
Up before
I blow your brains out!
Relax.
Be calm.
Gotcha.
Mrs. Redmond, you're
certain about those two men?
Yes, I'm certain, they're the ones.
Okay, let the others go.
Thank you, ma'am.
Let's go.
You guys are crazy.
See, I ain't murdered nobody.
Uh-huh.
Well, that's okay Hoop.
We got plenty of time.
I tell you what, why don't we just start
at the very beginning, shall we?
Who hired you?
Hey, come on.
I don't know what the
hell you're talkin' about.
I'm tellin' ya, I never
even heard of Redmond
until I saw his name on television.
Hey, hey, take it easy, Billy.
Didn't do anything,
we're gonna find it out.
I didn't do anything.
Well, if you did do something,
we're gonna find that out, too.
Tell us again.
I gotta have some sleep.
We all have to, Ed.
But not until you tell us
who put out the contract.
Morning.
- Bye.
- Eric, wait a minute.
I gotta run, Mom.
Eric, I wanna talk to you.
Mom, I gotta
rehearse with the band.
Honey, listen to me.
I'm concerned about you and Ron.
I'd appreciate it if you
talked to him once in a while.
Why?
Because he's your
stepfather, and he loves you.
Mom, what Ron loves is Ron.
He's a jerk, and
everybody sees it but you.
Eric, he is my husband,
and I married him
because I love him,
now if you don't wanna make
an effort for yourself,
will you please do it for me?
Sure.
Just like he's doin', huh?
Come on.
Mom.
Give me a hug.
That's my boy.
I'll talk to you later.
Precinct.
Yes, and I said there was a weapon
they need to knew on
Paulson Street this time.
Any luck?
No, still workin' on it.
Another shift in there now.
Gentlemen.
Mr. Hooper just broke.
Gave me two names.
Bobby Cruz and Arnie Merrill.
Hey.
Breakfast is on me.
Let's go to work.
I told you.
Thank you, buddy.
Terrific.
We get the warrants late and
the two jokers skip town.
We'll get 'em.
Got any mugshots for me?
Yeah.
Bobby Cruz and Arnie Merrill.
They both have records.
I sent copies to every police
department in the country.
Mm.
So, we catch these two, we
solve the crime of the century?
Yeah, I wish it was that easy.
I got a feeling these two
guys are just the middlemen.
Cruz.
He's Joe Farriola's nephew.
- Chicago family?
- Uh-huh.
He involved in this?
Maybe.
See Cruz thinks he runs Arizona.
He borrowed three boys into town.
What about Arnie Merrill?
Arnie's just a cheap wise guy,
runs a small time burglary ring.
He does jobs for Cruz, he picked
our boys up at the airport.
What's the connection to Pat Redmond?
I don't know, but we're
making connections fast,
don't worry.
See Cruz is in real
estate with Arthur Ross,
see Arthur Ross is
Joyce Lukezic's brother.
Business partner's wife?
And guess who Joyce
dated way back in New York
before she met her first husband?
Arnie Merrill.
- Interesting.
- Uh-huh.
But you're not giving me
anything I can take into court.
Joe, you'll be in court
soon enough, all right?
Right now, the name of the game
is to force these guys out,
Arnie and Cruz, make them talk,
then we can grab the bastard who paid 'em.
I don't care what the reason is,
the color bled here.
I won't accept inferior work.
Ron, this is an old machine.
I don't want excuses,
I want it done right!
Do I have to do everything myself?
- Honey, what's the...
- Oh.
What's going on?
Old Ron's been wound
a little tight lately.
Honey, did you have
to chew 'em out like that
in front of everyone?
I'm sick and tired of
their lame excuses, hello.
Yeah, hold on a second.
What are you doing here, anyway?
Well I was hoping
you might be able to come home for dinner.
Can I call you back?
Look.
We haven't spent one night
together since the funeral.
I wish I could, I'm swamped,
the machines are breaking
down, I'm going out of my mind.
We never see you anymore.
Joyce, it's tough without Pat.
Don't you understand that?
Just come home for dinner,
and I'll drive you right
back here afterwards, okay?
I've got work to do.
Hello, right.
Excuse me, I'm lookin'
for Harriet McClay.
Are you Merrill's daughter?
Yeah, who's lookin'?
Dan Ryan, with the
county attorney's office.
I'd like to talk to you about your father.
What's he done now?
Well, your father's been connected
to a very serious crime.
I have a warrant for his arrest,
I'd like you to get him a message.
How am I supposed to know where he is?
Just do it, okay?
I have your old man dead
to rights on a murder rap.
Tell him to call me, and
maybe we can make a deal.
Otherwise, he's going to the gas chamber.
Have a good one.
What, what do want right now?
I need something
for the next two months.
I can't talk about
it now, I really can't.
Joyce, we made a
commitment to this business,
do or die, whatever it
takes, what happened to that?
Look, I would love to stay
here and talk to you about it,
but my kids are waiting on
a hot street corner for me,
I have to go!
Well Joyce, I just
wish I had a rich husband
to fall back on.
Hey, what's wrong?
Kathy is upset with me.
I can't say as I blame her though,
I'm not exactly carrying
my share of the load.
Why not?
God, Arthur, these murders
have got everybody crazy.
Ron is flipping out at work,
Eric is not talking to anybody.
I don't seem to be able to keep
my mind on business anymore.
Oh, I know, it's getting to me, too.
I had a visit from the
county investigator.
Lookin' for Bobby Cruz.
Why?
Is Cruz involved?
Do I know?
Took off weeks ago, I
haven't seen him since.
Listen, Joyce, I had a run-in
with Ryan a few months ago,
I mean, this guy is something else.
He drove a truck right through
the window of my gun shop.
Why would he do that?
Oh, he had some idea
that I was running a bookie operation.
Were you?
Joyce, the point is,
he's got it in for me,
and I'm just paranoid enough to think
he's gonna try to pin this thing on me.
Oh, come on, that's ridiculous.
No, no it's realistic.
This is a big case,
they're under a lot of
pressure to make a bust.
Now, I'm not gonna take a fall
for something I didn't do.
And Joyce, I'm gonna tell you something,
if I were you, you better look out.
Ryan.
Arnie Merrill here.
Arnie, you're lookin' at
a charge of murder one, pal.
Why don't you do yourself a favor
and come in out of the cold?
Harriet said something about a deal.
I'm not after you, Arnie,
but I want whoever's pulling your strings.
First, we talk.
No cops, alone.
You got my word.
Now where you at?
The city that's so
nice, they named it twice.
Taxi!
Arnie Merrill?
You Arnie Merrill?
You buyin', I'm talkin'.
We both know I'm no trigger man.
No, that's right, Arnie.
You're just a warm and
wonderful human being
who fingered the Redmonds, come on,
I'm tired of this song and dance.
Talk!
I just, I don't know
what's in it for me.
Oh, is that it, eh?
Fine, you don't wanna talk?
I got a warrant right here
that says I extradite you
back to Phoenix tonight.
You ready?
Okay, okay.
Bobby Cruz.
What's the matter with you?
What, you don't hear too good?
We know all about Bobby Cruz,
I need to know who was behind Cruz.
Come on, Arnie, try.
Come on!
Gimme a break, eh?
Hey, this was your break, pal.
Only you're too dumb to know it.
You wanna break?
Come on, let's get outta here,
come on, get up, come on!
All right, hold on.
Hold on, what's the
problem, cool your jets.
- What's the problem?
- Yeah, sit down, eh?
You're under arrest, come on.
All right, all right, all right.
- You gonna talk to me?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Now, Arnie.
It was Joyce.
Excuse me?
Joyce.
Joyce who?
Joyce Lukezic?
You got it.
What, she planned the whole thing, eh?
Right.
Right, what do you take
me for, an idiot, huh?
What do you take me for an idiot, huh?
Get your hands off,
I tell you, it's true.
I can prove it, all right?
- You can prove it?
- I can prove it.
Joyce was the one.
Mom, do we have to wait?
I'm hungry.
Yeah Mom, let's eat.
Ron's not coming, neither is Eric.
Okay.
I'm starving, I'm gonna go.
Take the place mats.
I'm not gonna
call him, you call him.
No, I'm not gonna call the boy.
You wanna
eat, you set the table.
Those things make me nervous,
I told you last night.
We have a deal, remember?
I'm gonna take care of
you, but I need it on tape.
I can't put it on the tape.
I did it on account of fear, sheer fear.
I was terrified of Bobby Cruz.
And I didn't get a nickel for it.
Valium, I need it for my back.
Why don't you start talkin', Arnie?
About four years ago, Joyce came to me.
Wanted to know if I knew someone
who would kill her husband.
Her husband?
Why she want him killed?
She wanted to take over the business.
I told her no way, no way.
Okay, what happened next?
Nothin', until last September.
Bobby Cruz showed me this
picture of Pat Redmond.
I asked him where he got it.
And Cruz said, from Joyce.
Cruz offered me $10,000
to take out Mr. Redmond.
Did Cruz say why he
wanted Redmond killed?
Yeah, he said he wanted to
take over the printing company.
He also said within six months,
we get rid of Ron Lukezic.
How does Joyce figure that?
I don't know.
- You don't know?
- No.
Okay.
Maybe.
Were Cruz and Joyce partners?
And maybe they were planning on
running the business together?
It's possible.
Okay, then.
Why did Cruz want Ron Lukezic killed?
Said he wanted to
take over the business.
So he and Joyce could be partners
and run the business together.
Yeah, okay.
Businessman Robert
Cruz was extradited today
from St. Charles, Illinois,
and flown back for trial
here in Phoenix.
Police across the country
have been searching for Cruz
in connection with the
murders of Patrick Redmond
and his mother-in-law on New Year's Eve.
Three other men,
reportedly professional hit
men associated with the mob,
have also been charged with the murders.
Cruz has been working out
of a building in Scottsdale
where he maintained
offices with Arthur Ross,
a local real estate developer.
Police are speculating on
Ross's involvement in the case
but failed to comment
on whether he'd be called
in for questioning.
We will continue to bring.
What's the matter?
Something's wrong.
I'm gonna call your Uncle Arthur.
In other news today,
city officials are making
a controversial proposition
that will limit water use in
residential private homes.
As we turn to our weather map,
it was another scorcher today.
Temperatures of 107 in Phoenix today
while Tucson and Nogales both
reached a sweltering 110.
Come on, let's go.
Yeah, whatever they want.
They wanna go, us doing the report.
And she wouldn't tell?
Wally Roberts?
Dan Ryan.
I appreciate you callin' me.
Hi, how you doin'?
You want a drink?
No, thank you.
This you?
Graphic Designer of the Year?
Campaign of the Year, very impressive.
I manage to keep busy.
Yeah, you must be very good.
Me, I could hardly ever draw.
Well, I guess it's something
you have to be born with,
you know what I mean?
I guess so, this yours?
A pipe is not against the law.
I didn't say it was.
But uh, they use these
to freebase cocaine.
- Yeah.
- Don't they?
I wouldn't know.
The hell you wouldn't.
You're high right now, aren't you?
So Wally.
What is it that you wanted
to talk to me about?
There's a yellow car out there.
I recognize it.
I'm no idiot, and yesterday,
it was a blue car.
So?
Look, I am being followed
here, and I don't like it.
I don't like it at all.
You expect me to do something about it?
Right.
You make them go away,
and I'll make you a deal.
Hm.
Well, what have you got, Wally?
You uh,
you wanna know about the Redmond murders?
Okay.
If the information is good,
I'll see what I can do.
Do it now.
Sure.
Right after I leave.
So Wally, what have you got?
Joyce.
She uh, she told me.
Told you what?
Joyce said that she was
gonna have Pat Redmond killed.
Hi, I want another one.
What's the matter, Mom?
Something's wrong.
Your Uncle Arthur is in
some kind of trouble.
Well, I don't thinks so,
I think he just left town
on business or something.
No, without tell me?
No.
It's not like him.
You know what?
I like your hair like that.
Very chic.
Chic?
Ouch, Mom, old ladies are chic.
Excuse me.
Maybe that's why Mark
Campbell doesn't like me.
Maybe he thinks I'm chic.
And who's Mark Campbell?
I told you.
He's that senior that I was gonna call up
and ask to the backwards dance.
So?
I lost my nerve.
No guts, no glory.
No, see, he's got
this amazing girlfriend,
and I'm like from nowhere.
I had a similar problem
when I was in high school.
I'll tell you what Grandma told
me if you think it'll help.
She always used to say,
I think you're a wonderful young woman.
And if some bozo doesn't see
the beauty that I see in you,
then he's got a problem, not you.
Does that help?
No.
Never helped me either.
That was great, it was a lot of fun.
We should do that more often.
Well, once we get
that state contract, honey,
I'll have more time.
Ha, I'll never see you then.
Where are my keys?
What the heck?
- Joyce Lukezic?
- Yes.
Phoenix police, I have
a warrant for your arrest.
- What?
- Step out of the car, please.
Over here.
Put your hands on the hood of the car,
spread your legs, we're
gonna frisk you, ma'am.
What?
Mom, stop it, get away from her!
You're charged with conspiracy
to commit capital murder.
What?
You have the right to remain silent.
Eden, go call Ron.
If you up the right to remain silent,
anything you say can and
will be used against you
in a court of law.
- Mom, Mom!
- What are they saying?
What did they say?
They're gonna take my mom away!
- What are they saying?
- Mom, Mom!
Mom, Mom!
- Hold on, there.
- Mom!
Hey!
Mom!
Come on now, Joyce.
We all know you had Pat Redmond killed.
Now you'll make it a lot easier all around
if you just tell us thew whole story.
I don't know what you're talking about!
How could you even think I
would do a thing like that?
Those people were my friends!
Why do you keep lying, Joyce?
You're just making it harder on yourself.
I am not lying.
You have the wrong person.
Sooner or later, you're
gonna find that out.
Okay.
Okay, we'll find that out.
Bobby Cruz, you know
Bobby Cruz, don't you?
Wait, wait, please, let
me explain to you who I am.
All right?
I have a home and a family.
My husband is Ron Lukezic.
I have three children,
I run my own business.
How can I think that someone like me
would be involved in a murder?
You were introduced to Bobby
Cruz by your brother Arthur,
is that correct?
We have been through this, I told you!
Tell us again.
All right.
My brother Arthur said that Bobby Cruz
represented some investors from Chicago
who were looking for
real estate in Phoenix.
Did Cruz ever offer
to introduce Ron and Pat
to potential clients for
their printing business?
He talked to Ron a couple of times.
He offered to help him
get some printing orders
from a couple of casinos in Las Vegas.
What kind of printing orders, Joyce?
Ads, brochures, playing
cards, things like that.
It never came to anything.
What would those
printing orders be worth?
To start out with, $25,000, maybe?
Right.
With the prospect of additional orders
from the other casinos
totaling possibly several million
dollars, wouldn't you say?
If they liked their work, I suppose.
So, you could say these Vegas contracts
would make the company a
pretty valuable asset, huh?
What difference does that make?
You do know that your
husband and Pat Redmond
had a buy-back clause
in their partnership?
Yes, but so what?
So what?
So after Pat Redmond's murder,
did your husband buy his
share of the company?
Yes, he did, but...
And in the event of
your husband's death,
you would inherit the whole
company, wouldn't you?
My husband's death?
Yes.
Yeah.
My god, what are you trying to do to me?
Nothing you haven't
done to yourself, Joyce.
You see, you may not
have pulled the trigger,
but you're responsible
for Pat Redmond's murder.
I wanna see you die in a gas chamber.
Are they crazy?
Mom didn't do anything, how
can they just take her away?
Where is she?
- They had her in handcuffs.
- Wait, calm down, all right?
They just
pushed us out of the way!
Calm down, we're
doing everything we can.
Your mother is gonna see Mr. Busey today.
And who's Mr. Busey?
He's a lawyer, the best in Arizona.
He'll clear things up pronto.
Ron, why did they take her away?
It was all a big, dumb mistake.
They'll soon find out she didn't
do anything and let her go.
What if they don't?
They will.
They can't blame this
on her, she's innocent.
Now, I want you all to be real good.
Don't worry, your mom'll be home soon.
Oh.
Officer, I wonder if you could
give us a little privacy,
please, sir.
Mrs. Lukezic.
I'm Martin Busey, your husband's
retained me to defend you.
Thank god, how is Ron?
How are the kids, are they all right?
Everybody's fine, they
send you their best.
I'm gonna have you back
with 'em before you know it.
Do you know what the police are saying?
They think I had Pat Redmond killed.
I know.
I don't know anything
about this whole thing,
I don't know any killers!
Um, well, you do know Bobby Cruz.
See, well, they say he's family.
Now what about Arnie Merrill,
did you have an intimate
relationship with him?
Oh, 20 years ago I
had one date with him once,
I was 17 years old, for heaven's sake.
Uh-huh, well see, now I heard
the relationship was a little
more current than that.
Come on, that's ridiculous.
Well now look, I'm on your side, here.
But you've got to understand something.
In the next few weeks,
there's gonna be some very
ugly things said about you.
Some of it true, some of it not so true.
But I've got to know what to believe
in order to fight for you.
All right, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Now.
Our friend, Mr. Merrill.
He says that your
brother's organized crime.
That's a lie.
My brother Arthur buys
and sells real estate.
He goes to Las Vegas once
in a while and he gambles,
but that doesn't make him a criminal.
Do you also know that the
police have another witness?
Someone who'll testify
that they heard you say
you wanted to have Pat Redmond killed?
Witness, what witness?
Name is, uh, Wally Roberts.
Oh, that's totally crazy.
Why in heavens would Wally
say a thing like that?
I, uh, I wish I knew.
Mr. Busey.
Honest to god, I would
not do a thing like that.
I'm innocent.
I believe you, and I'm gonna
do everything in my power
to get you back home where you belong.
We're working on a bail bond right now.
Wait, wait, wait,
where are you taking me?
Club Med.
No, I'm not supposed to go to jail.
My lawyer is posting a bond.
No seriously, I'm not
supposed, this is a mistake.
You're not supposed to take me here.
Look, you really don't understand.
I don't belong in here,
I didn't do anything,
I'm not a criminal.
Now wait a minute!
No, wait a minute, no!
No, you don't understand,
I don't belong in here,
I'm innocent!
Listen to me!
You know girl,
I don't think she does belong in here.
She ain't no criminal.
No, she's innocent.
That's right, she's
just here for a visit.
A rich lady on a visit.
A conjugal visit.
Honey, I'm gonna treat you so good.
I'm gonna wish I was you.
Why can't I come see Mom?
Aw please, try and understand, Jason.
They're only allowing two visitors today.
Even Eric can't come.
When's she coming home?
Real soon.
We're gonna have to
tough this one out, champ.
Be real grown up about it, huh?
Yeah, you can come see Mom next time.
I'll look after him.
Love you, honey.
Hi, sweetheart, are you all right?
I'm okay, Mom.
And don't worry about Eric and Jason.
They miss you like crazy, but
they're handling it real well.
Oh, thank god, I've
been going out of my mind.
Everything's gonna be all right.
We're gonna get you out of here.
When, Ron?
Busey said I wouldn't have
to spend one day in here.
It's a capital offense.
They say it'll take a few more days.
We've got a great lawyer.
We've gotta trust Busey, okay?
We'll get you outta here, I promise.
Hold on, hold on.
What do you want?
Guess.
Ooh!
Excuse me.
Hey!
- Get her arms.
- What are you doing?
- Get her arms!
- Turn around!
What are you doing?
We're doing.
You Central Avenue bitch.
Please god.
Oh god, no don't.
Just relax, please.
Oh god, don't, don't, don't please.
That's right, squeal!
I like it when you squeal.
No, no!
No, no, please god, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
Don't, no, no, no!
Oh god, no, no!
Ron, you have to get me outta here.
Somebody hurt you?
What happened?
They put me in this cell.
Joyce, tell me.
Women held me down.
What are you saying?
They raped me.
Oh my god.
Ron, please get me out of here.
You can't go back in there.
I'll make them move you.
Please, help me.
I will, Joyce.
I will.
I promise.
Eric, did you do the laundry?
No, I forgot.
You know, it's not like I'm asking you
to take the clothes down to the lake
and beat them with a rod.
Okay, I'll do it as soon as I can.
How's Mom?
Is she okay?
Is she fine?
She's been in there for three weeks!
Hey, I'm doing the best I can.
Yeah, you could've fooled me.
You got a big mouth, Eric.
Why don't you shut it up?
What are you lookin' at?
When's Mom coming home?
She'll be home when she's home.
This place is a pig sty.
I want it cleaned up.
Pick that up.
No!
I said pick it up.
Hey, don't you touch him.
Let him go!
Is that what you want, Eric?
Come on, Eric, is that what you want?
Just stop it, all right?
Stop it!
Come on, stop it.
Come on, okay, Mom's got
enough trouble, just stop it.
Any time, Ron, any time!
Lukezic.
Your bond's been posted, let's go.
I can go?
You're outta here.
Come back and visit sometime.
Wait, bitch!
No, uh-uh, it's not worth it!
Oh!
It's nothing, stop, just stop.
Mom's home!
Mom!
Oh, sweetheart!
- Mom!
- Oh, I missed you!
Oh god, I missed you
guys, let me look at you,
let me look!
Oh god, you look good.
You look great, Mom.
Mom, I hope you don't have
to go back to the slammer.
Hey, I'm home for good now,
that's it, I'm here, okay?
Four death sentences came in today
and the end of the first trial
in the Redmond murder case.
Robert Cruz, alleged to be a member
of one of Chicago's most
prominent mob families
and three professional hit men
have been found guilty
of conspiracy to murder.
The four men were sentenced to
die in Arizona's gas chamber.
Coming up next week is a
hearing for Joyce Lukezic,
the Scottsdale wife and mother
who is accused of
masterminding the murders.
The principle prosecution
witness is Arnold Merrill,
who claims that Mrs. Lukezic
entered into a conspiracy with Cruz.
Just can't figure out
why Arnie would name you.
I wish I knew.
How about Arthur?
Why'd he run?
He was just scared.
He tried to warn me,
but Arthur could never
do anything like that.
At any rate, Busey has filed
a motion for dismissal.
They'll have to drop the charges.
They don't have any choice,
this case doesn't make any sense.
Oh, god you feel good.
Uh, come on in.
Would you all like a cup of
coffee, something cold to drink?
- No, thanks.
- No, not for me.
Uh Joyce, Ron, I appreciate
you coming down here.
Um, I hate to start off on a sour note,
but we've had a bit of a setback.
What?
The dismissal wasn't granted.
What does that mean?
It means we're gonna
have to go to a trial.
I, I'm sorry.
Martin, you said that couldn't happen.
Well unfortunately,
the evidence presented
at the preliminary
hearing was strong enough
to warrant that.
What evidence?
Since when are lies evidence?
I can't believe this.
You mean that they seriously think
that Joyce planned to kill Pat and me
and take over the company?
See, the prosecution is going to argue
that your company was about to be worth
a great deal of money
because of a printing order
from Las Vegas.
Now you did go to Vegas last year
with Bobby Cruz and Ross, right?
Sure, they took me around,
introduced me to some people.
Took me to some casinos, hotels.
I almost pulled off a big
deal, but it didn't happen.
And Ron could testify to that.
Well Ron's not gonna testify.
Why not?
If I put Ron on the stand,
they can cross-examine,
and boy they'll have a field day with Ron.
There's no limit to
what they can insinuate.
Well he has to testify.
Martin knows what he's doing, honey.
Look, we have every
reason to be optimistic.
Joyce, there's no physical
evidence against you.
I can convince a jury
that this was a robbery
that went tragically wrong.
I don't know.
Joyce, please.
Let me do it my way.
I'll do my best, you have nothing
to worry about, I promise.
Hello?
Marilyn, hi, it's me.
How are you?
I'm doing okay.
I hadn't seen you.
I just wanted to make
sure you were all right.
I'm just fine.
It wasn't me, Marilyn.
You know it wasn't me.
- Don't say that!
- Shut up!
You shut up!
Jason!
Stop it!
Jason, stop that!
Stop it, Billy, get off of him!
- Stop it!
- Jason, what are you doing?
Come here, hey, hey,
what's the matter with you?
Take it back!
You take it back!
I'll grind you to mush, I'll kill you!
I'll kill you!
What happened here?
Who started this?
He started it.
Liar!
You did, you said they
were gonna kill my mom!
Billy, did you say that?
Mom, you said they were gonna
put her in the gas chamber.
I mean, you're kid's turning
into a real troublemaker.
Come on.
Hey, sport.
Leave me alone.
What's with him?
He just had a fight.
Billy told him I was
going to the gas chamber.
Let him calm down first.
Oh god.
He's having trouble now,
what's gonna happen once the trial starts?
They're gonna drag me through the mud.
All you have to do is tell the truth.
Oh, what's the truth?
They're gonna sleaze
everything up, you know that.
Our marriage, our divorces,
our bank accounts,
our companies, my brother's business.
I can't let Jason go through that.
Flight 20 to Boston,
now boarding gate three.
I wanna stay with you.
I want you to stay, honey.
It hurts me as
much as it hurts you.
But you're gonna have a
great time with your dad.
If it hurts, why are
you sending me away?
Did I do something bad?
No, no, not at all.
I love you very, very much.
I'm always gonna be there for you.
As soon as this dumb trial is over,
we're all gonna be
together again like family,
just like we always were.
All right? Flight 409 to Chicago
is arriving at gate nine.
To carousels four.
Ready to go, little guy?
So long, champ.
Watch out for yourself.
You have fun, okay man?
I'm gonna miss you little brain.
Mm, gimme a kiss.
- Gimme kiss.
- Yuck.
- Bye, Mom.
- Be good.
I see 'em, go!
Come on, let's go.
Come on, guys.
Mrs. Lukezic, Mrs. Lukezic.
Are these your children here?
Are you innocent or guilty?
Are these your two children?
How long do you expect the trial to last?
Excuse me, sir, excuse me, sir.
We've been
waiting out here for hours.
We need some help here.
How long do you expect
the trial to last, please!
All rise.
Department A of the Superior
Court of the State of Arizona
is now in session.
The Honorable Rudolph
Gerber Judge presiding.
Please be seated.
People of the State of
Arizona versus Joyce Lukezic.
And um, Pat told me
that Ron was negotiating
a big order in Las Vegas.
Joyce's brother was gonna
get them all the printing
they wanted, worth millions of dollars.
And what happened
to that Las Vegas business?
Well, it fell through.
Pat said, I don't want to
have anything to do with it.
He was not willing to kick
back or pay bribes to the mob.
I said to Joyce, I hear
the Vegas deal is off.
She was mad.
She said, the deal is not off.
What else did she say?
She said she was tired of
Pat holding the business back.
She said, I'm going to have
the son of a bitch wasted.
She said, I have the connections
to have Pat Redmond killed.
I will bar from this court anyone,
including any member of the media,
that disrupts these proceedings.
Your witness.
Mr. Roberts, you have a
severe drinking problem,
don't you?
Objection, Your Honor.
Irrelevant and immaterial.
It relates to the witness's credibility
and objectivity, Your Honor.
Overruled.
Yes, I'm a recovering alcoholic in AA.
Uh-huh.
Now, Mr. Roberts.
Did you also have a problem
last year with narcotics
or drugs of any nature?
Yes, I did.
In fact, Mr. Roberts,
isn't it fair to say
that every single day, you
were either high on alcohol
or high on cocaine at
some part of the day?
Yes, I was.
I was high most of the day
on one thing or another.
No further
questions, Your Honor.
Don't worry.
Wally looked like a jerk.
The jury's gonna discount his testimony.
Maybe not.
See, maybe they're thinkin'
we wouldn't be so dumb
as to use that clown as a witness
unless he was tellin' the truth.
Oh yeah?
We'll get hurt.
I need to re-establish credibility fast.
Well, I'm workin' on it.
Don't work on it, fix it.
My job is on the line, so is yours.
Be careful with that.
Set it down here.
Having a little garage sale?
More like a
going-out-of-business, sale.
Mm, I was gonna get one of these.
But I figured, why spend all the money.
I could just go out and run five miles.
Of course, I didn't do that either.
Can I do
something for you, Mr. Ryan?
Yes, you can.
You could answer a few more
questions about your partner.
If you don't mind.
My ex-partner.
And I've already told you all I know.
Oh yeah?
Well, seems to me
you had a pretty good
little business here.
Why'd you walk away from it?
Well, I'm not the one doing the walking,
so I can't really answer that, can I?
So Joyce quit?
Yep.
After I left a good job to go into this.
You know.
She's gotta spend some
time now with her family.
Her husband.
They're pretty close, aren't they?
Her husband?
You really don't know anything, do you?
They got a few problems?
A few?
Have you talked to anyone else?
I mean, it's not exactly a secret.
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?
I'm saying that Joyce was upset
because her husband was having
affairs with other women.
Objection, Your Honor.
Move to strike, this is not relevant.
Objection is provisionally overruled.
Go ahead.
What did she say?
She said that she would
have Ron taken care of.
She said her brother had
connections in the mob,
she said she'd have Ron's
ass and his business, too.
Order, order in the court.
Order in the court.
Why didn't you tell me?
- It was nothing.
- Nothing?
You knew we were vulnerable.
Why did you conceal that affair from me?
It happened last year.
It was an affair, it meant nothing.
I was devastated when I found out.
All I wanted to do was to hit back at Ron.
Now wait a minute here,
did you actually say those things
about having Ron taken care of?
It didn't mean anything,
it was just crazy talk.
We talked it over
and decided to give our
marriage another chance.
Is there anything else I need to know?
No.
How badly did Kathy hurt us?
She just shoved a knife in our back.
Hello?
Murderer,
you're gonna burn in hell.
You have a nice day too.
I'll have the number changed.
No, you won't.
Days of this.
I just want it all to be over.
Joyce, would you be very upset
if I didn't come to court tomorrow?
Ron, I need you there.
And I wanna be with you,
but I've been thinking about the TV news.
They'll be on us like flies tomorrow.
There's not much we can
do about that, now is there.
Yeah, we could avoid it.
I just don't wanna create a situation
where our marriage is
on trial in the TV news.
The trial belongs in the courtroom.
Honey.
I really need you to be there for me.
I mean, it's bad enough that
my own brother took off.
How do you think I feel?
Look Joyce, I am doing
everything I can for you.
Everything.
The lawyers are expensive,
the business is damn near bankrupt.
We don't agree on this,
but I know I'm right.
Joyce, honey.
Joyce.
Last Thanksgiving, I was
sitting in the waiting room
of Sunview Development, and Joyce came in.
She went into her brother's office, right,
and Mr. Cruz was there at the time.
Did you attempt
to listen at the door?
I didn't have to listen at no door.
The sound came right through the wall.
What were they talking about?
Well, Joyce asked Mr. Cruz
why Mr. Redmond hadn't
been taken care of yet.
Did Mr. Cruz reply?
Yes, he did.
He told Joyce that Mr.
Redmond would be dead
before Christmas.
Your witness.
Mr. Merrill, do you
tell lies very often?
Objection, Your Honor,
he's insulting the witness.
Sustained.
Isn't it true, Mr. Merrill,
that you knew you were about to be charged
with first degree murder
unless you could come up with a story
that could cut yourself a
deal with the prosecution?
No, sir.
And in order to save your own skin,
you tried to convince them
that Joyce Lukezic was
involved, didn't you?
No.
Isn't that why you
concocted this whole story?
- Objection.
- No.
He asked and answered,
he's putting up a smokescreen.
No, nope, nope, I
didn't make up no story.
I'm tellin' the truth.
You just don't wanna hear the truth, eh?
Joyce was behind the whole thing.
I was there, I heard her.
Order.
Order in the court.
They walked right into that one.
Oh yeah.
Do you have to read that here?
Okay, we'll throw
all the newspapers out,
we'll unplug the TV, we
won't think about it,
we won't talk about it at all.
I just don't wanna
see Arnie Merrill's face
in my own house.
Honey, you're acting like a kid.
Mm, smells good.
Hope she serves it
sometime before Thanksgiving.
Isn't it a beautiful day?
What are you, the weather girl?
I gotta run.
Are you gonna be in court today?
I'll try and make it.
You'll try and make it.
I got a problem at the plant.
I don't give a damn
about the plant, Ron.
I need you there.
Busey is putting me on the stand today.
Honey, please.
Please what?
Just go ahead and tell
everybody I'm guilty,
and get it over with?
We just don't seem to be
able to communicate, do we?
I'm doing all I can to help you.
I'm paying for your lawyer.
How am I supposed to do
that if I don't work?
Well, just go ahead
and get outta here then!
Mrs. Lukezic,
could you speak a little louder, please?
I said, I didn't hire any killers.
I wouldn't know how to.
This whole thing has been some
kind of incredible mistake.
Thank you.
No further questions, Your Honor.
Did Bobby Cruz ever tell you
that he knew three hit men?
No, he never told me
anything about any hit men.
I don't know any hit men.
I don't even know Mr. Cruz that well.
Are you telling this jury
that your ex-boyfriend,
Arnie Merrill, was incorrect
when he said you went
to your brother's office
and asked Cruz why Redmond
hadn't been taken care of?
Yes, I am.
But uh, you wanted that Las
Vegas business, didn't you?
I wanted it as much
as my husband did, yes.
Mm-hm.
And Mr. Cruz wanted that
business a lot too, didn't he?
I don't know what Mr. Cruz wanted.
And your brother wanted it
as well, isn't that right?
No, that's not true.
Isn't it?
Weren't you and your
brother and Bobby Cruz
all planning on murdering
your husband next
so you could all get your
greedy hands on that business?
Objection, Your Honor.
He's badgering the witness.
Sustained.
What was your share of
the spoils going to be?
Nothing.
Well.
That's exactly what Pat Redmond got.
Isn't it?
Mr. Brownley.
Pat Redmond was a friend of mine.
We're talking about the
murder of my close friend.
I couldn't do that.
Don't you understand, I
couldn't do that!
The defendant said,
I have the connections
to have Pat Redmond killed.
This is not a robbery or a burglary.
Not at all.
This is a calculated contract murder.
Joyce Lukezic intended
to kill her own husband
six months later.
And her motive was money.
She wanted that printing company
so that she could make millions.
This is a ruthless, greedy woman,
who bought the death of her best friend.
Joyce?
Joyce, you okay?
- Hm?
- Mm-hm.
- I do.
- Here she is.
It worked, everything's gonna be fine.
How long do you
think the jury'll be out?
What do you think your
chances are, Mrs. Lukezic?
Are you okay?
The lady needs some help here, Joyce.
Get that stuff outta here!
Hey, call a doctor!
Call a doctor!
Dr. James to hematology.
- Joyce.
- Dr. James to hematology.
Joyce.
What happened?
They think it's a heart attack.
A mild one.
Oh, great.
The state wants to kill me,
my heart wants to kill me,
everybody wants to kill me.
Joyce.
I love you so.
And you're gonna be just fine.
Where are Eric and Eden?
Right here.
In the waiting room.
I feel so sorry, baby.
I feel it's my fault.
I should've been with you.
I did all right, it doesn't matter.
I'm so sick and tired of
this thing coming between us.
Be patient with me.
Someday I'll grow up.
Just hold me.
Baby.
I'm so sorry.
I understand the jury
has reached a verdict.
Due to the sudden
illness of the defendant,
we will waive her presence
for the taking of the verdict.
Bailiff, show the jury in.
Mr. Foreman, would you
please hand your verdict
to the bailiff?
What honey, what is it?
What?
Oh god Mom, they found you guilty!
No, no!
No, don't do this!
I didn't do anything!
Jesus, I didn't do anything!
Oh, Mommy!
Mommy!