(film projector clicking)
(alarm clock beeping)
(soft music)
- [James] My father
always used to say to me,
"Son, you only come this way once.
See the world, tell people what you saw.
Leave your mark,
interpret the human
experience through your lens."
So how did I end up here?
(car horn beeps)
(phone rings)
Good morning, James Hayes.
How may I help you?
Hey, Teresa.
He's downstairs to see me now?
Did he say he had an appointment?
Okay.
I gotta stop and get his loss report,
but tell him I'll be down
there in just a few minutes.
Yeah. Thank you.
- Look at that.
- That's it?
- What do you mean "That's it?"
My car didn't look like that before.
- Did you say your wife was
injured in this accident?
- Yeah, and?
- How could anyone
possibly have been injured?
I mean, the bumper's barely scratched.
- All I know is after the accident,
my wife's neck started hurting.
So we went to the hospital
and they gave her a cervical collar
and a prescription for medicine.
We're supposed to follow
up with her doctor.
That's what we're gonna do
and your company's gonna pay for it.
- Let's go inside, Mr. Frowd.
(smooth music)
- Hey.
You know, sometimes when
I'm driving to work,
I wonder how the hell did I get here?
You get paid just enough
to create a lifestyle you wanna maintain,
but you'll never make enough money
to be as comfortable as you like.
- At least you have a
job, your bills get paid.
What's the big deal?
- The big deal is we give away
the best years of our life
and energy to a place we
don't really wanna be.
- Every morning when I come in,
I see you working on something
that is clearly non-insurance related
on company time using company equipment
and it's not costing you a thing.
- I spend 40 to 45 minutes a day writing.
The rest of my day
is spent listening to people lie to me
and they don't even have
the decency to do it well.
- Speaking of lying and deceiving,
what do you think about that nonsense
they're trying to pull with the raises?
- You mean the raises we're
not getting this year?
- It's because our
expenses are really high.
- Oh, come on, Angela.
The company's losing money
because of consistently poor decisions.
- That's not it.
- Obviously you've been
drinking the Kool-Aid.
- No, I just read the annual report.
- You know, two months ago they tell us
we're not getting the raises
that we deserve this year,
only to tell us last week that
they're spending $75 million
on a brand new hockey arena in a town
that doesn't have a hockey team
and never had one.
- Yeah, but it's not like
they're gonna write a
check out for 75 million.
- I mean, do they think
that we can't figure out
that we're not getting
the raises this year
because they're spending
money on unnecessary bullshit?
- [Angela] You have options.
- Yeah, so Angela,
since you've got those hooker heels on,
why don't you to come over here
and give me a quick lap dance?
- Grow some equipment
and I'll think about it.
- You know what?
Why don't you just give him some?
Maybe he'll leave you alone.
- He wouldn't know what to do
if he had printed instructions.
(phone chiming)
- She wishes I needed
printed instructions.
- Hello?
Hey, what's up?
Oh, I know. It was awesome, wasn't it?
- Let's get started.
- That's my supervisor, Sharon.
She's required by corporate to
hold these biweekly meetings
which are a complete waste of time.
I mean, I can't even
act like I care anymore.
Not at all.
Now you've already met Steve and Angela.
That's Holly and to her right is Greg.
The people I work with
make this job bearable.
Now the only reason I ask
questions in these stupid meetings
is to keep myself from falling asleep.
♪ We said all that we could say ♪
♪ Can you relate to me in another way ♪
Uh-oh.
- What?
- When a woman is looking at a dude
like you looking at me now-
- First of all, I'm not just some woman.
I am Sanaa Medcalf,
the love of your life.
Now rephrase that.
- Okay.
When my crazy ass girlfriend, Sanaa,
is looking at me like
you looking at me now.
- Now why am I crazy?
(James groans)
- Because, damn, Sanaa,
it's 2:00 in the morning.
You gotta be at court
first thing in the morning.
And let's not forget we just had the best-
- We did not just have sex.
We made love.
(James chuckles)
- Are you gonna let me
finish the sentence?
- I just did.
- Just ask your question.
(Sanaa sighs)
- Well,
do you believe in open marriages?
- We're not married.
- Exactly.
So, I'm not talking about us.
Answer the question.
- No.
I don't believe in open marriages.
- So you feel like you
could stay with one person
for the rest of your life?
- Well I hope so.
- Do you think that's realistic?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
- I don't.
I think that some women
and most men cheat.
So, things would work out a lot better
if they could just be open
and honest with each other from the start.
- Okay, so why get married
if you wanna have sex with other people?
Just stay single.
- Do you think that I love you?
- [James] (chuckles) I hope so.
(Sanaa laughs)
- Stop being silly. You know I love you.
- Yes, baby, I know, I know.
You love me.
- What if I told you I wanted
to have sex with someone else?
- [James] Man or woman?
- Does it matter?
- [James] Yeah.
- Why?
- [James] Because if it's a woman,
I may wanna watch.
But if it's a man, I'm gonna
tell you to keep it moving.
- Well, I wouldn't mind if you
had sex with another woman.
- Okay, what's really going on here?
- Nothing.
We're just having a discussion, babe.
- Are you serious with all this?
- I just wanna pick your brain.
I think it's healthy for couples
to have these types of conversations.
♪ Show me, show me ♪
- Okay.
What if I said I wanted to
have sex with your sister?
- Karima?
- [James] Yeah, Karima.
What if I said I wanted
to have sex with Karima?
- So that's how you look at her?
- (laughs) No, but you just
sat up in here and said
you could watch me have
sex with another woman.
So what if that other woman was Karima?
- Yeah, but the fact that she was
the first person you thought about
makes me believe that
that's how you think of her.
- [James] (laughs) No, it doesn't.
- Yes, it does.
- Wait!
Sanaa.
Don't leave, Sanaa. Wait a minute!
Come on, hey, sweetheart.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Come back.
(door slams)
I knew it.
I knew it, I knew it,
and I still took the bait.
Boo.
- You know what?
This whole time that we've
been hanging out with Karima
you were secretly hoping I
would get drunk and fall asleep
so you could have sex with her.
- Get drunk? Fall asleep?
What are you talking about?
I didn't start this. You did!
- I was speaking hypothetically.
- Can we just get back in
bed and talk about this?
- No.
- Why are you feeling some type of way
about a conversation you started?
- Don't you remember me telling you
about the last guy I dated
who only used me to get to Karima?
- [James] Jesus.
♪ Got a pretty girl on the turntables ♪
♪ Bunch of pretty girls on the couch ♪
♪ See a couple mama's on the dance floor ♪
♪ They just got a bottle on the house ♪
♪ Trouble look better
with the lights off ♪
♪ Still see it written on your face ♪
♪ When the rhythm hits your
body like adrenaline shots ♪
♪ No chase, can't wait to see you move ♪
♪ Side to side ♪
♪ The revolution's on the floor ♪
♪ Now televise ♪
♪ 'Cause when you're body's in my hands ♪
♪ It never lies ♪
♪ Come get yourself some satisfaction ♪
- What's up, dude?
- Always jamming.
What's up, Beau?
- Not much, bro.
Where's your car, man?
- I took the train today.
- I hear you.
See the people, get a
little creative inspiration.
- Exactly.
That's all the footage from Rio.
You see the edit notes
that I put in your email?
- Yeah, I got it.
- Perfect.
How long do you think it's gonna take you
to get me a sample together?
- Give me a week.
- Cool.
That's what I'm talking about.
- All right, man.
- All right, I'll give you a
call in about a week or so.
- All right, bet.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's go burn one.
- No, no, man.
I can't today.
- Come on, dude. Let's go.
- Ah, maybe next time.
♪ And I've been going too long ♪
♪ Trying to catch my breath ♪
♪ If you close at four ♪
♪ You get no respect ♪
♪ Man these rows got me thrown ♪
♪ But ain't no regrets ♪
♪ Over glow, it's a show ♪
♪ It's a mother fest ♪
♪ It's a jet, it's supreme ♪
♪ I just got high with
the girl of my dreams ♪
♪ I just arrived super high to the scene ♪
♪ Pink shades make these
nights look rose colored ♪
♪ Hair long, care gone ♪
♪ Feel like soul brother out here ♪
♪ Walking on ice like four brothers ♪
♪ Baby I'm a bad ♪
♪ What you mean ♪
♪ I'm a lit man ♪
♪ Drink kerosine out of red cups ♪
♪ True life and I had a few nights ♪
♪ Where I lived too fast ♪
♪ Did the most ♪
♪ Full gas, I know this won't last ♪
♪ Trying to put put fast to the coast ♪
Baby.
♪ Ride that wave to the coast ♪
Are you still mad at me
about what I said about
your sister the other night?
- Yeah.
I'm in my feelings a little bit.
- So you brought me out here
so you could be mad face-to-face?
- Pretty much.
- Babe, we were just
having a conversation.
I really didn't mean anything by that.
And you laughin'.
What's so funny?
- I'm not really mad at you.
I just wanted to see
you squirm a little bit.
- Really?
- I mean, yeah, okay.
I was a little upset that night
but I thought about it and, like you said,
we were just having a conversation.
But.
- [James] But.
- If we're ever out with Karima
and I even so much as think
that you're checking her out,
I'ma have your ass sent for a year.
- Yeah, I hear you, babe.
I'm a peaceful brother.
I don't want none of your
people pulling up on me.
(Sanaa laughs)
You gonna have your goons pull up on me?
- I might.
(James sighs)
- So, why did you wanna meet out here?
- Okay.
Um...
I am considering
moving to New York.
- New York? Why?
- Well, a partner's retiring
and they named a woman to replace him,
a black woman.
So she reached out
and she said that this would
be a good opportunity for me.
- Opportunity to do what?
- [Sanaa] To make partner.
- Did they say that they
were gonna make you partner, Sanaa?
- Well no, but with her on my side
I have a pretty good chance.
- So is this definite?
- Well, no, nothing's definite
especially I haven't
talked to you about it.
- Babe, I appreciate that, I really do,
but damn.
New York?
- I want you to come with me.
- How am I gonna go with you?
I'd have to find a job
and what about my house?
- Yeah, I mean, there's
plenty of insurance companies
in New York
and your house, shit, you can rent that.
- I don't want another job
in the insurance business.
And I'm not just gonna be able
to rent my house out just like that.
- Babe, you work in insurance already.
I don't see what the difference is.
- I don't want another
insurance job, Sanaa.
I wanna travel so I can blog about it.
- Yeah, you can do that eventually,
but babe, right now,
I mean, come on, this is-
- Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
If we moved to New York,
it's gonna about money, marriage,
and Sanaa, what if you get pregnant?
- Well, what would be so wrong about that?
- Nothing would be wrong with any of that
once I'm established as a writer.
- All right.
I'll leave it alone.
I'm not gonna rush you into anything.
Just know that this is a
huge opportunity for me.
A game changer.
You hear?
- I get it. I get it, okay?
- Come on.
Give me a hug.
(James chuckles)
(knocking on door)
- Oh, Tony.
Uncle Tony!
- Nephew, what's going on, baby?
- What's good?
Come on in.
Hey man, why don't you get
yourself a nine millimeter
and get rid of that starter pistol?
- Shit, it'll put a hole in you.
- Yeah, but you only got six shots.
- Shit, all I need is one.
- I still say you need a
nine millimeter though.
- Nah, revolvers don't jam.
Hold on, hold on.
- What?
- How are you gonna have
me over here at dinner time
and I don't smell no grease?
- Uncle, who said anything about cooking?
I called you over here so we can talk.
- How you gonna have family
over here at dinner time
and you ain't got no food on the table?
- I don't even cook for myself.
So you know I'm not cooking you jack.
- Well, since I can't get a meal,
what you got me over here for?
Make it quick. I got shit to do.
- [Announcer On TV] Scored
Edwards landed three goals
helping pass the Wolves eight to three.
The chargers throttled
the Bucks nine to two.
- You know this some bullshit, right?
- [Announcer On TV] Tonight the Bullets
put their first place lead on the line
in a game with with the Tempests.
- Do you remember my girlfriend, right?
- The one we went to the Falcons
game with last year, right?
- Yeah, Sanaa.
- Yeah, I remember.
- What do you think?
- Personally?
I usually like them a little
thicker than that, you know?
I like them like Serena Williams.
That real big fat-
- Timeout, Uncle, timeout, timeout.
Whoo.
You wild, Unc.
That's not what I meant.
- Damn, I'm just fucking with you.
I know what you meant.
- What do you think about her?
- I mean, you know, she seems nice.
You know, I didn't talk to her that much.
She's a lawyer, right?
- Yeah.
- What's the problem?
- She got a job offer in New York,
wants me to go with her.
- Weigh your options, make a decision.
- Oh, I don't wanna go
but I love her, I care about her.
So me saying, "I don't wanna go"
it's just not that easy.
- So if you don't wanna go, don't go.
All that other stuff is your heart
trying to override what your mind
knows to be true.
- I don't know if I
wanna go down this road.
- You plan on marrying her?
- I don't know. We haven't
talked about all that.
- Do you think she wants to marry you?
- I don't know. I don't know.
- It's a yes or no question.
- Yes.
- Okay.
And you say you care about her.
- I do.
- You say you care about her
but you don't wanna tell her
that you don't wanna move to New York.
That doesn't make any sense to me.
- That's why I'm over here
talking to you about it.
- [Announcer On TV] The Gladiators
shouldn't have much
trouble with the Henchmen
and the Barbarians are still 14.
- If you say you care about her
and you're not ready to commit,
what you gotta do
is let her go to New York
and meet other people.
- [Announcer On TV]
Five games were featured
in hockey action last evening.
- If she meets a guy that
she wants to be with,
you let her go.
That's the way you treat
somebody you care about.
Now the selfish thing to do
is to, is to, you know,
lie to yourself and lie to her
and keep her around
until you figure out what you wanna do
with no regard to how
it's gonna affect her.
- So just tell her I don't wanna go?
- Why don't you wanna go?
- Because, Unc, I wanna quit my job.
You know that.
I wanna travel,
I wanna shoot my videos,
I wanna blog and I wanna write about it
and if I go off to New York with her,
it's gonna be about her,
it's gonna be more expensive,
and I'm never gonna
able to do my own thing.
- Why don't you just make-
(cell phone barking)
Hold on a second.
Hello?
- [Announcer On TV] The
front running Bullets
ripped the Crusaders 14-three
and the Dragons got
past the Jets seven-six.
- [Tony] No, I don't care nothing...
Well who is still there?
No, fuck that.
I'm gonna say it just like this.
You tell whoever is still at the house
to tell Shamal that he better
find me before I find him.
It's as simple as that.
All right, I'll see
y'all when I get there.
I gotta go.
- All right.
Hey, when you gonna stop
by and look at the deck?
- Your deck?
- [James] Yeah, remember I told
you some stairs were loose.
- Uh.
What about this time next Wednesday?
- Wednesday works.
All right, now.
(gentle music)
Who are you texting?
- Oh, it's just someone from work.
- Can it wait till tomorrow?
- No, she actually,
she's working out of her New York office.
What?
- You should go natural, grow an Afro.
(Sanaa chuckles)
- No.
Yeah, no.
- I'm serious, baby.
- No, sweetheart, that's not me.
Plus I don't think that'll
go over well at work.
- Ah, so that's it.
They won't let you go natural.
- No, they can't stop me.
But I think that it might
inhibit my advancement.
- Chemicals and all, out
here trying to assimilate.
- I am not trying to assimilate.
I like my hair the way it is.
I got you with my hair like this.
- Damn, babe, that's because
I used to squint real hard
and then I'd fantasize, ooh,
with a big old Angela Davis Afro!
You would look like this, babe.
So you wanna talk about
that big pink elephant sitting
in that chair over there?
- Oh, you mean New York?
- Yes.
- Well, I wanna go.
Are you coming with me?
- No.
- Well, why not?
You don't think it would
be a good move for us?
- I think it'd be a great
move for you and your career.
- No, it would be a good
move for the both of us.
I mean, you've established a career
in the insurance industry
and you can just take it to the next level
by coming to New York.
- Sanaa, you know I don't like my job.
I hate it.
- [Sanaa] Yeah, but your
job is your reality.
- You know, to me, you only
got two options in life.
You can either live your dream
or help someone else live theirs.
And I'm tired of helping other
people live their dreams.
- So you think coming to New York,
you'll be helping me live my dream?
- I was talking about
me, my life, my career.
I wanna get up and do
what I love for a living.
- That's unrealistic.
I mean, I love my career too,
but there's sometimes I don't
feel like getting out of bed.
I mean, everybody feels like that.
- Would you practice law for free?
- No.
- Well see, I travel,
I shoot video, and I blog about it
and I do it for free because I love it
and I wanna do what I love for a living.
- What you're talking about is a hobby.
- I'm gonna make a career out of it.
I don't know why you
don't understand that.
- So you're really not coming?
- No, I gotta be on the right path
before I can make a move like that.
- Well what about us?
- If you go to New York
and you're meeting another people
and you're working on-
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on.
- What, what?
- Meeting other people?
I thought we were in a
committed relationship.
- We are.
- So why are you talking
about meeting other people?
Is that what you're trying to do?
- Of course not.
But what I'm saying is-
- No, I heard exactly what you said.
I think it's some bullshit.
I think that you had a Freudian slip
and now you're trying
to reel back from it.
- It wasn't a Freudian slip.
I meant what I said.
- I know!
- Hold on, hold on.
- No, don't touch me!
- Will you just relax?
Babe, just chill out for a minute.
- Get off of me!
- Okay, I'm not touching you.
- So, what, I'm supposed to think
that you're going to sit
in front of your computer
for 24 hours?
You know what?
If you didn't wanna be together,
you should've just said something.
I can't do this.
- Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Come on now.
Can we talk about this?
- We just did!
- I don't wanna leave
things unresolved like this!
(door slams)
(soft pop music)
May I speak to Oscar Heiler, please?
Yes, ma'am. My name is James Hayes.
Yeah, I submitted an article
for next month's publication.
Good morning.
My name is James Hayes
and I submitted a story for December
and I got an email from you guys
saying that you needed some
more source information.
This is James Hayes.
Mm-hmm.
And I submitted a piece.
Hey Beau, what's going on, man?
I'm doing good.
Hey, well I was looking at the rough cut
from Rio last night
and there's some things I
wanna incorporate into it.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna send you the edit now.
Be careful.
See what I'm talking about?
This, this?
- Oh yeah, damn.
- [James] Yeah.
All of that.
- Yeah, see here, see?
They used nails instead of screws
and they're pulling right out.
- [James] Oh, okay, okay.
- That's an easy fix though.
- So how much is it going to cost me?
- It's not gonna cost you anything.
I'm gonna show you exactly
what needs to be done
and I'm gonna watch you do it.
- Come on, Unc, you know
I'm not handy like that.
- Yeah, I know,
that's why I'm gonna supervise.
(James laughs)
You talk to Sanaa about going to New York?
- Yeah.
- [Tony] And?
- She's in New York.
- I take that to mean you're not goin'?
- I told her to go up there, chill,
and she didn't find someone,
maybe we could be together.
- Is that how you said it to her?
- Yeah.
- No wonder she left.
- What you mean?
That's what you told me to say.
- Yeah, but I thought
you'd be smart enough
to say it the right way.
- Well, be that as it may,
what's done is done, so.
- [Tony] When did she leave?
- Mm, about two weeks ago.
- When was the last time you spoke to her?
- Tried to call her numerous times,
she won't answer the phone,
won't respond to my texts either.
(Tony scoffs)
- So how's the video blogging
and writing stuff going?
- Now that's going good.
As a matter of fact, on my way to Europe.
- Europe?
- Yeah.
- Didn't you just come back
from Rio a couple months ago?
- [James] Mm-hmm.
- [Tony] Are you sure that you
can afford to go to Europe?
- Unc, I can't afford not to.
- I respect that.
Stepping out on faith.
- Coming from you, that
means everything, man.
Everything.
So what's up with this?
- Next weekend.
Yeah, next weekend should be good.
- Cool.
- Since you're a writer,
the next time you have
something to say to Sanaa,
you should probably
write to her, all right?
This way there's a 50/50 chance
that you'll be able to edit yourself
before you say some stupid shit like,
I wanna have a threesome with her sister.
- [James] You think you
know what, you got jokes.
You think you funny.
- I'm serious.
- [James] So that's
how you do nephew, huh?
- It might be the best
advice I ever gave you.
- [James] You got jokes. Very funny.
- Now let's get out of
here. It's hot as shit.
- Of course.
Going at me about her sister.
Boy, I tell you.
(soft pop music)
Yes, sir.
Firststateinsurance.com.
Just like it's...
Yes, sir, I'll spell it for you.
F-I-R-S-T insurance.com. That's right.
Okay.
Yeah, once I receive it,
I should be able to get payment to you
in a couple of days.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for calling.
(phone rings)
Good morning. This is Jay.
How can I help you?
You wanna know if I received
the email, Mr. Frowd?
Did you get an error message?
Well then that means the
email was received, sir.
Yeah, they kinda got this email thing
pretty much figured out.
♪ I wanna lie to him ♪
♪ I just applied to win ♪
♪ I'ma provide for kin ♪
♪ The fuck with the gas again ♪
♪ I'ma get high again ♪
♪ Wanna take a flight again ♪
♪ She wanna ride and I got the drive ♪
♪ Now she wanna ride a spin ♪
♪ I can tell you judged
before we had a conversation ♪
♪ On this trip I think I
look like condensation ♪
♪ Why do whippet niggas
think I'm Ronald Reagan ♪
♪ Why you got me like
you need confirmation ♪
- Excuse me, sir. Do you have any change?
I'm just trying to get enough money
to pay for my hotel room.
They won't let me back
in the room until I pay.
- [James] No, I can't help you.
- You don't have to give the money to me.
Just go to the lobby.
- I don't have any change.
- Man.
(car horn honks)
Excuse me, Miss. Excuse me.
(soft music)
- [James] When people
come up to me begging,
I usually just brush them off.
But for some reason,
I couldn't forget about
that woman at the store.
- Look, I appreciate you
taking care of this room
and helping me with my bags and all,
but I don't have nothing for you.
- How did you end up homeless?
- We ain't even got that kind of time.
- As a matter of fact, I do.
All right, now look.
This is just gonna be two people
having a conversation, okay.
Real easy.
We're just talking
like we did a couple of days ago, okay?
- Okay.
All right.
Where do I start?
- Why don't you tell me
the first recollection of your family?
- Okay.
It may sound strange but my
first memory is of my mom.
She was arguing with someone
on the other side of the door.
I was really little,
maybe like two or three.
I couldn't tell what
she was arguing about,
but I remember that it was a man
and she was so upset.
He was screaming and cussing her out,
calling out her name.
It was a mess.
(phone rings)
Hello?
- Hey, I just finished the edit.
We're about to go live.
- About to go live?
- Yeah, the Gram, Twitter,
Facebook, YouTube, Vimeo, everywhere.
- Wait, okay.
So how am I gonna see it?
You know I don't have a phone.
- They got computers in the
hotel lobby, don't they?
- Yeah, but I never used them.
- They're for the guests
and you're a guest.
- All right, I'll check it out.
- Okay.
Hey, how's that job search going?
- Nothing ye but I'm
gonna keep it pushing.
- It's gonna happen for you.
You're too strong of
a girl to be kept out.
- Yeah, I really hope you're right.
- Well, look, I'm gonna get
back to the grind, okay?
You call me if you need something.
- You want to take a six
week leave of absence
to go to Europe to do what?
- Well I'd like to finish a project
I've been working on and I-
- Project? What project?
- Well, it has nothing
to do with insurance.
It's something I actually
do outside of work.
- And what kind of project is it?
- Well I'm writing and shooting a video
on international travel.
- That's the kind of stuff
you do when you retire.
- Well, the retired
people I see when I travel
don't seem like they're
enjoying themselves.
As a matter of fact, they look like
they just wanna sit down somewhere
and, you know, Sharon, I want to do this
while I'm still young, you know,
while I can still turn up.
- Turn what up?
(James chuckles)
- All I'm asking for is
three additional weeks
on top of the three I already have.
- Three weeks.
(upbeat music)
- My first stop was in Southern France
for the Cannes Film Festival.
(James speaking foreign language)
Natalie Portman, Kate
Blanchett were all there.
I was also just on the outside,
but I was there too.
(singing in foreign language)
And then on to Paris.
The Louvre Museum.
By the way, the Mona Lisa is a lot smaller
than you would think.
Get a flight to Rome to see the Colosseum.
And then back to reality.
(phone chiming)
Hello?
- [Sanaa] Hey, it's Sanaa.
- I know.
I still have your number
programmed in my phone.
- [Sanaa] First of all, let me apologize
for not taking your calls
or responding to your texts.
- Yeah.
I would've thought you were dead
unless your mom would
have told me otherwise.
- [Sanaa] I just...
It was a lot with the move and everything.
- I get it.
I get it, Sanaa.
But I thought you may have
at least called me before you left.
- [Sanaa] I wanted to but
I didn't know what to say.
All I could think about
was the fact that you
weren't coming with me.
And I knew if I saw you, it
would all come back to that.
- So how are things going?
- [Sanaa] Great.
I'm learning a lot.
I have more responsibility
than I did before.
I'm adjusting.
So what's going on with you?
- Well I literally just
walked through the door
from Europe.
Phone rang and it was you.
- [Sanaa] Wow.
I always wanted to go there.
Couldn't wait to dump me
so you could start jet setting, right?
(Sanaa chuckles)
- So when are you coming back to Atlanta?
- [Sanaa] Thanksgiving.
Yeah, I'll be back for Thanksgiving.
- Well, when you get in town,
if you got some time, give me a call.
- [Sanaa] That would be my first thought.
Jay, can you hang on for a second?
- Yeah.
- [Sanaa] I really have
to go. I'm still at work.
It's good to hear your voice though, Jay.
- Yeah, it was good talking to you too.
Bye.
♪ I can tell you judge before
we had a conversation ♪
♪ On this trip I think I
look like condensation ♪
♪ Why do whippet niggas
think I'm Ronald Reagan ♪
♪ Why you got me like
you need confirmation ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I just touched down back in town ♪
♪ Now I'm at peace ♪
♪ She a pretty brown round thing ♪
♪ She quick at the beach ♪
♪ Yeah I thank God everyday
that I'm existing ♪
♪ Won't you tell me why
you different, huh ♪
♪ I can tell you judge me
'fore we had a conversation ♪
♪ On this trip I think I
look like condensation ♪
♪ Why do whippet niggas
think I'm Ronald Reagan ♪
Hey, are you looking for Beau?
- Yeah, I am.
- [James] I just called him.
He said he'd be here in about 20 minutes.
- Wow.
I don't have time to wait.
All right. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hey, I was gonna tell you, if you...
You wanna roll your
window down a little bit?
- I can hear you.
- Yeah, but I can barely hear you.
- [Monet] I'll talk louder.
- What do you think I'm gonna do?
- [Monet] I don't know.
- I'm saying I'm waiting
for Beau just like you are.
- Okay.
- I was just gonna say, you
know, if you had to leave,
I could tell Beau that you were here,
but you just couldn't stay.
- I was just about to call him.
I'm good. Thank you.
- All right.
I'm just trying to help.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
(dog barks)
- No.
Why?
Come on, come on, come on.
Damn.
Hey, do you mind if I use your phone?
My battery died and I
don't have my charger.
- Can I see your teeth first?
- Why do you need to see my teeth?
- To make sure you got some.
There you go. That wasn't so hard.
- It's locked.
- [James] Oh, my bad.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
I just tried to call Beau
just before you pulled up.
He's probably not answering
because he'll be here in a few minutes.
- Okay.
Well, I might as well sit.
- Yeah, sit.
- I guess I can wait on him.
So when did you go to France?
- Actually, a couple of weeks ago.
That's why I'm here.
Dropping off some of my footage to Beau.
You ever been to France?
- I went there to study for a semester.
- Uh-huh, wow was it?
- Um, it was nice.
It was really a great experience.
I got to see a lot of Europe
and see a lot different
people, different cultures.
It was cool.
- You must speak French fluently.
(both chuckle)
- Well, I wouldn't say fluently,
but I know a little something.
I mean, I think the problem
is that people from France,
they speak so fast and the
accent is so different.
- Right, right.
- Yeah, I'm just used to people
from America speaking
French and, you know,
but I made it work.
- There you go, there you go.
Obviously, learning a foreign
language can be tough.
- Mm-hmm.
You go by yourself?
- Yeah, I did.
Actually, I needed to get
away for a little bit.
I was also finishing up a project.
Then I went to the Cannes Film Festival.
Man, that was awesome.
- What do you do?
- I work for an insurance company.
You know, but what I really wanna do
is I wanna travel and shoot video
and tell my story like only I can,
you know what I mean?
Yeah.
- Right. That's nice.
- How about you?
- I'm a photographer.
- Head shots and baby photos?
- No.
(both chuckle)
More like urban landscapes and-
- Really?
- I like to take pictures of
people with interesting faces.
- Nice, nice.
- You know, I like how
natural light hits an object,
so I just try to capture it.
- That's awesome. That's awesome.
I'd love to see some
of your work sometime.
- Yeah, you can ask Beau.
I'll let him know that you
wanna see some of my stuff.
He's working on a reel
for me right now, so.
- Mm, I would like for you
to show me some of your work.
- Why?
- Because it's your work. (laughs)
Duh.
I'm Jay.
- Monet.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- So is Jay your government name
or is it some kind of nickname?
- Yeah, it's short for James.
- Okay.
And my name really is Monet,
not Diamond or Lexi or
some kind of stage name.
- You don't have a stage name, do you?
- No.
I haven't had a stage name
since fifth grade when I played Juliet.
And if I did have a stage name?
- Gotta get it how you live.
- Yeah, okay.
Most men say they'd date a stripper,
but if it came down to it,
they wouldn't even take her seriously.
- Wait, you trying to date me?
- I didn't say you.
(James laughs)
I said most men.
- Oh, you did, you did.
So when are you gonna let
me see some of your work?
- I'll give you my number
and then we can talk on the phone first
and then we'll see.
- Okay, so let me ask you this.
Are you into hip-hop?
♪ If knowledge is the key ♪
♪ Then just show me the lot ♪
♪ Got the scrawny legs ♪
♪ But I moved just like Luke Brock ♪
♪ With speed I'm agile ♪
♪ Plus I'm worth your while ♪
♪ 100% intelligent black child ♪
So you're A Tribe Called Quest fan.
- What?
I love, love, love, love
me some old-school hip-hop.
- Okay, Biggie or Pop?
- Biggie.
- J. Cole or Kendrick Lamar?
- J. Cole.
- Drake or Weezy F Baby?
- Drake.
- Best to ever do it?
- Hmm.
Commercially, you'd have to say Jay Z.
But Illmatic may be the
illest album of all time.
So is Nas the greatest?
Then Snoop's been around 20 years
and then you still got
Black Thought, Rakim,
Eminem, Biggie, Pusha T.
I mean, you could make an argument
with any one of those guys, so.
- Wow.
Impressive.
- My roommate when I was in grad school,
she was an intern for a label.
So she used to keep me up on everything.
- Grad school?
- Yeah.
I got my master's degree in education,
even though I knew I
wanted to be an artist.
- So why get a master's in education
if you wanted to be a photographer?
- My parents wanted me to
have something to fall back on
in case the creative
thing didn't work out.
So I promised them that I
would get my master's degree
and then they gave me a
little bit of seed money
to tie me over just in
case things didn't work out
and, you know, that way
I could get started.
- Sounds like a waste of money to me.
- Mm-mm.
No, you are totally off base with that.
- Okay, so tell me one meaningful thing
you learned while you were in grad school.
- The word Negus, N-E-G-U-S,
is a word using in reference
to Ethiopian sovereignty
and the root of the word, N-G-S a noun
derived from the ancient language of Geez.
So basically when someone refers
to a group of people as niggas,
they're basically calling
them a group of kings.
- That's not true
because I'm quite sure
that back in the day,
master was not referring
to his slaves as kings.
- Right, because they were ignorant
about where the word came
from and what it meant
much like yourself before I told you.
- How do I know that's true?
- Okay, well, since
you're a visual person,
go to YouTube and type
in spelling bee N-E-G-U-S
and then you don't even have to
tax your little brain to read.
They use it in a national spelling bee.
Now there's so much more to the
etymology of the word nigger
but I don't even want to go into it
because your whole head might explode.
- I'm just gonna let that go.
(Monet laughs)
I totally didn't mean to say that.
I'm a good girl.
- You know, we're gonna have to have
some sort of date set up
before we get off this phone.
I mean, we've been havin'
hella conversations
and I feel like it's my duty,
no, no, no, my obligation
to get us in the same space.
I just wanna see you again
and I don't care where.
♪ Got a couple wild things in Tokyo ♪
Can you at least tell me how
much further we gotta walk?
I mean, I haven't walked this far since
before I had my driver's license.
♪ You ain't on my swag ♪
♪ You ain't, you ain't on my swag ♪
♪ On my swag, swag radar ♪
♪ You ain't on my swag ♪
♪ You ain't, you ain't on my swag ♪
♪ On my swag radar ♪
- Oh, you know you wanna look.
(James laughing)
- I saw her, I saw her,
but I'm walking with you.
To stare at her would be disrespectful.
- Mm.
So you don't like girls
that look like that?
- No, no, no, no.
She's got a nice body, true that.
But I mean,
she don't have to put it
all out there like that.
- Oh, so you calling her a thot.
- She a little thotty, a little thotty.
- What is a thot?
- You know.
A bird.
- No, I wanna hear your definition.
(James laughs nervously)
- You know, uh...
Come on, Monet. Stop playing with me.
You know what a thot is.
Come on.
- So what do you call a guy
that exhibits the same behavior?
- Uh, for a guy?
A player. Player?
- Okay, so same, same situation,
but different connotation based on gender?
Right.
And you think that's right?
- Probably not, but I mean, let's face it.
That's the reality of
the world we live in.
- Ah.
Kind of like how women
get paid way less money
than men to do the same exact job.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Pay disparity is institutional.
Sexual mores are more societal.
Yeah.
- Okay, and one affects the other.
You men are raised with
an antiquated notion
of what it is to be a woman
and you take that with
you everywhere you go.
(James chuckles)
- Do you secretly hate men?
- No.
Not all of you.
I do love my dad and
my brother very dearly.
- What am I supposed to think
when I see a woman like
that with a body like that
walking down the street dressed like that?
- She's liberated.
(both laugh)
- Now you said liberated.
Come on, I don't want
that kind of liberation
for my daughter.
- Okay, well then you better impregnate
a forward-thinking fully developed woman.
And the only way you're
gonna be able to do that
is if you open up your mind
and start forming your own opinions
instead of carrying on these antiquated
and provincial ways of thinking.
What?
- You know what, ordinarily,
this kind of conversation
would be a huge turnoff.
But for some reason today,
I find it real stimulating.
- Oh, you stimulated?
- [James] Yeah.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
♪ You ain't on my swag ♪
♪ You ain’t, you ain't on my swag ♪
♪ On my swag radar ♪
So where are you taking me?
- I'm not gonna tell you,
but we're almost there.
Oh, look at that.
- [James] Yeah, I've heard of this place
but I've never been here before.
- [Monet] Yes, I love this place.
Can I get my camera out of the back?
- Yeah.
♪ In my swag ♪
♪ Hey ♪
Hey bro, I like that T-shirt.
♪ You ain't on my swag ♪
- I appreciate that.
We've got a petition going around.
Now, if you're interested,
go to the website, check it out.
Now, look right here.
This is we're doing.
We need a brother like you to help out.
You know what I'm saying?
- Yeah, yeah, let me get one.
- All right.
- Resist.
- I appreciate that, man.
♪ Swag, swag radar ♪
♪ You ain't on my swag ♪
- [Monet] Wow.
What was he talking about?
- He just gave me some great information.
I know this sounds random as hell,
but have you ever noticed that some people
say "I was at my work"
instead of "I was at work"?
(Monet laughs)
- Yes, that was random.
But yeah, I get it.
I mean, I'm not sure what's it about.
I would just say I'm at
work, not I was at my work,
but it's like the people
who say on tomorrow,
instead of just saying-
- [Both] Tomorrow!
- Yes!
I'm glad to see it's not just me.
- No, it's not.
Although I do think that that
is particular to the south.
- [James] Could be, could be.
- [Monet] So.
- [James] What?
- You have any other random
things you wanna ask me?
Why is the sky blue?
Where do babies come from?
Why does a caged bird sing?
- Very funny. Very funny.
- [Monet] I know.
♪ You ain't on my swag ♪
♪ On my swag radar ♪
♪ You ain't, you ain't on my swag ♪
♪ You ain't on my swag ♪
♪ On my swag, swag radar ♪
(upbeat music)
(crowds chattering in foreign language)
(phone chimes)
- Damn.
- What's the matter?
- Another rejection email.
- How many travel sites did you submit to?
- A lot.
- How many rejected you?
- 100%.
- You sent the guy you met from VICE TV
the links to your documentaries
from Morocco and Brazil, right?
They may call you. You never know.
- They ain't gonna call me.
- Stop with your negative energy.
- Got it.
- I think I'm gonna make you some dinner.
That'll change your mood.
- Ooh, okay, okay.
Ooh, this looks good.
- I would hope so.
- Have a seat.
- Thanks.
- All right, let's pray before we eat.
- Okay.
- Lord, thank you for this
food we're about to receive,
bless the hands that prepared it,
and may it nourish our
body for Christ's sake.
Amen.
- Amen.
Let me know how it tastes.
- Oh, I'm about to.
Mm, mm, Monet.
Mm-mm.
This is good.
This is really, really good.
- Yeah?
- [Announcer On TV]
Think it's time to hear
your wife's secret confession.
Julia, we came here today
to tell your husband-
- I want you to go to church with me.
- Where do you go to church?
- Mount Calvary.
- Yeah, I know exactly where that is.
Matter of fact,
I visited there a couple times
before I decided to stop going to church.
- Why'd you stop going to church?
- Just kind of felt like I
was going through the motions.
I mean, in the middle of the sermon,
everybody's jumping up and down.
I'm sitting back wondering
"When's the Falcon game start?"
- Oh my God. You are terrible.
- When we first started
going, I really liked it.
And I've...
- Oh, so you went to
church for some chick.
So what happened to the chick
you used to go to church with?
- I don't know.
She's around, I guess.
- [Monet] She's around, you guess?
- (laughs) You don't see
me diving on my phone
every time it rings, do you?
- Well, your phone's always on vibrate.
- How do you know that?
- I picked it up one time by mistake.
- By mistake.
- Yeah.
- Where was I at?
- You were in the shower.
What?
Why are you so nervous?
What can I even do?
It's not like you're my
man or anything, right?
- True, true.
But I still don't see why
you feel the need to check.
I mean, you can ask me anything.
I'll answer it honestly.
- You're right.
I am so sorry.
I will never do that again.
(James laughs)
- Yeah, right.
- I'm not like that.
If I gotta check up on you,
I'm gone like the wind.
Believe me.
- Deuces.
(smooth music)
♪ Place your love on the table ♪
♪ I am sure that you're able ♪
♪ To with care be the man that I need ♪
♪ I'm giving all of me, yeah ♪
♪ Give it all, give it all ♪
♪ Give it all, give it all away ♪
♪ Away ♪
- Come on, so you can walk me out.
- So you just gonna stick and move, huh?
- No.
It's not even like that.
I have to get up in the morning.
- No, I understand,
but I don't see why you just can't stay.
You know what I'm saying?
Go home in the morning.
- I can't.
I have a client at 7:00 AM,
so I need to get it together tonight.
(announcer chattering on TV)
What?
- Nothing really.
We can talk about it tomorrow.
- What are you thinking?
(James laughs)
- Like you said, you gotta go
and it's no big deal, I'm serious.
- Okay, but I'm here now.
So tell me.
- [Announcer On TV] Struck out 41
and his 26th inning is pitched
giving up 12 hits in the process.
- You know, I'm really glad I met you.
- [Monet] I'm really glad I met you too.
You're so sweet.
- Sweet?
What? Quit playing!
What about sexy, strong, intelligent?
- [Monet] Okay!
- And not to mention, a
machine in bed. (laughs)
- All of that, all of that.
- Do you remember when
we were talking earlier
and you asked me whose idea it was
to go to the church I was attending?
- [Monet] Mm-hmm.
- I wanna be honest with you.
- [Monet] Jay, you don't
have to explain anything
that happened in the past.
- I was seeing someone
and she got this great
job offer to New York.
- You got a girlfriend?
- [James] No, we broke up before she left.
- So why didn't you tell
me about this before?
How long were you guys together?
- Three years.
- So why are you just now telling me this?
- I don't want you to be upset.
- The only reason why you would tell me
about an ex-girlfriend is if
you're still in love with her
or if you're lying to me
and you're still with her.
So which one is it?
- We broke up.
But she's coming home for Thanksgiving.
- Home?
Where's home? She live here?
- [James] No.
She's from Atlanta.
Her family lives here.
- We just had this
discussion earlier today.
Why didn't you tell me
about that then, huh?
Because you wanted what you wanted tonight
and you knew that you wouldn't get it
if you were to tell me the truth, right?
- [James] No, I didn't plan
for it to go like this.
- Yes, you did it.
- Come on now.
- Come on now?
- Monet.
- [Announcer On TV] Here in
the bottom half of the first.
(knocking on door)
- Hey!
- Hey, you.
You look great. Come on in!
- Thank you!
I can't stay long.
My ride is outside waiting.
- Ride?
Things must be working out for you.
- Thanks to you.
- Me?
I mean, we haven't spoken in weeks.
- And what about the video you did for me?
- Oh, the video that all
of 100 people have seen?
- Well, someone from
Safehouse Outreach saw it
and when I applied for the position,
they recognized me and
hired me on the spot.
- What?
- Yes.
I'm an assistant to the director.
- [James] Oh, that's
great. Congratulations!
You deserve it!
- Thank you. Thank you.
There's more, but I have to go.
My director went to college with her
and she saw the video
and wants you to call her, okay?
I gotta go.
- [James] All right. You keep doing good.
- Thank you.
Hey, listen. Let me know
how that goes, okay?
- I will.
- All right.
(gentle music)
(smooth music)
- [Sanaa] May I?
- [James] Yeah, why would you ask?
- Just checking.
- Can I get you something to drink?
- Do you have wine?
- Of course.
- [Sanaa] I'll take that.
- Be right back.
(Sanaa sighs)
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- So tell me all about New
York, this new job, all of it.
- Brooklyn is lit.
All the neighborhoods, and the people,
like they're completely different,
but they're all right
next door to each other.
So, yeah.
And the restaurants
and the cafes, (sighs).
But you spent time in Brooklyn.
You know what I'm talking about.
- Yeah, I always said
if I moved to New York,
I'd probably live in Brooklyn.
- Oh, well, you had your opportunity.
(Sanaa clears throat)
Anywho, how's your mother?
- She's doing good.
Matter of fact, she asked about you.
- And what did you say?
- I told her that you got a
great job offer in New York
that you just couldn't refuse.
- Did she ask you if we were together?
- I told her that we keep
in contact, you know,
and that we're still friends.
- What, I've been gone for three months
and we've only spoken like three times,
today being included?
I speak to my friends a little
bit more often than that.
- Well, I have called
you, tried to text you,
but if you don't respond, what can I do?
- Do you do this for all your friends?
- [James] What?
- This.
The fireplace, the low lights,
chilled wine, the soft music.
- No, I don't do this for everyone.
And as a matter of fact, I got a surprise.
Now, listen, obviously-
- Jay, I need to talk to
you about something else.
To be honest with you,
I was planning on taking this
in a completely different direction.
- Before we could even
talk about getting together
or considering that, you
know we'd have to talk about-
- Jay, I'm in love with someone else.
- I don't know what I was expecting,
but I know I wasn't expecting that.
- [Sanaa] I know I should
have said something,
but I didn't wanna tell
you over the phone,
even though I don't think
that you deserve the courtesy.
- Why wouldn't I deserve the courtesy?
- I don't wanna go backwards here.
I love him and he loves me.
I didn't mean for this to
happen, but it just did.
- You've been gone for
less than three months.
How could you possibly have
fallen in love already?
- I don't think you want me
to answer that, Jay, honestly.
- Try me. Yeah, I would.
- Well what he and I have
shared in three months,
you and I we never
experienced in three years.
You and I, we had something.
Yeah.
But it wasn't...
It wasn't what I have now.
And what I have now
is something that I need and I want.
- That's bullshit, Sanaa.
I know you and I know how you operate.
Ain't no way you're gonna let some dude
get that close to you so quickly.
- We spent a lot of time together.
Look, I fell in love with someone else.
It happens.
People fall in love.
People fall out of love.
- So, on your mama's life,
you gonna sit there and look me in my face
and tell me that you done
fell in love with some cat
in less than three months?
- Okay, we met before I moved, but like,
it wasn't anything, okay?
It wasn't anything.
- Where'd you meet him?
- Does it make a difference?
- I mean, you might as well tell me.
I don't see why you feel the need
to lie to me at this point.
- I met him while I was working here.
He came to the Atlanta office for work
and, I mean, that's when I met him
but we didn't go out or anything, okay?
- But he had your number.
- I mean, we would talk about work.
I mean, that was it.
- Wait a minute.
Is this the guy who told you
about the opportunity in New York?
♪ I know you can see me ♪
- Yeah.
- Damn.
You know what? I can't even be mad at him.
Talk about laying the foundation.
I bet bro probably had it
mapped out from the start.
- Jay, I just-
- You know what? I got it.
I get it.
♪ I know you can feel me ♪
- I didn't mean to-
- Fall on his dick.
- [Sanaa] Okay.
- [James] After that, I felt like
I needed to hit the streets.
I figured I hit a club and chill
with some of the beautiful
women this city has to offer.
The problem was, deep down,
I wasn't really in the mood.
So I just drove around aimlessly.
♪ You would think it's imported ♪
♪ I gotta eat ♪
♪ I get down ♪
♪ I don't stick around, yeah ♪
Secondary to my problem
of saying the wrong
thing at the wrong time,
is the fact that when I'm
thinking about something deeply,
I sometimes ignore the obvious,
which can lead to trouble,
like running out of gas.
♪ Sip on the side ♪
♪ Squirt, squirt ♪
♪ I like it, yeah ♪
♪ Swimming in a pool ♪
♪ I'm excited, yeah ♪
- And then he made the shot.
♪ You can take my order right now ♪
♪ Yeah you got me wild ♪
♪ We get out of order ♪
♪ I gotta eat ♪
♪ Throw that back and party ♪
♪ I beg you, get me started ♪
♪ 'Cause I feel like I'm starving ♪
♪ I gotta eat ♪
♪ Yo, this thing that I'm smoking ♪
♪ Yeah this be so potent ♪
♪ You would think it's imported ♪
♪ I gotta eat ♪
♪ Throw that back and party ♪
♪ I beg, you get me started ♪
♪ 'Cause I feel like I'm starving ♪
♪ I gotta eat ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yo, this thing that I'm smoking ♪
♪ Yeah this be so potent ♪
♪ You would think it's imported ♪
♪ I gotta eat ♪
♪ I give you that super D ♪
♪ Then I call Uber Eats ♪
♪ Uh-Oh, that newer D ♪
♪ We bumpin' that newer D ♪
♪ Your shorty, she cool with me ♪
♪ She can come through with me ♪
♪ We hit the club, we gettin' drunk ♪
♪ We do that usually ♪
♪ The party is pumping up ♪
♪ Shorty, she poppin' up ♪
♪ Pull out my two ♪
♪ Probably gonna pop it up ♪
♪ You need to stop it though ♪
♪ The party gonna top us up ♪
♪ Yeah that's it ♪
(phone ringing)
- [Dispatcher] 911, what's your emergency?
♪ You my style ♪
♪ You can take my order right now ♪
- What were you doing
down there that late?
- I told you.
I was just doing some
driving around thinking
and I ran out of gas.
- Prostitutes and Johns are
usually the only ones
down there at that time.
- What?
- So the next time you have an argument
with one of your girlfriends,
why don't you try driving around Buckhead
or maybe at least
somewhere that's well lit.
- All right.
- I'm gonna get this filled for you.
- Thanks, Uncle.
(doorbell rings)
- I'll get that.
- Hi, I'm Monet.
I was wondering if I could
see Jay for a minute.
- Sure, come on in.
- Thank you.
- [Tony] Close this door.
- [Monet] Thank you.
- [Tony] I'm Jay's Uncle Tony.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you also.
He's right in here.
- Hey.
- How are you feeling?
- [James] I'm all right.
Just a concussion.
- Jay, I can see you're in good hands.
So I'm gonna, I'm gonna take off.
It was nice meeting you.
- Nice meeting you too.
- Thanks, Unc.
So thanks for coming by.
You wanna have a seat
or I can take your coat, you know?
- No, I'm not gonna stay long.
I just came by to check on you
and see if you needed anything.
- [James] I'm all right.
- I have to be honest.
I wasn't even sure I was gonna
answer the phone when you called.
I wasn't sure when you were
gonna hear from me again,
but I could tell from
the sound of your voice
that something was really wrong.
Do you need anything?
- I'm all right, I guess.
- [Monet] You need a
prescription filled or?
- No, my uncle already took care of that.
- Did you eat?
- [James] Yeah.
- Okay, well, since you
don't need anything,
I guess I'll just go.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I don't have everything I need.
- What do you need, Jay?
- You.
- Moving women around like chess pieces
for your enjoyment is not a need.
- I wanted to be honest with you.
I wanted to be sure I was over her
before we went any further.
- You come across as disingenuous
and you talk about being honest
after you intentionally
withheld the truth?
All that matters is what Jay wants, right?
- No.
Just give me another opportunity, Monet.
- No, I'm gone.
- [James] Monet.
(door slams)
- Let's get started.
All Texas licenses have to be renewed
by the end of the week.
I take it you all have the required
continuing education hours.
(tense music)
What is the problem?
You're all professionals.
Why do you wait till the last minute?
- Some of us have families.
- I assigned a time management module
and to date none of
y'all have completed it.
If you took your career seriously,
you would have completed it
and implemented but you aren't.
- Why are you speaking
to us like we're kids?
- Maybe because our
customer service results
are the worst in the company.
We get more home office complaints
than any other region.
And as result, I get a
call from the home office
ripping me a new one on a weekly basis.
- They send us questionnaires
to one out of every 25 policy holders.
- It doesn't matter.
Our results are the worst in the company.
- You know, I got one of those last week
from a guy who totaled
out a 2002 Ford F150.
We had the value at $6,350,
but he valued it $15,000
because he put a new set of tires on it
and he got a brand new paint job.
So what do you think he's gonna say
when somebody asks him about his claim?
- You're not the only one
that settles total losses.
Let me repeat.
Our results are the worst in the company.
Fix it.
All right.
Last thing.
Take one and pass it down.
As you can see, this
is a policy endorsement
that was effective the
first of last month.
- So why are we just
hearing about this now?
Based on this,
I told somebody something
that wasn't true.
We should have known about this.
- We need to do what's required by-
- Sharon, you just sat up in here
and said we had issues
with customer service.
So what does it say about customer service
when we broaden the coverage
but we can't tell them so
they can take advantage of it?
- I just became aware of it myself.
That's why we're having this meeting.
- This is bullshit.
- Watch your language.
- You know, you bring us in here
and tell us how poorly
of a job we're doing
like we're supposed to sit
up in here and take it.
It's insulting.
- It sounds like an intentional move
from the executive office to me.
- It wasn't.
- You know, if the insurance
department found out,
we could get hit with a pretty heavy fine
or maybe even be prevented
from writing the policies.
This is a big effin' deal.
- It is not our job to worry about it.
That's all I have.
- I'm taking a leave of absence.
- This is a joke, right?
- No.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
You just got back from vacation.
- And I'm taking a leave of absence.
- You got a set on you, you know that?
Meet me in the conference
room after lunch.
I said in the conference room after lunch.
What part of that do you not-
- I've worked here for nine years
as a senior claims specialist.
I even interned two summers
here when I was in college.
I've gone along with the
changes this company has made
in an effort to keep up
with our competitors.
And you know what?
You owe me nine years and two summers.
Because the arrogance
displayed by this company
is only eclipsed by the absurdity
and selfishness of its decision making.
And you know what?
I fear that it's contagious
and that I've taken years off my life
by breathing the air that
circulates in this building.
So you know what?
I'm not giving you a two
weeks notice because I quit.
- Yo, where are you going?
- I'm out, Steve.
I'll call you, man.
It's amazing what you
see when you slow down
and just allow yourself to be.
(uplifting music)
- What motivated you to tell this story?
- Well, I can tell you
that it wasn't planned.
I actually was headed
into a convenience store.
It had already been a
long day and I was tired.
And you know how it is,
I wasn't exactly in the best of moods.
And I was about to head
into the convenience store
and this young woman just approached me.
That meeting turned into a job
producing special projects for CNN.
Don't ignore that little
voice in your head.
That's your conscience talking to you.
Once you realize that,
the next step is to figure out
what you're supposed to do
and how you're supposed to do it.
I like to write and document what I see.
I wanna do that in a way
that informs and helps other people
because in the end,
helping other people is all that matters.
(smooth music)
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Openly ♪
♪ Showing me ♪
♪ How to breathe with you ♪
♪ In your eyes ♪
♪ I see it ♪
♪ The truth in you ♪
♪ Placing love on the table ♪
♪ I am sure that you're able ♪
♪ To with care ♪
♪ Be the man that I need ♪
♪ I'm giving all of me, yeah ♪
♪ Give it all, give it all ♪
♪ Give it all, give it all away ♪
♪ Away, yeah ♪
♪ Simple sweet ♪
♪ Finally ♪
♪ Love I see it clear ♪
♪ Higher love ♪
♪ Sent from above ♪
♪ All that I need is here ♪
♪ Placing love on the table ♪
♪ I am sure that you're able ♪
♪ To with care be the man that I need ♪
♪ I'm giving all of me ♪
♪ Give it all, give it all ♪
♪ Give it all, give it all away ♪
♪ Away, yeah ♪
♪ Erase the past ♪
♪ Rewrite the future ♪
♪ We're gonna last ♪
♪ 'Cause you love me so perfectly ♪
♪ I can't let go of you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Erase the past ♪
♪ Rewrite the future ♪
♪ We're gonna last ♪