(MultiCom Jingle)
(grand piano)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Walter] Bob?
Walter Winchell.
- Walt.
- [Walter] It's Marilyn.
I'm sorry to have to tell you this.
She died this morning.
Bob?
- Hold on.
Okay.
- [Walter] They think it's suicide.
One more thing.
No one is claiming the body.
Would you come out to the funeral?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I want to be there for her.
- [Walter] Bob, I'm sorry.
- [Bob] Thanks, Walter.
(piano resumes)
- Can I help you?
- [Bob] I understand no one's
claimed the body of Marilyn Monroe.
- What business is that of yours?
- I'm here to claim it myself.
- I see.
What's your relationship to the deceased?
- I was her husband.
- [Orderly] Are you Jim Dougherty?
- No, my name is Bob Slatzer.
- You're not Arthur Miller.
- [Bob] Bob Slatzer.
- And I know you're not Joe DiMaggio.
- My name is Slatzer.
- Your name isn't on the list.
And if it isn't on the list,
you weren't married to her.
- Now wait a minute.
- Look mister, either you're
just another fan of
getting too carried away
or your marriage was one of
the world's best kept secrets.
Either way, if you don't leave,
I'll have to call the cops.
(somber jazz)
- [Bob, Interally] To
me she wasn't a star.
She wasn't even Marilyn Monroe.
To me she was Norma Jean.
Always was, always will be.
(upbeat jazz)
I was writing stories about movie stars
for a newspaper back in Ohio.
I got paid by the story
when I could hunt one down.
Things weren't going too well
and the paper wanted me to come home
but I didn't want to leave.
And then, one morning while I was waiting
to interview a casting director.
You okay?
- And then the very moment,
the danger was over.
It was as if nothing had happened.
I was again your doll, your lark.
- Excuse me?
- It's from the play you
were reading, A Doll's House.
I did Nora in Van Nuys.
- Oh, I see.
I didn't recognize it.
I guess I didn't get that far yet.
- Waiting here for an audition?
- No, just for fun.
- Oh.
You're not an actor?
- Oh no.
- I'm Norma Jean Baker.
- [Bob] Bob Slatzer.
- I think I'll call you Ibsen.
You're the only man I've
ever met in Hollywood
who wasn't reading Ibsen for anything
but a scene in an acting class.
You work here?
- Well yes and no.
I'm a writer.
Well actually, I'm trying
to make it as a screenwriter
but mostly I freelance
articles for a paper in Ohio.
- Oh.
I love writers.
The sexiest thing in the world
isn't Darryl Flynn with his pants off,
it's Hemingway with his hat on.
- [Woman In The Distance]
Norma Jean Baker.
- That's my big call to stardom.
(jazz resumes)
Oh, Ibsen.
I was looking for someone
to help me write my resume.
- [Bob] Well, um.
- Maybe we could talk
about it over dinner?
- Dinner?
I, yeah, I'd love to.
- How about tonight?
Pick me up at the 'brask
and Barrington at seven.
- [Bob] Oh, is that the corner
of Nebraska and Barrington?
- That's it. See you at seven.
(upbeat jazz)
- [Norma] Hi.
- Hi.
- Oh.
White roses are my favorite.
Did you know that white roses
were kissed twice by the sun?
You're shy.
That's beautiful.
- Yeah, it's always been
a little bit of a problem.
- I think it's nice.
Do you know what white roses are good for?
Breath mints.
I love driving past these big old houses.
But they're too cold, too dark.
I'd never live here no
matter how much money I make.
- Plan to make a lot of money, do you?
- If they'd ever let me show
them how good I could be.
- They won't let you act now?
- The casting executives
take one look at me
and they see me as a nude model.
Or maybe they see me flat on my back.
(giggles)
- I don't think that's too fun.
- Neither do I but you can't
take life too seriously, right?
- I'm no expert but I think
if you want anything in this life
you've gotta take yourself seriously
or nobody else will.
- I'm so hungry I could eat a mountaintop.
But an actress doesn't work regular,
she doesn't eat regular.
- Writers have the same problem.
- You know, you're the first real writer
I've ever gone out with.
- Well I wouldn't call
writing celebrity stories
being a real writer.
- What do you want to write?
- Movies, mostly.
I've been working on a script for months
that I just can't seem to finish.
I sit down every night and
I look at my typewriter and.
Laughs at me.
- Don't worry.
You'll finish your script soon.
I have faith in you.
Besides, you look like you're doing okay.
- Well I don't want to kid
you, the suit's borrowed.
Have you done much acting?
- Back to my resume?
- That's what I'm here for, isn't it?
- I thought you were here
because you liked me?
- Of course I like you.
- Good.
I like you too.
- You're being very sweet about this.
Beautiful girls like you don't
usually go for guys like me.
- Why not?
- Well I mean I'm not as
handsome as some guys.
- Come on.
- Hey, I thought you were hungry?
Don't worry so much.
You can always get another steak.
But a moon like that.
- Yeah, only comes up once every night.
- No, it'll never be the same.
Tomorrow it'll be different.
- Why?
- We won't be here.
- We could come back.
- But then we'd be different.
- How so?
- After tonight, we'll
always be different.
- You always say the first
thing that pops into your head?
- My husband used to ask
me the same question.
- You've been married?
- We're divorced.
Jimmy was a nice boy, really sweet.
But we were too young.
I think my father had a concession stand
down there somewhere.
- You don't know?
- I never really met him.
He left the night before I was born.
Mom and me, we moved around some.
Sometimes I had to live in foster homes.
But when mama was cutting films,
we got to be together.
- Well maybe I know her.
Where's she working these days?
- Remember what I said.
I said we'd be different after tonight.
- How are we gonna be different?
- Can't you guess?
(sultry jazz)
- Norma Jean, this is a public beach.
- Relax Ibsen.
- My name is Bob.
- [Norma] Come on in, Bob.
Don't be afraid.
C'mon!
You know how to get undressed don't you?
- Norma Jean, I don't
know if I can do this.
- [Norma] If you don't,
you'll always be sorry.
Come on, Bobby.
Do it once, just for me.
- [Bob] Incredible, isn't it?
But I swear it's true.
That was my first date with Norma Jean.
Of course I didn't want it to end but,
sooner or later, everything ends.
You want me to leave you here?
- I live with my aunt over there.
She gets upset when I'm out late.
I don't want her to hear your car.
- Well, if you need me, I'm staying
at the Hollywood Roosevelt Hotel.
You can call me any time you want.
Day or night.
- Always a gentleman?
- Try.
- Better warn you. I may
not see you for a while.
My moods can change pretty fast.
I may not like you tomorrow.
- Well then thank you for tonight.
- Then again, tomorrow
maybe I'll love you.
- [Aunt Dana] This is no hour
for a young lady to be coming home.
Forgive me child, I'm old.
I need my peace.
Now you can go stay at a hotel tonight.
In the morning you can go
find a place of your own.
If you need any money,
you know I love you, like you were my own.
- I know, Aunt Dana.
Everyone loves me.
Sooner or later everyone says goodbye.
(knocking)
I betcha thought you
wouldn't see me again.
At least not this soon, huh?
- [Bob] It was like one of
those storybook moments,
except it was real.
Suddenly I felt like the
luckiest guy in the world.
But life has a way of making
you pay for every break
and it would be long before I found out
how high the price could be.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- I think I dreamed about you.
But I can't remember much.
Isn't it awful we don't
remember our dreams?
- I think I'm dreaming right now.
- So sweet.
You're very unusual for a man.
At least the one's I've known.
- Say.
I don't have to be any
place in particular today.
One of the few benefits of
being a starving writer.
What do you say we spend
the day right here.
I could order up some breakfast.
- Oh, sure.
And let some other girl get the part
that could be my lucky break?
Besides, I have to find an apartment.
- I mean, not necessarily.
We could look for an apartment.
Think about it, two can
live cheaper than one.
- And is this strictly
a business proposition?
- Well, let me put it this way.
No.
Over easy?
- Sure.
- [Bob] We agreed to take
things one rent check at a time.
I finished the last interviews
for my paper in Ohio
and kissed the job goodbye.
I'd saved enough to rent
an apartment in the Hollywood hills.
Norma Jean kicked in what she could.
It was time for me to write and
for her to make it as an actress.
(Norma singing)
♪ You must realize ♪
♪ Smoke gets in your eyes ♪
(clapping)
- You've got a pretty good voice.
- I like to sing.
I don't get the chance very often.
Mama always sang when she worked.
I think I've got her voice.
She didn't give me much
else before she went away,
except these jelly glasses.
Isn't that sad.
- [Bob] Where is she now?
- Up north.
In the hospital.
Kind of a sanitarium.
But one day soon, she's gonna get better.
Then maybe she can come visit us.
- Yeah, that'd be great with me.
An old boyfriend?
- Jealous?
- Guilty.
- They're from my father.
- I'm sorry, I didn't meant to pry.
- He sent them to mama before he died.
Mama said it was a motorcycle accident.
It's all I have left to remember him by.
Just these cards.
That's my family.
A couple of postcards
and six jelly glasses.
- Hey.
I've got two, three
extra dollars to splurge.
What'll it be?
Serials or el macabre?
- I think I can do better.
- I don't know if I belong here.
- Neither of us belongs
here, but we'll get by.
Besides, this is business for both of us.
I see my agent.
He's been ducking me for two days.
See you later.
And Bobby, mix.
- Hey bub, my name's Walter Winchell.
You mind if I ask who's the dish?
- My name's Bob Slatzer.
- Nice to meet you, Bob.
I don't mean to be rude, but
they pay me to ask questions.
- Her name's Norma Jean Baker.
She's an actress.
- Hi.
- And you?
You're her?
- Friend.
I'm also a writer.
Undiscovered at the moment.
- Well you may not be
the most famous guy here,
but there isn't a joker in the joint
wouldn't trade places with you today.
Good luck, Bob.
- Thanks.
- I called you twice.
I guess you've been busy, huh?
- I'm sorry I didn't get back to you
but the truth is I don't
have any news for you.
- Come on, Harry, what did he say?
- He's not so sure you're photogenic.
- Not photogenic?
Has Zanuck gone blind?
- Shh, take it easy,
I'm still working on it.
We'll get you that screen
test one of these days,
but you've gotta help.
Zanuck, Schenck, Jack Warner.
These men are your future, so act like it.
- How?
- You've got to be nice to them.
- How nice?
- Very nice.
- And to Mr. Zanuck?
- Extra, extra nice.
- And is Jack Warner a extra,
extra or just a very, very?
- And while we're on the subject,
if you're gonna crash a party,
the least you could do is look available.
Who's the kid you walked in with?
- [Norma] He's a writer.
- Stay away from writers.
They're all nuts.
Besides, he's a nobody.
He can't do you any good.
- Oh yes he can.
- Look, I don't care what
you do between the sheets,
wait a minute.
Good God, you don't love him, do you?
- I might, Harry.
I just might.
- Don't be foolish.
You've got no time for this.
Kill the romance.
- Bobby.
Bobby.
- Your agent wants me to go doesn't he?
- You're pretty smart.
- Look, why don't I leave.
You can get a lift home.
- No.
You stay.
They aren't gonna tell
me what to do, not ever.
Come on.
They're screening a Gene
Harlow movie inside.
Lets go see it.
- It wouldn't have sounded
better than an alarm clock.
It doesn't seem to ring
or anything at all.
Billy, have you got a headache?
- [Billy] Maybe. I don't know.
- Would you like me to rub your forehead?
- [Billy] Nope.
- [Woman In Film] Well could I
get you a drink or something?
- [Billy] No, thank you, darling.
- Well lets forget about the drink.
I'll just rub your
forehead with sandpaper.
- [Bob] When are you coming to bed?
- [Norma] In a minute.
I'm not quite finished yet.
- [Bob] Ooh boy.
- Whaddya think?
My mama taught me.
She was good with hair.
I bet this'll make them
sit up and take notice.
- You'll try just about
anything, won't you?
- So long as it's legal.
I just wish I had money to study.
- You need acting lessons?
Okay.
- What?
- I'll take that waiter's job
at Clifton's on the night shift.
- You'd do that for me?
You'd stop writing?
- I'm not spending a lot of time
in front of the typewriter anyway.
(Norma laughing)
- But Zanuck still doesn't
think I'm photogenic.
I'm good for nygard, he
said, but not as an actress.
Harry can't even get me a bit part.
- Well you still manage.
- Sure.
Some producer wants to go
to a premiere with a young actress?
Send for Norma Jean.
Need somebody to jump out of a cake?
I'm sorry you wasted your
money on a wind-up toy.
- You are not a wind-up toy.
- Then when do I get a chance to act?
- Well, you keep trying.
That's all you can do.
You know, this television
thing is amazing.
Maybe this is the future.
- Too small.
I want to be 40 feet tall
with a teardrop 10 feet wide.
- Don't worry, you'll
get there Norma Jean.
Might take a while, but you'll get there.
(engine stalling)
Course it might take a
little longer without a car.
Nice streak of luck we're having, huh?
- Well actually there is a job for me.
I met a photographer, Tom Kelly.
Well known, respectable.
He asked me to do a calendar.
- You mean nude?
- It's just another calendar.
There's a million of them out there
and a million nude models.
We need the money.
- I don't know.
Greasy paws hanging you up in gas stations
all over the country?
- Bobby, it's just business.
What do we care who looks?
You're the only one who gets to touch.
Would it make you feel better
if you went to the photo session with me?
Make sure everything's on the square?
- Maybe.
- Tell you what, if you don't
like the looks of Mr. Tom Kelly,
I'll call it off.
- Well he seems like a very nice man.
Got to admit, I like his work.
- See, told ya so.
- You sure you want to do this?
- We're broke and without a car,
that's no way to live in Hollywood.
- You're welcome to stay for
a little while, Mr. Slatzer,
but then I'm going to
have to ask you to leave.
Models do better when there
are no friends or family
around to make them feel self-conscious.
You understand.
- Yeah, yeah sure.
I'll just stay a while
if you don't want anybody
to be uncomfortable.
- Okay.
Just the way we talked about, right?
Want you to stretch out.
That's right.
Just want you to feel that velvet, okay?
That's it.
Stretch out as far as you can.
Okay, floating, right?
Floating.
- Can you feel it, Bobby?
- Feel what?
- Our luck is starting to change.
- Can you believe this?
Yes, yes, really nice.
Keep turning.
- [Mechanic] Yeah, hold on a second.
Hey Slatzer, you got a phone call.
- Y'ello?
- [Norma] Bobby, Fox wants me.
I'm signing the contract today.
- Hey, that's great!
Listen, I get off in a couple
hours, you want to celebrate?
- [Norma] I can't wait.
See ya.
- Damn.
She actually did it.
- It's a standard studio contract.
One year with at least one
speaking part, guaranteed.
- Where do I sign.
- Well I think you should
read everything first.
Carefully.
- Come on, Chuck.
Usual boilerplate, isn't it?
- Yes, Harry, but we know
she has a boyfriend at home.
- Bobby.
What does Bobby have to do with this?
- Well it's in your contract.
Paragraph 17.
- [Harry] Sorry, Norma Jean.
- Sorry?
Why?
What's in paragraph 17?
- And then what?
- So they said, "Norma Jean Baker
sounds like some freckle-faced
kid from Kansas."
They said, "How 'bout Marilyn Monroe?"
- Marilyn Monroe?
Sounds kinda slinky to me.
- He said live with it for a few days.
If I don't like it, they'll
come up with something else.
But I have to let them know so they can
put it out in a press release.
- Well I still prefer Norma Jean.
- You know what you are?
You're just a big romantic teddy bear.
This could be good for you too.
Who knows.
Maybe I'll be able to get some producer
to look at one of your scripts.
- Yeah, maybe you can.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I got you something to
celebrate signing your contract.
A dozen white roses.
Kissed twice by the sun.
- Oh, Bob, they're beautiful.
But I have to tell you something.
- What?
- I would have to move out.
- Oh.
Yeah, I get it.
- [Norma] You do?
- Yeah.
Can't have a guy like me
around messing up publicity.
- That's nonsense.
This isn't my idea.
It's the morality clause in my contract.
They're putting me up in a
woman's hotel, for heaven's sake.
- Is that what you want?
- This isn't about what I want.
Bobby, please try to understand.
I can't remember a day in my life
when I wanted to be
anything but an actress.
I don't know what it is.
But when I'm acting, I feel alive.
- Well I'm glad you feel
alive, I feel like hell.
- Bobby, I can't let
this chance pass me by.
It's still my life.
It's still us.
- No.
No, it's you and the studio.
Come on.
I'll help you pack.
We can get this over with.
[Bob] After Norma Jean
left, we drifted apart.
She changed studios from Fox to Columbia
and started to get more parts.
I had some assignments
but nothing clicked.
So it was back to Ohio for me.
Back to my old newspaper job.
A chance to forget Hollywood
and a girl that was unforgettable.
♪ Every baby needs a da-da-daddy ♪
♪ To keep her worry free ♪
♪ But where's the one for me ♪
♪ A rich old bull ♪
♪ I don't care who ♪
♪ If he hasn't got a million ♪
♪ Then a half'll do ♪
♪ Every baby needs a da-da-daddy ♪
♪ Could my da-daddy be you ♪
- [Director] Cut, that's a print.
(applause)
(phone ringing)
- Slatzer.
- [Norma] Hello Bobby, it's
your Hollywood Gazette.
(phone ringing)
- Y'ello?
- [Norma] Bobby, I think we got cut off.
- No, we didn't.
- Don't you wanna talk to me?
- It cost too much.
- Why?
It's my nickel.
- What do you want, Norma Jean?
- Come on, ask me how I am.
- Okay, how are you?
- I'm working.
I'm singing in a movie here at Columbia.
Isn't that terrific?
- [Bob] That's great.
- And guess what.
Harry Cohn invited me to a big party.
Come back, be my escort.
- Don't start.
We have this same argument
every time you call.
- Then don't argue.
Maybe things will be different this time.
- [Bob] Different how?
- I don't know.
Why do you always have to know
how everything's going to turn out?
- Writers are funny that way.
- Well then I'm sorry I asked.
But don't worry, I'll never ask again.
- Thank you, Monroe.
- I thought you said we were
going to a party, Mr. Cohn.
- We are a party, now get back here.
If you don't come here right now
you're gonna have to walk all
the way back to Hollywood.
- That's okay, Mr. Cohn,
I was born in Hollywood.
I know the way.
- [Harry] Well, you've
really done it this time.
- Columbia's going to dump me.
- Sure looks that way.
Fox, now Columbia.
Congratulations.
- Harry, I can sing.
I did that number last
week and I was really good.
Even the crew applauded.
- Who cares?
- I care.
- Sorry.
See how much you upset me?
Of course you have talent, I know that.
But this business is about people.
You can't treat people badly
and expect them to help you.
I'm gonna call Harry Cohn.
Now what should I tell him?
Just be nice to him, kiddo, you can do it.
It's in your hands, Marilyn.
What should I tell him.
- Tell him I'm thinking
about getting a new agent.
(phone ringing)
- Slatzer.
- [Norma] Come home for
the holidays, Bobby.
I don't want to be alone.
- And I'm the only one you can call?
- [Norma] You're the only
one who's never let me down.
- So what does that make
me, Norma Jean, your pal?
Sorry, that's not enough.
- [Norma] Columbia dropped me.
No studio contracts.
No morals clause to keep us apart.
Besides, what's so immoral about
making love with someone you love?
- What happens when you
get another contract?
- [Norma] We'll cheat.
- Do you mean that?
- [Norma] Of course I do.
Aren't you tired of working
for that silly old newspaper?
- Well, all things considered,
I'd rather be making westerns.
- [Norma] Do it, Bobby, come back.
- Alright.
I'll be there at Christmas.
But we are gonna have a talk, alright?
- [Norma] Let me know when you're arriving
and I'll pick you up.
Oh, Bobby, it's going to be
wonderful having you here again.
Bye.
(dial tone)
- This is Valentino's house.
The radio said they're
gonna tear it down tomorrow.
I thought we should look
around once before it's gone.
- You know, you're the best
drinking buddy I ever had.
- You can almost feel the history.
This is where he danced the
tango and became the sheik.
- You were too young for those pictures.
- Mama took me to all of his movies.
She loved Valentino.
Sometimes the way she used to
look at him up there on the screen.
I almost thought he was my father.
I used to imagine that
anybody could be my father,
even Valentino.
He was so famous.
People loved him.
You know they still bring
him flowers, even today.
Promise me when I die you'll
bury me near Valentino.
So I can always see his flowers.
(Norma humming)
- What's going on down there?
- [Bob] We're sorry, we didn't
mean to make any trouble.
- We just wanted to dance
where Valentino danced
before they tore it down.
- C'mon pal, is there any
harm in a little romance.
- No, no harm.
But you might as well get it right.
(tango record spins)
- You know what this means?
- Yeah, it means we're
the last people to dance
where Valnetino danced.
- More importantly, lets do it right.
- At least I finally finished it.
- You did more than
that, it's good, Bobby.
It's really good.
- I sent to a friend at Monogram.
We'll see.
- You mean you might stay for a while?
More than just a week?
- Well that depends.
I figured it was about time that I asked.
- Excuse me.
Ms. Monroe, do you remember me?
- Of course, Mr. Hyde.
I met Mr. Hyde in Palm Springs.
- I'm Johnny Hyde, with the Morris office.
- Bob Slatzer.
- I'd been hoping I'd run into you again.
There's a party at Pandro
Berman's house tonight.
I promised I'd stop by.
Would you both like to come?
You'd be with me.
I know they'd be delighted to have you
and not the sort of thing
that could exactly hurt
a struggling young actress.
- Bobby?
- I'll tell you the truth,
I've been on the go for about 18 hours.
I could use some sack time.
Why don't you go?
Catch up with me later at the Roosevelt.
- You're sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- Well if you're certain you don't mind,
I promise to have her back at the hotel
at a decent hour, unscathed and untouched.
- And what about your friend Slatzer?
- He's back in town for
the holidays, maybe longer.
- That's good.
You have him give me a
call, I like that guy.
- That makes two of us.
Mr. Winchell, I was wondering
if you'd mind telling me;
is Johnny Hyde the gentleman
everyone says he is?
I think he wants to represent me.
- You take it from me.
If there was a company on
the stock exchange called
Decency Incorporated,
he'd own all the shares.
Excuse me, Marilyn.
I see someone who's dying
to tell me a secret.
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
- And what did Mr. Winchell say?
- He said I could trust you.
- I told you he would.
Now will you let me help you?
- Why me?
- You're a smart girl.
Your IQ is a lot bigger than
those magnificent breasts
of yours so act like it.
All these stars, you know
who they're watching?
You.
And if they do it here, they'll
do it in movie theaters.
I want the world to know you.
That takes work, time,
whoops, something we're
running very short of.
We'd better go.
- So soon?
- Yes.
I promised your friend that I would
get you back to the hotel unscathed.
And I always keep my word, to everyone.
- Bobby.
You would not believe it.
- Well I'll try.
- Johnny Hyde just
offered to change my life.
- Oh, whoopee.
- Acting lessons, singing
lessons, dance, voice.
He wants to shake my career.
He wants to take me under his wing
and make me into a star.
- I thought you wanted to be an actress?
- Are you angry with me
for going to the party?
- No, absolutely not.
It's my own fault for coming 2,000 miles
just because you asked me to.
- Oh Bobby.
I'm sorry.
Your first night back and
- No, I said it was okay, it's okay.
But there is something I'd
like to get out of the way.
I've been sitting here drinking this
excellent, extraordinarily cheap champagne
trying to screw up the
courage to ask you a question.
- Don't ask me to marry you.
I mean, you weren't
gonna ask me, were you?
I had this feeling.
- No.
No, I wasn't gonna ask you that.
Yes, I was.
- Bobby.
I love you.
But now's not the time for me
to concentrate on a marriage.
I'd only foul it up.
You understand, don't you?
- Sure.
- But if I ever do get married
again, I hope it's to you.
- I don't want to be bribed, Norma Jean.
- Does this feel like a bribe?
- Yeah.
And thanks for the offer.
But no thanks.
Not tonight.
(upbeat jazz)
- Good evening, sir.
- Norma Jean, I've got great news.
What's goin on?
- I wanted to write you a letter
but I knew I couldn't do that.
I knew I had to tell you.
- Tell me what?
- Johnny Hyde's asked me to move
in a house he owns in Beverly Hills.
He wants me to have a place
where I can entertain people.
Meet the magazine writers, you know.
He's doing so much to make
things happen in my career.
And he isn't well.
He's got heart problems.
I just want to be good to him in return.
At least for a while.
- Are you sleeping with him?
- No.
I wouldn't do that while
I was living with you.
- Will you sleep with him
when you move into that house?
- I think I might.
- Norma Jean think about
what you're doing here.
The man's 30 years older than
you are and he's married.
- He's getting divorced.
They've already started.
- You love him?
- No.
But he isn't well.
I just want to do what's
right, that's all.
I just want to make him
happy for a little while.
Maybe we could get together sometime and,
I don't know.
Johnny's got me up for
a John Houston film.
Maybe if I get the part we
could celebrate or something.
You didn't get to tell me your news.
- It's not important.
- [Norma] I'll call you in a few days.
- Don't.
I'm tired of watching your
life from the sidelines.
- Bobby.
- They're making my script.
Monogram is making my movie.
Miss you already.
You're still the best
drinking buddy I ever had.
Now I would appreciate
it if you'd get out.
- Take the sheet away.
I want to see you again.
Now I can die a happy man.
- Stop talking about dying.
- Sorry but it's a subject
near and dear to my failing heart.
You know, maybe it's time I get rid
of this damn medication of mine.
- Why would you do that?
- May keep my heart beating,
but it doesn't exactly make
me a great partner in bed.
- What we have in bed is wonderful.
It was even better tonight.
- It was, wasn't it?
- Yes, it was.
- I love you, Marilyn.
Marry me.
- I can't, Johnny.
I don't love you the same way.
- You don't have to.
My divorce is final, we
could get married tomorrow.
Tonight.
- No.
Sorry.
- Alright.
But I at least want you to inherit
some of my money after I die.
- I hate all this talk about death.
I want to talk about life.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Tell me.
- Nothing, Johnny.
Nothing.
- Come on.
Lets get dressed, lets get out of here.
We need a few laughs.
(swing music)
- Oh, that's the best medicine there is.
- That's what I've been
saying to you all along.
People just can't keep their eyes off you.
Champagne?
- Yes.
Bobby.
- Norma Jean.
Nice to see you again.
- You remember Mr. Hyde.
- Yeah, nice to see you
again too, Mr. Hyde.
- Good to see you.
- I'm sorry, this is Diana McShane.
- Hi.
- [Johnny] Good evening.
- Hi, you're Marilyn Monroe, aren't you?
- Yes.
- Bob took me to see "Love Happy".
It must have been crazy doin
a movie with those Marx Brothers.
- Oh, it was real crazy.
But I was only there
for a couple of hours.
I only had two lines.
- And Bob took me to see
"Scudda Hoo! Scudda Hay!"
- I only had one line in that.
Well, it wasn't really a line.
It was really a word.
What I said was,
"Mmm."
(Johnny chuckles)
How are you?
- Fine.
They're shooting my western next month.
Maybe you'd come out to the set?
- I'd like that.
- Well it was nice seeing you again.
- Bye.
- [Norma] Bye.
Johnny.
Can you excuse me?
Bobby.
I need to speak to you, it's important.
- Sure.
Give me a call at
Monogram tomorrow morning.
- No, it's very important,
we need to talk now.
- I can't, Norma Jean, I'm with somebody.
- But
- I'm sorry Norma Jean.
Call me tomorrow morning, okay?
(knocking)
(knocking continues)
Norma Jean look,
- I'm pregnant, Bobby.
It isn't his.
He can't have children anymore, it's ours.
Please Bobby.
We have to do something.
Now.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Take it easy.
Take it easy we'll do something.
Norma Jean think about this one last time.
- What do you think I've been
doing for the last few hours?
I have no other choice.
- Yes you do.
You can marry me.
We can have the baby.
- [Speaking Spanish]
You're very healthy, muy bueno.
This will be easy.
Up here.
- You're gonna do this on a kitchen table?
- It is a good place, don't worry.
Up here.
- It's okay, Bobby.
- We have no medicine.
No sedatives here.
But you can drink all you want.
- That's okay, I brought my own.
- Where did you get those?
- They're tranquilizers and they help.
They really help.
- Bueno.
You.
Outside.
Okay?
She's just a little sick,
from the tequila maybe.
- Is she okay, doc?
- Si.
All she needs is a little rest.
Sleep.
That is all.
- Where are we going?
- Back home.
Don't you think you've
had enough of those?
- It's for the pain.
I've got to relax, I need to rest.
It was our child, Bobby.
But I had to do it.
You understand, don't you?
- Don't ask me that.
- Bobby.
- Look, I helped alright?
I always help.
Doesn't mean I always understand.
- Forgive me.
- Sure.
Go to sleep.
(orchestral music)
After Mexico, Norma Jean
went back to Johnny Hide.
She won that part in "The Asphalt Jungle"
and a short time later had a
small part in "All About Eve."
She wasn't a star yet,
but she was on her way.
And then.
- And so John Hyde will be
missed by all who knew him
and whose lives he touched.
In all of Hollywood,
there was no bigger heart.
- What is she doing here?
- I don't know.
- She has no right to be here.
Do something.
- Would you come with
me please, Ms. Monroe?
- Who are you?
- Please don't make a
scene, just come with me.
- I just want to say goodbye.
- Quietly.
Have respect for the family.
- I made him happy the last few months,
nobody else even cared.
- We want you to leave.
- Johnny!
I loved you.
(sobbing)
- That's it, come on.
- Get her out of that house today.
I want you to pack her clothes,
throw her out, and change the locks.
- Bob, you're a life saver.
Thanks for coming.
- Well you didn't think I'd
leave you out on the street, did you?
- You know I loved him, Bobby.
- Yeah, I know.
- And you don't hate me?
- I wish it was that simple.
Look.
I could either take you to a hotel or
I could take you to my place.
But,
if I take you to my place,
it's only for a while until you get set up
and it's strictly platonic between us.
- I don't want to go to a hotel.
- You don't?
- So it's your place until
I get set up somewhere?
- Okay.
But, separate beds.
- Whatever you say.
- [Bob] I felt bad about
giving in to temptation.
But she was Marilyn Monroe,
even though I called her Norma Jean.
And when she wanted to make love,
she had a way of getting her way.
I don't know how many guys on earth
could've turned her down but
I wasn't one of them.
Sure, I still wanted us to get married but
I decided to wait until
she felt secure enough
in her career to settle down.
I never imagined how impossible
that was for Norma Jean.
But I would soon find out.
- Mama!
Oh mama, I'm so glad you came.
You look wonderful, really wonderful.
Doesn't she look wonderful?
- Yes she does.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Mrs. Baker.
- This is Bob Slatzer.
I wrote you about him, don't you remember?
It's my hair, how do you like my hair?
You've never seen me blonde before.
I bet this is really confusing.
- It's nice.
- Are you okay?
Mama was your trip okay?
- Here, why don't I take the suitcase.
- No.
- Well it's very nice to have you
staying with us, Mrs. Baker.
- I'll bet you're hungry.
Would you like to get something to eat?
- That would be nice.
- I was back in the old
neighborhood last month,
back in Van Nuys?
Remember Sim's Grocery Store?
Remember where I used
to sneak a few smokes?
Well it's still there, the
old store and everything.
- That's nice.
- And remember Mrs. Howard,
my old dance teacher?
She's still there too.
She still had that ruler,
the one she used to rap
me on the knuckles with
when I didn't get the dance step right,
which was most of the time, right mama?
When she saw me, she
remembered me right away.
She asked me what I was doing
and I told her I was
trying to be an actress.
She told me I was wasting my time.
That I didn't have any
talent in her class.
When I asked her how she
could be so sure she said,
"Because when you danced nobody clapped."
(Bob chuckles)
Won't you please talk to me mama?
I've waited so long to see you.
- Tell you what, lets
go back to the house.
She isn't ready yet, Norma Jean.
Maybe this is all just a
little too much for her.
- But she has to hear me.
- Give it a little time.
- I need you, mama.
I need to know that you hear me.
Please.
- Norma Jean.
- Yes, mama?
- I want to go back to the hospital.
- Mama wait.
I'll come too, just wait.
- No.
I want to go alone.
Please do you have to forgive me?
- Mama.
- Norma Jean, wait.
- Stay away from me,
Bobby, I'm no good for you.
- Stop!
Stop this.
- Don't you understand,
I'm just like my mother.
- Stop talking like that.
- My grandparents both
died in an institution
and my mother will and
so will I so stay away!
- Norma!
Norma Jean!
- I don't have any time,
don't you understand?
I'm running out of time.
- Afternoon.
- [Bob] Norma Jean got a place of her own
and then we lost touch.
She wouldn't even return the phone calls.
I understood her fear now,
but that didn't make it any
easier for me to lose her.
But in the beginning of 1952,
she'd done some small parts in some films.
She still wasn't a star but
she was becoming a celebrity.
Especially when she started
dating the Yankee clipper,
Joe DiMaggio.
I made a few movies myself.
B westerns.
Not exactly the big time, but
it sure beat washing dishes.
(phone rings)
Hello?
- Bobby, is that you?
- Hey, how ya been?
- You don't sound happy to hear from me.
- No, I'm tickled pink.
- Sounds like you need some cheering up.
Why don't you come here for a visit?
- Well Niagara Falls is
strictly for honeymooners.
- Bobby I need you.
It's been awful, I'm
doing everything wrong.
Mr. Hathaway is ready to kill me.
- Suppose DiMaggio is busy?
- I didn't ask him, I'm asking you.
If you don't want to help me, fine.
(dial tone)
- Jack.
I need some time.
Norma Jean, I mean,
Marilyn's having some trouble
on this movie she's doing.
- What are you, her priest?
- No, I'm just a friend.
- What about my movie?
- I'll be back in a week.
- No you won't, Bob.
If you take a walk, I'll
have to replace you.
- Come on, Jack, she asked for my help.
- No, you're the one that needs the help.
- Look, she's scared, alright.
"Niagara" is her first starring
role and she's messing up.
- Tell me something.
What do you get out of the deal?
- Some of the best days of my life.
Some of the worst.
(upbeat jazz)
- Pull her away from
the fan club, will you,
and lets get this shot moving.
- Yes, sir.
Ms. Monroe, Ms. Monroe.
Ms. Monroe, Mr. Hath would
like you back to set, please.
- I'll be finished in a few minutes.
- They're just fans, Ms.
Monroe, they'll understand.
- But I won't. Just a few more minutes.
- I don't think Mr. Hathaway's
going to approve of this.
- Really?
Well how do you think
he'll feel about this?
- Hi, my name is Bob Slatzer.
Marilyn sent for me?
I'm a friend.
You mind if I go say hello to her?
- Suit yourself, bud.
- Bobby!
You came!
And just in time.
- I don't know, Norma Jean,
looks like I got here too late.
- You saw?
- Yeah, I saw.
- I think I was wrong.
- Well, I think this is what
you've been fighting for all your life.
And now you're throwing it away.
- It's my life.
- Yeah.
But ever since I've known you,
you life's been about acting.
Now you've got the starring role
in a Henry Hathaway picture and.
- Bobby, I'm tired.
No lectures.
- Norma Jean, this is a business.
You can't get up one morning and say,
"I'm scared, call of the extras,
to hell with the director."
- I can do whatever I want.
- No you can't.
Not without wrecking your
career before it even takes off.
Fear is normal.
You just have to stop taking
it out on everybody else.
- I'm not afraid.
- You are afraid right down to your bones.
You're afraid to carry the entire movie
on your own shoulders,
and I don't blame you.
- I don't get it.
How does a nobody like you
talk to me about success?
Oh, Bobby.
- Listen to me, I am not a nobody.
The only thing I have ever
failed at in my life is you.
I can't seem to get us right.
- Where are you going?
- [Bob] Back to LA.
- Don't you dare walk out on me like that.
- Bye.
- Don't!
- Ow!
- Oh my God, oh my God.
What did I do, what did I do?
I don't mean to hurt you.
But I do it all the time.
And I hate myself for it.
I love you.
Why don't you ever give up on me?
- Because you're exciting.
And incredibly beautiful.
And the way you look at me
makes me feel like your leading man.
- Marilyn?
I want you to just walk down the steps,
make a bee line for the
camera and then turn left.
- Yes, Mr. Hathaway.
- She's been great the past
few days, a real pleasure.
What's with her?
- Not what, who.
- [Hathaway] And, action!
- [Cameraman] Enough?
- No, keep it going.
- She's gonna get mad, Henry.
- No she won't, Mr. Hathaway.
She'll be fine.
- Men.
Say cut already, Henry.
You've shot more film on my keister
than you have on my close-ups.
- [Hathaway] Cut!
(cheering and applause)
(sultry jazz)
- [Bob] After "Niagara" was
finished, we went back to LA.
Henry Hathaway seemed to
be happy with the picture
and so was Norma Jean.
As for me, I was fired.
The price of getting her back.
Not that we were going to live together.
We'd both had enough of that for a while.
But we were dating pretty regularly.
(doorbell rings)
(car engine settling)
She's not home, Mr. DiMaggio.
- I'll wait.
- Cigarette?
- No, thank you.
- Sorry, Joe, honey.
It's just a little dent.
- Forget it.
Who is this guy?
- Bobby?
What are you doing here?
- We have a date, remember?
- So do we.
- I guess I screwed up, huh?
- [Bob] Guess so.
- Why don't we all go
inside and have a drink?
- What would you like, Joe?
- How come he knows where the bar is?
- This is my house, Joe.
Bob's a friend.
He's been here before.
- He acts like he lives here.
I don't like it.
- I just remember where
the bar is, that's all.
- Who are you going out with Marilyn?
Make up your mind.
- I don't like being pressured, Joe.
- Fine.
Fine.
Good night.
- Good night, Joe.
- [Bob] Gee, he took that
pretty hard, didn't he?
- You did that on purpose.
- Wait a minute, Norma Jean.
- Get out.
I don't want to manipulated
by either one of you.
Get out!
(somber jazz)
- Marilyn?
Slow down.
Are you always in such a hurry?
- I'm on a tight ship, Mr. Zanuck,
I don't want to miss my call.
- I'm going to see a cut
of "Niagara" next week.
I hear good things, especially about you.
- I hope they're all true.
- You know what I predict, Marilyn?
I predict a great future for us.
- Aren't you the same man
who wouldn't give me a contract with Fox
because you didn't think I was photogenic?
- Someone may have been foolish enough
to say so a few years ago,
but you've given him ample
reason to regret such
very poor judgment.
Now what's this I hear about you and Joe?
Nothing I hate more than seeing
my favorite people having a spat.
- It's not a spat, really.
- Well I don't care what it was.
I want you two to kiss and make up.
- But
- Want to keep me happy,
that's what you'll do,
kiss and make up.
(knocking)
(knocking continues)
- Look at that moon.
- What are you doin here?
- I thought we needed a drink.
- What are we celebrating?
(Norma laughing)
- Whoops!
I baptized myself.
That's what the mother said
in "The Glass Menagerie".
(both laughing)
Joe proposed to me.
- What did you say to him?
- I said no.
Zanuck told me I should marry him.
So did half the people on the Fox lot.
So.
Everyone wants me to get married.
Bobby, marry me.
We can do it in Mexico.
- Are you serious?
- You've been wanting to
marry me for a long time.
Lets do it.
- Oh, this is crazy.
No, this is too impulsive,
this will never work.
- You've been trying to get
me to the altar for six years
and you have the nerve
to call me impulsive?
I love you, Bobby.
Marry me.
- It's not the way I had
it planned, Norma Jean.
- Help me do what I want us to do
for the first time in my life.
- We leave now, there's no turning back.
- Not until we're married.
- We're gonna go all the way this time,
there's no stopping us.
- So what are we waiting for?
- [Minister] And Norma Jean,
by the laws of the state of Baja,
in the Republic of Mexico,
I now pronounce you, man and wife.
Please, a beautiful kiss.
(both giggling)
- We really did it, didn't we?
- Don't pinch me.
If I'm dreaming, I don't want to wake up.
- I don't feel any different yet.
- I do.
Oh I feel incredibly different.
- I wish we could stay in Mexico.
I wish we didn't have to go back.
- Marilyn, I didn't marry you
so that we could run away.
I married so that we could
weather the tough times together.
We don't have to hide anymore.
We'll handle Zanuck and the studio
and we'll do it together.
- You called me Marilyn.
- Yeah, I guess I did.
- Don't.
I like it when you call me Norma Jean.
- Okay.
Then Norma Jean it is.
For now
and forever.
- [Fox Exec] She has definitely got it.
This is one beautiful doll.
- You want to tear her clothes off,
she's willing to be gentle about it.
You know men don't dream
about jumping into the sack
with Betty Grable anymore,
they need something new.
They need Marilyn Monroe.
She's already getting
1,000 fan letters a week.
When "Niagara" opens,
that number could double,
maybe even triple.
Marilyn could become this
studio's most valuable asset.
- Then why is she getting
married in Mexico?
My secretary's sister works in wardrobe.
Said Marilyn borrowed an outfit
and went to tie the knot with some guy.
And it was not Joe DiMaggio.
(both giggling)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
Yes.
It's for you.
- Yes?
Yes, Mr. Zanuck.
We'll be there tomorrow.
- Well you two kids, welcome back.
Marilyn, I'm so happy for you.
This must be the lucky
fellow, Bob Slatzer.
You two, what a pleasure.
Right off the bat with congratulations.
Come sit down, please.
- Thank you, Mr. Zanuck.
- Thank you.
Marilyn thought you
might be a little upset.
- Why would I be upset?
We can't control matters of
the human heart, now can we?
If I could, all my pictures would be hits.
Now, whatever makes Marilyn happy,
that's all that matters.
This marriage will only set
her back for a little while.
The damage, it's reparable.
- Damage?
- Come on Marilyn, lets don't be naive.
What do you think you're
selling up there on the screen?
Sex.
Plus talent, of course,
but the men who buy tickets
to come and see you, well they like to
imagine that you're available.
And when they find out you're married,
well you lose some of your appeal.
We have to protect ourselves.
We have to cut back on some of the ads,
the campaign for "Niagara".
- Excuse me.
Is that why you called us in here?
To intimidate my wife?
- I'm not an ogre, Mr. Slatzer.
I can't stop Marilyn from
doing what she wants.
All I can do is advise.
In my opinion, this
marriage is bad timing.
Now, it's Marilyn's happiness
and it's Marilyn's decision.
- Well I'm glad to hear you say that.
- Point is, what's going
to make Marilyn happy.
Is it to follow through with
"Niagara", make the most of it,
or wait a couple of years
in the hopes that maybe
a role this good might come along again.
- What are you suggesting?
- An annulment.
I know, I know.
It seems like an enormous sacrifice.
But hear me out.
Go back to Mexico, get this
marriage wiped off the books.
And wait.
A year or so from now, you
kids can get married again.
After "Niagara" has made
Marilyn Monroe a star.
Now I want you to understand,
I don't like putting this
kind of pressure on you two.
But we have an entire
campaign sitting on hold
just because of this.
We have to know.
Now.
I'm going to leave you two alone.
You have a very big decision to make.
- Well it's easy to see how
he got to be a studio boss.
- What are we going to do?
- Do?
We tell him to go to hell.
He's bluffing, Norma Jean.
They're not gonna hold back on "Niagara",
not after they already
spent the money to make it.
- How do you know that?
Tell me Bobby, how can you be so sure?
What Mr. Zanuck said, it
made sense, didn't it?
Didn't it?
"Niagara" is my lucky break.
It's everything that
you told me it could be.
What if it's ruined?
What if the press finds out?
- Take it easy.
Alright?
I'm not gonna let anyone or
anything ruin this for you.
Not even me.
- I don't want to lose you.
You must believe that.
- You're never gonna lose me.
But, maybe for now, maybe
it would be best if we
went along with him.
- Maybe it would.
- So, has your marriage been consummated?
- [Together] Yes.
- You want no record of the marriage?
- That's correct.
- Well, you understand, I
am responsible of records.
Perhaps an extra $50?
- What about your copy of
the marriage certificate?
- Oh, I'm sorry, I
cannot give that to you.
But I think I have another way.
- [Bob] We'd been married five days.
The best days of my life.
As we drove back to LA, we
told each other it wasn't over.
We must have said it a thousand times.
And a thousand times every morning.
"Niagara" made Norma Jean a big star.
Several months later, I was
working on the set of a western
when I heard this story over the radio.
Marilyn Monroe had married Joe DiMaggio.
America's sex goddess
married an American hero.
I knew it was a wedding
Zanuck approved of.
But the marriage lasted only nine months.
And then a few weeks after their divorce.
- Hi.
- Marilyn.
What are you?
- I was in the neighborhood
and I thought I'd stop by.
Still there isn't it?
- What?
- That old feeling.
- Look.
Please don't.
- Bobby, I'm all alone.
And you know who I think about?
You.
Not Joe, not anyone but you.
This time.
- No, no there is no "this time."
It wasn't in the stars for us, Norma Jean.
I think I've always known that.
God.
You can make a man crazy with wanting you.
You're like a drug.
I can't do it anymore.
- I guess you took the cure.
- No.
No, there is no cure.
That's why I'll always love you.
- Everybody loves me, Bobby.
Didn't you know?
- [Bob] So here I was on a
brutally hot afternoon in 1962.
Joe took charge of the
funeral arrangements
and he wouldn't let anyone
from Hollywood attend
so we were all forced to
watch from the sidelines.
Maybe he was right.
Hollywood sure didn't save her.
Four of the men who
carried Norma Jean's casket
never even knew her.
Later that day, Walter Winchell
asked me if it was worth the heartache
to have married a goddess.
I said yes.
And that's when I realized
that was her special gift.
Up there on that screen,
Marilyn Monroe made all men feel love.
Maybe she was a goddess.
To me, she was my very own Norma Jean.
(somber jazz)
(tango record)