[no audio]
[engines revving]
[school bell rings]
[indistinct murmuring]
There is a distinct difference
between poetry and prose.
Don, will you please stand and read
William Ernest Henley's poem on page 376?
[pages turn]
[book closes]
[book slams down on desk]
Poetry's dumb.
[laughter]
♪[instrumental music]♪
Heh Donnie.
-Wanna beer?
-Sure.
So, why aren't you in school?
- School's a waste.
- Yeah.
Who needs it?
Heh, Eddie here thinks he's
pretty fast with his hands.
Oh yeah?
No one beats me.
Okay if I use just one hand?
I'm holding a beer.
[two hand slaps]
Heh, wait a minute.[laughter]
I wasn't ready.[laughter]
[two hand slaps]
Dang!
[laughter]
My eye.
Just call me Mr. no one.
How come?
You said no one beats you.
[laughter]
Heh, reflexes don't mean nothin.
I can still out ride you.
Let's race and see.
Sounds good.
- Tonight at seven?
- No, now.
Yeah Donnie, you can use my bike.
Okay. Where?
Here.
- What about the stop sign?
- We run it.
Unless you're scared.
[chicken clucking]
Let's do it.
- Alright!
- Come on now. Let's do it!
[engine starts up]
[engine revs up]
[engine idles]
[barrel hits the street]
[engine revs]
Alright, when this hits the ground,
first one down and back here wins.
[engines rev up]
[engines roar]
Wooh!
[brakes screech]
[car horn blares]
[engines roar]
[tires screech]
[engines hum]
[engines roar]
[thud]
[truck's horn blares]
Go! Go!
[engines roar]
Whooh!
[engines roar by]
[engines fade]
[engines trail off]
[brakes screech]
[engines hum]
Good job Donnie.
Yeah! Alright!
Yeah!
Nice race Don.
Hey, did you see your old man back there?
Nah.
Think he saw you.
Not as fast as I was going.
[laughter]
Still...
I think you better
have a story for tonight.
No problem.
My old man only
knows what I tell him.
I'll tell you what we'll do.
I don't know what to do Emilio.
Don's slipping away.
I don't have any control.
What does Don like to do?
He likes motorcycles.
Why don't you give him one?
Give him a motorcycle?
He is street racing and
cutting school now.
I can't reward that.
You don't.
If he doesn't do what you want,
you take away the motorcycle.
Emilio.
That's brilliant.
[chuckles]
Thank you for noticing.
But I can't justgive it to him.
No, you have to make sure that,
he thinks, he's earned it.
That shouldn't be
too hard to do.
[motorcycle outside]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Where's your jacket?
Oh I, uh, lent it to a friend.
He had a motorcycle race today.
Oh, I see.
[knock at door]
Must be him now.
[door opens]
- Mike, what's happening?
- Heh, Don.
Hi Mr. Castro.
Hello. [door closes]
Look Don, I gotta go.
Thanks for the jacket.
Did you win the race?
Nah, but it was close.
I hear around town that
Don's a pretty good racer.
He's the best.
Oh, he can't be the best.
Why can't I be?
You're not racing at the track.
Should I put a motor
on my bicycle to race?
I'd buy a motorcycle for you.
If that's all you needed.
See you later.
What do you think I need?
You are just not good enough.
I'm the best there is.
You get a motorcycle
and I'll win every race.
You got to be able to ride.
I'll show you I can ride.
You show me C's in school too.
Or the wheels stop turning.
I'll get the grades.
You street race, and I
will sell the motorcycle.
Okay.
Do we have a deal?
Deal.
Where did you get that?
Your grandfather took it in trade.
Why?
That's, one of life's mysteries.
What are you going to do with it?
It's for you.
I didn't make a deal to join the circus.
I thought you were going
to show me you could ride.
Not a circus bike.
For dirt bike racing, you need balance.
- If you don't think you can do it.
- No. I can do it.
We'll see.
String these up between the
fences in the back yard.
Why?
Because, I don't want
you to break anything.
I don't need this.
Just put it up.
Here you go.
[thud]
Maybe you should just quit.
I'll ride it.
Hi Don.
I saw you from my window.
What are you doing?
I've got to show my dad I have balance
before he'll let me race motorcycles.
Talk about dumb.
This rope is another dumb idea of his.
It is not going to hold me up.
Well, let me help.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
You look different.
What do you mean?
Bigger, I mean taller.
Well I grew an inch.
Yeah, at least.
- Put your arm on my shoulder.
- Sure.
Got it.
[thud]
You want to try again?
Sure.
♪[inspirational music]♪
I gotta go.
I could use some help tomorrow.
Okay.
- Bye.
Maybe I was wrong about you.
What do you mean, maybe?
You look like, maybe you can ride.
I can ride.
We'll have to get you a
motorcycle this week, to find out.
- When do I race?
- In the Hollister Open, next month.
- Alright.
- You did it.
I'm so proud of you.
Oh no problem with your credit
Mrs. Naygrow,
I am buying a motorcycle for my son.
And, I am asking everyone to pay cash,
for the deliveries this month.
Thank you very much.
I know just the bike I want Dad.
I saw it over at Hollister Cycle.
It's a 650 cc TT Special.
- Brand new bike?
- It's a beauty.
Would it be excellent, if we bought it?
Yeah, it sure would be.
Well, you're getting C's in school,
not A's.
So, here's a fair bike.
- Hi.
Hey.
How about me being your first rider?
Sure, come on.
♪[uplifting music]♪
What a great feeling.
Let me show you a better one.
Why do you and your dad
yell at each other so much?
Let's don't talk now.
I want to get to know you better.
It's personal.
Well what you are doing
now is personal too.
My old man don't care about me.
Well, my parents care about me.
But they never bought me
anything like this bike.
He's always working.
He never takes time to do things with me.
Well maybe that say more about his
business than it does about him.
Yeah, maybe.
What happened to you at
school on Friday, anyway?
We've talked enough.
What happened Don?
I don't like school.
Well, why?
I just don't like it!
We've talked enough.
Take me home.
It's a package deal Don.
My mind and my body go together.
If you just want to feel good,
you can go and do that for yourself.
Where have you been Tina?
With Don Castro.
Why were you with him?
I don't know.
♪[contemplative music]♪
[phone rings]
Tina: Hello?
I'll be in the garage,
if you want to talk.
Okay.
♪[contemplative music]♪
Hi.
I'm sorry about today.
It's okay.
No, I'm not sorry I tried.
I'm sorry you didn't want to.
Go all the way?
Yeah.
So...
if I had let you, what would
it have meant to you?
What should it mean?
Well, that you love me,
and that you would someday want me
to marry you, and have your baby.
That's pretty serious.
I think that's how it should be.
I'm not ready for that.
Me either.
You're the only one who has
ever wanted to get to know me.
That's because I like you Don.
I like you too, Tina.
Maybe...
instead of going all the way...
we could go a quarter of the way.
Maybe.
You never told me why
you don't like school.
I don't like school...
because I am not that good at it.
Why not?
I can't read.
Not at all?
Not many words.
Can you spell?
Sometimes.
How did you make it this far?
I faked it.
Who knows you can't read?
Only you.
I can help you Don.
I am getting an A in English.
You think you could?
It'll be okay.
I am good at racing Tina.
With this motorcycle...
I can make something happen for myself.
I'm getting, tired of talking.
Where were you?
Over at the Castro's.
Your mother and I don't
want you over there.
Why not?
He's a loser.
Don's not a loser Dad.
He's been kicked out of high school.
He's disrespectful to his father.
- There are reasons for--
- Oh, I am sure there are.
There's always a reason.
And, since you understand there is always
a reason for not doing something,
you'll understand that your mother
and I, don't want you over there.
We're just friends, Dad.
He's not even my type.
Good. Enough said.
- Dad, is it okay if I ask Tina to come?
- Sure.
[knocking]
- Hi Don.
- Hi
- Do you want to come and watch me race?
- Sure.
Mom, I'm going with the Castro's,
I'll see you this afternoon.
I'm going to win today.
What would winning mean, Don,
finishing in the money?
That's not good enough.
I don't want to be fourth.
There are 100 motorcycles entered today.
When the race is over,
fourth is gonna look good to 96 of them.
Fourth won't look good to me.
Race announcer: It's been an action packed
afternoon here at the Hollister Open,
as we've seen some seasoned
veterans fully surprised by,
a newcomer here at the track, Don Castro.
[announcer listing rider names]
What are two greasers doing here?
It looks like they're going to race.
That's the trouble with America.
Anybody can do anything.
So, now I have been reduced to
competing against a Mexican.
- Mexicans ain’t so bad.
- Are you kidding?
Go move the truck upwind from
the re-fried bean eaters.
Okay.
[inaudible announcer]
[engine noises]
♪[build-up music]♪[inaudible announcer]
[engines revving]
♪[build-up music]♪
Race announcer: As Castro begins
the line in the pole position.
[engines revving]
♪[build-up music]♪
[applause]
♪[rock music]♪[engines roaring]
Race announcer: Down on the inside, is
Jerry Johnson as he jumps into the lead.
♪[rock music]♪[inaudible announcer][engines]
Jerry Johnson powering out in front.
On number 79, Dennis Kritzer.
Stan Morris is our third place rider.
Then Castro on number 11. Castro moving
to the outside as Morris bobbles around.
Leading the race number 18 Jerry Johnson.
On the inside, is Don Castro locked in
battle with the number 79, Dennis Kritzer.
Kritzer to the inside, Castro wide
to the outside. There's a little war.
Down on the front straight
away and into turn number one.
It's Castro back in the pack.
Out in front it's still
number 18, Jerry Johnson,
as they head to the back straight away.
Castro, wide to the outside. Taking
big horsepower to come out there.
Now it's Stan Morris picking
up sight of the lead rider.
It's Castro, wide to the outside.
Morris now dominating.
Jerry Johnson is your number one.
Bill Holland, Stan Morris and Don Castro.
On the back straight away, it's still
Kritzer in the second place spot.
Out in front is number 18, Jerry Johnson.
Don Castro trying to fight a little
bike as he continues on the inside.
Yeah!
Kritzer and Dan Castro down in turn one.
The last straight away,
Castro moving to the outside.
Takes more horsepower out there.
Your leader as they go into turn number
three, number 18, Jerry Johnson.
Dennis Kritzer, holds
onto the second spot.
Native of ours Don Castro, ahead
of 55, is in the fourth slot.
That's the white flag.
It's gonna be Jerry Johnson's race.
Dennis Kritzer starting to advance.
Johnson wide to the outside now,
as Castro looks to move on the
inside, coming out of turn two.
Kritzer, down on the inside now.
Now, as they come out of turn
four this is the checked flag.
Looks like it's going to be a
victory for Dennis Kritzer.
Then Jerry Johnson, Stan
Morris and Don Castro.
[cheering]
♪[triumphant music]♪
[applause]
Great race Don.
Yeah babe, you were fast.
Yeah, fast fourth.
You're gonna win next time out.
I am?
You got balance and speed.
Next time you'll have knowledge.
I will?
[slam]
I should have won that race.
Don't ever do that Don.
But isn't it good to let your
frustrations out, Mr. Castro?
Don represents a whole race
of people when he rides Tina.
He can't be a poor sport.. ever.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
♪[emotional music]♪
Thanks for taking me today.
Sure son.
♪[emotional music]♪
My parents don't want me to
get involved with anyone Don.
Why not?
I guess they don't want what's already
happened to me, to happen to me.
- Do they know we're going together?
- No.
That has to be our secret.
♪[emotional music]♪
Let's keep another secret.
The racers who beat you last week, were
walking the track when we got there.
Now, no one will have
an advantage over you.
I'll do better today.
You'll win if you pay attention.
Look at this.
Stay high on the second
curve, to miss this.
Okay Dad.
You want the most out of racing?
You have to put the most into it.
You're the only one,
who can make you a winner.
Race announcer: A little bit of sea
breeze is gonna cool us off.
As they come out of turn number one,
Don Castro out in front, here in Salinas.
Jerry Johnson, number 18,
working on the inside.
As they come up on him straight away.
Woodie Rodgers, 55, on the outside.
Scott Chappell number three,
trying to make a move
Don Castro leading this
as they come out of one.
Then it's Johnson, Rodgers,
followed by Kritzer.
[engines roar]
Down in turn three is still Don Castro.
Castro now opening a wide lines
as they go into turn four.
Johnson down on the inside then
it's Woodie Rodgers, and Kritzer.
[cheering]
Don Castro the leader as they
go down into turn one again.
Jerry Johnson working on the
inside, then Rodgers and Kritzer.
[cheering]
Out of turn three
it's Don Castro with the lead.
Castro followed by Johnson and Rodgers.
It's Don Castro working
down into turn four.
Jerry Johnson maneuvering around, he's
gonna look for Castro on the outside,
as they come out of turn four.
Castro to the inside line.
Johnson wide to the outside,
follower by Johnny McGill,
Dennis Kritzer and Mark Butler.
[cheering]
[engines roaring]
Coming after him now is,
number18, Jerry Johnson.
Followed by Woodie Rodgers and
Dennis Kritzer, then Johnny McGill.
Trying to make a move in there,
it's the number three rider.
It's still Don Castro, looking back
he sees Johnson on the move.
[cheering]
Bottom of turn four, number 18 Jerry
Johnson with a sudden burst of power.
Now, it's Johnson moving on the outside.
Castro looking over to Johnson's burst
of speed, as they enter the turn four
Johnson looks back, waving
at Castro, as they exit four.
It's Johnson then Castro.
- No.
That's the checkered flag.
Jerry Johnson, Don Castro, Dennis
Kritzer and Scott Chappell.
[distant] Announcer: A very surprised Don
Castro, on his way back to the pits.
And Jerry Johnson, with that first
prize, taking this one away.
For the final at Sully,
as we close up today's action.
Mark Butler pulling into the pits,
but the win goes to Jerry Johnson.
As Castro pulls into the pits,
and they are really going to
have to check this one out,
to see what happened to the motorcycle.
That, was the right amount of nitro.
I toyed with the greaser.
- Did you see me cruise up along side him?
- Yeah.
- Then, did you see him look over at me?
- And then, did you see me look at him?
- Yeah, yeah.
Then, what did you see?
You blew him away.
Yeah.
[sinister laughter]
I don't understand it.
I was in full throttle.
What's nitro?
Nitro methane, some
race cars use it for fuel.
Well, I heard him say he
had it in his gas tank.
I'll never win against nitro.
- Unless I burn it myself.
- You know it is illegal to use.
- They did it.
- Then they're wrong.
- They're not the only ones.
- Would you rather be wrong and win...
or right and lose?
I want to be right and win.
You will son. You will.
♪[subdued music]♪
Mr. Castro, could you let me off here?
- I want to go see a girlfriend.
- Sure.
♪[subdued music]♪
Will I see you this afternoon?
I hope so.
I'll try and get away.
♪[subdued music]♪
Tina's not with the Castro's.
Dad.
Why did you and mom get a divorce?
Well son, I guess you could say that our
bodies grew up before our minds did.
When our minds grew up...
they wanted different things.
Why didn't you remarry?
Do you remember when our dog, Shorty died?
and you didn't want to get another one,
because you knew the next dog would die?
And you didn't want to feel so bad again?
Yeah.
I remember.
Do you think you will
ever get married again?
Someday son.
What's the matter?
I want to keep racing...
but my grades are going to out soon.
I am not going to get a C in English.
Then I'll take care of it.
How?
Don't worry about it.
I love you, Tina.
I love you too Don.
- Hi Mr. Boggs.
- Well hello Tina.
Do you have any filing for me to do today?
Yes, would you put those records
in that file over there please?
Sure
I'm sorry we haven't been able to have
this meeting before now Mrs. Lopez,
but Don Castro's file had been misplaced.
Mr. Boggs, I don't think Don can read.
I think he should be
held back another year.
I'm afraid we can't
do that, Mrs. Lopez.
Don was held back
in the third grade.
The law allows us to hold a student
back only once in his school life.
We are doing him an injustice, letting him
graduate without the ability to read.
We have to obey the law Mrs. Lopez.
Now, there are hundreds of
students in this school.
We can't help them all.
Let me assure you Mrs. Lopez, I think
you're doing the right thing with Don.
But, if I call on him to read,
he leaves the classroom.
- Then don't call on him.
- I'm sorry Mr. Boggs.
I just don't feel right about it.
Are you alright?
Just a hangover from a bachelor
party last night. Oh, what a party.
By the end of the evening,
the groom was a verbal dyslexic.
[polite laughter]
Thank you Mr. Boggs.
- Thank you for your help.
- Oh, anytime Mrs. Lopez.
An A Tina?
Don, you can't make an F into a C.
An F has to either be an A or a B.
Then why not a B?
Because the A was
easier to make.
You never said thank you.
- I didn't want an A.
- Then maybe you should just keep the F.
Hey...
I'm sorry okay?
We have a bigger problem
than your F, Don.
What?
I think I'm pregnant.
Then we'll get married.
I want you to marry me
because you love me.
Not because I'm pregnant.
I love you Tina.
Race Announcer: This is what
you folks have been waiting for,
this afternoon's feature at Santa Rosa.
It's Mark Butler on the line, number 76.
Number 3, Scott Chappell.
Number 79, Dennis Kritzer,
Number 11, Don Castro.
55, Woodie Rodgers.
[engines roaring]
[inaudible announcer]
Down into turn one, Castro out in front.
Behind him is Butler, then
Chappell followed by Rodgers.
Down they go out of turn number two,
Don Castro pulls out by
about a three bike lead,
as they go up the back straight
away, and start's us into turn three.
Castro, takes the turn three out in front.
Don Castro, setting a foot down,
holding a nice inside line.
Behind him is Mark Butler,
Scott Chappell and Woodie Rodgers.
Out of the turn number four,
advancing a bit more, is Don Castro.
Then Mark Butler, holding onto second.
Scott Chappell, down on the
inside, on number three.
Then it's Woodie Rodgers,
followed by Stan Morris.
Then the outside, number 18, is
Jerry Johnson, well back in the pack.
Don Castro taking down the
turn three on number 11.
Castro from Hollister California,
having a great ride here today.
It's Castro followed by
Butler then Scott Chappell.
Dennis Kritzer, number 79,
well back in the pack.
On the inside of Stan Morris.
Going down into turn
number one, is Don Castro.
[engines roaring]
[inaudible announcer]
Out of the turn it's still Don Castro.
Stan Morris trying to close
from the back of the pack,
as Castro takes down another one.
White flag out. One more lap to go
with Don Castro, then Mark Butler
Butler, back in second place.
Mark's started closing now
As they go into turn three, Castro,
your leader. Butler coming on the outside.
Castro! Castro with problems!
Butler over on the outside.
It's got him the win.
Castro might not cross the line
for second place finish.
Don Castro, scooting it across the
line for a second place finish.
[distant] Castro with definite engine
problems and takes it into the pits.
I haven't seen anything like this, a
scooter ride, your second place finish.
In third..
[cheering]
Way to go, Scooter.
[distant] Race announcer:
This winds up today's action.
We certainly hope you all had a good
time, and have a great trip home.
Still thinking about that race today?
I wanted to win today.
I could use the money...
now that Tina's pregnant.
Pregnant?
Yeah.
I'm gonna marry her next month.
Do you know for sure, she's pregnant?
She went to Dr. Garcia’s, yesterday.
I called her from the track,
and she is pregnant.
[phone rings]
Hello.
Hi Emilio.
Hey, compadre. How's it going?
Fine Emilio.
Is it true that my
son has to get married?
No. But you didn't hear it here.
Okay?
- I need you to come by the house now.
- You saved me.
I was just going to mow the lawn.
Thanks Emilio.
Have a cold one ready.
Son...
sit down.
You don't have to
get married Don.
We are not having an abortion.
Tina's not pregnant.
Yes she is Dad.
She told me.
Tina is not telling
you the truth Don.
No.
You're lying to me.
Because you don't want me to marry her.
Marry her if you want Don.
But she's not pregnant.
- That's a lie.
- I am not a liar.
[knocking]
Don.
I missed you so.
I've missed you too, Tina.
Let's drive to Reno and
get married tonight.
Are you really pregnant?
Why do you ask me that?
I told you I was.
Just wanted to see you tell me.
Tonight's fine with me.
[knocking]
Let's not answer.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to come by and make sure you
understood, you're no longer pregnant.
Why did you lie to me?
Excuse me.
I didn't want to lose you.
You won't keep me
by lying to me.
I won't keep you anyway.
My parents don't want me
to see you anymore, Don.
They'd have to accept you,
if I was pregnant.
I was pregnant.
But I, had a miscarriage.
Tina...
I love you.
Don't worry about your parents.
Then marry me.
I will.
But, not now.
Now, is the only chance we have.
My parents will see to that.
Your parents will say I'm okay,
once I make some money.
They won't change their minds, Don.
A year from now, we'll be married.
What can your parents, or
anybody else, do about it?
If you really loved me,
you'd marry me now.
If you really loved me, you'd wait a year.
Tell you what...
six months.
We'll be married in six months.
Okay Frank. I'll take care of it tomorrow.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
That's okay son.
I've been there before.
I'm going to the store.
You want to come?
No.
I'm gonna try to, fix that oil leak.
Okay.
See you later.
Stay away from my daughter.
Don't you want her to be happy?
I'm warning you.
[school bell rings]
Tina.
Hi Don.
[short car horn]
Race Announcer: 105 degrees
here in the Lodi Cycle Bowl,
as the forward team comes pounding
out of the fourth turn.
On the inside, is Don Castro. Wide to
the outside is number 67, Stan Morris.
It's Castro with engine problems.
Castro, up at the top end, over two
runs, can transfer to the main.
Castro's got problems.
Working on the outside now,
number 67 Morris, with the win.
In the second spot, it's Don Castro.
Followed by number 76, Mark Butler.
Then number 20 Scott Eichelbaugh,
number 31 John Eichelbaugh.
But, Castro on the number 11, makes the
transfer spot, with a blown top end.
Don Castro, lucky finish.
Question is, now, can Castro repair that
bike, in time to get back to the main?
Last chance qualifier coming up.
What do you think?
I don't know.
A little hard to scoot across
that finish line this time,
with that blown engine, huh scooter?
Hey Don, let's play some soccer.
Not now Jerry.
You might as well play.
You're not racing.
Some other time.
I thought you greasers loved soccer.
Let's play.
I knew you couldn't
pass up a soccer game.
My goal, is your motorcycle.
Your goal, is my motorcycle.
- You got it.
- You say go.
Go.
You knocked my bike over.
You bent the handlebars.
I'm sorry.
Heh, Jerry.
Look at Scooter limp.
What a pussy.
What's the matter Don?
- I think Jerry broke my ankle.
- Oh, no.
It was worth it.
Does it hurt, real bad, Scooter?
Not bad enough to lose to you.
- Tape it Dad.
- Tape it?
It's your slide foot.
I'm gonna win today.
It's not worth it son.
Yes, it is.
Okay.
Dave, can I use your bike for the finals?
Sure Don.
Race announcer: Don Castro sits poised
and ready aboard Dave Canon's number 203.
Set for the feature.
With him, on the inside is
number 20, Scott Eichelbaugh.
On the other side is
number 76, Mark Butler.
Both in this for a last chance qualifier.
Moments away from start.
There's your green
They head for the first turn.
Don Castro, slow off the line.
[inaudible announcer]
[engines roaring]
Now your leader is, Mark Butler.
As the come up on the front straight away,
It's Don Castro on his
way through the pack.
[cheering]
Here is a setup to turn one,
with Butler in the lead.
With Castro, definitely on the move.
[inaudible announcer]
[engines roaring]
Mark Butler your leader,
but Castro on the charge,
as they go to the back straight away.
Don Castro, 203, on the move.
Don Castro heading for turn
three, he's out in front.
Castro, your leader now
as we set for turn three.
Mark Butler is not out of this one,
76 begins to fight his way back.
Butler on the move on the
front straight away.
Castro worked to the inside, Butler's in
the lead as they go down the final line.
[cheering]
♪[rock music]♪
Don Castro, moving down to the inside.
He's going to be presenting his side foot.
Tremendous battle going on for
that third and fourth positions.
Stan Morris now in that third
spot, way out in the corner.
Jerry Johnson well back as they
go into this back straight away.
It's Don Castro and Mark
Butler in the battle,
Don Castro, number 203, out in front.
Wide to the outside is Don Castro
as he heads into the corner.
Now it's Don Castro on that
borrowed number 203 bike,
he's looking great as
he gets the feel of it.
Down on that third turn, it's
Castro pushing for all he's worth.
White flag, one more lap to go.
It's Don Castro followed by
Stan Morris, Mark Butler,
then it's John Eichelbaugh
and Jerry Johnson.
It's Don Castro, wide to the outside.
♪[inspirational music]♪
Don Castro your leader,
on number 203, a borrowed bike.
Takes it back, one more time Castro
heading into the turn.
♪[inspirational music]♪
Don Castro had a blow out on his
own bike up on this corner.
It comes to the checkered flag.
It's Don Castro!
Followed by Mark Butler, Stan Morris,
Scott Eichelbaugh,
Jerry Johnson, John Eichelbaugh.
[cheering]
Tina.
You want me to talk to them?
No.
We'll work it out.
[cartoon noises]
[chuckling]
I don't understand, son.
Your ankle's broken.
Your bike is totaled.
And you are not depressed?
Because I know I'm good.
No, not good.. great
at racing motorcycles.
I'll have my day.
Can you do some
shopping for me?
Sure. What do you need?
A hacksaw... [taps cast]
and the largest pair
of boots you can find.
You sure you want to do that?
You can't get the most out of racing...
without putting the most in.
I'm sure glad you're my son.
Me too.
Race announcer: Here at
the Columbus half mile,
it's a win for Don Castro,
followed by Butler..
[engines]
Race announcer: It's a great afternoon,
for the win it's Don Castro,
followed by Butler.
[engines]
Race announcer: Giving us all a
pull off win it's Don Castro!
♪[uplifting music]♪
[joyful laugh]
Great Dad.
Leave a note.
Dear son.
This...
motorcycle...
is "rof",
for
This motorcycle is for...
you're...
A...
in...
English.
I'm...
sure...
"droup".. of.. you.
Yeah.
[school bell rings]
Alright people, let's not forget,
we have a test tomorrow.
[groans]
Don, would you
please stay a moment?
Please, sit down.
What word do you see here Don?
Saw.
And what word it this?
Dog.
You're not dumb, Don.
What's wrong with me?
You have dyslexia.
What does that mean?
It means the circuits of your
brain don't always connect.
So, reading is hard for you.
Is there a cure?
No.
Now that you have told me this,
am I supposed to feel better?
Well, is should be nice
to know you're not dumb.
Not dumb...
just defective.
There is one advantage,
if you continue racing.
How did you know I raced?
Women read the sports section too, Don.
At high speeds, race car
drivers who have dyslexia,
claim they see things in slow motion.
How is that good?
Well, you'll have more time to
react than your competitors.
So, you'll be able to go faster.
I've never had that happen.
Have you ever raced on a mile
track like the race cars do?
No.
Are you gonna fail me?
I'm, going to give you a C.
I'm sorry I walked out of your class.
I understand, Don.
Thank you for your help.
Dad.
Yeah.
Can you help me with this carburetor?
I've got some deliveries
to make today, Don.
Oh.
Tell you what...
I'll help you, if you help me.
Okay.
Dad.
How'd you like to be my partner?
What in?
Motorcycle racing.
I was your partner already.
Yeah, but you are putting everything in,
and I'm getting all the benefit.
I wouldn't say that.
All the money you spent.
The time driving me to the races,
being my mechanic.
I'm the one...
who gets to watch his son.
I didn't get that A in English Dad.
And, I want to pay you back for the
motorcycle with my prize money.
- And then split the money I win with you.
- You didn't get the A?
No.
Why did you tell me this now?
I didn't want to live a lie with you.
I'm glad you told me.
Partner.
♪[soft music]♪
That wasn't so bad.
The first load never is.
♪[soft music]♪
This is our fourth load.
Is this it?
Not quite.
♪[soft music]♪
Is it always like this?
No.
Most days I make more loads.
How long are you going to
keep working this hard?
When your grandfather had his stroke,
I told myself, I would help out for
six months, until he could handle it.
And here I am.
That was seven years ago.
Do you like what you're doing?
Like being my own boss.
What are you gonna do
when you stop racing?
I don't know.
You better decide, or the
choice gets made for you.
Well, you're all ready son.
Better get some sleep.
I'm gonna groove the tire
for traction, first.
Okay. Good night.
Good night Dad.
[cheering]
[distant] Race announcer: Castro,
down on the inside route.
They come out of four and
it's, Castro, Mertins..
At turn one, it's Don Castro, Tim Mertins.
Don Castro's won it!
[cheering]
Thank you, for taking the time from
your busy schedule to come and see me.
It is my pleasure, Mr. Iuno.
Our company has benefited from your
past leadership in America, Mr. Igetsu.
You are too kind, Mr. Iuno.
Our motorcycles sell themselves.
Oh no, Mr. Igetsu.
As you can see, our
motorcycles sales move,
with the winning of our
motorcycles in races.
America loves winners, Mr. Igetsu.
Yes, Mr. Iuno.
Our company loves to win.
Who is Don Castro?
He is new to the racing circuit.
An independent?
Yes, Mr. Iuno.
He has won four races in a row,
with a broken ankle.
- Yes, but he has never won--
- Perhaps...
Mr. Castro should join our racing team.
We have four good
riders now, Mr. Iuno.
Good is winning, Mr. Igetsu.
Our company, holds you personally
responsible to keep winning for America.
Yes, Mr. Iuno.
Where are you going?
[whispers] Hi Tina.
I'm going to Sacramento.
Why are you whispering?
[whispers] I don't want
your parents to hear me.
That's not funny.
[whispers] I know Tina. It's sad.
[whispers] When can I see you?
I don't know.
We'll be home around ten.
Come out your window and
meet me in the garage.
I'm tired of sneaking Don.
What else can we do?
I gotta go.
Try to make it tonight.
Okay, I'll try.
I wish I was going with you.
Me too.
♪[contemplative music]♪
Can I borrow the car, Mom?
No, Tina.
I have to have the car.
- Tina, I don--
- Mom.
I need the car.
I really need it.
The keys are in my purse.
Thanks Mom.
I love him, Dad.
You don't know what love is Tina.
Extra, extra, read all about it!
Tina loves Don!
What's wrong with her?
Where's she going?
Race Announcer: And there's the
finish of the last chance qualifier..
[announcer][engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
Transferring to the feature
here, at the Sacramento Mile.
It's been a flurry of activity,
this afternoon, here at the mile.
Tuners, riders, mechanics all
in there working on the bikes.
No one has been able to find just the
right piece of gearing, the right setup,
for this particular track.
Warm afternoon, seems to
be bringing the sand up.
This is definitely not a
race, fit for the dirt track,
as the moisture seems to have gone away.
We've got some top runners here.
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
Looks like now they're going with
everything they can, the gearing.
That's what the backup motorcycle is for.
Changes in setup as they get set and ready
to come out for today's feature event.
It's been an incredible afternoon of
people searching for the right thing.
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
Race announcer: ..unless they
change something drastic.
One rider though, who has
definitely got this dialed in,
Don Castro and his tuner
father, all the way from Hollister.
They've had an incredible year.
This is the first time
Castro has been on the mile.
He has qualified for the pole
position, with the track record
and he's got four major victories in
the last four races of this season.
So, as we go down here for the
season finale in Sacramento,
we are going to be looking
for a lot from this young man.
He really looks like he is a
promising rider on the way up,
and going to give us
a great thrill today.
As Castro and the other riders
get set and ready to come out,
in this afternoon's feature,
the season finale.
It looks like the greaser
got a new motorcycle.
Well...
nothing, beats the tiger in the tank.
[sinister laughter]
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
Race announcer: On the pole, it's the
new rider, number 11, Dan Castro
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
The finale, this evening, is
about ready to get underway.
[engines roar]
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
Don Castro, down on the inside. Right
behind him, number three Scott Chappell.
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
Coming out of four, it's Don Castro
behind him is number three Scott Chappell.
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
on the back straight away, Castro
really opening up that lead.
Castro with a record time already today.
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
It's lap number 18.
As Don Castro looks on the back of the
riders, down to number one and two.
Castro, with a bump. It's Castro
off flying out in the soft stuff.
Get the kitty litter, it's
Castro down on the ground.
Flopping around trying to pick that
bike up, the engine's still running.
Castro, with his hand on the
clutch, as he fights to get back up.
It's Castro, working that
bike back up on the track.
Castro trying to get back
up and get in this one.
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
Don Castro setting up for turn three.
Your leader, Scott Chappell, in the lead
already down the front straight away,
setting up for the first turn.
It's Castro now, making
his way out of turn four.
He's gonna try for the group
and make up some time.
But he's really gonna have to
work to get back in this one.
Don Castro is really
showing us some stuff.
This weekend he's had the top
time and sat on the pole.
Right now his works cut out for him.
It's Don Castro working hard.
Your leader Chappell, and
Taylor and McDonnell.
As Castro begins to track
number 64, Rob Damron.
Castro working hard, as he pulls
himself back in this one.
It's Don Castro now, on the move.
He's lined up with Tim Mertins, on number
53, as they come out of turn four.
Don Castro already on the fly.
He's working back into the pack.
It's Don Castro on the move as they
come up the back straight away.
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
It's Don Castro back into the thick of
things, as they close on the leader.
Don Castro with an incredible move, as he
works this one for everything he's worth.
Don Castro had an incredible season,
and now, it's almost unbelievable,
as he climbs to the lead.
It's still Chappell out in front, but
Mertins and Castro closing rapidly.
Also in there, Rob Damron, number 64.
As they work towards
the end of this event,
the track looks like it's
holding up very well.
Castro continues his record
climb towards the front.
It's unbelievable, I've never
seen anything like this.
Castro's thrilled before, but
never anything like this.
It's Don Castro, down on
the inside, on number 11.
Don Castro in there with the leaders.
Tim Mertins and Rob Damron also up there
in the thick of things.
[announcer] [engines]
♪[upbeat music]♪
It's number 11, Don Castro flies to
the front. He's wide and outside.
Unable to spoil off the speed, as
they come to the front straight away.
Don Castro working his way up there.
Castro's amazing. One more lap to go.
The white flag is out.
It's Don Castro climbing
now, towards the front.
They go to the back straight away and Don
Castro, number 11, he works on inside.
He's moving up now on
number 64, Rob Damron.
Heading up on number 66, George Roeder.
He takes Damron on the back straight
away, now he goes by Roeder.
They're setting up for turn three, only
one thing between him and victory,
it's number 53, Tim Mertins.
Wide on the outside, it's Mertins.
Castro's down on the inside of the grove.
They come off four and
it's Castro back in front.
There's the checkered flag.
It's Don Castro!
[cheering]
Castro's won it! He's got the flag.
Castro goes back to the pits,
calming sitting on the bike, like he's
just come home from the grocery store,
Don Castro has no idea, in his
rookie season, what he's done.
He doesn't even realize he's won this.
[cheering]
Castro's realized it!
Okay, the number one rider is
headed for the winner's circle.
[cheering]
[thud]
Ow!
Who wants some stickers
or the front number?
$300 for the front number!
I'll give you $400
$500
[cheering]
[applause]
Race announcer: Well there a season
finale for ya, this is one for the books.
You, definitely got your money's worth
here, at the Sacramento Mile day.
This is Michael Schnell, for the city
all the people here in charge of the mile,
wishing you a really great winter
and we'll see you all next year!
♪[instrumental music]♪