Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[ROMANTIC INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you think?
I don't know.
BRIDESMAID: Hmm?
What do you think?
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
Who, me?
Oh, I think you look
just perfect.
I can see why my little boy
is head over heels for you.
Yeah.
Perfect.
That's the problem.
Isn't perfect a good thing?
It just doesn't look like me.
I'm just saying,
when someone gets murdered,
they investigate
the spouse first.
That tells you everything
you need to know about marriage.
GROOMSMAN: Come on, guys. Marriage brings
a lot of great things into your life.
Like, uh, come on, guys.
Help me.
- Feminine hygiene products.
- Empty wallets.
GABE: They take over
the bathroom.
And they withhold sex until you're
in, like, actual physical pain.
I mean, so I've heard.
[ALL LAUGHING]
You guys done?
Are we all done being jealous?
- GROOMSMAN: Are you guys done being jealous?
- Yup.
DON: I was wondering where everyone
was hanging out for a smoke.
Yep, I think we're all done.
Sorry, sir,
you can't smoke up here.
Want one?
No, no, you really can't
smoke in here, though.
It's ah, policy.
Can't smoke anywhere these days.
And you guys think everyone of my
generation who smokes is an idiot.
- I never said that.
- Yeah, but you're thinking it.
Hey, I get it.
Smoke is not your vice.
I'm sure you have other vices.
Come on, out with it.
Chewing tobacco. [CHUCKLES]
No, you are not the type.
A little too much alcohol.
Probably drank your way through
college with your buddies, right?
Or is it pot?
You like that wacky weed, Noah?
Yeah. Pot's not that bad,
I guess.
I tried it once.
God, that was a long time ago.
[CHUCKLES] You know that
whole munchies thing, it's true.
You smoked pot.
DON: I'm not the total square
you think I am.
You did just use
the word square, though.
DON: But, you know,
people grow up, Noah.
And when they grow up, they usually
learn that grownups aren't all idiots.
My point is...
The foundation of a marriage is
how are you going to support each other,
raise a family, that sort of thing.
And you, you do not have a plan.
Sir, I'm going to grad school
in the fall.
Grad school.
To be a filmmaker.
That's not a plan, son,
that's a fantasy.
DON: How many filmmakers
are there in the world?
Quite a few.
DON: And how many can buy
a home and raise a family?
How many put that family first?
Sir, this might sound,
I don't know,
pretentious, but...
I want to change the world.
Or whatever part of it
I can impact.
And I feel like I can do that
through film.
Look son,
I don't have a problem with you wanting
to make movies. I mean, whatever.
I guess someone has to do that.
But it doesn't have to be
the guy married to my daughter.
Now...
I need to lay down
some hard truth on you
that you may not be ready to
hear, but it's truth nonetheless.
And I'm a dad,
so I have to say it.
Noah, you know me.
And you know how much I care
about my daughter.
You know,
I want the best for her
and I believe that you want the
best for her, too. I really do.
So that's why we've got to talk
about how difficult it is
for someone like her to be married
to someone of another color.
You know, I'm not a racist,
that's not my issue.
These are difficult times
we live in
and I just worry about
what her life will be like
and the lives of kids
you might have together.
What's it like for mixed race
children out there these days?
DON: You don't want her children to start
out life with a disadvantage, do you?
I know you love her
and you want
what's best for her.
I want what's best for her too.
I'm willing to throw away all the
money I've spent on this wedding
because I want
what's best for her.
So I want you to think about,
really think about
what's best from Madison.
If you really love her,
you'll do the right thing.
Okay?
Yeah.
DON: Okay.
Good talk.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Who is it?
NOAH: It's me.
What do you want?
NOAH: I don't know.
Turn around.
- NOAH: What?
- Turn around.
NOAH: Why?
Because I don't want to talk
to you through a closed window,
but I also don't want you
to see me before the ceremony.
NOAH: Really?
MADISON: Yes, really.
NOAH: All right,
I'm turned around.
MADISON: You okay?
Are you sure you want
to marry me?
What? Of course, I am.
Are you sure
you want to marry me?
NOAH: I want you to be happy.
That's why
we're getting married.
You're not worried
about our life together?
I'm anxious about
starting our life together.
What you talking about?
Is being married to a Black man
gonna be too difficult for us?
Noah,
we talked about this.
Where is this coming from?
Did my dad talk to you?
I'm gonna kill him.
Better yet, I'm gonna get Mom
to kill him. [CHUCKLES]
I thought he was over this.
My dad's views are my problem.
They're sort of my problem now.
I didn't want them
to be your problem.
NOAH: Can't pretend like
there's not gonna be an issue.
I'm gonna see him
at thanksgiving,
family gatherings
all the time.
Not all the time.
Probably, hardly ever see
our parents.
Do you really think
he's a racist?
Don't you?
He raised me and I'm not racist.
Noah,
he's my dad.
I love him.
I don't like what he believes,
but I can't just
stop loving him.
I'm not asking you to.
But what if he's right?
MADISON: He's not right.
He's right that it won't be
easy for us.
So, Black and white people
can never be together?
- That's not what I'm saying.
- Then what are you saying?
I don't know. I'm...
I'm just trying to figure out
how all this is gonna work.
Aren't you?
Yeah, sometimes.
Can you imagine our families
at thanksgiving dinner together?
It'll be like the meeting of the
five families in The Godfather.
I can't really imagine that because
I have never seen The Godfather.
Madison.
I don't like old movies.
You know, I was worried about
the whole Black man
married to
a white woman thing, but
now I'm worried about being married
to a woman that knows nothing about
one of the classics
in modern cinema.
Take my hand, Noah.
I'm not giving up just because
this is going to be hard.
Of course it's gonna be hard.
MADISON: I didn't expect it
to happen right now, but fine.
We'll face it together.
Because there's no one else
I want to face it with
and because I can't face it
without you.
MADISON: We're not doing
this for them.
We're doing it for us.
So, you know, let's...
Let's do it right here.
Do what right here?
Get married.
In a bathroom?
Well, me in the bathroom,
you out there.
Why don't I just come in there?
Or you come out here.
Because we're still going to do
the whole ceremony after this,
but right here,
right now is for us.
You sure about this?
Do you Noah, take me, Madison,
to be your lawfully wedded wife,
to have and to hold,
to love and to cherish to...
hold my head when I vomit,
like, when we had those tacos
from taco truck
and then you made me ride
that rollercoaster
that you said wouldn't be
too intense,
to not care when
I want to sleep in all day
even if we had plans,
to pick up after me
because I hate folding clothes
and putting them away,
to be okay with me
occasionally making us late
because I'm ready to leave,
when I'm ready to leave.
To remember what you love
most about me,
right in the middle of a fight
and to support me as
I pursue my dream
of becoming
a professional ballerina.
I do.
And do you, Madison, take me,
Noah, with all of my baggage,
even though I'm a mama's boy
who thinks he's always right,
promise not to get upset with me
when I pee with the seat down,
because I promise that I will
clean it up if I miss.
To...
let me keep the thermostat
at 70 degrees,
even if that means
you need to get under a blanket,
and to give me space
when I'm in a crappy mood
for no reason at all,
and to never withhold sex
as a weapon,
which I'm not saying
you would do
something like that.
I just, you know,
I heard that could happen.
Uh...
And to support me in my dreams
of becoming a great filmmaker
who changes the world.
I do.
I always did.
NOAH: I hope you washed
this hand.
[MADISON GIGGLES]
NOAH: Okay, so remember, you guys
come from two very different worlds.
All right, so what we want to do
is they really want to hit that
and kind of feel that difficulty
and that separation between the two.
JASON: I think we get it.
You want us to talk at each other
- but not with each other.
- Yes, exactly.
That's exactly we want. So, at this
point, we're trying to figure out
if these people can get past
what they're supposed
to think about each other
and really hear one another.
You know? Really, really listen.
You know, so what,
there has to be conflict.
You know,
they're really passionate
about what they believe.
Great. Let's run
the scene again.
Yes. Great idea.
- We can do that. Absolutely.
- SARAH: Noah?
NOAH: One second.
What's up?
I was just about
to come find you.
We're actually going to run
the scene one more time,
- I think we're ready to shoot so if you want to get everybody...
- No we won't.
- What do you mean?
- Audio.
- What about audio?
- They got a paying gig
and they said, that you said, that you
wouldn't hold them back if one came.
I didn't say they could just take
off without giving us any notice.
Okay. Call them, tell them
we will fire them.
We've had this scheduled
for weeks.
I tried that, they don't care.
You're paying them in meals
and credit
and this other gig's
paying them in actual cash.
[SIGHS]
All right, uh, B roll,
we got B roll to shoot here, right?
I'll get started on that while you
track down some more audio people.
- I know it's last minute...
- That leads us to our second problem.
The bar owner has
changed his mind.
Why?
Maybe he finally read the script
and didn't appreciate his place
being described as
and I quote, "A dive where people go to
get drunk and avoid making eye contact."
That was in draft three.
We clearly updated the script
to make it a nicer place.
Maybe you should have sent
the more recent version.
Tell him that we will make sure
that the bar's name
isn't mentioned.
I suggested that,
it didn't change his mind.
He can't do this.
We have a signed agreement,
right?
We do, but he's still
kicking us out.
Isn't the signed agreement, isn't
that, like a contract or something?
- Yeah, it is.
- So enforce the contract.
But unless you want to take him
to court right now,
you cannot force him to do
anything he does not want to do.
And you can't actually
take him to court right now,
I wasn't being serious
about that.
That's not helping.
Just trying
to keep things light,
but we do have to leave now.
Well, what are we gonna do?
Loose a day of shooting,
at least a day, maybe more.
At least until we find
a new bar.
I'll get everyone to start
striking everything in here.
You okay?
SARAH: Noah?
Yeah. Okay.
Okay.
SARAH: Okay, everyone.
We'll strike this location immediately...
Hi. I was planning on coming in
for today's audition,
but I couldn't get anyone
to cover my class,
so I was hoping there might be
some other times available?
Yes, I understand.
Um, are there maybe
any other auditions coming up?
Right.
Okay. Thank you.
Okay, everyone. Here we go.
Changement, changement,
chaine, pique,
sous sous, plie.
Okay, ready?
Come on, girls. Everyone on your feet.
Let's start learning this.
- Come on.
- Miss Maddie,
I need to go to the bathroom.
Okay, Laney. Come on.
Starting in fifth position,
girls.
What are you doing here?
Location.
Location bailed on us and we lost
an entire day in the schedule
and I don't know
what we're gonna do.
I am so sorry. That's terrible.
I'll have to talk to
you about it later.
Wait, Maddie,
I need you right now.
I'm working.
I have to get back to my class.
And I need to figure this out.
My entire film is collapsing.
Not right now.
[BOTTLE OPENING]
NOAH: Yeah.
Hey, Mom, I gotta call you back.
Yeah, I love you too.
So, does your mom know
every word
spoken between us
or just the highlights?
She called me.
Really?
For what?
Hmm.
She's calling to see if you got
that birthday money she sent
because she never heard
from you.
MADISON: Mm-hmm.
Welcome home.
NOAH: I'll just pick this up
for you.
Put it on the bed with the
rest of the stuff on the floor.
How was your day?
Fine.
Would you like to know
how my day was?
Pretty sure I know
how your day was.
Oh, you were listening.
Well, it was kind of hard not to
when you showed up where I work.
I do have a job, you know?
I thought you might be
between classes.
But I wasn't.
You couldn't stop
and talk to me for five minutes.
We never have anything to eat
in this apartment.
Is that directed at me?
How would that
be directed at you?
Because I'm not working
while finishing this film.
[MADISON SIGHS]
NOAH: Just order a pizza.
- We can't afford to order pizza.
- NOAH: Because I'm not working
- while finishing this film.
- Because we just can't, that's all.
What do you want from me?
I'm trying to finish this film,
it could be my break
and everything is falling apart.
What do I want from you? I want you
to have some respect for my job.
But how would you like it if I...
You don't even like your damn job.
You complain about it all the time.
Okay, first off, please don't
talk to me like that.
And yeah, I don't even like
my job because
it wasn't supposed to be
my job forever.
What happened to our deal?
You get to do what you love,
every day.
What are you talking about?
You get to be around dance,
every day.
That... that's not
the same thing.
And whether I like my job or not
is not the point.
When you bust in
and act like I should stop
everything I'm doing.
I mean, how dare you?
Madison, you're my wife.
- I can't stop by work and see you?
- Give me a break.
Stop by work and...
You demanded my attention
and completely embarrassed me.
I would never do that to you.
I can't lose any of
these classes.
Our budget is tight enough
as it is.
How much are you getting
per class again?
All I'm saying is that maybe
you should ask for a raise.
I am the newest person there,
not including the interns.
I cannot ask for
a raise already.
But you could get
a part time job.
Not this again.
I am not making enough
to pay the bills.
We're going more
and more into debt.
And I had to miss another
audition today
because I'm the only one
bringing in any money.
NOAH: We talked about this.
I have to finish this film.
I cannot change the schedule
right now and go and get some job.
But you can work somewhere
that pays you better.
Noah...
Honey...
I am thrilled that
you're pursuing your passion.
You know, it's one of
the reasons we're together.
I love that you're trying to do
important things with art.
But I am just
as important as that.
We are just
And Noah,
don't drink anymore tonight.
Okay?
Yeah, okay.
[DOOR CREAKING]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DREAMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
MADISON: I thought
you'd be asleep by now.
Wanted to get some work done.
Ended up writing.
Changes on the film?
Langston Hughes Bio.
When you finish that,
it's gonna be awesome.
I have to face the facts
that there's not a huge audience
for a movie about jazz poetry.
Aren't you curious where I was?
I know where you were.
How?
It's where you always go.
MADISON: Hmm.
And I tracked your phone.
- Ah.
- [CHUCKLES]
I just want to make sure
you were safe.
I know.
I'm sorry about all this.
It's just...
[EXHALES]
Feel like things
are slipping away, you know.
I want to finish this film,
but all I can think about is...
the film I actually wanna do,
the thing this film
is supposed to get me to and...
It feels like
it's all falling apart.
Maybe you should just...
do one thing at a time,
you know.
Do your best on this,
and then...
then you can move on
to the next step.
Yeah.
Hey, how was your audition?
I missed it, remember?
Couldn't get someone
to cover my class.
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry.
What are we gonna do?
About what?
Bills, jobs,
future,
everything.
[CHUCKLES]
That's a lot of problems
for me to solve
at midnight after four beers.
For us to solve.
But...
do you mind if we solve them
after I go to the bathroom?
[CHUCKLES] Four beers.
You okay?
Yeah.
Are we okay?
We will be.
Okay.
Don't forget to lift the seat.
Just clean it up,
for once.
Clean it up.
[SIGHS WEARILY]
[MACHINE STEADILY BEEPING]
DOCTOR: Madison.
The anesthesia will kick in soon
and then we'll need
to wait a bit
until your cervix
is fully dilated, okay?
[MACHINE BEEPING]
[EXHALES LOUDLY]
DOCTOR: Madison,
are you still with us?
Get Claire. Let's get started.
NOAH: Hey honey, I'm here.
Hey.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
Are you okay?
No, no.
No.
[MADISON SOBBING]
[SOBBING]
NOAH: Hey.
I was gonna clean up a bit.
Didn't know where you wanted
to put all of this stuff.
Do you know where
you want me to put all this?
I'm uh...
I'm gonna head out
for a bit, so.
Head out, where?
Just scout some locations
for the work thing.
Today?
NOAH: Yeah.
Do you have to?
We talked about this.
I got some appointments
at some places
and I can't really
cancel on them again.
You know,
it'll just be a few months
till we can start trying again.
Maybe.
Don't you want to?
Yeah.
Maybe not right away.
Are you gonna go
to your audition today?
I don't know.
Noah,
I'm gonna take a break
from auditions for a while.
NOAH: A break?
For how long?
I don't know.
Do you think we were gonna have
a girl or a boy?
NOAH: Too early to tell,
wasn't it?
What do you think?
I don't know.
I think
we were gonna have a girl.
NOAH: Okay.
Do you like the name,
Molly?
Yeah.
Yeah. Molly is a nice name,
I guess.
I wanted to name
our girl, Molly.
Okay.
So you like that name?
Yeah.
'Cause she's not just mine,
she's ours.
I need to know
that you like that name.
I do.
Noah, I'm, uh,
I'm gonna need to focus
on Molly for a while
before I can think
about trying again.
Okay?
Okay.
All right, well...
I'm gonna head out, but...
I'll make it
as quick as possible.
I promise.
[SOBS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- No.
- [MADISON GASPS]
NOAH: Uh-huh.
That is you.
Maddie.
Oh, isn't that
just perfect for you?
How much is it?
Oh, come on. We can afford it.
Mr. full-time videographer.
Oh, it's my favorite term.
Okay. I know you hate it, but...
Marketing is still
telling stories.
Just itty-bitty short ones.
At least it means I can keep you
in fancy T shirts.
Oh, my prince.
I don't know.
I mean, these I can afford,
but I'll buy you just one more.
[EXHALES]
WOMAN: Are you okay?
I'm fine. [SNIFFLES]
WOMAN: Are you sure?
Uh, yeah, yes.
WOMAN: Is there anything
I can do?
No, thank you.
Hey, you okay?
- I'm fine. Let's just go.
- Wait.
- What happened?
- Nothing.
I-I just want to go home.
Maddie, what's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Why does this stuff
never bother you?
Why does what never bother me?
- The baby.
- Oh.
It's like you don't care at all.
Of course, I care.
All right? It's just different
than you do.
Just not as much as I do.
That's not fair.
This is different for men
and for women.
Okay. You had it inside of you.
Her.
You had her inside of you.
For me,
she wasn't even real yet.
Where'd you read that, WebMD?
I'm just trying to understand.
I'm trying to understand
why you haven't touched me
in four months.
I was waiting for you
to tell me when you were ready.
Maybe I need you
to reach out to me.
I can't read your mind, Madison.
I don't know what you want
or what you...
Maddie.
Maddie, talk to me.
MADISON: Unlock the car, please.
[CAR BEEPS]
Do you think
I don't wanna be with you or...
Turn the AC on, it's hot.
Do you?
Of course, I do.
Why wouldn't I?
I don't know. I mean,
people change
after stuff like this.
Guys change.
You look at me
like I'm some fragile flower.
It's only because
I want to take care of you.
I don't know how.
You have to stop
thinking of me like that.
We have to go back
to the way things
were before, before...
Molly.
I'm just Maddie
and you're just Noah and...
I don't know.
You know, maybe that's...
all we'll ever be.
I don't know
what's gonna happen.
I don't know when
or if I'll get
through this and...
I need you to be okay with that.
Okay.
I need you to be okay with me
being in a bad place
emotionally.
You can't always fix my moods.
Okay.
And I need you to...
want to make love to me.
Even if I'm not over this yet.
I do.
I might not want to sometimes.
I might say, "No,
not now. I can't."
Yeah.
I can do that.
You can?
Are you sure?
Uh, I can try.
Don't try.
Just be sure.
I need you to be sure.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Then take me home
'cause I need you
to make love to me right now.
Don't you want to?
Yeah, yeah. [CHUCKLES]
Then let's go.
Let's go.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
And then you ran into the room
with a balloon on your face.
I said, "Give me all the money
or the balloon gets it."
I can't believe
you didn't get arrested.
- I actually did.
- What?
Yeah, I did.
I just never told anybody.
Why not? I would
have bailed you out.
It just made it really clear
that a Black male, 20 something,
should never,
never pretend to rob anyone.
Well, I need another drink.
- Grab you another?
- Uh, I'm good, man.
Nonsense. After that story,
we need to get drunk.
[LAUGHS]
- Oh, my God.
- What?
Carol Stone.
Well, I was kind of hoping
she wouldn't make it.
You didn't want to see your ex?
It's not a big deal.
GABE: Wow. She has aged
quite gracefully indeed.
NOAH: Yeah, she looks good.
This isn't gonna be
a problem, is it?
Man, I'm a, I'm a married man
now, all right?
She is ancient history.
Really. You, my friend,
are as magnanimous as ever.
- Magnanimous.
- Monogamous.
Whatever. See?
College education worked.
Yeah.
Shit. I lost her.
- CAROL: Hi, guys.
- Whoa! Hey.
[LAUGHS] Hi.
Nice to see you too, Gabe.
Carol Stone,
as I live and breathe.
- Hi. Um...
- Hi, Gabe.
Noah.
How've you been?
Great, great.
I'm good too.
I'm going to go
get us some drinks.
Hey.
- Won't you let me do that?
- No, no.
No, you're great. I'm...
Be right back.
LUKE: Is that Maddog Madison?
Luke.
Hi.
- Everything okay?
- I, uh, yes.
Wow, this is embarrassing.
What?
Oh, no, I-I'm sorry.
I knew you'd probably be here.
I just didn't know how I'd feel
when we saw each other.
How do you feel?
Do I have to answer that?
Hey, uh, at least
join me for a drink.
Then you can decide
how you feel.
[CLEARS THROAT]
So, I see you're still married.
NOAH: Yeah. Still married.
Any kids?
No.
I can't believe you got to meet
with the Prime Minister.
That is so cool.
It wasn't that big a deal.
It's not like I had an audience
with the Queen.
True.
Why am I even talking to you?
[CHUCKLES]
You know, I'm glad
we're both here tonight.
Why is that?
Because it gives me the chance
to say something to you
that I have wanted to say
for a long time.
I'm sorry.
For what?
I was a terrible boyfriend.
Oh, Luke.
Whatever. It's in the past.
No, no.
I look back on the way
I behaved in college
and not just to you.
God, I just cringe.
So I'm hoping that
you will accept my apology.
Yeah, of course.
Maddie,
I mean it.
I just wish
you had said that years ago.
You do?
No, I mean, not that I didn't...
Uh, that came out not what I...
how I meant it. Sorry.
CAROL: I just always thought
you and I might end up together.
I thought we had more in common.
- Like what?
- [LAUGHS]
I don't know.
- Life experience.
- [CHUCKLES]
Anyway, I interrupted you.
Not much since then.
I've been working
at the university for a while,
marketing department,
making videos.
Not exactly the type of work
I set out to do.
Still trying to get
funds together, to...
start this film
that I've been working on.
Oh, what's it about?
Used to be about
Langston Hughes,
- Mm.
- but it sort of evolved.
And now I found myself
more interested
in writing about
the types of people
and situations
that he wrote about.
Anyway, somewhere in there,
ten years passed and...
Ten years.
Madison and I, we've...
we've been through
some stuff together.
Hasn't always been easy,
but we're still standing.
You?
Honestly, I should have known
better from the beginning.
What do you mean?
I mean, we met
in a dive bar downtown.
It's not how great romances
begin, you know.
I don't know, stranger things
have happened.
Yeah, but not likely.
For example, you guys have been
together for ten years.
I bet you have a great story
about how you met, right?
Don't know if it's
a great story...
I mean, it's a story.
Tell me. Come on.
So, uh, you guys are doing good?
Yeah, yeah, we're, we're good.
Do I detect a little doubt?
We had a little fight
on the way over here.
We were running late
because I wasn't finished
getting ready.
Being late drives him crazy.
Seems like a pretty minor thing.
Certainly does to me.
So you met him
after you broke up with me
because I was such an asshole.
Noah was one of my best friends
the whole time we were dating.
You met him
before we were dating
or during?
I would have to tell you
the whole story
and I know
you don't want to hear that.
No, no, I'm curious.
Annie, my younger sister
told me that she knew this guy
that was a freshman, uh,
that I should meet him,
that he was funny and nice.
I was a lonely freshman
so I was all about
making new friends.
But we'd just never seemed
to cross paths.
Until one day, I had to go
to the Dean's office
'cause I missed
too many arts events.
You remember that requirement
where we had to see
so many plays
or musical events or whatever.
A requirement I was not paying
attention to, whatsoever.
And...
- There she was.
- There he was.
I figured out who he was
because Annie
had described him to me.
I wasn't expecting her
to be so, so pretty
or so down to earth.
CAROL: So you fell for her
right then and there?
[CHUCKLES] No, not at all.
We just kind of clicked
and became really good friends.
I loved spending time with him.
We had a blast,
we did everything together.
He was so passionate.
He, he believed art
could change the world.
When she danced...
it inspired me.
But I didn't see him
as boyfriend material at all.
LUKE: Why not?
I don't know. You know how it is
when you're attracted
to someone.
With Noah, he was my friend.
And whatever that thing was
that had to click for me
to be attracted to him
just hadn't clicked.
Every time I thought about doing
something, I would call her.
We really were best friends,
but...
something started to change.
It became clear to me that he
wanted more than a friendship.
She was just not interested.
And I did a lot of cheesy stuff
to try to convince her.
He left notes in my car,
for example.
This one time,
I borrowed her car
and I left the CD player queued,
so that when she turned
the car on,
that particular song would play.
And I'm listening
to this song play...
[CHUCKLING] I mean, there's this entire
song about not being able to let go.
And I'm thinking,
"This is going to be a problem."
I mean, I told myself,
"I'll get over it."
"She's my best friend
and I'll get over it."
But he couldn't.
I felt like I was hurting him
being around him.
And just like that,
we stopped hanging out altogether.
I cut it off.
A year and a half goes by
and I finally got over her.
And I started seeing you,
focused more on school
and I just moved on.
And, one night, I'm having some
friends over to watch a movie
and he was with them.
By this point, we hadn't
spoken in probably over a year.
So, yeah, kinda awkward,
you know, but... [LAUGHS]
We talked the entire night.
I don't remember
what we talked about.
Just caught up on
what we missed, I guess.
I remember new feelings
swirling around.
I didn't know
what I was feeling, really.
But, now I'm just
thinking to myself,
"Do not get feelings
for her, again. Just don't."
[CHUCKLES] But I could tell
it was happening.
And I wake up
later in the day
and I'm going over this in my mind.
I'm thinking, I'm like,
"I'm pretty sure she was
giving me some signals."
But after everything that has
happened, I do not trust myself.
The phone rings and it's him.
And he asked me if I want
to get a bite to eat sometime.
Dinner and a movie, maybe.
I said, "Yeah, sure."
And he says,
"Just to be clear..."
"I'm kind of thinking
of this as, an actual date."
Me too.
We went out that weekend and...
And I fell in love with him
within a few weeks.
We got engaged
a couple of months later.
And we've been
together ever since.
Through good times and bad.
CAROL: See, I told you.
What?
Great couples
have great stories.
Through good times and bad?
Well, every marriage
has its ups and downs.
It is nice seeing you, Luke.
I'm gonna
find my husband now.
So, can I get one dance
before the night is over?
It was really
nice to see you, Carol.
I got to go find my wife.
Take care.
- MADISON: Hey, you.
- NOAH: Hey.
Wanna dance?
- Thought you'd never ask.
- [MADISON CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Is that your ex?
- Yeah. It is.
- Hmm.
And where have you been?
My ex is here too, actually.
- Hmm.
- Yeah.
You know,
[WHISPERING] I think
she wanted me to ditch you.
Oh!
What did you say?
I told her
I was a married man.
So what the short is ultimately
about is these three generations.
Grandfather, father and son,
passing on the tailgate tradition
from generation
to generation,
through winning
and losing seasons.
It's about being a fan,
and it's about bonding
with family through sports.
How will this help me
sell hamburger buns?
- Well, I'm not trying to sell...
- [DAVID CLEARS THROAT]
I'm not just trying
to sell hamburger buns.
I'm trying to tell the story
of your brand
to connect your brand to the way
people think about family and sports.
When they associate
those two things,
they will see your brand
as an integral part
of the tailgate tradition,
and that will
sell hamburger buns.
I don't get it.
WOMAN: Could they bond over a
shared love of hamburger buns?
Well, of course, we'll end on the
classic, 'Bite and Smile'.
With a big close-up
on the bun,
around the juicy burger.
Why didn't you just say so?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hey, David,
I know I'm new here
and everything,
- but, what the hell was that?
- DAVID: Mm?
I thought you and I, we were on the
same page with this entire pitch.
Calm down. Look, they were not
tracking with that idea at all.
Just trying to keep it
from going further south.
But the cheesy,
'Bite and Smile.' Really?
That is literally every
commercial they've ever done.
I'm trying to give 'em
something new. Okay.
People would have
remembered that spot.
They would have cried remembering
tailgates they had with their grandfathers.
Okay, well, I just don't think they're
ready for this kind of campaign.
Some brands are just
more conservative.
Well, maybe they'd
have gone for it,
if you would have
backed it up a little.
It's one 'Bite and Smile.'
If they let you do
the whole thing,
you just add that at the end.
- What's the big deal?
- Then it's not a story.
It's just another
hamburger bun commercial.
They're paying us for another
- INSTRUCTOR: Forehead five, six, seven, eight.
- [CELL VIBRATING]
And one, two, three, four,
plie, six, seven, eight.
[INSTRUCTOR CONTINUES]
- [PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
- [INSTRUCTOR] Slide, and...
Rond de jambe, Rond de jambe,
classic, arabesque.
INSTRUCTOR: Nice.
It's looking really good, ladies.
Um, some of us need a little
more practice than others,
but just make sure we're
working on it over the weekend.
Yeah?
[INAUDIBLE CONVERSATION]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- [ZIPPER OPENS]
Ava not doing well?
Oh, yeah. She's not picking it
up as fast as the other girls,
but she'll be fine.
She just needs
a little confidence.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I'm not worried.
You know, every girl
who starts teaching here,
wants to be
or wanted to be a dancer.
I saw that in you too.
You know, the kids
were just a distraction.
You have a look of someone
who had settled for this job.
Oh, I'm sorry...
It's okay.
It's okay. Everyone here
has settled to some extent.
But, [SIGHS]
I've been watching you this
year really take to the girls.
Really encourage them,
mentor them,
and teach them about
this beautiful art form.
You've helped them build their
self esteem until it spills out
- into every other aspect of their lives.
- [MADISON SIGHS SOFTLY]
When I see you
with girls like Ava,
I can see that you understand,
that dance is not just about
being a good dancer.
It's about expressing yourself,
regardless of who's watching.
I... I don't know
how else to say this?
Um...
I'm announcing my retirement
at our last
recital performance this year.
What?
And because I've seen
all of this and you,
I want you to take over
the studio.
I want to sell it to you.
Wh...
- [EXCLAIMS IN DISBELIEF]
- Well, you're the only person that I trust
to do the things that
I've always done here.
And I won't charge you much.
You can make payments
with the monthly profits.
[LAUGHING] I don't care
about the money.
What I mostly care about
is you running it.
Um...
- Noah just took that job in Texas.
- I know.
And I also know that you're not
so sure about this whole move.
Dear, you have to decide
what is right for you.
If this school
is right for you.
- Okay?
- [SOFTLY] Okay.
[DOOR OPENS]
[CLASSIC ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[CELL VIBRATING]
Hey, man.
How did the pitch go?
- Double vodka.
- That good, huh?
Yet another great idea that
will never see the light of day.
Well, speaking of...
What?
There's been some interest.
In what?
In what? Come on!
The Langston Hughes script.
What kind of interest?
Well, don't get your hopes up
too high,
but a producer with
a first-look deal,
with a very small
production company.
But he's interested
and wants to read it.
He hasn't even read it?
Man, this is good.
It's a start.
Yeah, you're right.
Uh, hey, here's to getting
our hopes up.
Hold on.
Just you wait.
Where were we?
- Here's to getting our hopes up.
- But not too high.
Here's to getting our hopes up
to just the right height.
So, Noah.
You wanna talk about
why you're here?
I don't know.
My wife wants me here.
I feel like things are fine.
I have a decent job,
even if it's not what I want to be doing.
I might, one day, maybe,
get to make this film that I've
been working on for a long time.
I don't know.
She hasn't even moved here yet.
So, maybe we should ask her?
Oh. [SIGHS]
Why do you think
she wants you here?
She says she wants me to
understand the source of my anger.
Because she says
that I get angry
and then I take it out on her.
What do you mean
when you say, "I get angry?"
I don't know.
I get angry about...
Little stuff.
DR. LEVY: Like what?
Like work.
How my ideas are constantly
looked over and...
Oh, it's just a job.
It's not my passion,
so I guess it doesn't matter.
What else?
- Is work all that bothers you?
- No.
Other things
bother me too, like,
the way people drive, how Madison
never picks up around the house.
Yeah. Yes, I know how petty
and stupid that sounds.
Why do you think these things
make you angry?
Is this ever successful?
When someone goes to therapy
because their spouse
effectively forces them to.
What do you mean,
forces you to?
It feels like
emotional blackmail.
Like, if I don't come here,
she'll leave me.
- She said that you?
- It's just a feeling.
You never
answered my question.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Which question?
Does this ever work?
It can.
If you're willing to go beyond
whatever reasons
that brought you here
and see if there's work
we can do together.
For example, what I'm hearing
you say is that
some of the things
you're angry about
are likely representing
your frustration
at not being in control
of some areas of your life.
In areas like your marriage,
your job.
Does that ring true?
Maybe.
Then why don't we try
to unpack it a little,
see if I can help?
Hmm?
What do you say?
Yeah, okay.
[CELL VIBRATING]
- Hello.
- MADISON: Hey.
Hey.
You'll never guess
where I am right now.
- I need to talk to you.
- Okay.
- I'm not coming.
- You're not coming where?
There to Texas.
I'm not moving.
Why?
Gloria is retiring and she's
selling me the studio.
I'm gonna stay here
and run the studio full time.
You're leaving me.
This can't come
as a complete surprise, right?
You're leaving me
to run a dance studio.
I'm not leaving you
I'm leaving you because
you're an unhappy person
and you're making me
an unhappy person.
It's not like we haven't had
this conversation
a hundred times
and it's always the same.
And now I have to pick up
and change my life
because you took a job
that you don't even want?
I need to work, okay.
We need to pay bills.
So, yes,
I took a job in marketing.
A job I don't exactly want.
A job you encouraged me to take,
might I remind you.
I encouraged you
to take it because
I thought it would
make you happy.
You know, it's, it is...
It's better than sitting around
and complaining all the time
about not being able to
do what I want to do.
I do not complain about that.
I was talking about me.
No, you're not the person
I married.
Nobody gets this far in life
without changing.
Okay?
You've changed too.
Look, let's not do this
right now.
We're just gonna fight.
It's not gonna help anything.
You won't work on this.
That's not true.
Okay? I literally just came out
of a therapist's office.
It's just too late.
Let's talk later
about the details.
The details?
The apartment and stuff.
I might sign a new lease,
but I don't know
if I can afford it by myself.
If I move, I'll let you know.
Is there anything
that you left behind?
Anything I need to send?
Yeah, I'm sure there's...
I don't know.
If I find anything,
I'll send it over, okay?
Noah?
- Okay?
- Madison, please, okay?
Let's just talk about this, all right?
I'll drive out tonight.
- Then we can work on...
- Don't drive down. Please no, don't.
Let's just do it this way,
please.
It hurts now, Noah.
It'll hurt for a while.
And then one day,
you'll realize,
it's been a few days
since you thought about me.
And then you'll go
few more days.
And the days in between will
keep getting longer and longer.
And how do you know that?
I've been getting past you
like that for a while now.
It wasn't easy,
but it happened.
I didn't realize
it was over until
Gloria asked me
to take over the studio.
When she did,
my only hesitation was
whether or not
I could afford it.
And I knew
that meant something.
I'm gonna go now.
Look, don't drive
until you're ready
to concentrate
on the road, okay?
[EXHALES]
[SOBBING]
Uh, I can, of course, provide
most of these services for you.
I'll just need whatever
information you want to provide.
This is the full range
of casket options.
You'll see both wood
and metal options on there,
along with a variety
of interior fabrics.
From a simple crepe to a
more luxurious velvet lining.
What's the difference
between wood and metal?
The metal caskets are
more protective.
Meaning, they're designed to withstand
the entrance of outside elements.
- Outside elements?
- Like tree roots or burrowing animals.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean that anything...
It's okay. We know you didn't
mean anything by it.
Why don't you take Mom home
and I'll finish with
the arrangements here?
Are you sure?
I'm the oldest. It's my job.
It's not just your job.
It can handle it.
Okay. Come on, Mom.
Let's go home.
We can let Madison finish the
arrangements and we'll go home and rest.
I don't want any
tree roots getting in, okay?
Okay, Mom.
- [FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
- [FUNERAL HOME DIRECTOR] I'm truly sorry.
It's fine. Uh, what else
do we have to cover?
There are a number of
arrangements I can handle for you.
Uh, the obituary.
You can either write it yourself
or I have a template here that you
can fill in with relevant details.
Does your family have a preferred
church or a member of the clergy?
No.
We can arrange that, too
if you'd like.
So that's a yes to arranging
the clergy for the service?
- Uh, yes.
- Uh, do you already have a family plot in a cemetery?
- Uh, no.
- We can help arrange that as well.
Lakeview and Trinity Memorial
are both wonderful locations
and very easy to work with.
You may want to consider
thinking ahead now
for your mother's sake,
about whether she would
eventually like to be interred
beside your father
and you,
and your sister as well.
The only reason I mention it
is that you would want to be sure
to plan a plot near your father.
[FUNERAL DIRECTOR
CONTINUES TALKING INAUDIBLY]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC BUILDS]
Hey.
- Thought you might need these.
- [MADISON SOBBING]
[GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING]
You have another
candy bar?
How many have you had?
Shut up.
- The coconut enhances the flavor of the beer.
- Hmm.
Thanks for coming.
[EXHALES SHARPLY] Of course.
I know you and dad
weren't the best of friends.
Madison, I'm here for you.
Why?
Because I knew no one else
would be. [SIGHS]
My mom and sister
are here for me.
Yeah, but eventually
you'd be the one to take over.
That's always been your place
in your family.
You're the one that makes sure
things get done.
[SOFTLY] Hmm, thanks.
You're welcome.
How's work?
It's good.
We added two more
studio locations
to handle
all the new students.
Yeah, I heard.
Really? From who?
I looked online.
MADISON: Hmm.
How about you?
Are you still working on your film?
Yeah. I'm trying, um...
Waiting on this producer
to get back to us.
Gabe thinks there's still hope,
but I don't know.
And how's work?
Work is work, you know?
There's potential for me to make
creative director at the agency.
- Wow!
- Yeah.
At least, this is
how I feel today.
- You ask me tomorrow, and I'll be an insecure mess.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- It's pretty common, actually.
- Yeah.
- Well, I'm glad to hear it.
- Hmm.
- Not the insecure mess part, but
- Mm-hmm.
- The rest of it. [CHUCKLES]
- Yeah.
[WHISPERING] Now's the part
where you ask me
if I feel like I settled
by going into marketing.
- Do you feel like...
- Don't actually ask me that. [LAUGHS]
What?
It's rhetorical.
I don't want to answer that.
Had you talked
to your dad lately?
I had called him
on Father's Day.
We didn't talk long 'cause
he wasn't feeling very well.
I don't remember
what we talked about.
All I can remember
are his last words.
Ernie, gotta go.
Mom needs my help
in the kitchen.
Ernie?
Yeah. That's my boy name.
Did I never tell you that?
Your boy name?
Yeah. That's the name they were
gonna call me if I was a boy.
- Ernie?
- Yeah.
[LAUGHS]
What?
Nothing.
Let's just be
glad I'm a girl.
Yeah, I certainly am.
[CHUCKLES]
Do you have
a girl name?
I don't know.
I never asked.
Hmm.
What are you doing?
I'm asking.
Now?
Mm-hmm.
[SIGHS]
Uh-oh, she's responded.
Noelle.
Noah.
Creative.
Consistent.
Whenever he called me Ernie,
it was like...
something we
shared between us,
like something
only for us.
He could be so
loving and kind.
And he'd turn around
and treat you like you're dead
or yell at Mom for a mess
he had to clean up.
And we...
we raise our parents
up in our minds
to be these... these icons.
It's never that simple.
They're human beings
just like us,
and we have to love them
in spite of their flaws.
It's kind of what they do with
us, when you think about it.
Coming from the guy
whose dad wasn't sort of racist.
That's true.
That is true.
I do have perfect parents.
- [LAUGHS]
- It's probably why I'm so wise.
- Jerk.
- [CHUCKLES]
What happened to us?
- Madison... Madison...
- Wh-what...
I can't... I can't.
Well, why?
Have you been
with anyone else?
No. No.
Have you?
No, of course not.
We're still technically married.
Right. [CHUCKLES]
I just...
[SIGHS] I don't want
to complicate things.
You and... You and I,
we've never really worked
through any of our issues, and...
I don't... I don't want
to be that guy.
What guy?
Your father died.
And I don't want to be the kind
that takes advantage.
You're not
taking advantage.
I'm the aggressor here.
It doesn't make it
any better.
Actually, it kind of makes
- my point for me.
- Noah.
You came here
to help me.
This is what I want.
This is what
I need right now.
I need to get lost in you
for a little while.
Forget all that stuff.
Are you sure?
Stop being so whiny.
It's killing my mood.
Thank you.
One thing real quick.
What?
Do you mind just going.
um, to the bathroom
and brushing your teeth,
or using a mouthwash
or something?
Why?
You just... You taste like
that beer you've been drinking.
You know I hate
the taste of beer.
[SCOFFS] Yeah.
No, really.
I feel like I picked you up
in a bar.
Please.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sure.
Thank you.
All right.
All minty fresh.
Um...
Um, maybe...
Maybe you're right.
Well, of course.
I should go.
No, no. Please. Please don't.
Maddy, I...
I can't stay here.
Please.
I'll stay until you fall asleep.
Okay.
So let's hear it.
Let's hear what?
Your pitch.
My pitch?
You obviously planned
everything here
to try to convince me
not to go through with it.
So go ahead.
Nah.
"Nah?"
What does that mean?
Just... nah.
So I mean
nothing to you?
Maddie, I didn't
want to meet here
to try to convince you.
There are no
magic words I can say
that'll turn back time
and change things.
We were married long
enough for me to know
that the only thing that
convinces you are my actions.
My actions were
screwed up enough that
I can't change them
with words.
I used to think that.
But now I know
it's all just a fantasy.
[SIGHS] It's not how
real people deal with life.
Honestly, I just...
I just wanted to meet here
because it reminds me of
how we felt
the day
we said "I do."
I haven't felt that
in a long time.
and I thought maybe
being here with you,
I might feel that again.
Just a little.
And, yeah,
I thought we both might
feel it a little.
Do you feel it?
I don't think so.
I just feel regret.
So I guess
it backfired on me.
You have the papers?
[CLEARS THROAT]
You have a pen?
What?
Who carries pens anymore?
Everything's electronic.
[MADISON] Not this.
No, not this.
Where?
Initial here, here,
and sign there.
[SIGHS]
Why are we
shaking hands?
I don't know.
Um... More official this way?
Bye... I guess.
Noah, come back
and sit down, please.
Why?
Just don't walk away.
Just please, come sit down.
Walk away.
It's funny.
You know, I'm not the one
who wanted to get a divorce.
Please?
You didn't want
to get a divorce,
but you didn't want
to fix things either.
Now, at the risk of
sounding petty,
now that we're
officially divorced,
do I still have to sit here
and get lectured on my flaws?
I don't want to be here either.
But this isn't all my fault.
I never said it was
all your fault.
Why couldn't you put me first?
Why was your career
more important than mine?
What about my dreams
and my plans?
Maddie, I don't know.
I don't know why my career
was so important to me.
It was. I know.
I wanted to do something
great with my films.
I wanted to touch
people's hearts.
I wanted to change their lives.
That sounds silly now because
I couldn't even get
my own shit together.
Sorry.
The truth is, you were right
and I was wrong.
I regret it all, because,
[SCOFFS] as much as I still hope
I have a chance of making films
that matter to people,
I'd rather be with you.
So what can I say?
I screwed it up because
I was too immature to see all
of that until it was too late.
I accept the blame.
And I'm sorry.
I've heard the apologies before.
I understand that.
I have nothing to gain.
Nothing to prove.
I'm just sorry.
It's not all your fault.
I wanted to be a dancer,
and clearly that wasn't
going to happen.
It was like cold water
on my face.
Seeing how good
everyone else was
at something that
I loved so much.
I was good.
Yes, you were.
But not near good enough.
Time kept ticking away.
And I can never rehearse or audition
as much as I needed to, so...
becoming a mom,
that consumed me.
You know, I never really
even wanted kids
when we got married.
Then that got taken away
from me, too.
And when the doctor told us
we couldn't have kids, I just...
I shut down.
And I didn't let you
or anyone in, and...
that's my fault,
'cause it just...
It drove us further apart.
[SIGHS]
Um...
Thank you.
I wish I had known
some of that before.
I wish I had been smart
enough to see it for myself.
I could have told you.
I don't know why
I waited till now.
Noah...
I want to be okay
with the fact that
I'll never be the dancer
I dreamed of being,
but I'm not.
I want to be okay
with the fact that
I'll never be able
to have children.
But I'm not.
I want to be okay
with the fact that
you've constantly put me in
second position behind your career
and my career
behind that,
but I'm not.
I want to be okay
with the fact that
you take your frustrations
about your career out on me.
But I'm not.
I want you to be okay with the
fact that you might never be
that filmmaker
that changes the world
but I know
that you're not.
And maybe you never will be.
I want to be okay
with the fact that...
my dad died
before I could directly
deal with his racism
and the way that
he treated you.
I'm ashamed that I never did,
because I had plenty of time.
I want to be okay
with being a coward
and not being able to reconcile
the idea of my daddy...
who I loved...
with this man who believed such
horrible things about the world.
But I'm not okay with that.
And... And he's dead,
And I'll never
be able to fix it.
I want to be okay
with the fact
that 14 years
into our marriage,
it's nothing like
I thought it would be.
It's full of
a lot of raw...
shit...
that I never saw coming
and that neither of us
responded particularly well to.
But I'm not okay
with that either.
I'm not okay
with any of it.
My life,
our life together
it's... it's...
nothing like I
wanted or imagined.
I really, really want
to be okay with it.
And...
I don't know, I mean...
maybe...
wanting to be okay with it
is enough
for now.
[GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you gonna write about this?
You're going to write
about this, aren't you?
♪ In the silence ♪
♪ Deep resounding violence
Of two hearts ♪
♪ Beating for each other ♪
♪ In the quiet stillness
I'm reminded of ♪
♪ What it means to ♪
♪ Love another ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I would carry it all ♪
♪ For you ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ When the light has gone ♪
♪ And all the night
Has fallen ♪
♪ When the bird
Sings goodnight ♪
♪ When the sigh of songs ♪
♪ Inside your heart
Come calling ♪
♪ Let it lead you home to me ♪
♪ Oh my only ♪
♪ One ♪
♪ Sweet like summer sun ♪
♪ When the light has gone ♪
♪ And all the night
Has fallen ♪
♪ When the last bird
Sings goodnight ♪
♪ When the sigh of songs ♪
♪ Inside your heart
Come calling ♪
♪ Let it lead you home
To me ♪