[male #1]
'’Okay, we'’re rollin'’.'’
'’Your name, please?'’
[female #1]
'’Oh, I'’m sorry. I was waiting
for you to say action.'’
Uh, hi. My name
is Jasmine Hampton
and I'’m 26 years old.
'’Current occupation?'’
Currently, I'’m employed
by the Miami Tribune.
I work as a writer, um...
I write an advice column.
Actually it'’s my advice column.
It'’s called
"Jysk-Ask-Jazz."
'’And what kind
of advice do you give?'’
Bad.
Well, I don'’t really
give bad advice.
I'’m really tired
of giving advice
on pimples, periods
and cellulite.
You know, I just...
that'’s why this opportunity--
Do you have broadcasting
or talk show host
experience, Justine?
Jasmine. Um, no, no.
I don'’t professionally,
but I-I really do feel
very comfortable
in front of the camera.
Probably, can'’t tell
by this interview.
But, uh, my friends and I
were always messing around
with this video camera
that my ex-boyfriend bought me.
Ironically that'’s how
I came with an idea
for a talk show
called "Girl Talk."
Once my friends and I
were in the living room
and just started
videotaping each other.
We were talking
about the pros and cons
of being female
in the '’90s, you know
and uh, we even started
demonstrating sexual skills
for each other. It was
really very interesting.
- I learned a lot.
- Yeah, right, okay. Thank you.
- You'’re welcome.
- Uh, another one.
'’That'’s it for now.'’
'’Just leave your demo
presentation on the table.'’
[camera clicks]
I was-I was
under the impression
that I was going to be reading
my presentation on camera
and you were going
to video tape it.
Not that simple.
'’Your presentation has to be
an actual demonstration'’
'’of the show you'’re
proposing to host.'’
You mean I was
supposed to come here
with my show
already recorded?
[door clicks]
Hey. Hey.
How did it go?
It didn'’t.
My video presentation
was supposed
to be an actual
presentation on video.
Oh..
I told them I'’ll have it
by Tuesday but there is no way.
Michelle, he was so insensitive.
Well, fuck him! You can
have it in by Tuesday.
No, I can'’t.
I can'’t do it by myself.
And where will I find
all those girls?
Uh, okay. Well, firstly, girls
always wanna talk about stuff.
'’Secondly, you'’re not
doing it by yourself.'’
Between the three of us,
we can make this happen.
You think Lena
would be in too?
When she gets home from work
we'’ll beg her.
Come on. I know
the perfect place to start.
[Jasmine]
'’You'’re right.
It'’s the perfect place.'’
'’We'’re handing out flyers
today hoping that women'’
will come over on Sunday
and talk to us
about dating and mating
in the '’90'’s.
- Are you into guys or girls?
- Both.
I'’m pretty addicted
to penetration.
Guys make the world
go round.
'’Men! I love men.'’
- '’Tell you the truth.'’
- '’I love penises and asses.'’
- '’Well, the muscles and stuff.'’
- '’I love their shoulders.'’
- '’What do I do sexually?'’
- '’What wouldn'’t you do?'’
Well, nothing I wouldn'’t
feel natural, of course.
I love the penis.
I love it being inside me.
Um, I like it in my mouth.
What I like about guys?
Um...givin'’ head.
A gay friend told me
how to do it.
Your position'’s
gotta be quite right
and coming from a queen
you better cope.
I'’ve learnt that
you'’ve just gotta open
your mouth a lil'’ bit wider.
Take a deep breath
and just go for it.
But they pee outta that.
- '’And who are you?'’
- I'’m Lena.
- '’Lena who?'’
- Lena your roommate, duh.
Lena, whom you dragged outta
the gallery to help you do this.
[Jasmine]
'’So what'’s your favorite
sexual position?'’
Uh-um...bein'’ on top.
On my back
with one leg up.
Being on top'’s pleasurable.
Plus, I'’m more into control.
I just like.. I don'’t know,
good, rough sex.
I cannot believe
these questions.
[ship'’s whistle blows]
- '’I like it doggy style.'’
- '’I don'’t like to be the dog.'’
'’One on the knees,
bein'’ on the knees.'’
'’Reach between your legs,
grab their scrotum.'’
If I want, I'’ll melt you.
If my mom heard me
talkin'’ like that..
'’I like to say
really dirty things.'’
'’You know what,
I like to tease him a lot.'’
♪ Let'’s talk tonight.. ♪
'’What'’s the worst pick up
line you'’ve ever heard?'’
'’Baby, why don'’t you
suck my tootsie roll'’
'’with your luscious lips?'’
[Lena]
'’Ah, wait, Michelle.
There'’s your sister.'’
- Hey.
- Girls.
You guys just can'’t stay off
your old college campus, huh?
[Michelle]
We'’re helping Jazz recruit girls
for a TV show she'’ll be hosting.
[Jasmine]
'’I don'’t have the job yet?'’
Yeah, yes you will.
Why don'’t you interview them?
- '’Can I interview you guys?'’
- Yeah, sure.
[Jasmine]
'’Cool, so I guess you'’re
into girls, yeah?'’
- Yeah.
- '’Each other?'’
Sometimes.
- I have a lesbian list.
- '’Tell us about that.'’
A list of women
that I'’d do it with.
'’Oh, cool.'’
Starting with
Melissa Ethridge.
She'’s cool.
♪ Let'’s talk tonight.. ♪
- '’So you girls ever kiss?'’
- No.
- Yeah, we have.
- No, we haven'’t.
- Yeah, that night we did.
- I don'’t remember.
'’Busted. Tell me what
you like about sex?'’
'’Some girls are just sexy.'’
I see her, I know what she is
gonna like '’cause she'’s like me.
'’Get a vibe from the woman.
Something goin'’ on. Then fine.'’
'’So who'’s the man
in this marriage?'’
- Neither. We'’re both women.
- My balls are bigger than hers.
Well, yeah, then
she'’s some homo-lesbian
she likes dick too.
- '’O-oh.'’
- Fuck off.
'’At least I don'’t think
I have a dick.'’
[Jasmine]
'’Oh-oh.'’
What is the deal with her?
You gotta get her in line.
[Jasmine]
'’How should she keep her girl
in check? Huh, Michelle?'’
- How?
- Strap it on.
'’Tina Gershawn. She is
on my list. That'’s for sure.'’
You guys coming
to Drew'’s party tonight?
We'’ll be a lil'’ late
'’cause Jazz wants to
interview some girls
on the street first.
- But we'’ll be there.
- Great. See you later.
- Bye.
- Take it easy.
- Thank you.
♪ Yeah, you can do it
♪ I'’ve been through hell
and her tonight.. ♪
'’Best thing a guy can do
for you, Lena?'’
- Love me.
- '’Yeah?'’
- And not leave me.
- '’Aww.'’
'’And what about you, Michelle?'’
Obey me and not question me.
To please me, a guy
can just eat me out.
- All the way down.
- You know, nice, gentle.
And not just for two seconds.
"Okay, baby. There,
is that enough for ya?"
'’Minute man, They come up and
you get five minutes of dick.'’
'’It'’s ridiculous.'’
♪ Girl, you can do it..
'’How do you
please your partner?'’
- Whatever floats his boat.
- You have to whip it on him.
That makes him, that gets him
there and keeps him there.
Make them please me.
Then I'’ll please them.
I'’m not only into
freaky shit, but..
I can suck start a Harley.
Does that tell you anything?
Imagine my dad
sees this stuff.
"Hey, you,
you'’re a sicko."
♪ Yeah, you can do it..
'’My ultimate sexual fantasy is
to be with a woman and a man.'’
Mine'’s sex
with a black guy.
I don'’t have a sex life
in America.
- '’How important is penis size?'’
- '’You should have a penis.'’
A guy once
had one like this.
Oh, shit!
[chuckles]
'’Is that really the size
of the boats?'’
'’Or more like...
the motion of the ocean.'’
'’Usually the guys I like
have big penises anyway.'’
'’It'’s the heart behind
the penis that matters.'’
Whoever said size
didn'’t count, didn'’t matter
either had a small penis
or didn'’t have one.
[Lena]
'’Making this presentation
is gonna be fun, girlfriend.'’
[Jasmine]
'’I want it to be a hit.'’
'’Would you watch a show
called Girl Talk?'’
I would. It'’ll be interesting
to see women...talking.
Hear women talking about things
that are important to us.
'’Cause I wanna know if other
people feel the same way I do.
'’Guys have no idea
what we talk about.'’
[both]
We talk about sex
all the time.
♪ Let'’s talk tonight ♪
♪ Yeah, you can do it..
[random cheering]
♪ ...Let'’s talk tonight.. ♪
[Jasmine]
'’Guys, my ass look
too big in these pants?'’
Jazz, your black ass
is big, girl.
- You used to love it.
- '’Cause her ex used to love it.
Why are black guys
so obsessed with big asses?
More cushion for pushin'’?
Speakin'’ of pushin'’, I don'’t get
laid, I'’ll shrivel up and die.
[Michelle]
I have a definite
fuzz flying.
[Lena]
Mm, my ecstasy is
kickin'’ in too, Michelle.
[Michelle]
Oh, that shit fucks
up your spine.
- Shut up.
- What'’s happenin'’?
- Luky, darlin'’.
- Welcome.
- Hey, James.
- Hey, wassup?
- Hello, gorgeous.
- Hey, James.
♪ Hey, hey, why you'’re missing,
please understand ♪
♪ The female dog
that I am on demand.. ♪
- Hey.
Hey, I need your guest list
for the Marlin party.
I'’ll get it to you.
Home or office?
Office. Fax it, Andy.
I don'’t get it,
your people don'’t get in.
♪ Like it ain'’t nothing ♪♪ Do it now
♪ She'’ll rock you
She'’ll rock you ♪
♪ Hey, I'’m out
If you miss her ♪
♪ She'’ll rock you like
it ain'’t nothing ♪
♪ Now you'’re listenin'’,
please understand ♪
♪ Female dog that I am
♪ On the real
here'’s the deal ♪
♪ On how I feel
♪ Close your eyes
and what do you see ♪
♪ To treat you like you
wanna be treated as me ♪
♪ Think twice
before you step ♪
♪ A female dog is whacha get
if ya trip, yeah.. ♪
[Michelle'’s sister]
'’Troublemaker'’s in the house.'’
[all]
Hey.
- Your DJ is jammin'’, girl.
- '’Well, he should be.'’
- '’Yeah.'’
- '’Let me buy you a drink.'’
- Water, yeah.
- I thought I saw you drink.
A.J., my sister Michelle and her
friends, take care of them.
Sure, my pleasure.
- Hey, wassup.
- What can I get for you ladies?
What do you got?
Whatever you want.
[Lena]
'’Ah-Umm.'’
Vodka cranberry.
- Just water.
- Two.
One vodka cranberry.
Two waters.
[A.J.]
'’So how long
you'’ve been sober?'’
[chuckles]
On a scale from 1 to 10
I'’d put him in about a 9.5.
You'’re being way too generous.
The night'’s still early.
Yeah, he'’s got that bushy
brow thing happenin'’.
Hey, don'’t knock it.
Learned a valuable lesson
from a Greek man once.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, bend over, baby.
And I did.
[laughing]
- Here, ladies.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Excuse me?
- Yeah?
Do I know you
from somewhere?
Yeah, we went to different
schools together.
[A.J.]
'’Yeah, you went to..'’
That-that was a good line.
Come here.
Lemme give you a lil'’
piece of advice.
Next time you connect with
a woman the way we just did.
Don'’t ask her if you
know her from somewhere.
Politely tell her you'’d like
to take her somewhere.
And touch her body
in all the places
her last lover forgot to.
♪ Take it higher
Get over the top!
- Does he take direction?
- I think he might.
I think you could handle it.
♪ ...Take it higher..
Oh, shit. Is that Drew?
The birthday girl
in the flesh.
What'’s she doin'’
with that guy?
Doesn'’t bother me.
She'’s loaded.
- Ow!
- Sorry, I couldn'’t resist.
Hey, you made it.
Michelle? Uh, Chloe. This is
my lil'’ sister, Michelle.
- Michelle.
- Chloe.
- Nice to meet you.
- Same here.
- I'’ve heard a lot about you.
- Really?
You do Marlin Hotel
promotions, right?
Yeah.
The five year anniversary
party you are throwing
will be the hottest
ticket in town.
Better be.
That'’s my job.
[club music]
Morgan, mom'’s comin'’ over
tomorrow for Mother'’s Day.
Lunch at 5. You might
wanna come down--
No. But thanks.
Gotcha, okay.
- Nice meeting you, Chloe.
- You too.
- Bye.
- See you soon.
Let'’s get outta here.
♪ Take it higher
[music continues]
[laughing]
- '’That Gucci belt is too fly.'’
- '’Thank you, girl.'’
'’You know I put my
best gear tonight.'’
'’And as I was getting dressed,
all my man could say was'’
'’"Why you ain'’t wax your shit?
You know I'’m gonna want some."'’
- '’No, he did not.'’
- '’What did you say then?'’
'’She told him
to go wax his hairy ass.'’
[all laughing]
'’Not like my shit was so hairy,
that he couldn'’t find it.'’
Guys just don'’t know.
Maintenance, upkeep.
That'’s a full time job for us.
Between the tweezing, trimming,
the plucking, the tucking
the waxing, the facials
and then the shoppin'’.
They'’re lucky we even
have the energy to get laid.
[female #2]
'’Yeah, we can find
the energy for that shit?'’
Oh, yeah. Like I did
all this shit for nothing.
Thank God, you'’re here. I gotta
go home. I am rollin'’ too hard.
Don'’t tell me
we did some bad shit.
[Lena]
'’Why don'’t you guys
ever listen to me?'’
Ran into some bad breath
motherfuckers today..
[dog barking]
[Lena]
'’I got serious
about you guys.'’
- What the hell..
- What'’s that?
Oh, what a surprise.
My mom stopped by.
Oh, again?
[Lena]
'’Can'’t believe I'’m not
getting laid tonight.'’
'’I may smoke lots of weed
but if it gets too heavy'’
I eat a bunch of cookies
and pass out.
You take that X shit, God knows
what trip you'’re in for.
'’Nothing'’s gonna happen
unless, like Michelle'’
you do tequila shots
with some wannabe model
who'’s probably still surprised
he'’s even fucking.
Enough already, you guys. Okay?
I'’m fine. I just had a bad rush.
You could'’ve stayed
if you wanted to.
'’I just don'’t you.'’
You'’re a beautiful, educated,
successful woman
'’who is like obsessed
with boys.'’
What'’s there to get Jazz?
When it comes to peach fest,
girlfriend just looses it.
- Sure.
- Oh, please.
[Michelle]
Like I'’m gonna advice
from you on relationships, Lena.
At least I don'’t get dogged
or dumped every week in my life.
First of all, Michelle.
Nobody dogs me.
And if I get dumped, it'’s '’cause
of the cards on the table.
If they can'’t deal with my
honesty then fuck '’em very much.
Lena, the minute you let a guy
know that you like him
or that you'’re just happy to
see him, you gonna get dogged.
And that card on the table crap
doesn'’t work in today'’s society.
Oh, bullshit.
Works with the right person.
My parents had the perfect
marriage, let me tell ya.
If my daddy
was alive today
my parents would still be
married...in today'’s society.
Well, what worked back then
just does not now.
[Lena]
'’That'’s because guys and girls
just don'’t communicate anymore.'’
'’We gotta get rid of all this'’
'’segregated
Venus-Mars bullshit.'’
- '’Just come together as one.'’
- Agreed.
'’Move as one
and think as one and..'’
'’That'’s what
it'’s all about.'’
'’You know, it'’s about bonding.
Of being together.'’
[Michelle]
You mean, bondage?
Oh, God. Come on.
Why'’d you think Jazz broke off
her engagement with Michael?
That'’s '’cause she was losing
her individuality.
That'’s not exactly
true, Michelle.
[Lena]
'’Well, something is off.'’
[Michelle]
My point is...Lena.
[Lena]
'’Bad feng shui.'’
Hey-hey, Lena. What you doing?
What you doing? Stop it.
The energy is still
off in here.
[Jasmine]
Please. Energy is always off
when you'’re confused or high.
[Michelle]
My point is..
Lena, you live in a fantasy
world that does not exist.
[Jasmine]
'’No offence, Michelle. But your
reality isn'’t exactly normal.'’
- '’Yeah.'’
- No, it'’s not.
Just having sex
with two guys at once.
[Michelle]
'’Feeds into their
competitive nature.'’
- Oh, please.
- Keeps them on their toes.
Doubles my chances of being well
served and pleasantly pleased.
'’Actually, you should
look into it sometime.'’
No, thanks. I'’m not into
waking up with a crowd.
[Michelle]
Yeah, well.
Neither am I.
Eternity is from...
the moment I come
until the moment I hear
that front door close.
[Michelle]
Goodnight, ladies.
[doorbell rings]
Who'’s that?
Who is that?
'’It'’s me, Scott.'’
Scott?
[Lena]
Oh!
[both]
Booty call.
Don'’t you dare?
Don'’t you dare.
I'’m serious.
Hello, beautiful.
What'’s up?
She'’s mad at me?
Scott, it'’s 4'’o clock
in the morning. You know?
You stop by without calling
and...you haven'’t returned calls
since the last time
you came without calling.
I guess you could say
I'’m a little pissed.
I just came by to apologize
for being such an asshole.
Thanks.
You going to invite me in?
No. I gotta get up
in a few hours.
So, go to sleep.
We can talk about it tomorrow
over breakfast.
You know I'’m going to
be serving it to you.
In bed.
I'’ll even feed you.
Come on. I'’ve been going through
lotta shit lately.
My band just broke up.
- Your band broke up?
- Yeah.
It'’s been a real drag.
I'’m sorry.
I just really need someone
to talk to right now.
Okay, but just talk.
I'’m serious.
[moaning]
[moaning continues]
[music]
So much for talking.
'’Nothing like a good doobie.'’
You want some?
No, I-I really should
let you get some sleep.
What, are you kidding?
I'’m wide awake. Oh, I feel good.
'’Let me cook you breakfast.'’
I'’ll even feed you.
I really..
I gotta go.
Oh...okay.
- Scott.
- Yeah?
I really...really like you.
Maybe we can...go out on
a real date sometime, you know.
I mean, don'’t get me wrong.
Sex is awesome
and everything but..
I'’d like to think that
we'’re capable of connecting
on...another level, you know.
So what are you doing
tomorrow night?
Ha ha.
I don'’t know.
Why don'’t you tell me?
[Michelle]
'’Oh, please. I cannot believe
you'’ve never faked an orgasm.'’
[Jasmine]
'’How do you fake an orgasm?'’
'’No, who are you fooling?'’
[Michelle]
'’Him. And who cares anyway?'’
Sometimes it'’s the only way to
free yourself from a bad fuck.
[Lena]
'’Yeah. It'’s the politically
correct thing to do.'’
Thank God, Scott
takes good care of me.
P.C. fucking. No way, honey.
When my show gets on air,
it'’ll be about
real issues females
face when it comes to
dating and mating in the '’90s.
[Lena]
Uh, hello. Uh, what do you think
faking orgasms is, girl, huh?
It'’s a serious issue
for females.
Bullshit. Look, if the kiss
ain'’t right
you just keep your legs tight.
- You gotta know before you go.
- '’Uh-huh?'’
[beatboxing]
No, you guys, I'’m serious.
Wa-what do you think that
the guy gets better the further
down your body he travels?
- Hello.
- Sometimes.
- Like I wanna wait.
- Ha, ha, ha.
By the way, Lena, could you have
been any louder last night?
- I thought you were dying.
- Oh, my God.
Yeah. Well, I did.
Four times, guys.
You came four times last night.
Uh-Huh. Yup.
- For real?
- '’Yeah.'’
Oh, my God.
I love when that happens.
Thank you.
Well, I can'’t believe
you even went there with him.
He'’s using you for sex.
Really? Is that why he'’s taking
me out to dinner tonight?
Oh, he'’ll take you
to dinner, honey.
But you'’re still
gonna be the dessert.
Wait-wait-wait a minute.
I thought you'’re
interviewing girls with me
on the street
today after lunch.
I am, honey. He'’s taking me
out to dinner.
I tell you, he'’s using you for
sex. You'’re wasting your time.
What makes you think
she'’s not using him for sex?
Oh, Michelle,
because she'’s not you.
Guys, can we talk
about me behind my back?
- Sure. Turn around. Ha, ha.
- Oh-ho, ha, ha, ha.
- Ha, ha, ha. Oh, God.
- Ha, ha, ha.
Well, Lena wet the bed
until she was ten years old.
Mom, can we please talk about
something else? Thank you.
[female #3]
'’Jasmine was bed ridden until
she was around'’ nine years old.
She practically lived
in the hospital.
One illness after the other. She
was so accustomed to being sick.
'’When she first started
growing breasts'’
she thought those cute little
lumps...were cancerous tumors.
- '’Ha, ha, ha.'’
Thank you
for sharing that, mom.
Maybe we should open
the presents.
Nonsense. What'’s the rush?
[female #3]
Jasmine was...
she was always beautiful.
'’Well, until she
cut off all her hair.'’
'’I don'’t understand,
for the life of me'’
'’why you cut your hair.'’
It makes you look like
one of those, you know
sexually confused
type of girls.
Thank heaven, Michael likes it.
No. I like it.
Letty, you must meet Michael.
He'’s delicious.
[Jasmine]
'’Michael'’s history.'’
Before Michael came,
Jasmine had me worried sick.
She was dating guys
that couldn'’t even afford
to put her on
lay away. Ha, ha, ha.
May be we should
open the presents.
It'’s definitely time
to open the presents.
[Jasmine]
'’Stood up by my own mom.'’
Well, thank God, Mother'’s Day
only comes once a year, huh?
- At least your mom'’s made it.
- I'’m sorry, Michelle.
- Did you try calling your mom?
- No. Why waste the money?
Come on. Put that out.
We got a show to make.
[techno music]
♪ Free
♪ Speak about love
♪ Sex ♪
[laughter]
- Excuse me, ladies. Hi.
- Hi.
Hi, um, we'’re doing
a presentation for a talk show
and I just wanted to know
if I could ask you some
questions on camera about guys?
- Yeah, okay.
- Okay.
Great. So the talk show
is called "Girl Talk"
and our categories are likes,
dislikes, skills and thrills.
But today we'’re
just doing dislikes.
Do you have any dislikes?
Oh...yeah.
Okay, great. So I just need you
to look right into camera
and speak up, okay?
Alright. Action.
I don'’t understand why we have
to cover our chests just because
we have tits and guys can'’t
control their boners.
And "boners". Where did that
word come from?
[chattering]
I don'’t know, you guys.
I just hope that maybe someday
on a day like today,
me and my friends
we can go out
and have a really nice lunch
in a public place...topless.
[female #4]
Without having to be fondled,
harassed and grabbed at.
Penises get out of control
and start going on radar around.
- Okay, great. Thank you.
- Brilliant.
♪ Details please ♪
[Jasmine]
'’What don'’t you
like about guys?'’
Um, I don'’t like guys
when they'’re...too aggressive.
Okay, I don'’t like it when my
boyfriend...lifts the cover
and puts it over my head when he
farts. That just...eh-h-h!
They eat food like they
have to cover their plates
so they wouldn'’t
have to share or something.
Like, it'’s really weird.
I dislike guys, who yell out
nasty and dirty names to you.
"Bitches" or "chicks."
Hate it when we walk
down the street
and they call you like,
"Hey, baby." You gotta--
[men yelling]
- See what I mean?
- Right there.
Hate it when
the toilet seat'’s up.
I don'’t like it when guys
concentrate on my breasts.
I like the attention. They'’re
real, they'’re natural
and I mean...I love it.
I don'’t like arrogant men.
- What I don'’t like?
- The male ego.
They have very big attitudes,
especially the lookers.
That'’s why
I like the dorky ones.
- Half of them aren'’t honest.
- They cheat by nature.
It seems that it'’s very
easy for the guy
to just go on
into another relationship.
Like, you know your relationship
with him never existed.
Don'’t like it when
they do this to me.
While I'’m giving them head.
[Lena]
Order me an ice-tea.
I gotta pee.
[Jasmine]
There'’s gotta be a happy medium.
Ha, don'’t worry about it.
It'’s...just the beginning.
- You'’ll get what you need.
- I hope so.
- You know you will.
- You'’ll see.
[Michael]
Jazz.
Michael.
- Hi. How you doing?
- Good, okay, yeah.
Good, good.
Can I talk to you
for a moment?
Yeah, I'’m gonna go
and join Lena, in the bathroom.
So, um...I don'’t know
if you got any of my messages.
Actually I, um, I did.
I'’ve just been...really busy.
No, no need to apologize.
It'’s just that you said that
we could be friends
and it'’s been...
it'’s been a month now.
- Michael--
- No.
You did what you had to do.
What can I say?
Yeah, well.
Enjoy your tea.
[Jasmine]
'’How do you feel about guys'’
ability to communicate?'’
They suck.
I don'’t think they know
how to communicate. As adults.
More guys nowadays,
are learning that in order
to have relationships, they have
to learn how to communicate.
It'’s like
I know they feel.
But it'’s like, they just
don'’t know how to express it.
I think they'’d be better off
if they didn'’t talk.
[Jasmine]
'’What are the excuses
you'’ve heard guys use'’
'’when it comes to
not wearing a condom?'’
"Baby, trust me,
it'’s not gonna break."
"You think I'’ll
get you pregnant?"
That'’s not it! Just use
a fucking condom.
"The condom won'’t fit
my penis." I'’ve heard that.
I'’ve heard them all.
If it don'’t fit,
then you have to acquit!
That'’s right, sisters.
Before he even get'’s
it up, you whip it on.
It'’s time to stop the madness.
I know as many lies
as I'’d have heard a brother say
nose be growin'’ and everything,
they been lying, talking about.
"Uh, you know I can'’t wear
any condom, baby
"'’cause you know,
my shit too big.
It don'’t fit up
in the condom." Ah-uh!
[laughing]
'’Cause see they even
got the Chihuahua condom
for you Vienna sausage packing
brothers, see? There go.
And for you brothers
that claim your business
is too big to be bagged?
Oh, no. Not no more, bam!
On your way. For you
Zulu carrying motherfucker.
Oh, yes. I'’m gonna show ya.
It '’bout to fit.
See that? If this fit
this head, it'’ll fit you.
Do I make myself clear?
[laughing]
♪ How do you fuck
♪ C'’mon, discover.
C'’mon, they say ♪
♪ C'’mon, c'’mon ♪
- Phew! Oh, this color is..
- Hi!
- Can I help with something?
- Yeah.
Tell me, how much
for those pants in the window?
They'’re originally a 150.
But they'’re on sale for a 100.
- For those?
- The fit is mint.
Unlike most hip-huggers,
the crotch is cut low.
So they'’re
really comfortable.
[Jasmine]
'’Oh, wait a minute.
While we'’re here.'’
You have any dislikes
when it comes to dating
or mating in the '’90s?
- Oh, God! Here she goes again.
- Oh, God!
- What are you kiddin'’?
- Oh, no.
[Jasmine]
'’Guys, come on.
Just one more.'’
Okay, just look right
in here and...smile.
The one problem I really
have with guys
is the way they behave
after having sex.
Hey, sweetheart.
- Ah, honey?
- What?
I was just wondering..
Well, I was just thinking
maybe we could..
You know...talk.
Talk? Come on! I talked
to you before I fucked you.
Give me a break.
'’The only time I see him
is when he wants to have sex.'’
'’And if he doesn'’t
fall asleep, he leaves.'’
I'’m sure other girls go through
the same thing, you know.
Ahem-ahem!
[Lena]
You know, actually,
we'’re out of time.
Jazz, can we go? I gotta
get ready for my date.
- Yeah.
- See you later. Thanks.
- Thank you very much.
- Take care.
[Jasmine]
'’One thing a guy does that
pisses you off after sex?'’
Rolls over
and goes to sleep.
He has to get up and smoke
and he does it normally.
They always wanna ask
how they were?
Did you cum? Did you cum?
And what pisses me off, is right
after sex and this is dirty
but I mean, I can be honest.
We'’re all girls here.
When they throw you
the towel to clean up with.
That is the most unromantic
thing in the world.
Here, baby, take this.
[Jasmine]
'’I had a lotta
fun today. Thanks.'’
- '’Me too.'’
- '’Yeah.'’
Kinda weird running
into Michael, huh?
No. Not really.
- '’What time is it?'’
- It'’s almost midnight.
Damn, I wanted to try answering
some of the letters
for my article tonight.
I'’m calling Stu on Tuesday.
So? You got tomorrow
and Monday to do it.
Oh, yeah.
I'’m so over that tired ass job,
I can'’t even tell you.
That'’s why this
presentation'’s gotta kick ass.
It'’s really time
for you to move on.
- It'’s gonna to be great.
- Mm, yeah.
- Tomorrow is skills.
- '’O-oh!'’
- That should be fun.
- Uh-huh!
Mm-hm. Maybe we'’ll learn
a thing or two, huh?
- Speak for yourself.
- Oh, you'’re so skilled, huh?
- Uh-huh.
- Alright.
What'’s your, uh,
most skillful position?
Skillful position?
Skillful sexual position?
Yes, absolutely.
My most skillful sexual..
On top.
On top?
Ride him like
a fucking cowgirl.
It'’s the best, man. You'’re on
top. You guide the gear--
I like both.
I-I like it from behind.
Like it from behind?
Me too. Double time.
Hard on. Edge of the bed..
- Double time from behind.
- Oh, I miss you. I'’m so white.
[laughing]
[Michelle]
'’Lena'’s still sitting
out there waiting for him?'’
Yeah, he'’ll show up.
Two o'’clock in the morning
for another booty call.
I told her he'’s just using her
to get his shit with.
[Lena]
Stop talkin'’ about me
behind my back.
Lena, we were just
worried about you.
Well, don'’t worry
about me, okay?
[footsteps]
Oh, shit.
What is the problem
with me?
'’Huh?'’
I'’m just so sick of this shit.
[sobbing]
He could have
at least called.
Oh!
[Lena]
I can'’t believe
I'’ve been stood up again.
I was stood up
at a bar one time
which was really embarrassing.
It'’s kind of humiliating.
If they don'’t want you,
they should tell you
straight up and stick with it.
It does something to your ego.
I guess you feel like
you know, "Oh God, what-what
did I do?" Like, you think.
I think I give him
too much attention.
Maybe, that could'’ve been it.
Um, maybe, I-I know
I didn'’t neglect him.
So, I sit on my couch
and stare out my window.
He never, he never told me why.
I had to be the one to call.
That'’s a good indication that
it'’s probably not the person
you wanna spend
any time with.
I don'’t think
she should call him.
[female #5]
'’If he calls you
just for booty calls'’
time to turn off your ringer.
It'’s time to pretend
you don'’t remember what
his name is or who he is.
I dealt with it the wrong way.
I blocked guys out and thought
"All guys are trash, creeps. All
guys are dogs." But they'’re not.
I think it has to do
with self-esteem.
You gotta have more
confidence in yourself.
Um, '’cause confidence just,
is so attractive.
I'’m so convinced that
the reason why girls
like to shop is because clothes
give us confidence. Just think.
You can walk into a party,
you can feel like shit.
But if you look good,
it'’s all good.
- It'’s true.
- I know. Sick!
Our confidence comes
from a shopping bag.
- Well, better than from a guy.
- Alright, Ms. Ball-buster.
Well, come on.
You know what I mean.
There are many girls who need
a guy to make them happy.
It'’s like they'’re dying for a
man to validate their existence.
I'’d die before I let someone
have that control over my life.
It'’s one of the things
I liked about Michael.
I was always
just free to be me.
Jazz, why did you really break
off the engagement with Michael?
Even I thought
he was a keeper.
Hi, guys.
Hey!
Can'’t believe I overslept.
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
Oh, I forgot to do
laundry today.
- How come nobody woke me?
- '’Cause we didn'’t want to.
You guys are just
too good to me.
Yeah, we are. Yes, we are.
Oh, man! Look at the rug
on this guy'’s head.
- Oh, God!
- What? Let me see.
- Look at this, unbelievable.
- Oh, ho-ho-ho!
This asshole actually
thinks it looks real?
No. This has gotta be a joke.
Oh!
- Hey, guys.
- Yeah?
Thank you.
You'’re welcome.
- '’You don'’t have anyone?'’
- '’Does this look like I'’m--'’
[Jasmine]
'’Lose the chair. Lose the chair.
C'’mon, help me.'’
'’The table'’s gotta go.'’
- '’And the table?'’
- Where were the pictures?
I took the pictures off.
Lose the chair. Come on!
- Okay, you better be ready.
- I'’m right. Trust me.
Oh-h!
- Oh!
- Shit!
Michelle, help me?
I can'’t get the shutter open.
What are you doing?
Well, '’cause you have
to turn the camera on
before you can record.
- The camera is on. Duh!
- Duh!
[knocking on door]
- Oh-h!
- Showtime.
- You ready?
'’Bring them in.'’
- Hi, is this Girl Talk?
- Yeah.
- I'’m Michelle. Come in.
- O-oh, um, what about them?
[all cheering]
Uh, uh, help!
- What'’s goin'’ on?
- Oh!
Hi. My name is Monica
and I have a very special skill
I'’d like to share
with you today.
In order for me to perform this
skill, I'’ll need two things.
'’A bottle of good spray and any
potent guy of your choice.'’
But today,
I'’ll be using...Mr. Cucumber.
[giggling]
You just spray
a little bit of this..
[spraying]
...in your throat.
Nothing numbs better.
Oh, and don'’t worry about the
tingling sensation you'’ll feel.
You'’ll find the guy
likes it too.
Okay, watch me carefully.
[giggling]
Here we go.
[retching]
Shh!
[laughing]
That'’s okay. We got the point.
Thanks for coming.
'’Okay.'’
[moaning]
I'’m blowing! I'’m blowing!
'’I'’m coming! I'’m coming!'’
'’Ah! I'’m blowing, I'’m blowing!'’
[laughing]
Coming. I'’m coming.
I'’m coming.
- Oh, my God.
- No, let go.
[moaning]
♪ Show and tell
♪ You do it well
♪ You need to show me
♪ Then do it to tell me
♪ Show and tell
♪ What
♪ You do it well
You do it well ♪
[laughing]
♪ Everybody'’s gotta story ♪
♪ Everybody'’s gotta fantasy ♪
♪ Baby, let me tell you
♪ Let me tell you
how hard it is for me ♪
Ha, ha, ha.
♪ Never had a problem.
Telling you what I wanted.. ♪
Oh, no. Uh-uh!
Disgusted.
In addition
to the obvious, girls.
I think we'’re all familiar
with these? Hmm?
[vibrating]
♪ It'’s time for
a little show and tell ♪
♪ Show and tell
♪ Are you? Are you
showing Do tell ♪
♪ You do it well
♪ Are you showing
♪ Do it well
♪ Show and tell
♪ Not gonna tell you
what I'’m gonna do to you ♪
♪ You do it well
♪ And love you long
♪ Show and tell
♪ You'’re gonna
know the details ♪
♪ You do it well
♪ Do it well.. ♪
[Michelle]
'’A door knob?'’
What?
Would you like a demonstration?
- I-I'’d go for it.
- Yeah.
- Are you close?
- '’Uh, yeah.'’
Good, now come closer.
[female #6]
'’Okay. I'’m ready.'’
It'’s about fucking time.
My friends think I'’m strange.
But what'’s strange about wanting
to be the belle of my own balls?
[female #6]
'’Must be in control.'’
'’Young puppies
are easier to train.'’
'’And doubles my chances'’
'’of being well served
and pleasantly pleased.'’
Yeah!
[moaning]
♪ Yeah
♪ You should try it sometime..
Stop the tape.
♪ Who do you love?
♪ I love you, I want you,
I need you ♪
♪ Louder ♪ I love you
♪ I want you..
Stop the tape.
♪ ...I love you,
I need you ♪
♪ I want you,
I love you ♪
[Michelle]
Stop the fucking tape!
[female #6]
'’Wow! What was that all about?'’
Nothing, we...I don'’t
wanna run out of tape.
Oh, okay.
Whatever is clever.
[door slams shut]
[Jasmine]
'’Michelle!'’
'’Michelle, why did you
walk out like that?'’
[Michelle]
Just leave me alone.
[Lena]
'’Maybe we should
leave her alone.'’
[Jasmine]
'’No, I'’m not gonna leave her
alone. She'’s always running.'’
We'’re not gonna leave you alone.
Turn around and let'’s talk.
[Lena]
'’You'’re taking this way
too personally.'’
'’I mean, so what?
You both like'’
'’to use boys for toys
and you both into control.'’
[Michelle]
Oh, please. She had no idea
what she was talking about.
All I know is I am really sick
of the whole fucking charade.
Hey...what'’s going on
in that head of yours?
I'’m so angry.
And I'’m tired.
And I'’m tired of being
so fucking angry.
When does the pain
go away?
When do I stop trying
to prove to the world
that I can fucking
handle it all?
Michelle, it'’s okay.
No, it'’s not okay.
What'’s okay about being
emotionally dead?
What'’s okay about...waking up
every morning and looking
in the mirror and knowing
I'’m never, ever gonna
be enough for someone?
- Michelle, that is not true.
- That is not true.
No. It is true.
It'’s my truth, and the fact
of the matter is
I use because I live
in fear of being used.
And I walk first because
the thought of one more person
pushing me aside
or walking out on me
is un-fucking-bearable.
♪ They don'’t understand me ♪
♪ Some say it'’s my alcohol
sometimes I don'’t drink at all ♪
♪ My depression is my life
overdose on magic pearls ♪
♪ Every night I sleep
in the morning I wake ♪
♪ All this complain
but will I take a life away ♪
♪ I don'’t really want to die.
Everything will be alright ♪
♪ Emotions unstable up and down
something just ain'’t right ♪
♪ Don'’t care what people say
but then I guess I do ♪
♪ Not sure I care and love.
I think I'’m too confused ♪
♪ They don'’t understand me.
I don'’t understand myself ♪
♪ I can'’t be understood
by you or no one else ♪
♪ They don'’t understand me.
I don'’t understand myself ♪
♪ I can'’t be understood
by you or no one else ♪
♪ They don'’t understand me.
I don'’t understand myself ♪
♪ I can'’t be understood
by you or no one else ♪
♪ They don'’t understand me.
I don'’t understand myself ♪
♪ Didn'’t ask to be understood
by you or no one else ♪
[car approaching]
[doorbell ringing]
Who is it?
- '’It'’s me, mom, it'’s Michelle.'’
- Michelle?
- Hi.
- Are you busy?
- No, come on in.
- I'’ll get something to eat?
- No.
- Coffee?
- No, I'’m not staying on.
I just came to bring you this.
I'’m sorry it'’s dirty.
- Happy Mother'’s Day.
- Oh, honey.
Ah, I'’m so sorry,
I couldn'’t make it.
Mum, you know,
you could'’ve called.
Yeah, well. I got home from work
and the twins prepared me
this beautiful lunch that their
father helped them with.
- And I just couldn'’t help--
- Yeah, no.
I don'’t wanna compete
with your new family.
- Michelle, please.
- Mom, I need to know.
What is it gonna take
to make me feel like
I could still have
a part of you for me.
- Michelle, honey, don'’t.
- Don'’t what, mom?
Don'’t express the...the pain
I'’m feeling because I'’m finally
accepting the fact that I don'’t
exist in my mother'’s eyes.
Knowing that my
whole life
I'’ve tried to be
the perfect daughter
and that'’s still
not enough.
- What are you talking about?
- Oh..
You really don'’t
get it, do you?
All I get is I married your
father and he left me alone
with two daughters
and no future.
And now finally I found
someone who loves me.
Honey, we have
children together.
Now, you and Morgan never so
much as give him a hello
when you call.
How is that supposed
to make him feel?
I don'’t give a shit
how that makes him feel.
He'’s never cared
about me.
I'’m talking about my
relationship with you.
- He is a part of me.
- Uh, who am I part of?
Who'’s Morgan, a part of?
Mom, all we have ever
done...is love you.
And you'’re saying that
by accepting our love
you'’re afraid that
you gonna loose his?
Oh, my God, mom.
How can you let him
control you like that?
[girls laughing]
I like a man who treats me
with respect.
- Mmm.
- '’That'’s really important.'’
I like a man
with a sense of humor
and the man that
smells really good.
I mean, when he leaves
the fragrance on your pillow.
When he leaves or something. You
just gonna snuggle and smell it.
I have to say, I think I like
a man with a nice smile.
- Definitely, a nice smile.
- Yeah.
It'’s really simple.
Brains in both heads.
I mean, I'’m sorry, you'’ll
all mushy and that'’s great.
But I like a man with money.
[all]
'’Who-hoo.'’
That could make up for it here
where he lacks everywhere else.
[all cheering]
- Hey, how you guys doing?
- Hey, Michelle.
Are you gonna join us?
Yeah. I'’m gonna change on my
monkey suit and I'’ll be back.
- Hey, you okay?
- Never felt better.
- Good.
- I'’ll be right back.
Okay.
- Foreplay that'’s real sad.
- Foreplay.
[all]
'’Foreplay, foreplay, foreplay.'’
♪ Forever enthroned
♪ It makes it easy
♪ To turn and let it go
♪ And crawl over
♪ Into you
♪ More than I
you make it easy ♪
♪ To letting go ♪
He used to lick
and everything. Love it.
'’We also like kissing.'’
[Jasmine]
'’Oh, no doubt. Kissing is
the best foreplay, girls.'’
'’I could definitely kiss
until I came.'’
[all cheering]
- Let'’s talk about that, honey.
- '’Oh, no, no.'’
- Oh, yes, yes.
- Alright.
Alright, with the right mouth,
with the right mouth.
I could definitely kiss
until I came.
'’First, the lips have
to be really nice and soft.'’
♪ Sciences repeat
♪ Every thought you stop
♪ Your eyes complete
♪ No word you'’re saying ♪
♪ Remind me of a time
♪ A place where love
used to be ♪
'’You know the best thing is?
Never feeling like your alone.'’
Always knowing that
he'’s there for you.
No matter where you are.
If you'’re 2000 miles away it
doesn'’t matter. He'’s there.
He'’s a phone call, he'’s a beep,
he'’s-he'’s gonna call you.
When they really know
how to love you.
When you really feel loved.
That'’s a big deal.
'’Show me your love.
Just don'’t feel it. Show it.'’
'’Grandparents are married for 50
years. And both my grandfathers'’
'’still pitch my grandmothers
on the booty--'’
'’This is what'’s it all about.
Together in the end.'’
'’I have more pictures of one
set of my grandparents kissing'’
'’than I have of
any of my friends.'’
- '’That'’s right.'’
- '’I'’m serious.'’
Jazz?
Oh, hi.
- '’Hi.'’
- I was...just looking for you.
[boy #1]
Michael, we'’re ready.
Alright, fellows, run the layups
again and I'’ll be right there.
- You'’re looking pretty good.
- Well, season still early.
So what brings you
to this neck of the woods.
Um, I was-I was just
thinking about you and..
I also wanted to just let you
know that I'’m sorry
if the energy was off...when
I ran into you at the cafe--
You know, Jazz, when I ran into
you at the cafe the other day
it occurred to me that there is
just nothing left to say.
Nothing more than I can
afford to hear anyway.
You made a decision
on my behalf.
And now, I have to do
my best to live with it.
You take care
of yourself, okay?
Michael.
Michael, wait.
I gotta tell you something.
- Michael, don'’t ignore me.
- Don'’t ignore you?
You know, you are yet to say
anything that I need to hear.
Explain why I spent the last two
years of my life with a woman
I thought was
gonna be my wife.
And I don'’t wanna hear
any of that bullshit.
I don'’t wanna hear
any of that bullshit about
you and me not being
right for each other.
Michael, I only suggested
that we not get married.
You know, Jazz, I don'’t wanna
hear it. I just don'’t wanna.
You wanted it over.
Well, it'’s over.
I'’m sick and tired of listening
to your unsolicited opinions
and your well thought-out
decisions and your advice.
I don'’t need your advice. I'’m
sure don'’t need another mother.
I'’m not trying to be
your mother--
That'’s your problem, Jazz! You
think you'’re everybody'’s mother.
Just ask Jazz and she'’ll tell
you what'’s right with the world!
Fuck you!
I don'’t think
I'’m everybody'’s mother.
As a matter of fact, I'’ll never
be anybody'’s mother, Michael.
I can'’t have children, Michael.
I can never, ever give you
what you want the most.
[boy #1]
'’Michael, man, come on!'’
♪ Hold me
♪ Hold me even though
♪ Nothing'’s gonna change ♪
♪ Tonight
♪ Fighting with your heart
♪ Darlin'’, find a way ♪
♪ Tear this thing apart
♪ Give me.. ♪
[door closing]
[Jasmine]
'’Hey, ladies, I'’m back.'’
'’I found him on the
basketball court. We talked.'’
- '’Yes.'’
- That'’s so good!
That'’s what happened.
It was great.
- '’Hey, guys.'’
- Hey.
- So, what did he say?
- A lot.
And we'’re going to talk more
over dinner, Saturday night.
- Oh, that'’s so good!
- '’Great, yeah.'’
Did you invite him to the Marlin
party Friday night?
- No, I thought about it. But--
- What do you mean?
You know, one step at a time,
honey. One step at a time.
- '’Okay.'’
- Yeah.
Aren'’t you supposed to be
in the editing room right now?
Yes. I gotta go.
I still haven'’t touched
any of my letters for tomorrow'’s
article. So, I'’m gonna go now.
- Take care, ladies.
- '’See ya, honey.'’
- Good luck.
- '’Thanks!'’
How I hope it works out for her.
Me too.
[bass music]
♪ Girl talk
[music continues]
♪ Let'’s talk tonight ♪
♪ Girl talk ♪
- Good morning.
- Michelle. Some Coffee?
[Jasmine]
Oh, no thanks.
I don'’t have time.
I was editing in the studio
till 4.30 this morning?
I'’m telling you, girls can
talk their asses off.
That was the idea,
wasn'’t it?
So, how does it look?
- Ta-da! Excellent.
- Great.
Listen, I know I'’ve worn my
favors out with you guys.
- Hmm.
- Yeah, I know.
This tape has to be
at the studio by 10 o'’clock.
And I still have
six letters to answer
and have on my editor'’s desk
by nine. So.
Well...I can'’t answer
your letters for you.
But I have a meeting
with the caterers at 10
and I can drop it at
the station on my way.
- Oh, you don'’t mind?
- No, I don'’t mind.
Oh, and Lena, I didn'’t
get a chance to print labels.
- So, if you don'’t mind.
- No problem, baby.
Cool.
When do you think you'’re
gonna know something?
Well, the producers are
viewing tapes this week.
And if they happen to like mine,
they invite me to the studio
to discuss further
show topics and ideas.
And if the meeting goes well,
I'’m on my way, darling.
Yeah! To Gucci.
♪ A Gucci, Gucci, Gucci
[all]
♪ A Gucci, Gucci, Gucci ♪
Alright, guys.
[doorbell ringing]
You guys expecting someone?
[door screeches]
Morgan, what'’s wrong?
- Everything. Is Michelle here?
- Yeah, are you okay?
Problems with Drew, again?
- Drew?
- We broke up.
Oh. It'’s okay, okay.
- What'’s up?
- They broke up.
Morgan, I don'’t mean
to be rude
but I have a deadline
to meet.
'’Oh, no. Go. I-I understand.'’
'’I just didn'’t have
anywhere else to go.'’
Well, you'’re always
welcomed here. Okay?
Thanks for dropping off
the tape.
And can you ask the studio
if they can make a copy
'’cause I didn'’t get to run
any copies of this morning.
- Will do.
- Good luck.
Phew, so.
[door opens]
Some..
Remember, that girl I introduced
you to at Drew'’s party?
Ah, that night is a bit
of a blur for me.
[sighs]
Well, anyway her name
is Chloe, and..
[sighs]
The other night
when Drew was at class we..
We smoked a joint
and decided to..
Well, make a home movie
and-and--
- Drew found the tape?
- Oh, shit.
[knock on door]
[Chloe]
'’Open the damn door, now.'’
- Oh, God.
- Okay. No, I got it.
[knocking continues]
- Oh, no.
- Chloe, please wait.
No. Where is she?
I hop in the shower
and you decide to take off?
- I'’m tired of arguing with you.
- Then just say that.
Don'’t just fucking walk out.
If you really gonna leave then,
take your shit with you.
Fuck you!
- Meg, stop it.
- Come on.
Stop it.
You'’re hurting her.
- Stop it. Beg you.
- You selfish whore.
Oh, I'’m the whore?
What the fuck are you?
I mean, every time
I turn around
you'’re flirting with this girl
and that guy. Fuck you!
One minute you'’re gay
the next minute you'’re straight
then yourself, I'’m damn tired
of trying to figure you out.
Like you'’ve ever tried to
figure me out. You don'’t care.
All you care is
keeping me around
like some kinda trophy
to show off to your friends.
Oh, yeah, well, you'’re some
fucking expensive trophy.
I'’ve never asked you
for anything.
You'’re so tied up in being
the heartbreaker
club owner of miss
nothing can hurt me.
You know I'’m only human.
I hurt, I feel, I have needs.
Drew, I always tell everyone
how great you are
and how much I love you.
Yeah, you ever think
about telling me?
Some things you
should just know.
Why should I have
to tell you?
Why?
Because I love you so much
and I need to hear
and feel that
I'’m not left alone.
That'’s why.
[sobbing]
[vehicle honking]
- Good morning, may I help you?
- Hi, yeah.
I'’m here to drop off
a demo talk show presentation.
- Hm, for whom?
- That'’s a very good question.
I'’m dropping it off for a friend
she didn'’t tell me who.
Eh, excuse me?
Do I know you from somewhere?
Hi, weren'’t you
the bartender--
At Drew'’s party, yeah.
Yeah. Ha ha.
Oh, hi.
Listen, I'’m really sorry
if I was rude.
No, not at all, it, uh,
it was good for me.
So what you here for?
I'’m dropping off a presentation
but I dunno who to give it to.
You'’re looking at him.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Small world. Are you one
of the producers?
Oh, no. I work
in the editing room.
Putting reels together and
making copies. Things like that.
That'’s funny, my next question
was can I get a copy made.
My friend didn'’t have
to do it for herself.
- Sure. Come with me.
- Okay.
Have a seat.
Alright. Let'’s see
what you got here.
"Girl Talk."
Great name for a show.
Yeah.
- So you work two jobs?
- For the time being.
I'’m in the process
of defending my dissertation
on sexual niblets.
You'’re a shrink?
Nah, I prefer research
over clinical practice.
Okay, let'’s see
what we'’ve got here.
[moaning]
- '’Oh, my God!
- '’Whoa.'’
Oh, my God. That'’s the wrong
tape. I grabbed the wrong tape.
It'’s-it'’s alright. How soon can
you get a hold of the right one?
- Can I use your phone?
- '’Yeah, sure.'’
[dial tone]
Oh, Lena, pick up.
[Lena]
'’Hi, it'’s Lena.
Leave a message, bye.'’
Lena, it'’s Michelle. I think you
labeled the wrong tape.
Are you there?
Pick up if there.
[dial tone]
[softly]
Sorry.
[Morgan]
'’Hello.'’
It'’s Michelle, did you take
the tape of you and Chloe
when you left this morning?
Lena? Lena?
- Lena!
- What?
God, I got your message,
there was only one tape
on the coffee table.
What is it?
What? Michelle, what happened?
[soft piano music]
[Lena]
'’Talk to me. What?'’
Morgan took Jazz'’s tape
by accident.
And..
- Shit, they..
- What?
They burnt Jazz'’s tape.
Oh, my God.
Michelle, Michelle,
that was her only copy.
My editor is such
a bitch on wheels
I can'’t wait to..
What'’s going on, you guys?
Michelle.
Did you take the tape
to the station?
What do you mean, no?
Jazz...Drew and Morgan
took your tape
instead of theirs
when they left this morning.
Did you get it back?
I tried.
What'’s that supposed to mean?
They burnt it.
Before I could get it back.
They what?
[piano music continues]
[sobbing]
[Michelle]
Jazz, I'’m so sorry.
[Lena]
'’Jazz.'’
[piano music continues]
♪Every wrong they say ♪
♪Tomorrow'’s another day ♪
♪But how can I believe ♪
♪When yesterday'’s
all I'’ve seen ♪
♪It all tumbles round ♪
♪Well, I'’m here breaking down ♪
♪And if I just call your name ♪
♪You'’ll just say
it'’s not the same ♪
♪So I ♪
♪I wave goodbye ♪
♪To the loneliness
and the lies ♪
♪I call on to find ♪
♪When I need
to leave it behind ♪
♪Gathering up my tears, yeah ♪
♪To wash away
every last fear ♪
♪You and I ♪
♪I wave goodbye ♪
♪So the strong
and weak survive ♪
Why can'’t I do anything right?
See, sex is important to me
because I'’ve failed before.
I had very high expectations
for myself and..
Even though I have
put all my all into it
that I just didn'’t do
good enough and if it hurts me.
Maybe, if I wasn'’t
so busy judging other people
in their imperfections,
I'’d have time to stay on back
and look at my own.
The closest people around me,
I sometimes slip and want
and expect them
to do things for me.
[Lena]
It'’s just the mother
in you, Jazz.
No, no, it'’s not
the mother in me.
- Yeah, it is.
- No.
It'’s the insecurity
that comes from knowing
I'’ll never be a mother.
One day there were like kids,
ten kids all over me.
So that'’s probably
what'’s so deep about it.
To not be able to do that, um,
my family is already very small
so, I feel like the generations
are based on me.
[Jasmine]
I just wanted
to know what it felt like
to create and give life
to something
that I can call my own.
[Michelle]
Yeah, but you did.
You'’ve created something
'’that has changed all
of our lives forever.'’
[thunder rumbling]
[guitar music]
♪And there are five
or twenty Gods I'’ve tried ♪
♪To help me move
the pain on fire ♪
♪Well, twenty numbers I can
always call until dawn.. ♪
- Hey Michelle.
- '’Hey.'’
Hey, you guys are late. Oh, God.
Out buying some confidence.
[Lena]
'’Couldn'’t help ourselves.
Yeah, I got excited.'’
Oh, yeah, she did.
Her dress is awesome.
- What is it?
- You'’ll see.
- Skin thigh, shows it all off.
- For the party.
- How are you doing?
- I'’m good. I'’m good, I'’m okay.
She'’s doing
better now, you know.
Um, did you speak to A.J.?
I did and...he spoke
to the producers
and he did everything he can do
but that time slot is gone.
- '’I'’m sorry, he'’s--'’
- It'’s alright. It'’s alright.
Okay, he was just my last hope.
Isn'’t there anything
that can be done?
- We can submit it next year.
- Next year, that'’s good.
- You sure you okay?
- Yeah, I'’m fine. I'’m fine.
I'’m getting better
by the moment.
- Um, I have some good news.
- Good news? What?
I made a phone call
and I invited Michael
to join me
at the Marlin party.
- And he said, yes.
- '’Great.'’
- He'’s gonna meet me there.
- Great. Good.
What was that nudge for?
- What?
No, you elbowed her,
why did you elbow her?
Nothing, I would, nothing.
I'’m.. That'’s great.
I, ah, invited A.J.
- A.J., the man?
- '’Yes, A.J., the man.'’
Yeah, this one even
has pubic hair.
[laughing]
It'’s a family restaurant.
- I'’m starving.
- Look, we gotta get menus.
- '’Cause I have to go.
- Talking on the phone there.
Menu.
[phone ringing]
[Lena]
'’I got it.'’
Michelle, would you
please hurry.
You'’re gonna be late
for your own party.
'’I'’m almost ready.'’
'’Oh.'’
Look at you,
you pulled your hair back.
- You like?
- Yeah. It'’s pretty.
- Thanks.
- Looks very nice.
- Who was on the phone?
- They hung up.
- Star 69.
- Like I got time.
Since you'’re ready,
do me a huge favor.
I left my Viata Spice lipstick
in your car. Would you--
I like what
you have on.
- It'’s too dark.
- No, it'’s good.
I hate it, please.
Fine. Then we'’re leaving '’cause
I told Michael I'’d meet him
at the Marlin at 8 O'’clock.
I'’m not gonna be late.
- Okay.
- You know what I'’m saying.
- I hear you.
- Alright.
- Thanks.
- Yeah. Alright.
[door shuts]
[slow music]
Looking for this?
And..
...I think that
this belongs to you too.
I want you
to be my wife.
[slow music continues]
Jasmine Hampton, will you
please, please marry me?
- Say yes.
- Come on. Say yes.
'’Say yes.'’
Yes.
♪ Falling with your hearts
♪ Darlin'’, find a way.. ♪
♪ Celebration
♪ Celebration is a rough
form of game ♪
♪ Won'’t stop the chart
till the world retains ♪
♪ Celebration all up
in the sky ♪
- Yeah.
- Cheers.
♪ You'’ll have dance hard
to a mass ♪
♪ When I hear the cop scream
just double style rock ♪
♪ I reach for the sky
Don'’t stop till we stop ♪
♪ Times we didn'’t wanna
make it to the car ♪
♪ Anything that we feel
is way to me.. ♪
Lena, come on, come on, girls,
we are going upstairs.
- Coming.
- Yeah.
♪ In California me
venuejam packed ♪
♪ In the Island
which I really love ♪
♪ No matter if you'’re red or
yellow, white or you'’re black ♪
[soft music]
♪ Ever since we met.. ♪
- '’Hey.'’
- '’How are you?'’
- Hey.
- Hey, how you doin'’?
- Good.
- Nice to see you again.
- Glad you could make it.
- I wouldn'’t miss it.
Hey, Morgan.
How you doing?
Oh, my God.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- You remember, Lena?
- '’Yeah, nice to see you again.'’
Yeah. You too.
And Jazz and this is Michael,
Jazz'’s fiancé.
- How are you?
- Nice to meet you.
You too.
Hey, I'’m sorry
about your presentation.
I tried to get
extension on the deadline--
It'’s alright. It'’s okay.
Everything happens for a reason.
I'’m getting that job next year
though and speaking of which
if you guys send
anymore flowers to my office--
- Me.
- Oh, it'’s you?
I just can'’t tell you how sorry
I'’m about the whole thing.
Really, it'’s okay.
It'’s okay.
Um, I have to check on some
things. Can I show you around?
- Yeah. Sure.
- Okay.
- '’Bye.'’
- Bye.
- Mmm.
- Mh-mm.
- She really did a great job.
- Yeah, she'’s great.
- She'’s beautiful.
- She'’s really great.
Well, okay, lovebirds. I guess
I'’ll go show myself around.
- See ya.
- Bye. See ya.
- Bye.
- Bye, have fun.
Fuckin'’ wind.
- Scott.
- Wassup.
What you doin'’ here?
My band'’s got a gig here,
playing on the weekends.
Your band? I thought
you guys broke up.
Broke up?
Oh, yeah. Um..
You never
like gold chains.
[soft music continues]
Hey-hey, so,
why-why you leavin'’?
'’Cause I don'’t really
see any reason to stay.
See, Scott. I don'’t wanna hear
about your band anymore.
I don'’t wanna see
your new headshots.
I don'’t wanna hear
your new music.
Fact the truth is
I don'’t want anything to do
with...people like yourself.
Bet you'’ll be wanting this,
sooner or later?
Oh, I want it, Scott
but I just don'’t need it.
You know how that goes.
[crowd chattering]
[music continues]
It'’s really nice to..
It'’s really nice
to see you again.
If I have it my way you'’d
be seeing a lot more of me.
Maybe I could even
take you somewhere
and talk to you about all the
things your last lover forgot.
I think I said touch.
Well, if you don'’t mind I'’d like
to know how I'’m touching first.
♪ Wo-oo-oo
♪ I don'’t know nothing
about you ♪
♪ But I could be in love
♪ Yes, I could be in love ♪
[reggae music]
♪ People, are you ready
for the original rap? ♪
♪ If you'’re ready
just dance and follow me ♪
♪ Sweet music
in all the world ♪
♪ No time to work
No time to stress ♪
♪ I tell your fullness
still not gone yet ♪
♪ I wouldn'’t mind talking
or just romancing ♪
♪ Like little children
one big family ♪
♪ That'’s how we live ♪
♪ I like fire
Don'’t try to cool me down ♪
♪ '’Cause I can'’t stop rocking
till I see the rising sun ♪
♪ Don'’t cool me down ♪
♪ Mr. Dj, don'’t cool me down ♪
♪ Man, oh, don'’t mind
Don'’t cool me down ♪
♪ Tell the people
don'’t cool me down ♪
♪ Police man, now
stroll me down ♪
♪ Me tell the girl
now chill me down ♪
♪ Me tell a boy now
pull me down ♪
♪ One more time
don'’t cool me down ♪
[Jasmine]
'’Do you feel like, um,
sex is overrated?'’
No. No way.
In fact, I was only thinking
the other night
that orgasm is like
a taste from God
of what it'’s gonna
be like in heaven.
And it'’s like every now and then
we get this like waft
of like amazing feeling
and it'’s like
when we like we'’ve come back
through different life times
and where a point
where we'’re totally elevating
to another level.
It'’s like that'’s how
it'’s gonna feel
like you'’d be...totally
in the orgasm state. Period.
♪ Let'’s do it ♪
♪ Let'’s undo it ♪
♪ Come on
Come on ♪
♪ Girl talk ♪ Do it
♪ Girl talk
♪ Girl talk, girl talk
♪ Do it ♪ Girl talk
♪ Girl, you can do it
♪ I'’ve been through hell,
hell tonight ♪
♪ Girl, you can do it
♪ I'’ve been through hell,
hell tonight ♪
♪ Girl talk, girl talk
♪ Baby
♪ Hey
♪ Come on ♪ Do it
♪ Girl talk ♪ Oh, yeah
♪ Hey
♪ Come on, baby
♪ Do it
♪ Let'’s do it ♪♪ Do it
♪ Let'’s do it ♪
♪ Come on, come on
♪ Let'’s do it ♪♪ Do it
♪ Let'’s do it ♪
♪ Come on ♪ Do it
♪ Let'’s talk tonight ♪
♪ Baby
♪ Let'’s do it ♪
♪ Let'’s do it
Let'’s talk tonight ♪
♪ Hey, hey
♪ Girl, you can do it
♪ I'’ve been through hell,
hell tonight ♪
♪ Girl, you can do it
♪ I'’ve been through hell,
hell tonight ♪
♪ Do it
♪ Let'’s talk tonight ♪
♪ Let'’s do it ♪
♪ Come on, come on
♪ Let'’s do it ♪♪ Do it
♪ Let'’s do it ♪
♪ Come on, come on
♪ Do it
♪ Hey, hey, hey
♪ Girl talk
♪ Do it
♪ Girl, you can do it
♪ I'’ve been through hell,
hell tonight ♪
♪ Girl talk ♪