i
May I help you?
I hope so
I'm looking for the
Mayfield nuclear power plant
Mayfield, you're way off
That's 300 miles away
Oh no
I've got a map in the shack
I could show you how to get there
Great
Here we are
See you go straight back past the
Breast Western
I mean the Best Western
and you hop on the freeway
and head south
Oh great, thank you so much
Oh, could you do me one small
favor though?
Anything I can
Sit down
Hey
Let's go
Let's move it out
Move it
Your attention please students
Varsity and junior varsity
football practise out on the track
in 15 minutes
Dude, so what's up with Winorski
and the cheerleader with
the big sweater?
I mean he's supposed to be
our coach and he's making
a meal out of it
What?
You're just the new guy
Hi, let me guess
the Mayfield ballet club
What are you? A wise ass new guy?
No, no, Leny, Leny Slater
How are you doing?
Leny. Well that sounds like
a real woos name to me
So Leny
what's that short for huh?
Leonard?
Leny the lezbo
I hadn't thought about that one
You guys must be from
the literary society huh?
Where are you from Leonard?
I told you it's Leny
I'm from the Broncs
The Broncs, New York
Oh, big city b0)!
Tough guy huh?
Not especially
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you writing a book?
Yeah, maybe I am
Then leave that chapter out
Eddy, what are you gonna
take that shit?
Kick his pussy ass
Oh, now you're gonna kick my ass
No, man
Hey come on he's from New York
Hey come on
You got some sort of aiming
problem or something?
Shit
I'm here
Martial arts huh?
Standing
Come on
What's wrong with the defense here
Oh yeah
Oh, oh, that's so pretty
Come on Eddy, kick his ass
Come on
Hey you kids
You guys know the rules about
loitering in the halls after hours
It's all right sir.
My new friends here
were just showing me some
new dance moves, you know
You son of a bitch
Hey, what's the matter with you?
Are you deaf?
Get out of here
All right, all right, all right
Thanks anyway
See you later Broncs boy
Great
It was a pleasure to meet you
You guys too. It's my pleasure
Take care
How you doing sir
It's Leny, Leny Slater
Nice to meet you too
Bye Guys
Shit. These lids suck
Tell me about it
Did you see this thing about this
warehouse in Greenville?
Sarge mentioned it in briefing
this morning
He did. t's sick
Yeah. Big white truck
We're supposed to keep
an eye out for it
Like it's gonna come
through Mayfield
Right me finish the routine
That's one and two and three
and four and five
Great job girls
We're done for today
Hit those showers
Hi Eddy, how are you doing?
Hi Stacy
Hey Eddy, come here
What?
You check this out
All right
Hey, I've got to go you guys
What's up?
Take a look at the new kid
Mr. Hotshot
That's all right
We'll take care of him later
All right?
Dude let's go
Pull over and get rid of them
Watch it, I'll cover you
Yeah
ls there a problem officer?
Sorry ma'am
We had a report on a truck like
this so we had to check it out
Oh, I can understand that
I do have a small problem
though, that you might be able to
help me with
Oh, and what might that be?
Well, I hate cops
Unit 6 to base
Officer down on State Street
1100 block
In the pursuit of suspect
heading south
Big white truck
Requesting back up
as soon as possible
Let's check
Gosh, he's so cute
I think he likes you
Shut up. He does not
He does, I'm serious
I've saw him
I saw the way he was looking
I swear
That was good
we'll practice later
Yeah
But I don't get that part where
we're turning around
We'll work it out
I'm nervous
I think he likes you
Come on
No I do, I've seen it
No, I'm serious
I saw, I watched him
He's watching you
He has that thing in his eye
Really?
Yeah, I think he does
Oh god
Stacy
Oh my god!
Get out of here Get out of here
What is it?
Come on pervert
Slap my ass in the
guy's locker room
and you're calling me a pervert
Come on wise guy
You're coming with me
Hold on there big boy
Not until you meet my parents
Don't worry, that can be arranged
And my books
can I get my books please?
And watch the ear
Pull in
This is as good as it's gonna get
Thank you Ray
He's a real wise ass this one
I can handle it from here
Well...
You know, you may have gotten away
with this sort of behavoir in
the New York City school system
but I can assure you that we will
not tolerate it here at Mayfield
Look Mr. Vogel I didn't...
But Mr. Vogel nothing
Mr. Slater, you've already gotten
off on the wrong foot here
and I can further assure you that
if you do not straighten up
and fly right
the only school that you will be
attending will be reform school
Sir I'm really not a bad guy
once you get to know me
Look, it's obvious I've been
framed for something I didn't do
Ah, yes, that is just what the
owner of this said
And he is now doing, oh let's see
5 to 7 years
in the state penitentiary
thanks to my diligence
Sir, you got me all wrong
All right. have it your way
Perhaps a little detention will
give you the opportunity to
consider your future here
at Mayfield
Let's say 3 weeks
3 weeks, for what?
You know, you're right
let's make it 4 weeks
But Mr. Vogel I...
One more word and it could be five
What the hell is...
Security report to the yard
immediately please
You sit down right there
and wait for me young man
Yes sir
Shit
He}! YOU guys freeze
Piece of cake
Take it inside
Round up the strays
We're here for a while
What do you people think
you are doing here?
Anything we want
My god. Are you the proprietor of
this establishment?
Don't hurt me. Don't hurt me
I asked you a question
Yes, I'm the principal
Good, looks like we'll be here for
a while and we require
some hospitality
What do you want?
What we need is cooperation
and that means
you only speak when
you are spoken to
Now turn around and walk
I'll get Boomer
Quickly
Attention all students, faculty
and personnel still in the building
Please report at once to
the assembly hall
This is an emergency
Please everyone go to
the assembly hall
This is not a drill
Now the police
Tell them to keep their distance
or we start throwing out corpses
Young teenage corpses
Hey Stacy, what do you say we
hang out here for a little while?
But they said it was an emergency
It's probably just a fire drill
or something
I don't know
Oh come on, I'll protect you
Oh yeah, and who's going to
protect me from you
Me?
Yeah
If you can't trust me
who can you trust?
Stacy, come on
I'll meet you there
Yeah, come on Betty
you and me babe
Cool
Just stay calm Mr. Vogel
we'll get you out of this mess
all right
Give them whatever they want
Ok
They won't release their demands
until the FBI gets here
Get me a perimeter set up
I want a SWAT team
Get me fire department
bomb squad, EMS
What about the press?
No, no, leave them out of this
till we know more ourselves
ls your boy still in there?
Not likely no
not after school hours
Jesus
I thought this is where you come
to get rid of this kind of crap
in your life
Guys, guys, hey listen to me
Don't go near the assembly hall
all right?
You got to help me to get everyone
together and get them
out of the building
Eat shit dirtbag
Listen to me man
We still ain't finished with you
city boy
Fine, fine, let's go outside
I'll let you kick my ass
all you want
Just let's do it outside huh?
You woos
Faggot
Let's go boys and girls
to the assembly hall
Let's cut come on, let's cut
All right, all right
Come on, we haven't got all day
Let's go
Hey man, something bad is cooking
Sit
Boomer, phase one
Yes sir
Check for stragglers
Now that I have your attention
You all have the great opportunity
today to be a part of history
in the making
Now you can either sit back and
enjoy it
or watch it face down in a pool
of your own blood
It's your choice
Makes no difference to me
Damn
I shouldn't have bought that
second milk
Who was that?
Who cares, they're gone now
Come on Eddy
let's get out of here
The girls are going to be
wondering where I'm at
Then let them wonder
You know I do have a reputation
to think of here
Yeah, so do I
Wait, did you here that?
Sounds like sirens, listen
Will you come on
Listen
Chief Slater
What options are you taking
to apprehend the terrorist?
We're considering all our options
What about the hostages?
That's our priority
Is it true the terrorists have
possession of the new top secret
missile guidance system?
Yes, I'm sure they have the
atomic bomb too
Now please, just let us
do our jobs okay?
The warehouse at Greenville
we've got reports that
that's where it was stored
Do you?
Chief is it true
you were one of
the officers
in the
World Trade Center bombing?
That's a matter of record
Is it also true that your son is
a student here?
Well, if it isn't Leonard
Guys, you've got to get out of
here right now
So it was you in the locker room
wasn't it?
Hey me and you got some unfinished
business Broncs boy
I told you, my dad told me
not to fight girls
You son of a bitch
Aiming problem again eh?
That's it man
That is it. You are dead
Do me a favor will you
chill your boyfriend out all right?
We've got to do something to get
out of here right now
Hey, you're not getting out of it
this time city boy
He's not my boyfriend
Forget that all right
We've just got to get out of here
Wait, wait
what are you talking about?
What am I talking about?
I'm talking about a half dozen
heavily armed dudes who blew away
a cop and that sorry ass security
guard Ray
I'm also talking about some bitch
they got with them
Some crazy bitch who almost blew
my head off when I was
in Vogel's office taking the rap
for your boyfriend's little
peeping Tom stunt
That was you?
I don't know what
he's talking about
You son of a bitch
Forget that now
We just got to get out of here
Hey, hey, wait a minute
I'm not going anywhere till I know
what the hell's going on
What, you don't trust me?
No
Yeah, well then I dare you
to follow me
Come on
Come on tough guy
All right fine, let's go
I want snipers on the rooftops
there, there and there
Tell them to report any movement
My men can pick of anything
within 500 yards
Well that's all we need
dead bodies in the school yard
I don't want heroes Hawkins
I want hostages all right?
Shooters are a last resort
Whatever you say chief
Any word?
Nothing
Want me to call the feds again?
Yeah, find out what's keeping them
Well except for the
Empire State Building
I'd swear I was back in New York
Chaos, potential for bloodshed
At least there I can
get a good cup of coffee
Yes?
Excuse me sir
I have to go to the bathroom
Wait
You have to make some kind
of arrangement for them
Shut up
Number one or number two?
Number one
You may go in the corner
That's the last of them
Boomer
Yes sir
Phase two
Shit, you're right
It looks like they've got some
kind of bomb or something
Whatever it is it ain't good
What now genius?
You just get out of here
while you got a chance
What about you?
There's a gun in Vogel's office
What are you crazy?
Those dudes have machine guns
I can see that guy
I think we should call
the police guys
That's a good idea
A really good idea
Chances are they're probably in
the dark about what's going on
in here
You're nuts
I'm getting the hell out of here
You go ahead if you want to
I want to help
Fine come help
Wait, wait, wait
what is with you people?
Come on
FBI will be here soon
Good
He put it in a desk or drawer
somewhere
Call 9110k?
Shit
What?
The bastard left the mike on
I'll get him
Shut up
Speak
This is police chief Slater
I have FBI agents
Doogan
Doogan and
Du mford
Put them on
This is special agent Doogan FBI
Ah, a woman, I like that
You're very perceptive
Who am I talking to?
That's unimportant
What is important is that you call
your men out of this building
or I start throwing dead teenagers
out the window on time for
the six o'clock news
You got anybody in there?
No, of course not
We don't have anyone in there
You wouldn't lie to me would you?
You got anybody
pulling a cowboy act?
My men follow my orders
I follow yours
We have no one in there
I give you my word
Very well, I guess I'll just have
to take care of it on my end
Now don't do anything rash
We're here to make a deal
What the hell is it you want?
0k, listen closely, because I'm
only going to say it once
We are in possession of enough
explosives to level this entire
building and everyone in it
I get the picture
Get to the point
Right now they are strategically
placed and armed for maximum impact
We have several hostages
Just imagine what they would look
like if we were to detonate
I couldn't agree with you more
Now what do we do about it?
Oh, it's very simple
First we require the
federal government to completely
disband and dissolve all its
military, law enforcement and
bureaucratic agencies
Second, all assets and arms
in possession of these agencies
shall be turned over to our cause
the Free Peoples Militia
for distribution to their
rightful owners
namely the American tax payers
We have a loony on our hands
You can't be serious
Does the term dead serious
ring a bell?
Now I suggest you get started
You have 2 hours or you're going
to be sifting through debris
scattered over a 3 mile radius
Oh and don't try anything foolish
The slightest sign of aggression
and I will automatically detonate
without further discussion
Wait, hello, hello
Damn
Anybody seen what
they took in there?
The rumor is they have
a big crate
Four of them carried it in
It's big enough
If you have any bright ideas
now would be a good time
How long to break the code?
Well, it's more sophisticated
than I thought
2, maybe 3 hours
You got 2, make it work
There's still some strays
wandering the halls
I want them found
Now
Come on
Shit
That's it man
That is it
I'm out of here
Let's go
He's right
How far do you guys think
you're gonna get huh?
I've seen these guys shoot ok
They don't miss
And what do you think you're
gonna do? Stop them?
Shit
Great
Broncs boy here is gonna fight
them off with an empty gun
Let me tell you something
loud mouth all right
It doesn't take much to get in to
fights in the Broncs
The real talent comes from getting
out of fights with a good bluff ok?
I don't know guys
What are we gonna do?
0k, just chill ok, relax
Just get back in the can
stay there and be quiet
Look I might be scared
but I'm not gonna
go hide in the bathroom
All right fine
What about you?
What are you gonna do?
0k, what's your plan asshole?
Follow me
There's someone else, find him
You got it
They bought it
And Boomer?
He's got 2 hours
He better figure it out
He's supposed to be the best
He'd better be
Hey, I tell you man
we searched the whole school
Yeah, but we're not going back
till we check it twice
Listen, we can do this a lot
better if we split up
That's a good idea
Why don't you take this floor
You take the basement
I'll take the first floor ok?
Let's go.
Got you
Dude, what are you doing?
That's gas
I know just let me show you
Just help me
Are you crazy man.
Come on, just do he says.
Let's go
Stacy, get those, get those
Let's go...
Come on man
Stacy get in here, get in here
Let's go
Come on
Eddy man, you got a cigarette?
Why?
Just give me one
Come on, hurry up, give him one
Come on
All right, all right
Got a light?
Would you like me to smoke
it for you too?
Just give me a light man
I want every call going in and
out of that building monitored
right through here
And get me the local utility
company and the lines
Cut off the electricity pronto
Got it
How good are your sharp shooters?
That's taking a chance
Ok
You cut their power
flush them outwith tear gas
and cut them off one by one
as they come out the door
Outstanding ma'am
W0, wo, wo, Miss Doogan
It's Agent Doogan
Yes, of course it is
You do remember that the bad guys
have hostages in there?
Yeah
I figure a 33 to 48 percent loss
I can live with that
Really?
How sad for you
oh?
Your from New York aren't you?
No, not originally, no
I like happy endings and if we
don't get in there
If they blow up that school
you could be looking at
100 perecnt loss
Precisely my point
What is it you suggest we do?
Give in to his demands?
I suggest you think with your
heart not just with your badge
One body bag is going to be one
too many for the parents of
those kids
Let's get them all out
He's not gonna do what
I think he's gonna do
Shh
He's gonna do it
Watch it
Let's go, come on
Come on
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Mayfield power, can I help you?
This is the Mayfield police
I need to speak to whoever
is in charge
That will be Mr. Johnson
One moment while I connect you
to his office
Not now, wait! Wait!
Mr. Johnson's office
This is detective Worshak
of the Mayfield PD
I'm calling for Mr. Johnson
One moment please
Detective Worshak on 3
Detective, what can I do for you?
Sir, we've got a problem and we
need your cooperation
A group of terrorists have taken
control of the high school
Terrorists?
What are you talking about?
Look, this is an emergency
We have a hostage situation here
My two daughters go there
Jenny, get my wife on the phone
I don't have time for this
Turn on your radio or your TV
if you need conformation
Jane it's Jenny
Mr. Johnson
I've got your wife on the line
Well check if the kids are ok
One second detective
Are the kids there with you?
0k, they're there and
they're fine
But she says something terrible
is happening at the highschool
Sorry detective
now what can I do for you?
I need you to cut all the power
to the school
You don't understand
That means shutting down the
whole south west quadrant
I don't care if it's
the whole state
Just do it
Ok, 0k
Call the plant
get Berny on the line
Tell him to be ready for my order
to shut down the whole
south west grid
I'll leave the line open
Well if we get disconnected
you can reach me direct at
5555646
Got it, hold on
Whatever you say
I've got Berny
Be rny
Yeah?
Look, be ready to shut down the
whole thing on my order
What ever you say boss
Detective, detective
Will you give us an update
on the negotiation
Right now you know
as much as we do
We know that chief Slater's son
is somewhere up in that highschool
and we need to know what...
Hey, hey, if they find out his
son's inside that school
they'll use him and kill him
if we don't meet their demands
Would you want that to happen
to your son?
Shit
More people in there
than I thought
Guys
What?
Oh man, that's Mr. Vogel
Or was Mr. Vogel
Oh my god
Shh, Shh
Go, go, go, let's go
What happened?
Get back to work
You find them and you
bring them to me
Got it boss
You obviously don't take my
threats seriously
What the hell is going on in there
Don't play dumb with me
This little stunt of yours just
cost you one hostage
Wait, we didn't do anything
Then you should have prevented it
You and you, up
Now
Pick him up and follow me
We got a clean shot at two of them
first floor window
Take them out
No, no, hold your fire
I've got your son on the phone
What? Where is he?
He's in the principal's office
What? Leonard?
Leonard, are you all right?
Boss
What the hell are
you doing in there?
Well, you told me to spend more
time at school didn't you?
Leonard, get out of there
immediately, you hear me?
All right, I'll try, I'll try
Listen
here's the situation here ok?
All right, there's 5 of them left
they have 13 hostages
and they're all in
the assembly hall
And most of them are kids
A couple of them are teachers
And Eddy, Stacy and myself
we managed to stay hidden so far
Oh, by the way, you know
Mr. Vogel the principal here?
He's kind of dead
Yeah I know that
You know something ain't right
also they have a bomb
And if you have a bomb wouldn't
you put it in the basement
plant it down there
some maximum damage you know?
Yeah why?
Well they got it on the
second story
I mean the second floor
It's pointing out a window
like they're going to shoot
it at something
Leonard listen to me
Leny, Leny come on, they're coming
Got to go Pa
Speak to you later
Leonard, listen to me
Leonard
Worshak
Get me air reserve on the line
Leave him alone
What did you say?
Nothing
That's what I thought
Well?
No luck boss
If I was counting on luck
I would have ordered Lubritarian
Keep looking
Yes sir
Come on boys, come on
Wait a minute
Where are we going?
Shop class
Shop class?
General Wainright
Yeah General, this is Leo Slater
I'm the chief here in Mayfield
I need some information please
Oh yes
what can I do for you chief?
Have you had any security problems
there at the base lately?
Any robberies?
What do you mean?
I mean are you missing any bombs
or missiles?
That's classified
information chief
I can't deny or confirm that
information without approval
from Washington
Well listen General
here's what I can confirm
We have a situation here
and if your bomb is part of it
then you have a situation too
Now you can either talk to me or
you can talk to the media soon
as they're sniffing my hind leg
and I'm running out of answers
Now listen here whoever you are
General you listen to me
Now we have something pointing
at our nuclear power plant
I need to know if that's a problem
Jesus
Off the record
Yeah, whatever
0k, but you didn't get it from me
Shit
Get me Doogan
Yeah
Boomer, progress report
Almost got it
Excellent, please continue
I'm beginning to get excited
Your enthusiasm overwhelms me
There's no need for sarcasm
We stand to make quite a fortune
when all this is through
And with two less people to share
it with
Yes, it is unfortunate
We could make it even less
Let's not get too greedy
At least until our little task
is completed
But you won't be upset if we
inherit a few extra shares?
The fewer loose ends the better
And I know how to handle
the loose ends
Oh yes you do
I've noticed you seem to have
quite a knack for it
Well, I just pay attention to
detail that's all
Don't be modest Tanya
I truly believe you have an
honest to go blood lust
I just do what needs to be done
Yes, but you can't tell me you
don't get some small measure of
pleasure from it
Oliver my darling
one should enjoy one's work
Don't you think?
Oh, absolutely
All right
Go in the supply room and get all
the empty bottles you can
Dude this is no time to be working
in a class project
This isn't a class project
trust me, just go
Come on, let's just go
Want some little girl?
I got two of them boss
Oh shit
Come on, come on
When you want your girlfriend
you know where to find me
Yeah, I'll take care of it
Mayfield Electric
they're ready to cut the power
Yeah, this is Doogan FBI
pull the plug
You got it
Be rny
Yeah
Kill it all, now
You got it
Here it goes
What's that?
You take him up to the
assembly hall
I'll handle it
Ok
When I give the word I want you
to go in and secure the area
Your siege plan won't work Doogan
I'm in command here
Well good, then you become famous
for a nuclear fallout that could
make Chernobyl look like
a weenie roast
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about an armor
piercing arrowhead missile
with a state of the alt
guidance system pointed directly
at a nuclear power plant
and that makes me nervous
Don't be ridiculous
He didn't mention a thing about
that in any of his demands
or his threats
Well maybe this guy is more of a
nut case than you
give him credit for
It's our boy
I'm growing tired of your
silly antics
You don't really think turning off
the power is going to stop us
do you?
Well
it's the atomic energy commission
What?
So they can't disband unless they
shut down nuclear power plants
all over the country
And as you may know we here in
Mayfield get our electricity from
a nuclear power plant
Who is this?
This is Slater
And where is Agent Doogan?
I'm right here
They said they have to cut off all
the other sectors before they
can shut down the plant
And you expect me to believe this?
I'm just telling you what
they told me
Well, I'm telling you that as long
as the power is off
I'm going to be
disciplining students
What does that mean?
Figure it out
That's my direct line
I have to call you back
Johnson, you still there?
Yeah
Yeah, it's all been cut
I know, but now we have to have
you turn it back on
Excuse me for saying this but do
you guys know what the hell
you are doing down there?
We're trying our best to keep
sixteen kids alive
Be rny
Yeah
Look, you're not going to believe
this but
You got to be kidding
Here we go
What the hell are you doing here
there's still one missing
You want me to go get him myself
He's just a kid
I'll go get him
Well I wish someone would
I know how to handle little boys
What is your friend's name?
Won't you tell me?
Why?
Because
Leny, Leny Slater
Shut up
Thank you
Wait, Slater?
Be sure to bring him back alive
I want to see this kid
Arrowhead 3 to arrowhead 1
Come in
Mission accomplished
all systems go
Guidance system is locked
on the main reactor
one hour and counting
Good work
Boomer, what if they were to shut
down the main reactor
No difference
the core would still be hot
Thank you
Would you kindly stay with the
unit until we have captured
the intruder
Affirmative
I hate school
Freeze mother fucker, hands up
Hands up, now
Right, hand it over
Hand it over now
Come get it
Come on boy
Come on
Drop it or
I'll blow his brains out
Boomer, toss me the detonator
Don't do it man
I said now
You are one sick bitch lady
Thank you
Now drop the pea shooter Rambo
Don't even try it
You've been a bad, bad boy Leny
You're not so tough after all
are you?
Come on, move it
You know my dad told me
not to fight girls
Good advice
In your case
I'll make an exception
Luther, send Black up the
west stairway
We've got him cornered
You think you can handle that?
I'll back her up
You better hope we find
your boyfriend
He's not my boyfriend
What a Pity
You'd make such a lovely couple
Dying in each other's arms
The only ones that are going to be
dying in each other's arms are you
and that demented slut
Hey man
No
My god
No respect
Shit
Wow
Reminds me of home
Oh Leny
It's all speculation
I can't advise evacuation of the
whole city without some
positive threat
Well there won't be any point
evacuating once they fire
that thing, will there?
We're not even sure they have
the missile
If we start evacuating the whole
city now, there'll be more deaths
from sheer panic than there would
be if they blew up the school
It's your son
Leny, are you all right?
Yeah paps I'm fine, I'm fine
but listen
They've got this thing
It's set, it's armed
it's ready to go off in less
than an hour
I overheard them saying the
guidance system is locked on
the main reactor
Look I want you to get out of
there immediately Leny
can you hear me?
I'm not sure about that dad
Look, this lady they got with them
she's got some sort of detonator
I think it's for the missile
Self-destruct detonator
It's the only thing that'll
stop it now
We have to get that
All right Leny
you're doing a good job
Good work in there
I want you to get out immediately
do you hear me?
No can do Paps
Look, they've still got
Stacy and Eddy
They've got me pinned down
The good news is there's only
three of them left
Can he get to the detonator?
This is a 17 year old kid who
skips physics class for Christ sake
Our only other choice is a
full frontal assault
Paps, Paps, you still there?
Yeah
Paps, I'm scared, what do I do?
All right Leny, listen to me
Oh great sure, sure
Yeah listen Paps, you want me to
throw in a cure for cancer
while I'm at it?
Your our best chance son
All right Paps, just let me ask
you one more thing all right?
What's that?
Can we move back to the Broncs?
I guarantee it
All right, I'll call you
Shit
I should have hit him up for a car
Hey
You scared the shit out of me
All three of these rooms are
connected, I checked them all
Well
I know he's around here somewhere
I can sense his fear
I'll check this hall
Oh, sure
Just get the detonator from the
terrorist, disarm the missile
No problem
Well I haven't checked the
teacher's lounge yet
so let's go check that out first
The receiver is warm
he can't be far
Check all these doors and closets
I'll get this side
All right
Great
Put it down right there
Not long now
Come here you little prick
Game is over Leny
Are you gonna come out like a
good little boy
or do I have to come in there
and get you
Promise you won't hurt me
I promise
Somehow I find that
hard to believe
Come on lady, you promised
You right Leny
but I had my fingers crossed
Now say goodbye
Well the old saying is true
The pen really is mightier
than the sword
Come on, You can't print that
Give me your number
Let me take that
Oh chief, my wife brought over
the best damn coffee in town
Your right
Remind me to have all out shoot
outs at your place from now on
I don't want to pry but I heard
your son had some problems
at the schools back home
Yeah, well, you know, good kid
bad environment, shit happens
Must have been tough on you when
you lost your wife
Yeah, well that's one of the
reasons we came here
New beginning, fresh start
that kind of thing
Funny thing is that Mayfield's
usually a nice quiet place
I've heard, that was our plan
In fact the craziest thing I
remember happening was when
the environmentalists used to come
protesting the plant
And they were peace loving
hiPPV TYPES
Well that's what I don't get
Warshak, I mean why would anybody
be coming here to Mayfield to
stage a war with the
Federal Government?
Besides the power plant
there's nothing
Unless you count the
reserve incinerator
What?
Federal reserve incinerator
It's here
You know it's where they
inventory and then destroy
all the old currency
I've never heard of that
Come on, that's our claim to fame
We burn more money than
any town in the country
How much at any given time?
I'm sure it's millions
Well that's it
We're not dealing with a bunch
of right wing militant fanatics
here, we've got a common
bunch of thieves
The money if worthless
I mean all the serial numbers
are out of circulation
Who do you know who checks
serial numbers
Jesus Warshak
Hey everybody
Freeze
Shit Eddy, Eddy
you all right man?
Bastard shot me man
Yeah I can see that
Got to get you out of here man
Forget me man
He took everybody up to the roof
He made Stacy and the other guys
put on them suits
This
Yeah
Ok
Hey Lei'!!!
Yeah man
You're ok man
You too man
Eddy hang in there
I'll be back for you
I ain't going nowhere
Yeah I can see that
Stay cool
It makes sense, he wipes out the
town then I guess he and his
men take whatever they want
Well then why all the
free peoples militia bullshit?
He probably needed to buy
some time to figure out
the guidance system
I say we move in
I say do what you have to do
Go for it
Base, got some activity
up on the roof
Looks like five anti-radiation
suits surrounded by what could be
hostages
Can you get a clean shot?
Yeah, I think so
No, wait, wait, hold your fire
I'm in charge here Slater
Yeah but something's not right
There should only be three of
them left
Decoys, he must have put some of
those kids in those suits
This is not your call
Listen there are 16 hostages
in there, one of them is my son
This is not Wako
this is not Ruby Ridge
This is Mayfield and I'm not
gonna allow you to screw it up
You are way out of line
I don't give a shit, shut up
Hawkins, hold your fire
They're pulling back but they
left something behind
something big
Let me guess, an arrowhead
armor piercing missile
I'm no expert
but I'll take your word for it
That conformation enough
for you General?
Mr. Johnson's office
It's Warshak, put him on
It's Warshak
Detective, we've been watching
it on TV
You sure got your hands full
with that bunch
Those poor kids
Actually it's a lot worse
than you think
They've put a nuclear missile
on the roof and aimed it
at the reactor
What?
Those crazy bastards
I want you to shut the reactor
down right away
and get everyone the hell
out of there
It's impossible
Do you know how long it takes
to shut down a reactor?
No, how long?
12 to 24 hours, that's how long
Christ
Just send everyone home
Home, you got to be kidding
If that missile lands here
there won't be anything left
standing or alive for 100 miles
That bad huh?
No, probably worse
I'll leave the line open for you
Sound the alarm
Jenny, go home
Come on let's go
Come on, come on, come on, come on
come on
No, no, come on
Move it, in that room
Right there, come on
Let's go, let's go
Ain't gonna do much good
without this asshole
Well, well, well
you must be Leny Slater
No, to you it's Mr. Slater
Drop your gun
Drop it
I don't think so
Do it
Go ahead, you'll kill us all
You see we took the precaution of
planting explosive charges
throughout the building
It's out little failsafe mechanism
if you will
The charges are all wired to the
same frequency as the self-destruct
mechanism on the missile
In other words, if the missile
gets detonated prematurely
so does the school
No, you're bluffing
I don't bluff
0k, have it your way
Don't do it Leny
Ok
The detonator too
Carefully
Get out of here, everybody get out
School's out
Listen to me, go to the
assembly hall, get Eddy
and get out of the building
you hear me, get out of the building
This is not my day
Come on, come on, come on, come on
Go, g0, 9°
Len'!
Hawkins, move in
I'm still giving the orders
around here
Hawkins, move in
Yes ma'am
Guys, show time
Very good
We've got one on the roof
He's going for the missile
Take him out
Yes sir
Hey, good guy, good guy
They've got this whole place
wired to blow
We've got to get out of here
Look
Come on
Get the hell out of here
Johnson, they've launched it
Come on
Outside, go, go, go
Get in there, get in there
Get him, get him
Right, help me shut this thing off
Close the doors
Medics, come on, get in here
Come on, help him out
Leny are you all right?
Stacy, yeah I think so
Let's go find my dad
Come on, let's get out of here
Ok
You're all right
Hi Pap, good to see you
You are ok
Good. This is Stacy
Stacy, hi
Hi
I'm glad you're all right too
Thank you. Nice to meet you
You'd better call your folks
Yeah, you'd better do that
Dad
we're going to the prom together
0k, well it's gonna be outdoors
this year I think
Looks that way
Listen,
I'm gonna need some new clothes,
new shoes and spending cash
Could you rent me a limo
or something
Limo, yes, sure
See you
Love you dad
Love you too
Kids