Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Hey everybody, it's family night ♪
♪ We better take the
phone off the hook ♪
Family home
evening was huge in my home.
I know most members of the
church keep it pretty chill
with movie night or game night,
if you know Carrie Carrington,
she has no interest in being chill.
So we went all out.
Like clockwork, every Monday night,
we got together to plan our week,
share a spiritual lesson and
of course, eat lots of treats.
But of all those 936 Monday
nights in the first 18 years
of my life, there was one lesson
that stuck out to me the
most, eternal marriage.
My friends from school used
to ask, why our temples
look like Disney castle?
What can I say?
Members of The Church of Jesus
Christ of Latter-day Saints
are obsessed with marriage
in a good way of course.
I don't know what made
me more nervous,
getting down on one knee
or asking grandpa Robert
for permission.
Oh come on, it
wasn't that bad.
I couldn't get him alone.
And then one day, I had him
cornered while shoveling snow
and instantly like a
switch, my lips went numb.
Thought they were going to fall off.
Your lips fell off?
Yeah, almost.
Why were you so nervous?
You knew I was gonna say yes.
I mean as long as you didn't ask me
in front of a billion people.
Oh no, you made that
perfectly clear.
That goes for you boys too,
never ask a girl to marry
you in public.
It's very uncouth.
How can you ever be
sure that you wanna spend
the rest of your life with someone?
Heavenly father tells you it, dummy.
Tyler said the D word.
Tyler, not the D word, buddy.
Well I'm right, aren't I?
Yes and no.
We prayed about it and it
felt like the right thing
to do, but the rest was
on us, our commitment.
Part of what makes it makes it right
between two people is
because they choose for it
to be right and then they commit
themselves to that choice.
We prepare for
marriage our whole lives.
So it's a lot of pressure.
Best decision of my life.
Well it better be.
- Ewe.
- Oh come on,
it's not that bad.
Oh, who wants treats?
- Me, me, yes.
- Oh me.
Hey, hey, line up.
Come on, we're not animals.
Seeing the example
of how much my parents
loved each other
always made me excited for
the day I would meet the man
that would propose to me, the
man I would be with forever.
One Sunday when I about 13,
we did this activity in Young Women's
that really made me think.
Maybe you've heard of this.
All right girls, settled down.
Sister Valentine is going
to give each of you a piece
of paper and an envelope
because you're each going
to be writing a letter.
Can we just text it instead?
No, Hannah, you have to
actually write it down.
My dad says texting's a
terrestrial form of communication.
No one cares, Mykelle.
- Guys.
- Okay, can we all focus?
This is no ordinary letter
because it will be addressed to you.
Not that you of today,
but the you in the future
on the day of your wedding.
I've actually been
thinking a lot about this.
- Of course you have.
- I know this is subject
to change, but I currently
have zero interest
in the inferior gender.
So what am I supposed to write about?
Well maybe you could
write down the attributes
that you want in your future spouse.
How do you spell anesthesiologist?
Good one, Paige.
Can we put that he has
to be super hot,
like brother Carrington?
- Charlotte.
- You can put
whatever you want.
These letters are just for you,
you're not turning them in.
But we do want you to focus
on inner attributes and not
just what's on the outside.
What advice would you
give to your future self?
What qualities are important
to you in a healthy marriage?
Really put some thought into it.
Choosing who you wanna
marry is also choosing
who you wanna be.
Use it as a guide for the
type of person you wanna date.
I want you to hold on
to these letters, keep
them in a safe place.
You may wanna refer to them
over the next few years.
Bree honey, it's
your turn to set the table.
I'll be right down.
As excited as I was to write
that letter, for some reason,
I kind of forgot about it.
I put it in my hope chest,
but never really looked at it again,
that is until my wedding day.
Anyone who knows me knows
it was my absolute dream
to go to BYU, but not to
the Provo campus.
And no, I don't mean BYU, Idaho,
either.
You can't even wear sandals there.
I meant BYU, Hawaii.
I feel like if Brigham
Young would have seen
how beautiful Oahu is,
he would have said,
actually, this is the place.
Oh my gosh, look, a whale.
I lived in the best house
with the best roommates
and my new college bestie, Leilani,
that's her with the camera.
And what better place to
pursue my lifelong dream
of becoming a Marine biologist?
The professors are amazing
and the program is top notch.
I couldn't imagine going
anywhere else.
We studied hard and we
played hard too.
And I might have found
myself a boyfriend.
Not him, gross.
Nope, still not him.
Him, Thys Abner Chesterfield.
I know, right?
Only the most sought
after man at BYU, Hawaii.
He just got back from his
mission in Thailand last fall.
He's super smart,
athletic and amazing at
games, like freakishly.
I mean he could totally
be on college jeopardy
if he wanted, he's just
started taking the test.
We got to know each other
in a real organic way
because he was waiting for
his high school girlfriend
to get back from her mission
and I was about to leave
on my mission.
We both knew we had to break
up at the end of the semester,
but he was a really good guy
and a really good kisser.
So it wasn't going to be easy.
Gosh, I love Hawaii.
And then on Saturday, Thys took
me to hike the Ka'au Crater.
Mom, there are so many waterfalls
and the crater is huge,
you and dad would have loved it.
Seems like you're spending a lot
of time with this Thys fellow.
That's why it's gonna be
so hard to break up with him.
Oh don't think about it
as breaking up.
Think about it as supporting
each other's dreams.
Yeah, I like that.
And it's true, I mean
you’ll always hold
a really special place
in your heart for him.
But it's okay because
now that my papers are in,
I can look forward to
getting my mission call.
Wait, what did you say?
I submitted my papers this morning.
Oh!
I thought you were gonna
wait till Christmas break.
I know, but then I got
the most inspiring email
from Paige and I just
figured, you know, why wait?
Like the sooner I send them in,
the sooner I can get out
there and serve.
Oh honey, I am so excited for you.
Where do you think you're gonna go?
I don't know, but I really
hope I get to learn a language.
Oh, don't say that,
you don't wanna jinx it.
You know what happened to your father.
I mean, not that there's
anything wrong with Montana.
Absolutely, your father
was meant for Missoula.
But wouldn't Switzerland be great?
My gosh, please let it
be anywhere in Europe.
Anywhere in Western Europe,
we don’t want a Saratov situation.
You know what?
Bring it on.
I'm ready for anything
because I know that
wherever the Lord takes you
is where he wants you to be.
Oh, I am so writing this down.
Oh, you are just gonna
be the best missionary,
Bree, the best.
I am so jealous that they
lowered the age after my time.
I so would have served when I was 19.
Well, you became the best mom ever.
So I'd say you served that mission
- pretty well.
- Still serving,
thank you very much.
Tyler, get off the internet.
O-F-F you've already
used your screen time.
Speaking of screen time,
I had better scoot.
Nedra's having us over
for a potluck dinner
to meet her new boyfriend.
What, sister Rockwell.
I need all the details.
Well his name is Bud
and that's all I know,
but I'll give you the full
report tomorrow morning.
I can't wait.
Margaret, you know those
cookies are for the Folkners.
I am so proud of you, I love you.
I love you so much.
I miss you.
You guys, Bree
turned in her papers!
Hey, you be a good girl, yeah?
You be a good girl when
I'm gone, yeah, yeah?
I'm gonna miss you.
You know, you wouldn't have
to miss her if you took the
internship I offered you.
I know, oh, I wish I could.
I'm just giving you a hard time.
We're just gonna really
miss you around here.
Yeah me too a lot, but
you know what?
I'll be back before you know it.
Great 'cause that's an offer.
- Really?
- Yeah,
you have a talent for this.
I mean I really hope
that you stick with it.
Yeah, I plan on it.
Bye Patenka, I'll miss you.
So most people know that crabs
and lobsters are related, right?
They're both part of the
arthropod family.
Do you know what else is
part of that same family?
Spiders.
That's so crazy, that's so cool.
It is cool Thys, it's very cool.
I think I know what's bothering you.
- You do?
- Thys, I get it.
You're upset about saying goodbye.
Look, so am I, but let's
not think about it that way.
Just focus on all the fun
times we've had this semester,
all the memories we've made.
I mean, look, we're not breaking up,
we're just headed in different paths.
- So let's not be sad.
- Oh, I'm not sad.
I promise I'm not sad, I'm
actually like super happy.
Okay, well you don't
want to say it like that.
Gotta go, we gotta go,
- let's go, get up.
- Wait, what?
Okay, grab
your crab leg, let's go.
How's everybody doing
out there tonight?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a special treat
for you tonight but first, I'm
gonna need a lady volunteer.
Let me look around.
You, yes.
- What's your name?
- Bree Carrington.
- Is that a real name?
- Yes.
It sounds made up.
All right come on everybody,
give it up for Bree Carrington.
How many of you have seen
a dance battle?
Because tonight, Bree is going
to battle my man, Fanaue se Ein.
It's a fire night dance battle.
- What do I do?
- I don't know.
You're the one that volunteered.
Just give it your best, all right?
Yeah, that's a good start.
Come on everybody, give it up.
Let's check out the competition.
It's okay, Bree, we'll keep you safe.
It's safe to come out now.
Bree Christine Carrington,
will you marry me?
Do it!
Of course I will.
- I love you so much.
- I love you too.
Give it up for the newly
engaged couple, Bree and Thys.
Almost had a heart attack, Thys.
I mean, what happened to the plan?
My mission, your girlfriend.
She's not my girlfriend.
Okay but she was for like 10 years
and you're always talking
about how you're gonna
wait until she gets back
and you know, give the
relationship a real shot
because you owe each other that.
Oh, is that how I sound?
- Is that my voice?
- Just answer the question.
Okay, okay, fair.
What happened?
You happened, all right?
Yeah, I had a plan.
I thought I had everything figured out
but then you change all that.
Bree, you change everything.
No, what about my mission?
I know.
I'm sorry, I know, I just,
I didn't wanna lose you.
Did you talk to my dad?
Is that still a thing?
Yes, it is a thing.
Even with like feminism
and everything?
- Thys.
- No, sorry, yeah.
Look I'm sorry it came as
a shock to you, genuinely.
It came as a shock to me too, right?
'Cause yeah, we talked
about it, we talked about
it like a million times,
but every time I think
about losing you, I go nuts.
Like even right now, the
idea of us breaking up,
it hurts in a way that
I can't really handle.
Did you pray about it?
Everyday since I met you.
Like it feels right, right?
- I don’t know, maybe.
- Maybe?
She says maybe 'cause
like five seconds ago,
you were on stage going, oh my gosh,
yes Thys, of course I will.
Oh is that what I sound like?
Yes, yes, the cadence
is a little off,
but the tone is like dead on.
Okay, so what's your answer?
Because I can't really handle a maybe.
I think I just need a second
to process it and to pray about
it and talk to my parents.
But are we talking
like, days, months, years?
Like what are we thinking?
I don’t know exactly.
I mean, Thys, do you realize
that tonight is the first time
that you've ever even
said, I love you, to me?
True, but Bree, I mean it.
And you said it back, so
what does that tell you?
Did you mean it?
Yes, I love you.
I love you too.
I've wanted to say that for so long.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry if I scared you.
No, I messed up.
I should've talked to you,
of course I should've talked to you.
Take as long as you need
and maybe you don't say
anything about this to people.
I mean, just until you figure it out.
Of course.
Give it up for
the newly engaged couple,
- Bree and Thys.
- Look at my cinematography.
I captured you perfectly.
I was so scared.
Here it is in slow motion.
You look possessed.
I still can't believe he did it.
I can, that hull is crazy.
What'd your mom say?
I haven't called her yet.
What, it's like 03:00 a.m. for her.
I'll call her in the morning.
Wanna to watch "Black Mirror"?
I'm exhausted, I think
I'm just gonna go
to bed and read and do
a little praying, okay?
Fine, I'll just check my Finsta.
I told you to
delete that account.
If Obama has one, so can I.
♪ I never thought that ♪
♪ A guy like you would give
a girl like me a shot ♪
♪ I think maybe I like you
just a little ♪
♪ Or maybe it's a lot ♪
Okay, okay, would you
rather fight one duck,
but it's like the size of a
horse, like a real big duck,
or would you rather fight 100 horses
but they're the size of
like the little ducks?
Oh M gosh.
He's cute, I mean no
Neville Longbottom, but.
More like centered Diggory, R.I.P.
He's got six brothers.
Come on, choose.
Can I use a Katana?
No, no weapons, bare hands.
Will you marry me?
Yikes.
Of course I will.
♪ You were the one ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
Bree Christine
Carrington, will you marry me?
Should we wake Mykelle?
♪ You were the one ♪
Now with these final few breaths,
I want you to let go of any
negativity you may have had.
Any miscommunication with a loved one,
let it go and breathe.
Don’t let what you can't control you.
And have a good day, namaste.
Namaste.
All right my little early birds,
you go to catch that worm.
Oh and remember that the
Hawkins reception
is here tonight in the cultural hall.
So let's leave it a little bit better
than we found it, okay?
Nedra, your practices is
really improving.
Well it's no CrossFit,
but my boo says that
it's calming my temper,
- so I'll stick with it.
- Okay.
I really like what you said
about letting go of
what you can't control.
Oh good 'cause I stole
it from a fortune cookie.
I am running out of
Eastern wisdom, like fast.
Should I learn Sanskrit?
No.
There go the lsraelites
back to their idol worship.
I wonder about the
buzz is all about.
- Bree Carrington.
- Is that a real name?
- Yes.
- It sounds made up.
Bree Christine
Carrington, will you marry me?
Namaste, namaste, namaste, namaste.
Namaste!
Get up, we got 20 minutes
to get to the airport if we're
gonna catch the non-stop.
What's happening?
Honey, you know what?
I know what's not happening,
but I know what’s not happening,
this is not happening.
Okay, this is one of
those meme, gify things.
It's not a gif and it's not a joke.
Get your butt out of bed, let's go.
Okay, but you know what?
Before we go completely insane
and fly to Hawaii, hey,
let's give her a call.
Oh I tried calling her 37 times.
She's not answering her phone,
so I need to go and talk to
my daughter face-to-face.
Okay honey, we're not
really in the best
financial situation to
take the last minute trip.
I've got it all covered.
Nedra is gifting us her sky miles
and Holly is taking care of the kids.
Lodging and there's some food...
I don't care if we need
to build a lean
to on the beach and eat coconuts
for every meal, I need
to talk to my daughter.
We need to talk some sense into her.
I'm gonna pack.
I got you covered.
72 Hour kits, those are
for emergencies.
What do you call this?
Leilani wake up.
Someone posted my engagement video
and now everyone is reposting.
So messed up, who would do that?
You did it.
You're the only one who
had this video.
Who did you send it to?
I only sent it to Lily.
Lily Porter?
You might as well send it to Buzzfeed.
Leilani what were you thinking?
She promised
not to post it.
Well she lied.
That's so messed up.
Over 500 likes and no photo credits?
You don't understand,
my mom saw this.
Wait, my video is
how your mom found out?
I mean, she's literally
going to kill me.
What do I do?
I know a cave on the big island.
It's not much we can hide
in there until this all blows over.
I'm not hiding in a cave.
I'm just brainstorming.
- I just have to call her.
- What are you gonna say?
I just have to call her
and tell her the truth.
Maybe if you saw a picture
of the cave, it's not so bad.
Do you hear that?
Crazy, it sounds like it's
coming from outside the door.
Aloha, Bree.
Is there something you wanna tell us?
I don’t understand,
are you engaged or not?
Well at first I said yes, but
then I needed more time to...
More time, perfect.
How about a quick 18 months?
Yeah, sounds perfect,
let's get you packed up
so that we can catch the
red eye tonight.
No, I'm not leaving here
until I figure this out.
What's to figure out?
The semester's over, you’re going
on a mission, you're not contributing
to the national teenage
bride statistic.
You were a teenager when
we got married.
I was six days shy of 20
and that was your fault
for asking too soon.
And I still regret it by the way.
You regret marrying dad?
What, are you serious?
No, of course not.
I would have always
married your father.
But in a perfect world, I would
have served a mission first
and had more life experiences
while I was still single.
Okay, I think what your
mother's trying
to say is that her choice
to get married wasn't
necessarily her plan,
but it was a choice that she made
after careful consideration
and a spiritual confirmation.
And not a split second decision
after gorging myself on crab legs.
I'm sorry, that was insensitive.
I'm just trying to understand.
It doesn’t seem like
that's what you're doing.
Sweetie, do you
remember what you told me?
I tell you everything.
You have to be more specific.
About your mission.
- No.
- Well I do
and I stitched it for
you on the plane.
Wherever the Lord takes
you is where he wants you
- to be, your words.
- Okay,
but he took me to Hawaii.
So what if marrying Thys
is what he wants for me?
How could that be?
He proposed to you in
public for crying out loud.
Well, that's the thing,
at first I did just say yes
because I felt pressured
with all these people watching us,
but then when we talked
about it, just me and him...
He and I.
- Mom.
- Sorry, go on.
When it was just the two
of us, it started to make more sense
and then I prayed about it.
- And?
- Well it wasn't like
an angel came down and told me
what to do, but it felt
good and it felt peaceful.
It just feels right.
Oh my sweet girl, he's beguiled you.
- Oh geez.
- No.
Bree, honey, come.
What did I do?
Well, your daughter just
left the room in tears.
What do you think?
Well, she's crying because she's
about to give up her
dreams over a boy.
Her dreams or your dreams?
I'm her mother, our
dreams are the same.
She's the one that wanted
to serve a mission.
I mean, sure, I might've
pointed her in that direction,
but she submitted her
papers of her own free will
and choice and now 24 hours
later, she's getting married.
Well, this is a
difficult time of life.
You remember being this age?
We need to be here for her.
Bree, honey, can we come in?
The Chesterfields have invited
us over for dinner tonight.
Oh, we wouldn't wanna impose...
No, that sounds lovely.
I need you to be more than cordial.
They may well end up
being my future in-laws,
so I need you to be respectful.
When am I not respectful?
Mom, I don't wanna fight with you.
This is new for all of us.
I don't expect you to know
exactly how to deal with this,
but I do expect for you
to treat me like an adult.
Is that fair?
That's fair.
- Hi, auntie.
- Oh Leilani.
What's this all about?
She was scared of mom.
♪ There is beauty all around ♪
Curt, I can't
believe you wore cargo shorts.
Well I’m sorry I didn't think
about fashion while I was
packing my 72 hour emergency kit.
Always think about fashion.
Well next time,
I'll pack a matching onesie.
Aloha.
- Oh, thank you.
- This is so nice.
- They're for me?
- You of course.
- That's how you do it.
- Matches your shirt.
- Thank you.
- Oh, these are so beautiful.
Thank you didn't need to
bring anything.
Oh no, it's the least we could do.
This is so generous of you to have us.
Are you kidding?
We've been dying to meet you.
Bree has told us so much
about you, we feel like
we know you already.
Only the good things, don't worry.
And anyone who raised
a daughter this amazing
has gotta be pretty incredible.
Well, thank you very much
and we've heard nothing but
great things about you too.
- So the bribes work.
- Yes.
Good job, Breebee.
Where's Thys?
He's out getting a key
ingredient for din-din.
He'll be back soon though.
Hey, let's move this
party onto the patio.
- Please come on in.
- Great, yeah,
let's do that.
Welcome to our
little beach pad.
It's amazing, wow.
I figured with all the fresh coconut
and pineapple on the property,
I was just one Vitamix away
from the most delicious drink
known to mankind.
Please help yourself.
They're virgin of course.
I can't understand why
anyone would want
to ruin this with rum, am I right?
I agree.
I'm still tinkering with
the recipe a little bit.
So feedback is welcome.
- Cheers.
I'll look at those waves.
Swell's coming in.
Oh, we've got a live one here.
Is that true, Curt?
Do you like to hang 10 as they say?
Well, no, yeah, I used to surf.
I mean, being from SoCal,
but I just don't get a chance
to do it very often anymore.
He's being modest, he's very good.
- Well.
- Well then you'll have to
borrow one of our boards
while you're here.
I don’t think we're going
to have time for surfing.
We might.
I still can't
get over this view.
Trust me, you never do.
And the ocean wildlife, incredible.
And you can
see it from here?
Oh mom, all the time.
You see everything, spotted
dolphins, spinner dolphins,
bottle-nose, whales too, humpbacks,
sperm,
- false killer whales.
- False killer whales?
Yeah, they're a little
larger than a dolphin.
They're the only surviving
species of the Pseudorca genus.
They're one of my favorites.
Wow Bree, you really got a knack
for this Marine biology stuff.
She has definitely
taught us so much.
I think I see something.
Oh really?
Is that a dolphin?
That is a rare and peculiar species
of the Chesterfield variety.
It's Thys with our dinner.
Aloha, Carringtons.
- Aloha.
Mom, dad, this is Thys.
I'm so excited to finally meet you,
but I smell like tuna fish
and I'm holding it gigantic spear gun.
So I'm gonna do this properly
and go inside and shower first.
Actually before you get cleaned up,
why don't you take Curt
out and catch a few sets
- before dinner?
- Oh heck yeah.
- Oh yes.
- Nonsense.
No, we are here to visit.
Curt can surf later.
- Yeah.
- No really, it'd be fine.
Besides it's gonna take me a
while to clean those bad boys
and get everything ready.
- Okay, okay.
- Well Curt can help you
clean the fish.
I can help, dad, you should go.
My own sous chef, I like that.
Mom, You should have Mrs.
Chesterfield
give you a tour of this
place, it's amazing.
Oh yes, that would
give us some girl time.
You don't mind, do you, honey?
- It's wonderful.
- Oh yay.
Come on, let's go.
You know it's funny,
I didn’t think I'd
actually enjoy living
in paradise, but you know what?
It turns out, it's not so bad.
So where should we start,
the east or west wing?
Oh, I...
When in doubt,
go east I always say.
So for openers, all of the
wood here was locally sourced.
Oh, of course.
It was tricky.
I didn't wanna go overboard
with the decor here.
I mean the beauty of these islands,
it just, it speaks for itself.
That's why I opted for simplicity.
Can see that.
You know it's funny, initially,
we never even planned
to have a second house,
but we found we were
spending so much time here
with foundation and all, you know?
It just, I don't know,
didn't make sense not to.
Ah, and there they are,
my Stripling warriors,
all served missions and
all married in the temple.
Well all except Thys of course.
I mean, not yet anyway.
- So handsome.
- Yes, they are definitely
blessed in that department.
Derek here, he struggled
with his weight a little bit
for a while, but still he
married a Romney cousin.
Come on through.
Next stop will be my home clinic.
You'll have to excuse the mess.
I can't tell you
how excited I am about this.
Yeah, feeling good?
Yeah, it’s been a little while.
So no judgment.
Oh no, from what Bree tells me,
you're probably gonna
show me up out there.
I don’t know about that.
So how are you doing
with all this craziness?
The guts are kind of
gross, but it is interesting.
No, I mean between you and Thys.
I understand he took
you a quite by surprise.
I think he was just trying
to make it special for me.
Well that's our Thys,
he never wants to miss an opportunity,
but sometimes he jumps, doesn't
know where he's gonna land.
Hope he didn’t scare you too badly.
It's not that, it's just I...
And you don't have to defend him.
I mean, he messed it up
and he knows it.
But between me and my sous chef,
I hope he has a chance to
make it right.
It has been way too long.
You've been great,
you haven't missed a beat.
Well, we've got to head back in.
I don't want to put it with Carrie.
It looks like a lull anyway.
Real quick before we
head back inside,
I owe you an apology.
For what?
For proposing the Bree
without your permission.
No, no, I don't know what
I was thinking.
I heard some podcasts say that
it's an archaic sexist ritual
to ask the father first.
So I was really conflicted, you know?
'Cause Brie's like really
into the whole feminist thing.
So am I obviously.
I mean I think everyone should be.
Not everyone, if you're not,
like that's totally like,
everyone's got a different
like trajectory to the
same spot, you know?
Like you might be one
and you don't, it’s just about,
you know,
valuing women are the
same, as we're equal.
Mr. Carrington, what I'm trying
to say is that I love
your daughter very much
and nothing would make me happier
than if you gave me your
blessing to marry her.
I got you.
You good, are you okay?
- Let's get you back inside.
- Yeah.
Come on.
Hang on a second, you
got my permission.
Are you sure?
'Cause you probably concussed.
Hey, you saved my life.
What am I gonna say?
But don't get too excited, you
still need Carrie's blessing.
But if this is what Bree
wants, you got my support.
All right.
Well the good news is
you are not going to
need any stitches.
That's great.
But I went ahead
and sealed up the wound
with some medical glue just in case.
- Thanks.
- Okay, just gonna shine this
in your eyes, okay?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Great, no concussion,
but I’m going to keep an
eye on you just in case.
- Thank you.
- Great.
- My pleasure.
- Honey,
what were you thinking?
You could have drowned.
He was in good hands.
Thys is a Red Cross
certified lifeguard.
There's the dinner gong.
That means Scott must be ready for us.
Hey listen, I hope you don't mind,
I took the liberty of pulling out
a pair of fresh shorts for you.
You're roughly the same
size as my Luke.
Okay, why don't you guys go ahead
and change and I'll meet
you out there.
- Thank you so much.
- It's my greatest pleasure.
What was that all about?
Well, I'm sorry.
It wasn't planning on getting
pounded by an eight foot wave.
I'm talking about this family.
Something is up, I mean
this is next level kindness.
Well maybe they're
just really great.
Look at all these throw
pillows, nobody's that perfect.
Something has got to be
wrong with them.
Okay, you told Bree you'd
give them a fair chance.
I am giving them a fair chance
and they're totally winning me over.
And that's not easy, so
what does that tell you?
Be honest, do you think
that they put something
in our pina coladas?
Okay, you're done.
That’s the second gong.
Okay, so I'm gonna change
into Luke's shorts, which
are very nice by the way
and I can go out there and
support our daughter Bree
and I hope you join me.
Fine, but you're
getting me a dinner gong
and I don't care how much it costs.
It's bone appetit in Japanese.
Well eata tacomas to you too.
This looks amazing.
When you spend three years
in Osaka, you pick up a thing or two.
Oh, were you there for business?
Technically yes, but it
was the Lord's business.
Mom and dad were mission presidents
in Osaka when I was in grade school.
Of course they were.
Shall we bless the food?
- Yeah.
- Son, would you say it?
Yeah, of course.
Our dear father in heaven,
we are very thankful to be here
with the Carrington family,
thankful for their amazing daughter.
She's been a blessing to
everyone at this table
and then some.
We are thankful for the food,
we ask you to please bless
the hands that prepared it.
We're thankful for the
ocean that gave us this food
and for the beautiful
place where we live.
We'd ask you to bless us
with the spirit
of love and friendship,
that we will truly be able
to get to know each other tonight.
We will also ask you to bless
that those of us making
big life decisions may do
so carefully and with the
guidance of the Holy Spirit.
We say these things in the
name of Jesus Christ, amen.
Well, it's been wonderful
to get to know you, Bree.
It's just been a treat for us
and to bring your parents
with too, it's really nice
to meet you and know what
a terrific job you've done
in raising your daughter.
You can't know what she means to us.
Excuse me for a second,
I'm gonna go outside
to get some fresh air.
- I'll join you.
- Great.
Aren't they're just the most
adorable couple in the world?
I remember when you used
to look at me like that.
Oh, I still do.
You must be so jet lagged.
Oh, it's fine.
I am looking forward to a good
night's rest though tonight.
So are you staying, Turtle Bay?
- No.
- The Marriott?
Well not...
We actually don't get to
spend much time
with Bree these days, so
we're gonna crash at her pad.
Nonsense, you're staying
in our guest house.
- Yeah.
- Oh no, yeah, no,
we'll be fine, it's fine.
We insist, end of discussion.
- Okay, okay, thank you.
- Okay, thank you.
I'm onto you, mister.
What are you talking about?
Just taking my dad
surfing and saving his life.
- Is it working?
- On my dad,
but the jury is still out on my mom.
I asked your dad for permission.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'm trying to make it right.
Well what did he say?
He said he trusts you
and that if this is what
you really want,
I have his blessing.
Ask me again.
Wait, what?
Get on your knee and ask me again.
Bree Christine Carrington,
will you marry me?
- Yes.
- Yes?
For real this time.
Shizah, I put my best bottle
of Martinelli's on ice just
in case we had a reason
to celebrate and I am
sure glad that I did.
Many, many years ago...
May I have the honors?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
First of all, I just feel
like I need to apologize.
I started the day off as
a real negative Nancy.
Bree, I have tried to teach
you correct principles
and help you make good choices
and you've never let me down.
I trust your decision and I'm proud
to share you with Thys
and this amazing family.
I admit that I am a hard nut
to crack but once I'm in, I'm all in.
I'll drink to that.
- Cheers.
I hate to break up a good party,
but we'd better get
planning the wedding.
February 13 is but less
than two months away.
Two months?
February 13th, the 13th of February.
Two, one, three.
Mum, it's okay.
Bree, why didn't you
tell your mother
you already had a day picked out?
- Dad, I...
- Because she didn't know.
I talked to my parents about it
but I didn't have the chance
to talk to Bree yet, sorry.
I thought we should wait
til the semester is over.
Well it's just a
simple miscommunication.
But we're all here, so why
don't we just pick a day
that works better for everybody?
Great idea Curt 'cause
I gave it a shot
and it's just not gonna work.
No matter how I read it
or say it, it's just not
numerically aesthetic
and hello, the 13th?
Who wants to start their
marriage together on unlucky day?
Well actually worked
out okay for us.
And your parents too.
Oh, let me guess, and
your grandma too.
Actually.
You all chose February 13th.
I wouldn't say it was a
choice per se.
It was...
You see, it was the day after
the Pearl Harbor attack.
My grandpa Glenn, he'd lied
about his age and he enlisted
in the Marines and as fate
would have it, he was called
to action the following
Valentine's day, 1942.
He was only 17, so his
parents wouldn't let him marry
his sweetheart, Clarice.
So they eloped the day before.
February 13th.
Unfortunately a couple
of months after he received
the Congressional Medal
of Honor for bravery,
he went missing in
action in the Philippines
and was never seen again.
But luckily for us,
his wedding night had been well,
fruitful.
So you can see why Thys
chose the 13th,
to honor their wedding.
Thys, I love that you thought
about that and gosh, so
special, but it's so soon
and we really should be
deciding these things together.
Right, yeah.
When were you thinking?
Okay, what about April 25th?
I mean the semester will be
over and I've always really
wanted a spring wedding.
I love that idea.
Except my parents have there
Nourish the Children trip
starting in March.
How long does it last?
Six months.
Okay, how about the
end of September then?
Oh, I love fall.
Babe, that's a
nine month engagement.
So?
Some people consider nine months
to be a really short engagement.
Yeah, they're called Catholics.
I don’t want to get married
in the dead of winter, Thys.
Okay so we could get
married out here.
- You know my granny
- The sooner this happens,
- the pricier it's gonna get.
- Can't travel.
If cost is a problem,
we can help with that.
Is my dad seriously
- talking about money right now?
- I'm not saying that.
Thys, we've waited this long.
Let's wait, what's the big deal
about waiting another nine months?
Everybody, settle down.
As mother of the bride, I
invoke executive decision.
Eight weeks is a ridiculous amount
of time to plan a wedding,
especially if we're gonna do it right
and make it special in the
dead of winter mind you.
I would have to call in every
favor anyone ever owed me
and pressure all of my friends
to work non-stop in order to
plan and execute it properly,
it would be insane.
But if anyone can do it,
Carrie Carrington can.
Chock it up.
In honor of Glen and
Clarice, February 13th it is.
Oh wonderful.
Did she just referred to
herself in the third person?
I just go with it.
Now somebody get me a binder.
Okay, did you see that shower?
There's like 12 nozzles.
This is the guest house, wow.
Now how did Monica have
this all ready to go?
Well, we called it homemaking night
in the 90s, it's what we did.
Poor thing didn't have any daughters,
so this is her last chance to use it.
Well, well, did someone
changed their tone?
No, what can I say?
They're amazing.
I think she's my spirit animal.
I thought your
spirit animal was a cougar.
Well she's that too.
How amazing does she look for her age?
Well she's no Carrie Carrington.
Hey, what'd you say we go
to bed and you can finish that later?
Later?
There is no later.
We have 36 hours to take advantage
of everything that we need to do here.
Well, how about taking
advantage of this amazing place
before things get crazy?
Too late, bub, things
are already crazy.
Besides I'm in business
mode, not surfs up dude mode.
Right, right, yep.
Well our oldest daughter
is getting married
and there is no time to celebrate love
or the union of souls.
Oh please, I
know what kind
of union of souls you wanna celebrate.
We need to have a clear plan
if we're gonna pull this off.
Oh yeah, what if I pull this off?
Come on baby, let's go.
Valiant effort, dude, but
it's gonna have to wait.
Besides I'm about to
put my grind guard in.
Pouting only hurts your chances.
The key to victory is
to divide and conquer.
I know we haven't
finalized the exact venue
or event details,
but we can at least
finalize the guest list
and collect addresses.
Monica and I will take the lead.
We also need to shoot and
finalize the engagement photos.
Make sure you choose a
photog you can trust.
Thys, fix your face,
you look constipated.
Can someone remind me why
we're doing this in the studio?
We live in Hawaii,
we already have the best
backdrops in the country.
Okay, well someone
wanted a winter wedding,
so we need a winter setting.
Okay, enough arguing.
Mama C gave me a 24 hour turnaround,
so I'll just fix it all in post.
Face the fan and pretend
you're in love.
Crank it, Maurice.
Smile Bree, awesome.
Thys, your face.
Curt and Scott,
don't be discouraged,
but I need you to take
care of the boring stuff,
mostly phone calls.
Plot your information on
the detailed spreadsheet
I've prepared for you.
- February 13th?
- Correct.
I know it's a long story.
It's available?
That’s amazing, can we
put a hold on it?
I'm sorry, February 13th this year.
When you finish that,
call the list of preselected temples
that Thys and Bree have
provided you with.
Find the open ceiling times
and available officiators.
This will be tough,
but we're counting on
you guys to come through.
This is my favorite,
definitely the most cinematic.
Supposed to be an engagement photo,
not a film noir poster.
What about this?
Oh, I like that, I
look good in that one.
Are you serious?
It's not about you, Thys.
No one cares about the dude.
Perfect, print it.
It there's
always the classic collage.
When you love yourself so much,
you can't just choose one.
Tempting, but no.
Or you could just go with this.
It's perfect.
♪ I am somewhere in the sand ♪
♪ And I wish I was an ocean ♪
Where have you been all day?
Well I'm sorry, did you
not check the Google doc?
You'd have to nominate me for an Oscar
'cause I'm done so Donso
Washington, thank you very much.
All right, I stand correct.
Hey, I've got another
hour rental on the scooter.
Wanna head up the coast?
Don't push it, come on, chop, chop.
I don't think that there's
any way we can pair this down,
- do you?
- No, I agree.
So we have 753 for the reception.
And what, 100 for the luncheon?
What are you thinking
about the luncheon?
Something the day off?
Scott and I were thinking
of dinner the day before.
We just have so many
people traveling in.
It would just be family
and the wedding party
oh, and a few VIPs perhaps.
Well let me know if you
need any help planning it.
Listen, you have your plate
so full with everything else.
We'll handle the dinner, okay?
Probably keep it simple.
Just I don't know,
book a restaurant or the
governor's mansion, we'll see.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Sometimes I get so focused
that I forget to tinkle.
Oh my goodness, of course.
Down the hall and to your left.
Thank you.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
I got a really cool it
with the LaCroixs,
you know what I mean?
Fun family photo wall in there.
Oh nice, right?
Yeah, who's the family
that you're with?
Oh, those are the Lees,
they're our oldest and
dearest friends.
Mark's been friends with Scott since,
boy,
- I guess high school.
- Really?
Yes, they're on the invite list.
Of course.
Unfortunately, I'm not sure
they'll be able to make it.
Bridget gets released about
a week before the wedding.
So they might just happen
to be in Barcelona that week
if you know what I mean.
How did she take the news?
I mean from about Thys.
She doesn't know yet but
that's only because I told Thys
that a proper Dear Jane
letter should be hand written
out of respect.
Well, I hope she takes it well.
She'll be fine.
She is such a catch.
When she comes back,
she'll have her pick up
any young man she wants.
Well, Bree's quite the
catch herself.
Mom, look.
Oh gosh.
- You okay?
- Yeah, it's no big deal.
Do you still feel good about this?
Yeah, yeah, I mean
it's been a little crazy,
but we knew it would be that way.
I don't want our
engagement to be crazy.
No, no, I just
meant like with scheduling.
- It'll be fun.
- Okay.
I wish you were coming
with me tonight.
I can't believe we're
spending Christmas apart.
I know, hey,
but the good news
is that it's not gonna happen again.
- Last time.
- True, true.
All right, we
should probably get you
to the airport.
No, no, just a
few more minutes.
You still felt good about all this?
As good as I can, this is life.
Our parents trusted us, I
guess we gotta trust them.
I mean they're adults, right?
Technically.
I wonder what the
Chesterfields are thinking
about all this.
Oh, I bet they're just
as stressed as we are.
We have got to hit the ground running.
Come here just a minute.
I'm sorry that I was
short with you earlier.
I'm so glad that you got
the temple appointment
and the country club squared away.
Oh, about that.
Don't tell me they cancel.
No, no, they didn't cancel,
but I don't know if it's
worth the money.
I thought they gave you
the Chesterfield discount.
Yeah well I guess
some people's definition
of discount is different than others.
Well if you're so
worried about money,
then why are you buying
all these crappy souvenirs?
These are for the kids.
I spent tens of dollars
on this, not tens of
thousands of dollars.
I just, I think that we should
find a low budge solution.
You want our daughter's
wedding to be low budge?
Do you think I wanted to
be unemployed right now?
I didn't exactly ask Randy
to cancel my contract.
He was supposed to take care of us.
It was a startup, it
failed, I mean that happens.
How long are we gonna be poor?
We're not poor, Carrie.
Well we can't afford that
venue for our daughters wedding.
What do you call that?
I didn't say that.
I just say we need to come up
with a contingency plan, that's all.
Fine.
Thys is gonna pull the car around,
okay?
Is everything okay?
- Yes, of course.
- Of course.
Thank you both so much.
I couldn't imagine doing this
without you, but I'm
getting really excited.
Oh yeah?
I love you both so much.
You really think
we can pull this off?
- Yes.
- Oh yeah.
But we're gonna need our girls.
Are you sure you're not
feeling jet lagged, Carrie?
We can always start
this tomorrow, you know?
- Yeah.
- Please, please,
forgive me for what I'm
about to reveal to you.
It is the biggest cause
of shame I have
in my life, but there
are no other options.
I promise we'll finish it one day.
The timing is just never right,
you know?
Who knows that's what
the boys do down here.
I feel so vulnerable.
At least no one
will bother us.
Except for maybe a few
brave spiders.
This was a mistake.
I'm gonna kick Curt
out of his home office.
- No, it's perfect.
- No, no, no.
Look, we're all set up here.
I really appreciate both of you.
I couldn't do this without you.
I mean, it just means a world
to me that you would drop everything
- just to help me.
- Enough with the chit-chat.
I've got a hard out at 1800 hours.
It's Jazz versus the Nuggets tonight
and Bud got us court side seats.
So let's plan the heck
out of this thing.
All right, let's pound it.
Will we ever learn?
Kat, guess who's back.
At first, she totally wanted
to kill me, but now she's all in now.
You know that even though she's
on her mission, Paige is
my official maid of honor.
It's a pact we made for each
other in the seventh grade
and I have to honor that,
but I wanted to ask you if you
would be my first bridesmaid?
D.C., yeah, wow.
What an amazing opportunity for you.
No, no, not at all,
just remember me when you're
running for president.
Trinity, what's up girl?
Yeah, Thys, T H, Y, S, it's Dutch.
Jenny, my cousin went
two years ago actually
and she really loved it.
So I think you're gonna love it.
Ashley, I just can’t believe
you're gonna be gone.
But Erica, what up?
I did always want a spring wedding.
In total, six months, but
honestly it feels like forever.
Sarah, Lisa, Haley, Taylor, Hi,
it's Bree.
I thought camp was complicated,
but this is next level.
She's only just begun.
I hope Bree appreciates all this.
Where is that little diva anyway?
Oh, I'm sure has her
own to do lists.
Do you think she would
miss me if I went out
and got some snacks?
I'll take some Flaming Hot Ruffles
and a Wild Cherry Pepsi.
Here, take the hog.
You'll be quicker.
I'll cover for you.
Don't even think twice about it.
You're not missing a Disney
cruise for my wedding.
You guys, thank you so
much for inviting me.
I figured it was time
we all got together again.
After you.
Oh thank you, Phoebe.
Surprise!
♪ Mormon Mormon Mormon Mormon ♪
♪ Bree met a Mormon boy ♪
♪ He is her pride and joy ♪
♪ She goes most everything
from Alma on down ♪
♪ Someday she'll be his wife ♪
♪ She'll have eternal life ♪
♪ Oh how she loves her Mormon boy ♪
Oh you guys.
So are you going to
have babies soon?
'Cause I'm like a really
good babysitter.
- Very, veery good.
- If you have too many,
we can totally babysit
together if you're nervous.
Have you seen how hot Thys is?
I'm like Smuckers 'cause
I'm like jelly.
You seriously had no
idea he was gonna ask?
No idea.
I would have seen it a mile away.
Credit card receipts, ATM
withdrawals, bank statements,
rock that big has got a
paper trail mile long.
Easy to find if you know
what you're looking for.
Can I see your ring?
- It is so pretty.
- I know, right?
- Is it real?
- I hope so.
I do hope your heart's not
set on the riches of the world.
Was it hard to say yes with
all those hot Hawaiian dancers
all around you?
Not for that reason, just
'cause I was so nervous.
How much can he bench press?
How's school going, Bree?
Well I get to swim with dolphins
and I get school credit for it.
So it's pretty awesome.
But honestly I love the
academic work too.
Have you studied narwhals yet?
Not yet, but I'm excited too.
Buckle up, they're so awesome.
Wait, so what happens
with your mission then?
Can Thys come with you?
I wish, no.
Well technically he could,
but when they're like 70.
Actually I won't be able
to go on my mission anymore.
My call doesn't come for a couple
of months and when it does,
I'll just have
to tell them that I'm not able to go.
But that's okay, you know?
'Cause I have a new mission, marriage.
- Yeah.
- Great.
The most important
mission of your life.
- Yeah.
- Really is so good.
Oh, it's my mom.
You guys, I have a question.
I just wanted to ask each
of you if you guys would
be my Bree's maids?
Okay, I can cross off
pick bridesmaids.
Wow, I blew it.
What do you mean?
We were at that restaurant for
over two hours and I only
cross off one thing on my list.
That's okay, we were
catching up and having fun.
I'm not supposed to be having
fun, I'm planning a wedding.
Well just try not to be so stressed.
I'm not stressed, I just..
Wanna hold Roxy for a bit?
I'm fine.
See, perfect.
Oh look, we're here.
Thank you guys so much for lunch.
You really are both the sweetest.
Bye.
You think she's okay?
She's a Carrington, she
kinda has to be.
Oh this looks amazing.
Hi ladies.
What are we working on?
Just bugging away.
Well it's the reception
line logistics.
We're trying to find the right flow.
Here, this is a diagram
of the cultural hall.
But my reception's at
the country club?
Well mama said it was
too much moolah.
Well I just wanted to
have a backup plan
just in case there are any problems.
What sort of problems with there be?
I mean, dad booked it already, right?
Well just in case we
change our minds.
I'm not changing my mind.
You know we have a plan
for the country club too.
Just want to cover all our base.
Looks great.
I feel like reception lines
are a little superficial,
even archaic.
I just think it'd be nice
if Thys and I could mingle
organically with our guests
and not spend the whole
night talking to, you know,
someone's grandpa that
we don't even care about.
No reception line?
What are we, cave people?
You know, let's just put a pin
in it and your mom asked me
to help you with your dress.
And so I called a couple
of local boutiques.
Or you could wear my
old dress, ta-da.
It's you know, it's got
that retro, vintagey vibe.
Mom, I'm sure that you
looked beautiful
when you wore this, but I just
really don't wanna look like
a polygamous hipster.
What are you talking about?
She's got a point.
I mean I'd know because
my niece is one of them.
A hipster, not a polygamist.
Well we could alter it.
I mean the fabric has
really held its quality.
Mom no, this is my wedding
dress that we're talking about.
Okay, why are you being
so cheap all of a sudden?
Thank you so much for
your help today, ladies.
We really appreciate it,
but if you'll excuse us,
my daughter and I need
to go to a safe place
and work some things out.
I'm sorry that I called you cheap,
I know it's your trigger word.
Frugal is just such a
superior word on so many levels.
I know, I didn't mean it.
So are we like poor now?
No, we're just in conservation mode.
Why didn't you guys tell me?
I don't know.
I mean, we didn't keep it from you.
You were just away at college
and we really thought that your
dad would have a job by now.
Poor dad, ah and I was such a brat.
But I was really excited
for that country club.
I know and we can still
have it there.
We have some savings that
we can dip into.
It'll be a stretch,
but I can see that this
is really important
to you and I don’t want you to
think that we're not willing
to make sacrifices.
Well, I can make sacrifices too.
But the cultural home?
Listen, I get it,
it's a vaudeville stage
with a basketball court,
there's nothing cultural about it.
Let's just stick to the original plan.
Okay, hypothetically if
we were to go with plan B,
do you think you could make
it feel really special?
Oh please, with all the
money we'd save,
I'd make it Buckingham
palace in there.
Okay, I trust you.
Let’s do it.
Are you sure?
- Yes, yeah.
- Oh.
But since we're gonna be
saving all that money on a venue,
do you think I could have my
own wedding dress, a new one?
Of course.
I wish Paige was here
to help me pick it out.
I could really use a maid of honor.
Has there ever been like a mother
of the bride that's also
been the matron of honor?
I mean, that could be
pretty cool, couldn't it?
Nice try mom.
It's worth a shot.
All right, you ready to do this?
Yeah, let's get you stirred up.
Nope, we don't do that.
We just say registered.
That’s what we say when
we go inside, okay?
Okay, all right.
So whatever we scan
shows up on our registry?
- Yup.
- Rock and roll.
♪ I start to talk and you
already know ♪
Oh mattress pads,
- you gotta have those.
- Oh and I need these.
- Oh and mom, these.
- Naper, yes, I love him.
You can never have to
may throw pillows.
Mom, candles, Emerald Amazon.
- White spruce.
- Citrus water.
Snuggly sweater.
lsland moonlight.
Good lighting is so important.
Oh look at these frames.
Mom, I have so many cute
pictures from Hawaii.
Planners!
Vases and a really cute toaster
over and a charcuterie board...
And you really didn't
get anything for me?
Camping stuff, a Frisbee,
some beef jerky?
Well if you cared so much,
you could have been there, mister.
Ouch.
Was that supposed to be
your "E.T." impression?
Oh no, that'd be awful.
No that'd be more like,
- oh.
- Oh.
Yours is so much better.
I miss you.
We FaceTime like every three hours.
I know but this is not the same.
I know, I miss you and
your cute face.
And you sure you’re okay
that we changed the reception venue?
You know my parents would have paid
for the country club, right?
I know they would have,
but it's the bride's responsibility
and you know how
traditional my parents are.
Yeah, but Bree, our
guests have to come too.
What do you mean?
I mean, it's fine.
Like if my parents have the
rehearsal dinner, it's all good.
It's whatever you want.
I promise it's gonna be awesome.
It's a weird that I
don't care at all?
'Cause only care about marrying you.
Are you sure?
Because our invites go
to the printer tomorrow.
Print away, do your wifely duties.
Okay, well I have to go
to bed because I need some sleep,
but...
You sure, for real this time?
For real, I'm hanging up.
But I love you.
I love you too.
- I love you so much.
- I miss you forever.
Oh, it already hurts.
Thys Abner, honey, haven't
written to her yet, seriously?
Take care of this honey.
I will.
Okay, Sister Brodhead was
up all night addressing these.
So please be careful.
Oh, this definitely makes it real.
Last chance to push
the eject button.
What's the big deal?
It's only for eternity.
All right, peasants, do your job.
We have some serious
business to attend to.
See ya, suckers.
You hear that, boys?
Hop too.
Oh honey, you use the
moistener, that's what it's for.
No way, love the taste.
- It fits perfectly.
- Right?
In some parts.
Holy Meghan Markle, I
think this is it.
When you smile, don't use so much gum.
You know how you can get.
All that lace, you know
you're gonna snag.
If you don't like my opinion,
then I don't have to give it.
I don't wanna wear any, I'm
not gonna go to the wedding.
I think I found it.
♪ I promise I'll keep it ♪
Wow, it's perfect.
You look so pretty.
I love it so much.
Think we got a winner.
- Oh boy.
- What's the problem?
Is it too expensive, is
dad gonna freak?
Yes, but I have ways of
convincing your father.
I have an old bottle of CK One
fragrance in my top drawer.
Okay, mom, I don't
need to know the details.
Just do what you need to do.
Ring us up, Lucas.
Oh my, wow.
How did they know we were here?
Let's give her some room.
Home stretch, guys, almost there.
Mitt Romney.
No way.
Oh, you think that's cool?
Heard Steve Martin might show up.
Who's Steve Martin.
You're not my son.
All girls, show me, Hannah.
You were right, I love it.
I love it, Mindy, Charlotte.
The zipper goes in the back.
- It's a choice.
- Flip it, Mindy.
Anderson sisters, how we doing?
- It's so tight, Bree.
- Well you're not supposed
to wear clothes underneath
it, Mykelle, Phoebe?
Oh, you're adorable, Lane?
I'm obsessed, you crushed it, Lucus!
All right, I'm out.
♪ Just my luck, yeah ♪
♪ Make new friend or maybe ♪
Are you done yet?
What took you so long?
Oh, that's lane.
She's given me a ride to
the post office.
Oh, tell her to step
on it because the last
pick up is in 23 minute.
Where's Cars?
You really invited
700 people to your wedding?
To the reception.
We only invited extended family
to the actual temple ceremony.
Your temples are gorgeous.
It must cost so much money
to get married there.
Actually it doesn’t cost a thing.
Serious?
Not a dime.
Okay, well to be fair,
you do pay 10% of your annual
income for your entire life
to the church.
So it's not free per se,
but you can think of it
more like a membership perk
than an upfront cost.
Okay, right there
to the left, perfect.
Can I ask you guys
something in confidence?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
Is it weird that Thys is inviting
his ex-girlfriend's family
to the wedding or am I
just being super paranoid?
Well, that doesn't
sound super normal.
But didn't you say they're
his close family friends?
Yeah of like 30 years.
Okay, then maybe it's
not super weird either.
Did he at least ask you
before you invited them?
No, they were just on
the Chesterfield list.
Well I mean he definitely
should have asked you
just to make sure you
were okay with it.
But maybe his parents did
it without even thinking.
I don't know, if you're uncomfortable
with it, you should probably
have a conversation.
You're right.
I'm just gonna talk to him
about it before I said there's out,
yeah?
- Yeah.
- I'll put it in my purse.
Okay, let's go.
♪ I found what I need ♪
♪ Like honey to a bee ♪
♪ And I'm buzzing 'cause
it feels so sweet ♪
♪ And I've got you by the hand ♪
♪ And I'll never give it back ♪
♪ 'Cause together, you
and me are made to last ♪
You guys, I think
I'm getting cold feet.
Okay, you have one minute
to pull out as many of
these rings as you can.
Good luck with
those sausages.
Now go.
You got one!
So now we're going be
asking Bree trivia questions
about her beloved fiance.
If she gets one right,
then we have to stuff a
marshmallow in our cheeks.
But if she gets it wrong, then
she has to stuff it in hers.
All right, stretch those
cheeks ladies,
'cause this is going to
be easy Breezy.
Enunciate, we can't hear you.
Did you say "Napoleon Dynamite"?
I'm so sorry, it was "Princess Bride".
No fair, I've never even seen it.
What?
Who are you?
Thank you, Sister Robinson.
And now I have the whole trilogy.
Well, as long as we're
on the subject.
Thank you, Nedra.
You are always so
thoughtful with your gifts.
Don't thank me now, thank me later.
Oh, Bree, would
you mind getting the door?
- Thys!
- Aloha, stranger.
Just warms my heart.
You get anything good?
Yeah, got lots of good stuff.
Nice, show me what you got.
I will on our wedding night.
Right, good.
- So good to see you.
- You too.
- Wanna get outta here?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Wanna see what we've been up too?
Now I know the basketball
hoops are hideous,
but don’t worry, Curt and
the boys are gonna go early
and take them down.
Now I didn't have time to
make everything exactly
to scale, but I think
this paints the picture
thematically and otherwise
and you might've noticed
that there is no caterer
on the vendor list, but don't worry,
we have something better.
It's called Costco and the
Relief Society.
It's beautiful, mom.
Oh, did you guys happen to
have any extra invitations?
Yes but if you're going
to add to the guest list,
I'm gonna need to know ASAP
'cause I have to make
some arrangements.
It's not extra, my parents' friends
didn't get theirs somehow.
It's the Lees.
Maybe it got lost in the mail.
Yeah, that's fine.
- I'll just snag an extra one.
- The Lees.
Now why does that name
sounds so familiar?
It's my ex-girlfriend's family.
My mom said she talked
to you about them though.
I kind of was under the impression
that they'd be out of town.
They are, yeah, I think they
were gonna pick up Bridget
from Barcelona, but I
think they must've just
canceled their trip.
Why do you say like that,
With that weird little lisp thing?
Barcelona?
It's just how you say it in Spain.
Oh, we’re not in Spain.
Yeah, that's just how
Bridget taught me to say it.
Anyway, Miss Carrington,
you don't have to worry.
I totally get it,
but I sent her a Dear Jane,
pretty clear Dear Jane letter.
They're just close family friends,
so we thought it would be
weird if they weren't invited.
That's okay, right?
I don't want...
Sure, yeah, sure.
Okay, this is great by the way.
I love the whole spread.
It's just like, yeah.
I have a surprise for you.
- Great.
- Sound good?
♪ I don't believe I met yet ♪
♪ A light to break my light ♪
Are you ready for your surprise?
I thought this fancy
dinner was a surprise.
Oh no, it's way better.
Are you ready?
No.
I need to get something
off my chest first.
Okay yeah, what's up, what's wrong?
Promise you'll forgive me?
It kind of depends on what you say.
I lied to you.
The Lees invitation didn't get lost
in the mail, I just never sent it.
Why?
I meant to talk to you about
it and I just got so busy
and then I was just so excited
to see you and I forgot.
That's fine, that's fine, but like
why did you feel like
we had to talk about it?
I don’t know, I guess...
I guess I felt threatened.
I know the history that
you have with them and
with Bridget and Thys, your
parents basically have a shrine
dedicated to her in their bathroom.
Yeah but like, we're not a thing.
We're not, you don't have
to be worried.
I know, but she gets back
so soon and I just, I just...
I didn't want either of us thinking
about her on our wedding day.
Honestly, they're probably
not even gonna show up.
I kind of hope not.
Yeah but if they do, like
I can't control that, right?
Okay Bree, at some point
you're gonna have
to start trusting me, okay?
I do trust you.
It's just, I don't know.
You haven't been around and
it's been really stressful.
Yeah, totally, I just...
I'm here now though, all right?
Everything's fine.
- Promise?
- Promise.
And you forgive me?
Oh, forgiven and forgotten,
you're good.
Okay, now I’m ready for my surprise.
Okay, here is a hint.
Oh, it's my surprise dessert?
Is this like a scene from
"The Princess Bride" or?
♪ Ba, baba, ba ♪
Oh, Blues Clues, is it Blues Clues?
I don’t know you, no.
First down, wee-oh, wee-oh.
I am so lost.
You really don't know?
I got nothing.
I got accepted into the
business school at BYU Provo.
I start second block.
But I thought we were going
to finish Hawaii together first?
Yeah we were, but that was
before I got accepted into Real BYU.
Thank you very much.
But what about me?
I didn't get accepted.
Yeah but you will, eventually.
And what do I do before then?
I just forget about my internship
and drop out of school, go to UVU?
Maybe.
Thys, they don't even
offer my major.
You switch majors, big deal.
Bree, Marine biology?
That’s something you say
when you're like five.
You don't really stick with that.
Sorry, that was...
That was mean.
I didn't mean that.
I overreacted.
I just was really pumped
about this and I thought
you'd be excited for me.
I didn't even know that you applied.
That's because I didn't tell anyone.
I mean my parent knew.
I don't care Thys, I'm your fiance.
I need communication.
This is our life, not
your Instagram story.
You're right, I'm sorry.
I just, I felt so much
pressure to provide for the two
of us and their business school
is one of the top programs.
I just thought he'd be proud of me.
I am proud of your Thys,
but I need you to include me
in these decisions from now on.
I need to be able to have a say
in things that affect us both.
You're right, you're
completely right.
I'm sorry, will you forgive me?
Of course, forgiven
and forgotten.
Don't say anything.
Just follow my lead, be cool.
What is happening?
Stacey, oh that's so
beautiful, is it French?
No, it's just Stacey, it's American.
It's very Regal.
Listen, I have a coupon
from a competitor.
Will you honor it?
This is expired two years ago.
That's not gonna be a
problem though, right?
No.
Amy?
Okay, what are your wedding colors?
Okay, I'm so glad you asked.
How much time do you have right now?
Is that Madagascar vanilla?
- It is.
- I knew it.
What flavor is that?
Oh that’s our cookie dough.
- The cookie dough.
- Super popular.
Oh mom, how about the funfetti?
Not for a wedding,
that's not appropriate.
It's fun for like fun,
but it's not elegant.
It's so good though.
So what would you suggest?
I really like fantasy creatures.
Like maybe a nice friendly
dragon or maybe a unicorn,
a Pegasus or something like that.
I mean, we were mostly get temples,
but you imagine like a mermaid
scene, a mermaid and a merman
and they're, you know,
they're close to each other.
It could be really nice.
But how much do you
charge for a custom design?
No, the prices are in the brochure.
It's really impressive.
And a little bit
more than I anticipated.
Well, there's a lot
that goes into it.
It's not just an easy thing to do.
So time and creativity.
Do you offer correspondence courses?
Well, Jesse has a YouTube channel.
How many subscribers does he have?
It looks like you two
are all squared away.
Got your temple prep
class you're finishing up
on Sunday, you've got your recommends
and you've got the
appointment at the temple
for the ceiling.
And knowing Carrie, I
imagine the planning
is all squared away.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Is there anything else
you guys need?
I think just any advice that
you have for us, you know,
- before the big day.
- Yeah, yeah.
Think I've unloaded
all my wedding wisdom.
It's really up to you two
at this point.
It's all about your commitment
to God and to each other.
Okay.
Thank you, thank you so much.
Thank you, Bishop.
Oh one more thing.
I did hear rumblings about the girls
planning a bit of a bachelorette
party for you this weekend
and I don't know your
pals probably have
something planned for you too.
I just, you know, make
sure you take it easy.
- Of course.
- For sure, yeah.
♪ Walk into the room ♪
♪ I can't help stop and stare ♪
♪ Show me what you got ♪
♪ I hope you came prepared,
right there ♪
♪ 'Cause when you're messing
with someone like me ♪
♪ Get in check, get in check ♪
♪ 'Cause there's no way
that I'm gonna leave ♪
♪ 'Til I get, 'til I get ♪
♪ That thing, that bling, that ice ♪
♪ That makes me cool like crazy ♪
♪ That fire, desire, that's lit ♪
♪ No if's, no but's, no maybe's ♪
♪ It's what I want ♪
♪ This is what I want ♪
♪ What I want, this is what I want ♪
♪ That thing, that bling, that ting ♪
♪ That makes me cool like crazy ♪
♪ Makes me cool like crazy ♪
I'm gonna go up
to you and come on all these floors.
♪ If you give me the
thing that I want ♪
♪ Wait a sec, wait a sec ♪
♪ And I'll give
everything that I got ♪
♪ Wanna get, wanna get ♪
♪ That thing, that bling, that ice ♪
♪ That makes me cool like crazy ♪
Aren't you guys gonna go?
♪ No if's, no but's, no maybe's ♪
You guys are pathetic.
Leilani, Leilani.
♪ This is what I want ♪
Presenting the bride to Bree.
♪ That thing, that bling, that ting ♪
♪ That makes me cool like crazy ♪
- Oh yeah!
- Oh man.
- So good.
- Anything made of gelatine.
♪ I want it all, I want it ♪
♪ That thing, that bling ♪
♪ That ting, that makes me ♪
♪ Cool like crazy ♪
♪ I want it all ♪
♪ I want it, I want it all ♪
♪ That thing, that bling, that ting ♪
♪ That makes me cool like crazy ♪
♪ makes me cool like crazy ♪
♪ This is what I want ♪
♪ What I want, this is what I want ♪
♪ That thing, that bling, that ting ♪
♪ That makes me cool like crazy ♪
Marriage.
Marriage is what brings us
together today.
I wish I had six fingers.
Such quick texting.
Rob Reiner's a cinematic genius.
Shhh.
Did you know that Cary
Elwes actually broke his toe
six months before the movie?
Just like in "Lord of the Rings."
Never eating that
much yogurt ever again.
Thank you for my blanket.
Of course, I had to
get my girl something.
And thank you for taking
us to the club.
I thought you hated it.
Yeah, I did, but I had
to experience it, you know?
We lasted less than 10 minutes.
Okay, but we crushed
every second of it.
Am I right?
Especially Hannah.
I just hope Thys doesn't care.
Why would he care?
He might just think
it was just too crazy.
I mean, who goes to a club
for their bachelorette party?
Literally everyone.
Besides I'm sure that his
bachelor party is way crazier.
He's going to Top
Golf with his brothers.
Or maybe slightly less crazy.
I love you, Laney.
- I love you too.
- Seriously,
you have always had my
back, like no judgment,
no matter what.
Even though Paige is
officially my maid of honor,
unofficially, you're my maid of honor.
Thank you for saying that, Bree.
It really means a lot to me.
I know I haven't been around
much, but if you ever.
I love you.
Thys is here.
What?
Babe, we were only at the
club for like five minutes
and nothing happened, I swear.
I mean, one guy smelled
my hair, but that's it.
Babe, what's wrong?
You told me this was over.
It is, but I feel like
she has a point.
I mean, we were together
so long, it makes sense
she at least wants to meet.
And go on a date with an
engaged person?
It's not a date, it's not a date.
You're going to dinner
alone with her.
Thys, it's a date.
You read the letters,
she just wants closure.
Yeah I know what she
wants, but what do you want?
I would love for
things to not be awkward
between me and her.
I mean, like, I feel
like I over that, right?
I used to take baths with this girl.
- That's not helping.
- When we were two.
I know Thys, you have
so much history with her and
that's what makes it so hard.
And you know, you keep saying
that you don't wanna make it awkward
for her and for her family,
but why don't you care about
making it awkward for me?
I do care.
Then why do you feel
like you have to do this?
If you don't want me
to go, I won't go, okay?
I will do whatever you say.
But if you let me do this,
I feel like it'll be the best for us.
How?
How can this be good for us?
I know it's confusing
and it isn't fair,
but it happens, okay?
It happened and I'm just trying
to be honest and communicate
with you and keep you
involved with the decision.
I thought that's what you
wanted me to do.
No come on, don't.
I know I wanna be with you, Thys,
and you can give that back
to me when you are sure
that you wanna be with me.
Honey, 07:45, you
wanna take a break?
Carrie, babe,
- hey, wow.
- Hey.
Look what you made me do.
Oh, you ruined my feathering.
Are you sure that's not
an improvement?
This is a lot
harder than it looks.
I dunno, it looks pretty hard.
Still you know, I think you
should get a professional
to do this.
We might be able to afford it
now I got that new job offer.
Shut up, serious?
Oh that's so great.
They're called Little Wagon,
it's a smaller firm, but
they're great.
- Okay.
- So let's celebrate.
Get rid of those goggles.
I've got a surprise for you.
Oh, is it chicken parm?
No guessing, come here.
- All right, okay.
- Okay, all right,
big surprise, I'm going in.
Deserved a little something
special, so here we go.
You turkeys, what are you doing?
I thought
you set this up for us.
With the candles.
It was so good.
Oh, well that's great, I...
It's fine, it's not their fault.
I've been so busy planning.
You know that family's schedule
is totally out of wack.
All right, don't worry, boys,
all this wedding stuff
is going to be over soon.
- You made the right decision.
- Absolutely.
Just doesn't feel right.
Well, it's gonna be really hard
but if he comes back,
you're both gonna be
the stronger for it.
Yeah but mom, what if
he doesn't come back?
Then he's an idiot.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
But what do we do about the wedding?
We're not gonna overstress.
We're gonna move forward
as if it's happening
and if we get to that bridge,
we'll deal with it then.
Yeah but we'd done so much already
and we've spent so much money.
Listen I don't want
you to worry one minute
about the money, okay?
We can make more money
and Costco has a generous
return policy.
I just want you to worry
about getting this right
and while he's thinking things over,
you take this time to reconsider
if this is still
something that you want.
But I've made up my mind.
I know, but things have changed.
This is new information.
Why is everything falling apart?
This is my engagement.
This is supposed to be
the best time of my life.
Wait, who told you that?
Everyone, I mean movies,
Instagram, you guys.
Oh, we did not have
the perfect engagement.
Things got a little
hairy for a minute there,
thought I was gonna get
my heartbroken.
For real?
Yeah, well I had my doubts.
I mean, I knew I loved your father,
but I had feelings come up
for someone else,
someone from my past.
Daniel Gregory.
His name's not important.
Anyway, they were real
emotions that I had to deal
with and lucky for me, your
father was really patient.
How do I not know about this?
I don’t know, I guess I just
don't like to think about it.
Engagements are the worst.
I mean, they're the worst
because they're the best.
It's a trial time that God gives us
to really test out our relationship
before we make the biggest
commitment of our lives.
You have the right to change your mind
from the second you put
on that ring to the moment
you kneel at the altar.
Why didn't you tell me it
would be this exhausting?
I guess we kind of forgot.
We've been together
so long, it’s hard to
remember our lives before.
Honestly, I just, I just
want what you guys have.
Oh sweetie, you'll get there,
I promise.
Hey, can I use my screen time?
Tyler.
♪ They say true love is
one in a million ♪
♪ And that one was never me ♪
♪ Til you walked through
the door full of passion ♪
♪ Full of strength, like a king ♪
♪ Now the sun shining
brighter than ever ♪
♪ All my darkest days are gone ♪
♪ And I'm trying to take
in every moment ♪
♪ But it's still not long enough ♪
♪ I've got forever ♪
♪ On the front of my mind ♪
♪ I wanna hold you ♪
♪ Even longer than life ♪
♪ My heart starting beating ♪
♪ A new rhythm tonight, oh ♪
♪ And I'm gonna find a
million ways to love you ♪
♪ One day at a time ♪
♪ Oh ♪
I'm sorry.
Made a huge mistake.
So I guess this is goodbye?
No.
I never should have let
you take this off.
Can I please put it back on?
Yes, yes please.
♪ Don't you know I'll
never let you go ♪
♪ I've got forever ♪
♪ On the front of my mind ♪
♪ I wanna hold you ♪
Mom.
♪ My heart started beating ♪
Were you up all night, mom?
- Maybe.
- Know yourself out.
Isn't marriage magical?
Focus Bud, these lights
won't untangle themselves.
Who's the lucky guy?
Are you sure I should
be wearing this?
It feels really weird.
Yeah, I don't know why
my mom insisted,
but you've made her very happy.
Think she just wants to show
you off to all of her friends.
You know, it's bad luck
to see a bride
in her wedding dress
before the big day.
And how can something
this beautiful be bad luck?
Come on, I wanna show you how too.
How many layers is this?
- It’s a lot.
- It's a lot, yeah.
- Mark, hey.
- Hi.
- Mark Lee.
It's wonderful to meet you.
And I'm Alison.
We’ve heard such amazing things.
So have I.
We'd love you to meet our Bridget.
- Hi.
Congratulations honestly.
Congratulations to you too,
for just being a great person
and yeah, the whole mission thing.
That’s a really big deal.
Thank you, yeah, no, it was
a really great experience.
If I could have
everyone please be seated,
we'd like to start
- the festivities.
- Good to see you.
- Talk to you later.
- Yeah, please.
Why didn’t you tell me
she was coming?
What's the big deal?
I thought we were over this.
Are you over it?
You should get to know her actually.
She's a really great person.
Maybe I should just make
her one of my bridesmaids.
Please don't make this weird.
Everything's fine, for once,
let's just have some fun
tonight with no drama.
Okay.
You know, it's kind of
ironic that Thys asked me
to be his best man considering
I was his worst brother.
So that makes him either
the biggest moron
Or the most forgiving
guy that I've ever met.
I'm proud to be your brother.
- Love you, man.
- Love you, buddy.
You're the best.
And Bree, I did not
forget about you.
I know that we don't know each other
that well yet, so you might not care
what I have to say, but
I think I have a message
from somebody you do care about.
Oh, who could it be?
Who does Derek have a direct line to?
He really wanted to be here
tonight, but he, you know,
I guess he's a busy guy.
So if you could direct your attention
to the back, I have a
special message for you.
Reading from our nation's Capitol.
I'd like to take a moment
and offer a special congratulations
to Thys Chesterfield
and his lovely fiance,
Bree Carrington.
Tomorrow's the day
you've always dreamed of,
now make that dream come true.
I'm Mitt Romney and I
approve this marriage.
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ When I look in your eyes ♪
♪ I see two eyes that
look just like me ♪
♪ And I know that you marrying Bree ♪
♪ But I want you to know
that I'll always be ♪
♪ Your OB, older brother ♪
♪ Older brother, your OB ♪
♪ Older brother, older brother,
your OB ♪
♪ Your OB ♪
Dear Bree,
I know this is crazy,
but for the first time in my
life, I don't know what to say.
We're supposed to write
something that will help you
prepare for your big day.
But I mean, I'm 13, what do I know?
I'm not gonna make a list
of marriage qualities
because if your fiance has
already won mom's approval,
you know he's a catch.
So I'm gonna take it to
the next level.
The thought that keeps coming
to my mind is just to be brave.
You know that as much
as we've been excited
for it, we've always been a
bit scared to get married.
I mean, how do you ever
know that it's truly right?
The answer is maybe you don't.
Maybe the best we can do
is make a choice.
If what you choose
makes you feel peaceful,
be brave about it.
If it doesn't, be brave
about that too.
That’s it, just be brave.
Sincerely, yourself.
The night we broke
up was the hardest thing
I've ever experienced in
my entire life,
but I knew I had to do it.
I had to listen to my 13
year old self.
I had to be brave.
As much as Thys loved me, he
somehow wasn't to put us first.
I loved spending time
with him, but I never felt
completely safe
or at peace when I was with him.
I know Thys will grow to
be a great man
and he will make a great
husband, just not the one for me.
It's a horrible realization
to have the day before your wedding,
but that's how long it
took me to figure it out.
Oh my brave little Bree.
The next morning when I
saw my family,
I remembered what it was like
to feel completely safe again.
Why are you guys all dressed up?
Well.
Apparently bud was
so inspired by the wedding spirit,
he proposed a sister
Rockwell that very morning.
Not one to waste time or money,
she decided to carpe diem.
And the smile on her face helped me
forget my pain for a moment.
♪ I know that the view from my side ♪
♪ You showed me every way you go ♪
♪ You don't like to feud, am I right ♪
♪ And maybe it's supposed to show ♪
♪ No body grove, they
grove with no body ♪
♪ We all grove, don't go ♪
♪ Go ahead on ♪
♪ Go ahead on baby, just go ahead on ♪
♪ You look like you a dream made of ♪
♪ You took me on tonight ♪
I was worried about
talking to people that night.
I thought they wouldn't understand,
that they would judge
me for calling it off
so late, but in truth, everyone
was really understanding.
Turns out a lot of people
have stories just like mine,
broken hearts, broken engagements,
and of course, broken marriages.
People ask me if I had
the chance to do it all
over again, would I change anything?
It's hard to say.
Sure, I would have saved myself a lot
of heartache and saved my
parents a lot of money.
But that experience became
a part of who I am today.
I made those choices and
I accept the consequences.
Honestly, I don't know if I
would change it if I could.
All I know is that I'm not ashamed
to say that once I was engaged.
So that’s my fun fact.
What about you, Sister Roblez?
You don't have to think of one
now, we have plenty of time.
♪ 10 to midnight ♪
♪ And my thoughts tick
like bombs in my head ♪
♪ Only one life ♪
♪ And I'm walking a tightrope
like it's last day ♪
♪ Down in the alley words take
over walls, the graffiti ♪
♪ Reads like a message,
it's subliminal ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm running through the city ♪
♪ All the pretty lights a line ♪
♪ In the corners of my eyes ♪
♪ All the faces in the rear-view ♪
♪ Are gonna fade into gray ♪
♪ I gotta go catch that train ♪
♪ I'm running through the city ♪
♪ All the pretty lights a line ♪
♪ In the corners of my eyes ♪
♪ All the faces in the rear-view ♪
♪ Are gonna fade into gray ♪
♪ I gotta go catch that train ♪
♪ Drove for miles on this dusty road ♪
♪ Felt so lost and on my
own with you ♪
♪ With you, with you ♪
♪ Life has had me up a creek ♪
♪ Been up here this entire
week with you ♪
♪ With you, with you ♪
♪ And I'm feeling a little better ♪
♪ And I think it comes down
to a few small letters ♪
♪ T-O-G to the E to the T ♪
♪ Then you add on HER and
it's together ♪
♪ T-O-G to the E to the T ♪
♪ And then you add on
HER and we're together ♪
♪ Together keeps our fears faraway ♪
♪ Together, we are dry in the rain ♪
♪ Together, here we are
underneath the sky of stars ♪
♪ Together, we share joy and pain ♪
♪ T-O-G to the E to the T ♪
♪ And then you add on
HER and it's together ♪
♪ T-O-G to the E to the T ♪
♪ And then you add on
HER and we're together ♪
♪ T-O-G to the E to the T ♪
♪ And then you add on
HER and it's together ♪
♪ T-O-G to the E to the T ♪
♪ And then you add on
HER and we're together ♪
- Hello, good afternoon.
- Hi, good afternoon.
I’m Sister Carrington
and this is my companion,
Sister Roblez.
We’re representatives of The Church
of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints.
I don't know if you've ever
heard of that church before.
Oh okay, great.
Well, we would just love to
share a message with you.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull