(film reel clicking)
(solemn music)
(shovels thump)
(solemn instrumental music)
- [Teddy] Deep in the
Appalachian Mountains,
people here, they play by their own rules.
There are secrets that
never leave these hills.
Summer of 1929 was the year I turned 13,
a summer of loss, fear, and
the beginning of a new chapter.
I lost my father in a railroad accident,
and I became the man of the
house while still a child.
- [Both] Ready, set!
- [Teddy] My best friend, Willy Stamper,
lived up on Adam's Ridge.
(water splashes)
His daddy hated mine, never knew why.
They had a feud between them
since me and Willy was born.
Do you, William John Stamper
accept the Lord Jesus
Christ as your savior?
- Oh yes, Lord.
Please, forgive me.
- And do your repent for all your sins?
- Yes, Lord, please forgive me.
- [Teddy] But Mama, she
always let Willy come over.
We were as tight as shoe leather
until one day that
would change everything.
(melancholy music)
(majestic orchestral music)
(bright music)
Willy!
- Shh!
Teddy, if I don't make it back home alive,
you gotta tell my girl I love her.
(bright music)
Incoming!
(Willy spits)
No!
(Willy grunts)
- Damn it, Willy.
You always die first.
I never get to die first.
- Come on, come back.
Can't you tell my legs
are full of shrapnel!
I could shoot you from here and lame ya.
- [Teddy] I'm going swimming.
- Wait up!
(majestic orchestral music)
- The water is so cold.
- Yeah, I tell ya.
- We better pick up the
pace, we can't be too late.
- Why is he always so mad?
- Who?
- Your daddy.
- Buck?
I don't know.
Think it might be all that drinkin'.
First the war, then Mama left him.
You lucky you don't have a daddy.
- Take it back.
- What?
- I said take it back right now.
- Jeez Louise, Teddy, don't
got your panties in a bunch.
I just meant your lucky you
don't have a daddy that hits ya.
I guess any daddy's better than no daddy.
- My daddy was a good
man, salt of the earth.
You think we got enough crawdads?
- Probably not.
I can handle the Buck,
just make sure he's got plenty of drink.
He'll be asleep all night.
Teddy, look!
- [Teddy] What?
- A quarter.
- Let me see that.
Wow, a real quarter.
- This is going in my getaway jar.
- Your what?
- I got a jar under my porch.
It's full of every change I find.
One of these days I'm
gonna run off from here.
I ain't never coming back.
- You can't leave me, Willy.
You're my best friend,
what'll do I do without you?
- Jeez, Teddy.
Hey.
I got an idea.
(Willy groans)
Give me your hand, come on now.
- What are we like, eight?
- Well, I already cut myself
so you ain't backin' out now.
(boys groan)
Now, we're full-on blood brothers.
Can't nobody ever take us apart.
- That stings.
Mama's not gonna like this.
She's gonna think I was being careless.
- She'll be all right.
- She lost her husband and her baby.
Maybe we can cut her some slack.
- Come on, let's go.
- That's it?
- Yup.
That's my getaway jar.
- Why is it full of dirt?
- It's not all dirt.
Feel how heavy.
'Cause if Buck finds it,
he'll think it's a jar of
dried money nightcrawlers.
But really it's my jar of get away money.
Pretty smart, huh?
- Yeah.
So you water it down every
time you add money to it?
- Yes, sir.
Sometimes when he sleeps,
I can get some change from his pockets.
He never knows.
Dimes are my favorite 'cause they're small
and they add up quick.
He never notices a few
dimes here and there.
- How much you think you got in there?
- Hard to say, but I'm getting close.
- [Buck] That you boy?
Get on in here.
- Ah shit.
- You wanna have supper at my house?
- So, then Teddy gave me three dips.
That should get me in, right?
- I don't know what I'm
gonna do with you boys.
You know this can get infected.
- That's what I told him,
and he didn't listen.
- [Willy] It's fine.
- All right, well you're clean for now.
I'm sure it won't stay that way.
- Hey Willy, you want to go
catch some lightning bugs?
- [Willy] Oh yeah.
- [Clara] All right.
- [Teddy] Come on.
(footsteps patter)
(crickets chirp)
(light clicks)
- Where you been, boy?
- Me and Teddy was
catching lightning bugs.
- Well, I can see that.
I'm not an idiot.
Wipe your face.
So you with that boy, that bastard boy?
- His daddy died.
(ominous music)
- So you went to that
Smallwood place again?
- No, sir.
(hand slaps)
- Don't you lie to me, you hear me?
- Yes, sir.
- Go clean up, get to bed.
(train horn honks)
(solemn music)
(horn whistles)
(train chugs)
(train carriages thud)
(whistle blows)
- Dad!
(Teddy gasps)
(birds chirp)
- [Willy] Gotcha! (laughs)
- Dang it, Willy.
You know what Buck might've done
if he saw me peaking in
his window like that?
- (laughs) Oh, he ain't gonna hurt nobody.
He's out like a light.
- What happened to you?
- I guess we didn't get enough crawdads.
- He hit you?
- Oh, I got him good.
I peed in his drink.
He's so drunk he don't even notice.
- That's not funny, Willy.
Look at your eye.
- Here you go.
Breakfast?
- No thanks, they'll give me the runs.
You too if you're not careful.
- Not me.
(teeth crunch)
Guts of steel!
(hand taps)
- So, what do you want to do today?
- I got an idea, let's have some fun.
Hold my apple.
(playful music)
(bright music)
- Willy!
Buck's gonna kill us if he
finds us playing with his gun.
- Come on, don't be a scaredy cat.
You getting soft on me?
- No.
- Come on!
- Willy!
(sighs) Wait up.
(gunshot pops)
(body thuds)
(Teddy groans)
(Willy laughs)
- Oh, Teddy, I thought you
was gonna piss yourself.
- What?
I can't hear a thing.
- [Willy] You done gone deaf soon.
- I just wasn't ready, that's all.
- Here, let me show you how to do it.
See that coffee mug?
I'm gonna get that one.
(gunshot pops)
- [Teddy] Ha, you missed!
- I'll get it this time, you watch.
(gunshot pops)
(can rattles)
Yeah!
Told you so, got it
square between the eyes!
- Okay.
Come on, let me try.
(trigger clicks)
I think we're outta bullets.
- Hey, how adventurous you feeling?
- Should I be worried?
(adventurous music)
- Come on!
(boys grunt)
(tractor idling)
Listen, you hear that?
- Yeah, sounds like a tractor.
- Come on, let's go!
- Wait.
- Come on!
- No, wait, Willy.
(tense music)
(tractor idling)
- Teddy, he left it idling.
- Okay, so?
- Come on, let's go.
- We can't just go take it.
- Teddy, it's like he's begging
for us to just go ride it.
Let's go, come on!
- No, we can't just ride it.
Wait, Willy.
- I'm going with or without you.
(bright music)
- Willy!
- Climb up here.
- Me?
- Yes, you.
Come on.
(tractor idles)
All right.
First, release the break.
Then you pull a little on the throttle.
- This thing?
- That's it.
Now, it ain't easy, but you
gotta get it out of neutral.
Put it into gear.
(tractor engine hums)
Throttle, throttle!
- I'm trying.
(chuckles) Woo hoo!
- Come on!
- I'm trying!
I'm getting it!
I'm like a tank! (roars)
- You shoot the missiles and
I'll take the ground cover.
- Yeah, woo!
- Come on, pick it up!
- I can't go any faster!
- I can literally run circles around you.
- I'm going through the compound!
Woo!
(Teddy laughs)
(suspenseful music)
Woo!
Yeah!
Willy, Willy!
Willy!
Willy, stop, stop, no!
Willy, stop!
Help, help, Willy!
Willy, stop, stop!
No!
♪ Just as I am, without one plea ♪
♪ But that Thy blood was shed for me ♪
♪ And that Thou bid'st me come to thee ♪
♪ Oh lamb of God, I come ♪
♪ I come ♪
(birds chirp)
- Folks.
These services are probably the hardest
for me to get through.
It ain't right
that any parent should ever
say goodbye to their child.
But Jesus said, "Let
the children come to me
"and do not hinder them."
For to such they belong
to the kingdom of heaven.
He heals the brokenhearted
and binds up their wounds.
For this child, I prayed
and was granted my petition.
Therefore, I have lent him to the Lord.
- Enough.
Open it.
- Mr. Stamper, I don't think
that's a very good idea.
That little fellow's in some rough shape.
- I don't remember asking
you, now do I, Pastor?
So if you'd so kindly do as I ask
and open up the goddamn
casket before I kick it open.
(tense music)
- Don't look.
(solemn music)
(Teddy whimpers softly)
- Look at him.
Look at him!
(Teddy cries)
You did this.
- Teddy!
- You killed my boy!
You killed my boy!
(solemn music)
(shoes thud)
(Teddy whimpers softly)
- Now, let's have a look.
- What you working on?
- Just a silly little drawing.
- Hey, don't sell
yourself short, young man.
You are quite the artist.
Your daddy loved your drawings.
(car engine hums)
(tense music)
- Mom, it's Buck.
He's got a gun.
- Teddy, take the girls to their room.
Girls, go with Teddy.
(tense music)
(crickets chirp)
Can I help you, Mr. Stamper?
- Send that boy out here.
- Mr. Stamper, I think
you had a little bit
too much to drink.
- Don't you tell me anything, woman.
I said send that boy out here right now.
- I will do no such thing.
Now you best be leaving my home.
(rifle cocks)
- The way I see it, you got two choices.
You either send that boy
out here and I kill him,
or you give that boy to me.
It's the only right way.
It's the only right
way, an eye for an eye.
Your boy killed mine, now I kill yours.
- [Clara] You ain't taking my boy.
- I'll kill him, it's your choice.
- Like hell you will.
(tense music)
What happened to Willy was
tragic, but it was an accident.
I know you are in pain,
but my Teddy loved him.
I loved him.
You aren't the only one mourning here.
So, I advise you to go
home and sleep it off.
- You don't preach to me.
Now that boy's coming
with me, dead or alive.
And if I have to take
all you out, so be it.
I got enough bullets.
- It's okay, Mom, I'll go.
(tense music)
I don't want anyone else to get hurt.
- Teddy, you get back
inside, he can't take you.
You get back inside.
- Mom, Mom, Mom!
- Teddy, no.
Teddy, let him go!
Let him go!
- Please stop!
(Clara shouts)
(Buck groans)
(foot thuds)
(Buck grunts)
(Teddy shouts)
- No, Mom!
(Buck grunts)
(motor hums)
- Teddy!
Girls, get back in the house!
Get back in the house, lock the door!
Lock the door!
No, Teddy, Teddy.
- Mom!
- Huh?
- No, no, don't hurt her, please!
- He's my boy now.
You say goodbye, son.
He'll never come back.
- Teddy, no, don't!
You son of a bitch!
No, Teddy!
(solemn music)
No!
No! (cries)
(suspenseful music)
- Get out.
Get out.
Get up.
I said get up!
(Teddy groans)
(Buck grunts)
(latch rattles)
(footsteps patter)
Welcome to your new home, boy.
Way I see it.
If my boy has to sleep in the ground,
you sure as hell could sleep on it.
(door creaks)
(Teddy whimpers)
(lock rattles)
(Teddy cries)
(birds chirp)
(rooster crows)
(door creaks)
Get up.
I said get up, come on, boy.
You're not gonna be lazy around here.
There's work to do.
Now get out to that
coop, bring in the eggs.
You ain't so ignorant you
can't figure that out, right?
- Yes, sir.
(rooster crows)
- I said git, come on now.
What is wrong with you, boy?
You messed up in the head
or do I have to get my belt on you?
- I have to pee.
- Well, you know where the woods are.
Now, get to them chickens
and bring in the eggs.
I like mine over easy.
And don't break my yolk.
(rooster crows)
(cars hum)
(heels clack)
(door creaks)
(doorknob rattles)
(hand bangs)
- Hello?
(spatula scrapes)
(spatula clangs)
(plate clatters)
(coffee splashes)
(toast snaps)
(teeth crunch)
(coffee splashes)
(liquor splashes)
(fork scrapes)
(footsteps patter)
- Sheriff.
- I'm the deputy.
- He took my son.
- Hold on now.
You say somebody took your boy?
- Yes, Mr. Buck Stamper,
up on Adams Ridge.
- Stamper.
- He took my Teddy.
- He's the one who lost his boy, right?
- Yes, please.
You have to help me.
- Now, Ma'am, I reckon
this is a better job
for the sheriff himself.
- Fine, where is he?
- Well, now he's in Charlottesville,
and he'll be back tomorrow.
- You have to do something.
He is going to kill my boy.
- (sighs) My hands are tied.
I promise you, the sheriff
will take care of it.
Now why don't you run along back home,
and I'm going to call him in the morning.
- You're not gonna do nothing?
- Ma'am, I suggest you calm down.
Now that man is suffering,
and he's just lashing
out at your boy, okay?
We'll handle everything.
- You better pray hard
my son is all right.
- Oh, I'll pray.
You should pray too.
After all, he did kill his boy.
(door slams)
- Coward!
(broom scrapes)
(shoes thud)
- Sit.
I said sit.
You ain't walking around this
farm with that long hair.
It ain't clean, and you ain't
bringing lice into my home.
You best be still.
(bird warbles)
(chain rattles)
You better eat somethin'.
You're gonna need your
energy for tomorrow.
You can make a bed out
of one of them bales.
Get another blanket from the horse.
(chain rattles)
(dramatic music)
- I'm coming home, Mama.
(thrilling music)
(door thumps)
(hand scrapes)
(thrilling music)
(footsteps patter)
- I see you, boy.
(suspenseful music)
(footsteps patter)
(Teddy groans)
You think you could get away from me?
I own you, boy, come on!
- Ow, ah, stop!
Please, please stop!
Ah, ah!
(belt whips)
(Teddy screams)
No, ow, why are you doing this to me?
Why? (screams)
- [Buck] 'Cause you killed my boy.
You killed my boy!
- No, no, ow!
Please, stop!
- The only thing I had.
Huh, you hear me?
You don't ever try to
run away from me again.
If you do, I'll take one
of them sisters of yours.
If they run away, I'll take your Mama.
Get up.
Huh, get up.
(Teddy shouts)
(Buck grunts)
(Teddy groans)
I had a fine boy.
He was good, and now I got you.
Pathetic.
You ain't half the boy Willy was.
(Teddy cries)
(door creaks)
(engine hums)
(tires rumble)
(car doors thud)
(door creaks)
Morning, Sheriff.
Little early for a house call, ain't it?
- Morning, Mr. Stamper.
Sorry to hear about your son.
I got Ms. Rogers here.
She tells me you came and
took her boy against his will.
Is that true?
- Why don't you ask him yourself?
(Teddy grunts)
(shoes thud)
- What happened to you, baby?
- Now, boy, you want to tell
me what's going on here?
You got your Mama mighty
shooken up about this.
You afraid to talk, boy?
What happened to your face?
- Teddy, come on, let's go, baby.
He can't hurt you no more.
- Now, Buck.
I don't know what you have in mind here,
but that boy ain't yours.
He belongs...
- No!
- Home with his Mama.
- I fell off the truck.
- [Sheriff] What'd you say, boy?
- I said I want to stay here.
This is where Willy was.
I don't want to go back with you.
- Now, it seems like we've
arrived at an impasse.
You heard the boy.
He wants to stay here.
- Boy, why don't you want to go home?
- This is my home.
I don't want to be with a bunch of girls.
I need a man in my life.
If you brought me back, I'd just run away.
- Now, we'll just give him a few days.
- No, that is my son,
and I am not leaving here without him.
- Now, now, you heard the boy!
- Teddy!
- We force him to go, he'll just come
on right back.
- Teddy, come home!
Teddy, I love you, Teddy!
Teddy, come home!
- I guarantee...
- No, you have to stay,
you have to get him!
- Give it just a few days.
- No, please!
- He'll be running down your driveway
in just a few days now.
- Please, please.
- You just get on down now.
- Please.
- You know kids, now come on.
- Teddy, Teddy, I love you, baby!
I love you, come home, Teddy!
(melancholic orchestral music)
Teddy!
(motor hums)
(melancholic orchestral music)
(somber music)
(footsteps patter)
(dimes jangle)
(birds chirp)
(dishes scrape)
- Sounds like a goddamn parade in here.
Can you be any louder?
- It's Thursday, we need milk.
Gonna need to head into
town if we expect to be...
- Don't tell me what needs
to be done around here, boy.
- You want your egg fried?
- Don't I always want my egg fried?
- Yes, sir.
(motor hums)
(lid scrapes)
- [Buck] What the hell
you doin' in here, boy?
- Nothin', just thinkin'.
- You stealing from me?
- No, sir.
Willy must have found that years ago.
- Don't you ever mention my boy!
Huh, you understand that?
He would have been one hell of a man
had you not killed him.
I'll teach you to steal from me.
(belt whips)
(Teddy groans)
(fist smashes)
(Teddy grunts)
(fists smashes)
(Teddy groans)
(suspenseful music)
(fist smashes)
(knee smashes)
Willy!
Willy, help me!
- Don't you call on Willy.
You never cared about him.
We did all the work.
When Willy died, I took his place,
but this ends tonight you
will never hurt me again,
and you will never
threaten my family again.
(tense music)
(latch clicks)
(suspenseful music)
(top rattles)
(gasoline splashes)
(suspenseful music)
(lighter clicks)
(flames crackle)
(suspenseful music)
(mallet thuds)
(Teddy grunts)
(flames crackle)
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
(Teddy groans)
(Teddy panting)
(somber music)
(shoes thud)
Mama!
Girls, anybody home?
Hello?
Mama?
(shoes thud)
Girls, come on, anybody?
Hello?
Mama?
(shoes thud)
Girls.
(Teddy panting)
(head thuds)
(gunshot blasts)
(ominous music)
(shoes thud)
(dramatic music)
(birds chirp)
(pump creaks)
(water splashes)
Thank you, Willy.
(glass shatters)
(majestic music)
(cars hum)
(people chatter)
(majestic music)
(shoes thud)
- What are your plans for the day?
- Well, we were supposed to
have a picnic, but the rain.
- (laughs) Isn't that always the way?
- Always.
- Okay, that'll be five cents please.
- There you go.
- Thank you so much.
Here you are.
- Have a good day.
- You too.
(register rings)
Can I help you?
- Me?
- I'm not looking at
anybody else, now am I?
- No, Ma'am.
- How much for an apple
and two jerky sticks?
- That'll set you back about four cents.
- And a hard boiled egg.
- Another two cents.
- All right.
- That'll be 6 cents there, big spender.
You all right?
- Oh my goodness.
I don't need all this!
Unless you'll be needing half the store!
- No, Ma'am.
I think that'll be all.
(register dings)
- You forgot your change.
(door creaks)
(door thuds)
(dramatic music)
(motor hums)
(tires squeak)
(footsteps patter)
- Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
Pardon me, pardon me.
(man groans)
Here you go.
(footsteps patter)
Hey, Willy!
- Can I help you?
- Um, I'm sorry, sir.
You know where public records are?
- That way.
- Thank you.
(footsteps patter)
(women chatter softly)
Oh, oh my gosh, I am so sorry.
- Oh no, they were all
separated by jurisdiction.
- I'll gladly help.
- It's all right, I can do it.
- [Man] (groans) Sarah.
- I can resort them.
- It's my fault, sir.
- [Man] Are you from around here?
- No, sir.
Just looking for somebody.
- Who you looking for?
- Clara Rogers.
Maybe you got records or
a forwarding statement?
- Clara Rogers.
You mean Old Widow Rogers up on the Ridge?
- Yes, sir.
I believe that's her.
- There's no forwarding address for her.
You might want to check the cemetery.
- Beg your pardon?
- After her husband died, her
boy, he killed another boy.
And then he ran off.
And then she got scarlet fever real bad,
and the state came and took her girls.
Why are you asking?
- I'm mostly interested in her place.
- Well, in that case I'd try the bank.
They'd have the records
and lien information.
(hand taps)
Good luck, son.
(footsteps patter)
It's a good farm.
Somebody oughta be living in it.
(footsteps patter)
(dramatic music)
(footsteps thud)
- Whoa, hey, hey, whoa, whoa, easy now.
- I need to get help.
- What's wrong, is that blood?
Are you okay?
- We snuck into the mill
when everyone left for lunch
and Paul, he's trapped inside the gears.
He's bleeding pretty bad.
We're in so much trouble.
- Just tell me, where is he?
- Downstairs of the Wells grain mill.
In the grinding room.
- Okay.
(suspenseful music)
- I need a big stick, like
a garden rake or something.
- Oh, um.
(footsteps thud)
(dramatic music)
- Gosh
(footsteps thud)
(Teddy grunts)
- [Elizabeth] Here, try this.
- You gotta come over here.
- Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
- Okay, come on, grab him, grab him.
Okay, ready, pull.
- Okay.
- Pull, now!
(Teddy grunts)
(Elizabeth grunts)
- [Elizabeth] Oh my God, oh my God.
(dramatic music)
(footsteps thud)
- Hey, he needs a doctor, quickly.
- [Man] Uh, I can take
him, follow me, come on!
- Careful, careful.
(Teddy grunts)
- Guys, come on.
Doc, Doc, there's been an accident.
It's Mr. Wells's nephew, sir, it's Paul.
- Dear God, put him on the table.
- Greta has the day off today.
I'm gonna need one of you
boys to stay and help.
(Doc groans)
That's not gonna work.
Can you tell me how long
he's been unconscious?
Son, you with me here?
(footsteps patter)
(doorbell chimes)
- What the hell happened to you?
- Passed out from the blood, sir.
It's mighty bad.
- Why don't you head back to the mill.
We got a pretty big mess to clean up.
(doorbell chimes)
- What in the Sam Hills
all the ringing in here.
Oh, Clarence.
Suppose you're here to
check on your nephew.
- How is he, Doc, I
heard it was pretty bad.
- You heard right, but he's gonna make it.
The leg, I'm not so sure,
but we did our best.
If it wasn't for your employee back there
helping with the boy,
your nephew might be talking to St. Peter.
- You mean Howard, who just left?
- No, the young man in back.
He stayed and helped me stabilize him.
Couldn't have done it by myself.
Sheriff is bringing an
ambulance to get him
over to Charlottesville.
- If you won't be
needing me any more, sir,
I think I'm gonna head out.
- What's your name, son?
- Ted.
Uh, Theodore, sir.
Theodore Rogers.
- Hell of a job, Mr. Rogers.
That boy owes you his life.
- Glad I could help.
- Hey, hey, son!
Hey, stop there!
- Sir?
- I'm Mr. Wells, I'm
the owner of that mill.
So you're the fella that
carried Paul from the mill here?
- (stammers) Yes, sir.
- I need to shake your hand.
You saved that boy's life.
- I just carried him.
- Don't be humble, you
did an amazing thing.
You looking for a job?
- Oh yes, yes, sir.
- Be at the mill at dawn tomorrow.
I'll have a job waiting for you.
How's $8 a week sound?
- That's fine, I'll be there.
- Starting tomorrow, you can
use one of our delivery trucks
to go to and from and to get your own.
All right, get on out of
here and change them clothes.
You're a fearful sight!
(shoes thud)
Gentlemen, you remember Theodore Rogers.
He's gonna be delivering with us.
Let me show you how we do this.
Now on Tuesdays and Thursdays,
you come over here and
you see how many bags
go to Charlottesville, how
many bags go to Jacksonville.
Now, each driver's responsible
for their own vehicle.
You fill it, deliver it and get
it back here by supper time.
The rest of the days, you just
spend here filling the bags
and grinding the corn
into mash, sound good?
- I can do this.
Thank you for the opportunity.
- Oh, and Theodore,
next time you play hero,
try to spare me some equipment.
(Teddy chuckles)
(mill machinery hums)
(motor hums)
(bags thud)
(Teddy grunts)
(car door slams)
(handle rattles)
(Elizabeth chuckles)
(footsteps patter)
- You all right there, big spender?
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm just used to cranking
it a little differently.
- Oh yeah, sure.
Those cranks can be real tricky.
You have no idea what
you're doing, do you?
- It's been a while.
- (laughs) All right so.
(groans) Just start your engine.
You're gonna want to press
on that lever to your right
and turn your key.
That's your coil buck switch.
Good job.
- Okay.
- Now, you need to make
sure your car is in neutral,
which is this lever in the center.
- Okay, right here?
- Mm-hmm.
Now, you have two pedals on your left,
which are your clutch and your brake.
And then this pedal on the
right is your accelerator,
which is going to advance the car.
So, first we clutch and then you gas.
(tires rumble)
Good job.
Now actually, if you turn right up here,
I know a really good
place for you to practice
before you head out for delivery.
(tires rumble)
(motor hums)
Good job.
Good job!
Now, you need to make
sure that it's in neutral
before you try and start it again.
(laughs) You'll get it.
Not too bad for your first driving lesson.
- Second, it's my second time.
- Well, you're a very good cranker.
So, are you going to drive me back to town
or do I need to walk home?
- Sorry, I'll take you home.
(engine revs softly)
- (laughs) I'm glad you
remembered the lever.
(motor hums)
(birds chirp)
(door thuds)
- Can I help you?
- Yes, I have a delivery.
Cornmeal from Wells Feed and Grain.
- Ah, you must be our new driver.
- It's you!
You're a real hero.
Good news spreads like
wildfire around these parts.
- 10 bags, that sound right?
- Yes, Ma'am.
- You can put 'em in
the back with the rest.
Melanie will show you where.
- Right this way.
- [Woman] Go on girls.
- Candy!
- Girls, no running, be respectful.
(girls chatter)
- One piece each, girls, just one.
- [Woman] You both excited?
- Yes.
- Yes, all right.
There you go.
You're picking out the two very best ones.
- [Girl] Mine is bigger than yours.
- Let me show you what
we got in the other day.
Come over here.
Look at these little twin dolls.
Don't they look just like you?
Look at their twin dresses.
- This one looks like me.
(gentle music)
- What about this one over here?
(people chatter softly)
Nice to see you, stay out of the heat.
- That family that was just in here.
- Reverend McCall, them little girls?
- Yeah.
Have they always lived here?
- Sure.
Except them little girls.
Their Mama got real sick and
she couldn't take care of them.
And the Reverend and
his wife weren't blessed
with any children so they stepped in.
What part of the country are you from?
- Ma'am.
- You from Maysville or you
here in Charlotte, Jackson?
- Oh, neither really.
I'm just from up the Ridge.
- You're awful young
to be out on your own.
- I'm almost 18, Ma'am.
Thank you, have a good day.
(distant thudding)
- Is that you, Daddy?
- Elizabeth.
- Hi, Daddy.
(lips smack)
What brings you into town this afternoon?
- Oh, thank you, darling.
- Of course.
- I heard you got in the car
with some young man yesterday
and headed outta town.
- You spying on me, Daddy?
- Spying is such a harsh word.
- He's not a stranger, he's a hero.
Did you hear about that man
who saved Paul Wells at the mill?
So you can see he's not all that scary.
- I heard you helped
in that rescue as well.
That's my girl.
What do you know about him?
That's what makes him a stranger.
- Hi, can I help you?
- Y'all got anything to drink around here?
- I can pour you a glass of sweet tea.
- (scoffs) That's not exactly what I'm
in the market for, young lady.
- There's a little thing
called prohibition, sir.
We don't break the law here.
- Well then I guess I'll
just take some sugar
and corn mash then.
- I can get you the sugar,
but the mash is gonna be over at the mill.
- Well, that's about ignorant.
- I believe your time here is done.
- Who the hell are you?
- You got no business here.
- That's a hell of a
way to treat a patron.
Show me some respect.
I could teach you a
thing or two, young lady.
(chuckles) Oh.
- Daddy!
- All right, looks like
somebody struck a nerve.
(motor hums)
(footsteps patter)
- Hey, big spender.
- Howdy, Ma'am.
- Howdy Ma'am, that's all you got to say?
- Ma'am?
- You are quite the talk
about town, you know.
A real life hero.
Oh, and humble too.
- All in a day's work.
- I spoke too soon.
- I better get going, Mr.
Wells is expecting me.
- Oh, but we don't want
to keep the mayor waiting.
- Mr. Wells is the mayor?
- Where are you from hero?
- Around.
- Oh, I like a mystery.
What's the name a hero goes by nowadays?
- Theodore.
My name is Theodore Rogers.
- Well, Theodore Rogers,
you and I made a pretty
good team the other day.
Maybe we can work
together again some time.
Welcome to Maysville.
- Say,
what does a clerk from the
general store go by nowadays?
- I'm gonna make you work for that one.
(footsteps patter)
- Mr. Wells, sir, I have your invoice.
- Well, I hope you have a
little bit more than an invoice.
Like about 110 more things.
- Yes, sir.
- I must admit I wasn't expecting
to be carrying money like that.
- You got nothing to worry about.
(chuckles) If you have any trouble,
use that Colt .45 under your seat.
Ain't nobody gonna bother you
with that peacemaker in your lap.
- Night boss.
- See you later, boss.
- Good night, boys,
see you in the morning!
- Say, you hungry?
- [Teddy] Yes, I could use a bite.
- Excellent, let's you
and me grab some supper.
Have you eaten at that
restaurant in town yet?
- No, sir, but I must admit
I'm kind of short right now.
Maybe another time?
- Oh nonsense, my treat.
I'll tell you, Della
makes the best biscuits
and fried apples this
side of the Mississippi.
(guests chatter softly)
- [Della] Well, here you go, gentlemen.
Excuse me.
Will you be having any iced
tea with that or coffee?
- Coffee?
Thanks, Della.
You know, son, for you to
drive the truck back here today
with all that money in your pocket
shows a lot about your character.
I ain't never let nobody
but family deliver for me.
Of course, I never had a son of my own,
but if I did, I'd hope he'd
have character like you.
Integrity.
- Thank you, sir.
- Two coffees.
Enjoy your dinner.
- Thanks, Della.
I'll tell you, them taters
have just the right crunch.
- They look delicious.
Say, Mr. Wells, can I ask you a question?
- [Mr. Wells] Well, sure,
son, what do you need to know?
- Well, there's this young
girl over at the general store.
- Oh, Mr. Smallwood's daughter.
- Smallwood, like the
berry farm Smallwood?
- Berry farm, general store, horse farm.
Good family.
- What's her first name?
- Elizabeth.
She's the only daughter.
Has three sons too.
- Elizabeth Smallwood. (chuckles)
(utensils clang)
Looks like it might rain later.
Thank you for dinner.
- My pleasure.
Theodore, I think I'm
gonna give you an advance
on this week's salary.
You never know when you might need to buy
something at the store.
- Why are you being so
kind to me, Mr. Wells?
- I like you, you impressed me.
Have a good evening.
(shoes clack)
- We gotta stop meeting like this.
- Well, hello there,
Ms. Elizabeth Smallwood.
- Gee, detective, that
sure didn't take long.
You must've been working
real hard to get my name.
- Maybe.
- [Elizabeth] How was your
ride to Charlottesville?
- Ah, it wasn't too bad.
- I'm glad.
(rain pours)
Do you want another driving lesson?
- Yeah, that'd be nice.
(car door thuds)
So, where do you want to go?
- Now, where is the
romance in asking a woman
where she wants to go?
Take me somewhere I've never been.
(crickets chirp)
You did good, Mr. Rogers.
This is quite nice.
- I used to play here as a
child with my best friend.
- I bet you fished and threw rocks
and caused all sorts of trouble.
- (chuckles) Yeah, something like that.
You know, I baptized him
right there in that spot.
- You were a strange kid, Mr. Rogers.
What do you like to do now?
Besides baptisms and lifesaving?
- What do you mean?
- For fun, you a wild man?
- Oh, no, nothing really.
- Nothin'?
Everybody likes something.
- I like to draw.
- Michelangelo, aye?
- Michael, who?
- Theodore Rogers, you don't
know who Michelangelo is?
- No, Ma'am, I'm not familiar
with any of the Angelo family.
- (laughs) He painted the Sistine Chapel.
The Creation of Adam?
The Statue of David?
We're gonna need to work on this.
Where are your folks?
- They're passed.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Your best friend?
My, Mr. Rogers, you sure
hold some serious heartache.
Is your world always this sad?
- Up until now, I reckon so.
- Well, I guess we'll
need to fix that then.
- What are you doing?
(zipper clatters)
Okay.
Yeah.
And there's the dress, right.
(Elizabeth giggles)
(water splashes)
- Oh, it's freezing!
- You'll catch your death.
- I'm fine.
Oh, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine!
(Elizabeth giggles)
Baptize me, Theodore Rogers!
Wash me of my sins of what I have done
and what I am about to do!
- You are crazy.
- Made you smile, didn't it?
No more heartache, Mr. Rogers.
(shoes thud)
(water splashes)
- You sure you want to do this?
- Save my soul, Theodore.
(water splashes)
(lips smack)
I saw the light.
- And we keep ending up in water.
- It must be destiny.
(dramatic music)
- Theo.
- I need to go.
I should get you home.
(water splashes)
- You'll need to take a right
at the fork in the road.
- Is this a horse farm?
- Yes, but don't go down the drive.
Just drop me off at the driveway.
- What kind of gentleman would I be
if I didn't walk you to your front door?
- A live one.
- All right.
- What happened back there?
Are we just gonna pretend we
weren't having a good time?
- It's hard to explain.
- I got time.
(bell chiming)
- Maybe not.
- You are saved by the
bell, Theodore Rogers.
(car door thuds)
And another thing,
Theodore doesn't exactly
roll off the tongue.
I'm gonna call you Theo or Teddy.
- My mother called me Teddy.
- Theo it is.
Sleep well, Theo.
I'll see you tomorrow.
(crickets chirp)
(head thumps)
- It's pretty late.
- Damn it, Daddy.
Not spying on me again?
- [Mr. Smallwood] Watch your
language, you're still a lady.
At least I hope so.
- What is that supposed
to mean, "hope so"?
- It's not proper for a young woman
to be gallivanting around
the whole damn country.
- [Elizabeth] Watch your language.
(door creaks)
- With some boy in the
late hours of the night.
And don't you get saucy with me.
Why are you wet?
- Well, Daddy, you have
nothing to worry about.
He was a complete gentleman,
despite my overtures.
So, you can sleep well tonight
knowing that your young, innocent
daughter is still a lady.
Good night.
(footsteps patter)
(motor hums)
(car door thuds)
(door thuds)
- Hello.
- Theo.
- I hear you have the best sweet tea.
- You have good sources.
(tea splashes)
Well?
- Mm, yup, that's delicious.
Don't tell Della.
(Elizabeth laughs)
I'm sorry about last night.
I was wondering if maybe you
can give me a second chance.
- What exactly were you thinking?
- Oh, I have something in mind.
You know, Elizabeth doesn't
exactly roll off the tongue.
I'm gonna call you Beth.
(gentle guitar music)
♪ Roots can't ground
unless a seed is sown ♪
♪ And trees without a
foundation can't grow ♪
♪ Though the soil of my
heart has been cold ♪
♪ These Kentucky mountain
songs have found their home ♪
♪ My roots are found at the
bottom of the Appalachians ♪
♪ They've been sown in coal ♪
♪ And watered by a bottle of bourbon ♪
♪ I can't cut them off ♪
♪ When I am just now learning ♪
♪ That my roots were made to grow ♪
♪ Into this bluegrass I call home ♪
(motor hums)
(suspenseful music)
(rifle cocks)
(rifle blasts)
(Teddy gasps)
(engine revs)
- Mr. Wells, sir.
I have your invoice and payment from
Jacksonville this week.
- Oh, that's fine, Theo.
And thanks for all the hard
work you're putting in.
How long has it been now?
- About three months, sir.
- Three months.
Never late, always willing to
lend a hand, strong as an ox.
I tell you, you're a
true asset to this mill.
- Thank you, sir.
Not to be rude, but I
do have someone waiting.
- Oh, I see.
You got a cold refreshing
ice tea waiting for you,
I presume?
You know, Theo, tea is a wonderful thing.
It's cool when you need
it, warm when you need it.
But you can't let it sit too long.
The ice melts.
And the warmth wears off.
And then all you got is something
that's just sitting there.
If you really want to enjoy
the freshness of that tea,
you gotta take the necessary steps.
Now, don't be pussyfooting around.
- We still talking about tea, Mr. Wells?
- (laughs) You tell me.
Do you know, Theodore.
I've never held the hand
of a woman after church.
Or carried a child to his
bed to tuck him in at night.
Don't make the same mistakes I made, son.
Don't let time slip away.
(gentle music)
- [Elizabeth] You're back a little early.
- Oh, light load in Jackson.
- Extra sweet, just like you.
- Oh.
- What?
- You're wearing pants.
- Yes, is that a problem?
You know, I vote too.
- I've just never seen a
woman wear pants before.
- Well, there's a lot of things in me
you haven't seen, Theo Rogers.
Imagine what's in store for you.
- Keep talking like that
and you might have just a little kiss.
- You do that in this town square
and this town would lock you up so fast.
- Oh, I'll take my chances.
- Oh, I have a gift for you.
It's a collection of Michelangelo's work.
The Sistine Chapel is on page 72.
- Wow, thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know I was thinking
I might take you somewhere tonight.
- You taking me back for
another dip in the creek?
You feeling sinful?
- Oh, not quite.
How about picking you up at six?
Don't keep me waiting.
(car door slams)
(lips smack softly)
- Theo, you can't be doing that in public.
- Sorry, I guess I can't help myself.
Sometimes you're just
more than I can handle.
Say, you know that man?
Never seen him in town before.
- He comes into the store every so often.
I don't know his name.
But he always smells like whiskey.
I guess every town needs a town drunk.
- Yeah, I guess.
Thank you for the tea.
You know it means a lot.
I'm grateful for every
time you give me this.
And the book.
I can't wait to read through it.
- Well, as long as you'll let me,
I will always have a tea for you,
but now I have to get back to the store.
I will see you tonight.
(footsteps patter)
(door thuds)
(Elizabeth sighs)
- [Mr. Smallwood] That was
quite the display out there.
- Whatever do you mean?
- You've been seeing that
boy for some time now.
- That boy has a name.
- I think it's time you bring him by.
- Why, Daddy?
So, you can tell him
that he's not good enough
for your only daughter?
- Now that's just not fair.
- What's fair, Daddy?
Are you telling me you're gonna
welcome him with open arms
and say, "Welcome to the family, son."
- You gotta give me a chance first.
He can't be all that bad
if you care about him.
- Now, Daddy, don't you go
be an all supportive on me.
- I'll give him a chance, Elizabeth.
- That's all I can ask for, Daddy.
Your move.
(pieces thud)
(Elizabeth laughs)
(bright music)
(car door thuds)
Where are we, Theo?
- (sighs) This is my home, I grew up here.
- It's beautiful.
(bright music)
(Elizabeth laughs)
(gasps) Theo, this is wonderful.
Oh.
Well, thank you.
You have green beans!
- Yes, I do.
- Did you make those?
- I did.
- They look incredible.
- And...
- Did you get those from Della?
- No, all me.
- Well, color me impressed.
- Well, I hope you're hungry.
Should still be warm.
- It looks perfect.
- You haven't even tasted it yet.
- I don't need to.
And you have such a lovely home.
- I tried to clean it a bit.
It has sat its spell.
- (laughs) It could use a woman's touch.
- I agree.
- Dinner was lovely.
Where'd you learn to cook like that?
- I used to cook for a
man I worked for once.
- Oh.
Well, I would let you cook for me anytime,
but don't break my egg
yolks, whatever you do.
(tense music)
(Teddy clears his throat)
Theo?
Theo.
(gentle music)
Do you mind telling me
what happened in there?
Theo, you're doing it again.
You're pushing me away.
What the hell is going on?
- He was not a good man.
He was evil, he was horrible.
- Who are you talking about, Theo?
- The man in town today.
- [Elizabeth] What man?
- The drunk.
He, uh...
- Theo, it's okay, I'm right here.
- [Teddy] No, I'm just being stupid.
- Theo.
If you do not let me in,
if you don't let me close to you.
Please, you have to let me help you.
- He hurt me as a kid.
He hurt me when I worked at his farm.
He...
- It's okay.
It's okay, I'm so sorry.
Theo I love you.
(bright music)
(lips smack)
- You're the most beautiful woman
in the world, Ms. Elizabeth Smallwood.
I need to stop here.
Some things are just worth waiting for.
(tires rumble)
(car door thuds)
(distant thudding)
(safety clicks)
(shoes thud)
Can I help you?
- It's alright, you can put away your gun.
- Ma'am, do I know you?
- I know you.
- You're from Charlottesville?
The Emporium.
- I guess you could say that.
Teddy.
(gentle music)
- My family called me Teddy.
- That's right.
Do you remember me?
Look closer.
It's all right, it's been a long time,
and I know a child's memory fades.
- My, how you've grown.
- Mama?
So, how long have you known?
- About a month?
Mr. Wells confirmed it for me.
He told me about your
mother and your sisters.
But when he told me about
your father and the railroad,
that's what I knew it was you.
- And you chose to stay away from me?
- I chose to do what you wanted.
Four and a half years ago you told me
that you didn't want me, that
you wanted to stay with him.
- Mom, I was protecting you.
Couldn't you tell?
- You told everyone I was dead.
- I was told you passed away,
and the girls were adopted out.
And then I went to
Charlottesville and I saw them.
It all made sense.
Wait, do you know about the girls?
- I know them, but they don't know me.
The pastor and his wife
bringing them around
once a month for me to see them.
They're very well cared for.
- It really is you.
- So, you don't hate me?
- No, Mama.
When I escaped I came looking for you.
- Did he hurt you?
- You don't wanna know that, Mama.
I'm alive, I'm here, we have each other.
(Clara whimpers softly)
- You've done very well with yourself.
You know, Mr. Wells,
he told me all about
that boy that you saved.
And some other things too.
- Other things?
- He told me about her.
- Elizabeth.
- I've seen her.
She's very beautiful.
Do you love her?
- I do.
- When you're ready,
I want you to give her this.
- No, Mama, this is the ring from daddy.
- I'd rather give it to
somebody who is in love
than keep it as a reminder
of the love that I have lost.
- Thank you.
When the time is right,
I will let you know.
I guess I better get going.
Lot of explaining to do.
A lot to talk to Beth about.
(floor creaks)
Can you stay?
Please, come home.
- You want me to stay?
- I'll figure this out.
You're safe.
This is the best day of my life.
I'm finally home.
(shoes thud)
- Theo!
Thank God.
You have never been this late.
We really need to get a phone
installed in that house.
I was worried sick.
- Listen, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
- There you are.
You know, I was just bragging
on you for your punctuality.
- Mr. Wells, look, I'm sorry.
- Well, hell!
Is that what I think it is?
- Theo, you said you needed
to talk to me about something?
- This isn't exactly how I planned this.
- Never is, son.
Come on, what are you waiting for?
The tea is getting cold.
- Ms. Elizabeth Smallwood,
would you do me the honor?
- Yes, Theodore Rogers.
I accept your offer of marriage.
- Woo, hot damn!
This is a cause for celebration.
What do you say we gather
all the folks tonight
in the Lewis and Clark ballroom.
I'll get Della to whip up a feast.
We'll have music and dancing
and celebrate your announcement in style!
- Tonight, sir?
- No time like the present.
- Thank you, sir.
I'm sure Pa would love to help as well.
- Now, don't you worry your
pretty little head about it.
Now, go on, get gussied up.
We'll see you tonight.
- Yes, sir.
I love you.
(lips smack)
- That is one happy lady.
You did good, son.
- Thank you, sir.
- Now, come on, we gotta
get you cleaned up too.
We got a party to plan.
(vibrant fiddle music)
(guests clap)
(guests cheer)
You're getting a fine
young man for a son-in-law.
- I don't know, Clarence.
Sure don't know much about him.
- What more is there to know?
He's a hero, he's a damn good worker,
and he's head over
heels for your daughter.
He'll be good to her.
- You don't know anything
about his family?
What he comes from?
They could be a family of
convicts for all we know.
- I assure you that
young man has character.
There's not an evil bone in his body.
I'll vouch for him.
- Is that right?
- Closest thing to a son I'll ever have.
(vibrant fiddle music)
(guests clap)
(guests cheer)
- Thank y'all so much,
I sure appreciate it.
We're gonna take a short break.
Y'all can come on up and grab some grub,
and don't forget to
congratulate the happy couple.
(guests cheer)
(door thuds)
- You look beautiful.
- Thank you, it was my mother's.
(spoon taps)
- Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight is a great night!
We're all united in support
of this fine young couple.
(crickets chirp)
(shoes thud)
- Evening.
Where are you going all gussied up?
- We were just celebrating Mr. Smallwood's
daughter's engagement.
- And you decided to stand
out here on the streets alone?
You looking for somebody?
- I'm gonna have to ask
you to leave her alone.
I'll be the one taking her home tonight.
If you're looking for
the party, it's inside,
but you're gonna have to leave her alone.
- Engagement party, huh?
Who's the lucky fellow who's gonna
roll into all that money?
- He's not from here,
you wouldn't know him.
None of us do.
His name is Theodore Rogers.
- Theodore Rogers, you're
like the son I never had.
And for an engagement gift,
I'm offering you a permanent
position at the mill.
Son, I'm offering you a foreman job.
Will you accept?
- Yes, sir, thank you, sir.
- All right.
(guests applaud)
- Thank you, thank you.
(hands clap slowly)
- Hip hip hooray.
Let's all give it up for the happy couple.
- Who in the hell are you?
- You're supposed to be dead.
- Mister, I don't know your
name or where you're from,
but we don't want any trouble around here.
So, why don't you get the hell outta here?
- You don't know my name.
You don't know my name.
Well, why don't you just
ask the groom to be here?
Ain't that right, Teddy?
- What's he talking about?
Theo?
- Theo?
(laughs) Who the hell is Theo?
Oh, he's got you all fooled.
You don't even know who you're marrying.
(laughs) Don't that beat all.
Lady, you're standing next to a murderer.
Go ahead.
Ask him, ask him if
he's ever killed anyone.
- What's he saying?
Is it true?
- I can explain.
It was an accident.
- You lied to me.
- I would...
- How could you?
- I would never lie to you.
(shoes thud)
Mr. Wells, I swear to you.
I was just a child, okay?
I was playing.
- Son, I'm the least of
your worries, now go.
- That's right.
You run, you coward!
You run just like you did
when you killed my boy!
My Willy was drug all across that farm,
cut all to pieces and dismembered.
From your hands!
- Mister.
- It's not true.
- Beth, please, stop.
Let me explain.
- Explain what?
That your name is really Teddy,
that you murdered someone?
- I told you, my mother called me Teddy.
- Oh, thank you for that.
You just left out the part
about killing another human being.
Damn it, Theo, I told my
father you were a good person.
I am so ashamed.
- Will you just listen to me?
- How could you embarrass me like that?
How would you embarrass my entire family?
I could never marry a liar,
let alone someone who
killed another person.
- Damn it, will you just let me explain?
- I can't.
- If you've ever loved
me for even a second,
you will let me explain.
I will tell you everything.
- Where are you taking me?
- Little Willy Stamper.
You're Buck Stamper, right?
- Who wants to know?
- My Pa was there.
He's the one who found Willy,
you can ask the sheriff.
- See?
Now you all know
that boy killed my son.
- It seems you and I
remember this differently.
They were two kids doing something
they shouldn't have been doing, yes.
It was an accident.
That's why no charges were
ever leveled against that boy.
They were playing with
your gun, Mr. Stamper,
before they got on that tractor.
If you'd been a better father,
your son would be alive today.
That boy, he ran to get help.
He tried to get his Mama to save Willy.
He never left him to die alone.
He left him to save his
life, and that's the truth.
(somber music)
- You're not welcome here.
Now get the hell out of
Maysville before we run you out.
(shoes thud)
(motor hums)
(tires screech)
(car door slams)
- Elizabeth, when I was a child, 13,
I was with my best friend, Willy.
We were playing bandits
with his daddy's gun.
Beth, the bullets ran out.
We went to your grandpa's farm.
- To steal his tractor, I know the story.
- No.
Because we wanted to be grownups
and drive the damn thing.
That's when things went terribly wrong.
Willy fell, and I couldn't make it stop.
- Who the hell are you?
- Everything he's saying is true.
- What is going on here?
- Beth, this is my mother.
- Oh, great.
More lies.
What's next, Theo?
Is your dead father going to
walk out of the chicken coop?
What is wrong with you people?
How long have you been
planning this charade?
And you have been coming to
the store for over a month now!
And the whole time you
were just fooling me
into being some part of
your big master scheme!
My God, I'm such a fool!
- No, it's not like that.
Okay, I just escaped a few months ago.
- [Elizabeth] From who, your mother?
- No, from the devil himself.
That man in town today,
he was Willy's father.
And when he died, I had to take his place
or he was gonna kill me
and my entire family.
I survived for four years with pure evil.
Being yelled at, beaten,
tormented every day of my life.
And he threatened to hurt
my family if I ever left.
And then a few months ago,
I went looking for the girls
and Mama, but they were gone.
And I went into town and I met you.
And I still see him.
Willy stills haunts me.
But he's my best friend, and
I never wanted him to die.
Never.
- Is this true?
(solemn music)
You did this to save them?
(motor hums)
- Well, ain't that sweet.
Got ourselves a real family reunion here.
You showing her your scars, boy?
I did you a favor.
You spare the rod, you spoil the child.
I made a man outta you.
You look different.
- Leave her alone.
- I can still see you clearly.
- Seems our little
agreement didn't suit you.
You left, not before
causing me to lose my barn.
- You tried to kill me.
- Deal's off.
Back to square one.
- So this is never gonna end?
- This is my family now,
and you are messing with the wrong...
- You better mind your little lady.
You don't want her getting hurt.
You're not gonna hurt her or anybody.
I've paid any debt I had to you.
I owe you nothing.
- That's not the deal.
An eye for an eye, a life for a life.
- Your reign of terror ends here, Mister.
Do you have any idea who I am?
I could have my daddy on you...
- Your Daddy can't help
you right here right now.
This gets settled tonight.
- Then take me.
- No, Mama.
- If you have me, I'll go with you.
I'll take his place.
- Well, ain't that a twist of fate.
Your Mama done saved you boy.
- I'll kill you.
- Teddy!
I love you and I can never repay you
for what you did for me and the girls.
But right now I need you to
put her in that car and go!
Go!
- [Buck] You best listen
to your Mama, boy.
- I love you, I'll be back for you.
- [Clara] Go!
- Stay strong, I'll have my
Daddy get you before sunrise!
- It's might chilly out.
Would you mind if I got my shawl?
It would make the ride more comfortable.
(solemn music)
- Kind of ironic, don't you think?
I ended up with you after all.
(solemn music)
(motor hums)
- We need to get straight to the sheriff.
- No, he won't help, I
just need to get you safe.
(gunshot pops)
Did you hear that?
- Gunshot.
Go.
(suspenseful music)
(Elizabeth gasps)
(Clara cries)
- Hey, Mama, hey.
You all right?
- I don't know, I don't know!
We were arguing and he was...
I went to get my shawl. (cries)
Theo, what do we do?
What do we do, Teddy?
- We get you somewhere safe.
(gentle music)
Elizabeth, you take her to safety.
- Okay.
Theo, are you coming with us?
- No, I've gotta stay with the body.
Send the sheriff, I'll take it from here.
It's all over now.
(solemn music)
Go.
(engine revs)
There are secrets in the mountains,
and sometimes secrets are covered by lies.
I know my Mama killed
Buck Stamper that night,
a secret I hold to this day.
But it wasn't until years later
she finally told me the truth.
(Clara groans)
- You got this, okay.
I can see the head.
(Clara whimpers)
(baby coos)
It's a boy.
William.
Little William.
He can't stay here.
- [Teddy] The truth was always there.
- John will now.
- [Teddy] I guess we just
choose to see what we wanna see.
- Think it might be all that drinkin'.
First the war, then Mama left him.
You lucky you don't have a daddy.
(tense music)
(solemn music)
- [Young Teddy] She lost
her husband and her baby.
Maybe we can cut her some slack.
- I don't know what I'm
gonna do with you boys.
You know this can get infected.
- [Buck] Look at him, look at him!
- My Teddy loved him too.
I loved him.
You aren't the only one mourning here.
- You didn't love Willy.
He was mine.
(solemn music)
You gonna tell him or should I?
He killed his own brother.
(gunshot blasts)
(birds chirp)
(solemn music)
- You can't haunt me anymore.
(gentle music)
- [Willy VOICEOVER] Now, we
are full-on blood brothers.
Can't nobody ever take us apart.
(gentle music)
- Rest in peace, Willy.
(majestic music)
(gentle music)