( starts engine )
( turns off engine )
♪ MY GAL IS RED HOT...
( tires screeching )
( siren blaring )
♪ WELL, I'VE GOT A GAL
♪ SIX-FEET-FOUR
♪ SLEEPS IN THE KITCHEN
♪ WITH HER FACE OUT THE DOOR
♪ BUT MY GAL IS RED HOT
♪ YOUR GAL AIN'T DOODLY-SQUAT
♪ YEAH! MY GAL IS RED HOT
♪ WELL, SHE AIN'T GOT MONEY
♪ BUT, MAN, SHE'S REALLY
♪ GOT A LOT
♪ YEAH! HA!
( tires screech )
( siren blaring )
♪ YEAH, MY GAL IS RED HOT
♪ YOUR GAL AIN'T DOODLY-SQUAT
♪ WELL, SHE AIN'T GOT MONEY
♪ BUT, MAN, SHE'S REALLY
♪ GOT A LOT
♪ WHOA!
♪ WELL, SHE'S THE KINDA WOMAN
♪ WHO'S A LOUNGE-AROUND
♪ SPENDIN' MY BUSINESS
♪ ALL OVER TOWN, BUT
♪ MY GAL IS RED HOT
♪ YOUR GAL AIN'T DOODLY-SQUAT
( screams )
( tires screech )
SHIT!
GOD DAMN IT!
♪ SHE'S A ONE-MAN WOMAN
♪ THAT'S WHAT I LIKE
♪ NOT A WISHY-WASHY WOMAN
♪ CHANGE HER MIND EVERY NIGHT
♪ BUT MY GAL IS RED HOT
♪ YOUR GAL AIN'T DOODLY-SQUAT
♪ YEAH, MY GAL IS RED HOT
♪ WELL, SHE AIN'T GOT MONEY
♪ BUT, MAN, SHE'S REALLY
♪ GOT A LOT
WHOA, STOP!
READY!
SEE ANY ACTION UP THERE?
A COUPLE OF FEDS.
NOTHIN' SPECIAL.
DONE?
DONE.
MMM.
PAPPY AIN'T LOST HIS TOUCH.
SMOOTH AS SILK. HEH.
WANT A CUP?
AIN'T OURS ANYMORE.
SKINNER ORDERED 150 GALLONS
FOR THE LODGE.
THAT THERE TANK HOLDS 152.
REMEMBER? I BUILT IT, I KNOW.
TAKEN YOUR CUT?
DOES IT NEED ANYTHING?
NO. CRUISED DOWN,
HARDLY GOT WARMED UP.
LISTEN, YOU GOTTA WAIT FOR
SKINNER, OR CAN I BUY YOU
A DRINK?
HELL NO. SKINNER CAN
HELP HIMSELF OUT BACK.
THAT'S SKINNER.
BESIDES, HE WANTS TO USE
HIS OWN JARS ANYHOW.
HEH HEH HEH.
OLD SKINNER WANTS
TO USE HIS OWN JARS.
THAT CAR IS A GODDAMN
TANKER.
COME ON, THERE'S GOTTA BE SOME
LIQUOR LEFT IN IT.
SON, YOU'D FIND MORE LIQUOR
IN A NUN'S HABIT THAN YOU WOULD
IN THAT LINCOLN.
( groans )
YOU BOYS WANT TO MAKE A MARK
AROUND HERE, YOU BEST DO THINGS
MY WAY.
SURE AS HELL,
YOURS AIN'T WORKIN'.
YOUR WAY? DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE YOU GOT A WAY.
LOOK, SHERIFF, THE BOYS
DOWN IN MEMPHIS WANT TO GET A
HANDLE ON THIS LIQUOR BUSINESS.
THERE'S THOUSANDS OF GALLONS
BEING MADE UP IN THOSE HILLS,
AND NOT ONE DAMN CENT
BEING PAID ON TAX.
IT'S AN EMBARRASSMENT
TO THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
SHERIFF, WE NEED YOUR HELP.
YOU KNOW HOW THESE BOYS
OPERATE, HOW THEY TRANSPORT IT,
WHO DRIVES.
PROOF.
YOU GOTTA CATCH ANY OF THEM
IN THE ACT, THAT'S WHAT YOU
GOTTA DO.
THIS GUY MULDOON--
YOU MUST HAVE MORE ON HIM
THAN JUST HIS WAR RECORD.
HEH. I GOT PLENTY.
JUST NOTHING I CAN
BURY HIM FOR...YET.
LOOK, HE'S GONNA BE GONE AS
SOON AS HE HAS HIS BREAKFAST.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO THEN?
YOU GONNA QUESTION HIM?
NO.
I'M GONNA GO HAVE
SOME COFFEE WITH MY WIFE.
THINK HE'S DIRTY, BILL?
IF HE'S ON THE TAKE,
HE'LL GO DOWN FOR IT.
BUT RIGHT NOW, WE NEED HIM.
MISSED YOU.
HI, LORNA.
ETHYL.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA
BE DOWN THREE DAYS AGO.
BEEN MEANING TO--
I NEED TO TALK.
IT'S BEEN KIND OF TOUGH--
FEDS SNOOPIN' AROUND AND ALL.
OF COURSE. I WOULDN'T DREAM
YOU'D COME ALL THE WAY DOWN
HERE JUST TO SEE ME.
IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
HEH.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE, JED.
WENDAL COMES AROUND ALL THE
TIME LIKE HE OWNS THE PLACE...
AND
ME.
ROSE HAS CHANGED THE LOCKS
THREE TIMES, HE JUST
KICKS THEM IN.
HE'S NEVER GONNA SIGN THE
PAPERS, NOT VOLUNTARILY.
IT'S BEST NOT TO PUSH HIM.
HE SCARES ME, JED.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M UP AGAINST.
I'VE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
I CAN'T LEAVE PAPPY
UP THERE ALONE.
WE'LL TAKE HIM WITH US.
OH, HELL. I'M LEAVIN'.
JUST STAY. IGNORE HIM.
I'M NOT JUST TALKIN' ABOUT
THE COFFEE SHOP, JED.
I MEAN THE TOWN.
FIVE DAYS--YOU'VE GOT TILL THEN
TO MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
THEN I'M LEAVIN'.
WELL, WELL, WELL.
LOOK WHO WE HAVE HERE--
MY LOVELY WIFE AND MR. MULDOON.
FAST CAR DRIVER.
EX-WIFE.
SO...
WHAT BRINGS YOU TO TOWN?
THE COFFEE.
IS THAT SO?
WELL, I'D BETTER
HAVE ME SOME, THEN.
LORNA?
MR. MULDOON HERE THINKS THAT
YOUR COFFEE'S GOOD ENOUGH TO
DRIVE ALL THE WAY DOWN
THE MOUNTAIN FOR.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT?
SAME AS ALWAYS, WENDAL.
SAME AS ALWAYS.
LOOKS LIKE YOU RUSHED DOWN HERE
TO GET SOMETHING YOU COULD'VE
GOTTEN UP ON THE HILL.
AND RUSH, I RECKON YOU DID.
SEEMS YOU PASSED A COUPLE OF
FEDERAL AGENTS ON THE WAY DOWN
LAST NIGHT.
HEH. THEY WERE MORE THAN
A LITTLE PISSED THIS MORNING.
SEEMS THEY WAS IN THE PROCESS
OF DRIVING INTO A DITCH
AS YOU FLEW BY.
THEY RECKONED YOU COULD'VE
HELPED THEM.
WHAT, TO GET IN THE DITCH?
( chuckles )
THEY SUSPECT YOU WAS CARRYIN'
A TANK FULL OF MOON.
THAT'S ILLEGAL, AIN'T IT?
YEAH.
SO IS SPEEDING.
WHAT'S OLD HOOCH GOT THE
LINCOLN PULLIN' THESE DAYS?
ABOUT 500 HORSES?
I HEAR IT'LL DO
MORE THAN A BUCK-SEVENTY.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THE COFFEE AIN'T THAT SPECIAL.
I'D BEST BE GETTIN'
BACK UP THE MOUNTAIN.
ETHYL.
SHERIFF.
IF I'D KNOW HE WAS BUYING,
I'D HAVE ORDERED BREAKFAST.
( chuckles )
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO HANG AROUND
A DUMB HILLBILLY LIKE THAT FOR?
HE'S JUST PLAYIN' WITH YOU.
LET ME OUT, WENDAL.
WAIT A MINUTE.
SIT DOWN HERE.
DON'T RUSH OFF.
WE NEVER TALK ANYMORE.
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO TALK ABOUT, WENDAL.
IT'S OVER BETWEEN US.
OH, WE HAD A LOT OF GOOD
TIMES, DIDN'T WE?
AND A LOT OF BAD TIMES.
DON'T MAKE THIS MORE DIFFICULT
FOR ME OR FOR YOU.
PLEASE JUST SIGN THE PAPERS.
I AIN'T SIGNING SHIT.
IT'S FINISHED BETWEEN US,
WENDAL!
DON'T YOU EVER RAISE YOUR
VOICE TO ME, YOU UNDERSTAND?
PLEASE JUST LET ME GO,
WENDAL.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
GO ON, GET OUT OF HERE.
LORNA?
GOIN' COLD ON ME.
IT'S NOT THE ONLY THING
GOIN' COLD.
WHEN ARE YOU GONNA GIVE UP?
HEH. SHE KEEPS WANTING
TO COME BACK.
YOU GONNA BE AROUND TONIGHT?
YEAH. I GOTTA WORK.
MAYBE I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
McCULLOUGH!
COME ON, DOG.
GO OKAY?
FINE.
SEE ETHYL?
YEAH, I DID.
YOU GOT A LOAD FOR ME TONIGHT?
THERE'S A MEETING TONIGHT.
ABOUT RUNNIN' CONVOYS?
YEP. AND DECOYS.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK
OF THAT.
WELL, YOU MAY NOT NEED ONE.
BUT YOU COULD DECOY
FOR OTHER DRIVERS.
BE LESS RISK OF GETTIN' KILLED.
WOULD THEM OTHER DRIVERS
BE THE CLAYTONS?
CLEM'S A GOOD DRIVER.
A GOOD FELLA.
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN THERE FOR YOU
WHEN YOU NEEDED HELP.
CLEM'S FINE.
HIS COUSINS ARE LOOSE CANNONS.
IF CLAYTON WANTS TO STAY
IN THE LIQUOR BUSINESS, ALL HIS
BOYS ARE GONNA HAVE TO DRIVE.
THERE'S NO SENSE
IN YOU DOING EVERY RUN.
YOU'LL GET FINISHED BURNIN' UP
ON THAT DAMN HIGHWAY,
IS WHAT YOU'LL DO.
HASN'T HAPPENED YET.
IT'S ABOUT TIME A FELLA
OF YOUR AGE GAVE HIS OLD MAN
SOME GRANDKIDS.
WELL, THERE'S MORE TO LIFE
THAN JUST RUNNIN' UP AND DOWN
THAT DAMN MOUNTAIN AT 140.
YOU CAN LEAVE THAT TO GUYS
LIKE THE CLAYTON BOYS.
AT LEAST THERE'S TWO MORE
OF THEM IF CLEM GETS
WRECKED UP SOME DAMN TREE.
THOSE BOYS AIN'T SAFE.
THEY DRINK MORE MOON
THAN I HAUL.
IS THAT WHAT YOU ARE?
SAFE?
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN FAST AND DANGEROUS.
I'M FAST, THEY'RE DANGEROUS.
NOW, AS YOU ALL KNOW,
THE FEDS HAVE SENT UP
A NEW TEAM FROM MEMPHIS.
SINGLE CARS ARE GONNA BE
TOO RISKY FOR A WHILE.
I BELIEVE WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
START RUNNING CONVOYS.
WHAT WE GOTTA DECIDE IS,
WHO'S GONNA BE RUNNIN' DECOY,
AND WHO'S GONNA LEAD.
GOOD EVENING, BOYS.
DON'T MIND ME.
NOW, PARKER...
YOU KNOW AND I KNOW THAT YOUR
BOY MADE FOUR RUNS LAST WEEK.
ONE OF YOUR DEPUTIES
CHASED HIM FOR 20 MILES.
GOTTA MAKE A SHOW OF IT
EVERY NOW AND THEN.
KEEPS YOU BOYS ON YOUR TOES.
GENTLEMEN, THERE'S GONNA BE
SOME CHANGES AROUND HERE.
THESE SPECIAL AGENTS HAVE BEEN
SENT UP HERE TO PUT AN END
TO YOUR OPERATION.
I THINK THEY'RE ON TO OUR
LITTLE ARRANGEMENT.
WE RUB THEIR NOSES IN IT,
WE'RE ALL GONNA GO DOWN.
SO, YOU'RE GONNA STOP
RUNNIN' FOR A WHILE.
STOP RUNNIN'?
JUST FOR A COUPLE OF
MONTHS--THREE OR FOUR, TOPS.
A COUPLE OF MONTHS?
YOU'VE BEEN PAID.
TAKE CARE OF IT!
IT PAYS FOR WHAT'S GONE ON
BEFORE, NOT FOR WHAT'S
GONNA GO ON.
I AIN'T GONNA WAIT.
THREE OR FOUR MONTHS.
MY BOYS WILL RUN AS USUAL.
( indistinct muttering )
YOU'RE ALL RICHER THAN GOD.
WHY DO YOU WANT TO PUSH IT?
'CAUSE IT'S OUR RIGHT.
IT'S AGAINST THE LAW.
( all laugh )
OUR KIN WERE MAKIN' MOON
IN THESE MOUNTAINS
BEFORE THERE
WAS
LAW.
( chuckles ) YOU OLD FARTS,
YOU OUGHT TO COME DOWN OFF THIS
HILL SOMETIMES AND TAKE
A LOOK AT THE REAL WORLD.
THE DAYS OF OUTRUNNING SOME FED
WHO MIGHT IMPOUND YOUR CAR,
THEY'RE OVER.
MY BOYS ARE GOING TO RUN.
IF THAT MEANS RUNNIN' CONVOYS,
THAT'S WHAT WE'LL DO.
BUT WE'RE GONNA RUN.
THEY CLAYTON BOYS RUN...
SO WILL JED.
WELL, YOU'VE BEEN WARNED.
YOUR BOYS RUN LIQUOR DOWN THIS
MOUNTAIN, I'LL STOP 'EM...
ANY WAY I HAVE TO.
♪♪
THERE'S A ROADBLOCK.
THERE'S THREE CARS,
AND MILLER'S WITH THEM.
IF MILLER'S WITH THEM,
THEY AIN'T GONNA GO FOR
NO DECOY CHASE.
WHAT'S WITH YOU, HAYWOOD?
THEY'RE GONNA GO FOR IT.
COME ON!
SHUT UP, CLANCY!
WHAT DO YOU RECKON, JED?
YEAH, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, IF YOU'RE WORRIED,
DON'T GO.
THERE AIN'T NOTHIN' WORSE
THAN RUNNIN' SCARED.
WELL, IF IT WAS JUST US,
YOU KNOW I WOULD.
IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW, RELYING ON
THOSE FELLAS, I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL HAVE TO PASS, FELLAS.
I'LL FOLLOW YOU BACK HOME.
YOU BE CAREFUL, JED.
I ALWAYS TRY TO BE.
WHY DON'T YOU SEND
YOUR COUSINS HOME BEFORE
THEY GET SOMEBODY KILLED?
SORRY, JED.
HEY, FORGET IT.
YOU'RE DOIN' WHAT WE
PROBABLY SHOULD.
SEE YOU.
YOU READY, HOTSHOT?
OR ARE YOU GONNA RUN HOME
AND HIDE, TOO?
( engine revving )
DUMB SHIT.
( tires screeching )
HANG ON!
HEE-HEE!
COME ON, SISSY BOYS!
CATCH THIS! YEAH!
KILL THAT MOTOR.
THAT'S JUST WHAT
THEY WANT YOU TO DO.
IT'S A DECOY.
THERE'S A TANKER OUT THERE
SOMEWHERE.
THEY AIN'T BUYIN' IT.
WELL, YOU GOT THAT GOOD
REINFORCED FRONT END.
YEAH, CLEM, IT AIN'T GONNA
HAPPEN TONIGHT.
NOW, COME ON.
IF IT LOOKS SAFE,
I'LL JUST FOLLOW YOU THROUGH.
MILLER AIN'T GONNA LET
TWO GET THROUGH.
YOU DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
YOU TAKE THE RADIATOR,
I'LL SHOOT THE TIRES.
( tires screech )
THE TIRES!
YOU SAID YOU'D SHOOT THE TIRES!
YEAH, WELL, I MISSED.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR BOY
PICKED THE WRONG PLACE
TO WATCH THE SHOW FROM.
( grunting )
♪♪
( glass shatters )
I'M GONNA GET OUT OF HERE.
I NEED SOME FRESH AIR.
CLAUDE, RUN THESE BOYS ON HOME,
BRING THE CAR BACK HERE
WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE GONNA NEED
A NEW DRIVER.
COUNTRY LIVIN' DOESN'T SEEM
TO AGREE WITH THIS BOY.
HE'LL LIVE.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOIN'
COMIN' IN HERE, WENDAL?
THIS IS
MY
HOUSE.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO,
SWEETHEART, CALL THE COPS?
GET OUT.
YOU CUT YOURSELF.
TROD ON SOME GLASS.
IT'S NOTHIN'.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING BREAKIN'
GLASS THIS TIME OF NIGHT?
WENDAL, PLEASE.
YOU GOT SOME BLOOD
ON YOUR LIP.
COME HERE. COME HERE.
LET'S YOU AND ME GO TO BED.
NO, WENDAL, NO.
UHH!
I TAKE WHAT I WANT...
ANYTIME I WANT. YOU UNDERSTAND?
PLEASE, WENDAL, NO!
NO!
WELL, WELL, WELL...
WHAT AM I INTERRUPTING HERE?
A LITTLE RECONCILIATION?
I WAS JUST VISITING.
YOU GOT NO RIGHT
TO BE HERE.
THIS POKEY LITTLE CORNER
OF TOWN HAS GOT ITS OWN LAW,
I GUESS, HUH?
SORT OF A DIFFERENT SET OF
RULES FOR THE HENHOUSE?
( chuckles )
YOU KNOW WHAT, WENDAL?
YOU SHOULD GO PLAY WITH
YOUR GUN SOMEWHERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
( chuckles )
I WAS JUST LEAVIN' ANYWAY.
GOOD NIGHT, LADIES.
BOCK-BOCK-BOCK-BOCK-BO-O-OCK!
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU COME IN THE NICK
TIME, ROSE.
AS LONG AS I LIVE, I WILL
NEVER UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU SAW
IN THAT SORRY SON OF A BITCH.
HONEY, YOU ARE GONNA HAVE TO
GO THROUGH WITH IT THIS TIME.
YOU ARE GONNA HAVE TO LEAVE.
'CAUSE ONE OF THESE DAYS,
I'M NOT GONNA BE HERE, AND THAT
MAN IS GONNA DO SOMETHING BAD.
I KNOW, I'M TRYIN'.
ETHYL, I HAD TO DO THE SAME
WITH MY EX IN TEXAS.
IF I HADN'T HAVE LEFT,
HE'D HAVE KILLED ME.
OR I'D HAVE KILLED HIM.
YOU HAVE GOT TO GO.
IT'S JUST--
I SHOULD'VE NEVER MARRIED HIM.
WELL...
WE ALL DO THINGS WE REGRET.
YOU JUST MAKE SURE YOU GO.
MULDOON'S JUST GONNA HAVE TO
MAKE UP HIS MIND WHETHER HE'S
GONNA COME AFTER YOU
OR LET YOU GO.
YOU JUST GET YOURSELF.
THE HELL AWAY FROM WENDAL.
YEAH.
YEAH, YOU DO LIKE
TO LIVE DANGEROUSLY.
IT SEEMS THAT WAY.
WELL...
MOTOR...
RUNNING GEAR ALL SEEMS FINE.
GOODRICHES AREN'T TOUCHED.
AND FRAME REINFORCEMENT'S
HOLDING UP REAL WELL.
LUCKY YOU'RE NOT DEAD.
YEAH, WE SHOULD BE RACING.
THE LINCOLN WOULD BE
PERFECT TO RACE.
HOW LONG, HOOCH?
THAT'S ANOTHER THING.
IF WE WERE RACING, WE'D HAVE
ALL WEEK TO GET THE CAR FIXED.
THEY MOSTLY RACE ON WEEKENDS.
WHAT'S ETHYL'S CAR
IN HERE FOR?
SERVICE.
SHE WANTS TO TAKE A LITTLE TRIP
IN A FEW DAYS.
DIDN'T WANT MILLER
TO KNOW ABOUT IT.
OH.
JED, DON'T YOU
GET ME INVOLVED.
YOU TWO GOT TO SORT IT OUT.
IF SHE WANTS TO GET THE CAR
CHECKED OUT, WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO SAY? NO?
YEAH, THEY MAKE MONEY--
THOSE RACERS.
GETTIN' MORE ALL THE TIME.
CROWDS, THEY LOVE IT--
SEEING ALL THOSE GOOD OLD BOYS
DRIVIN' SIDEWAYS.
DOOR-TO-DOOR, ABOUT 140.
YEAH, THAT'S THE FUTURE, BOY.
RACING.
140, HUH?
I DON'T TURN THE LIGHTS ON
TILL I'M DOIN' 150.
HOW LONG, HOOCH?!
A FEW DAYS.
THAT'S ALL I CAN DO FOR NOW.
YOU KNOW, I'M GONNA HAVE TO GET
SOME PANELS.
I DON'T WANT TO GO TO A DEALER.
COULD CAUSE TALK.
I MEAN, I'LL--I'LL--
I'LL TRY OUT THE TRACK.
THERE'S A COUPLE OF FELLAS
DOWN THERE THAT RUN LINCOLNS.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO COME ALONG.
YEAH, EARLY IN THE MORNING--
MAY AS WELL.
YOU'RE NOT GOIN' ANYWHERE
TILL I'M DONE HERE.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
IF I GO, WILL YOU SHUT UP
ABOUT IT?
NOT ANOTHER WORD.
GOOD. MAYBE THERE'LL BE
SOME BOYS PRACTICING.
22 FLAT!
DAYTON'S BEST TODAY
IS 23 AND CHANGE!
( laughs )
( girls cheering )
WHO'S THAT--IN THE CHEVY?
DAYTON.
DWAYNE DAYTON?
YEAH, HE RUNS HERE
ALL THE TIME.
HE WINS BIG.
USED TO BLOW HIS DOORS OFF
WHEN HE RAN LIQUOR.
HE AIN'T NOTHIN'.
♪♪
HE MAKES A GOOD LIVIN'
RACING.
THAT CHEVY RUNS STRONG.
YEAH.
AIN'T BAD FOR A CHEVY.
THEY MAKE A LIVING DOIN' THIS,
JUST DRIVIN' AROUND IN CIRCLES?
GOOD LIVING.
THIS IS WHAT'S HAPPENED TO
ALL THEM BOYS--THEM GOOD OLD
BOYS FROM ATLANTA.
THEY CALL IT STOCK CAR RACING.
IT'S SLOWER, THOUGH.
WELL, THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE
THE BEST DON'T RACE YET.
DINOSAURS LIKE YOURSELF STILL
TRYIN' TO BUST THROUGH
ROADBLOCKS.
IT'LL COME, THOUGH.
DAYS OF BEING SHOT AT AND
KILLED FOR A LIVING ARE GONE.
THE FEDS ARE USING AIRPLANES,
TIRE SPIKES.
AND THEY GOT RADIOS IN THEIR
CARS, ALL SORTS OF THEM.
THIS IS THE FUTURE--RACING.
A GUY LIKE YOU
IN A GOOD-LOOKING CAR COULD
MAKE SOME GOOD MONEY HERE.
( sighs )
YES, SIR!
( girls cheering )
21 FLAT, BOY!
JESUS, THAT WAS FAST!
YOU SHOULD STICK AROUND
AND SEE THE RACE.
COME ON, YOU GONNA GET THOSE
PARTS, OR ARE YOU GONNA SIT
AND WORSHIP THIS CLOWN ALL DAY?
THIS GUY MIGHT NOT BE
AS FAST AS YOU IN A LINCOLN,
BUT HE'S NO SNAIL.
THE GUY COULDN'T MAKE
A LIVING RUNNIN' LIQUOR.
THE FACT IS, HE GOT CAUGHT,
IF I REMEMBER.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOUR HERO IS SO DAMN GOOD,
HE GOT CAUGHT BY THE FEDS.
WELL, HE'S THE TOP DOG
IN THIS ALLEY.
YEAH, AGAINST OLD GUYS
IN SLOW CARS.
A LEGEND IN HIS OWN MIRROR.
SO, WHERE ARE THESE
LINCOLN FELLAS, HMM?
I'LL GO FIND 'EM.
HERE, GIVE ME ONE OF THEM.
HEH. ANY CHANCE OF YOU EVER
BUYIN' YOUR OWN SMOKES?
HEH.
MEYERS WILL NEVER
GET NEAR YOU.
DWAYNE DAYTON?
WHO WANTS TO KNOW?
RICKMAN. BUREAU OF
INTERNAL REVENUE, DIVISION OF
ALCOHOL, TOBACCO AND FIREARMS.
I WONDER IF I COULD HAVE A FEW
WORDS WITH YOU, UH...
IN PRIVATE.
WHY DON'T YOU TWO
CUTE THINGS GO WATCH THAT
RACECAR GO ROUND AND ROUND?
YOU MIGHT COULD SEE
A CAR WRECK. COME ON.
I MUST BE OUT OF MY MIND,
SENDING THEM AWAY TO TALK
TO REVENUE.
♪♪
YEAH, SEE THAT?
A MAN'S GOTTA KNOW
HIS LIMITATIONS.
YOU TRY AND RUN OUT OF YOUR
CLASS, YOU CAN LOSE IT ALL.
SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WELL, YOU, I BELIEVE,
USED TO RUN MOONSHINE
A WHILE AGO.
( scoffs )
WHAT'S THIS SHIT?
YOU KNOW THAT. YOU KNOW I SPENT
TWO YEARS IN THE PEN FOR IT.
I'M A PROFESSIONAL RACECAR
DRIVER NOW, HAVE BEEN FOR
MORE THAN A YEAR.
DOES IT PAY GOOD?
IT'S A LIVING.
THE GUYS BEHIND DON'T
SHOOT YOU.
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO GET
BACK IN THE LIQUOR BUSINESS?
ARE YOU NUTS?
I SERVED MY TIME.
YOU SCREW UP OUT HERE,
YOU'RE WRECKED, LIKE
THAT OLD CLOWN.
HE WRECKED UP, BUT HE DON'T
GET LOCKED UP.
THIS TIME, YOU'D BE WORKIN'
FOR
THE LAW, NOT AGAINST IT.
DOIN' WHAT?
SAME AS YOU DO HERE--
DRIVIN'.
DRIVIN' WHO AND WHAT?
ME, AND WHATEVER YOU WANT,
AS LONG AS IT'S FAST.
( laughs )
WHAT'S IT PAY?
TWICE WHAT YOU MIGHT WIN
HERE THIS AFTERNOON--
EACH TIME YOU DRIVE ME.
THERE'S NO "MIGHT" ABOUT IT.
I'LL WIN.
WHO WOULD WE BE AFTER?
OH, I'M SURE YOU KNOW
THEM ALL--LIQUOR DRIVERS.
FIRST OFF, A PAIR OF BROTHERS,
NAME OF CLAYTON, AND A GUY
CALLED MULDOON.
YOU KNOW HIM?
YEAH, I KNOW HIM.
MULDOON.
DOES THAT BOTHER YOU, GOIN'
UP AGAINST ONE OF YOUR OWN?
HE AIN'T ONE OF MY OWN.
GOOD. SO...
IT WON'T BE A PROBLEM
GOIN' UP AGAINST HIM?
KNOCKING HIM OFF HIS PERCH
WOULD BE A PLEASURE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
THEM MOUNTAIN BOYS CATCH WIND
OF THIS, THEY'RE LIABLE TO
KILL YOU AS SOON AS ME.
I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES.
WHAT ABOUT THAT CROOKED
SON OF A BITCH--MILLER?
HE IN ON THIS?
NO. HE DOESN'T EVEN NEED
TO KNOW ABOUT OUR DEAL.
DO WE HAVE ONE?
SO, YOU KNOW ALL ABOUT HIM?
I'M BEGINNING TO.
DO WE HAVE A DEAL?
LOOKS LIKE IT.
KIND OF LOOKIN' FORWARD TO
RUNNIN' UP ON MULDOON.
HE'S GOT MORE PARTS
THAN DETROIT BACK THERE.
WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
THE OLD BOY IN THE FORD
STEPPED OVER THE LIMIT.
NOT MUCH ELSE GOIN' ON.
LEASTWAYS NOT ON THE TRACK
ANYWAY.
♪♪
PA! PA!
CLAUDE AND ME BEEN TALKIN'.
WE RECKON WE GOTTA DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THAT SON OF A BITCH
MULDOON.
HE HAD TO BE IN WITH 'EM,
FOR THEM TO LET HIM THROUGH
AND NOT CLEM.
WHAT WE SHOULD DO IS SHOOT--
NOTHIN'!
LAST THING WE NEED AROUND HERE
IS A WAR.
JED WOULD NEVER CAUSE HARM TO
CLEM IF HE COULD'VE HELPED IT.
LET'S SHOOT THE BASTARD!
BLOW HIS GODDAMN HEAD OFF!
YOU'RE JUST GONNA SIT BACK
AND LET OUR COUSIN DIE
WITHOUT ANY REVENGE?
CLANCY, YOU DIDN'T
EVEN LIKE HIM.
YOU KNOW MULDOON'S BEEN
RUNNIN' AROUND WITH
MILLER'S WIFE.
SURELY HE'S GONE AND DONE
HIMSELF A DEAL IF HE
LEAVES HER ALONE.
I KNOW IT!
YOU DON'T KNOW NOTHIN'.
HE'S RIGHT! I'LL BET YOU!
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
THINK? HEH!
YOU TWO AIN'T NEVER HAD
A THOUGHT BETWEEN YOU.
THERE AIN'T GONNA BE ANYBODY
GETTIN' THEIR HEAD BLOWN OFF.
GO HOME, BOYS, BEFORE YOU GET
INTO SOMETHING YOU CAN'T
HANDLE.
( starts engine )
HEY, SHERIFF.
HOOCH.
JUST THOUGHT I'D DROP BY
AND SEE HOW THE CARS ARE DOIN'.
OH, THEY'LL BE A FEW DAYS.
MOST PROBABLY THE BEST PART OF
A WEEK BEFORE THE PARTS
COME IN.
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'
WITH THIS ONE?
JUST ALIGNMENT.
WAS SHE GOIN' SOMEWHERE?
JUST A BUMP ON THE CURB,
I GUESS.
THAT ONE THERE AIN'T WORTH
FIXIN', REALLY.
IT'S TOTALED.
HEH. YOU MEAN
YOU CAN'T DO IT?
OH, NO. I CAN--
I CAN FIX IT, BUT...
IT JUST DON'T MAKE SENSE.
IT'S GONNA COST YOU MORE
THAN IT'S WORTH.
WELL, YOU FIX IT.
I AIN'T GONNA HAVE SOME DAMN
MOONSHINER GOIN' AROUND
BRAGGIN' HE'S RIDDEN OFF
ONE OF MY CARS.
YOU'RE THE BOSS.
HMM.
ANYTHING ELSE COME IN WRECKED
LAST NIGHT?
YEAH, IT DID,
AS A MATTER OF FACT.
OH?
( laughs )
YEAH, SHERIFF, OLD MITCH ESTES
RAN INTO A TREE UP IN
THE WOODS BY STANFORD.
( tires screech )
I'LL KILL YOU,
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
NOW, BOYS, I TOLD YOUR PA
THESE FEDS MEAN BUSINESS.
GO HOME, BOYS.
DON'T MAKE IT ANY WORSE THAN
IT ALREADY IS FOR YOUR PA.
YOU STAY OUT OF THIS,
MULDOON.
WHAT THE HELL YOU KNOW HOW BAD
THINGS ARE FOR OUR PA?
HE'S RIGHT.
YOUR FAMILY'S ALREADY LOST ONE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
SHOOT 'EM BOTH! SHOOT 'EM!
( grunting )
GIVE ME THE GUN, MULDOON.
IF YOU THINK THIS MEANS
I OWE YOU, YOU'RE WRONG.
I COULD'VE KILLED YOU
LAST NIGHT.
IF YOU COULD'VE KILLED ME,
YOU WOULD'VE.
DON'T YOU EVER POINT
A GODDAMN GUN AT ME AGAIN.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
( tires screeching )
MM. I OWE YOU.
YOU MIND?
DO I KNOW YOU?
WELL, WE ALMOST MET
THE OTHER NIGHT, BUT WE KIND OF
JUST MISSED GETTIN' INTRODUCED.
RICKMAN. FEDERAL AGENT RICKMAN.
REVENUE.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO,
BUST ME FOR SPEEDIN'?
I SAW YOU JUST NOW OUTSIDE.
IT'S A SHAME, AIN'T IT?
ALL THAT TAXPAYERS' MONEY
WENT INTO TRAINING YOU, ENDS UP
BEING USED IN A STREET BRAWL.
I DONE MORE THAN MY SHARE
FOR THIS COUNTRY
AND ITS TAXPAYERS.
I KNOW, I READ YOUR
WAR RECORD.
YOU'RE VERY IMPRESSIVE.
DECORATED BY THE PRESIDENT.
HEH.
YOU DON'T REALLY WANT TO GO
TO JAIL NOW, DO YOU?
NOT AFTER ALL THAT.
LAST I HEARD, YOU GOTTA GET
CAUGHT DOIN' SOMETHING BEFORE
THEY SEND YOU TO JAIL.
NOW, HAS THAT CHANGED?
NO, NO, THAT'S STILL
THE WAY IT GOES.
THE THING IS, SOMEONE ELSE
CAN GET CAUGHT AND THEN TAKE
ALL SORTS OF PEOPLE DOWN
WITH HIM.
THERE'S NO SENSE WORRYING
ABOUT WHAT ANOTHER FELLA
MIGHT OR MIGHT NOT DO.
WHY THE HELL'S A GUY LIKE
YOU BOTHER WITH A BUSINESS
LIKE MOONSHINING?
YOU'RE RISKING YOUR LIFE
FOR WHAT?
IS IT THE DANGER, EXCITEMENT?
WHAT? IT SURE AS HELL CAN'T BE
JUST MONEY.
WHAT IS IT?
WELL, SOME PEOPLE DO THINGS
FOR OTHER REASONS MORE THAN
JUST MONEY--
BECAUSE IT'S THEIR RIGHT.
BECAUSE THEY ALWAYS DONE IT,
AND THEY ALWAYS WILL.
IT'S WRONG.
IT'S AGAINST THE LAW.
LAW ISN'T ABOUT RIGHT
OR WRONG, IS IT?
IT'S ABOUT GIVIN' YOU BOYS
A SLICE OF THE PIE.
IT'S NOTHIN' PERSONAL.
IT'S THE LAW.
I'LL TELL YOU, GOVERNMENT'S
NOT GONNA LET IT GO ON.
A FEW YEARS, THERE WON'T BE
A DRY COUNTY LEFT IN
THE WHOLE DAMN COUNTRY.
THERE'D BE NOWHERE FOR YOU
TO RUN IT TO BY THEN ANYHOW.
MOONSHINE'S A THING OF
THE PAST.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
I KEEP HEARIN'.
YOU GIVE ME MILLER,
YOU'RE OUT OF IT.
LET ME TELL YOU HOW
IT WORKS AROUND HERE.
WE KEEP TO OURSELVES,
FOR GOOD OR FOR BAD.
NOW, YOU WANT THE SHERIFF,
YOU GO RIGHT AHEAD.
YOU GOT SOMETHIN' ON ME,
YOU ARREST ME.
( indistinct chatter )
♪♪
YOU GONNA TELL ME ABOUT IT?
WHAT? OH, THOSE, UH--
THOSE BOYS THERE ARE COUSINS
OF THAT FELLA IN THE FIRE
LAST NIGHT.
NO. MULDOON.
WHY'D HE SAVE YOU?
SAVE ME? HEH.
HE'S JUST LOOKIN' AFTER
HIS OWN ASS.
HE AIN'T A COMPLETE FOOL.
HE KNOWS THAT IF A SHERIFF GETS
SHOT DEAD IN THE STREET,
YOU BOYS WILL SEND THE ARMY,
THE NATIONAL GUARD,
AND HELL-KNOWS-WHAT
UP INTO THEM HILLS, SHUT DOWN
EVERY DAMN STILL.
WELL, MAYBE THAT'S WHAT
WE SHOULD DO.
WHAT, SEND THE ARMY?
NO, I DON'T HAVE
THE POWER FOR THAT.
BUT I CAN GET MORE AGENTS
UP HERE. WE CAN GO UP AND FIND
THE DAMN STILLS.
AND JUST HOW ARE YOU
GONNA DO THAT?
FINDIN' THEM SHOULDN'T BE
THAT HARD.
THEY FEED THE USED CORN MASH
TO HOGS, RIGHT?
WE JUST FIND A HOG FARM.
STILLS CAN'T BE FAR AWAY.
( laughs )
MISTER, YOU AIN'T GOT A CLUE
WHAT YOU'RE TALKIN' ABOUT.
IS THAT RIGHT?
THEM MOONSHINERS, THEY GOT
MORE TRICKS UP THEIR SLEEVES
THAT YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE.
THERE'S ONE OLD BOY UP THERE,
HE HAD A SMOKESTACK THAT RAN
FOR A HALF MILE AND CAME OUT
UNDERWATER TO HIDE THE SMOKE.
THEY GOT UNDERGROUND BOILERS,
BOOBY TRAPS, SHOTGUNS,
AND MORE KIN THAN YOU CAN
SHAKE A STICK AT.
NO, SIR. YOU GO UP THERE,
YOU'RE DECLARING WAR.
BLOWIN' THEM TO HELL
ON THE ROAD--THAT AIN'T WAR?
HEH. GOIN' FAST AND
CRASHIN'--THAT'S A WAY OF LIFE
FOR THEM.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU DO?
JUST LET 'EM FEUD
AMONG THEMSELVES.
( laughs )
SO, YOU MEAN DO NOTHIN'.
THE CLAYTON BOYS WILL BE
DOIN' US ALL A FAVOR
IF WE JUST LET 'EM SETTLE THEIR
OWN ACCOUNT WITH MULDOON.
SAVE US ALL A LOT OF TROUBLE
AND THE TAXPAYERS
A LOT OF MONEY.
SO, I'M SUPPOSED TO CALL
MEMPHIS AND TELL THEM THAT
WE'RE JUST GONNA SIT AROUND
AND RELAX AND WAIT TILL THEY
KNOCK EACH OTHER OUT?
BEST THING ALL AROUND.
NO, SHERIFF.
THAT AIN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
♪♪
HEY, BILL, AL.
HOW YOU BOYS DOIN'?
HOW YOU DOIN'?
I'LL NEED FIVE BAGS.
AND GIVE ME YOUR TWO OLDEST
DAUGHTERS WHILE YOU'RE AT IT,
WILL YOU?
( laughs )
ALL RIGHT.
UHH! GODDAMN.
YOU MISS THIS?
I RACE, THAT'S WHAT I DO.
IS IT MORE EXCITING?
THAN BUYIN' LOADS OF SUGAR?
ALL OF IT--
RUNNIN', AVOIDIN' THE LAW.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHIN'.
RACING'S SAFER, IT'S SLOWER,
AND YOU DO IT IN DAYLIGHT.
NOW, DOING 160 BY MOONLIGHT,
DODGING ROADBLOCKS, YOU GUYS
RUNNING BEHIND, SHOOTIN'--
THAT'S EXCITING.
ALL RIGHT, BOYS.
SEE YOU IN ABOUT A WEEK, UNLESS
I GET THE OTHER BOILER GOIN'.
ALL RIGHT.
( starts engine )
HERE WE GO.
NOW, HE'LL STAND ON IT
WHEN HE GETS CLOSE TO HOME...
JUST TO MAKE SURE THERE'S
NOBODY ON HIM.
UNTIL THEN, HE'LL JUST
WANT TO CRUISE.
♪♪
WILL THIS STAY WITH HIM
IF HE RUNS?
( laughs )
WHOO.
LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE WENT OFF
THE ROAD IN THE WORST WAY.
GUY BY THE NAME OF
CLEM CLAYTON.
WELL, IT HAPPENS.
CLEM WAS WILD SOMETIMES.
YOU CAUSE IT?
I--I DON'T KNOW.
WE ON.
I'M GONNA CROWD HIM NOW,
SEE IF HE'LL PANIC.
LOOK AT THIS DUMB BASTARD!
HE'D HAVE STOPPED TEN MILES
BACK, WE'D HAVE NOTHIN' ON HIM,
NOTHIN' WE COULD'VE DONE.
HE'S RUNNIN' 'CAUSE IT'S ALL
HE KNOWS HOW TO DO.
HELL, HE AIN'T EVEN
BROKE THE LAW!
YEAH, EXCEPT SPEEDIN'.
HELL, THAT DON'T COUNT.
YOU SEE THAT? HE BRAKED FOR
THAT DIRT ROAD WITHOUT
EVEN THINKIN'--A REACTION.
BET YOUR ASS YOU GO UP THERE,
YOU'D FIND A STILL.
DO YOU WANT HIM?
WHOO!
WHAT THE GODDAMN HELL'S
GOIN' ON?!
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?!
AGENT RICKMAN, REVENUE.
WHO THE HELL'S THAT GUY?
IS THAT DWAYNE DAYTON?
SHIT!
DWAYNE DAYTON!
WHAT THE HELL YOU WANT FROM ME?
I AIN'T GOT NO HOOCH ON BOARD!
I'M ONLY CARRYIN' SUGAR!
WELL, THAT'S A HELL OF
A LOT OF SUGAR.
MAYBE IF I CRUISED UP THAT DIRT
ROAD BACK THERE, I WONDER
WHAT I'D FIND--MAYBE A STILL?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
( crying )
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
JUST SOME INFORMATION.
NAMES, DATES, THAT SORT
OF THING.
WHAT ARE YOU?!
YOU OUT OF YOUR MIND?!
LISTEN, I'LL COME BACK
WITH 50 AGENTS, AND I'LL BLOW
THAT STILL ALL TO HELL.
AND I'LL MAKE SURE EVERYONE
KNOWS YOU SHOWED ME WHERE
IT WAS!
SHIT, YOU'LL GO DOWN FOR
THREE YEARS ANYWAY, UNLESS YOU
GET YOUR GODDAMN HEAD
BLOWN OFF FIRST.
YOU GIVE ME NAMES, DATES,
DESTINATIONS, I'LL KEEP YOU
OUT OF IT.
IT'S YOUR CALL, BOY.
YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH,
BILLY BOB, HOW ABOUT A COFFEE?
THAT'S WHAT GONNA HAPPEN TO YOU
IF YOU STAY AROUND HERE.
END UP DRUNK AND ALONE.
I HEARD ABOUT YOUR FIGHT.
JUST A COUPLE OF
MOUNTAIN BOYS.
YOU GOTTA BE CAREFUL AROUND
THEM CLAYTONS, JED.
THEY'RE DANGEROUS.
YOU DON'T GET ME OUT OF HERE,
I'M GONNA DO IT MYSELF.
I'M GONNA GO,
WITH OR WITHOUT YOU.
PAPPY AIN'T READY YET.
NO, JED. IT'S YOU,
NOT HIM, THAT AIN'T READY.
ETHYL.
HOOCH.
IT'S DONE.
PRETTY GOOD, HUH?
EVERYTHING?
YEAH, PAINT'S DRYING NOW.
GREAT! WELL, YOU GOT
THREE DAYS.
YOU'RE STILL RUNNIN' LIQUOR
DOWN THAT MOUNTAIN AFTER THAT,
YOU'RE GONNA FIND ME GONE.
GIVE ME A SMOKE, WOULD YOU?
HMM. I THOUGHT YOU SAID IT WAS
GONNA TAKE A FEW DAYS.
WELL, HOW THE HELL ELSE
WAS I GONNA GET YOU DOWN
TO THE TRACK?
WHOO-WHEE!
LOOK AT YOU, LORNA!
NEED A DATE?
YOU LOOK GREAT.
SHE'S WAITIN' FOR WENDAL,
NOT YOU, HOOCH.
I'M SORRY, I DIDN'T MEAN--
DID JED TELL YOU...
I FINALLY GOT HIM DOWN TO
THE TRACK TODAY?
I'M IMPRESSED.
HOW'D YOU DO IT?
BY PROMISING TO SHUT UP.
( laughs )
HE WAS IMPRESSED.
WASN'T YOU, JED?
OH, THE HELL I WAS.
WAS?
ON A REAL ROAD, THOSE BOYS
COULDN'T RUN FAST ENOUGH
TO KEEP WARM.
( telephone rings )
YEAH, HELLO?
WHO?
IS THERE A RICKMAN HERE?
YEAH!
SCOOT OVER, HOOCH.
ANOTHER BEER.
IS THERE ANYWHERE ELSE
MORE PRIVATE?
YOU WANT PRIVATE, DON'T TAKE
YOUR CALLS IN A BAR.
GOOD-LOOKIN' GUY FOR YOU.
HONEY, YOU JUST REMEMBER
SOMETHING--NO MATTER HOW
GOOD-LOOKIN' OR HANDSOME
THEY SEEM, SOMEWHERE,
TO SOME WOMAN,
THEY'RE A PAIN IN THE ASS.
ROSE, DO I DETECT A HINT
OF BITTERNESS THERE?
OH, YOU JUST GO WASH UP
YOUR HANDS BEFORE YOU GREASE UP
MY BAR.
WHEN?
WHERE'S IT GOIN'?
DOWN THE MOUNTAIN.
THAT AIN'T VERY SPECIFIC.
WHO?
A FED.
REVENUE MAN.
REALLY?
LOOKS TOO NICE.
THOUGHT THEY WERE ALL SCUMBAGS
LIKE WENDAL.
YOU MARRIED HIM.
AND I LEFT HIM.
AT LEAST
I
DIDN'T RUN OUT
WITHOUT TELLIN' YOU.
HE CAME AROUND AGAIN, JED.
WELL...
WHAT KIND OF TIME?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHIT, NOT TILL I SAY SO,
THAT'S WHEN.
I'LL SETTLE UP.
SHERIFF.
HI, WENDAL.
LORNA.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA BE
A LITTLE EARLIER.
I GOT TIED UP.
DO YOU LIKE THE DRESS?
I WAS GONNA WEAR THE TAFFETA,
BUT I KNOW HOW MUCH
YOU LIKE LACE.
I GOT IT OVER AT EDNA'S
BOUTIQUE AFTER WORK ONE DAY.
GO AND GET THE CAR.
I OUGHT TO GO HOME.
MM-HMM.
STAY.
THAT'S JUST WHAT WE NEED--
HAVE HIM COME AROUND
AND SHOOT US BOTH.
STAY AT THE HOTEL, THEN.
OHH, WORK.
YOU KNOW, NORMA BROUGHT IN
HER WHOLE BROOD OF EIGHT KIDS.
THEY WERE ALL OVER THE PLACE,
THROWIN' FOOD...
( echoing ) PEAS AND CARROTS
AND POTATOES ON THE FLOOR
AND ON THE WINDOWS.
AND WHAT DOES SHE KNOW--
YOU WANT ANOTHER BEER?
OH. NO, I'M FINE.
WHOO-WHEE, SHE'S
A GOOD ONE, JED.
YOU OUGHT NOT TO LOSE HER.
YEAH.
UNTIL SHE'S DIVORCED,
AIN'T SAFE HER BEING WITH ME.
SHERIFF SHOOTS HIS CHEATIN'
WIFE DEAD, HELL, IN THIS
COUNTY, HE'D GET AWAY EASY.
HE KNOWS THAT, THAT'S WHY
HE DON'T SIGN THOSE PAPERS.
YEAH, WELL, IN A FEW MONTHS,
PAPPY WILL BE READY TO RETIRE.
IT AIN'T GOT NOTHIN'
TO DO WITH PAPPY.
AND YOU AIN'T GOT MONTHS, JED.
SHE AIN'T GONNA WAIT.
YOU KNOW, IN A FEW DAYS,
SHE'S GONNA BE--FFFFT! GONE.
I SEEN THIS BEFORE.
GUYS LIKE YOU THINK GIRLS ARE
GONNA WAIT AROUND.
IT AIN'T GONNA HAPPEN.
IF YOU KNOW SO DAMN MUCH,
HOW COME YOU'RE ALL
BY YOURSELF?
YEAH, I COULD DO WITH
A WALK ANYWAY.
BY THE TIME YOU GET THIS THING
GOIN', I'LL BE SLEEPIN'.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT MECHANICS
AND THEIR OWN CARS ANYWAY?
THIS IS A GOOD TRUCK.
IT'S JUST MY GODDAMN IGNITION.
IT'S GONNA START ANY SECOND.
( engine won't start )
IT'S BECAUSE I AIN'T GOT
NO DAMN TIME TO FIX
MY OWN STUFF!
I'M TOO BUSY PLUGGIN'
BULLET HOLES IN LINCOLNS!
IF WE WAS RACING--
SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
IT'S GONNA START
ANY TIME NOW.
5:00. BE THERE.
♪♪
YOU STILL RUNNIN' DOWNHILL?
YOU JUST KEEP DRIVIN'
AROUND IN CIRCLES.
THAT WAY, YOU WON'T GET LOST.
( engine starts )
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
HAD TO WALK.
YOU'RE HERE EARLY.
WENDAL LEFT THE BAR,
SO I TOOK THE REST OF
THE NIGHT OFF.
DON'T WORRY, I LEFT
THE CAR AT HOME.
HE WON'T KNOW I'M HERE.
YEAH? WHO LET YOU IN?
MISS EDGAR GAVE ME A KEY.
HMM.
I KNOW, I ONLY GOT THREE DAYS.
( laughs ) YEAH.
TILL THEN...
( moaning )
( dog growling )
McCULLOUGH!
WHAT'S ALL THE FUSS?
THERE'S NOTHIN' THERE.
( barking )
COME ON, COME ON.
STAY WITH ME.
STAY WITH ME, McCULLOUGH.
GOOD DOG.
STAY WITH ME.
GOOD DOG. COME ON.
DROP THE GUN, PAPPY.
DO IT REAL SLOW.
AT MY AGE, THE ONLY WAY
I MOVE IS SLOW.
DO SOMETHING WITH THAT DOG.
COME HERE.
LIE DOWN. LIE DOWN, McCULLOUGH.
COME ON, STAY.
STAY THERE. GOOD DOG.
YOU SHOULD'VE KEPT A BETTER
LINE ON YOUR BOY.
YEAH?
HE'S BECOME A REAL PAIN.
ARREST HIM, THEN.
HEH. WELL, WE BOTH KNOW
THAT WOULDN'T DO NO GOOD.
HE AIN'T NEVER GONNA LET UP.
GUYS LIKE HIM--
JUST GOTTA GET RID OF THEM.
IS THAT SO?
HOW ARE YOU PLANNIN'
ON DOIN' IT?
WELL...
EVERYBODY KNOWS YOU FELLAS
ARE ALWAYS FEUDING UP HERE.
THERE'S MORE THAN JUST ME
THAT'S GOT A BEEF WITH HIM.
THE CLAYTON BOYS--I FIGURE
THEY'RE CRAZY ENOUGH TO COME UP
HERE AND KILL HIS OLD MAN
AND LEAVE THE GUN HERE.
YOU THINK JED'LL BUY THAT?
YOU THINK HE'S DUMB ENOUGH
JUST TO GO ON OVER THERE AND
SHOOT 'EM SO YOU CAN HANG HIM?
WHETHER HE DOES OR NOT,
HE AIN'T GONNA BE ABLE
TO HELP YOU.
YOU DUMB BASTARD.
EVEN AS A KID, YOUR OLD MAN
USED TO TELL ME YOU WAS DUMB
AS A BOX OF ROCKS.
HEH.
HE USED TO FIGURE
YOU WEREN'T HIS,
THAT YOUR MA HAD A LITTLE
FLING WITH AN OLD HILLBILLY
FELLA, NAME OF GABBY.
( laughs )
HE WAS CERTAINLY DUMB ENOUGH
TO HAVE BEEN YOUR KIN.
KILLED HISSELF.
THE BEST THING, REALLY.
HE NEVER HAD TO KNOW YOU.
( laughs )
WELL, YOU TELL HIM HI
FOR ME.
( gunshots echoing )
♪♪
( engine revving )
♪ I'M GONNA GET
♪ SOME REAL GONE LOVE
♪ THAT'LL DRIVE
♪ A COOL CAT WILD
♪ I'M GONNA MOVE
♪ ROLLIN' RIGHT ON DOWN
♪ GONNA GET ME A GAL
♪ THAT'LL GO OUT ON THE TOWN
♪ WELL, YOU GOTTA
♪ MOVE ON DOWN THE LINE...
( engine revving )
♪ WHEN WE START STRUTTIN'
♪ GOTTA GO, GO, GO
( turns off engine )
McCULLOUGH?
( dog howling )
( howling continues )
PAPPY?
PAPPY? PAPPY?
WHAT THE HELL
TOOK YOU SO LONG?
WHO DID IT?
MILLER.
HE'S LOOKIN' TO BLAME IT
ON THE CLAYTON BOYS...
SO YOU'LL GO AFTER 'EM.
BE CAREFUL, JED.
I'VE GOTTA GET YOU
SOME HELP.
TOO LATE.
I'M ONLY ALIVE NOW 'CAUSE...
I WAS EXPECTING A RAID.
SO, I'VE BEEN CARRYIN'
THE ORDER BOOK.
DIDN'T THINK IT'D END UP
PROTECTING ME.
GIVE ME A SMOKE.
YEAH.
I'LL KILL HIM.
NO.
LET IT GO, JED.
HE'LL HANG HIMSELF IN TIME.
YOU JUST GET AWAY...
FROM HIM.
OFF THIS MOUNTAIN.
TAKE ETHYL AND MY HOUND
AND GO.
HERE YOU GO.
THERE'S ENOUGH LIQUOR
READY FOR A RUN.
TAKE IT AND THE MONEY...
AND GO.
MAKE A BETTER LIFE
FOR YOURSELF.
GET AWAY FROM THAT...
DAMN MOONSHINE HIGHWAY.
JED!
PAPPY.
NEVER, EVER LOOK BACK.
THINK YOU'RE GONNA
NEED THAT?
HOPE NOT.
YOU PREPARED TO
IF YOU HAVE TO?
HOPE SO.
WELL, YOU BETTER BE.
A MAN WITH A GUN HE CAN'T USE
IS LIABLE TO GET HIMSELF
KILLED, NOT TO MENTION
HIS PARTNER.
NOBODY'S GONNA GET KILLED.
I DON'T CARE IF ANYBODY
GETS KILLED--JUST AS LONG
AS IT'S NOT ME.
THAT'S A HELL OF
CHARITABLE OUTLOOK YOUR GOT
YOURSELF THERE.
YOU DIDN'T HIRE ME
FOR CHARITY.
♪♪
( sighs )
OHH.
( starts engine )
I JUST CAN'T FIGURE
YOU BOYS OUT.
YOU RISK IT ALL JUST TO RUN
LIQUOR DOWN A MOUNTAIN.
TO UNDERSTAND THAT,
YOU GOTTA KNOW HOW WE GREW UP.
SEE, UP IN THE MOUNTAINS,
WE WAS POOR...FOR GENERATIONS.
MORE THAN MOST OF YOU
CITY FOLK COULD UNDERSTAND.
RUNNIN' BOOZE CHANGED ALL THAT.
PEOPLE STARTED COMIN' IN
WITH A WHOLE BUNCH OF MONEY.
PROBLEM IS, THEY STILL
THOUGHT POOR.
STILL DO.
YOU GET POOR INGRAINED IN YOU.
I WANTED--
WANTED MORE.
STILL DO.
MORE WHAT?
EVERYTHING, MAN.
MONEY, RESPECT.
I WAS TIRED OF FEELIN' POOR.
SEE, UP THERE, EVEN IF YOU HAD
MONEY, YOU HAD TO ACT POOR.
THAT'S JUST THE WAY IT WAS.
YOU DIDN'T WANT TO LET ON
THAT YOU HAD ANYTHING FOR FEAR
OF GIVIN' THE GAME AWAY.
I WANTED TO FEEL RICH.
STILL DO.
RACING DO THAT FOR YOU?
SOME.
PUTS ME AT THE TOP
OF THE HEAP.
IT'S SOMETHIN' I'M GOOD AT.
BETTER THAN MOST
EVERYBODY ELSE.
SORT OF LIKE HOOCH WILSON
BUILDIN' TANKERS,
OR YOUR MULDOON THERE
RUNNIN' THE LIQUOR.
HE THE BEST?
HE THINKS HE IS.
EVERYBODY ELSE UP ON
THAT MOUNTAIN DOES, TOO.
( turns off engine )
( clicking )
( telephone rings )
HELLO?
HEY. YOU STILL GOIN'?
I'VE GOT TO GO, JED.
MIND IF I GO WITH YOU?
REALLY? YOU SURE?
YEAH. YEAH, I'M SURE.
JUST WAIT FOR ME.
I'LL WAIT.
NOT AT THE HOUSE.
CALL HOOCH, HAVE HIM
PICK YOU UP.
ALL RIGHT.
DO IT NOW, DON'T SPEND
A LOT OF TIME PACKIN'.
OKAY.
SEE YOU LATER.
JED?
I'M SO HAPPY.
OH, HEY, I ALMOST FORGOT--
YOU, UH--YOU LIKE DOGS?
YEAH.
EVEN OLD HOUNDS?
EVEN OLD HOUNDS.
GOOD.
OH, GOD, I'VE GOTTA PACK!
YOU'RE IN LUCK.
( sighs )
YEAH, I GOT TIRED OF LIVIN'
IN HIS GODDAMN SHADOW.
SO, I CAME DOWN OFF THE
MOUNTAIN, STARTED RACING,
MADE MY OWN SHADOW.
IS HE THE BEST?
BETTER THAN ME?
I'LL BLOW MULDOON IN THE
WEEDS, WE RUN UP ON HIM.
( telephone rings )
( ring )
HELLO?
I'M GIVIN' YOU A CHANCE
TO RUN.
IF YOU'RE STILL IN TOWN
WHEN I GET THERE,
I'LL KILL YOU.
TAKE THOSE.
AND THAT.
YOU SEE THE WAY THE MOON
HITS THE ROAD JUST ENOUGH?
SO, IF YOU KNOW IT--
I MEAN KNOW IT--YOU CAN RUN
WITH YOUR LIGHTS OFF.
AND STILL GO FAST.
REAL FAST.
♪♪
( starts engine )
SHOOT HIM!
YOU GOIN' SOMEWHERE?
WENDAL...
YOU AIN'T GOIN' ANYWHERE!
GODDAMN BITCH.
YOU THINK YOU CAN JUST
RUN OFF AND LEAVE ME?!
AFTER ALL I'VE DONE FOR YOU.
( scoffs )
SHOOT THAT DAMN CAR!
YOU AIN'T NEVER LEAVIN' ME.
I OWN YOU.
YOU'RE MINE.
YOU NEVER LISTEN.
( cars approaching )
LISTEN, YOU HEAR THAT?
IS IT THE CLAYTONS?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHATEVER IT IS, IT'S MOVIN'.
TIME TO ROCK 'N' ROLL, MAN!
IT'S DOUBLE STAMPS DAY!
MULDOON!
( indistinct shouting )
( shouting continues )
HOLD HER STEADY!
I'M RELOADING!
HE'S RIGHT THERE!
SHOOT HIM!
SHOOT SOMEBODY!
COME ON, MAN!
( tires screeching )
SHOOT HIM!
( shouting )
KILL THAT SON OF A BITCH!
GET AHEAD OF HIM!
HE'S RIGHT HERE,
ON YOUR SIDE! SHOOT HIM!
( screaming )
HANG ON TO SOMETHIN', MAN.
IT'S TIME TO SHOW MULDOON
WHO'S THE BOSS.
McCULLOUGH?
THIS BOY THINKS HE'S A HOTSHOT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE MAKE HIM ONE?
SON OF A BITCH
TRIED TO KILL US!
IF HE TRIED TO KILL US,
WE'D BE DEAD.
♪♪
COME ON.
SHE CALLED ME.
AND WHEN I GOT THERE,
MILLER HAD ALREADY LEFT.
POOR GIRL.
JED?
WHY DIDN'T YOU GET HER
TO A HOSPITAL?
SHE WANTED TO SEE YOU.
I WANTED TO GET TO YOU.
YOU NEED A DOCTOR, HONEY.
NO, I'LL BE FINE NOW.
DID THAT SON OF A BITCH
COME THROUGH HERE YET?
YEAH. HE'S BEEN AND GONE.
HE COMIN' BACK?
NO, HE'S GONE FOR GOOD.
AND US?
WE'RE STILL GOIN'?
YEAH. WE'RE STILL GOIN'.
IS THAT DAYTON AND--
AND THE FED?
YEAH.
WHAT THE HELL ARE THEY
AMONGST THE TREES?
YOU SHOULD GO ASK 'EM.
THEY MIGHT NEED A TOW.
THE FEDS WILL PAY.
IT'S GOVERNMENT BUSINESS.
WELL, LOOKIE HERE.
GEE, CURSES.
HEY, HOOCH?
YOU KNOW, YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT.
IF THAT'S THE BEST THEY GOT,
WE OUGHT TO BE RACING.
MM-HMM.
( starts engine )
♪ WELL, WHIRLWIND
♪ OF LOVE, MY DARLIN'
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE, MY DEAR
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE WILL BE
♪ JUST A HURRICANE
♪ FROM THE SEA
♪ WELL, THE WHIRLWIND CHANGED
♪ AND IT BROUGHT ME LOVE
♪ WHIRLWIND CAUGHT
♪ A TURTLE DOVE
♪ TOOK IT FROM
♪ ITS PLACE SO DEAR
♪ WHIRLWIND COME
♪ AND A-BRING ME CHEER
♪ WELL, WE HAD FUN
♪ LOTS OF FLINGS
♪ PARTIES, DANCES
♪ AND EVERYTHING
♪ THE WHIRLWIND CAME
♪ AND BLEW US APART
♪ THE WHIRLWIND MADE
♪ A LONELY HEART
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE
♪ MY DARLIN'
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE, MY DEAR
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE WILL BE
♪ JUST A HURRICANE
♪ FROM THE SEA
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE
♪ MY DARLIN'
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE, MY DEAR
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE WILL BE
♪ JUST A HURRICANE
♪ FROM THE SEA
♪ WELL, THE WHIRLWIND
♪ BROUGHT MY LOVE TO ME
♪ THEN IT BLEW IT BACK
♪ OUT TO SEA
♪ IT BROUGHT ME LOVE
♪ THAT WAS OH, SO SWEET
♪ AND THEN IT KNOCKED ME
♪ OFF OF MY FEET
♪ WELL, WHIRLWIND
♪ OF LOVE, MY DARLIN'
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE, MY DEAR
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE WILL BE
♪ JUST A HURRICANE
♪ FROM THE SEA
♪ WELL, RAGING STORM
♪ DON'T LET ME CRACK
♪ BLOW MY TROUBLES
♪ UP THE RISING SEA
♪ I HOPE IT'LL SWING
♪ AND SOON COME BACK
♪ AND BLOW MY BABY
♪ BACK TO ME
♪ WHIRLWIND
♪ OF LOVE, MY DARLIN'
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE, MY DEAR
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE WILL BE
♪ JUST A HURRICANE
♪ FROM THE SEA
♪ WHIRLWIND
♪ OF LOVE, MY DARLIN'
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE, MY DEAR
♪ WHIRLWIND OF LOVE WILL BE
♪ JUST A HURRICANE
♪ FROM THE SEA
Announcer:
HERE THEY COME
AROUND THE FAR CORNER.
IT'S CAR NUMBER EIGHT.
THAT'S MULDOON!
MULDOON'S GONNA DO IT AGAIN!
HE'S LOOKIN' A LITTLE
SIDEWAYS THERE.
THEY'RE BUMPER TO BUMPER.
HE'S ALL THE WAY DOWN
THE GRASS. THAT'S HIS STYLE.
HE'S GONNA NEED A BIG
DRIVE OFF TURN FOUR HERE.
HE'S DOIN' IT.
AND MULDOON'S GOT IT!
HE'S GOT IT!
HE DOES IT AGAIN!
( cars racing )
ANOTHER WIN BY JED MULDOON
IN A HOOCH WILSON-PREPARED
LINCOLN.
HOOCH HAS GOT THAT ENGINE
BUSINESS GOIN' PRETTY GOOD.
I THINK HE'S HAD CARS IN
THE TOP FIVE ALL SEASON.
HE'S SURE MAKIN' A BUCK.
YEAH, THEY SURE MAKE
SOME MONEY, THOSE RACERS.
( cars racing )