The following dramatization, although fictionalized,
was inspired by an actual event.
(lightly tense music)
(crowd chattering)
(guests chattering)
(light upbeat music)
It's very sexy, very sexy.
Waitress?
Excuse me!
Ah, waitress?
What's it like?
Beautiful, barren, dank.
I remember one time
I camped under the stars,
and I felt something crawl over my chest.
And I froze not breathing till it crawled away.
And I looked, it was a tiger snake,
one of the deadliest snakes in the world.
Oh god.
Yeah, I didn't know what to do.
Round for everybody.
What are you laughing for?
Well I tell you no.
No, it wasn't funny. (chuckling)
Stay right there.
Dangerous in here, like the Outback.
Oh, I got it.
Looks good.
Thanks, mate.
Don't mention it, cowboy.
Hey, hey, over here, over here.
Hey, hey, you're ignoring my friend right here.
Right here.
What can I get you?
I don't remember anymore.
I do.
Thanks, but I think you were flirting
with a punch in the nose there.
From him or your boyfriend?
Hey.
Seeya.
Have a nice time.
You know those clowns?
Nope.
Good.
And by the way, Tad isn't my boyfriend,
We just work together.
We drove in from Sacramento.
In fact, there's a group of us over there.
You're welcome to join us and tell us
all about life and death in the outback.
You already heard my best whopper.
You're not Australian.
The accent was the costume.
Oh, hmm.
So why are you giving it up now?
I don't know.
I just didn't feel like putting you on.
Well, I have a confession to make.
I'm not a real cowboy.
No kidding.
You can still join my friends and I if you want.
Does it have to be with your friends?
Tad, can you handle the drinks?
I think so.
It's a pretty neat, Alyson.
It's very lyrical, Alyson.
What's yours?
Dave.
It's not quite as lyrical.
Same with the last name, Bay.
Dave Bay.
I like that.
It's short, simple.
The name, not you.
You're tall and complicated.
What makes you say that?
Well you are tall.
I mean the complicated.
Because you had me buying the Australian thing
and then all of a sudden you just dropped it.
I didn't like the fact that you were buying it.
Although, actually I did live in Australia
for a while as a kid.
My dad was ambassador.
Oh, so you want me to buy this one?
He really was.
An ambassador.
Really?
So how long were you there for?
Not long.
My parents were killed, small plane.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was sent back to the States, the foster parents.
And how was that?
It was fine, they were great.
I took their name, Bay.
Oh, oh!
Hey.
You know what, are you hungry?
I'm always hungry.
Aha, there you are.
Come on, Alyson,
we're gonna head to some other spots.
Yeah, we should go to the-
Sure.
I think I'm gonna stay a while.
I got my car.
Okay, okay, seeya.
Yeah, all right.
Let me make a quick phone call.
Okay.
I got my hands on two F-14 Tomcats.
It's what they've been wanting.
No, don't say a thing, it'd be my little surprise.
Yeah, I'm at the base,
but I'll be unreachable the rest of the night.
We're in the middle of a training exercise.
Okay.
My parents are still married, 41 years.
Three brothers, three sisters,
all of us close enough to make Norman Rockwell gag.
Sounds nice, I miss that, having a family.
What about your foster family?
No, no, they're gone too, it's just me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Here I am going on about my wonderful family
and everything.
No, no.
I like hearing it.
There's a downside to all that family stuff too, you know.
Like fortuning Christmas presents.
And everyone asking, why aren't you married?
Why aren't you married?
I knew you were going to ask that.
I retract the question.
Why aren't you married?
Because of my work.
You're a priest.
I work for the government.
Part of the military.
What I do is,
it's dangerous and secret and to be good at it,
you have to be alone with no one to care about
and no one caring about you.
So I guess you can't tell me where you live either, huh?
I don't live any one place
and I'm going to be leaving here tomorrow.
And I can't tell you where I'm going.
(sultry jazz music)
I wish I could be completely open with you
because I think you're great
and tonight's one of the nicest nights I've had ever.
But as weird as this might sound
it's for your own good that you know as little
about my current circumstances as possible.
But we have the rest of the night.
Oh, Dave, tonight.
Tonight's been real nice for me too.
You're very attractive,
interesting guy, but I,
but I don't want a one night kind of thing.
You know what I mean?
I mean, I've done it.
I don't need to go there again.
I'm sorry.
I think you're hot, shoot me.
I just don't wanna leave yet.
Can we just hang on a while?
Sure.
(gentle music)
What happens if you fall into enemy hands?
After 48 hours,
any information you possess will become obsolete.
The enemy knows that!
They will do anything to break you in those first hours.
Your lungs will fill with water.
Your captors may not know the fine line
between life and death.
Maybe you'll drown!
(coughing) I'm drowning!
Dammit!
You broke!
You showed no control.
All you have is control, you read me?!
Do you read me?!
Yes, sir!
Get out!
Johnson!
Sir!
Bag me!
He hasn't moved.
Sir, you okay sir?
Sir, move if you're okay, sir!
I think he drowned.
Control.
So.
How'd it go with the crocodile dundee wannabe?
Fine.
Your sister Patty's on the phone, line one.
Hello?
Hi.
Have you gotten a present for Dad yet?
Oh, that's right, it's dad's birthday.
I knew you'd forget.
Wanna shop together?
Yeah, at the places you shop
I can't even afford to browse.
Oh, cut the self-sufficient crap.
I'll pay, okay?
I'll even buy lunch.
I could eat.
I have been thinking about him all weekend.
I can't get him out of my mind.
Why am I doing this to myself?
I don't know.
Kind of got me thinking about him
and I didn't even meet him.
It's like a schoolgirl crush.
I mean, I didn't even have crushes
when I was a school girl.
And over what?
Some guy who's probably just looking
for a little action on Halloween.
The way you describe him,
he sounds like James Bond played by Mel Gibson.
(laughing) He is definitely attractive.
But you know, I'll bet everything is a load of crap.
A pickup line.
Probably parks cars somewhere.
Well, whoever he is,
maybe he can't get you off his mind either.
Meaning what?
Meaning that you might hear from him again,
meaning that you better decide how you feel about him
before that happens.
Well, how can I do that
if I don't even know who he is?
There's a couple of references to his name.
You look in this volume,
I'll look in the other one.
Oh, hell.
What?
Rescued two English pilots.
Icelandic glacier, extensive bravery, blah, blah, blah,
decorated by the president
and the prime minister of England.
He's a real hero.
There's another reference in this one.
No, I don't want to know.
I don't want to know.
God, I feel like such an idiot. (sighing)
Yeah, right Patty,
he's off somewhere thinking about me
as he's having a wild affair with a beautiful girl
in some exotic place.
(birds chirping)
(kid whooshing)
Uh oh, look out!
Incoming!
All right, careful.
Careful with those, all right?
Come over here, come on!
They missed you.
I was gone a week.
I brought back the F-14s they wanted.
They'd rather have you here.
So would I.
(helicopter whirring)
You won the commandant's award and I get to read it
in the post notice.
Why didn't you tell me, you bum?
A training, it's an award for training.
I miss the action, Bill.
I feel like some old man
who's teaching something he's too dried up
to do himself.
Come on, Dave.
You're still part of the most elite unit in the Air Force.
I mean, Cindy figured that dead heroes
don't make very good dads.
Is that a hard one to understand?
I did everything she wanted me to do
and it's still not enough.
Now she doesn't even want me conducting training exercises
away from the base.
She wants me in a cage!
And that's where I am.
I swear, I feel like I got to bust out or die.
You got a life who lives for you, pal.
You got it great!
I mean, people never appreciate it when they got it great.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Hello, cowboy.
Dave?
I've been thinking about you.
Where are you?
Oh, I'm sorry, you probably can't tell me that.
Right, sorry.
Well, I didn't expect to hear from you.
I didn't expect it either to be honest with you, but
I can't stop thinking about you.
Well what are we going to do about that?
We're going to have me come there.
I just have to work it out.
But I will work it out.
It's a two week course underwater demolitions.
I think you'd be able to teach them a thing or two.
Well there'd be instructors there from Russia,
China for the first time.
Could be invaluable.
All right, well,
I've never had reason to question your judgment before.
If it's useful to you, make your arrangements and go.
(gentle music)
This feels right.
We've been together forever.
So you're here.
Yeah.
What does that mean?
I'm not sure.
It's something we're going to have to find out.
You know, this is my birthday.
Someone's supposed to be cooking for me.
Oh, don't let him kid you.
He'd stab anybody who touched his precious barbecue.
Dave, how do you like your steak?
I'm a vampire sir, I like mine pretty bloody.
A man after my own heart.
So Alyson tells us that you're into some
hush hush government villains.
Dad, grill the steak, not Dave.
Just making conversation, princess.
That's all right.
It's his job, he's a dad.
Yes, sir.
All I can tell you is
I'm proud of what I do.
And if you knew more,
you wouldn't think less of me.
Impressive answer.
Well-spoken.
(baby crying)
Okay honey, what's up with you?
What's up with my little nephew?
He lost his balloon in the tree.
Here you are, Grandma's got another balloon
here for you.
Oh look here!
Yeah,
I'm afraid he wants his balloon.
I'm afraid you're right.
Where you going?
(crowd clapping)
Well done!
Look at that.
He's a little bit crazy, but I like him.
He's not crazy, he's
kind of perfect.
(crowd cheering)
(speech drowned by clapping)
What are you thinking?
I was thinking how the past few days,
I've never been happier.
I'm happy, I want to stay happy.
Well, if there's anything I can do to help.
You could marry me.
(gentle music)
Marry me.
I love you.
I know it's not supposed to happen this fast.
But it did.
You too, huh?
Mhmm.
Okay, so let's do it.
Let's get married.
I don't know.
I don't know who I would be marrying.
A man who vanishes and then reappears,
no questions allowed.
I don't think I can handle that.
You won't have to.
My stint is almost over.
I'm going to be a full fledged four-star civilian.
When?
Soon, soon.
And then what will you do?
Come back here, sit on the porch,
get old with you.
Our parajumper training these major's shaping up.
I'm putting you in full charge.
I want you to analyze the weaknesses
and implement any necessary changes.
As always, I trust your judgment.
I've been doing a lot of thinking.
My life, my career.
I'm not sure this is what I'm meant to be doing.
For god's sake, Dave, you're the best there is!
That's reason enough to keep doing it.
I don't want to hear this kind of crap from you again.
No, sir.
(cartoon booming and clapping)
Oh Popeye, I'm scared.
Ain't nothing to be scared about.
(gentle music)
Olive, get back from under the table!
I'm still scared!
Attention, attention everybody,
the virus strikes again!
You need something from the fridge?
Nah.
The boys are wanting a dog.
I said I'd ask you.
Okay, sure.
Good.
Go, tell 'em.
They'll love hearing it from you.
(gentle music)
Going for my ride.
Turn on the sprinklers.
Sure.
(crickets chirping)
(suspenseful music)
(bike clanging)
(tense music)
(water splashing)
(suspenseful music)
(phone ringing)
Yes?
We're going to go over here.
Current's moving pretty swift.
Let's get some boats in now.
Dispatch to unit three,
dispatch to unit three, what's your 20?
This is three,
we're just pulling up on the scene now.
Dispatch due to fire rescue,
we're gonna need some more units out here.
Okay Paul, let's dig in.
Rescue One, this is ground.
Have you got any vision at all up there?
Got nothing at all, Sarge.
I'll hover down to 300 feet,
gonna slide on downstream,
see if I can get any more visual.
It's pretty murky.
Okay if you brake down a little bit lower
and just take a little slower.
Look, we got to find this guy.
10-4.
Yeah, we're sure it's nothing else.
Let's just wait till we hear something.
Okay, okay, okay.
Come on, come on, dig in, boys, let's go.
(Cindy sobbing)
Okay, okay.
Okay.
(thunder rumbling)
(pebbles clanking)
(gentle music)
Mission complete.
Where's your stuff?
I just showed you my stuff.
Stop it, you know what I mean.
Well, I can't get my gear or my pay till I'm debriefed.
They owe me a huge chunk of back pay
and all my severance, but
I want to see you, so I came here first.
So you're going away again?
No, not till I feel like it.
I told you my stint is over, I can do what I want.
They'll debrief me at my convenience.
So you've got no job,
no money, no home,
and no clothes?
Yeah, yeah, that's about the size of it.
And you did this for me?
I did it for us.
Well, that's what I meant.
Oh boy.
I thought you wanted me if I didn't have to disappear,
if you could know where I am.
I did, I do.
I do.
Okay then.
No regrets?
No regrets.
Alyson, you have got a slew of phone calls to return
and there are clients coming in.
Listen, Tad, anything you can handle,
just handle without me and reschedule everything else.
For this afternoon?
No, I'm not going to come in today.
It's pretty crazy in here, Alyson.
Can't you at least come in?
No, I can't, got it?
Got it.
Okay.
I like that.
That's nice, you'll finally be able
to settle down in one place.
So what are your plans now that you're out of the service?
I don't know.
It's been a while since I've been out there
in the real world.
Well, as I see it,
real estate's on the upswing.
There's good money to be made, buying old houses,
fixing them up and reselling them.
Mama and I renovated a couple of fixer uppers
during the last boom.
We started out just for fun, but
ended up with a tidy profit.
If the idea appeals to you,
you might be able to ride this market while it's strong.
A thing like that, you need to spend money to make money.
I gotta wait for my funds to come in.
Look, Dave.
I got a pretty strong line of credit at the bank.
I could loan you enough to make a real start.
A hundred thousand, say?
You can repay me with your profits or your back pay,
whichever comes in first.
That's incredibly generous, sir.
I love my daughter.
My daughter loves you.
As long as that remains the case,
I want to do right by both of you.
Looks like he went along with daddy's proposal.
He's given up everything for me.
I don't know,
I feel really weird about this.
Honey.
That's a kind of romance most girls dream about.
Mom, I'm not most girls.
Alyson, are you marrying Dave
because you think you got yourself into something
you can't get out of?
No.
I love Dave.
I love what I know about him.
I mean, it's not like I know that much about him.
Daddy and I have been married for 41 years.
We're still learning about each other.
Imagine how dull it would be
if you knew everything there was to know.
When I become a mother, am I going to say stuff like that?
Yes.
(both chuckling)
I've been thinking about something.
It occurred to me that the unit that I was in,
I mean, you know,
we were involved with some
anti-terrorist operations.
We had dealings with drug lords,
people who tend to hold a grudge.
Meaning what?
That our lives are in danger?
No, no.
What?
It's not going to be any ninjas
busting in here in the next five minutes
but I do think that
obscurity is not a bad idea right now.
That's why I want to start using my real last name.
My parents' name, Haywood.
Haywood?
Yeah.
Dave Haywood.
Dave and Alyson Haywood.
Can you explain that to your family?
So, you know, we're all on the same page.
Oh, yeah.
We're good at keeping secrets.
My father had the whole family swear
never to reveal I campaigned for Dukakis.
(somber music)
The union of man and woman and heart, body and mind
is intended for their mutual comfort and help,
that they may know each other with delight
and tenderness in acts of love.
In marriage, husband and wife give themselves to each other
to care for each other in good times and in bad.
They're linked to each other's families
and they begin to do life together in the community.
I David take you Alison to be my wife
to have and to hold from this day forward,
for better, for worse.
I David, take you Alyson to be my wife,
to have and to hold from this day forward
for better or worse.
For richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health.
For richer, for poorer, in sickness and in health.
This flag is presented on behalf of a grateful nation.
I Alyson take you David to be my husband,
to have and to hold from this day forward.
And as a token of our appreciation for the honorable
and faithful services rendered by your loved one.
Alyson, I give you this ring as a symbol of my vow
with all that I am and all that I have.
I honor you in the name of God.
Honor guard, atten-hut!
Park arms!
Ready!
Aim!
Fire!
(guns firing)
Ready!
Fire!
(guns firing)
Ready!
Fire!
(guns firing)
You may kiss your bride.
Dave?
I've got some stuff to photocopy
and then you can show me that house, okay?
Okay.
What do you think?
As long as nobody huffs and puffs.
We could rip these up, just put a new floor.
And we're gonna need some new cupboards in here.
Needs a new kitchen.
The price is right.
I mean, at least it sounds right,
but this is all new to me.
You're awfully anxious to get cracking
on this renovation thing,
aren't you?
Yeah, yeah.
For you, for us, for your dad.
But you know more about this than I do, so,
I'm going to need your help.
That's for sure. (laughing)
Well, you're right, it is well-priced.
All right!
Yo, Al, if you could take one more week off,
we'll be done here.
I can't, Dave.
I feel guilty enough already.
Hi.
Yeah?
Is this house on the market?
Well, eventually.
You want to take a look?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Honey, what do you think?
Well, it's not finished yet.
Yeah it's not, it's not finished.
Well we're just looking for a starter.
I mean we've really had our heart set on this neighborhood,
but looking around and...
Can we make an offer?
You know, we've gotten a lot of offers lately
and we decided that we wanted to finish and get top dollar.
If you call us tonight,
maybe we could make a deal.
Yeah.
Yeah, we'll give you a call.
Great.
Yeah.
We'll talk.
Good.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
That was easy.
Very, very slick.
You're good.
No, no, no, no, we're good.
Heads up.
You realize what we could do if we did this right?
I mean really did it all the way, we can make a killing.
You pay your dad back tenfold,
we could have it all, cowboy, everything you ever want.
(bottles clinking)
Guys, you'll be fine.
You're making a big mistake, Alyson.
She'll really be missed.
Good luck, Alyson.
Bye bye.
Alyson, you put five years in this place.
This place is you.
I'm going to miss you.
Bye, guys.
Bye.
Good luck.
We'll miss you.
Bye.
You look like you know what you're doing.
I've done it before.
Oh yeah, where?
Some covert military lawn care system?
Yeah.
Traded sprinklers for hostages.
So whose car is that?
Ours.
We made a nice chunk of change on that house.
Dave, we're supposed to be paying dad back.
I've been paying him.
He's not expecting the whole thing back overnight.
I know, but we should be saving.
That's one thing.
Al, Al,
we're not retired.
We're just starting, okay?
Let's enjoy ourselves along the way.
We should be saving for our kid.
What?
I'm pregnant.
(both laughing)
(light music)
I love this house, Travis
Yeah.
Too bad we're selling instead of buying.
I don't get it.
We're doing beautiful work, busting our butts.
We're listing at a loss, practically.
David, the market is down.
When you spend so much on renovation,
you face the law of diminishing returns.
Yeah, yeah.
I've been hearing about that.
Well, the bank's gonna own this in a few days,
I just hope they appreciate good craftsmanship.
Well, open house is over.
I gotta get going.
Okay, all right.
See you.
Bye.
See you, Alyson.
Bye, Travis.
Bye, Christopher.
We sold five houses in nine months.
It's not like
we tanked here, okay?
I know, I know.
What is it?
Open it.
Open it and see.
I'll trade you.
Come here.
Dave.
Come here, come here big boy, come on.
You like it?
It's beautiful, but why?
It's a Millard Fillmore's birthday today.
We just celebrated Grover Cleveland's birthday.
So what?
You got to stop buying me stuff.
I can't help it!
We are juggling three mortgages.
We have to be careful with our money.
Relax, okay?
I mean once you resolve whatever you have to
with the government, you get your back pay,
then we can relax.
You're gonna put that on?
Huh?
Go ahead.
Okay.
See?
It looks great.
It's beautiful.
Don't sweat the small stuff.
He's not worried.
He's so quiet.
Marcus was really cranky at this age.
Oh, he's plenty cranky.
He just has good party manners like his dad.
What does that mean?
It means what it means.
All right, Alison, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Something's wrong.
Come on.
Nothing is wrong.
What is it, Alyson?
It's not a big deal, it's just, I...
I think we're a little in over our heads financially and
with the baby and all I let Dave take over the books.
You know I don't like doing that kind of stuff anyway.
Look, this is not exactly new, sweetie.
Look, I know you've barely been scraping by.
Dave explained it to Dad.
Dad's been very good about it,
hasn't pressured him about the loan.
The loan?
Look, we know he'll pay it back when he can.
We're just happy that he's so good to you,
and we all like him so much.
Dave shoots a 71.
Dirty bum, we're playing five bucks a hole.
Patty, give me a couple, please.
Mom, do you mind taking care of Christopher tonight?
Jerry.
I didn't tell you because
I didn't want you to know how badly
I messed up our finances.
You didn't not tell me, you lied.
You said you'd been paying dad back
and you lied to me.
I was afraid
that you would lose respect for me.
Oh, well you were right about that.
Knock it off!
Stop it!
(tires screeching)
I'm trying to make you happy.
What more do you want?
I gave up everything for you!
I didn't ask you to give up anything for me!
You know, if you're having regrets...
I don't know what to do.
No regrets.
Remember.
I'm not sure how you're going to take this, but
I got word I can collect my back pay and severance.
Well, why would I have a problem with that?
Because it means going for that debriefing
I never went for.
Where would you go?
I can't tell you that.
The good news is it'll get us out of this bind.
You're not volunteering for something,
something dangerous.
No.
No, that's the old days.
But I would do anything for you, you know that?
Anything to make you happy.
(lightly suspenseful music)
(leaves rustling)
(water splashing)
Oh, Dave.
(woman gasping)
Listen up!
Everybody down and stay calm!
Down, on the ground!
Oh, oh my god, okay.
Go!
(dogs whimpering)
(dogs barking in distance)
Yeah, yeah!
Good girl!
(suspenseful music)
Oh.
We lost him.
(guns firing on TV)
What are you doing here?
You call the machine?
No.
You stop by the apartment?
Uh-uh.
Well, if you did, you'd know what I'm doing here.
What are you doing here?
I just kind of blew it in.
Wanted to take a shower, change,
look nice for you.
Kind of stinky.
Hmm, can't argue with that one.
What?
Well, I decided,
well, I thought that we'd move in here,
save on rent while we're renovating.
Just brought the essentials.
Everything else is divided
between Mom and Dad's and Patty's.
So you've been busy.
Mhmm.
So have I.
Oh my!
That's only part of it.
The bastards only gave me a fraction.
Dave!
Come on, give me a hand.
It's wet.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Not only do they short me on the amount,
but when they give me directions where to find it,
I had to take a little swim.
What do you mean find it?
How come they didn't give you a check?
A check?
Yeah.
Checks can be traced,
bank accounts scrutinized.
This is part of a government that doesn't officially exist.
They give me directions and I follow coordinates.
And what do you know?
It's at the middle of a lake, 20 feet deep.
They send me a little message.
You know, you want to get out the outfit, Dave,
you want to get paid?
Well dive for it, screw ball.
Let's see how good you are, you know?
I'm good enough.
These are the guys that work for our government?
I'm not going to miss them.
At all?
Not a bit.
It feels so unreal.
There's over $40,000 here.
Is that real enough for you?
We're going to pay back dad first, right?
Wait, wait.
Who are you calling?
What are you doing?
You look good in green. (laughing)
Okay folks, straight down there,
walk down left.
I should never have agreed to come here.
I was figuring, you know,
some fast food and a few bucks down a slot machine.
Why bother coming?
Look, most of it went towards paying off your dad
and our creditors.
We got a right to splurge
with the little we got left.
I risked my neck for every dollar of this money.
I'm sorry, you're right.
You're right.
Nice, huh?
I'll tell you what, why don't you sit back,
relax and enjoy this
while I'm going to hit up to the room,
make a couple of business calls.
I got a couple of leads,
but I don't want to lose them
just cause we're on vacation.
Okay, don't be too long now though.
I might get really drunk
and start taking off all my clothes.
Oh, I'll be back in time for that.
(Alyson chuckling)
(crowd chattering)
(lightly tense music)
(dice clattering)
Red, 14 red 14.
Place your bets.
(wheel clicking)
Cash it in.
(glass shattering)
Ah.
It's okay, I'm going to my room anyway.
(dealers chattering)
A secret gambling habit, huh?
What next?
That money was supposed to go towards
paying back dad.
It will.
I couldn't do it then, I couldn't tell you.
What couldn't you tell me?
What lie could-
Listen to me!
You know the world I came from, it's not a game.
What I don't tell you,
I don't tell you because it's dangerous.
They paid me with dirty money, okay?
That's how covert operations are financed.
Confiscated drug money pays for a lot of things
our government has to do.
I'm turning around this money
so there is no risk of your father being tainted in any way.
Now we can stand here and argue about it,
or you can help me.
It really doesn't matter.
But I gotta keep doing this until I'm done.
(trunk slamming)
Let's get a drink first.
I don't want a drink.
Come on.
Ah, thank you.
I think you'd want to keep a clear head
for what you're doing.
You know what, you're right.
Soon as I'm done here we're going home.
Come on.
Damn.
(tense music)
Al?
I'm back, I got the face plates.
Great.
What do you think, you'd buy that?
Nice.
Yeah, it'll work.
You know what?
These are too white.
Should have got off white.
Got to go back to the store.
Do you want me to come along?
No, no, I won't screw it up twice.
(suspenseful music)
That's my boy.
Such a good boy.
Yeah, I got word today.
I can get another chunk of my back pay,
maybe all of it, but
it means taking part in a mission.
What kind of mission?
Well, it's not exactly what I call dangerous,
but it just, it might take a while, that's all.
How long?
Two weeks.
Maybe three.
Do you want your dad paid back in full,
us out of debt, free and clear,
our lives back together?
Yes.
Okay then.
Dave, look.
Whatever it is you're doing,
I know you're doing for me, but...
What?
Well, you got to know that you're what matters to me, you.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
What I'm doing, I'm doing for us.
Remember that.
Trust it.
(door knocking)
Hello.
Patty.
I was shopping for myself.
What's one extra bag?
It's not like I'm homeless or anything.
Yeah, but I bet you don't have anything
worth eating around here.
so I got you that lemon chicken
that you liked so much that time you were over.
Well, gee, the place is looking real good.
Real good.
All right, Patty, I know you're dying to ask.
No, I haven't heard from Dave yet.
And I'm, oh,
I'm really beginning to freak out about this.
Why?
Well, I do.
I think he might be involved in something
really bad.
Really what?
Rogue CIA, Oliver North kind of thing.
Well, he might be.
He might be just more than you think.
What are you saying?
Nothing, nothing.
Patty.
Jerry made me promise not to tell you.
So don't tell him I told you.
Tell me.
Dave borrowed $20,000 from Jerry
several months ago
and he hasn't paid back at dime.
Why didn't you tell me this?
Anyway, you know,
Jerry's sorta considered it a write off at this point.
Oh, no.
Take it.
Go in the back, in the back!
Clear out, let's go, hurry up.
Move it!
I said head down!
Let's go.
It's all in there.
Come on.
Big bills, nothing under 20.
Hurry up.
Hurry up!
Move it, let's go!
I said heads down!
Okay, that's it.
That's it, all right, bring it to me, come on.
Right here.
No please.
Please, no, no!
On the ground.
Shut up, don't talk!
You, you, let's go, come on.
Get up, follow me in the back.
You see her?
Open it up.
Come on!
I'd like to get a safety deposit box.
Are you a customer?
No, do I have to be?
No, just fill out this form.
Thank you.
Taxi over here.
(phone beeping)
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
I need your help with something.
(chill lounge music)
Would it bother you if I smoke?
Well if it did, I shouldn't be in a bar.
Here, I got it.
Thanks.
They booked me into a non smoking room
then told me I couldn't smoke in the lobby
and so here I am.
What about you?
What about me what?
Alone in a hotel bar.
They booked me into a non drinking room?
I don't know.
Well, are you here on business?
No, I'm just passing through.
What about you?
I'm a sales rep for clothing line.
It involves a lot of travel.
Yeah, you like it?
Yeah, it's an adventure.
When you're divorced with no kids,
adventure's a pretty good trade off.
Yeah.
Yeah, I feel that way.
I have to feel that way for what I do.
Which is?
I work for the government.
What I do is
secret and dangerous, but I love it.
I love the action, love the pay.
Sometimes it's lonely, but like you said,
it's a tradeoff.
I have a fully stocked minibar in my room.
I could give up smoking for the rest of the night.
I was feeding you a line.
I'm a jerk.
A married jerk who fixes old houses
and loses money doing it.
Somehow I have a hard time believing that.
Me too.
Good night.
Night.
I've got to get into my safety deposit box.
Okay, I'll just need your name and your number.
Haywood, 3334.
And just sign right there.
Thank you.
You can look at this in the cubicle out there.
Oh.
Hi.
Hello.
I'd like to rent a box,
but I'm not sure what size.
All right, well, these are the different sizes
of boxes that we have.
So what's the difference in price there?
Oh, thanks.
Excuse me.
I seem to have cut my finger
on the stupid box.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah.
We should figure something out there.
We should wash that.
It's very sharp.
But you know, let's put your box back first.
That's a good idea.
Thanks.
What is your purpose for entering Mexico?
Tourist.
And for how long?
Till you run out of tequila.
Vamos.
(door knocking)
Okay.
I went to that old locksmith
that mom and dad used to go to
because I figured that he wouldn't be suspicious.
Well he was, a little, I think.
Hi.
But...
I got it.
Now be careful this time.
I know the routine.
I'll just be a few minutes.
(lightly tense music)
Patty, I don't know what's true, what's not true.
Dave Bay is a name he was born with
in Illinois to parents that,
well, he always told me were foster parents,
which means he made up half the stuff about his childhood.
So what?
People do that all the time.
There's more, there's more.
The woman in the photograph,
the foster mother turned mother,
she was supposed to have died when Dave was in high school.
But in the photograph, he's already in an Air Force uniform,
which means that she didn't die when he said.
Meaning she still might be alive.
You're getting ahead
of me here.
No, god,
you're taking too long.
Cut to the chase!
I'm trying, okay.
According to his birth certificate,
he was born in Rockford, Illinois,
and the picture was taken
in front of Rockford Public Library.
Now, I had remembered that the mother was a librarian
or something, so I gave it a shot and I called the library.
You didn't.
Mhmm.
Carolyn Bay, beloved librarian for 25 years
is now retired, not deceased and living in Portland.
Portland?
So do you think Dave knows?
Stupid question, of course Dave knows.
The question is, now that I know,
what am I going to do about it?
All right, all right, come on, let's go sit down.
All right. (clears throat)
How does Dave's childhood,
his relationship with his parents, all that stuff,
how does that affect you?
Well it doesn't directly, but-
Then it's none of your business.
Patty, how can you say that?
I have accepted Dave
as a man of mystery who can only tell me certain things.
But I didn't know he was lying about the things
he was telling me.
I mean, what else is a lie?
I can't trust him.
He lied about his childhood, that's it.
So what?
It's who he grew up to be that matters.
And he grew up to be
honored by the President of the United States
and the prime minister of England.
Come on, sweetie, you saw the pictures.
(light somber music)
Oh my god, the key.
Hey.
Uh-oh, you look happy.
I would have called if I could,
but where I was is...
It's over, I'm finished with those guys for good.
You get your money?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, some.
Enough.
Come on, I'll show you.
At least it's not wet.
I didn't want to go back to Vegas
so I made other arrangements.
Come here, I wanna show you.
What?
Close your eyes and hold out your hands.
What now?
(bag zipping)
Okay.
Mexican gold pesos for $150 each.
Where did you get this?
From the unit.
They insisted they pay me in gold and they did.
And where did they get it?
They're very enterprising.
Now we can pay your dad back in full, get out of debt,
maybe take a nice little trip somewhere.
What's your dream vacation?
I don't believe in dreaming.
What aren't you saying?
What are the things you haven't told me, Dave?
I want to know.
I'll tell you.
I will, when it's safer.
And when will that be?
And say from what Dave?
If you're in some kind of trouble, let me help you.
You can trust me, you know that, you can.
I've been trained not to trust.
Trust equals death.
It's not easy battling that kind of conditioning,
but I'll try.
I want you to trust me so I can trust you.
Look.
I'm tired.
I want to take a shower,
maybe a nap.
Why don't you think about dinner?
(tense music)
Oh, Alyson.
It's all right, I'll grab something on the road.
Where you going?
I gotta deal with this.
It might take awhile.
How long a while?
A day or two.
I'll keep you posted.
I love you, cowboy.
Dave, what's happening?
Tell me what's happening.
I told you.
You told me nothing, always nothing.
I want to know what you're doing, Dave.
Tell me what you're doing.
I'm going to do what I have to do.
(car starting)
(lightly tense music)
(phone beeping)
What city please?
Portland?
The number for Carolyn Bay, B-A-Y.
Hold for a moment, please.
(phone beeping)
Hello?
Is this Mrs. Carolyn Bay?
(gentle music)
(door knocking)
Mrs. Bay?
Yes.
Hi, my name is Alison Haywood.
I'm a friend of your son, Dave.
He's told me so much about you.
And he's always said when I'm in Portland,
that I should look you up, so...
I'm sorry.
You are Dave's mom, aren't you?
My dear, why do you keep talking about Dave
as if he's alive?
Excuse me?
Maybe you better come inside.
As a friend of Dave's, how is it you didn't know?
Oh.
Well, I...
We've been a little out of touch.
Oh, you poor thing,
this must be a terrible shock.
Shock, yes.
That's when Dave and Cindy met the prime minister.
You know Cindy, she's doing better now.
They've been through so much, Cindy and the boys.
A wife and children.
You didn't know?
You can't have known Dave very well.
Dave was married before I moved to Portland.
How could you know where I am,
but not know about his family?
I'm sorry.
I'm having a hard time with this.
I know your voice.
You called yesterday for my address.
Who are you, what do you want?
I'm sorry.
It's a mistake.
Just go!
I'm going!
Sometimes when I'm having a bad dream,
I can wake myself up.
I'll be there in the dream and I'll tell myself
I don't want to be here anymore.
And then I wake up.
(sighing) I can't seem to wake myself up from this one.
Alyson, I think we all have to face the fact
that this nightmare is not over.
The question now is what are we going to do about it?
Well, that's easy, we nail the bastard.
I said he was crazy that very first day, remember that?
I said he was crazy.
Mom, you liked him.
We all liked him.
The whole world likes Dave.
That's how he can take you and Jerry.
And me.
So what are you going to do?
Alyson, the guy could be nuts!
Or dangerous.
Oh, that's great, coming from you,
the one who told me that it was none of my business,
that I should just leave
it all alone, right?
I was wrong,
okay?
Call the cops, call the military,
call the other wife.
This creep's got a lot to answer for.
I think we may see the return of public executions.
Patty, we're talking about that baby's father.
Dad.
We have to think very carefully before we act.
Because once this genie's let out of the bottle,
there'll be no putting it back.
(lightly tense music)
(boys giggling)
Hey!
Okay, boys, it's lunch time, come on!
Come on, come on, come on.
I got you, come here.
I don't wanna go in!
Dry yourself up, okay?
Now you too, come here.
You know what, get in there.
Wipe your feet up before you go in the door.
Go on.
(car starting)
Get this thing, yes!
Left, left, left right left.
(helicopter whirring)
I should've known.
He was trying to tell me
a few days before his accident.
He was feeling trapped,
he wanted to get out.
I didn't take him seriously.
Maybe I could have helped him.
Dave's a quitter who destroyed lives in the process.
Let me tell you about this unit.
We take the finest.
We put them through the hardest training in the military
and we produced 200 of the world's best.
They can go anywhere, do anything for one purpose,
to save lives.
All I know is he told me he resigned
and that he was being debriefed and
that he was getting his back pay you owed him.
Owed him?
We don't owe our men money.
I was grooming him to take over.
He had everything going for him.
I guess he didn't see it that way.
I can't believe what he put them through.
His mother, Cindy, the kids.
I'm on that list somewhere.
Yeah, sorry, of course.
So.
He's run away again.
Is that it, he's just disappeared?
Before today, I could have told you
with absolute certainty how any one of my men
would have behaved in a given situation,
but that's all gone to hell now.
But you were right to come to us with this
because we're the ones who can deal with it.
We don't leave our men out there.
And we always clean up our own garbage.
Wait a minute, what?
Wait a minute.
What are you...
Are you...
are you talking about taking him out?
You've been watching too many movies.
No, I want Dave to face charges in front of a court martial.
That's what he would want.
I'd like to be put in charge of this operation, sir.
Done.
I want you to go back to California with Miss...
Haywood.
We go by the name of Haywood.
Mrs. Haywood, yes.
If Dave does return to California,
you'd better be ready for him.
Remember, he taught evading capture.
So you're going to have to rely on sheer force of numbers.
(lightly suspenseful music)
Hello, cowboy.
Didn't mean to wake you.
What are you doing here?
I live here.
Hey, Christopher.
How you doing, buddy?
(baby babbling)
You miss me?
Sure.
You looking for this?
They must be close by,
the signal has a short reach.
Who did they send?
My old friend, Bill?
Bill prefers this model.
You think I'm going to hurt you?
Oh, you've hurt me already, Dave.
I loved you, Alyson, still do.
Always will.
Why?
Why did you betray me?
Betray you?
You have betrayed everyone who has ever loved you.
What are you talking about?
Not you.
I've never betrayed you.
Oh I can't believe that you actually believe that.
I do.
Well then you're crazier than I thought.
You could've had it all.
I just wanted us to be happy.
Let go of me.
Just let go!
No, not till you say
you believe me, please.
Believe?
What am I supposed to believe, Dave?!
I love you.
All of this was because I loved you.
Loved me? (laughing)
You loved me?
What were you thinking?
What was I thinking?
Yeah.
What were you thinking?
I had to be with you.
You know, someday you can understand that.
Oh no, I don't think so, Dave.
No.
It is Bill, isn't it?
Good.
(helicopter whirring)
Capture One Leader to Capture Ground,
we are airborne, over.
Capture One Leader,
this is Capture Ground,
could you give me an ETA, sir, over?
Roger, Capture Ground, ETA is six minutes.
(speech drowned by helicopter whirring)
Capture One Leader, this is Capture Three,
you have a flight of three on the go, sir.
Tell me one thing.
The money, the wet cash, the pesos.
Where'd you get it?
I robbed banks.
Do me a favor.
Tell Chris his dad was a hero once, okay?
He really was a hero, you know?
(somber music)
Master Sergeant David James Bay,
this is the United States Air Force Military Police.
You are ordered to surrender
according to the articles of the uniform code
of military justice.
Failure to comply will initiate hostile force
on your person.
(somber music)
(light music)