[bright music]
[ominous music]
[car engine idles]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
[gloves rustle]
[phone rings]
[Ashley speaks foreign language]
[Ashley] Extract and
clean up. Nothing more.
[suspenseful music]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[thud]
[muffled gun fires]
[body clunks]
[man grunts]
[muffled gun fires]
[Man 2] Who's there?
[grunting]
[muffled gun fires rapidly]
[man groans]
[muffled gun fires]
[body clunks]
[muffled gasp]
[muffled sobs]
[ominous tones swell]
[brooding acoustic guitar music]
[Ellis] I keep asking myself,
how did I get here?
Started out as an opportunity
to make things right.
A chance to be one of the good guys.
[chuckles] "Good guys."
There are no good guys.
Good guys don't exist.
It's just you and the
bullshit you tell yourself
so you can move on to the next moment.
I sacrificed everything,
as I believed the lies I was told.
That ends now.
You have to be willing to
die for what you believe in.
Or believe me,
you're already dead.
[breathes heavily]
[somber piano music]
[phone rings]
Ellis.
Ellis, I know you're there.
Listen.
There's no way out, other
than death, and you knew this.
I'm done, man.
- You're done?
- I said I'm fuckin' done.
I wish it were that easy.
There's no way, with all that you know,
that we're just gonna let you be done.
Look, you're done when we say you're done!
I'm done, man!
I fuckin' said I'm done!
- I'm not askin'.
- And neither are we.
You're one of our best agents.
There's no denying that.
But if you try to leave, I assure you,
we will hunt you down and we
will use all of our resources
to find you, and we will, and when we do,
we will kill you.
Is that all you called me for, man?
[Associate] Finish this
last situation for us,
and maybe I can convince
them to hear you out.
Is that it?
Well when you complete this
job, it'll work in your favor.
Fuck you.
[associate laughs]
I knew you were gonna say that.
Consider it, Ellis!
Needless to say, this is a
very dangerous situation.
High-risk.
If these files end up in the
wrong hands and this job go bad
it could be catastrophic.
Look, you wanna leave? Fine.
Give us our file back and
then we can talk about it.
Fuck, fuck you!
- Fuck me?
- Fuck you!
You're the one who's fucked!
You have family, no friends, no nothin'!
Just your little legacy here with us!
You've done some great work
for us, so I won't mix words.
Bring us our file back or we'll
send Kristof to retrieve it.
I don't give a fuck
who comes looking for me.
Bring 'em.
Neither you or me will want that.
Just bring us our file back.
[phone chirps]
That sound you just heard?
That's our next mission.
Let us know when it's done.
Oh!
And Ellis...
Take the girl back. She's
not worth the trouble.
I don't, I, I don't-
- Before you say you don't
know what I'm talkin' about,
we both know you do.
You got 24 hours.
Fuck you.
[phone bleeps]
[somber piano music]
Alexander.
Get a hold of Sparkle.
Yeah.
I've got a problem.
[phone bleeps]
[sighs]
[wind blows]
Fuck.
[grunts]
[brooding acoustic guitar music]
Fuck.
So...
I keep asking myself,
how did I get here?
When all I wanted to be
was one of the good guys.
♪ Where do I go from here ♪
♪ Because I don't know myself anymore ♪
♪ I say I don't know myself anymore ♪
♪ Where do I go from here ♪
[car starts]
♪ Because I don't know myself anymore ♪
[engine roars]
♪ I say I don't know myself anymore ♪
♪ Where do I go ♪
[crickets chirp]
[phone rings]
[Ellis] Esteban, I fucked up.
I've lost the file and
I need you to find it.
And to make matters worse, there's a girl.
[Esteban] What do you
mean there is a girl?
[Ellis] She was standing there
and I just fuckin' took her.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
[Esteban] Ellis, you know the rules.
I know.
[Esteban] Get rid of
the girl immediately.
I will find the files. I will be in touch.
Hey.
[phone bleeps]
You sleep well? You sleep okay?
You hungry?
I asked you in the car and
you didn't say anything.
Look, I know life is crazy right now.
But they got some people
that are trying to hurt me.
That means this place isn't really safe.
Do you have anybody you can
call? Is there anybody...
I can't...
Don't, don't do that.
Don't do that. Don't.
[Julia sobs]
Don't cry. Don't.
[sighs]
Damn.
[brooding acoustic guitar music]
This might be my best one yet.
I'm gonna just go set it down.
Sorry I'm late. I was at the
other house when you texted.
We good?
Never better.
Look, I need you to go back to the house.
Scan the perimeter, make
sure everything's everything.
Can you do that for me?
Anything I need to be worried about?
You heard from Sparkle, man?
Keep looking.
We good?
Never better.
But you want me to go and sweep the house?
You got a problem with that?
And if I find anything?
Do what you do.
[phone rings]
Ellis! Ellis!
Look, we need our file, Ellis!
No, I'm too fuckin'
tired of waitin', Ellis!
Didn't I tell you? I warned
you, Kristof is off the leash!
[Ellis] I can't, 'cause
I lost the fuckin' files!
So now what?
Didn't I ask you to bring the girl back?
Well, fuck Kristof. I'm comin'.
Listen to me.
[ominous tones]
[somber music]
[wind blows]
[birds squawk]
- You okay?
- What do you want, Kristof?
Hey.
Don't get mad at me.
This is not my fault.
I'm just doing my job.
And what exactly is that?
Your job.
Takin' care of loose ends.
Is that what you are, Ellis? A loose end?
[Ellis] You tell me.
You gotta admit, you
botched your last job.
Got your ass whipped
and lost the prospect,
who then handed the files that she stole
over to the Russians.
In our business, that's not good.
It was only a matter of time before you
and those misfits screwed up.
I told you before and I'm telling
you now for the last time.
The agency doesn't like
when you're careless.
Sooner or later, they're gonna
get tired of you, and then...
Well...
You know.
What do I know?
Huh, Kristof?
You've been warned, Ellis.
[phone vibrates]
Hi.
[Sparkle] Alex said
you were looking for me.
What do you want?
So it's like that?
Yeah, that's how it is.
[Ellis sighs]
I quit.
You can quit?
I didn't think they just let people quit.
[Ellis] They don't.
Well, what do you want from me?
A going-away party?
I just wanted you to know, okay?
I just wanted you to know.
Where you at these days? Where you livin'?
I'm with friends.
You need anything?
I'm good!
I'm good.
You are the one calling me, right?
So...
I just need you to look into
something for me, that's it.
I'll let you know, if
you let me know what's up.
All right.
All right, so, there's this
guy lookin' for me, right?
They sent him to kill me.
So the thing is, I gotta
find him before he finds me.
So this is what I need you to do.
I'm sending you a picture now.
[Associate] Didn't I
tell you? I warned you!
Kristof is off the leash!
There's no way out, other
than death, and you knew this.
Bring us our file back.
Consider it, Ellis!
You're the one who's fucked!
You have no family, no nothin'!
[dark music]
Take the girl back. She's
not worth the trouble.
[Ellis] Excuse me.
[Blonde Woman] May I help you?
Yeah, I'm just looking
for Maria. Is she...
[Blonde Woman] She's gone for the night.
Maybe I can help you.
You and me are a lot alike.
I can tell.
You see the opportunity,
you take advantage of it.
[crickets chirp]
[Ellis] It's crazy
when you think about it.
You rack your brain, trying
to come up with answers.
All along, it was sittin'
right there in front of you.
I'll be damned.
Hi.
I have to run an errand real fast.
Please, do not answer the door.
Stay away from the windows
and don't use your phone.
Can you remember that?
Good.
[gentle music]
What size are you?
It's just, you're the
same size as my ex-wife.
She has a closet full of some
really nice stuff in there
that I think will fit you and...
If you wanna get outta that,
you just take a shower and, um,
get changed up, if you feel like it, okay?
If you want.
Okay?
But I really gotta go.
Um...
Really need you to not
answer the door, right?
And stay away from the windows.
Don't answer the phone.
[Ellis] [chuckles] Yeah.
I'll be right back.
[muffled electronic music]
[phone rings]
[laughter and chatter]
Sparkle.
- This is crazy.
- Sparkle, calm down.
There are so many girls.
So many young girls.
[Ellis] Sparkle. Sparkle, listen to me.
Don't "Sparkle" me! Don't "Sparkle" me.
It's not even my name. Don't "Sparkle" me.
I have no idea what I'm doing. [sighs]
[Ellis] I'm sorry. You okay?
Don't worry about me.
I found him, if that's
what you're wondering.
[Ellis] You found him?
Where are you?
I lost him.
Do me a favor. Don't call me anymore.
This is the first and the last time
I do something like this for you.
[Ellis] I understand.
Anything I can do?
I'll find him, but
after that, I'm through.
[sighs] There's gotta be a
better way to make money.
I'll be in touch.
[Ellis] When you find him,
be careful. He's dangerous.
I'm a big girl.
Besides, danger is my middle name.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music]
Thirsty?
I'm good.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You look like thirsty.
- I do?
I'm the kinda man that
gets what I'm looking for.
Do you understand?
I've done a lot of things
in my life I'm not proud of.
Some of it I regret.
Right now, I'm just searching.
For what?
I just want to feel...
I just want to feel again.
Feel what?
Do you know what it
is I do for a living?
No.
Let's just cut the bullshit,
and talk about why I'm
really here, how about that?
You have a blonde that works for you.
I believe she's Russian.
She took something that
belongs to me. I want it back.
I called you. You said you
were gonna look into it and...
I understand you have a
problem with one of my girls.
- I do.
- You do?
- Mm-hm.
And?
In the past, there have been
so many girls of your liking,
and since most of my girls are Russian,
it was hard to find the
one you were looking for.
Mm.
But I did find her.
You found her?
And I spoke with her personally.
You spoke to her personally?
- Mm-hm.
- And?
Unfortunately, she doesn't seem to have
any of your property.
I apologize for the inconvenience,
but maybe you've misplaced
it somewhere else?
That is unfortunate.
Because the people who need
that file, they're willin' to do
unimaginable things to
you, to get it back,
and I don't wanna see that happen.
Once again.
- I apologize.
- You apologize.
I wish we could be of more help.
But since we don't have
what you're looking for,
maybe I can interest
you in something else?
Something more suitable
to a man of your taste?
Do you mind if I look
around a little bit?
I really need that file.
Too bad.
'Cause we don't have it.
[phone rings]
- I gotta get that.
- Mm-hm.
[phone rings]
No, but seriously, I gotta get it.
Mm-hm.
Okay, so I'm gonna get it.
[phone rings]
I'll be right back, okay?
Esteban. Talk to me.
[Esteban speaks foreign language]
I hope you haven't kill anyone.
Why is that?
One. I like visiting that
place when I come to town.
Two. The file you're looking
for is no longer there.
[Ellis] You sure about that?
[Esteban speaks foreign language]
You...
[sighs] You drive me crazy.
Can you put your hands on it?
Not without making a mess.
[speaks foreign language]
I thought you're supposed
to be the best at what you do.
- You're makin' messes now?
- I'm as good as it gets.
But the Russians have
it under heavy control.
[sighs]
[speaks foreign language]
You're the only one that
knows about this problem?
I doubt it.
Okay, I gotta go.
I'm offering you my services.
Mr. Esteban. Thank
you, but no thank you.
- If you change your mind-
- I won't.
[Esteban chuckles]
[Esteban speaks foreign language]
[phone bleeps]
Is there something I can
do to change your mood?
[Ellis sighs]
I have to go.
But I'll be back.
Can't wait.
[Ellis sighs]
[dark music]
[car door slams]
The house is empty.
Only way is through the front
door which already unlocked.
The alarm's been set on,
so you'll know if anyone
or anything is movin'.
And I already swept the
house and the perimeter, so,
nothin' to worry about.
I'll keep watch through
night, make sure you're safe.
You gonna tell me?
Tell you what?
What's on the file.
You the police now?
You interrogating me?
You need to know what's in the file?
The kinda shit that if...
The kind of information
that if it got out...
It ain't good.
Anything else?
Can I ask you another question?
[sighs] Can I stop you?
Who, who...
Who's the girl?
[brooding acoustic guitar music]
[Ellis] Goodnight, Mr. Alexander.
Goodnight.
[car door slams]
Call Sparkle.
[phone rings]
What do you want, Ellis? [sighs]
I told you, I'll find this
guy and then I'm done.
[Ellis] I've gotta find
the file before he finds me.
Is that all?
[Ellis] No. I need you to
pick something up for me.
No.
- Come on, Sparkle.
- No.
[Ellis] Word is, they're
already looking for me.
Please, help me.
Anything else?
[Ellis] There's a farmhouse
on the outside of town.
- Bye.
- Yeah.
Julia?
Julia!
[gentle piano music]
[chuckles]
I gotta get you outta here, away from me.
What're you doing?
I'm leaving.
[Ellis] Where you going?
You said you ain't got nobody.
I'll find a place.
Hey. Don't.
What?
What do you want?
I know what I don't want.
I don't want you to go.
Which is...
It's scary, is all.
Stay with me.
There are times in life
when you make a decision
and you know, you know
in that very moment,
your life will never be the same.
Nice.
Very nice.
What is it?
I said nice. So obviously,
I'm not talking to you.
Special occasion, correct?
Mm-hm.
Very.
Yeah.
Then this one must be best.
So, you gonna tell me who she is?
Excuse me?
The most important part
of a properly made suit
is the lining.
The extra fabric, it's an added layer,
between the outside shell,
and your body.
So...
You can have 1,000 things
goin' on in the inside,
but on the outside, perfect.
The only time I've ever
saw you this nervous
is when you met your wife.
- You know somethin' else?
- Mm-hm.
When you're hiding somethin',
your left eye twitches.
- My left eye's twitchin'?
- Yeah, like it's doin' now.
It's the girl from the
other night, isn't it?
You done?
You finished?
I'll be back in an hour.
- Make it two.
- Mm-hm.
[Alexander] Oh, and Ellis?
Be careful.
My eye ain't twitchin'.
[dark electronic music]
[phone rings]
Hi.
So, did you find my file?
I told you, I don't have it.
What about the Russian girl who took it?
That girl doesn't exist.
[Ellis chuckles]
Bye, Maria.
Don't you wanna know why I called you?
- Okay, ciao.
- Wait, okay.
Yeah. [sighs]
Hey.
Don't hang up.
What do you have?
There is a man, a very dangerous
man, that wants you dead.
He's American, white, cold.
Real stand-offish type.
Blonde hair.
[Ellis] And?
He said his name was...
Kristof?
Look, I gotta go.
[Maria] Be careful.
Yeah.
[tense music]
Alexander.
[Alexander] Talk to me.
I need you to go to
the other safe house.
[Alexander] The one in the mountains?
Yeah. Yeah, that one.
Secure it.
[Alexander] On it.
The house. Everything around it.
[Alexander] It'll be great. You comin'?
Yeah, I'm comin'.
- And I'm bringin' the girl.
- Of course you are.
[Ellis] Feels like I've
been fighting for somethin',
one thing or another, my whole life.
First it was honor.
Then it was my beliefs.
And now it's for love.
They say there's always
one thing that happens.
One event that changes
your whole life forever.
I never believed that shit.
[somber piano music]
Until now.
Help! Somebody, help!
Help!
Please! Somebody, help!
[woman sobs]
[muffled sirens wail]
Hey.
Are you awake?
[Julia moans]
I am now.
[both chuckle]
[sighs]
Can I ask you something?
[Julia] Anything.
[gentle piano music]
Anything?
[Julia] Anything. [chuckles]
[Ellis sighs]
Why me?
I mean, look at you.
You could have anybody you want.
Why me?
Well...
You're fine, for one. [laughs]
- I'm tryin' to be serious.
- Yeah, so am I.
- This is my serious face.
- Oh, okay.
Why are you asking?
I don't wanna fuck this up, you know?
What do you mean?
Just my life, you know.
Things I do.
A lot of people wanna hurt me.
I'd be dead already if it wasn't for you.
That's sweet.
It's true.
My turn.
[Ellis chuckles]
- Your turn?
- Mm.
I've got something I wanna tell you.
Oh, really?
You got somethin' you wanna tell me?
That I had to wake you
up to tell me? [laughs]
- I was dreaming about it and-
- Oh, did it just...
- Like an epiphany?
- Yeah, yeah.
I don't think [indistinct]. Mm-hm, okay.
So you had an epiphany. I
want to hear all about it.
Say it, come on.
- I don't know.
- Hey.
You ain't got nothin' to worry about.
Ain't nobody gonna do nothin'
to you. Say whatever you want.
Say it.
I love you.
What?
[Julia] I love you.
Stop. Just stop talking like that.
[Julia] Why?
'Cause you don't know
what you're talking about.
That's why.
[Julia] I don't know
what I'm talking about?
I want you to stop talking about it.
- Why?
- Stop.
- Because!
Why not?
'Cause you don't know
what you're talking about.
- Yes, I do.
- No, you don't.
- Why you wanna do this?
Do what?
Why you wanna mess things up?
Like, things are going
great. Aren't you happy?
- Yes, I'm happy!
- Okay, good!
- Then why you wanna-
- That's what I'm saying!
You love me?
- Yes.
- How do you know?
- I just do.
- How?
I just do.
And I think you love me, too.
[somber music]
Am I wrong?
[scoffs] Forget it.
- Hey.
- No.
- Just stop!
- No, why?
- Why?
- 'Cause I need you to stay.
That's why.
Because you love me?
Why?
'Cause I need you.
That's not enough.
Why?
Why're you doing this to me?
Okay, fine.
I love you.
You hear that?
Yes. [chuckles]
You happy now?
- Yes.
- You suck.
[Julia] You suck! You
suck, you're the worst.
- You're the worst ever.
- Oh, I tell you what.
- You made me work so hard.
- Oh, I tell you-
- You know, I knew it.
I love you.
It's not smart.
I love you too, baby.
Yeah, you do.
You love me. [chuckles]
[Ellis] Yeah, I love you.
[Julia] Better.
[muffled giggling]
[Ellis grunts]
[heartbeat thuds]
[Ellis breathes deeply]
[doorbell rings]
You must be Ashley.
You can have your seat.
Man's like beautiful thing.
[Ashley speaks foreign language]
There is a lot thing you can for me.
But nothing now. I'm good.
[ominous music]
[bullets click]
[magazine and barrel click]
[speaks foreign language]
[sighs]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I know this is not what you do,
and rarely ever do you come out.
So, thank you.
[Esteban speaks foreign language]
But, I understand the need for secrecy.
No problem.
Thank you, my friend.
Have a seat.
[Esteban sighs]
[Esteban speaks foreign language]
First thing first.
I found the ring you're looking for.
Took me some time.
But I found it.
How do you know it's the real thing?
[Esteban speaks foreign language]
Take a look.
[suspenseful music]
[melancholy piano music]
Thank you.
[Esteban speaks foreign language]
Today's your lucky day.
I guess so.
[Esteban] Man.
What a beautiful place.
[Ellis] You think so?
My wife loves this place.
[suspenseful music]
[Esteban speaks foreign language]
'Cause I don't accept any returns.
[chuckles]
[speaks foreign language]
What an interesting guy you are.
- It's clean?
- Of course!
- Untraceable?
- Abso-fucking-lutely.
- And loaded?
- Always.
[speaks foreign language]
Thank you.
I know you said you wouldn't
need my services anymore.
But if there is anything else,
you know where to find me.
[footsteps recede]
[melancholy piano music]
[eerie tones]
[Ellis pants]
[Heartbeat thuds rapidly]
[Julia chuckles]
[brooding jazz music]
How does that feel?
Nice.
Real good. Thank you.
Big day's coming.
Yeah.
[Alexander] Nervous?
No.
I've been waiting on
this day for a long time.
Gotta look my best, you know.
Ow!
So what is this now for us? 16, 17?
20.
20?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
- 20.
- Ow.
Sorry.
And don't you always look your best?
Yes. I do.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
This will be no different.
- Be still?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Finished.
[Ellis sighs]
Great. How much do I owe you?
This one's on me.
I can't take-
- Listen, you have to.
It's not necessary. I can pay you.
I've done suits for you
for every special occasion.
Baptisms.
Birthdays.
Graduations.
Every one.
It's true.
And now you say this is...
This is our last.
So, this is me saying thank you.
Okay.
Thank you.
You wanna do something for me?
Yeah. Anything.
Anything?
Then can you tell me
what's really going on?
And I mean really.
I can't.
Well, then can you at
least let me help you
with whatever it is that
you're not tellin' me?
I can help you.
I can be very
resourceful.
I know.
Okay.
Can you at least do me one favor?
Just one.
Ease up off the weights a little bit.
Any more muscular and you're
gonna be tearin' through
my double-stitched sleeves
and I can't be havin' that.
[chuckles] I understand.
You always say that.
Yeah.
I know.
I'll be back in an hour.
- Make it two.
- "Make it two."
All right.
[Alexander chuckles]
Yeah, right.
[birds tweet]
[melancholy piano music]
- Hey.
- Where are you?
- Taking care of some things.
[Julia] Yeah, well, you said
you were gonna be home early.
[Ellis] I know, I
know. It was important.
Uh-huh. Well, it's always something.
[chuckles] Well, can you at least tell me
when you're gonna be home?
- Why?
- Well, hello! [chuckles]
You know you're supposed
to tell me everything.
[Ellis chuckles]
- You funny.
- Uh-huh.
[Ellis] No, seriously.
I'll be there soon. I promise.
Lock up, you hear me?
[Julia] Okay, well...
- You gonna be okay?
- No, no.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
[Ellis] I'll be there soon. I promise.
Really?
[Ellis] Promise. I'll
be there real soon.
Mm-hm.
Okay. Well, you've got 30 minutes.
- You serious?
- Yes, I'm serious.
30 minutes. [chuckles]
If you're not home in 30 you
are going to be in big trouble.
[Ellis] Like that, huh? [chuckles]
Yeah.
Don't forget. Lock up
and turn on the alarm.
Yeah. Well, love you.
Bye.
Almost.
[door creaks]
[ominous music]
[door closes]
[gasps]
Sylvandale.
[chuckles]
What a surprise.
Overrated,
in so many ways.
Rough.
Unpolished.
Deceiving, on so many levels.
[sighs]
Only a fool would fall
for its false promises.
[sighs]
[glass shatters]
Where's Ellis?
I don't know.
Listen.
[Julia moans]
I'm gonna tell you how this is gonna go.
I'm gonna get what I want from you,
and then I'm gonna kill you.
The only question is, what
happens between now and then.
You tell me what I wanna
know, and I can be kind.
You don't...
[chuckles] Well, let's just say
what I have planned for you,
you're gonna be begging me to kill you.
[Julia sobs]
I'm waiting.
Please. Don't.
[gun cocks]
[gasps]
You're gonna make this
a lot of fun for me.
[Julia sobs]
Take off your clothes.
Take off your clothes!
[thud]
[Julia yelps]
[Julia sobs]
[thud]
[Julia yelps]
[Julia screams]
[Julia sobs]
What a waste.
[dark music]
Used to always say
this is where you come to
clear your mind.
I knew I'd find you here.
The ol' mountains.
My condolences.
I know how much you loved her.
And I told you, I told
you when you married her,
they wouldn't like it.
I know you're mad.
You want revenge. You
think you know who did it.
Probably calculating on
how you can hit 'em back.
But it'd be a big mistake.
They're waitin' on you to slip up
so they can kill you where you stand.
Just some friendly advice.
Yeah, but we ain't friends, are we?
Never intended on us to be.
Kristof wants to meet.
[suspenseful music]
[heartbeat thuds]
[brooding acoustic guitar music]
[melancholy music]
Hey, handsome.
Bad day?
The worst.
Well...
Is there anything I can
do to make it better?
[Ellis] I can think of a few things.
Oh.
Like what?
[Ellis sighs]
[Ellis mumbles]
[laughs]
I love you.
And it feels so good.
Hi, beautiful.
[Julia] Hi.
[metal door slams]
[Ashley speaks foreign language]
Why me?
How big?
[Ashley speaks foreign language]
[speaks foreign language]
I am in.
[metal door slams]
[Man] You were the head of a government
assassination team.
There's only one way out. Death.
[metal door slams]
[Ellis sighs]
[brooding orchestral music]
[magazine and barrel click]
[Woman] One day you're
not gonna make it.
[engine roars]
[distant muffled chatter]
[indistinct overlapping chatter]
[engine roars]
Are you fucking kidding me?
Like seriously, I almost died.
I'm never doing this again for you. Never.
Here.
[sighs]
I literally passed out.
- It's him.
- Are you sure?
Look at him.
His face was the last thing I saw
while he was choking
me, when I passed out.
That shack, it was in
the middle of nowhere.
Literally, spiderwebs,
freaking cobwebs everywhere,
and broken glass.
Reach into the glove
compartment, with your left hand.
Go up to the corner.
You feel that?
[Sparkle] Mm-hm.
Pull it out.
[Sparkle] How much is this?
[Ellis] I don't know.
What are you trying
to do? Buy my silence?
Pay me to keep quiet for...
A measly...
Oh, fuck.
30 grand?
'Cause if you are,
mm-mm, you're damn right.
You still couch surfing?
No.
I got myself my own place.
It's nothin' great, but it keeps me warm.
What's that?
It's a key.
You don't want it?
To your house.
It's my house, but it's your house now.
Thank you.
One stipulation.
You need to get off the
streets and live in it.
You can't sell it.
You can't rent it out.
[Sparkle] Thank you.
You're welcome.
Um...
Sparkle?
It's Tiffany.
Tiffany.
Take care of yourself.
I will.
[car door closes]
[phone vibrates]
[phone bleeps]
Yeah.
I need you to pick somebody up for me.
I know where he is.
[distant chatter]
[captive groans]
Take a walk.
[Captive] No, no!
You shut your mouth,
son. The king is here.
[slap]
[captive groans]
Shovel.
[Thug] In the trunk.
Horse tranquilizer.
Sure to bring down an elephant.
Enters the bloodstream quickly.
Shuts off all motor function.
Paralyzes everything from
his toes to his head.
Give him two.
[captive groans]
[phone bleeps]
I have some new information I
am sure you're going to want.
[ominous music]
[crickets chirp]
[ax thuds]
[shovel thuds]
What an interesting guy you are.
[speaks foreign language]
[dark music]
♪ Where do I go from here ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't know myself anymore ♪
♪ I say I don't know myself anymore ♪
♪ Where do I go ♪
[Ellis pants]
[lighter flicks]
Julia.
Honey?
Julia?
Oh, shit.
Julia.
Baby? Baby?
Somebody, help!
[dark music]
Everyone has a purpose.
As I think back on things,
it's clear to me now
what mine is.
For the first time in my life,
I feel alive.
[suspenseful music]
[ax clunks]
[Kristof moans]
[heartbeat thuds]
[Kristof grunts]
[ax thuds]
[blood splatters]
[thuds and grunts]
[pants]
[screams]
[thuds and grunts]
[blood splatters]
[pants]
[screams]
[ax thuds]
[pants]
[growls]
♪ Where do I go from here ♪
♪ Because I don't know myself anymore ♪
[overlapping chatter]
♪ I don't know myself anymore ♪
[Julia giggles]
♪ Where do I go from here ♪
♪ Because I don't know myself anymore ♪
♪ I say I don't know myself anymore ♪
[heartbeat thuds rapidly]
♪ Where do I go ♪
[gun fires]
[somber music]
Hey, handsome.
What took you so long?
[gentle piano music]
[Ellis] I've missed you.
The Japanese call it takotsubo syndrome.
When stressful events cause the
heart to balloon and distort
causing it to look like a
traditional fishing trap.
Like an octopus pot.
In other words, when
loving someone so much
means there's no living without them.
♪ Take from me ♪
♪ Took everything that I love ♪
♪ But I guarantee you can't
take this hate from me ♪
♪ No, they can't ♪
♪ All the heartaches and
pain, you can see it my eyes ♪
♪ Can't relate ♪
♪ At all ♪
♪ I'm a menace, try to do right ♪
♪ I did, now I'm back to sinning ♪
♪ What's the use of living
this life if you ain't in it ♪
♪ My mind's made up ♪
♪ Should probably ask the
Lord's forgiveness, for real ♪
♪ 24 hours and shadow in the day ♪
♪ Bury my enemies in the
shallowest of graves ♪
♪ On the daily I'm carrying
the heaviest of weights ♪
♪ Trying to come to grips ♪
♪ Look at all the
callouses this had made ♪
♪ In the mirror, see a stranger I forgot ♪
♪ What it's like to be alone,
not as easy as it once ♪
♪ Was before and now
the only thing I got ♪
♪ Is a vendetta and heart
like an octopus pot ♪
♪ Look it up ♪
♪ Where do I go from here ♪
♪ Because I don't know myself anymore ♪
♪ I say I don't know myself anymore ♪
♪ Where do I go ♪
♪ Break me, they try and tear
me down, look what it made me ♪
♪ I'm 'bout to send 'em to hell ♪
♪ Blood's boilin', feelin'
like my skin finna melt ♪
♪ Gonna have to lay me in the
grave before I sit in a cell ♪
♪ So when I come for you, let's
just call that Armageddon ♪
♪ Pray for 'em, you see me
better call the reverend ♪
♪ It's too late for 'em, close
your eyes, count to seven ♪
♪ In your pain, I'mma revel,
my theory on another level ♪
♪ Shit, I thought it was bad before ♪
♪ But I swore I wouldn't do this no more ♪
♪ I lost the only thing in life I adore ♪
♪ For our future, wanted
peace, now it's all-out war ♪
♪ What's done is done, there's
nothin' that I can do ♪
♪ No words that can explain the
feelings I'm going through ♪
♪ Was told if I ain't quick
things will catch up to me ♪
♪ But it's killin' me knowin'
that it caught up with me ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Damn ♪
♪ Where do I go from here ♪
♪ Because I don't know myself anymore ♪
♪ I say I don't know myself anymore ♪
♪ Where do I go ♪
[rumbling]
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull