Y'all know what
the fuck this is,
everybody get on
the fucking floor.
Get on the fucking ground.
Right now.
Which one of you bitches
got the keys to the vault?
Give me the motherfucking money.
Put the motherfucking
cash in the bag,
stop playing with me.
Don't fucking move,
give me that fucking money.
Get your ass
over here, come on.
Get your
motherfucking ass over here.
Let's fucking go, let's go.
Open this motherfucking
door, right the fuck now.
Don't you try shit,
open the fucking door.
Get the fucking keys
off the floor, come on.
Taking your sweet ass time.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Put this in the bag,
put, hurry the fuck up.
Come on bitch, come on,
get this shit in the bag.
Shit, come on.
Two minutes!
Come on.
Don't fuck with that shit.
Hurry up, put the mother
fucking cash in the bag.
Get that shit in there.
Hurry up,
put the motherfucking cash in
the bag, stop playing with me.
Get that shit in there,
come on, come on.
Come on, come on!
Speed that shit up, you
wanna make it home tonight?
A minute 30.
Don't fucking move, I'll
blow your fucking head off.
Hurry that shit, don't
take your sweet ass time.
Come on, come on.
Come on, is this it, is this it?
I'll kill every one
of you fucking bitches,
I don't give a fuck.
Get the fucking money in the bag
Fuck.
I told you no killing man.
God damn.
They are fucking
robbing us man.
Come on man.
You know that's not the case.
Then tell me
what is the case?
Bro, they just went public
plus their earnings
look absolutely amazing.
What did you expect?
Not to be
raped for a share.
You're so dramatic.
My man, look, this was
a great investment.
Give it about a year or two,
and I guarantee you, returns
are gonna look amazing.
Hands down, plus,
let's be honest,
have I ever steered you wrong?
Man, I will
give it six months.
That's all I'm
asking for my man.
Alright man.
I'll talk to you later.
All right, brother.
You keep
pulling this shit,
it's always the
same shit with you.
No, no, no, no.
Every fucking time.
It's always you,
it's always you.
You bring up the same
shit all the time.
Bitch, shut the fuck up when
I'm talking to you, bitch.
Put your fucking
hands off of me.
What, you gonna put
more bruises on me?
The fuck you looking at?
What you mad at him for?
911, what's
your emergency?
I think I just witnessed
a domestic violence case.
Were you assaulted?
No, not me.
I'm in my car.
I'm going
to transfer you
to someone who can assist you.
Can you please hold?
Sure, I'll wait.
Can I get
your address please?
Hey Roger.
Yeah, I just got home.
Yeah, I can take a look at it.
I'm gonna look at it now.
Okay, sure.
What's up little bro.
What's up Cyrus?
Damn, no hug or nothing?
I get it.
You bought you a new fancy
house and now you big timing me.
Huh?
That's cool, that's cool.
You finna invite a
nigga in or what?
I don't see any niggas here.
I'm fucking with you man.
For sure man.
Come on in here.
I see you're still into
this computer shit, huh?
Yeah, still into
computer programing.
Trying to make an
earnest living.
You still into that street shit?
They got my back, when
the family not there.
That cause I didn't visit
you when you in jail?
Moms did.
That's moms.
It's the only thing
we got left of hers.
I didn't even know you had it.
Yeah.
She came down to see me one day.
Sat across from me, and she
took it right off her neck.
Mama wrapped it around my hand.
And she said you gots
to fight for something.
Why she say that?
Cause I didn't feel like living.
I'm sorry man, I.
I should have came to visit you.
It's cool.
I know you had your reasons.
You seem like a smart dude.
Just like, why all
the dumb shit man?
Is it dumb shit because I
don't wanna follow the system?
You know, having this nice
house, nice car and job.
Doesn't mean you
made it little bro.
This shit don't last forever.
But robbing banks doeS?
Depends on what
you do with the money.
You take peoples money.
No, not the people.
Just the ones that
tax us, take ours.
You a lost soul.
I'm just unplugged little bro.
I'm not selfish in
this greedy ass world.
I ain't mad at you though.
This what a nine to five
gets a brother now a days?
Thanks.
You got any wifeys
or side chicks around
this motherfucker?
You happy in here?
I'm good, I'm good.
Come on bro, I'm not one
of your coworkers bro,
you ain't got to
try to impress me.
You still trying to find
love on them dating apps.
Ain't nothing wrong
with a dating app man.
I didn't say it was.
Then what are you saying?
That you worked hard to
build up your castle.
Be nice to share it with
someone, that's all.
I'm good.
And I mean like what is
this shit anyways man?
Lessons from a criminal?
Yeah, I'm a criminal,
but who's locked up?
You need to make
sure you get out,
enjoy your life a little bit.
Stop putting work in
front of everything.
Shit, help someone else
other than yourself for once.
Nigga, who you helped huh?
You'd be surprised.
But right now, I'm
trying to help you.
What do you want Cyrus?
I just want you to come
see me fight tonight.
Plus, me and Kelly got
something to tell you.
See you fight.
You mean that underground
shit where you
and a bunch of thugs try
to kill each other, right?
That's not fighting.
It's stupid.
I still won though.
Dropped ole boy after going
super saiyan two on him.
Hit him with that
muay thai elbow.
You funny, you funny, but
here's what's funnier,
you know they got higher
forms than that now, right?
Oh, I see.
You mad cause I got
better jabs then you, huh?
Is that what it is, it that?
Hey bro, you know you ain't
got better jabs than me.
I taught you everything
you know, my man.
Okay, okay.
I taught you everything
you know, bro.
I see, I see mister
golden gloves.
MMA Nigga.
Listen, this grown man shit,
you don't know
nothing about that.
You don't know
Okay, I don't know
nothing about that.
You don't know a
God damn thing bro.
Nothing.
Get out of here bro.
Nah though little bro,
the real question though,
what you working for here?
What's your end game?
What you mean end game?
Your end game, you know, like,
you got the nice house,
you got the fancy car.
But that's just material shit.
What about, you know,
starting a family?
Or shit, helping kids that
grew up like you and me did?
Nobody helped me up.
I had to grind for
everything I got.
That's why I sit where I sit.
That's true, that's true.
But does it feel right.
Does it feel, you rob
liquor stores and banks.
Does that feel right?
God works in mysterious ways.
There you go God, you God now?
You helping people out
and all that stuff,
you want some money?
Nah, I don't need
any money little bro.
Come on, I'm rich, in here.
Remember when we was kids?
Yeah.
I used to be
running the streets.
You was at home playing
video games all damn day.
You said that you
could hear the music
of the game even when
you wasn't playing.
I think one time you
didn't eat the whole day.
You got hella scared,
came running to me.
Big bro, make sure I don't
ever play a game
that long ever again.
I'm like man, you taking that
game shit, way to serious.
Yeah.
You need to come take
your ass outside with me.
What you used to tell me though?
I said I'd come
outside when I win.
Exactly.
When you motherfucking win.
Come see me fight tonight bro.
Damn baby, you looking good.
You tell your brother yet?
I told him that we have
something to tell him.
You still didn't tell him.
You know he doesn't come
to these things Cyrus.
He will tonight.
Is that so, why?
Because he's my brother.
He's not like you.
He'll be here, trust me.
I'm not gonna bet on it.
Can you just keep an eye out
for Marcus for me, please?
Thank you.
Yo, OG, I got next on this.
Put me down for five.
Five?
Yeah, yeah, I got
you young blood.
What you hear about the
bank on 25th street?
I hear a lot of things.
What you asking?
Is it clear to
make a withdrawal?
Word on the street's
that some large numbers
finna fly through there.
Early bird gets the worm.
Better be some big ass birds.
Sesame street with
all the characters.
You know a lot of folks
been looking at them worms,
but that show ain't
happening for a few days.
Is the network local?
Yeah.
So a few days.
Unless the chiefs
out of commission.
I think we can make that happen.
So, who you trying
to get in there with?
You know who.
Keep it down motherfuckers,
keep it down.
Y'all know how this shit goes.
No colors, no
sets, guns, knives,
or anything other than the
shit you was born with.
Now we all family
up in this bitch
and we just wanna get a little
something off our chest.
And if you're lucky,
make a little something
on the side to keep
the pockets right.
The fights over if you get
knocked out, tapped out, or quit.
Now our next fights
gonna be a good one.
We got Cyrus up against Malice.
All right you two,
keep it clean,
keep your guard up at all times,
but most importantly, let's
have some fun with this shit.
Come on
baby, you got this.
Look at your man now!
That boy got a mean hook.
You can't keep doing
this shit Cyrus.
What?
Stressing me out like that.
Come on baby, you know I was
just having a little fun.
Fun?
Yeah.
You can't continue to
move like this Cyrus.
Not if you're planning
on being here for us.
Yeah, no, no, you
right, you right.
I'll try to make sure the
blood stays inside my body.
All right?
Marcus isn't here Cyrus.
You need to tell him,
tell him everything.
Everything.
Let me handle
something real quick.
Masaai want to talk to you.
All right, I'll hit him
up when I leave here.
No, he said he want to
talk to you right now.
Really nigga?
You see I'm with my girl
and that's how you
finna pull up on me?
Cyrus I ain't trying
to disrespect you
cause we both on the same side,
but you know how Masaai is.
Said he wanted to talk to
you about that bank job.
To be honest with you,
I don't give a fuck
about none of this shit,
I'll smoke everyone
in this motherfucker.
You know how I get down.
Let's get our bundles back
up man, you know what it is.
All right, all right, relax
bro, it's good, it's good.
I'm a get my girl home,
then I'm a swing through.
Come on.
Don't come over
here with that shit,
what the fuck does he want?
Man, I gotta do something.
Do what?
Something.
Then I'm going.
Baby, I gotta go alone.
Alone?
Cyrus.
Baby, please.
Let me take care of this,
and I'll see you later
tonight, all right?
It's all right.
Promise me.
I promise.
It's gonna be all right.
Okay.
I'll be waiting for you.
Got this, got this.
Looking good, looking good.
All right.
Game time.
Tanya?
Yes, Marcus?
Wow, I gotta say,
you look amazing.
Thank you.
But yeah, yeah, come in.
Please, come in.
Can I get you anything to
drink Don Perignon, Don Julio,
let me guess you're
a Rose kind of girl?
Do you tell that to every girl
that comes into your house?
No, I don't, I
just figured you'd
want something to drink.
Just trying to be a good host.
No thank you, it's all right.
Can I put this over here?
Yeah, by all means,
make yourself at home.
You have a nice place.
Thank you.
I was actually
thinking about putting
a 60 inch screen
right over there,
with some surround sound
for the living room
and the kitchen, you
know, really make it pop.
You didn't want
anything to drink right?
No, it's okay.
Honestly I just want
you to come over here.
Sorry.
You know I'm honestly,
I've had terrible luck
with all of the dating
apps that I've been on.
So I'm really excited that
we're meeting right now.
Yeah, I think I can attest
to that, absolutely.
I'm actually kind of
surprised that you agreed
to come here,
especially to my house.
Okay, honestly I wasn't
thinking about coming over,
but my brother lives
right down the street
so if you're with
any funny business
he'll be over here, quickly.
Promise, listen, I promise
I don't want any big
brother problems.
Of course, understood.
Scouts honor.
I am so happy that you're here,
so that's genuine, that's real.
Thank you, thank you.
And I'm glad you asked me.
Definitely.
So you're into
computer programming?
Yeah, yeah, program
management actually.
Eight plus years,
got into some things
like stocks, Facebook,
Amazon, Google.
Could I get some water actually?
Yeah.
I'm a little thirsty.
Yeah, totally.
Thank you.
Can I, here you go.
Thanks.
Can I get you anything else?
No, it's fine.
Okay, cool, can just so
you know I got us a 9:30
at the Lounge, great restaurant,
I'm sure you'll like.
Yeah.
Cool, so you're a
teacher, high school.
That's awesome,
tell me about it.
It's actually middle
school, but it's great.
Honestly I think
my favorite part
is just watching kids
develop into who they are.
Like whatever
information I teach them,
they're gonna have
to go out into
the world and
utilize that one day.
So I honestly think
it's just amazing.
Wow, wow, I can tell you're
really passionate about it,
is it something
you've always wanted?
Yeah, I mean, no,
I mainly wanted
to be maybe and actress
or maybe a talk show host.
But I really just wanna
empower the world.
That's interesting.
If I can ask, what changed?
Did you always want to be
in computer programing?
No.
Funny thing about
that is I actually
just want to be just
like my brother.
And what does he do?
Not much actually, in
his words he lives free.
You kind of say that
like it's a bad thing.
Living free is great.
I mean, I mean like
there's no money in it,
and I mean bums live free.
I personally feel
like you should
just pursue the acting thing.
Keep your pursuing that
because everyone knows there's
no real money in being
a teacher, right?
Excuse me?
I don't know what you think,
but I don't think of money and
happiness as the same thing.
There's a lot of lonely
and rich people at the top.
Starting to sound
like my brother.
Maybe he's right.
I love him to death but he says
the same thing and he has
nothing to show for it.
Okay, let me get this straight,
do you think I have
nothing to show for myself?
No, no, no, you're
twisting my words,
that's not what I
meant, I'm saying
you're a high school
teacher, that's awesome.
Thanks asshole, I'm actually
a middle school teacher.
And maybe you should think
about building
relationships with people
before you just decided to brag
about all the cool
crap that you have.
I apologize, I didn't.
Can we just, can we
just take it back?
I didn't mean that.
It's okay, honestly.
I'm sorry?
And you know, I do
empower the world.
These kids, they're the future
and I'm trying to empower them.
So have fun sitting at
the top by yourself.
Call me.
This is Lucy.
700 pounds, a big bitch.
Loyal.
She keeps her mouth shut.
She lets me beat her, flip her.
She doesn't say shit.
Never talks, complains, and
separate men from beast.
You and your crew took care
of the brinks truck last week.
How much was in it?
Around 75K.
75,000.
Tomorrow I need you and
your crew at 25th street.
I want you all to
understand loyalty.
You take care of me,
I take care of you.
This right here, is a
small part of loyalty.
Trust.
Getting shit done for
the bigger picture.
That's you.
On the opposite end of
loyalty, you've got rats.
And you could flush
them out with cheese.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, please.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean it.
I didn't mean it,
I didn't mean it.
Please don't, please
don't, I'm sorry.
Nobody like rats!
I'm sorry,
please, I'm sorry.
I wanna go home,
I wanna go home.
Please.
Please, please, please.
I didn't mean it, I didn't
mean it, I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Please, please.
He's just a kid.
Mice and rats do the same shit.
Big Mike got 20 years
because somebody
recognized him in a lineup.
That could have
been any one of us.
Kids make mistakes Masaai.
It shouldn't cost
them everything.
It shouldn't.
Another reason why Lucy
separates men from beast.
Men and beast.
So tomorrow?
Yeah, tomorrow.
Let's go man, check
it out, check it out.
You know I gotta make
you look bad, all right?
I'm right here man.
Okay, show me.
Look what I got.
Got 'em cooach, you ain't never
too old for a spanking baby.
Yeah, okay, I call that luck.
Yeah, okay,
I call it skill.
All right up top.
Okay, I call it skill man.
Let me see that skill
from right there,
pull that J, what you got?
I want the jumper.
Damn.
I take that up top.
Let little bro show you
how it's done, yeah?
All right.
Check this up top.
Let's go.
Right here, I want it.
What you want, what you want?
Whoo!
That's how it's done.
Heavy, them W's are real
heavy right now man.
Wow, wow.
I mean you look like
you had a nice workout,
them L's must weigh something.
Oh my goodness, good
game bro, you got it.
Good game, good game.
You got that one.
Damn.
What's up bro,
what's on your mind?
You always could read me.
Honestly man I was just thinking
about what you
said the other day.
About what?
You know, if it feels right.
The cars, the money,
shit like that.
Yeah.
I just never thought about it.
You should bro,
you really should.
What happened to you last night?
I had a date.
A date?
Date.
Okay, my man, my man.
I thought you was just
trying to blow my fight off.
Come on bro, you know I just
don't get down with that,
that's all, it's no disrespect,
it's just that street shit?
I can't support it.
I'm not looking for
your support bro,
I just wanted you to see
my last fight in the ring.
Last fight for real?
Yeah, my last fight bro.
I got other plan in effect.
Setting something up that
I want you to be apart of.
Honestly, so long as those plans
don't involve you going back
to jail, I'm all for it.
The real question is this man,
when are you gonna let me
hook you up with a job?
Man, fuck all of that man,
plus we got something
to tell you.
We as in like you and Kelly?
Boy, you know she don't
mess with me like that.
She don't know
you like that bro.
You always busy, some new
promotion or some shit.
Fam, she cussed me
out smooth last time.
Disrespectful.
Yeah, that was funny.
That was funny?
That was funny.
Okay.
Look though man, try to
get to know her for me.
Y'all got a lot more in
common then you think.
Probably why I
love both of y'all.
Yeah, look I'll try
man, I guess sometimes
I just don't see the
similarities, that's all.
Well I gotta get up
out of here man, but.
Let me know when
you're free though,
to see me and Kelly, all right?
I gotta go.
You gotta, you
leaving right now?
Think we could
play one last game,
you know, pick up, something.
Give you this last I.
I gotta meet up
with somebody bro,
no more L's for me today.
All right,
I respect it man.
I love you bro.
I love you to bro.
Take care of yourself.
Stay up man.
Why you park over here?
Bank like, down the street.
Seemed like a cool little
vantage point from here.
All right you know the drill.
We in, we out.
No bystanders, and don't
get fucking greedy.
Cyrus, I don't know
about this one G.
Know about it.
Come on bro, why you so nervous?
Acting like we ain't
done this before.
Fuck.
Killah, this look
like a set up bro.
What?
A set up nigga.
Fuck!
All right.
Check it out.
We're gonna rob this
motherfucking bank regardless.
Even if we got to go through
that nigga, on my mama.
Serious Cyrus?
Dead ass bro.
That's a lot of sweat.
He sent you to do it?
So that big bitch couldn't
do it himself, huh?
When's it supposed to happen?
After we rob this bank.
Cyrus, he knew what you were
doing with that money bro.
I'm sorry man.
The fuck you doing nigga?
Motherfucker!
Killah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, man.
Hold on a second.
What you're really
trying to tell me
is you didn't even get a kiss.
Listen man, all I'm saying
is she started tripping as soon
as I said she should
get a different job
because, surprise,
teachers don't make much.
Damn man.
She should have
written you a check
for giving her financial advice.
Right?
I'm dropping gems,
and she's not even
trying to pick them up.
Man, her loss.
You know we need to
create our own dating app,
you know one that finds
chicks that understand us.
No, no, we don't need
to make an app man.
Come on man,
we have everything
we need in front of us,
and we know how to
operate the system.
My man.
Are we going to
get back to work?
Yeah, yeah,
we can get back to it.
I'm just saying,
since we're already
out here changing the world with
the way that people
interact with their phones
and computers, we
already understand
the back end development.
It'd be awesome to manipulate
the system and get what we want.
Yeah, but see,
that's the problem.
People are flesh and blood,
they're not just and app.
You can't program in it
and get what you want.
No, no man,
I call bullshit.
Everyone is so connected
to this system,
they probably don't
even know how to make
a decision without consulting
the social media overlords.
People will be fine man.
We got a system in place that,
so long as everyone
does their position,
you know, they play it
right, they'll be fine.
Yeah man, you
know man, you got some...
Rodger should be
announcing who's getting
that new position down
South in two weeks.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, that's gonna
be a lot of money
man, big money.
Hell yeah.
Plus stock options and RSU's.
You know, I think
you're gonna get it.
Fingers crossed man.
I mean, if everything works out,
we could put a whole
new system in place.
Wait, wait.
What system is that?
What the fuck, what the fuck?
You gonna be an uncle nigga.
Not like this, what the fuck?
What the hell did you?
Who did this, what the fuck
happened, who shot you?
Marcus, Marcus, hey, hey.
I love you man, I
love you brother.
No, no, no, no, no,
you ain't doing this.
You gonna be and uncle man.
You gonna be an uncle.
Stop, stop, you're gonna
be a great fucking dad
when that happens, but we gotta
keep pressure on this shit.
Stop talking.
You'll make it alive.
Fuck, you'll make
it alive, shit.
Hold on, hold, hold on.
Let me get the phone.
Shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit, shit, shit.
Get this bag to Kelly.
I need an ambulance right now!
I'm at 720 Kirkwood Avenue,
my brothers been shot.
Please, just come right now,
just come right now, fuck!
You're gonna
be an uncle bro,
you're gonna be an uncle.
You'll be a good dad, we
won't worry about that.
Just keep pressure here,
stop talking Cyrus.
Kelly's pregnant.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Pressure on the wound,
God damn it, fuck!
No, you straight, you straight.
No, I don't want
it, I don't want it.
You got to fight for something.
Fight for something.
Fuck!
I'm sorry I wasn't
there for you two.
I'm gonna find who did this.
I promise you.
Marcus, you've been pacing
for like an hour now
man, you need to chill.
Come on man.
The cops are going
to be here any minute
and I'm sure they'll
have some kind
of lead or something for you.
It's been three weeks.
Last time they were here,
they took me in,
wrecked my shit,
and accused me of killing Cyrus.
They need to start
doing their jobs.
Damn!
Officer.
Marcus Sims?
Yes sir.
Any news of who shot my brother?
Do you have a gun in the house?
What?
Do you have a gun
on the premises?
No, we went through
this already.
Do you have any
fucking thing for me?
You need to calm down Mr. Sims.
I was just asking
you a question.
No, who shot my brother?
Do you have anything for me?
Did you know your
brother was in a gang?
He even did some
time a few years ago.
It's only common that something
like this was gonna
happen sooner or later.
Common, so that makes it okay?
I haven't heard shit
about this case.
Are you guys even
fucking doing your jobs?
Don't question what we do.
Your brother robbed a
bank, and came here.
And yet none of the
money was found.
I could you run you
in as an accomplice.
Run me as a?
You mother.
You better choose your
next words carefully boy.
Or it won't be just your brothers
blood spilt in this house.
Officer, sorry about the hassle.
My friend here is still
a little shaken up
about the loss of his brother.
We'll call you if
we need anything.
Is there anything else we
can help you with officer?
No.
Looks like I'm done here.
You got a nice
place here Marcus.
What the fuck was
that shit about.
Bro, you almost got shot,
that's what that was.
They basically ain't doing shit
and then they want to
put the blame on me
so they don't have to
do their fucking jobs.
It's bullshit.
Relax dude.
You always say system works.
No, fuck the system.
I got it.
What?
Remember how we talked
about creating that program?
If the system doesn't work,
create one for yourself.
I still don't get it.
How did this turn
into getting chicks?
Are you trying to make
your own dating app?
No, no, no, no.
I'm gonna do what the
system's supposed to do.
By yourself?
Yeah.
Okay.
What's your plan?
First I gotta find out who was
there during the bank robbery.
YoU just want to get the
banks camera footage?
I'm pretty sure they wore masks.
Yeah, I know my brother had
a crew that he rolls with.
Shit, maybe they'll
know something.
So you want to go up to a bunch
of gangsters and say,
what, who shot my brother,
so I can turn them
into the cops?
Shit dude, I don't fucking know.
I'm just hoping
maybe if I'm around
and I fucking hear something.
No offense Marcus, but
your no Neio Brown.
I don't Know if
I should slap you
or high five you for
knowing that reference.
High five, but the fact that
you said high five
proves my point.
Whatever.
So how do you plan
on getting close to
your brothers crew?
Kelly.
Thank you for coming Kelly.
What do you want?
Can you just take a seat please?
I'm not trying to
reopen old wounds.
I need to know who Cyrus
was with during the robbery.
Is that why you brought me here?
No, that's not the case, listen.
The police think I killed Cyrus.
You're trying to
clear your name.
Kelly, that's not the case.
I actually thought you cared
about who killed Cyrus.
Don't, don't do that.
Sounds like something
you would do.
Selfish and only
thinking about yourself.
I earned that, that's fair,
but I still need your help.
Why should I help you?
Because we're family Kelly.
Because I'm trying
to be a good uncle
for my niece or for my nephew.
I'm trying to do everything
I'm supposed to do
for you, for myself.
For Cyrus.
He told you?
Yeah, he told me
before he passed.
I don't know who Cyrus was
with but I think I might,
I think I might know
someone who knows.
Who.
They call him OG.
OG huh?
Yeah.
He holds these
fights, and if anybody
knows who did it, it's him.
Can you get me in?
I'm pretty sure I can.
But Marcus, if the guys
who shot Cyrus are there,
what makes you think they
ain't gonna do the same to you?
No, I'm not worried about that,
they don't know I'm his brother.
So what are you gonna do
when you find out who did it?
I don't know right now.
You don't know?
Marcus, these people don't play
by the rules they will kill you.
So when are we leaving?
All right Marcus,
we gotta keep it cool.
Hey don't worry
about me, I got it.
See that guy over there?
Yeah.
That's OG.
In the pink?
Yeah.
All right, wait here.
You OG?
Boy what the fuck you want?
Are you OG?
Who the fuck is asking?
Marcus.
Who the fuck is Marcus?
Doesn't even matter,
I've got questions.
Well if you in my
house, it matters.
Tell you ain't a cop.
Hey Kelly.
I'm sorry OG, this is Marcus,
he's new to the house.
He doesn't know house rules yet.
What you mean house rules.
Yeah, little nigga, house rules.
This is my house, and there
are rules up in this bitch.
All right, let's try again.
Who's Marcus?
Somebody who's got questions.
To what?
I want to know about the crew
that robbed the bank on 25th.
House rules.
So who you fighting?
What?
Who you fighting?
I didn't come here
for a fucking fight.
Well you came here
looking for one,
plus if you want nay word on
the crew that rolled that bank,
you'll be stepping in that ring.
Listen here Marcus, in this
house people follow my rules.
And if you wanna leave
here with your face intact,
you'll be doing the same.
So, who you fighting.
Doesn't matter.
All right, we have
our winner Bear.
Now don't forget
to pay what you owe
so I don't have to come
looking for your ass.
And as always, house
gets ten percent.
All right motherfuckers,
we got some fresh meat
coming to the stage.
I'm pretty sure you'll all want
to give him a warm welcome.
Marcus and his opponent Barnes.
All right you two,
keep it clean,
keep your guard up at all times,
but most importantly, let's
have some fun with this shit.
You're mine.
What are the rules?
Win.
Fuck him up, yeah!
Damn.
I guess we have a winner.
Tell me what the
fuck I need to know.
That was a hell of a fight.
Somebody makes sure
Barnes ain't dead
and get him up off my stage.
Look, I got on your
fucking little stage
and I fought all right?
Now I want some goddamn answers.
I can tell by the way you fought
you're not a street fighter,
you're professional.
We don't get those down here.
I need to know.
Was your family in that
bank that got robbed?
Are you looking for revenge
against the robbers?
What I'm not seeking
is a goddamn father
figure, all right?
Who the fuck was in the crew?
Calls himself Masaai.
Masaai?
Yeah, it was his crew
that rolled that bank.
Word on the street is they
got ambushed by another gang.
I don't know who that was,
I just know that a lot
of folks were talking
about hitting that place.
How do I talk to Masaai?
There's no talking to Masaai,
you have to be in his crew
to even get close to him.
Then how do I get
in the fucking crew?
Boy, you must have a death wish.
Masaai ain't the kind of guy you
can just walk up to and
ask a couple of questions.
He'll take you out even
if you're a professional.
Who here is in his crew?
There's a few.
His right hand soilder used
to come around here a lot.
Who was that?
Cyrus, he got shot up by
another crew doing that heist.
It's a shame too.
He was a good soldier,
shit, he was a good man.
Him and Kelly was a thing.
Did You know him?
Anybody here from his crew?
Wait, wait, he talked about you.
This isn't your life Marcus.
If you take that step,
it's gonna follow you for
the rest of your life.
Point out the guy.
Guy in the black raiders cap.
What's up?
You know, you're not
the usual down here.
Shit, I'm here now.
So what business
you got with OG?
That old nigga?
Look, I'm looking to join
the toughest crew around.
That's what's up,
you got hands G.
Shit the way you took out Barnes
with the elbow, shit was dope.
Appreciate it.
We could use someone like you.
Who's in your crew.
No questions though.
You down to ride?
Where we going?
Dog, are you down?
Yeah I'm down.
All right look, finish
kicking with your girl,
enjoy a few fights.
I'll come grab you in a
little bit, all right?
All right.
All right, sure.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
I found the dude that Cyrus was
rolling with and their crew.
That guy?
Mmhm.
I'm rolling with them tonight.
Marcus, are you sure?
I'm telling you
this is not a game.
Cyrus always said I got to
step out eventually, right?
But nah, I got it.
You should head home, I got it.
Are you sure?
I'll be fine.
Marcus.
Thank you.
I'll see you later.
Get out the car,
get the fuck out.
Shit.
Nigga move.
Who the fuck Samson think he is?
Bringing these new
niggas to the spot.
See, that's why I had
to take care of his ass.
What the fuck you doing
with Samsom anyways?
Just looking to join
the toughest crew
around, that's all.
Nigga, who are you?
Marcus.
What do you know about loyalty?
Allegiance and trust.
Trust is earned,
respect is given,
loyalty is demonstrated.
Betrayal of any one of those.
You lose all three.
So you want to be apart of this?
Yeah.
You're gonna have to
earn your loyalty.
There's a liquor store
on tenth and Broadway.
You're gonna rob it.
At any given time, that place
holds onto about 15,000 cash.
Bring it to me, all of it.
You get it here, we can talk.
If it's not here
within 48 hours,
I'll start killing everybody
on this fucking phone.
I think you understand that.
Right Marcus?
Yeah.
Nigga, what the fuck
you still doing here?
Bounce!
What's up Marcus?
Yo.
Damn man, what happened?
Got into some shit man.
Does this have anything
to do with that gang stuff
you were talking
about the other day?
Honestly man, I'd rather
not talk about it at work.
Just stop by later on tonight
and I'll tell you all about it.
Call the cops?
If only it was that simple.
Marcus, you got a sec?
Yes sir.
What happened to your face?
Oh, just kick boxing classes.
Well I hope you got a few
licks in on the other guy.
Absolutely.
Let's talk in my office.
Yes sir.
You've been doing very well
with this company Marcus
and I'd like to thank
you for your hard work.
Thank you very much sir.
You're a strong leader, and
you're someone I can trust.
Very loyal to the company with
the sacrifices you've made.
I know you are aware
we are expanding
and we'll have a satellite
building down South.
I would like you to run it.
You okay with that?
Yeah, yes sir.
It will require some change.
Are you okay with relocating?
Of course.
That's great.
I actually want to send
you out tomorrow afternoon
to Los Angeles to meet
with the head of marketing
and go over some
quarterly business plans.
Tomorrow you said?
Yes, tomorrow.
Is that gonna be a problem?
Course not.
Okay.
Marcus, I feel you will
be the right person
for the position.
You have no attachments.
You understand how
to play the game,
and that will get you
far in this company.
Don't let me down.
I won't sir.
Excuse me.
You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Cyrus always had
bruises on his face.
Yeah.
Guess he has something to be
proud of me for now, right?
He was always talking about you.
He was always talking
about that obsession
with that Dragon Ball Z
show y'all always watched.
Anime, yeah.
I'm honestly surprised
he even told you that.
All the time.
He was a good spirit.
Just like Goku.
Yeah.
So did you hear about the people
that Cyrus was hanging out with?
I don't think I can do it Kelly.
Do what?
They want me to rob a store
and I have 48 hours to do it,
some sort of fucking initiation
or some shit like that.
I don't know.
And you told them no?
I don't think it works that way.
They have my phone and
all my contacts in it.
They, they said
they'd start to kill
everyone in my phone
if I didn't do it.
So what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
My boss, he offered
me a job in LA and.
I honestly just
feel like taking it.
A job?
Is it front end, or
back end programming?
How do you know that?
Before I met Cyrus, I
was a web developer.
I'm not just the girl
that cusses you out.
What happened?
Well.
I fell for Cyrus.
And everything
that comes with it.
I chose family.
They have a list of all my
contact Kelly, and my phone.
It's okay Marcus.
It's not okay.
You're in that
contact list Kelly.
Look Marcus.
Do what you need to do, okay?
You don't owe Cyrus or
me anything, all right?
Cyrus would be proud of you.
You know something?
I guarantee he's looking down
right now, and still proud.
Man, this is too crazy.
What are you gonna do?
I'm thinking.
A lot just fucking happen man.
What about wearing a wire?
Fuck no.
Shit.
What?
Rodger offered me the position.
Holy shit, that's great!
You took it, right?
I don't know.
He wants me to fly out tomorrow.
Well damn man,
that's your way out.
It's not that easy man.
Why?
Because they have your phone?
You can go to the cops,
they can track that thing,
and you can bust them.
It's because I still don't
know who killed Cyrus!
And that doesn't even
guarantees Kelly's safety.
Look, Marcus don't take
this the wrong way man,
but up until these
last couple weeks,
I barely even heard you
talk about your brother,
and we worked together
for five years.
I don't talk about Cyrus
because we took
different paths in life.
We all got family
members like that man.
We never knew our dad.
Mom was strung out on drugs.
In and out of
fucking foster homes.
My head would fucking spin.
Cyrus, he was my fucking rock,
he was my fucking everything.
He used to just
keep us together,
he tried to keep us together.
I'm sorry
to hear that man.
Over time I just
learned to block it out.
You can get real
good at blocking
stuff out if you
try hard enough.
He was in jail, mom was,
I don't know where
the fuck mom was.
Probably on drugs.
And then one day, police knock
on my door and
tell me she's dead.
I didn't even go to
her fucking funeral.
I just, I didn't
even fucking care.
I put my career in front of her,
in front of my fucking family.
I can't do that again.
Not with Cyrus.
He deserves better,
he deserves more.
Look man, I hear you, okay.
This isn't some game, you're
into some serious shit.
So what are you going to do?
I need to make
15,000 by tomorrow.
Fuck.
What about LA?
I can't.
If I'm gonna do this,
I gotta be all in.
Rodger can find somebody else.
So you're mind's made up?
Yeah.
Well, I mean you can't
dip into your stocks
because it'll take at least a
week to get everything liquid.
Yeah, I need something fast,
I need something immediate.
Maybe you can sell your watch.
That's not worth 15,000.
I got it.
What?
Craigslist.
What are you gonna
sell on Craigslist?
You got your phone
on you, right?
Yeah.
I need you to take
some photos of my car.
15,000.
Good shit, take a seat.
So, why do you want
to be apart of this?
I'm looking to join a family.
So you don't
have any family out here?
No.
Do you know why I had you
rob that liquor store?
Initiation.
Trust.
We do things to
preserve the trust
in the group, in the family.
Now you want to be
apart of that family?
Yes sir.
Don't call me sir.
We got some big things
getting ready to happen.
If you're apart of
this, it's all the way.
No half ass shit.
I'm in.
You can hold onto that for me.
That's good.
Honestly, I need to make
more money, 15K isn't enough.
I hear you.
Like I said, we have somethings
coming down the pipe line.
What about like, like banks.
What about banks?
You know, anything I need
to look out for if I
end up robbing one?
For what?
Couple weeks ago there was
a bank heist on the news.
Cats who robbed
the spot got shot.
Samson said it was one of y'all.
Yeah, shit happens.
I mean like what kind of shit?
Street shit?
You worried about beef?
No, I'm just saying,
looking out for myself.
The only nigga you need
to watch out for is me.
Samson saw you down at
the underground fights.
Yeah.
What do you
think about that place?
It's cool, why?
There's a lot of money
going through that place.
Okay.
It's a protected place.
What do you mean protected?
Kind of a truce between gangs,
to keep businesses running
smoothly from city to city.
And the cops
don't know about it?
Know about it?
Shit, it was their idea.
Why the underground fights?
Because pigs find
it entertaining.
You met OG?
Yeah, I met him.
A dirty cop.
He's the reason why
two of my soldiers
got hit during that bank heist.
You telling me OG's a cop?
OG orchestrated a hit that
put my soldiers Cyrus
and Killah in harms way.
Them pigs been trying to
get at me for the longest.
Why you ain't done
nothing about it?
OG?
That's what you're for.
I'm sending you and a couple
of soldiers over there to
take care of that place.
No disrespect Masaai,
but I feel like
that's a little much
to put on my shoulders,
don't you think?
This is called trust.
Look at it as your initiation.
Besides, if you don't do
it, you're dead anyway.
Okay.
When are we going?
Right now.
What's it gonna be?
You got a problem with this?
Not at all.
This is for Killah, and Cyrus.
Our family.
Yeah.
Take this to the
coffee shop on 16th,
let them know it's from me.
Get the fuck down!
Get up, get up!
Get up!
So you a cop?
What?
So you're a cop!
Yeah, yeah I'm a cop.
Look, just take the money,
I won't tell anyone.
So you set up the robbery huh?
You set up the ambush.
What are you talking about?
Marcus?
Marcus this isn't you.
There ain't no
fucking Marcus here.
I know it's you, I can tell
by the way you fight,
the way you move.
Why'd you set up the ambush?
Marcus, you're a good person,
just put the gun down.
You got Cyrus killed.
I didn't get your
brother killed,
I swear, I didn't set up a hit.
You know something!
That's what you do right?
You know everything!
Man, fuck that pig.
You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Nigga, where you get that at?
It's my moms.
That's good shit Marcus.
Now that we got the eyes
of the streets out the way,
we can put the real
plan into effect.
Get over here.
This right here, is gonna
be our biggest pay day,
I'm talking about millions.
Yes sir.
I was reached by someone
high up in the cartel.
They got a job for
us, a little catch
and release with the
mayors daughter, Danielle.
OG almost got in the way.
He had his ears to the street,
and he was a piece of the puzzle
that needed to be taken out.
Right on Marcus.
A little pay back
for Cyrus and Killah.
Fuck Killah and Cyrus.
Danielle is usually at the
coffee shop, on Geary and Vaness.
She gets there
around eight o'clock
to meet up with her boyfriend.
Her dad doesn't know about it.
But we do.
Right here, gonna have two
soldiers posted up in a van.
Then we get out,
snatch her ass up,
and don't worry
about wearing a mask,
we have all the cameras
down across the block.
From there we take her
little ass over here,
we escort her to this spot
where there is a tunnel
to get her ass out the city,
possibly out of the country.
That looks like,
looks like OG's spot.
Yeah, the cartel wants it.
So they could have access
points throughout the city.
There should be some rope here.
Tie her ass up, and
all you gotta do
is put her down that hole.
Once she hits the
bottom, oh she's gone.
Get the fuck out of here.
And our job is done.
And we'll be some
rich motherfuckers.
Hell yeah.
This is going out
tomorrow night.
Get ready.
You ready for tomorrow?
Hey Masaai, can I talk
to you real quick?
What's on your mind?
I killed a man today.
That was necessary, to put
the family's plan into action.
Plans, What else was
part of the plan?
Cyrus and Killah?
I thought that was your family.
Yeah they were.
It's a dirty game Marcus.
Somebody got to win it.
Pick up that money.
Go make a girl happy.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Look, man, we got to talk.
Still can't believe
that OG set up Cyrus.
He was like a father figure.
I killed him.
I killed a fucking cop.
A dirty cop Marcus.
One that got Cyrus shot.
Are you fucking happy.
What?
Are you fucking happy?
We found out who killed
Cyrus, are you fucking happy?
What the hell are you
talking about Marcus?
I lost my fucking job, sold
my car, joined a goddamn gang!
And I killed a fucking cop!
Are you fucking serious Marcus?
Your job?
I lost my fiance,
my baby's father.
Look at me.
Your brother, your blood Marcus.
You're worried
about your damn job.
I just don't get it.
What the fuck is Cyrus
doing, why the fuck
wass he giving his money to
these God damn criminals?
You really didn't
know your brother.
He wasn't giving his
money to the gangs Marcus.
I wanna show you something.
Cyrus was always talking
about how he wanted
to give back to the kids
who really needed it.
He wanted you to
see this Marcus,
he wanted you to be apart of it.
I never knew.
Hey Kelly, how you doing?
Teisha.
It is good to see you.
It's good to see you to.
This is Marcus.
Oh, hi Marcus, nice
to finally meet you.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Come on in.
Thank you Teisha.
I wanted to bring
Marcus over here
and show him how
much this foundation
has helped these kids lives.
Yeah, this is something
like a foster care,
but our main focus is to keep
brothers and sisters
together on this journey.
A foster home.
There's a lot of families
that fall on hard luck,
and the government,
they try to help but.
Sometimes they take away
the most important thing
that a kid has after
they lost their parents.
They take away their blood.
Thank you for
sharing that with me.
No, thank you.
I didn't know
anything about him.
It's okay Marcus.
No, no, I didn't know anything.
Marcus.
I should have been
there for him.
No, Marcus, Cyrus
was getting paranoid.
Paranoid about what?
I don't know, he
just kept coming home
and saying that he wasn't loyal,
and I don't know, it just kept,
it all caught up with him.
Wait, wait, wait.
Loyal about what though?
I don't know, he
kept saying that
his loyalty was being
questioned by the group.
Marcus?
What's going on.
Look, what I'm gonna tell
you right now is gonna be
very important, so I need
you to listen to me, okay?
Call the police in two hours,
tell them I'll be
at this address,
tell them there's guns, drugs,
and the gang leader
Masaai, okay?
I need your keys.
Kelly please, I need your keys.
Marcus.
Please.
Fine.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna make sure
he stays there.
Marcus Sims.
There's no one in here but us.
So you got
Cyrus killed, huh?
Your brother.
I had a couple of
guys look into you
because they saw you
wearing Cyrus's chain.
A white collar nigga
playing gangster.
Why'd you do it Masaai?
All I have is loyalty.
I found out he was
keeping money from me.
So your own people
ain't even safe, huh?
Like I told you,
the only nigga you need
to worry about is me.
That shit won't work.
You uncle Tom ass nigga.
Oh you want to feel the struggle
Family is nothing
without loyalty!
Fuck you, you're
nothing like us.
You're a pussy, just
like your brother.
They're coming for you.
Just fucking kill me.
Fucking kill me.
Fucking kill me!
You're right Masaai,
I'm nothing like you.
Kill me!
I won't give you
the satisfaction.
Of being with my brother.
No.
911, what's
your emergency?
Yeah, the
mayors daughter,
she's just been kidnapped.
She's been thrown in
the back of a van.
What's
your location sir?
I'm at the corner
of Geary and Vaness,
in front of a coffee shop.
Can you identify who
grabbed the mayors daughter?
No, I don't know
who grabbed her.
What about
a license plate,
did you happen to see that?
I didn't see the, I didn't see
the license plate
number, all right?
Okay sir, I'm gonna
need you to calm down.
But I do have an idea
where's she's going.
How do you know
this information sir?
Just listen!
All right?
Okay, if I can
have you calm down sir,
what's your name?
There's a warehouse
on the docks.
And where is this sir?
Seventh and Green.
And to make sure
this isn't a prank call
and we don't send units out
there, what's your name?
Just show up.
Come on, move.
You don't want to
damage the merchandise.
You're so pretty.
You're going to be very popular.
Get down, get down!
I want to start off
by saying thank
you for everything.
Thank you for letting me see
my brother for
who he really was.
Who he became.
It's a shame that I didn't
see it until he was gone.
I finally understand
what he meant.
I'm not doing this for me.
I felt like I didn't
have any family,
that I was taking
on this world alone.
Even when I was blinded,
Cyrus was there.
I can never give my niece
or nephew their father
but what I can give
them is something
me and Cyrus never
had, a better start.
In the envelope on the table
I signed everything over to you.
I don't know what the
future holds for me.
But I know it
finally feels right.