[ Suspenseful music plays ]
[ Sea gulls crying ]
Electronic voice:
Fuck you. You're an asshole.
Eat shit.
Who is he, frank?
He's Lyle Mason.
What's his rep?
He kills people.
Let me give you
a hand.
Thanks.
So, being that this is
your first date with cass,
I thought maybe you could
use a couple of pointers.
Why do you think
I need pointers?Well, you're a great d.A.
I mean, you're smooth
in the courtroom.
But when it comes to
cass, you gotta throw
out the book, see?
She defies all rules
of conventional dating.
Oh, yeah?
Why's that?
Yeah, why's that?
Simple. You treat her
like a lady, she's gonna
walk right over you.
Treat her like a gu,
and, uh -- huh.
You won't score, man.
[ Laughs ]
You are such a pig!
How should I treat her?
You should treat her
like a person.
Thank you, Rachel.
You've got class.
Always the right answer.
See? This is why
I married her.
Ooh, please!
You guys are making me sick.
McKenna,
we've got more gear.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
He's got company.
Man:
Who's with him?
I don't know.
Mr. Mason.
I've heard a lot about you.
You "dalillo"?
Dallio.
Frank dallio.
W-We talked on the phone.
Whatever.
I left my cigarettes onshore.
Do you have one?
[ Snaps fingers ]
Cigarette.
And, uh, this is?
[ Speaking Russian ]
He's with me.
[ Device beeping ]
What's with this guy, huh?
Hey! Come on, the biz
is out here, all right?
Something's going o.
Mason's talking Russian,
and dallio doesn't seem
too happy about it.
Relax.
Everybody sit tight.
Dallio: Fella, what
are you, fucking deaf?
Come on back out here.
What's your fucking problem?
Get out here!
What the hell is that?
What is this,
my friend?
A bug. They found the bug!
[ Stomping ]
[ Feedback ]Oww! We better move!
Oh, shit!
Go, go, go!We're on the move!
You set me up.Now, wait a minute --
you wait a minute!
Uhh!
Get on the boat now!
Go!I'm moving!
Don't move.Okay, okay.
[ Speaking Russian ]
[ Motor starts ]
Jeffries: All right, return
fire, but keep dallio alive.
Keep dallio alive!
Dallio, drive,
and fast.
Go for the yacht.
Go for the yacht!
Man on radio:
No sign of dallio.
We'll head back
for the speedboat.
Shit!
Take US down there!
[ Gunfire ]
Other side!
Take out the guy
in the stern.
[ Gunshot ]Aah!
We're hit.
Oil pressure's dropping.
Take US down, fast.
Dallio, head towars
the rocks. Straigh!
Man:
Stay with them!
Uhh!
[ Laughs ]
Yes! Fuck you!
Fuck the FBI!
The engine's gonna blow!
Head to shore!
All right!
Get an ambulance! Don't move.
Okay, okay, okay.
Are you guys alone?
Who else is with you guys?
You guys alone?
Answer me!
No.
Yes!
Dallio: All right,
let's go for a walk. Let's go.
Okay, okay. Come on.
You too, beautiful.[ Groans ]
Move!
Let's go.
Get to the truck.
Okay, okay, okay.
Freeze![ Cass, Rachel gasp ]
Drop the gun. Fuck you!
I'm a cop.
Now, drop the gun.
I got
a better idea, cop.
Toss your gun
on the hood,
or I'll blow her
fucking brains out.[ Whimpering ]
I think he's a little
hard of hearing.
Do it now.
Uhh!
Oh! No!
Your move.
Gun on the hood!
[ Rachel panting ]
Come on, asshole!
[ Whimpers ]
Okay.
Good.
Keys.
[ Grunting ]
Cass!
[ Helicopter blades whirring ]
Go get help.
Dallio, get in the car.
Let's go.
Uhh!
Damn it!
God damn it,
let me go!
Just keep her
off of me!
I am!
Stupid bitch,
will you just sit still,
and nothing
will fucking happen?!
Don't move!
[ Wails ]
Oh!damn it!
If you just fucking sit still,
nothing will happen to you!
Sit down!
Fucking sit down!Shut up!
[ Rachel screams ]
Shit!
Rachel!
No!
[ Crying ][ Grunts ]
[ Gunshot ]
Rachel!
That's great, dallio.I told her to sit still!
You idiot!
No!
Don't do it!
Aah!
Hold it!
Uhh!
[ Tires screeching ]
Uhh! Uhh! Uhhh!
Fuck!
[ Grunting ]
God, I want my money!
Aah! Son of a bitch!
Well, Washington's gonna
have my ass for breakfast.
Clamp a lid on this
a.S.A.P.
I don't want the press
climbing all over me, too.
Is this your boss?
Hey! Hey!
Who's in charge?
I'm talking to you!Just wait outside, miss.
I'm a cop, and my friend
is in the emergency room,
and none of your guys
are giving me any answers.
All right, officer.
Look, this is
an FBI operation.
Wait outside, and
agent Hurley here
will help you out.
What's your name?Special agent jeffries.
Now, will you please --
Turner.
Detective Turner.
My partner, Dan McKenna,
is in there, and
I want to see him.
Look, Hurley, will you escort
the officer outside
and give her all the information
she needs, please?
Hey! Hey! Get your hands
off me, all right?
All right,
I got it, I got it.
Woman on P.A.:
Dr. Kravitz, you have
a visitor in the main lobby.
Did the local authoritis
get involved?
No. Two off-duty cops
jumped in.
That's the casualty there.
What's the word, doc?
Not as bad as it looks.
He took a hollow point
to the face,
but the slug must have hit
something first
because it broke up
on the way in.
Fractured jaw,
lacerations --
nothing a little
plastic surgery won't fix.
I'm afraid we're not gonna
get anything out of Mason.
Mason's dead, huh?
Lost him in O.R.
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Elevator bell dings ] You heard
from dallio yet?
Yeah, well, look,
I'm at the hospital.
Let me see if he's here.
Orderly: What do you want US
to do with this guy?
Lyle Mason.
A piece of garbage.
Get him out of here.
Mr. Mason.
Mr. Mason, what happend
to Mr. Dallio?
Who are you?I'm Mr. Dallio's attorney.
He's Dan Porter.
Reps every scumbag in town.
[ Sighs ]
Mr. Mason,
where's Mr. Dallio?
Oh, no, this isn't -- this is none
of your business.
Get out of here.
Simpson, get this guy
out of here right now.
Have you got a lawyer,
Mr. Mason?
He has the right to
a lawyer, you know! Mr. Mason!
If you need my help,
Mr. Mason, you give me a call.
I can be here!
Did you see that?
He thought that
the cop was Mason.
Yeah, he did,
didn't he?
[ Knock on door ]
Detective McKenna?
Uh-huh.
Detective, uh...
Do you remember what
happened yesterday?
Rachel.
Where's Rachel?
I'm sorry...
But, uh...
Your wife is dead.
No.
[ Groans ]
[ Sobs ]
There were two men.
White males.
[ Gunshot echoes ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
He killed Rachel.
Frank dallio --
a punk looking to move up.
There was another guy.
Lyle Mason -- American muscle
for the Russian mafia.
Where is he?
He's dead...
Which is too bad,
really.
[ Sighs ]
This is the situation.
Dallio lucked ino
something big,
something worth a lot of money
to Mason's employers.
They need it bac.
Without Mason as a go-between,
there's no deal.
We've got nothing.
Don't worry.
I'll get dallio.
Perhaps.
But we need more
than dallio's corpse.
Now, I'm gonna
ask you something.
Detective McKenna,
what would you say...
If I asked you to be...
Lyle Mason?
Same height and weigh.
About the same ag.
I've talked to the doctor.
You're going to need
plastic surgery anyway.
Get out of here.
Detective mckenn,
these guys killed your wife
and four federal agents.
No matter how muh
you hate...
Your job comes first.
And right now...
My job and yours...
Is to prevent
that son of a bitch
from screwing
his own country.
I need your help.
People will ask questions.
The department --
knows nothing.
Mason survived,
but you didn't.
That's what I'll tell them.
As far as anybody knows,
you don't exist anymore.
Until this is over,
Dan McKenna is dead.
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
Hey, Turner.
Yeah?
Can I see you?
The FBI denied my request
for liaison.
They want to handle this
on their own. Sorry.
Fucking feds!
Jesus! Fuck!
Hey,
watch your language.
Well -- [ Sighs ]
We're just gonna have
to trust the feds
to bring him in.
The FBI?
With six months' surveillance,
a team of search dogs,
they wouldn't be able
to find their dicks
unless it was tattooed
on their foreheads!
Dan McKenna
was my friend, too.
I want these guys
just as much as you do...
Only my hands are tied.
Yourhands may be tie.
Turner!
Yes?
Don't make me be a hard-ass!
This is a federal case.
It's bureau business.
Now, stay out of it!
All right, I'll go write
some traffic tickets,
get my nails done,
maybe get a facial.
How about getting
my hair done?
Maybe I'll get
my head examined!
Write a few tickets.
[ Machinery beeping ]
[ Elevator bell dings ]
Do you have a patient
named Lyle Mason?
Uh, I can check for you.
Can you wait here
for just a minute, please?
It's healing nicely.
Another four or five week,
and you'll never know
he was here.
Just a little dye job
and some contacts,
and nobody will knw
the difference.
Let me see.
When do I get
my old face back?
As soon as the job is done.
That easy, huh?
The doc here is a geniu.
I'll check in
on you tomorrow.
Thank you, doctor.
Now, we don't hae
much time
to turn you
into Lyle Mason.
We've got a lot
of work to do.
We can make you
look like Mason,
but now you've got
to thilike Mason.
Think like Mason?
Ooh, that's rich.
Look at this guy.
He makes Charles manson
look like the good humor man.
He blew up
a busload of kids.
He was trying to kill the judge.
The kids got in the way.
Now, if you're gonna
be Mason,
the first rule is...
You don't let anybody
get in your way.
You've gotta be ruthless.
I've gotta be
a pathological killer.
Exactly.
Hey, it's me, frank.Jesus.
I brought you
some underwear.
Couldn't find your socks.
You're all right, Tony.
Yeah. So, you got everything
you need now?
What I need is to get
out of this rat hole.
Been holed up here
two weeks.
Every cop in town
is still looking for me
'cause somebody squealed.
You know what?
Take it easy.
Listen, things will calm down,
and we'll get you out of here.
Yeah, and then what?
I get to sit around
till this guy decides
he's gonna squeal on me again?
I'm not gonna spend the rest
of my life hiding out, Tony.
I want you
to find this fucker.
He's gonna pay.
He's gonna pay big-time.
[ Buzzer ]
Lyle Mason.
How'd he take the transfer
to his new digs?
I'm sure he loves it here.
Tr17b integrated circuit,
or microchip.
Star wars
missile technology.
Bertrand moody,
a gs-13 engineer
at beachhead
missile test center.
He had a gambling problem.
He owed frank dallio
40 grand.
One day
on his lunch brea,
he smuggled out
a prototype tr17b..
And never came back.
Guess who ended up
with the prototype?
And now dallio is trying
to sell it to Gregor grazynsk,
who heads up the biggest
organized-crime operation
in Moscow.
From there he'll go
to the highest bidder --
people's republic,
Iran, North Korea.
Who knows?
Where's moody now?
We found him
in a motel on carlsbad.
Throat slashed all the way
through to his spine.
One of dallio's jobs.
I'm gonna get
that son of a bitch.
This is not about reveng,
McKenna.
You lose your cool
with dallio,
and you're a dead man.
We've got Mason's mony
from the wreck.
Do the deal.
Get the microchip...
And we'll take care
of dallio.
Open up.[ Buzzer ]
Thanks.
Yep.
[ Buzzer ]
[ Muffled grunting ]
[ Grunting continues ]
Get out of the way!
[ Gunshots ]
[ Gunshot ]
Open the door, asshole!
Sorry, man.
Mason, come on!
Now!
[ Tires screech ]
[ Gunshots ]
Jeffries: What the hell
were you doing helping
that old guy up?
Lyle Mason wouldn't have
stopped for his own mother.
You could have blown
the whole operation.
All right, all right.
So now what?
You've gotta find dallio.
What would Lyle Mason do?
I don't know.
Bust some heads?
[ Sighs ]
[ Faucet running ]
[ Hip-hop music plays ]
[ Echoing ]
♪ looking up from the street
♪ your heart is skipping
a beat ♪
♪ you got your beat on
♪ looking up from the street
♪ keeping it down
with the beat ♪
♪ looking up
♪ Your heart is skipping
a beat ♪
♪ you got your beat on
♪ going down on the street
♪ yo, keeping it down
till you're beaten up ♪
♪ yo
[ jazz music plays ]
Hiya, handsome.
Hi.
You alone tonight?
I'm looking for frank.
Frank who?
Frank dallio.
Don't ring a bel.
Really?
You think you'd know the guy
who pays your salary.
Never met the guy
who owns this place
and never heard of
this guy.
Where do you think
you're going?
Hey, fatso, I think
this gentleman needs an escor.
Would you get him
out of here?
I'll take care of him
for you, jojo.
You got a problem, pal?
As a matter of fact,
I do.
See, a friend of mine and I
were involved with the law.
And, uh, well...
I'm looking for him.
His name is frank dallio.
You better get out of here
while you can still walk.
Not before I see frank.
Wrong answer.
Oh, you fuck!
[ Screaming ]
You son of a bitch!
I'll kill you!
You asshole! Aah!
[ Screaming continues ]
Oh, you're a fucking tough guy,
are you?
Tell dallio
where I'm staying.
[ Groans ]
Hey, Tony. Why don't you Ty
some of this chicken?
No, thanks.
Listen, we just --
no, seriously, it's
very good chicken.
You should have some.
I ain't hungry.
This is important.Will you have a piece
of fucking chicken?
[ Laughing ]
I got regular and extra chewy.
That's the extra chewy.
That's good, frank.
Listen, fatso just called
from the club.
A guy calling himself Lyle Mason
busted the place up.
Said you could find him
over at the sleepytime.
That's impossible.
Cops got Mason.
Claimed he escaped.
I mean, maybe we should
meet him, you know.
I don't like it.
I mean, it sounds like
a fucking setup.
Could be a cop.
What if the guy's
still alive, you know?
Maybe he does want to deal.
There's a lot of money
at stake here.
All right.
You check out his story.
If it sounds phony at all,
you waste him.
Yeah.
I'll beat him to death.
[ Both laugh ]
Ah, nice bananas.
You find out
where dallio is?
Not yet.
What happened?
[ Sighs ]
Well, I made some noise.
I let his people know
where they could find me.
And?
And nobody showed up.
[ Sniffing ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Pills clinking
in bottle ]Still hurts?
So, you got any ideas?
Yeah, go back to
the motel and wait.
See if anybody
shows up.
[ Sighs ]
Man, I don't have
the Patience for that.
Where you going?
I'm sure we'll
be in touch.
Frank.
Frank!
I'm starting to get
the hang of this, you know?
Thinking of calling
this one "going nuts."
What do you think?
Yeah, it's nice, frank.
So, what did you find out
at the hospital?
Well, it checks out.
Yeah, he, uh, he jumped
this food-service guy
and ran down the back stairs.
Guy's slick, huh?
Yeah, he's slick.
Aw, come on, frank.
Let's make the deal.
That's the idea, right?
I don't trust the guy.
Somebody tipped the cops,
right?
What,
you think it was him?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe he did, and
maybe he didn't.
But until I find out who did,
I'm gonna be slightly
paranoid, aren't I?
Yeah.
We're gonna deal
with Mason...
After you find me who the fuck
tipped off the cops.
And when you do...
[ Metal clatters ]
Right?
[ Needle buzzing ]
Something I can
do for you, friend?
Yeah. I'm looking
for a friend of mine
who might know
some of your friends.
This friend of yours --
he got a name?
Mm-hmm.
Frank dallio.
Maybe you better leave...
Friend.
Whoa, take it easy.
I don't want any trouble.
[ Bones cracking ]
[ Needle buzzing ] All right!
All right!
I know dallio!
But I don't know
where he is!
You got me all worked up!
I'm about to lose control!
[ Groaning ]
Ooh!
Ah! I swear!
I don't know where he is!
I'm losing my Patience.
Aah! Aah!
[ Buzzing stops ]A cousin!
He's got a cousin Ralph.
Ralph dallio!
I bet he knows!
[ Sighs ]
Thought you were
supposed to be working
on the bunco case.
[ Sighs ] I thought you were
giving up caffeine.
Turner...
I'm willing to cut you
some slack,
because I know
what you're going through.
You start sticking
your nose into where
it doesn't belong,
and you're gonna get US
all in trouble.
Now, stay out
of the dallio cas,
or I'll assign you
to traffic duty,
double shift.
Do you read me?
Yeah.
It's like talking
to a brick wall.
Della!
I'm home.
[ Muffled grunting ]
Della!
[ Speaking Italian ]
Hey, ralphie!
Who the fuck are you, huh?
I want to locate
your cousin.
Who?
Frank dallio!
Never heard of him!
Really?
Yeah.
Look what I found,
ralphie.
That's you...
And that's your
cousin frank, right?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Let's try this again.Come on!
Do you know the whereabouts
of your cousin frank?
You got a problem?
Huh, officer?
You think I'm a cop?
Yeah!
You talk like a cop.
You even smell
like a fucking cop!
What does a cop
smell like?
Shit!
You gonna read me my rights?
Huh, cop?
I got friends
in the department, man!
They're gonna
fix your ass!
You better pray
your cop friends
show up, ralphie boy!
You got no right
to remain silent!
You know who I am?
You got no right
to an attorney!
I got rights!
Bullshit!
[ Grunting continues ]
As a matter of fact,
you don't have any
fucking rights at all!
And where's frank?I don't know!
Guess!
Fuck you!
Are you okay?
The back!
The fucking back!
[ Dog barking in distance ]
[ Horn honks ]
[ Tires screeching ]
Cass.
[ Engine stops ]
Spare some change,
mister?
You guys were supposed
to keep cass off my back.
She almost put a bullet
through your expensive
plastic surgery.
Yeah, we'll take care of it.
Where you been?
Out looking for dallio.
Well, why don't you just
stay here and leave
the legwork to US?
[ Sighs ] You all don't exactly
inspire confidence.
You got a better idea?
Hey, you got
another quarter?
They got good & plentys
in the vending machine here.
[ Knock on door ]
What do you want?
Mickelson --
oh, I've been so worried.
Let me see your face.
Does it hurt?
Um...
What's wrong?
Why didn't you come for me?
I, uh --
hey, it was too dangerous.
[ Scoffs ] You know
I don't care about that.
Uh, how'd you find me?
Are you kidding?
[ Chuckles ]
Every two-bit punk in town
knows where you are.
You've, uh, been busting
a lot of heads.
What's the matter with you?
You're acting like
you don't even know me.
I'm just not myself.
Oh, poor baby.
Well...
I think I know
what you need.
Maybe this isn't
the right time.
Relax.
Oh...
Leave everything
to me.
[ Water running ]
[ Telephone ringing ]
Hello?
Yeah. Hi, stace.
No, it was
a purple pickup.
Yeah, just let me know
what the guys downtown find...
In the lab.
Okay.
How's Phil?
Yeah, just tell him
I said hi.
[ Water running ]
[ Silenced gunshots ]
Aah!
[ Growling ]
[ Breathing unsteadily ]
So...you feeling more
like yourself, honey?
Yeah,
it was terrific, baby.
Who the hell are you?
What do you mean?
Where's Lyle?
Lyle's dead.
So are you.
Why don't you go back
to where you came from?
Maybe you should go to hell.
[ Clicks ]
Sorry.
[ Vehicles pass in distance ]
[ Muffled screaming ]
Let's go!
What do you want?
Mr. Dallio requests
the pleasure of your company.
All right.
Hold on a second.
Now.
Listen,
I'll get my jacket.
[ Muffled screaming continues ]
Hey! Hey!
Knock it off in there!
I'll bust through
the wall and kick your ass!
Tired of this shit.
Where we going?
Out.
After you.
All right. Let's go.
Well, I had my doubt,
but here you are,
big as life.
No thanks to you.
You sound different.
Try sitting
in a hospital room
with a tube shoved
down your throat,
and see how you sound.
Yeah.
So, we still got a deal?
That depends.
You got a bad safety record
with me.
Yeah,
about our little problem.
Wake up,
you lousy sack of shit!
That the guy
that ratted you out?
No, he ratted usout.
That's why I wanted you here
to take care of him.
Me?
Well, he's the reason you were
in the hospital, right?
I mean,
I figured I owe you.
How do we know
this is the guy?
Maybe we ought to ask him
a few questions.
Why?
To find out who he knows.
We know.
Look,
is there something wrong?
I figured Lyle Mason
would jump at the chance
to smoke the guy that
put him in the hospital.
You got a problem?
Maybe I want to know
a little bit more about a guy
before I blow his brains out!
Now, why'd he rat on US?
I don't know.
I guess 'cause
he hates my guts.
Is that it?
Ice him down.
[ Clicking, whirring ]
[ Sobbing ]
I want you
to tell the man
why my cousin would tun
on his own fuckig
flesh and blood!
Shut the fuck up!I didn't --
I didn't fucking squeal!
Tony saw him talking
to that cop bitch.
What cop?
This afternoon.
Ralphie here -- he's sitting
in his kitchen
talking to that broad
from the beach.
Turns out she's a cop.
But we're taking care
of that, too, aren't we?
Consider it done.
But what concerns e
right now
is this piece of shit
over here.
Now...you want to do
the honors or not?
[ Chuckles ]
You're cold, man.
You're gonna
blow your cousin away
'cause you caught him
talking to a cop?
No, not just a cop.
Everybody -- FBI, d.E.A.
You'd talk to fucking
anything with a badge
on, wouldn't you?
Hey, Frankie --wouldn't you, ralphie?!
Don't, Frankie!
Fuck you!
I want you to kill him!
Do him.
[ Sobbing ]
You!
You're that fucking c--
Next!
[ Indistinct talking
on police radio ]
Gate's open. Why don't you
have a look, and, uh,
I'll check out
the parking lot.
The cops are outside!
All right.
Let's move.
You keep an eye
on Mason.
I gotcha.
All right.
Stay with him.
[ Siren wailing ]
Hands in the air.
What are you guys
doing here?
We're just taking a walk,
officer.
Turn around and
put your hands on the wall.
What, did we do something
wrong, Mr. Officer?
Keep your hands
where I can see 'em!
[ Gunshots ]
[ Groaning ]
Hang in there, man.
Hang in there!
This is squad 53-09.
Shots fired. Officer down.
All units in the vicinity
of the Glen cove fishery,
please respond. Over.
Man: Squad 53-09,
please identify yourself.
Squad 53-09,
come in, please.
Aah!
[ Rapid gunfire ]
Bitch.
[ Groaning ]
Nice shot.
Dallio:
You got the other co.
I guess I owe you one.
[ Clicks ]
[ Clicking ]
Hey, where's Benny?
Where's Benny,
for Christ's sake?
Ah, frank, come on.
We gotta get out of here.
Come on.
Did you see that guy?
He was gonna shoot me. You're crazy.
Victor, did you see him?
He was gonna kill me.
I don't know, boss.He saved your life,
Frankie.
Fuck that.
The guy is crazy.
Yeah, so,
what do you want to do?I want to get the money,
and I want to get out
of town.
What do you want to
do with the guy?
Get the guy fucking laid.
He could use it!
[ Telephone rings ]
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Maestro,
a little traveling music.
[ Slow instrumental music
plays ]
Boys...
We're going downtown.
Pick US up
a little entertainment.
Hey, yeah!
What are we doing?
Mr. Dallio wants
to show his appreciation.
We got business.
Mr. Dallio insists
you have a good time.
[ Clicking ]
Steady.[ Clicks ]
No ammo, no booze,
no broads.
Gentlemen,
this man needs our help.
Bad-hair day, Turner?
Fuck you.[ Laughs ]
Hey, Turner.What?
What's going on? What's going on?
I'll tell you what's going on.
One of dallio's men
just tried to kill me.
What?
In my apartment!
The coroners
are there right now.
[ Sighs ]
Okay, Turner.
You win.
What?
You want to go after dallio,
go ahead. I'll back you up.
You'll back me up?
You're gonna stick
your neck out for me?
Let's just say I don't like
people telling me
how to do my job,
either.
Thanks, captain.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, Turner.
What?
You know your hair is -- don't talk about
my hair!
[ Muttering ]
All right with me.
Sorry!
[ Rock music playing ][ Laughter ]
Why do I get the feeling you
guys are jerking me off here?
Relax. Mr. Dallio says have
a good time...Or else!
[ Laughing ]You hear that?
Go on, loosen him up
a little, baby.
What's that for,
your face?
Does your face hurt?
It's killing me!
[ Laughing ]
[ Laughter ]
You know, chemical pollutants
like that are simply a plot
by the big
medical-industrial complex.
Shut up.
Chinese herbs.
That's what you need.
Organic, holistic,
completely "biosympathetic."
You should check it out.
Shut the fuck up.
[ Rock music plays ]
[ Woman giggling ]Joey.
Yeah?
Go in there.
Get me some smokes. I'm going in.
No, you stay. Joey,
get him whatever he wants.
I'm going myself.
Keep an eye on this guy.
This is a bad neighborhood.
Ooh, you're pretty.
Hey.
How'd you like to party
with me and my friends?
Hey, fuck off!
Back off, scumbag.
I'm talking to the bitch.
What? You want to
fucking die?
What are you doing?
I bet she could make me see
stars in the back of that car.
Oh, you're
fucking dead, ma!
Chill out.
I'm having
a little fun with her.
Now back the fuck off.
Go on.
What are you, deaf?
Take off, all of you.
Get the fuck out
of here! Go on!
That's right. Good!
What the fuck
you looking at?
I'm coming back for you, man. Get in the fucking car
and go!
Come on, man.
Come on.
Are you out of
your fucking mind?
You don't even have
any fucking bullets.
No bullets...
When you got balls.
[ Door squeaks ]
Maybe you wouldn't be
so angry all the time
if you didn't put all those
chemicals in your body.
Look at all this
junk food, man.
Arterial stuffer-uppers.
Look at this.
[ Vehicle approaches ]
[ Tires screech ]
Look out!
[ Gunfire continues ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Groans ]
Ohh!
Ooh.
Ginseng. Cool.
[ Groans ]
Look at this fucking
goddamn mess.
You could have --
you almost got you killed.
You almost got me
fucking killed.
Shut up. You got her killed.
Hey, will you
shut the fuck up?
You're fucking lucky
I didn't shoot you in there.
Woman: All units in the
vicinity of third and gayley,
shots fired,
possible gang activity.
Suspect vehicle is
a light-blue 1978 sedan.
This is unit 92.
I'm in the area.
I'll keep an eye open.
[ Siren wailing ]
I see them.
I'm in pursuit.
Oh, fuck.
Cops, man. Cops!
Come on, step on it!
Fucking gaining.
[ Tires screech ]
[ Grunts ]
Hang on.
Fuck!
Pull over!
Give me
a fucking break, cass.
Pull over!
Okay,
hold it steady, man.
Aah!
Why you stopping?
Hey, hey, hey!
Excuse me, what the fuck
are you doing?
Let's get the fuck ot
of here!
[ Banging on car]
Come on!
You're nuts!
You're fucking crazy!
You're a wild man, man!
I love it.
I love this.
We gotta ditch the car.
Christ!
Fuck! Oh, look at
this shit.
We're in totally deep
fucking shit.
Nice driving,
you psycho fuck!
Look at this fucking shit!
Fucking great.
What the fuck are we gonna
do now, hotshot?
Shut up! Come here.
Come here!Fuck.
Give me a hand
with her. Grab her leg.
[ Grunting ]
Blood all over my fucking suit.
That's beautiful.[ Telephone ringing ]
Answer it.
Oh, fuck.
What am I gonna say?
Mr. Dallio's gonna shit
a fucking brick. What do I say?
Just answer the phone.
What the fuck
am I gonna say?
Ahh, fuck.
Huh!
[ Grunts ]
[ Screams ]
[ Grunting ]
Where's dallio hiding?
Aah! Fuck!
Get me down from here,
you stupid fuck!
Okay.
[ Screams ]
Okay, okay, okay!
[ Stammering ]
Where's dallio hiding? I don't know.
Look -- I don't know.
Look, look, I don't know.
I don't know. Tony knows.
Tony's the only one who knows.
Tony knows?
Tony knows.
Call him.
I-I can't call him.
I can't call him.
Dallio's paranoid.
I can't call.
I don't know the number.
Fucking paranoid ever since
he killed the fucking
cop's bitch wife.
Now, just fucking
get me down.
You want down?
Yeah, get me fucking --
what are you, deaf?
Get me fucking down!
You're down!
[ Screams ]
What's going on?
There are bodies
all over the place.
Looks like somebody
declared war on dallio.
Do you hear me?
Who's in my grave?
In your grave?
Mason.
Dig him up.
I don't want him
in there with Rachel.
When it's all over.Now!
I can't do it now.
Mason's girlfriend
showed up.
Did she come on to you?
What do you think?
Of course she came on to me.
We'll take care of it.
Like you took care
of dallio?
Or cass?
Like you took care
of my wife?
[ Sighs ]
Fuck you, jeffries.
You don't give a shit
about anything
except your fucking chip.
[ Scoffs ]
I killed a cop.
I'm turning into him,
you know.
I want out.
Look, McKenna...
You're a cop.
You know what
it's like undercover.
Sometimes it's hard to
remember whose side you're on.
But this...
Is a matter
of national security.
You're on the right side.
Get me that chip,
and I promise you
we'll make dallio pay.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
Aren't you going
to answer it?
Yeah.
Jesus, where the fuck
have you been?
Out.
Who's this?
Who do you think?
Mason, put Joey
on the phone.
Well,
Joey didn't make it.
What do you mean,
he didn't make it?
He's dead.
Joey's dead.
Oh, shit!
What the fuck happened?
Look, p-put one
of the other guys on.
They're all dead.Wait a minute!
You're telling me
all my fucking guys are dead
and walked away?
You're the only fucking
guy that walked away?
Is that what you're
fucking telling me?
Hey, I got shot at, too.
I'm sorry you missed I,
okay?
Now, I'm tired of this
horseshit. We got
a deal or not?
I don't know.
Send somebody to find out
what the fuck happened.
And have them
check out Mason's place.
I don't trust this
motherfucker.
Go ahead.
Crescent and redwood.
You be there in an hour.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
He wants to deal.
You got 3 million bucks?
Mason's money
from the car wreck.
[ Sighs ]
This is the car
that ran me off the road.
Get the lab boys down here.
We want prints,
blood samples, ballistics.
Did somebody call
the coroner?He's on his way.
Registration?
Stolen plates.
Anything else?
Got spent cartridges,
looks like 9mm.
Cigarette butts...
Tony Bennett tape.What's this?
For a cellphone.
That's the battery charge.
Looks like we're gonna get
to reach out and touch someone.
[ Television static ]
[ Static stops ]
[ Muffled cries ]
Wow.
Hot and cold
running babes, huh?
[ Muffled]
Get me out of here!
Get me out of this!
That son of a bitch!
I'm gonna kill him!
Mason?
He's not Mason.
What the hell are
you talking about?
I screwed Lyle Mason,
and I screwed that guy.
Believe me,
I can tell the difference.
So, where's Lyle Mason?
Jeffries:
What's keeping him?
[ Muffled ] Maybe dallios
got cold feet.
Do you ever stop eating?
It's my metabolism.
[ Muttering ]
Metabolism...
[ Ringing ]
[ Telephone ringing ]
Yeah?
I was beginning to wonder
if you were gonna answer.
I was expecting
your cellular.
Yeah, well, I don't trust al
that new technology bullshi.
Too many big ears listening.
You got the money?
Yeah, I got the money.
Good.
Nobody followed you?
No, nobody.
Pier 34.
You be there in two hours
or the deal's off.
Okay, let's move 'em out.
All units, chameleon
is on the move.
[ Sighs ]
It's a damn parade.
This is unit 92.
Do we have
that phone tap yet? Woman: Affirmative.
The next time this guy
uses his cellular, we got him.
All right. Let me know
when you hear something.
Where's he going now?
[ Beeping ]
Go around. Hurry.
Jeffries: Wait, wait, wai.
He's stopping.
Pull over
for a minute.
He took off
with the money.
All units,
chameleon is loose.
Chameleon is loose.
You Louie?
You got something
for me?
The bus station,
locker number 405.
It's got everything
you ordered. Enjoy.
This is unit 92.
Do we have anything yet? Negative.
Fuck.
[ Sighs ]
Patch me through
to jeffries.
Just tell him
Lyle Mason's on the line.
Unit 92, we've got
a trace on him.Excellent.
[ Cellphone rings ]
Yeah?
Put a trace on it.
What the hell are
you trying to pull?
Look, I want you
to promise me something.
I don't want that
son of a bitch in my grave.
Just tell US
where dallio is..
And we'll put him away
and bring you in with
no consequences.
Just promise me.
But -- but -- just promise me.
That's all. Man: Bus to Tacoma
now loading at gate 24.
Woman: We lost him, but hes
downtown, south of third.
There's an announcement
in the background
that sounds like
the airport.
Downtown?
It's the bus terminal.
I'm on my way.
I'm two blocks away. Hang on.
Found him.
There he goes.
Just leaving.
Twitch...
And I'll blow your brains
all over the wall.
[ Clatters ]
Where's frank dallio?
I don't know.
You got three seconds
to answer me...
Or I rearrange
your face.
What are you laughing at?
Rearrange my face.
That's pretty funny, cass.
How do you
know my name?
Because i'm
your partner.
My partner's dead,
asshole.
It's me.
What are you
talking about?
All right.
You don't take anything
in your coffee.
Your favorite baseball team's
the Cleveland Indians.
You keep the spare keys
to your house in your
top dresser drawer
underneath your
autograph-signed
picture of trini Lopez.
What happened
to your face?
They did plastic surgery.
It's me.
McKenna?yeah.
Jesus.
[ Exhales sharply ]
God...
Jesus, I missed you.
This is so weird.
I would have called you,
but they said not to talk
to anybody in the department.
They? The FBI?
Yeah.
Jeffries.
Well, what are you doing?
I mean, let's go.
We got a lot
of work to do.No, no.
This is my gig.
You stay out of it.
But I'm your partner.No!
No.
I stopped being a cop
when they turned me
into Mason.
[ Pills clinking in bottle ]
I killed a lot
of people, cass.
Anybody that got
in my way.
And I'll kill you, too.
What are those pills?
What are these?
I'm on the other side now.
I can't go back.
No, man.
Just give me that --no!
Ohh!
Uhh!
Stay out of it, cass.
Okay, okay.
Oh, god.
I got you now.
Dallio!
Don't fuck around!
Hold it right there.
Put the briefcase down.
Expecting trouble?
Seattle's a rough town.
Not before I see
the item.
Far enough.
Frank!
Well, if it isn't
the lucky Lyle Mason.
You got the chip?
Electronic voice:
Fuck you.
[ Laughs ]
That the money?
Let's do it.[ Snap ]
Let's. Hold it!
Look what I found.
Hey!
My little playmate
from the beach.
You remember me?[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
I remember you.
We're gonna play
some more.
But first I gotta take care
of some business over here.
Ohh!
Okay?
Man: Mr. Dallio!
That's not Lyle Mason.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Lyle Mason's dead.
Who's this?
This is Lyle Mason's
girlfriend.
What?
[ Chuckles ]
Is this some kind of joke?
This guy ain't Lyle.
When he found out I knew,
he tied me up
in the bathroom.
You son of a bitch.Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I told you this guy
was a phony.
What are you, a cop?
No, I'm the tooth fairy.
Yeah, well,
chew on this.
Shoot.
Very nice, Frankie.
All right, give me
the goddamn briefcase.
Now!
That's a lot of money.
I wouldn't want you to lose it.
Very funny, asshole.
Give me the key.
There is no key.
Tony, get the key.
Don't fuck around.
Just give me the key.
[ Beeping ]
It's a fucking bomb! Oh, shit!
Ohh!
I can't get it off.
I gotta get a --
no, you stay here!No, no, no!
Help me get this off! No, I don't want --
let me go, you goddamn
fucking asshole!
Shoot it off!
No!
[ Gunshot ]
Yeah, motherfucke,
you're not on it!
[ Both scream ]
[ Gasping ]
Oh, my god.
You blew up $3 million?
My boss is gonna have
a hard time explaining
this at headquarters.
Your boss is an asshole.
Well, detective,
you'll be pleased to know
there's no trace of dallio,
his men, or the microchip.
Am I still gonna get
my face back?
You just blew
a national security operation.
I don't think Washington's
gonna spring for one
goddamn cent.
Jeffries...
We had a deal.
Write your congressman.
[ Laughing ]
[ Laughing continues ]
Let's get out of here.
Yeah.
Did you really blow up
3 million bucks?
Not exactly.
There's a couple
of dead cops
whose families
could really use some help.
I'm starting to get used
to this face, McKenna.
Electronic voice:
Fucking jerk.
McKenna:
Look what I found. Turner: What is it?
I don't know.
Maybe a good luck char?
Might even help me
get my old face bac.
I like this new face.
It just needs
to smile more.