[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
I got a Cessna down
on the 405.
Barry,
you better get on it.
Anything I can do from here?
Yeah. You can show this to Ed
and make some coffee.
Thank you.
ANNOUNCER: Lowery, pulls up for
a three. That's no good.
[CHUCKLES]
Ed Arnold, you're not
even watching Chanel 5.
Loyola Marymount's
playing Portland. I love
this Gathers kid.
What Gathers kid?
ED: The one that can fly.
ANNOUNCER: ...out the back
running down
the left side line.
Alley-oop to Gathers.
NBA Play. Unbelievable!
Straight pass by Terrell Lowery
who's on the left side
and asked for it.
Threw it up, perfect pass,
Hank caught it, jammed it
right though...
ED: Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
ANNOUNCER: Hank Gathers on
the floor, collapsed.
He was standing right beyond
half-court and all of a sudden
he just fell down.
Trainers are all on the court.
Hank's mother is rushed on
the court.
Lisa, find out where
they've taken him.
I'll send Tommy
and the crew.
You get down there
and help.
Lawson, I don't know
a thing about basketball.
This isn't about
basketball.
[SIREN WAILING]
ANNOUNCER OVER PA:
Dr. Walker to Radiology.
There isn't any word yet,
so get us some coffee,
this could be a long night.
Oh, I don't think
you're allowed to smoke
those in here.
Hey, didn't this happen
sometime before?
You're thinking
of Len Bias.
He OD'ed on coke
the night the ha was
drafted by the Celtics.
So you think this guy
was into drugs too?
Drugs? Why drugs?
'Cause he'a black, right?
Okay, man. Take it easy.
Take it easy.
Look, I didn't mean
any harm.
Just leave us alone.
All right?
Sorry, Bo.
That young man is
Bo Kimble.
He grew up with Gathers.
They played on the same
team on high school.
I would liked to have
interviewed him.
Nice work.
Sorry.
Bank shouldn't have
been out there.
I should've just flat refused
to play with him.
Stop it, man. You know nobody
could keep Hank from playing.
I remember lots of times
Hank would have been
better staying off the court...
[PEOPLE LAUGHING]
BOY: I dare you to drive.
Here, Hank.
Yo, man, Hank.
You all right?
You see how I
picked his pocket?
Come on, man,
let's quit.
Scott Hardly, you give up?
They're killing us.
Come on. Let's play.
Hank, you better come home.
Derrick, watch this.
I'll give these guys a facial.
Big Loo, is looking for you.
and she is not happy.
Nice try, guys.
Better luck next time.
Didn't you see the way me
and Heat were handling
those "Dudes".
Hank, they were creaming
you guys.
And we showed them
a thing or two.
Yeah, like how to get
your butt kicked.
Anyway, you were supposed to
be home to help mama Moo.
She's gonna gawp on you, Hank.
Big Loo? Oh, hardly.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
I figure another four inches,
and I'll be able to palm.
What if you're all
through growing, Hank?
What if you're some kind
of freak of nature,
and you're the fattest kid
ever to stop growing at 11?
Then you'll never be
able to palm the ball.
I ain't through growing.
And what do you mean,
I ain't gonna be able
to palm the ball?
You never know.
I'm gonna grow.
And that's all
there is to it.
MAMA: So, how's everybody
doing in here?
Hank?
Did you finish
all your homework?
You check.
Honey, you think
I don't believe you?
Give it here.
Let me see.
Let me see this.
Mm-hm.
Oh. [SIGHS]
Oh!
You know, I've prayed
long and hard for this.
For Hank to do his homework?
Oh, hush, dearie.
No.
No, for a nice clean home,
where my kids wouldn't have
to worry about drug dealers
and thugs hanging around them
all the time.
Mama, we just moved
down the street.
It's not like we living
with the rich folks.
Okay. So, we have a little
ways to go.
We'll get there.
Yeah. As soon as I sign
with the Sixers
I'll buy the biggest house
there is.
Oh, Hank, you make me happy
enough if you just keep up
with your school work, okay?
But in the mean time,
when ya'll look out that window,
ya'll will see a tree.
[BOTH LAUGH]
What tree?
It's a great tree, mom.
Can make the all star team
for trees.
Thank you, Hank.
Good night, mama.
Good night.
Good night, boy.
Okay, now you go to bed.
Derrick, I'm telling you,
you wouldn't be able
to show these guys
how to play.
All right.
No question.
You want me,
got it?
Champion of the world,
and all of North Philly.
I'm telling you, man...
I'm the doctor,
and this is
my house-call.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
Right over here.
All right, welcome to
try-outs, gentlemen.
Some of you may know,
my name is Father Dave.
Now if you came here to play,
you came to the wrong place.
We don't play anything here.
That's what playgrounds are for.
This gym is for guys
who are willing to work,
and becoming a team.
Now, line up on the base line.
All I want each of you to do is
dribble the ball out to the foul
line and dribble it back.
That's all I want you to do.
Let's go.
Yo, Father,
watch this.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Give me quiet
or give me laps.
Pass it here.
But...
I've seen enough.
Just let me try it again.
What is your name, son?
Hank. Hank Gathers.
Okay, give me the ball,
go over there.
Next.
Specs.
I got them.
Man, you know
I do.
Hank, all he wanted
us to do was dribble
up and back.
So what's the big deal?
You seem to be
the only one who
messed it up.
Hey, man, I'm sure
I'm gonna be cut.
Me too.
Hey, Specs,
you know, somebody's got to
ride the pipe
or the starters get tired.
I don't remember Father Dave
mentioning a starting team.
Figure it out, D,
it's gotta be you,
Raymond, Lorenzo,
me ans Douglas.
Starting Derrick and Douglas
up front,
Lorenzo and Raymond at
the guards,
and, Mike, you're at pivot.
Ready...
ALL: Break!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
All right, you guys,
now don't bankrupt me.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Are we feeling sorry
for ourselves?
I'm better than most of them.
No, you're not, Gathers,
you're just bigger.
I could take them all
one-on-one.
I, I got the moves,
Father Dave,
you know I do.
What I know is you got
a couple of playground tricks.
I don't play that game.
In fact, you haven't shown me
anything except you got
a big mouth and a bad attitude.
All flash and no cash.
All start and no finish.
Don't you come moaning to me
about game time as long as you
gonna play that way.
[SIGHS]
I don't see why I have to go
to some stupid Catholic school
anyway?
I hate it and
I hate Father Dave.
Hank,
I paid to see you
to St. Elizabeth's
because it's the best chance
you have of making something
of yourself.
Hank, you listen to me.
Now, if I didn't think
you had it in you to do
all sorts of wonderful things,
I wouldn't even bother.
But I'm telling you, baby,
you're special.
You can do anything
in this world you want
to do.
Tell that to Father Dave.
No, you tell him.
Yeah, right.
Not in words, baby,
you show him.
You prove him wrong.
You show him that you are
as good as you think you are.
You show the man that
he's a fool for not playing
you in those games.
But you show him, baby.
Don't you tell him.
You show him, okay?
All right.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
That was a great game.
I did all the work.
Get off me,
little punk.
Punk?
I'm gonna show
these guys how
to play.
Yes! Yes!
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
Ah, yeah. Ah, yeah.
Ah, yeah.
All my free throws,
you know.
[ALL CHANTING] City champ!
City champ! City champ!
Okay, okay, okay.
Not yet, you're not.
I know you've worked very hard
but that's a tough team
down there.
Father Dave, we're gonna
drop them guys like
a bad trans...
All right.
Now, I'll feel very proud of you
as long as you play hard,
and play like a team.
Right? Having said that...
City what?
ALL: City Champ!
Get them!
All right.
FATHER DAVE: I don't care
that you lost,
it's how you lost
that kills me.
You played selfish,
and you played stupid.
You didn't look like
a team out there,
you looked like a street gang.
Everything we talked about,
everything that we worked on
went right out the window.
Now, go on. Go on
and get dressed.
Go on.
You talked hard
to those kids.
Yes, ma'am, I did.
You know, when I first heard
about you,
I was a little suspicious
about what this white man
was doing living up here.
Sometimes I wonder
myself.
You get thrown out of
some place else?
No, ma'am, I just left.
Oh. And where might that be?
Immaculate Heart.
[CHUCKLES]
You left there,
to come here?
But then, honey, you must be
the stupidest white man
I ever seen.
Here, honey,
Lucille Gathers.
Mrs. Gathers, I'm very happy
to meet you.
Those are both fine boys
that you have there.
They're like night and day.
You know with Derrick,
you always know
where you stand
'cause he's steady.
But Hank,
he's always trying to run
before he can walk.
He's got s lot of
good energy.
Hm. Tell me about it.
What we have to make sure of
is that he learns
how to use it.
[SIREN WAILING]
What do you want?
I wanted to say
I was sorry.
You said that already.
Look, I said
something stupid.
Yeah.
You know,
I was standing over there
listening to you talk about
this guy I never met,
and I was thinking
that there were probably
a whole lot more people
who were thinking
the same stupid thing I did.
So?
Look,
I'm an intern at Chanel 5.
Me and Hank did that too.
I know.
Ed Arnold's real broken up.
He's a good man.
Bank and I had some
good times with him.
Bank?
Hank.
Hank the Bank.
Give it to Hank,
it's in the bank.
[GRUNTS]
Were you two
always best friends?
Not hardly.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
That's Bo Kimble.
He's the one that knocked
Bobby out in the summer league.
We got winners.
That's right.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Thinks he's pretty nice,
don't he?
Hey, Hank, I think
he's pretty nice.
I mean, the boy
can flat play.
Let's go in, Derrick.
We got winners.
We called it.
Hey, player.
Can't wait all day,
right?
Come on.
Championship of the world
and all North Philly.
[CHUCKLES] Take it out.
Winners ball.
Winners out.
Okay.
Winners ball,
winner's out.
All right, this time.
Come one.
[SNAPS FINGER]
Let's go.
That's one.
[MOCKINGLY] That's one.
Only when you don't get,
brother. Come on.
Derrick.
One for us.
[GRUNTS]
You all right?
Play.
All right.
Twenty one.
Let's play one more.
That's okay.
Oh, come on.
Let's play
one more, man.
No thanks, guys.
What's the matter?
You scared?
We just took you guys
out, 21-4.
We was just warming up,
man. One more, come on.
Wait...
[SIGHS] [CHUCKLES]
All right,
be like that.
Chump.
No, no. It ain't
about that.
Oh, yeah. I've seen him.
He's a natural.
He's the kind of kid that
looks like he was born with
a basketball on his hand.
He ain't that good.
[LAUGHS] I'm sorry, Hank.
You're just not on that
league yet.
Bo Kimble is a serious
basketball player.
Oh, come on, Father.
Do you know how hard
I practice?
This isn't play of lot of hoops.
There's a big difference.
You know, Father,
it is a good thing
you're my friend and all.
'Cause anybody talk to me
like that who I don't like,
I'd go off on them.
Hey, Hank. Philly -75,
Celtics -62.
Third court.
All right.
Hey.
My, boy.
Ssh.
How're you doing
at school, Hank?
Dave, would you
lighten up?
You mother tells me
that you're failing math.
There's no such thing
as pro-math.
You're wrong, Hank.
There's pro-math,
there's pro-English,
there's pro-history.
Mm-hm.
The way I figure,
in the NBA
score, stats, and
signing bonuses
all the math I need to know.
FRIEND 1: NBA? [CHUCKLES]
What did you smoke?
[ALL LAUGH]
Tell him, Specs.
Yo, Specs.
I'm gonna get you...
Come on, man get you...
What? What?
Just sit down.
You're just starting to learn
what you need to know.
Get ready. Ready?
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Look at that, gentlemen.
Give me some mighty fine sister.
Forget it, man.
Be serious.
They won't have anything
to do with us.
Follow me.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Ah, excuse me.
Um, can I talk to you
for a moment?
Is he talking to me?
[ALL LAUGH]
I mean, look.
What's your name,
baby?
I mean, hey, girl,
you looking good.
You know what I'm saying?
Ah...
I mean, like, uh,
maybe you and me could
get together
and get busy?
[ALL LAUGH]
Wait. Wait. Okay.
You couldn't even spell
busy, okay?
Oh.
B-u-s-y.
Easy.
Oh, come on. I don't
got time for this.
Let's go.
No, no, no. Wait, wait.
Come on.
Hold up.
The skinny one's
kinda cute.
Come on.
Skinny?
Skinny.
What's your name, baby?
I'm Hank "The Bank" Gathers.
Oh, Hank "The Bank" huh?
You're gonna be a big man
on the varsity,
Hank "The Crank"?
[ALL LAUGHING]
Oh, we don't find out
till next week.
Oh, then, uh...
next week we shall see
what we shall see, huh?
Hank, The Wank.
Oh, girl.
Oh, hey.
My name is Derrick
and, uh--
Man, shut up.
I like to get to know
both of ya'll. Uh...
Ain't she fine?
She just...
Can I have your number?
ALL GIRLS: No.
Hi, mama.
Bye, mama.
What are you doing
up so early?
They're posting the final
varsity roster this morning.
Okay. Well, sit down
and have some meal.
I'm not hungry, mama.
What?
I'd never thought I hear
those words out of that
boy's mouth.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
HANK: Yes! Yes!
I made it! I made it!
Man, you never make
these free throws.
Shut up.
Here we go.
Try it again.
Spec, man, I can't believe
you didn't make the team.
Ah, man, it's okay.
Just frees up my time
for more important matter,
that's all.
Could you hold these
for me, please?
Hey.
You see me at the varsity?
[COUGHS] Oh please. They must
be scraping the bottom of
the barrel this year.
What you mean,
"bottom of the barrel"?
Bottom of the barrel.
Uh...
I'm going to my moms,
you wanna come with me?
She's, uh, at work.
You mean now?
I mean, we could stop
and get something to drink,
if you really want to.
I don't drink liquor.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
What else don't you do?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Why don't you tell
your friends bye.
Bye.
Later.
ALL: Bye.
Can I come?
HANK: No.
GIRL: Bye.
Yo, Specs.
Look out, man.
MAMA: Hank.
Could you come here
for a minute, please?
Sure, mama.
What's up?
Sit down, baby.
Hank, um...
You know, you can
come to me, don't you?
Mm-hm.
You know that no matter
what happens,
I'm on your side, right?
Yeah, mama.
You and me, we're a team.
Mm. That's good.
Okay.
Then, maybe you can explain
this phone call I just got.
[CLEARS THROAT] Some girl
and her mama
said that she's pregnant
and you're the father.
You're just a high school kid.
What are you doing
getting some kid pregnant?
[SOBBING]
What about college?
What about making something
of your life?
I...
How could you
not come to me?
I was scared, mama.
Oh!
I wanted to tell you.
I'm sorry, mama.
[CRYING]
You know...
[LAUGHS] You were always
trying to grow up faster
than you needed too.
Well...
But now, I guess you just
don't have any choice,
do you?
Come here, baby.
[BOTH CRYING]
I'm sorry, mama.
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
[BABY GURGLING]
I'm a father.
You?
I'm an uncle.
[CHUCKLES]
Uncle Derrick.
An uncle's cool,
I guess.
Go on, Hank.
Go on in there.
Get in there now.
But you just be careful
with him, okay?
I just want you to think
about what you're walking into.
When you're holding your baby
for the first time,
it's a feeling
you'll never forget.
You do understand
what I'm saying,
don't you?
Boy! Do you understand
what I am saying?
Uh-hm.
I doubt it.
Get in there anyway.
Go on, boy. Go.
DEREK: Go on, Hank.
[BABIES CRYING]
[LAUGHING]
Yo, Lez. Check it out.
I had a baby.
Have a cigar.
All right.
Just one.
Hey, Bo.
Have a cigar.
I don't smoke.
[CHUCKLES] Of course not, man.
These are candy.
Check it out,
I had a baby.
I'm a daddy.
I heard.
Ain't you gonna say,
"congratulations,"
or you know...
Get... What's up
with you, man?
Are you stupid
or just crazy?
What do you mean?
It's like everything
you do, Hank.
It's all a game.
Just a game.
I'm naming you Aaron.
'Cause it goes so natural
with Hank.
Hank and Aaron,
me and you.
Yeah, we're a team.
You don't have to
worry about nothing.
'Cause what ever happens,
I'm gonna take care of you.
Mm-hm. I promise you that.
Like it or not,
you brought a child
onto the world.
Now, you gonna have to decide
how to treat it.
Him, Father.
"It's" a him.
How are you going to
feed him, Hank?
You know, he's with her
and her family.
That's your plan?
Come on, Father Dave.
Recess is over.
I know that.
Well, what are you
gonna do now?
I'm gonna make
my son proud.
How?
What you mean?
I'm gonna play ball,
I'm gonna make millions.
You and a million other kids.
Are you willing to bet
your sons dinner
on basketball?
It's best bet we got.
I sure as hell hope not.
Don't do this to me,
Father Dave.
All this time you've been
telling me that if I go out
there and work my butt off,
that it'll happen for me.
Now, what are you saying?
Don't even try,
don't even bother?
But it's not just you anymore.
Don't you think I know that?
Man, Father, I held him.
No. Don't count me out, Father.
I'm gonna do this.
I mean, I got a long way to go.
But I just know that I can
do this.
[SIGHS]
I hope so, Hank.
You know, I've always been
on your side.
I promise you, Father,
that when those scouts
start coming around,
it won't just be Bo Kimble
they're looking at.
I promise you that.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
I was open.
When you get the hoop.
He won't give me the ball,
I can get my own.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER: Gathers...
Scouts.
What?
College recruiters.
It's sure they don't live
around here.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
HANK: Okay.
Finally, made one.
Come on, Hank.
You're gonna be here all day.
Let's go home.
Man, I got to keep shooting
these free throws. It's the
weakest part pf my game.
I got 25 more of those.
Damn. Come on.
You see that?
You getting tired,
let's go.
[ALL CHEERING]
Get him.
So, how much attention
is Gathers really getting?
Lots of letters,
personal visits.
La Salle is really interesting.
He wanted to go to
a local school?
They've got a good program.
[LAUGHS]
We got more for this kid
than just basketball program.
They've also got
a good school.
Yeah.
Well, I like him.
I like him a lot,
and I'll make you a promise,
at USC he'll get a good
education and a good
basketball program.
Besides a kid from here
should go away for school
any how.
You're always trying to
make her proud of me.
You know?
[CHUCKLES]
Always do. You know,
if I can just give her
something back. You know?
You just got to ease up
on your self.
Let the game come back
to you.
Man I--
No, you just nervous 'cause
there are scouts out there.
I don't think that's
what it is, Hank.
That ain't it, man.
I know I'm nervous.
That's because they looking
at you, of course you got to
be nervous.
They're looking at you too.
That's my point.
No, they're not, man.
They're not looking
at me, aye.
I mean, it's you.
It's you and Bo.
I mean, if it was just us
on the team, man,
there wouldn't be a scout
in the house.
It's you, Hank.
You and Bo, man.
You and Bo.
[CROWD CHEERING]
You should've got back.
They're killing us on
the break, man.
I was back, where the hell
were you?
Give me that.
I got it.
[GRUNTING]
CROWD: Oh.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
REFEREE: 32 and 12,
you're out of here.
[CROWD BOOING]
You really know how
to screw things up,
don't you?
Me?
All you had to do
was let go.
You don't seem
to get it.
I'm trying to win
basketball games.
Bo, I wanna win
just as bad as
you do.
Sure could've fooled me.
You know why?
Just because you think
the only way this team
is gonna win
is if you do everything.
You can't do it
alone, Bo.
Who else is there?
There's me!
[SCOFFS]
There's you.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah, there's me.
[SIGHS]
Maybe I lost it out there.
Yeah, you did.
Hey, you know what?
And so did you.
And to keep fighting each other,
it ends up hurting us both,
and we both end-up
looking bad.
Okay.
So?
So...
We're only on the same team
for another couple of months.
Why don't we go out there,
and play the best high school
hoops those scouts have
ever seen.
And then, we are out of
each other's lives for good.
Well, come on, Bo.
The Hank and Bo Show.
No, no, no. Okay.
The Bo and Hank Show.
Whatever you want.
What'd you say?
[SIGHS]
[MIMICKING SIGH]
[CHUCKLES] That's supposed
to mean yes?
Well, come on, Bo,
you can say it.
Come on. Let me help you.
it ain't that hard. Come on,
you ready?
Okay.
I'll give you the whole
sentence.
Okay, Hank,
it sounds good to me.
Come on.
You know, Hank,
you crazy.
Who me?
Yeah.
That's what they tell me.
[LAUGHING]
All right.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Pit ball.
Ready to go?
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
Okay. Thanks, man.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Gathers.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hey, Bo.
In lots of recruitment visit?
Some.
Good schools?
Pretty good. Yeah.
You see, everybody's telling me
to go here and don't go there.
And do this and...
I was just wondering
if it was the same thing
for you?
Yeah, it is.
Eh, Bo.
I hope it didn't take
too much out of you.
I mean, saying all that
in one time.
So you going to USC?
The football school?
They won the league
in basketball, last year.
You can do no better
than that.
Oh, my man Hank knows
what he is doing.
He's headed to
the new frontiers,
brothers.
Southern California.
So. Cal.
Home of show-time and
fine women running on beach
with floss bikinis on.
That's right.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, finally.
Hasn't been a descent player
come out of there since
that kid--
Ruined that boy.
Ruined a lot of kids.
Pull 'em down there
with a bunch of big talk,
something happens,
somebody better comes along,
next thing you know...
out of there.
What, you some kind of
expert now, Ray?
You're damn right.
Happened to my nephew
down in Florida.
Blew his knee
playing football.
Sorry, we can't use you no more.
Two years of college,
boy couldn't read a letter.
Not they lick?
They didn't care.
[LAUGHS]
BARBER: Where's Bo going?
On Kentucky, I think.
Now, that's
a basketball college.
Why don't you go with him?
[LAUGHS]
No, thank you.
After this year, we're going
our separate ways.
Uh-uh. It's been fun,
but where ever he goes,
I don't particularly need
to be.
Well, you go to California,
you won't have to worry.
Yo, you sure he didn't cut
too much in the back, man?
'Cause you know, me
and my girls don't like it
when it's too short in the back.
You know that, Hank.
You look beautiful.
There's no other way
to say it.
Yeah, that's it.
Hey, why you get
all duded up like this?
Sometimes, I just like,
you know, can't restraint
myself. I could just...
feeling like, you know,
I just wanna...
kiss you, man.
What? Get off!
[ALL LAUGHING]
HANK: You know, you can't
outrun me.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
Yo, excuse me, brothers.
But I got a little business
to take care of.
I chase you in it, baby.
Look, I'll check you all
out later, Specs.
Yo, Specs, man.
Yeah, what's going on,
Bank?
Specs man, we've been friends
a long time, right?
Yeah.
But I got to ask you
not to bring that stuff
around here with those kids.
You asking me?
Or you telling me?
It's up to you, man.
That's cold, Bank.
That's real cold.
And you know, I never
figured you for the high
and mighty routine.
I mean, now that you got
your little scholarship and
your California University,
what do you get off telling me
what I can't do for my own self?
Listen, Specs,
I don't like it.
What you do is up to you.
But when you start dealing
to these kids, man,
I got to throw my foot down.
And what if I say no.
I don't think you will.
Why?
Because you are the all mighty
Hank "The Bank" Gathers?
No. No.
Because I still believe
that you the difference
between right and wrong.
Come on.
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
What was that about?
Let's just say...
I will be glad when
I get to California.
[CHUCKLES]
Here we go again.
Soon, I'll be out there
with those palm trees,
and string bikinis,
and it'll be summer time
all year long.
Sounds awful good, Hank.
In fact, it sounds
too good for you.
Yeah?
Let me take this opportunity
to thank the all little people,
like you, Bo,
who helped me along my way,
and I'll be thinking about you
when you're freezing your
butt off in Kentucky.
You do like hillbillies,
don't you, Bo?
Who's going to Kentucky?
I thought for sure
you were.
Not me.
Oh, okay, Bo,
end the mystery.
Where you going?
We are... [YAWNING]
dying to know.
[CHUCKLES] Where you said to me
all that talk about palm trees,
bikinis and things.
What you mean?
I saw it last week, man.
We're brother Trojans.
Great.
[LAUGHS]
It's great.
Yes.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Do you know what I read?
No, Hank.
What'd you read?
The average salary
in the NBA
is $350,000.
And the guys picked
in the first round
of the opening round,
you know the guys
in the lottery?
They make really big money.
Are you sure this is
the student parking lot?
I think so.
Hey.
Can I help you?
Uh...
No. No, thanks.
I'll manage.
It's okay.
Hey, it's okay.
We live here too.
We're basketball players.
For USC.
Oh. Right.
Sorry. I, I didn't know.
It's okay. We don't
know you, either.
And if all we know
you could be swiping
this stuff.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Yeah, right.
Hey, I'm Hank Gathers.
Hi.
And, uh, this is
Bo Kimble.
Forrest Palmer.
I play tennis.
Really?
Yeah.
Uh... That's great!
I always wanted to
take up tennis.
Really?
Yeah.
Lovely game, tennis.
Very, very elegant.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Bo?
Bo, you awake?
No.
Man, would you still go
to school if you had as
much money as Forest?
You know, enough to buy
a Porche and all that?
I don't know.
You?
[LAUGHS] My mom
would still make me.
Bo?
What?
Listen, man.
I don't care what it takes,
I don't care how much work
we got to do,
when it comes time to go pros,
we got to picked in
the first round.
We got to be lottery picks, Bo.
Is that all?
What do you say, man?
I say, we just got to USC,
and going pro is years away.
Lottery, Bo.
What do you say?
Go to sleep, Hank.
Say it, Bo. Lottery.
Lottery.
Good night, Bo.
[SIGHS]
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
Let's go.
All right, go.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Gathers.
Let me tell you one more
time where this play
is supposed to go.
The same place it
all supposed to go.
Did you something,
Gathers?
No, sir.
Let me remind you
that last year there were
three guys over 6'10''
at UCLA alone.
So while you're trying to
post up guys that are
half a foot taller than you,
Dennis could be sinking
the jumper all the long.
Just get the ball to Dennis.
You're not on the playground
anymore. Just get it to Dennis.
He's our first option.
All right, son. Let's do it now.
Come on, let's go, every body.
Let's go.
Come on, Hank,
let's go.
Let's go!
[CROWD CLAPPING AND CHEERING]
Bo Kimble.
You just spent
your entire day
on the bench.
Where are you
going next?
Shut up, Hank.
You know, we... [LAUGHS]
We have this conversation every,
every two or three weeks.
You're driving yourself nuts,
you know.
It isn't personal.
It has nothing to do with you.
The offense just happens to be
designed that way right now.
HANK: What offense?
You know, this is the first time
in my life I've been in
a loosing team, Spence.
Hank.
And I don't like it.
You're a freshman.
A freshman.
Give yourself a chance.
But if we were winning,
It would be one thing.
But, I say, "Great.
The coach knows
what he's doing."
But this ship is sinking.
Hank, you gonna have to
have patience.
I came to play,
not to sit.
and I've come too far to watch
this team loose from the bench.
Okay. And we are here with
the surprise guest for
tonight's varsity-alumni dinner,
Mr. Hank Gathers
and Mr. Bo Kimble.
Surprise my butt.
Give me that thing.
What?
You don't know
what you're doing.
Oh, and you do?
Uh-huh. When I finish
my career in the NBA,
I'm gonna have a career
in broadcasting.
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen,
Our very special guest
this evening is that
sensitive, and, oh, so quiet,
young god,
Mr. Bo Kimble.
[PRETENDS CROWD APPLAUDING]
He doesn't say much, folks,
but maybe he'll grace us
with a word or two.
And we think it's important
that the alumni have
the opportunity to meet
the athletes and
the student leaders
in a small or intimate setting
like this.
So thanks for coming,
and I hope you enjoy it.
Now, if you ask me,
the name of the game
always was, and always
will be, defense.
Don't you agree?
Huh?
Oh, absolutely.
You got to have a good d.
Right.
You know, I don't see any reason
you fellows can't go all the way
to the Rollers Ball this year.
HANK: Rollers Ball?
Right. Pasadena.
Son, how long have
you been playing football?
Hank, don't you realize
that to these guys
this is a business,
and you know
what you are?
You are a product.
But we're in
the same business.
They wanna win,
that's what I want,
that's what I'm gonna do.
Oh, you are,
are you?
Uh-huh.
Hm, I guess you're gonna be
one of the lucky ones, huh?
[LAUGHS] Luck's
got nothing
to do with it.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Gathers, get in there
for Johnson.
All right, Hank,
you can do it.
ANNOUNCER: We get number 10,
Hank Gathers.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Gathers continues to pace
this resurgent USC team,
weighing in last night with 16
hard nose points and
12 monstrous rebounds.
This Gathers kid,
just can't say
enough about him.
[LAUGHS]
Along with side-kick guard,
Bo Kimble,
these two have literally
turned things around for SC.
The prospects for next year
appear rosy
with all five starters
returning.
This is... Hank
"The Bank" Gathers...
Maybe not.
What do you mean?
Coach is leaving.
Out of here. History.
He quit?
He took an administrative
position.
Oh, yeah. Right.
What about Spence?
Is he getting the gig?
You think he'd take it?
He and coach were real tight.
Oh, I heard that.
The new coach wanted me
to convey to you that
he's certainly aware
the sense of loss you must
all feel over the departure of
the previous coaching staff.
He's also aware,
some of you have made
statements to the press
regarding your displeasure.
He understands and appreciates
your sense of loyalty.
Particularly in the case of
assistant coach Spencer.
But now, let me say,
that is all ancient
history now.
It's a new day for
SC basketball.
Time to turn things around.
What do you think
we've been doing?
Think. You're finishing up
a losing season.
12 and 16.
You placed last in
the conference, gentlemen.
I expect congratulations.
Let me tell you something.
We know. Some new goals,
some new directions,
even this team
can win next season.
New coach will show you
how to do it.
You got to let him.
Our coach is gone.
That's right, son.
So, if you expect to play
next season,
it's time to get with
the new program.
Okay?
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
Hey, hold on a second.
You two, hang on
a second.
Couple of things
for you here.
What's this?
Written notification.
Bring it back signed
by March 15th or you'll
forfeit the scholarships.
I'm Hank, he's Bo.
Oh.
Okay, Hank, just
have it back by
the 15th, okay?
Yeah.
I told you, Father Dave,
the man says
he wants us to stay.
But then, look how
they treated Spense.
And if they really don't
want us, they not gonna
play us.
[SIGHS] Oh, God.
I just hope we're doing
the right thing, Father D.
Yeah, we'll check with you.
[SIGHS]
Hank, I can't stay someplace
I'm not wanted.
Of course not.
'Cause, you've always
been wanted.
Every place I've ever been
I had to fight to play.
For all we know, we'll be
riding the bench for
the next three years here, Hank.
That's no good.
We got to go someplace
where we know we gonna play.
Someplace where the scouts
are gonna see us.
Where we gonna go?
I don't know.
[SIGHS]
We're just gonna be
okay, right?
I mean, it's no big deal.
It's gonna be okay, right?
Right?
I didn't say that.
All I know is we can't stay.
[SIGHS]
And then
the library's
here.
Men's' dorm
right across here.
And Father Dave must
be losing it to send us
to a place like this.
Hank, what's the problem, man.
Coming out to California
was one thing, Spence.
At least we'd heard of USC.
What kind of place is
this Loyola Marymount?
Looks like I'm in Disneyland.
And checkout this schedule.
Gonzaga, Santa Barbara,
Pepperdine. [CHUCKLES]
Name me one guy
who ever went pro
from Gonzaga.
We're gonna be lost
and forgotten here.
Why don't we not be
so melodramatic here,
all right?
How're you gonna be
"Lost and forgotten"
when nobody's even heard
of you in the first place?
You two say
you wanna play pro-ball,
you got the head coach
here who coached
the Los Angeles Lakers
to the NBA championship.
And for my money,
the way you two play ball here,
I don't think you're gonna
find a better head coach
in college ball today.
I guess he told you,
didn't he?
Yo, Spence.
Gonzaga? Didn't Stockton
go to Gonzaga?
COACH: In this program
we try to make the game
very simple.
Our goal is to put this
in there,
as quickly, as often
as we can.
Any question so far?
What we're talking about is
non-stop, fast-break,
running-gun basketball.
It's the way a lot of you
grew up playing the game.
But we're gonna elevate
playground style ball,
to a science.
It's gonna require a commitment
on your parts,
to become the best condition
athletes in college basketball.
Come on. Come on.
Let's pick it up,
guys.
Only four miles
to go. Come on!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go!
You're right, Howard.
Being the strongest man alive
means I've got to be very
careful about what I eat.
Thank you, Hank Gathers,
star forward for
the Loyola Marymount
basketball Lions.
I didn't even know we had
a basketball team.
Yes, Aaron.
It's a big,
big basketball school.
Yeah, they're crazy
for hoops here.
AARON: Daddy, you're gonna
come home for Christmas?
What you think?
Of course, I'm coming home
for Christmas.
...big bad truck.
[LAUGHS] We'll talk about it.
You come home and stay, daddy.
Uh, I, I think it's time
for your bed time, isn't it?
Now, you go ahead
and be a good boy.
Tell your mama
I said hi.
I love you.
Uh-uh. I love you more.
I love you more.
[CHUCKLES]
Go to bed.
Bye, daddy. I love you.
Okay, bye.
[CHUCKLES]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
BO: All right, Hank.
This is it.
What do you think?
I think we're playing
somebody called Gonzaga.
[HORN BLOWS]
Tell me, what is
the Gonzaga?
I don't know, but we played
the bigger crowds at
Dallas High School.
I heard that.
There was so few people
out there we could've held
riflery practice.
We got to do this.
We got to make this work,
and we can be moving again.
We got to play so damn well,
those scouts are gonna...
[INDISTINCT PA ANNOUNCEMENT]
[HORN BLOWS]
All right?
You with me?
Let's do it.
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY]
[CHEERLEADERS CHEERING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[BURPS]
Something strange and unusual
is going on over at
Loyola Marymount.
Loyolians have never been
what you might call
"a power house"
among the college
basketball elite.
But after 12 games,
they're leading the nation in
scoring averaging at almost,
unbelievable 125 points
per game.
Their high... Get ready
for this, folks.
An astronomical 186 for Kimble
and Gathers and company.
The Lions of LMU
are definitely roaring.
What'd I tell you.
They're over-playing you
in the low post.
You move to the left,
you'll be unstoppable.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
ANNOUNCER: Basket by Gathers.
Basket by Gathers.
[GRUNTS]
HANK: Hey, Bo. Bo?
Hey, man.
Face it, Bo.
That was a stupid ass
thing to do.
Don't mess with me,
Hank.
Hey, they never fix these
things these days.
It's gonna be okay.
Hey, man, I don't know that,
neither do you.
Oh, yes, I do.
You're just gonna have to
work, Bo.
So, you just enjoy
laying up here in this bed,
'cause when you're ready,
I'm gonna whip that big butt
of yours back into line-up.
I've never wanted to sit out.
And then I've never
been injured.
[SIGHS]
That's why, it'a good thing
you got me, Bo.
'Cause working hard just
happens to be my particular
field of expertise.
Come on, we can do this,
my man. You're gonna be
just fine.
Come on, give it up.
Looking very good, my man.
Looking quick.
Looking graceful.
Shut up, Hank.
Come on.
I'll do one-on-one.
Yeah, right.
No, soon. You'll see.
Check this.
Yes!
You made a free throw.
You wanna call
a press conference?
No, no, no.
Did you notice
anything unusual?
Other than the fact
that it went in?
Watch again.
Yes!
Oh!
You switched to left-handed.
Mm-hm.
If the right hand
don't get you,
the left one will.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Eight, seven, six,
five, four...
Come on.
[GROANING]
Eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
All right! Come on!
[CROWD CHEERING]
Now, come on,
don't rest.
Come on, don't rest.
Yeah.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Come on.
Bend over, come on.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Spence say if
I go pro now,
before my senior year,
I'll be picked somewhere
in the middle of first round.
That's not lottery,
Bank.
I know. But after
what happened to you,
I got to think.
It might not be
such a bad idea.
Sounds like your mind's
already made up.
I'm just thinking
about it.
Mama, if I do this
you don't have to
work so hard,
we could pay up
all those bills.
Oh, Hank, please.
Don't do this for me.
But, mama, I had
a great year.
I led the nation scoring
and rebounding.
We do this now,
we're set for life.
Or you wait another year,
and you can do better.
Listen, baby, nobody
in my family,
nobody in my life has even
made it past high school.
But you work hard,
you can do it.
Look, even Father Dave
wants you to get this degree.
I agree.
And if you're worried about
getting hurt, we can take
an insurance policy out.
Or I can go pro now,
with a couple of
million dollars in the bank.
You know what, Hank?
You area man now.
I have told you
what I thought.
You do what you think
is best, baby.
That is not fair, mama.
But that's just the way
it is, Hank.
That's just the way it is.
You do what you think
is best, okay?
Ah! Looking good, Bo.
Still, long way
to go, man.
Uh, come here.
Lottery?
Huh, Bo. Lottery?
Yeah! [GRUNTS]
[BLOWS]
Lottery.
ANNOUNCER: And with
Hank Gathers having
a great senior year,
and Bo Kimble apparently
fully recovered from
last years knee injury,
Loyola Marymount is firing
of all cylinders once more,
and appears to have every
intention of making a run
at the NCAA tournament.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[CROWD BOOING]
Come on, Hank.
We need this, baby.
Two.
[CAPTIVATING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
One more, now.
One more.
Come on.
[CROWD GASPING]
Hank.
Hank?
Apparently you've suffered
a severe arrhythmia, Hank.
It's a sudden interruption
in your heartbeat.
You mean, I had a heart attack?
It's an episode.
But it's not something
to be take lightly.
We wouldn't want it
to happen again.
So, what's the deal?
Well, uh...
Rests.
More tests.
Uh, we'll have you see
some specialists.
I'm putting you on
medication right away.
We're gonna get
this thing under control.
So, I can still play,
right?
Well, uh...
Not immediately.
Uh, you can practice lightly
if you feel up to it, but...
I wouldn't want you in
competition until I know
more about what's happened.
But assuming positive
tests results,
regular observations...
I think it's a realistic goal.
It's good as new,
man.
Mm-hm.
Nah.
Tightens up sometimes,
but... it's good.
You want me to
help you stretch it out?
Nah.
I really don't have to
do this anymore.
Just became sort of
a habit.
Is there anything...
Is there anything
I could do for you?
Don't get all sympathetic
on me, Bo.
[GRUNTS]
I can carry my own bag.
I'm all right.
Okay,
ready?
BO: Hey, Hank, my fault.
Bad pass.
No, no. I should have
had that.
Come on.
The feelings that you describe
are not at all uncommon.
They are familiar
side-effects
of mediation.
It shouldn't last
too long.
It's already been
It's a process, Hank.
As we continue
to monitor your
response, we'll,
we'll adjust
the medication
accordingly.
Say what?
We've got to see
how it goes.
Oh! This is funny.
I've never been into drinking,
or drugs or nothing like that.
I just always knew
if I took drugs,
I couldn't play ball.
So, here I am,
like somebody's junkie.
It's not the same thing,
Hank.
It feels the same to me.
PLAYER: Heads up!
Hank.
I'll put you in when
I think you're ready.
You're not ready.
That's great.
I bust my butt against schools
nobody's ever heard of.
And now we're playing Oklahoma
on national TV,
and you're not playing me?
Two weeks ago
you collapsed
on the court.
I'm okay.
I hope you know
what you're doing
to me, coach.
It's practically
NBA week, you know.
You're killing my career.
It's too soon.
I don't think
you're ready yet.
When?
Hank--
No, let me tell you this,
I am gonna play
against La Salle
and St. Joe's when
we get to Philly
no matter what.
I waited four year to play
my home town,
I am gonna play
for my people.
Yes, you will...
if you're ready.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
One, two, three...
ALL: Lions.
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
your Loyola Marymount Lions.
ED: Even after falling
to Oklahoma,
and despite the loss
of Hank Gathers,
there's no stopping
the little engine at
Loyola Marymount.
Bo Kimble and company
are soon to be off
on a tough road trip,
and the help of Hank Gathers
could make the difference in
that sports.
I'm going on record
right now, my man.
I'm taking my headlines back
when we get to Philly.
You just get well.
Your headlines will take care
of themselves.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
RADIO HOST: This is WADW
Sports Room,
and we are taking calls
about tomorrow night's
game between
St. Joe's and Loyola Marymount.
As you know this marks
the return of our local hero's
Hank Gathers and Bo Kimble.
So you tell me...
Can the California kids
come home and still
make it to big bad six?
MAN: Oh, yeah...
I got good eyes glued
with Bo and Hank.
And, uh, both those dudes
have a lot of heart.
You know, as far as Gathers
coming back jacked
in West Philly,
too much sunshine
in the West coast.
They're gonna get entertained.
WOMAN: Listen, I'm a real
sports fan , you know.
And I'd like to tell you
I've been through a lot of...
Mama!
Oh, baby!
Mama.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Oh!
Oh, my goodness.
I'm okay. See, mama.
Oh, just shut up.
Come here, you big dope.
They're gonna kick St. Joe's
back if you ask me,
then they're gonna drop La Salle
like a bad transmission.
My dad's gonna dog them.
[BOTH HOOTING]
Yes.
You don't sit still,
I'm gonna carve my name
on the back of your head.
St. Joe's are
tough team to beat.
But nobody can beat Hank.
So he's been saying
since he was younger
than you.
You feeling okay?
You can talk to
my duly appointed
representative.
So you okay?
I'm gonna have some
cards printed up
saying, "Thanks for asking."
But Hank is just fine,
all right? I'm fine.
He's crazy to win,
that's all.
I'm taking this kid
down to Crowns,
get him a basketball.
Yeah.
Got you. Got you.
Crowns closed down.
No.
Yeah, you have to go all the way
on another side to German town
to find a sporting goods place.
These crackheads,
they don't need basketball.
I told you to
stay out of here.
Don't you know that boy?
That boys name is Spec,
isn't that, Ray?
Uh, I'll be right back.
What's up with you,
Specs?
I heard you was in town.
Came to, uh,
to welcome you home.
That worth something to you?
Yo, man.
Uh...
How 'bout sharing
some of that bank
with an old friend?
You had to know
I don't get paid
until I go pro.
Well, I don't know, man.
Looks pretty good
for you now.
Specs, man, uh...
Hank?
Put your jacket on.
Specs?
One, two, three...
ALL: Lions!
[CROWD CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER: Bo Kimble us on fire
in front of his hometown crowd.
But Hank Gathers isn't playing
with any of the... same hands.
And Gathers is down.
Color turnover by Hank Gathers.
Right now, you'd have to say
he's hurting the team.
Nick Jones is taking it
right to Gathers.
And again Gathers fails
to block out his man.
Score!
Easy lay off.
They extend their lead to 11.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Come on, bank, you're all right.
Relax. Let the game come to you.
ANNOUNCER: Loyola has
a chance here to cut
into St. Joe's lead.
Two shot.
ANNOUNCER: But, historically,
Hank Gathers has been
a horrible free throw shooter.
An air ball.
[CROWD BOOING]
It's okay.
Player.
ANNOUNCER: And another miss.
Hank Gathers missed both
free throws.
Here comes St. Joe's.
He changes almost
every possessions.
Still, Hank Gathers watches
from the bench.
[CROWD CHANTING]
ANNOUNCER: Five seconds to go.
Crunch time, folks.
Bo Kimble takes the pass,
...he better hurry.
[BUZZER BUZZES]
[CROWD CHEERING]
Bo Kimble wins the game!
With no time left on
the clock Loyola wins!
Loyola wins the ball game!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[CROWD CHANTING] Bo! Bo! Bo!
It's been a long time
since I've seen you
feeling sorry for yourself.
Come on, Father Dave.
You know, it's more
than that.
Every scout in the league
thinks there's something
wrong with me.
[SCOFFS] Who knows.
Maybe there is.
What are you talking about?
Ever since it happened,
it's like my brain
and my body
are playing
two different games.
I mean, I can see what
I wanna do out there
just as clear as day,
but I just can't do
what I see.
All my life,
I've been working...
for right now.
And it's just slipping away.
I can feel it.
[SOBBING]
It's just slipping away
from me.
I think there's a little more
at stake here than
making a pro-deal.
Come on, Father Dave,
it ain't about no deal.
It isn't even
about the money.
If I wanted money,
I'd cash that insurance
policy they got for me.
It's a million dollars, right?
All I have to do is give up
playing basketball.
This is what it's about,
Father Dave.
I just want to do...
what I always knew
I could do.
You know?
I just wanna play the best
I can.
I just don't know.
I'm scared, you know?
[SIGHS] [CHUCKLES]
[SNIFFLES]
[SIREN WAILING]
Hank.
Oh, baby, you sure
everybody knows how
to get here after the game?
I think so, mama.
Okay. Well, come here, baby,
won't you help me move the sofa.
Uh, mama, you sure
that's okay for me?
[LAUGHING]
Boy, don't you be playing
with me when I'm worrying
about you.
Mama, how many times
have I told you?
I am the strongest man alive.
Hey, put that down
and stop it.
Besides, I got a built in
warranty.
You.
Look, Hank.
People loved you before
you ever touched basketball,
and will still love you
if you never play again.
College, pro, never give
will be just fine with me.
But, mama, it won't be
fine with me.
Besides, everything is
gonna be all right.
You'll see.
Tonight is my night.
Yeah, sure.
Oh, what is that?
What?
Ah!
Stop. Get off.
No. no. no.
[LAUGHING]
Go practice, boy. Stop it.
Get out of here.
Bye.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'm out of here.
[DOOR CLOSES]
ANNOUNCER: Loyola ball.
Gathers in the long post.
A nifty pass to players,
it's gone. Beautiful.
Yes! Take it to him.
Take it to him.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Alley-oop and La Salle
got it scored.
Get back! Get back!
Kimble goes back door,
and Hank Gathers slams.
Hey, Father, what the hell
is wrong with him?
I want some of that.
[CHUCKLES]
Sorry, ma.
Go, Hank!
[CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER: Loyola with
the ball, score is tied,
six seconds to go.
Gathers in position,
but it's foul.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
ANNOUNCER: Loyola can
grab it up from free throws
from Gathers.
We saw last night,
Gathers is a poor
foul shooter.
Well, have a little faith,
Father.
Okay now. One-on-one now.
Play the match, one-on-one.
ANNOUNCER:
Nothing wrong with that one.
Gathers puts Loyola up by one.
One more now.
Play it.
Yeah!
ANNOUNCER: Loyola up
by two points.
[BUZZER BUZZES]
[CROWD CHEERING]
We take the final four.
Final four.
I say we take
the whole tournament.
[LAUGHS]
And then lottery selection.
And then...
BOTH: Rookie of the Year.
Yes. Yes.
Somebody call my name?
Liar.
Get out of here.
He used to sweep off
the snow in the winters.
And in the summer time
he'd hot-wire the lights,
anything to get on the courts.
He even swiped my keys
a couple of times...
BOTH: To get into the gym.
So any idea where
you might end up
playing?
I don't know, Charlotte,
Cleveland.
Orlando, maybe.
Orlando.
I'll play where ever
they send me.
I heard that.
Hank.
Could I live in Philadelphia?
It's not where you live.
And who else lives
in Philadelphia?
Hey, hey, don't clock me.
Leave my son alone.
Don't clock, yo...
You better, you better
hold me back.
But the best part for me
were the free throws.
Oh, yeah. Finally.
But it was all great.
I owe it all to you,
Father.
Every last bit.
Get out of here.
I'm really proud
of you, Hank.
You know, Father Dave,
you've always been my hero.
[HORN TOOTING]
I'm coming.
I got to go.
Okay. Look, uh...
Derricks been talking
about us flying out
for the regional finals,
I mean, if you're still
in the tournament.
Well, we gonna make it
to the finals, mama.
So, you tell that buddy
go ahead and buy those
tickets. Non-refundable.
Come here, honey.
Look you be good, okay?
And you take care of yourself.
I will, mama.
You hear me?
I will.
I have to go.
Okay. All right.
Take care of yourself.
I will.
I love you.
I love you too, baby.
Tell Derrick to buy
those tickets, mama.
I love you.
HANK: I love you more.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
And since Hank Gathers
returned the line-up,
the little engine you call
Loyola is ready and willing,
if not perhaps 100% able,
to make a run for
the national title.
But first they have to prove
themselves in regional action.
And tonight's semifinal game
versus Portland
should be an important test
for the Lions,
both physically
and psychologically.
Take it easy out there
tonight, Bank.
Why?
So you can get all
the headlines to
yourself again?
No, that's not it.
I'm worried about you.
Maybe I'm the only one
who see it,
but you're still not right.
You're still not playing
the way you used to.
[SCOFFS] What do you know, Bo?
You're just another
ignorant basketball player.
Then, it's perfect,
'cause that's just who
I am talking to.
It's like when
I tore up my knee.
This stuff happens, dude.
Even to lucky guys
like you and me.
Yeah, I heard that.
Be careful out there
tonight, Bank.
[SIGHS]
To get where we are
from where we came,
how much luck
do you think
we were owed?
[LAUGHING]
You know, Bo?
I think that's the most
words I've ever heard
you say at one time.
[LAUGHS]
Love you, man.
Thank you.
[SNIFFLES]
[GRUNTS]
Put me down, Hank.
Come on, man.
Let's go.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY]
[EXCLAIMS]
Hank.
[MAMA SCREAMING]
Sweet Jesus, no!
[CRYING]
[CRYING] Father Dave,
Hank's gone.
Mama...
[CRYING]
Mama.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SNIFFLES]
Everytime,
I pick up a basketball...
for the rest of my life...
[CRYING]
Hank Gathers will be with me.
Every jump shot...
[CRYING] every three pointer...
Hank is now part of me.
Hank,
was very happy when he left.
Very happy.
Hank would not have chosen
any other way, then the way
he left us.
On the basketball court.
I also know,
Hank you like to hear
one more cheer
from his fans, friends,
people who supported him.
One last applause
in his house.
[CROWD CLAPPING]
[CAPTIVATING MUSIC PLAYING]
Love you, man.
Thank you.