(light dramatic music)
- [Man] Local blues
player to provide a loan
to Lou's Entertainment
Company in Lancaster.
(static buzzing)
- [Man] Johnson starts to
get the sun poured on him.
It warms up and you can
feel it on your skin.
- [Man] I-90 northwest
tollway in Devon Toll Plaza
has ongoing construction.
(static buzzing)
- Let's see it.
- [Man] Posted detour
to the inbound mission
for the drivers who missed it.
- [Man] What do I do in life?
What I do is grab my paycheck
and put it right next to the stove.
(static buzzing)
- [Man] Give him a lunch, a guitar,
and put him into a studio.
The guy just started wailing out after
about 20 years of drinking.
(muffled talking)
(static buzzing)
- [Man] She said she might've missed work.
Fall prices are up and slipping,
but are still above $3.00 a
gallon for regular unleaded gas.
(static buzzing)
- [Man] If you know what
the blues are tonight,
keep it here, keep it
tight, on the G-spot.
(thunder rumbling)
(blues music)
♪ I'm counting off the minutes ♪
♪ And sadness since you've been gone ♪
(door creaking)
(door slamming)
♪ My loving lips are aching ♪
♪ Always begging, begging for some ♪
♪ Why did you decide ♪
♪ Now there's just pain ♪
♪ If I could help you ♪
♪ I'm goin' in the pouring rain ♪
(phone beeping)
- Dad, it's Meg.
I've left what, five or six messages
in the last couple of weeks.
Um, you have my cell number.
I'd like it if you called me back.
Um, I'm near you, I'm on a job.
Believe it or not, I miss seeing you.
(blues music)
(water splashing)
(Meg sighs)
♪ Pictures and memories ♪
♪ Are tearing me apart ♪
♪ I'd give anything to hold you ♪
(gunshot banging)
♪ Naked heart ♪
♪ If I could just turn back ♪
(gunshot banging)
♪ The hands of time ♪
♪ I'd just want ♪
(gunshot banging)
♪ To touch you, darlin' ♪
♪ And ask you to be mine ♪
(bullet casings clanking)
♪ Time to roll and tumble ♪
♪ So fast I can't hold on ♪
♪ Wishing for the pain to be over ♪
(gun clicking)
♪ Just waiting for the dawn ♪
♪ Waiting for the dawn ♪
(car engine rumbling)
- [Weatherman] Okay, we'll get right back
into it in a minute.
Watch out for a severe weather
system blowing out the-
- Look, we came here to talk.
- Showers and a chance
of thunder showers.
- Talk?
- [Weatherman] It should
clear up by morning though.
- Are you kidding me?
- Going into a great weekend.
So, if the wife is
dragging you shopping down-
- Look, I'm just not gonna be another one
of the girls that you bring up here.
(car engine rumbling)
(car engine sputtering)
(dramatic music)
(John groaning)
(car door slamming)
(suspenseful music)
(puddle splashing)
- You're imagining things.
Nothing happened with me and Julia.
- That's not what I saw.
- What were you doing?
Spying on me?
Look, Amy, we're just friends.
Nothing more.
- And I really thought
I was more than that, BJ.
(dramatic music)
(gun clicking)
- What do you want?
Just tell me.
- Your vehicle.
Just slip out, leave the keys.
Come on.
(BJ panting)
Down flat on the ground.
- Please don't kill me.
I just turned 18, I can't die yet.
- Flat on the ground now.
(keys jingling)
Hey, why would you wanna do
something so stupid, huh?
(car engine rumbling)
(dramatic music)
You stay down on the ground.
(car door slamming)
- Look, you can have whatever
you want, just let us go.
(Amy gasping)
Just stay cool, girl.
(Amy panting)
Just stay cool.
(Amy gasping)
- Wait.
(car engine rumbling)
No, no.
No, wait, you can't take me with you, no.
No, please, no, please!
BJ, help!
(BJ crying)
Let me go!
You can't take me with you!
(car engine roaring)
(Amy screaming)
(BJ crying)
- Help!
Somebody help me!
(muffled police radio)
Help!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, what's going on?
- Help.
(sirens wailing)
- [Officer] All units, feds sent a watch
for on a black '98 Trans Am
carrying Illinois plates.
Stolen, last seen in Chicago this morning.
The driver is believed to be John Lowman.
(gunshot banging)
He's wanted for six counts
of bank robbery and for the
murder of a federal agent.
- [Mark] Federal agent,
hold it right there!
Don't do it, Lowman,
you got no where to run.
(gunshot banging)
(light dramatic music)
(gun clicking)
- [Franklyn] Sheriff, we got bigger fish
to fry than that Trans Am.
- [Ray] Spit it out,
Franklyn, what's going on?
- [Franklyn] A local girl was abducted
at gunpoint at the lookout point.
We've got a witness.
(light dramatic music)
(gunshots banging)
(practice targets whirring)
- First week out.
How the hell you'd do that?
- Well, I've been shooting guns
with my dad since I was six.
Lessons are gonna cost you extra.
- Well, how about dinner instead?
It's Megan, right?
Mark Phillips.
- I'll pass on dinner, thanks.
- What am I not your type?
- Well, if I had a type he
wouldn't be wearing a ring.
- We're legally separated.
She thought I'd be better
off using my law degree
to take down some serious corporate money
instead of signing on here.
Her dad disagreed.
We're gonna be here for 18 weeks.
Why don't you think about
that dinner invitation, okay?
- That's um, that's good target work.
- Thank you, sir.
- Top 25% of your class, Saunders.
You shoot like you were born to it.
Good job so far.
- Thank you, sir.
Except, so far sounds like
there's a but lurking in there somewhere.
- Well, you know the
protocol here at the academy.
We not only discourage
romantic liaisons between
the trainees here, but
Agent Phillips is married.
- Sir, I didn't know there was
a law against having a conversation.
And Phillips says he's separated.
- I don't think you're hearing me.
If you're laboring under the delusion
that this is a free
country, this is Quantico.
There's no freewill here.
- With all do respect, sir.
I am not used to be reprimanded
for something I have not done.
- Oh, you got stones.
I admire that in a woman.
Just be careful.
Don't do anything that's gonna damage
the progress you've been making.
Won't look good in your report.
(dramatic music)
- All units, the suspect
vehicle is an '04 SUV,
burgundy with Illinois tags.
Repeat, '04 SUV, burgundy
with Illinois tags.
- [Officer] 61, up on your screen.
- Who's in charge here?
- Well, judging by your
badge, I'd say you are, Agent-
- Megan Saunders.
- That's a pretty fast
response from the feds
considering we haven't even notified you.
- I was in the neighborhood.
- Out of Chicago?
- I'm on vacation.
I picked up your chatter on my scanner.
- Uh huh.
Ray Taylor, Belgarde County Sheriff.
This is Deputy Franklyn.
- Hi.
- Looks pretty isolated out here.
- Yeah, the young folks drive up here
for the best view in town.
- And whatever comes with it.
- Uh, can you fill me in, Sheriff?
- We don't know a lot yet.
A young girl's been abducted.
Her boyfriend's SUV was stolen.
- [Megan] Have her parents been contacted?
- We don't have a phone
number or an address yet.
- Does the boy have her cell
number or know where she lived?
- I swear to God if you guys
didn't show up when you did,
we'd both be dead.
- The girl's name is Amy Kennedy.
She's new at the high school.
Not in the mainstream yet.
- Yeah, BJ here thinks that she
lives over on Willowbrook Avenue.
Says he has her cell phone
number, but it's not on him.
- Franklyn, why don't
you take the boy home?
Get him to give you the cell phone number.
- Yes, sir.
- Was there a GPS
device on the vehicle?
- No, that'd make it too easy.
- Hang on, BJ.
Did you or Amy recognize
the man who took her?
- No.
- Would you be able to
give me a description.
- Uh, it's a white dude, late 20s.
He was huge.
I'd say 6'4", maybe 210.
- [Megan] Did he look like this?
- That's him.
(suspenseful music)
(thunder booming)
♪ The system's giving me frustration ♪
♪ Been brought to me knee ♪
♪ They said they want
me to keep on giving ♪
♪ I'm gonna give when taking is free ♪
(John beatboxing)
(hand tapping)
- That's really annoying.
- The singing?
- And that drumming.
- Anybody ever tell you
you're bossy for a kid?
- I'm nobody's kid.
(thunder booming)
- [John] What would your
parents think if they heard
you saying something like that?
- They don't care how I feel.
- I remember.
I remember how it was when I was your age.
Parents don't give a damn.
Old man beating the crap
outta me for no reason.
(thunder rumbling)
Then one day I beat him back.
Harder than he ever beat me.
- You hit your father?
- No, I didn't have a
father, I had a drunk.
(car engine rumbling)
Didn't you ever wanna do that?
Hm?
Didn't your mind ever
scream out to you in spades,
you know to do it back to
somebody who was doing it to you?
Huh, come on.
- Look, I don't know your name.
I'll forget your face.
I won't tell anybody what happened,
just drop me off somewhere, okay?
- Yeah, not until I decide.
- Decide what?
- Whether you're gonna
be useful to me or not.
(John beatboxing)
(crickets chirping)
- Yeah, well, for the most part
we got a county that
people like to live in.
Very low crime rate and
we're very proud of that.
This kinda thing just doesn't happen here.
You know, the car looks clean.
He may have just ran outta gas.
- Or he needed to dump a hot car.
You say where he kidnapped
the girl and picked up
the new one is about a
five minute walk from here?
- Yeah, about that.
You can coordinate the
search through my office.
- Okay, as long as we understand
who's heading up this investigation.
- Look, I don't give a
damn who's in charge.
All I want is to get that
young girl back safely.
- So do I.
I've been following this
guy through three states.
- I thought you said you were on vacation.
- Is that a statement or a question?
- Maybe a little bit of both.
Look, can I be frank?
- I wish you would be.
- I've got nothing against you.
I mean, take Franklyn.
She's gonna be a damn good cop
once she gets the hang of it.
- So, youth and female go
hand-in-hand in this conversation?
- All I'm saying is, if you're
honchoing this operation,
I just hope you know what you're doing.
- We can get into my credentials later.
We're wasting time.
- Look, I feel it's never a waste of time
to know who you're working with.
- I was at the top of
my class at Quantico.
I've been on the field
for almost three years,
mainly on bank robbery detail.
- Which is why you're chasing Lowman?
- He robs banks.
I go after people who rob banks.
- [Franklyn] Sheriff Taylor?
- Taylor.
- [Franklyn] A letter
is out to our department
and the state police.
- Copy that, what's your 20?
- [Franklyn] Carol Kennedy.
- Follow me.
(light dramatic music)
Nice neighborhood if you got
an extra million or two to burn.
- [Franklyn] The mother,
Carol Kennedy, she's inside.
Father, Dennis Kennedy,
he's flying back from a business trip.
He's a commodities trader
and she's in real estate.
They're both pretty shook up.
- Do you have any idea
who would want to do this?
- His name is John
Lowman, he's a fugative,
and he's wanted on a few charges.
- But why, why would
anyone wanna take Amy?
- I think Amy and her friend were
just at the wrong place at the wrong time.
- What friend?
- A BJ Busconi, a young
boy from the high school.
You didn't know Amy was with him?
(Carol sighs)
- No.
She was supposed to be at a
school play with a girlfriend.
I asked her to call to let us know
when she was on her way home.
Her life is in danger.
- We know that, ma'am.
The man that took her-
- No, you don't understand.
Amy has type one diabetes.
He blood sugar swings very greatly.
If Amy doesn't eat regularly,
get her insulin on schedule,
she could go into a coma and die.
- When was the last time she
ate and had her injection?
- Well, she had a shot after school
because I found her needle, but-
- What?
(Carol sighs)
- I don't know if she had supper.
Without eating, taking her
insulin would put her in danger.
- Realistically, how long do we have?
- It could happen very fast.
- How fast?
- A matter of hours.
(dramatic music)
(car engine rumbling)
- [Newsman] It's 10:30 in
the Windy City, people.
Reports of a stolen late model dark SUV
in the Belgarde County region.
If you see it-
- Don't look back.
- Please don't approach it.
- At the car behind.
- [Newsman] Call the local authorities
with the location and the direction
the vehicle was traveling.
- What's your name?
- [Newsman] Try and get
that girl home safe.
- Amy.
We're gonna have one fast rule here, Amy.
You see the gun in my belt?
If anything bad happens,
it's gonna be all up on you.
(water splashing)
- We moved here when my husband
was transferred in his job.
(light dramatic music)
Amy still misses her old friends.
She hasn't adjusted
well to the new school.
- How does Amy handle her condition?
- She doesn't like to be
babied, that's for sure.
But she's self conscious,
feels it prevents her from
fitting in with the other kids.
She's become very good
at hiding her secret.
- Does she use the insulin pen
or does she just have injections?
- Injections.
We constantly have to factor and adjust,
check her blood sugars, give her shots,
just for her to stay alive.
We bought her a glucometer
so that she would always know
what her blood sugar is.
You know how scattered teenagers can be.
(Carol sighs)
That's Amy with her horse.
- She rides?
- Did.
We sold the horse when we moved here.
I mean, what else could we do?
It broke her heart.
- This one's better for the media.
- Sure.
- You say her cell phone is new which
is the voicemail hasn't been setup?
- Once we were notified
we kept trying to call,
but there's never an answer.
- We'll keep trying.
If the phone is used we
can triangulate the signal
between cell towers and get her location.
- Well, shouldn't we be
prepared for a ransom call?
I mean, doesn't the FBI come
in and setup a phone tap or?
- I don't think that's the situation here.
- What do you mean?
What is the situation here?
With Amy's condition she could die!
- A deputy will be with you at all times.
We'll notify the law enforcement
of her condition as soon as possible.
(Carol sighs)
- Thank you.
- We need your help, Mrs. Kennedy.
We need a supply glucose and
insulin as soon as possible.
- Yes, of course, I'm sorry.
Anything I can do.
- How many deputies do we have?
- Five.
- That's not enough.
- This isn't Chicago, Agent Saunders.
We have limited resources.
- A woman's life is at stake.
Make it happen.
(light dramatic music)
- Whoever it is, he's not going away.
Just relax.
- What if I don't wanna relax?
Suppose I don't wanna do
what you're telling me.
- If that even comes close to happening,
I'm not gonna be very
happy with you, am I?
(car engine roaring)
Uh huh.
There we go.
(hand tapping)
Nothing to worry about.
(eerie music)
Except your boyfriend
left us riding on empty.
Need to stop by a gas station soon.
- He's not my boyfriend.
(John scoffs)
- Not your boyfriend.
What you go up to a place like that
with just anybody who asks you?
- We were just talking.
He was gonna take me for a
burger after school, but hey,
I don't have to explain anything to you.
(John chuckling)
(crickets chirping)
- The reason could be to kidnap the girl.
I mean, not necessarily
Amy Kennedy, but someone.
- That's not his MO.
He usually robs banks.
- And he kills cops, too.
So it's not a big stretch to imagine
he'd snatch someone for cash.
- In any case, he could
be hiding out nearby.
Maybe in the woods near Cotter Creek
or by the old refinery.
- You know more about our
county than you've led on.
(officers talking over each other)
Listen up, people.
I need your attention.
For now, this'll be our
task force command center
for the investigation into
the kidnapping of Amy Kennedy.
This is Special Agent
Megan Saunders of the FBI.
- As of now, you are all
under federal jurisdiction.
Our suspect, John Carl Lowman,
is on the run for robbing
a bank and the killing of an FBI agent.
He's been IDed as the suspect
who has kidnapped Amy Kennedy.
- Now we believe that they
are still in our area.
But right now we're more than
three hours into this investigation.
- We're at a critical point right now
for more than one reason.
The chances of finding
a kidnap victim diminish
drastically after the first 24 hours.
In addition to that, Amy has diabetes.
She's in an unstable condition,
she needs regular insulin
shots and the clock is ticking.
- So, people, we need to move hard
and we need to move fast on this.
- I need a direct line
to the state police.
You don't have to look to
Sheriff Taylor, I'm in charge.
- Just do it, Franklyn.
- And you, I need you to
contact all neighboring
counties and see what
resources they can spare.
We need more bodies and we need them now.
- [Man] Around midnight, the
Midnight Blues with Papa G.
Just an hour away, it's your your guide
to the best new blues
coming out of Illinois.
All your favorite classics will be by
to help you wind things down.
- [John] Get out.
(crickets chirping)
- [Amy] Are you leaving me here?
- Just get out.
(car beeping)
(light dramatic music)
(screw rattling)
Why are you wearing makeup?
- What's wrong with makeup?
- Trying to look older?
- I'm not trying to do anything.
(John scoffs)
- I think you are.
I just think you're
trying to fit in, right?
- Wrong.
- You don't fit in anyway though, do ya?
Trying to run would be a mistake.
- I wasn't going to.
- [John] I know you
were thinking about it.
(license plate rattling)
(horse neighing)
- He's lonely.
(horse snorting)
(John scoffs)
- Who, the horse?
We're freezing our butts out here,
he's in the nice warm
stall, plenty of hay.
Not a worry in the world.
- Depends on who's taking care of him.
Who loves him.
- What do you know about horses?
- I had one.
His name was Buddy.
(John sighs)
- Where we're going there's horses.
- Where?
- You behave and you'll
get to see 'em, okay?
- Can I get back inside?
(John sniffing)
- Just don't try anything, okay?
(car beeping)
(car door slamming)
- So the area that I was mentioning,
it's all crisscrossed by farm roads.
Then there's woodlands
around the outer reaches,
so I'm thinking that if
Lowman goes in there,
well, he'll be like your
basic needle in a haystack.
Still think he's coming
to Belgarde intentionally?
- Just haven't figured out why.
- You never said when it was
you were through here before.
- Well, that was a long time ago.
- Business?
- I have some relatives nearby.
- I've lived here most of my life.
Be anyone I might know?
- I don't think so.
- [Franklyn] Sheriff Taylor.
You have a call on line two.
- [Ray] Thanks.
- Uh, the cell phone
company called and says
that she hasn't made a
call since yesterday,
but we have them monitoring the phones.
- Okay, just keep on it.
- Can I ask you something, Agent Saunders?
- As long as you call me Megan.
- Okay, Megan, well, okay I
know why I signed up to do this
and I do not doubt that,
but you know there's a certain
amount of day-to-day stuff
to deal with and well, I
guess I was just wondering
do you have any advice?
- On figuring out the alpha male?
- Yeah, that about spells it out.
- Just don't get discouraged.
- The FBI must be a
whole different ballpark.
- No, not that much.
They still wanna prove that
they're bigger and stronger.
- Oh.
- There's no law against being
smarter than them, is there?
- No, none that I've read.
- Why did you join up?
(Franklyn sighs)
- Well, it was my sister.
She uh, she was coming
home late one night,
she got car jacked and she was murdered.
- I'm so sorry.
- Thanks.
While you're here if there's
anything that you need, just...
- Thanks.
(phone beeping)
Dad, Megan.
I'm in Belgarde County on a kidnapping.
So far I'm coming up empty.
Listen, I don't have your address,
but I'd like to pick your brain.
(suspenseful music)
(Amy gasps)
- Don't you try anything.
(Amy panting)
- [Amy] Ow.
(light dramatic music)
- No, I don't think anybody saw us.
We need to get gas somewhere else.
(Amy panting)
What's the matter with you?
You okay?
- I'm not feeling well.
I need something to eat.
- Oh, we'll pick something
up when we get gas, okay?
Amy?
Look, I think I'm being
fairly accommodating here.
Okay, when I ask you a
question I expect an answer.
Huh?
(Amy gasps)
- Okay, yes.
- Yes, what?
- I'd like some food.
- You'd like some food what?
- Please.
- Aha, please, good, good.
(suspenseful music)
- So, he starts his criminal
career at the age of 14
by trying to murder his
father with a butcher knife.
I'd say that qualifies him
as having a screw loose.
- Institutionalized till he was 19.
Psych report said he can go off
at anytime and the judge lets him walk.
- Well, there's hanging judges
and there's revolving door judges.
Spare me from the latter.
Thanks, Tony.
So, a series of auto thefts
and petty crimes follow,
a hard time in Arizona and then again
at my favorite getaway, Joliet.
And then he graduates to the big time.
- A series of bank heists.
- And a suspected killer
of a federal agent.
- There's nothing suspect about it.
Lowman pulled the trigger.
- You say that with the conviction
of someone who was there.
- The agent who was shot was my partner.
- Well, that explains some things.
I may just be a country Sheriff
elected every four years
by a bunch of farmers and
loggers, but I know people,
and I knew something was nagging at you.
- It's a nightmare I keep reliving.
- Now, the thing is
when we catch this SOB,
with or without the girl he's looking at
a date with death row.
He's got nothing to lose.
- That's what I'm worried about.
- This is?
- My partner who was shot.
(phone ringing)
- Sheriff Taylor.
(static buzzing)
(lips smacking)
- The way you've been handling
the pressure out there
is nothing short of amazing.
- Pressure's only felt by people
who don't know what they're doing.
- Is that straight out of the manual?
- [Megan] Uh uh.
- An inspiring school teacher?
- My dad.
He also didn't want me to join the Bureau.
- That made you more
determined than ever, huh?
- It's genetic.
I don't think we should be doing this.
- What, getting to know each other?
Dating?
- Well, I don't know, we're
not even out on the field yet.
- Are you really gonna let
Jack Bryant stand between us?
I mean, we both want
the same things, right?
We'll be discrete.
- What does Jack Bryant have against us?
We're just getting to know each other.
(Mark sighs)
- He's my father-in-law.
- You were married to his daughter?
- Bryant's been bribing
me to go back to her.
But look, I have moved on with my life.
And I want you there with me.
(lips smacking)
- [Ray] And he meant something to you?
Agent?
(phone ringing)
- We met at Quantico and then
we were put on the bank detail together.
- So, he was more than just a partner.
- We were together for three years.
- Which makes it personal for
you and that's not healthy.
- I can handle it.
- What's your intent?
- To find Amy Kennedy
and if Lowman's with her,
I'll deal with him after she's safe.
- Fair enough.
The girl's mother is here,
dropping off her insulin.
(officers talking over each other)
- Oh.
This is all we had on hand.
The blue is long lasting,
the yellow is short.
She's gonna need both.
- How long will this last?
- A couple of weeks, maybe a month.
Oh, and I also brought this.
- What is that?
- It's glucose.
Basically sugar water,
she's gonna need this.
Maybe more so than the insulin.
If you, I mean, when you find-
(bottle clinking)
(Carol crying)
- Hey.
- I am so sorry.
- Look, come sit down, sit down.
- I'm so sorry, it's just my nerves.
- I know, I don't know
how you're holding up
as well as you are.
(Carol gasps)
- Amy's all we have.
She's my baby.
Thank you.
Sometimes Amy thinks she's a burden to us,
but oh, she means everything to me.
- Can I get you anything else?
- No, no, thank you.
I should go to the airport
and wait for my husband.
- Before you go, this isn't
going to be enough insulin
to hand out to all our units.
- All right, I'll call Amy's doctor.
- And we'll call the hospital.
Are there any more instructions
I can give to my people?
- Oh, it's just so complicated.
It's not like taking a
spoonful of cough medicine.
Her blood sugar has to be checked first.
Her glucometer should help.
- [Megan] All right, okay.
- [Man] This is 101.1.
Coming up after the break,
your up to the minute news to midnight.
Traffic, weather, together all after this.
(car door slamming)
(seatbelt whirring)
(light dramatic music)
(car door squeaking)
- [John] Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Looks like you had one too many, girl.
- I was just dizzy for a second.
I'm okay.
I'm just hungry.
- Okay.
And remember I've got
a gun under my shirt.
I don't want anyone damaged unnecessarily.
Do you?
- No, I don't.
- Okay.
You speak out of turn, you try to run,
you're the one that's gonna
get hurt and I don't want that
'cause I like you, okay?
(Amy panting)
- Okay.
- Okay, come on.
(door creaking)
- [Man] US-41 Lakeshore driving south.
- What will it be there, folks?
- Uh, vehicle at pump two.
I'm gonna need to fill it.
- Sure thing.
Anything else for you tonight?
- Hm, maybe some snacks?
Hm, huh?
- 580, 594.
Hickory Parkway westbound is slow going
with the ramp to 394 closed.
- Right there.
- You the boss, Jason?
- Night assistant manager.
11:00 to 7:00, I'm your man.
- Ah.
- The I-90, I-95-
- Why don't you, uh,
- Expressway inbound-
- Go see over there,
see if there's anything you'd like, okay?
- [Man] Are closed until further notice.
And only three local lanes are
available in each direction.
- Night assistant manager, huh?
That's a hell of a lot
of responsible, Jason.
- Sometimes it can be.
- Michigan Avenue.
- Huh.
- Or the combination of
the Skyway, Stony Island
and Lakeshore Drive.
The I-90 Chicago Skyway outbound
has scheduled construction
between St. Lawrence Ave.
(sirens wailing)
(dramatic music)
And light south winds
of 15 miles per hour, with a high of 64.
(beads rattling)
Overcast and chance of showers
throughout the day and into the night.
Breaking news now concerning
a stolen black SUV
in the Belgarde County region-
- Oh, I thought you were hungry?
- [Man] With reports that a young girl-
- They don't have much here.
- May be kidnapped.
- I think I just need some sugar.
- [Man] The vehicle was
reported stolen four hours ago-
- You hear that Jason, huh?
Empty shelves, that reflects directly
on your managerial skills.
- We run outta stuff pretty fast.
We're the last stop for 16 miles.
We have a delivery tomorrow though.
- Well, that doesn't help
us right now, does it?
Go outside, fill up the tank, okay?
Remember what I told you
about people getting hurt.
Yeah?
Now, go.
(eerie music)
Go.
- I can't unlock the
pump unless you've paid,
so will that be-
(Amy gasping)
- You know what, I don't
seem to have my wallet
with me tonight, Jason,
so I'd appreciate it if-
(Amy groaning)
- No.
- No?
- Sorry, I can't unlock the
pump unless you've paid.
It's policy, it's story policy.
(suspenseful music)
(Amy sniffling)
- Unlock the pump, Jason.
We need gas.
- I can't.
- Unlock the pump.
(suspenseful music)
Unlock the pump.
(neck cracking)
- We have enough glucose,
but we need more insulin.
Mrs. Kennedy's doctor will
meet you at the hospital.
- [Franklyn] Okay, I'll
pull my car around.
- Can we find her in time?
- We're doing our best.
- This is your area of
expertise, isn't it?
Kidnapping?
I mean, that is why Sheriff
Taylor brought you in.
- I had been working on
the bank robbery detail.
(Carol scoffs)
- You've never worked on
a kidnapping case before?
- This is my first.
I was in the area tracking
the movements of the man
who took Amy and then I
joined up with Sheriff Taylor.
- Oh, can't they send us someone-
- Who knows what they're doing?
- I didn't mean that.
- I know what I'm doing.
I've contacted the FBI
Field Office in Chicago.
There will be more agents coming.
I was trained for this.
(dramatic music)
- It's unlocked.
- Good boy.
Good.
(car door slamming)
(Amy panting)
(phone beeping)
(phone ringing)
- All I want is Amy back in
my arms again, that's all.
(phone ringing)
Amy, Amy is that you honey?
- Mom, Mommy?
Oh, God, something terrible has happened.
(suspenseful music)
(gunshot banging)
(Amy gasps)
- Oh, my God, I heard gunshots.
- Oh, God.
- Amy?
This is Meg Saunders, I'm with the FBI.
I'm gonna try to find you.
Are you alone?
- Yeah.
Yeah, for now.
- Do you know where you are?
- I need to talk with my mother.
- Talk to me.
- Okay.
- Is the man who took you nearby?
- He's inside a gas station.
And there were gunshots.
- Do you know where you are?
- I don't know.
We've been driving around and around.
- [Megan] Are you still
in Belgarde County?
- I don't know, I don't know.
(Amy crying)
- Ask the last time she had her shot.
- [Megan] When was the last
time you had your insulin?
- After school.
- Have you eaten dinner?
- He was gonna take me for a
burger, but we never made it.
- Have you eaten anything?
- I just, I just had a donut and a drink.
- Do you know the name of the gas station?
Do you see any sign?
(suspenseful music)
- It says-
- That's very, very stupid.
- [Megan] Amy, are you there?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, she's here.
(Amy crying)
Who's this?
- This is Special Agent Megan Saunders.
Is this John Lowman?
(Amy crying)
- I'm not gonna answer that.
But I am impressed that the
FBI is handling carjacking now.
- This is not a carjacking,
this is a kidnapping.
You took her against her will.
We need you to let her
go before it's too late.
(dramatic music)
(Amy crying)
- How do you know I have
her here against her will?
Yeah, maybe we're having a good time.
Ain't we, Amy?
Maybe she likes the adventure.
- Has she told you about her condition-
(phone clicking)
- Ow.
- You told me that
you didn't have a phone.
You said you didn't have a phone.
- I forgot I had it with me.
- Oh, yeah, yeah?
(Amy crying)
(phone thudding)
Well, you don't have
one anymore.
- What happened?
(phone beeping)
- She's with Lowman.
He hung up.
- Oh, God.
- What kinda watch is this?
- No.
It's not a watch.
(glucometer beeping)
Please don't hurt me, please.
- Okay, just relax, come on.
- Please, no.
- [John] Get in there.
(car door slamming)
(car engine rumbling)
(tires screeching)
- Whittaker's with the cell carrier now.
Trying to see if we can
pinpoint their signal.
- When I talked to her she
sounded scared to death.
It's been 10 hours since her last shot.
- Yeah, well, even if that
gas station is in the county,
I can guarantee you won't-
- Lowman's not gonna be there
when we get there, but I'm gonna do
what I should have done a long time ago.
I'm gonna go there and-
- You Sheriff Taylor?
- That would be me.
And you are?
- Jack Bryant, Special
Agent Chicago Field Office.
Can we talk?
(dramatic music)
(glucometer beeping)
- What do you mean it's not a real watch?
- It monitors my glucose levels
without me having to prick myself.
I have diabetes.
- You gotta take medicine for that?
- Injections after I eat.
What happened back at the gas station?
- Yeah, with Jason?
The boy took too much
corporate responsibility
on his shoulders.
It's not like we were robbing a bank.
- Why would you do that?
He wasn't even a threat to you.
- Honestly, sometimes I don't
know why I do what I do.
What happens if you don't
take your injections?
- I don't think about it.
I just think about tomorrow.
(dramatic music)
- [Jack] Well, is there a ransom request?
- None so far.
- Then what's the kidnapper's motive?
- It just happened when Lowman's
stolen car ran out of gas,
the new car had a girl in it.
- I'll get to you in a minute.
I trust you've got all your resources
on this case, Sheriff, yes?
- Well, because we're not
a big city department,
doesn't mean we're a bunch of hicks.
- Glad to hear that.
Specifics would be nice.
- Well, fine.
I put out a BOLO alert and-
- Good.
- Called in all off duty personnel,
engaged the state police,
and we start our search
parties at first light.
- While we're standing here,
Lowman could be getting farther away.
The victim is diabetic.
Her condition is severe
if she doesn't have these injections.
- I am sorry to hear that,
but you were on departmental leave, yes?
- That ended a week ago.
I asked the SAC for more
time and it was granted.
- Oh, so, you were freelancing?
You were tracking Lowman like vigilante?
- As soon as I assessed
the situation I called
the Field Office, which
is why you're here.
- Look, would somebody just
tell me who is in charge here.
- Yes, that would be me.
- If anybody knows Lowman, it is me.
I've already set everything in motion.
- You had your opportunity
to take him out, Saunders,
and you failed and an agent was killed.
- I need to see this to the end.
Don't take me off this, Bryant.
I'm asking you not to.
- You know, I've had a long drive.
We'll reconvene in the morning.
- In the morning?
A young girl's life is
hanging in the balance.
Her health is going downhill fast.
- Well, you've said that you have
a search party organized for first light.
We'll reconvene then and you'll
bring me totally up to speed.
I'm gonna be calling the
SAC now and I will tell them
that you will be reporting
for reassignment.
- You're making a mistake, Bryant.
- You already made yours.
You shoulda been suspended or worse.
Goodnight.
- Dammit.
There's a young girl's life in jeopardy
and what we don't need
here is an FBI turf war.
- There is none.
It's over.
(thunder booming)
(light dramatic music)
- I need to know when one of
these cars is gonna be the law.
We're gonna have to
stay off the main roads.
- Going where?
- You'll see.
You're not gonna go and get sick
like you said you were going to, are you?
- If I don't get my insulin, I will.
(dramatic music)
(rain pattering)
(bag rustling)
(somber music)
(keys jingling)
(beer bottle clanking)
(carbonation hissing)
(dramatic music)
- There's no rear entrance.
If Lowman shows there's only
one way in and one way out.
- Well, who's that?
Lowman usually works alone.
- That could be him with
the beanie and the glasses.
- Dispatch, this is 852.
We're at TriState National,
3rd and Melvo, requesting backup.
(dramatic music)
(sirens wailing)
Federal Agents, hold it right there!
(phone ringing)
- [Man] In the Windy City,
more of your favorite
blues all night.
It's after midnight and
we're heading into the vault
with some classics chords from the boys,
and a few jam sessions, my favorite.
(phone ringing)
You got something on your mind?
You pick up the phone
and give Papa G a call.
If you know what the blues are tonight,
keep it here, keep it tight
on the G-spot tonight.
- [Man] Falling with it, haze.
Hey, listen, while you're on the road,
keep an eye out for that stolen black SUV.
We're heading into our number 10.
Still no word on the young-
(dramatic music)
- [Mark] Federal Agents,
hold it right there.
Don't do it, Lowman,
you got no where to go.
(woman screaming)
(suspenseful music)
(gunshot banging)
(muffled woman screaming)
(Megan panting)
(gunshot banging)
(Mark groaning)
- Take the shot, Meg.
(gunshot banging)
(woman screaming)
Take the shot!
(gunshot banging)
- I don't have a direct line of fire.
(woman screaming)
(light dramatic music)
(Megan panting)
Mark!
- [Man] 101.1, you got
the bro on the radio.
Windy City tonight, Danline Expressway
is now a mess with construction.
You construction guys, come on,
how many coffee breaks
do you need out there?
If you're driving a-
♪ A long road coming ♪
(birds squawking)
(car door slamming)
♪ Waiting for the dawn ♪
(door creaking)
(door slamming)
♪ There's just pain ♪
- Hi, Dad.
Mind if I invade your space?
- Please.
As long as you don't preach
to me like you used to.
- I never thought I'd hear back from you.
- Well, I've been busy lately.
- Still going to meetings I hope?
- 96 days sober.
Headed for my personal best.
- What are the Vegas odds on that?
- Better than the money on you.
I hear you stepped in it.
- I hesitated when I
shoulda pulled the trigger.
(gunshot banging)
(somber music)
- It was a civilian or your partner.
- My partner.
- It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
- Hold on, Mark, hold on.
(somber music)
(Megan crying)
And I hit a wall.
Now I'm being hounded by Jack Bryant.
- Oh.
He made a name for himself with
some major busts earlier on.
Media darling for a New York minute.
Riding their pony ever since.
He's um, morally bankrupt.
Has fans in management.
- Well, Mark was killed and he was-
- His son-in-law.
- Ex son-in-law.
How do you know that?
- The Bureau used to be
built on honor and integrity.
Still good people there and
some remember my number.
- Jack Bryant's wrong about me.
- From his point of view
you're a homewrecker.
And you got his son-in-law killed.
- That's not what happened.
They were separated.
- Megan, your pain
doesn't matter to Bryant.
He has too much of his own.
(Megan sighs)
- Why can't I get over this?
(light dramatic music)
I thought while I'm in town
maybe we can do this again.
I could even give you a lift home.
- Next thing you know you'd
be sending Christmas cards,
and who knows where that would lead.
- Yeah, who knows.
(register dinging)
- No.
This Lowman, he's got you hooked, huh?
- I just, I have to find him.
- Go back to the file.
Go over it, go over it again.
There's always something you missed.
Always.
- Well, go over it for what?
I'm done, I'm toast.
- How much do you want this?
- I wanted it bad, for Mark.
- I could make a call above Bryant.
- Well, I've never asked you
for anything before, Dad.
I'm not gonna ask now.
- I guess that makes us even.
Because I've never given you anything.
(light dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
(car door slamming)
- Usually works alone, but
not on the TriState Bank job.
We engaged with his accomplice,
Mark is hit while I'm radioing.
Lowman and his accomplice
escape in separate vehicles.
- [Donald] There's always
something you've missed.
Always.
(Megan sighs)
(light dramatic music)
- Known associates.
Farrah Wyatt, Daniel Campos A.K.A Frogman,
Victor Kirk A.K.A. Captain Kirk.
(phone beeping)
Franklyn, Meg Saunders.
I need a favor.
I gave Sheriff a copy of Lowman's file
and there's a list of known associates.
I need to run locations on them.
When?
And word on Amy?
Where are you?
(light dramatic music)
(body bag zipper buzzing)
(camera clicking)
- We're certain this is the
station Amy made the call from.
- How certain?
- This is where we found her cell phone.
- Yeah, the night manager was shot inside.
He was just a kid, looked
like he didn't have a chance.
- There's a security camera right there.
Is there one inside?
- Yeah, we've already pulled the tapes.
- And there's a monitor, too.
- You know, I had just
about given up on you.
Something told me you
wouldn't go away quietly.
- Where's Bryant.
- Spoke to him after
Franklyn talked to you.
Thought we owed you a heads up.
(tires screeching)
Ut oh.
- I thought we had your bacon settled?
- What are you gonna
do, Bryant, arrest me?
- Well, you are impeding a
Federal investigation, Saunders.
- No, you are standing
in the way of our finding
a kidnapped girl with a medical emergency.
If this girl dies I'll make certain
my report details your interference.
Including a catnap you
took when those hours
could have made a difference.
(phone ringing)
- Bryant.
Yes, I'll wait.
SA Jack Bryant here, sir.
I understand.
Of course I understand.
Crucial it is to finding
this kidnap victim.
Agent Saunders' input
is definitely welcome.
We're on this together.
In fact, we're sharing a
significant lead as I speak.
Thank you, sir, for your support.
I really, really appreciate it.
It must be nice having
friends in high places, huh?
Is that what you do?
- You know, maybe somebody just recognized
the important thing here
is finding Amy Kennedy.
- Couldn't agree more, what have you got?
- Franklyn, cue up the tapes and let's go.
- Let's go.
(light dramatic music)
(door creaking)
(crows cawing)
(light dramatic music)
- She doesn't look like she's
under any duress at all.
She could be with him willingly.
- She could be afraid of him,
and in that case she would
do exactly as he says.
It could be the Patty Hearst Syndrome,
she could feel he's her only lifeline.
- She doesn't look very sick to me.
- When I talked to her she was weak.
- Really?
- She told her mother
she wasn't feeling well.
She hasn't had her last
insulin shot since yesterday.
- [Man] Hey, it's the bro at 101.1,
seven o'clock in the Windy City.
Report just in.
A young gas attendant found
shot dead in Belgarde County.
This is a big story-
(flare hissing)
Police have setup roadblocks
around the county.
Asking for your support.
- We're gonna need to make a detour.
- If you've seen an SUV,
it could be burgundy,
it could be black, white male.
(flare hissing)
Trust me, guys.
Do not go anywhere near this man-
- What's the matter with you?
- Because he's considered
armed and very dangerous.
- I'm tired and I'm thirsty.
(glucometer beeping)
- Let me see.
What's that mean?
- My blood sugar's too high.
- Here, you should drink.
Drink some of this.
Have some of it.
Come on, come on, you
said you were thirsty.
Drink, hey!
You need one of those injections.
That's what you need.
(light dramatic music)
(car engine rumbling)
(birds chirping)
(somber music)
- The kid behind the counter
is frightened of Lowman.
- Yeah, that's him showing
the gun under the shirt.
- Amy's gone during this?
- Yeah, he let her walk out the door.
- She could've run.
That's when you gotta run.
- There is no place for miles.
- She could've run.
- And she is weak.
- Well, that explains
why we found the phone.
- It doesn't explain where she is
and we are running out of time.
- All right.
- [Newsman] The disappearance
of a Belgarde girl
remains a mystery this morning.
Amy Kennedy, a junior
at Belgarde high school
was abducted at gunpoint late last night
by a John Carl Lowman.
Lowman is a suspect in
the coldblooded murder
of a Belgarde gas station-
- Unbelievable.
- [Newsman] Manager off
the north south interstate.
He's also wanted for a shooting
death of a federal agent
during a bank robbery several
months ago near Chicago.
You know, we do a feature
on the radio program.
You know it's 101 with the brother.
We have a tool of the day.
This guy has got to be
the tool of the day.
Put him in the toolbox, man.
God, this whole entire town
is going crazy over this.
We gotta get in to see one his-
(horse neighing)
(light dramatic music)
- What's going on here?
- This girl's sick.
- Oh, I'm Dr. Lycar.
This is a veterinary
clinic, not a hospital.
- Yeah, she needs
insulin, you got insulin?
- Yeah, I mean, for the care of animals.
But it's an emergency supply, so.
- If she doesn't take her
insulin, she's gonna die.
So I'd say that's an
emergency wouldn't you?
(horse neighing)
- I'm sorry, I can't help you.
I'm not licensed for what you...
Aw, man.
(suspenseful music)
Hey, you know what, you don't understand
because yes, I have
insulin, but it's in bulk.
It's not in individual doses.
And I don't know the patient's dosage.
It could be more harmful for her-
- Look, I don't have
time to argue with you.
Where do you wanna do this?
- It's right in here.
(horse neighing)
(light dramatic music)
- All right, so he arrives with the girl
without warning and just breaks in?
- According to Dr. Lycar's report,
he held a gun to the doctor
and forced him to give
her the insulin shot.
- [Jack] And he left with the same SUV?
- [Ray] Doctor gave me a
description, it's the same vehicle.
- So, he kills a service
station manager for no reason,
but risks getting caught
to get Amy insulin.
Why?
- There is nothing about
this guy that's made any sense so far.
- Maybe he's formed an attachment to her?
- They could be miles from here by now.
- They could've been miles
right after the kidnapping.
Instead he goes in almost a circle
from the kidnapping to the gas station.
- Yeah, it's as if he's-
- He's like biding time.
- Right.
- Why?
- Why is he here in the first place?
Where was he headed?
And then he breaks his pattern
and makes a direct line
to the vet's office,
giving her the shot there.
- Oh, before I forget.
I was able to run last known associates.
- Captain Kirk.
- As in "Star Trek."
- As in Victor Kirk.
He served time with Lowman at Joliet.
And he matches the description
of the accomplice who
did the bank robbery.
- Well, his last known
address was at Glendon Avenue.
That's at the farm nearby the refinery.
- Let's get back this, all right?
So, from the service station to here.
The route means he's going
north to the interstate.
- Not necessarily, I have a hunch.
- No, no more hunches, Saunders.
- Just hear me out.
The interstate runs north and south.
What makes you so sure he's going north?
- You wanna debate this?
Why is everything a debate with you?
- There are hospitals and
pharmacies near to Chicago,
instead he risks getting caught
and gets the shot near here.
- Well, you know what?
Amy got her insulin, which gets her out
of danger and buys us more time.
- Only the doctor didn't
exactly know what he was doing,
and she could be in more danger.
- You know, Saunders,
against my better judgment,
I was ordered by my superiors
to allow you into this
investigation again.
You are not running the show.
We are going north.
- To the interstate?
- Exactly.
Is there any objections?
- You're calling the shots, Agent Bryant.
- All right, I want the State
Patrol to meet us there.
Are you clear on all of this?
- I think I know where he's headed.
- Put it in your report.
Let's go.
(Ray sighs)
- That guy has got all the
instincts of a blind squirrel.
- I just wanna find Amy Kennedy.
If he's right, I'm happy.
- Right behind you, Sheriff.
Oh, wait, Megan, you're
not coming with us?
- Bryant and I are just gonna
go back and forth like this.
It's not gonna help us find her.
- It's more than that.
- I think I know why he's in Belgarde.
- You figure it's to
hook up with this Kirk?
- That's why he's been here
all night treading water.
- Yeah, but that's a lot of
trouble when you're on the run
just to hook up with an old buddy.
- An accomplice, if Victor Kirk
was in on the bank robbery,
the money was never recovered.
- And you figure Kirk has it?
- If he took off with the
money, it's over $200,000.
- Well, good luck to you.
If you need anything
just radio us for backup.
(light dramatic music)
(birds chirping)
(car engine rumbling)
- There.
What did I tell you, horses, huh?
There they are.
What's the matter with you?
I thought, I thought you loved horses?
- I do, I do.
- All right, you wanna, wanna
get out and take a look?
- I can't, my legs hurt
and my eyes are getting really blurry.
- I thought you'd be okay
if you got your shot?
- It only worked for a while.
(glucometer beeping)
My blood sugar's gone down again.
- You know what?
Here, we're gonna take care of that.
But first I'm gonna have a little talk
with Kirk about a debt he owes me.
(car engine rumbling)
(suspenseful music)
- [Newsman] There's a break
here up to the minute news
to eight o'clock with the latest.
And Bob, my nextdoor neighbor,
please, what the heck was
going on there last night?
If you're still-
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
- [Mark] Federal Agents,
hold it right there!
Don't do it, Lowman,
you got nowhere to run.
(dramatic music)
(gunshot banging)
(woman screaming)
(Mark groaning)
(gunshots banging)
(body thudding)
(Megan panting)
(gunshot banging)
(metal clanking)
(woman whimpering)
(gunshot banging)
- The shot, Meg.
Take the shot.
- [Megan] I don't have
a direct line of fire!
(gunshot banging)
(dramatic music)
(heartbeat pounding)
(Mark sighs)
(Megan panting)
(somber music)
Mark!
(Mark groaning)
(suspenseful music)
Agent down, Agent down.
Help is coming, Mark.
(heartbeat pounding)
(Mark sighs)
(birds chirping)
(light dramatic music)
(door creaking)
(suspenseful music)
(glucometer ringing)
(beer splashing)
(Kirk spitting)
- John, is that you?
- I came for what you owe me.
- Who's that?
- Nevermind about her.
- She looks real bad.
And what's that beeping?
(gun clicks)
- The money, Kirk.
(suspenseful music)
(Kirk stuttering)
- I didn't think you
were coming back, Johnny.
(suspenseful music)
- I didn't call you
'cause I didn't trust you.
Now, you wouldn't be trying
to shaft me out of my split, would you?
- No, please.
I got your money, all right?
But, but not here.
I wouldn't be that dumb.
- Where?
- Hidden where no one can find it.
- Oh.
- Your share and mine.
I, I can show you where it-
- Tell me first.
(glucometer beeping)
(Megan sighs)
(gun clicking)
(suspenseful music)
(gunshot banging)
(horse neighing)
(birds chirping)
(horses neighing)
(car door slamming)
(horse neighing)
(light dramatic music)
(glucometer beeping)
(suspenseful music)
(door creaking)
(door thudding)
(glucometer beeping)
(dramatic music)
- Move and you're dead.
- I need to do this.
I need to do it now.
- You're that agent I
talked to on the phone.
- She'll die if I don't do this.
- Look, you don't do
nothin' unless I say you do.
- Her blood sugar is dangerously low.
I need to give her this shot.
- I already gave her a shot.
- That was insulin.
She needs glucose.
Hang on.
It's Megan, I talked to you on the phone.
Can you hear me?
- Wait a second, wait a second,
I said you don't do
anything unless I say so.
- You must care about her
or she would be dead by now.
- Is anyone here with you?
(glucometer beeping)
Answer me!
- No!
No, I came here alone.
If you shoot me she'll die.
You need to let me give her
this injection and get
her to the hospital.
- Hey...
I've seen you before.
- I get that a lot.
- No, no, no, no, no,
I've seen you before.
Where was that?
- Let me concentrate.
- Fine.
I'm leaving, but if you try to follow me,
I will kill you.
(glucometer beeping)
(door creaking)
- Hey, Amy, it's gonna be okay.
Amy, Amy?
Can you hear me?
(dramatic music)
(gun clicking)
(car door thudding)
(car engine rumbling)
(dramatic music)
(nails clipping)
(water dripping)
Are you feeling better?
- Yeah, thanks.
Did you tell my parents.
- I'm gonna call them right now.
Did he hurt you?
- No, he was actually okay to me.
But I know he did other things
and you let him get away.
- You are what's important, Amy.
We can always catch up with him later.
Did he say where he was going?
- He's going after some money.
I heard the other guy say that
it was at the old refinery.
- Anything else?
- Something about a heating vent.
(water dripping)
(dramatic music)
(car door slamming)
(gun clicking)
(muffled police radio)
- Your parents are gonna
meet you at the hospital
and I'll check on you later.
- Thanks.
Be careful.
- I will, sweetheart.
- Are you gonna hurt him?
- [Woman] 2214, Tom.
- Bryant.
- Go ahead.
- I found Amy, she's on
her way to the hospital.
She's gonna be okay.
- Wait, wait, you went
in alone, without backup?
That's totally against protocol.
- She was virtually comatose.
- And Lowman?
- He's on his way to the old refinery.
- All right, Saunders,
you hold your position.
Did you hear me?
We will contain the area.
I will organize a SWAT team, over.
- There's no time, over and out.
- Saunders!
(gun clicks)
Turn it around.
We're going the wrong way.
(tires screeching)
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
(metal clanking)
(light dramatic music)
(metal walkway clanking)
(John groaning)
(pliers clicking)
(metal walkway clanking)
(air vent rattling)
(light dramatic music)
(bag rustling)
(metal walkway clanking)
(money thudding)
(money rustling)
(metal walkway clanking)
(suspenseful music)
- Lowman!
You helped saved Amy's life,
at first I thought about
cutting you some slack.
- But that's not in your nature, is it?
- Why did you take her with you?
- Who knows why we do what we do.
- I think you took her for insurance.
You thought you wouldn't get
shot if she was in the car.
- Yeah, whatever.
- But then things started to change.
You started to care for her, didn't you?
- You know what, think
what you wanna think.
Okay?
But that's not why you're here, is it?
- I'm here to take you in
for robbery and murder.
You shot and killed my partner!
- Now you wanna kill me, don't you?
(suspenseful music)
You know it was me or him.
And now it's you or me.
(suspenseful music)
(gunshot banging)
(door creaking)
(light dramatic music)
(John panting)
(metal walkway clanking)
(light dramatic music)
(Megan sniffling)
(metal walkway clanking)
(light dramatic music)
(gunshot banging)
(Megan gasps)
(dramatic music)
- [Mark] Take the shot, Meg!
Take the shot!
(suspenseful music)
(gunshots banging)
(John groaning)
(body thudding)
(gravel crunching)
(car engine rumbling)
(birds squawking)
(frogs croaking)
(water splashing)
(light music)
- Oh.
(Donald groaning)
(Megan sighs)
This could set a very bad precedence.
- All I had to do was
call the county tax roll
and find out where you lived.
- Well, uh, don't just stand there.
Grab a pole and the bait box.
(light music)
(water splashing)
The girl is okay?
- She's lucky to be alive.
(fishing reel clicking)
- Ballistics, they come through?
- The bullets taken from
the gas station manager
and Victor Kirk match the
bullets taken from Mark.
- How do you feel about it?
- What?
- Being able to pull the
trigger when you had to.
(Megan sighs)
- I thought it would make me feel better.
- And now?
- I don't know how I feel.
Like I finished a job, you know,
sense of completion but nothing more.
- Good.
That's how you're supposed to feel.
(fishing reel clicking)
- I could get used to it.
- Oh, don't, please.
(Megan laughing)
Who knows where that could lead.
- Yeah, who knows.
(gentle music)
(bird squawking)
(fishing reel clicking)
(blues music)
♪ When love walks out, the blue walk in ♪
♪ That's when your heartaches begin ♪
♪ Nothing goes right
when love goes wrong ♪
♪ You sit at home listening
to those old sad songs ♪
♪ You can't sleep at night ♪
♪ You just can't win ♪
♪ When love walks out, the blues walk in ♪
♪ You just wish that you
were back together again ♪
♪ She's got someone new
and you feel so blue ♪
♪ You only wish that she
was thinking of you ♪
♪ The blues have got you
in that downward spin ♪
♪ 'Cause when love walks
out, the blues walk in ♪