[ Swing music playing ]
Mama, mama,
look at me!
Look at me!
So this is
your first dance.
Don't let him
hold you too tight.
Mama!
Look at Sandra, Leona.
Isn't she beautiful?
You should be so beautiful
when you get her age.
Man:
Good morning, Leona.
Leona:
Good morning.
Now when the jury
comes in,
I want you to remain
composed, regardless.
Understood?
And after the verdict's
been read--
they don't know me.
They don't know
who I am.
They don't know what I am.
They don't know
what I've done.
They're gonna come in
and they're gonna pass
judgment on me.
- That's the system.
- Well, it stinks.
You think I'm worried
about what people
think of me?
I've been judged
by the best of 'em;
by the worst of 'em.
As far as I'm concerned,
it don't mean squat.
There she is!
[ Reporters clamoring ]
[ All shouting questions ]
- Any predictions, Leona?
- You think you'd be prosecuted
if you were a man?
- Absolutely not.
- No comment, please.
If I were a man,
they would've said
it was good business.
Do you still think
only the little people
should pay taxes?
- I never--
- Leona! Please,
will you let US through?
Hey, Leona,
if you need a job,
I got a coffee shop
just down the block.
Oh yeah?
I'd be the best
waitress you ever had.
You'd be lucky
to get me.
Leona, how's Harry?
When's he coming in?
- Female reporter: Leona.
- Male reporter: Miss Helmsley.
The jury's still out,
thank you.
Do you still believe
you're nothing but
a scapegoat
for other self-interested
individuals?
I'll be right out.
Leona, is Harry going
to be here for the reading
of the verdict?
- Get out!
- Is it--
get the hell out!
Woman:
Hi, Leona.
Excuse me.
I'm Joe lubin.
Would you care
to dance?
Sure.
You know,
I've watched
you here before.
Oh?
You come in with
some girlfriends,
dance a few dances,
and then you leave
by yourself.
I'm married.
So am I.
If you're married,
why do you come here?
These afternoon dances
are to pick up somebody.
Or just to dance.
[ Chuckles ]
Let's have dinner
together.
I can't.
Leo.
Well, I've been
shopping all day.
Are we still
on for dinner?
I called the house
already, Leo.
The babysitter's there.
Jay is fine.
All right.
Gatsby's, 8:00.
Mm-hmm.
Hi, Jay,
it's mommy.
Yes.
Did Rebecca
give you dinner yet?
No no no.
I don't wanna
talk to her.
Just be sure you do
what she tells you.
Yes, mommy and daddy
will be home later.
Well, we love
you too.
And mama called
while you were out,
and I expect her
to ask how Jay is.
You would think
she didn't have
a grandson,
because all she can
talk about is Sylvia
and her Insulin,
and how Sylvia
had a reaction
last night
and thank god
Sandra was there
and what would she do
without Sandra.
She wants me
to drive Sylvia
to the doctor.
Leo: Why not?
You've got a car.
Leona:
That's not
the point, Leo.
Leo:
What is the point?
Forget it.
Be right back.
Should I write this off
to coincidence?
I think maybe destiny.
My husband plays
gin rummy every
Saturday night.
I'll make
a reservation
at the Pierre.
Dinner at 7:00.
Have a good
evening.
Happy anniversary.
Six months tonight.
[ Chuckles ]
How you feeling?
Comfortable.
Comfortable?
[ Laughs ]
Comfortable is the best
feeling I've ever had.
Why have I never
seen you excited?
Why?
- I get excited.
- You get angry.
But isn't that
excitement?
You know what I mean.
I've never seen
you really happy.
I've never seen you
let go of yourself.
You seem to live
off of other people's
reactions to you.
Leo gives me $75
a week house money.
If you gave me
the same amount--
if you gave me
$75 a week,
I wouldn't have
to take Leo's money.
to sleep with
him anymore.
After all,
I can't give
him taxation
without representation.
Don't deprive him.
He's your husband.
Don't I make you happy?
Yes.
Do you have
any complaints?
I want to hear
you say you love me.
I love you.
And feel it.
When I sleep with Leo,
I feel like i'm
committing adultery.
If I divorce him,
will you marry me?
Yes or no?
Oh.
See how easy that is?
Sandra, stop picking.
- Now hold still.
- Stop it.
Isn't she beautiful,
mama?
- She was beautiful
at her first wedding.
- Thank you, mama.
They're waiting
for US, Leona.
Leona: So what's
the problem, mama?
You don't like Joe?
Sure, I like Joe.
- But he's not as rich
as Sandra's husband, right?
- Leave it alone, Leona.
Joe's got a lot
of money, mama.
More than Leo had.
- Sandra: What's
the difference?
- You love him?
- Did you love papa
when you married him?
- That's different.
It was tradition.
I feel sorry for Joe.
Mama!
Everybody's waiting.
Leona:
I'll be right there.
Leave US alone
for a minute,
will you?
Leona.
Jay, show your aunts
where to sit now.
- Sure.
Aunt Sylvia?
- You're such a doll.
You're wasting
your breath here.
Go.
All right, mama.
What is so wrong with me
that one day
out of my life
you can't even give me
the same attention
or approval
that you give Sandra?
Or even Sylvia?
- Sylvia's sick, she--
- Sylvia's fat!
- A diabetic
needs special--
- I need too!
Maybe that's the problem.
You need too much.
Leona rosenthol
needs it all.
And nobody's got
that much to give.
[ Door opens ]
Mama, come on.
I'll be right there.
Go ahead.
You're jealous of me,
aren't you?
You have always
been jealous of me.
You wasted your life
in the ghetto.
You just sat back,
and you let the poverty
wash over you.
Well, I am not gonna
wind up like you.
I am not gonna
wind up out of breath
in a fourth-floor
walkup.
That is the difference
between you and me.
You've just
accepted your life,
and you hate the fact
that I won't.
I wish you
happiness, Leona.
As much as I've
had in my life
that you think
I've wasted.
- All right, Joe,
we'll see you outside.
- All right.
- Are you sure you don't
want help with this?
- No, I got this one.
You'll get the next one.
Excuse me, sir.
I don't want
to embarrass you,
but occasionally
people like to steal
the silver salt-shakers.
Really?
I would be glad
to put it on your bill.
Well, wait a minute.
We didn't steal, uh--
why would we?
Let me check with
my friends first.
Of course.
The maitre d'
just stopped me.
He told me that--
well, he said
one of US took some
silver salt shakers.
- That's ridiculous.
- Well, that's what
I told him,
but he insists.
The fact is,
they're gone.
Man: But we certainly
don't need to steal
salt shakers,
none of US.
Leona?
I don't have them.
- You charge them to me?
- Very well, sir.
You shouldn't
have paid him.
They don't know
I have them.
They don't know.
You should have
just denied it.
They can't prove it.
Lumberton,
north Carolina?
The dye company
I bought is down there.
We'll have to live
there for a while.
There is not a chance
in hell I am gonna live
in lumberton.
- We have to.
- Joe, I would divorce
you first.
I thought you would.
And you still did it?
Yes.
That's abandonment.
I will take you
for every cent.
No, you won't.
You're refusing
to come with me,
remember?
I wouldn't
worry about it.
You're a beautiful
woman, Leona.
You have a way
of making men like me
feel handsome.
We'll pay almost
anything to feel
like that.
Almost anything.
There'll always be
some man somewhere
who's willing to give
you whatever you want
just to have you
in his bed.
I don't need
your damn wallet, Joe.
I will do just fine
on my own.
If I could stay
married to you,
I can do anything.
[ Door slams ]
- Excuse me.
- May I help you?
The whole city
is gonna go co-op.
Listen to me.
Listen to me!
The time is gonna come
when living in Manhattan
is gonna be like living
in a private community--
only for the rich.
Woman:
Excuse me,
miss Roberts?
Hold on a minute.
Well?
I think there's
a young man to see you.
You think?
He's asking for
a Leona rosenthol.
I told him we have a Leona,
but her name is Roberts.
Shall I ask him
to leave?
I'll call you back.
- Hi.
- Hi, Jay.
I'm gonna take you
for an elegant lunch.
Great.
This is it?
This is how you
come to see me?
Where's your blazer?
Of course they know
I have a son.
They just don't know
how old you are.
Jay:
How old do they
think I am?
Leona: Jay,
I needed the job,
so I told them
I had a son to support,
one that was young enough
to be in the free-lunch
program at school.
There's no free-lunch
program in college.
There is in grade school.
Oh, mother!
How old do they
think you are?
Younger than springtime.
[ Both laughing ]
So what's up?
I'm getting married.
- You can't be.
- Why not?
You're only
eight years old.
- Oh!
- [ Both laugh ]
- Is he in?
- Yes.
Would you ask
if I could see him,
please?
Whom shall I say
is calling?
Rosenthol or Roberts?
Just buzz him, honey.
- [ Intercom buzzes ]
- Yes?
Secretary: Leona Roberts
is here to see you,
Mr. Nederland.
Yeah, send her in.
Leona.
- Mr. Nederland.
- Sit down.
Thank you.
You're looking
marvelous today.
I tell the others,
"look after yourself
the way Leona does,
- and you'll be
a success here."
- Oh, well, I try.
After all,
sales is image
and you have
the right image.
Well, I'm more than image,
Mr. Nederland.
I've got experience.
I started here a year ago
as a receptionist.
Now I have
my real-estate license,
and I'm one of
the best producers
in this office,
and I did it
all on my own.
I'm well aware
of your record.
Then make me
the sales agent
for the park cinq.
[ Chuckles ]
You are hungry,
aren't you?
Park cinq is
a test case for every
co-op in New York.
If we can sell
the park cinq,
every landlord,
every apartment,
will be lined up
to convert.
And I can sell those
apartments faster
than anybody
in this office
and you know it.
Have you seen these?
Pictures of
my new apartment?
No.
- Oh, the dining room?
- Mm-hmm.
That's very nice.
This is the library.
Mmm.
Very nice.
What do you think
of the bedroom?
I don't see it.
You'll just have
to come up and see
it then, won't you?
It's got mirrors
on the walls and ceiling.
Come on, come on,
come on!
It will take me
just one second.
Thank you.
The bedroom.
I'm sure that's
your main--
I heard about you guys.
Yeah, I heard about
you all the way
back east.
Go on in.
I'll be right in there.
Get my purse, please.
Could you get me
my purse, please?
I'll be right there.
Thank you very much.
Some of you had the privilege
of working under me
at the park cinq,
and you made
a lot of money.
Well...
This building
is a new challenge,
and I expect
each and every
one of you
to meet that challenge,
because your record
reflects on mine.
- [ Door opens ]
- Man: Excuse me!
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Whoa whoa whoa.
Who are you,
the delivery boy?
Yeah, you're
the warden?
That's right, baby.
And if you're
working for me,
you're late
and may be fired.
Well, first of all,
I'm late because
there was a fire
on the b.M.T.,
and secondly,
you're not gonna
fire me
because I'm gonna
be your best salesman.
Now, where's my desk?
And I guess
that's yours,
so let's see.
That oughta do it.
Do what?
I hear you're very good
at snapping your fingers.
This way, we can't
see each other.
You won't have to snap,
and I won't have
to ignore you.
We're gonna
get along just fine.
Your tie is too wide.
And in the right light,
your earrings could
signal the entire
seventh fleet.
Leona Roberts.
Paul summerton.
[ Ballroom music playing ]
- Which one is he?
- He's married, Leona.
I don't care.
Nederland
will be jealous.
[ Chuckles ]
Hmm.
Table number 11.
See the man
on the left?
Mustache
with glasses.
See him?
Yeah.
Wish me luck.
He's the one
who's gonna need it.
Be right back.
If you take
Roosevelt island
as an example...
Easy access
to Manhattan
for commuters.
It's a gold mine.
Just wait.
- Mr. Helmsley?
- Yes?
I'm Leona Roberts.
Would you care
to dance?
I hear you're the best.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
You've taken lessons.
No, I just follow.
Something tells me,
miss Roberts,
that you never
"just followed"
in your life.
That's because
I never found anybody
who could lead.
Been a long time
since I've enjoyed
myself so much.
Thank you,
miss Roberts.
You're welcome,
Mr. Helmsley.
So when are
you two kids
tying the knot?
Oh, stop it.
I'll tell you, baby,
it is like meeting
Joe DiMaggio.
Harry Helmsley?
Yeah, I mean it.
It's true!
It's my dream.
He's my hero.
- Harry Helmsley?
- Harry Helmsley.
Harry Helmsley owns
more of Manhattan
than any single man
since the Indians
sold it.
He is self-made,
he's clever,
he's a great dancer.
A perfect gentleman.
Very attractive.
- Too bad he's married.
- So was your last husband.
Leo was never
married before.
I'm not talking about Leo.
I'm talking about Joe.
There was no Joe.
Joe lubin, Leona,
your second husband.
I was married once
to Leo panzirer,
the father of my son.
Aha.
So you're rewriting
your resume, huh?
That's right.
And if you keep
my secrets,
I'll keep yours.
I hope you'll both
be very happy.
[ Both laugh ]
You know something?
I think we will.
Man: She's considered to be
one of the leading real-estate
brokers in the city,
certainly a leader
in converting rentals
into co-ops
and both
"the New York times"
and "the post" have done
profiles on her.
- [ Intercom buzzes ]
- Yes?
Secretary: Excuse me,
Mr. Helmsley,
but a miss Leona Roberts
is here to see you.
She doesn't have
an appointment,
but she insists
on seeing you.
I'll bet she does.
Show her in.
Thank you, Ron.
Good work.
You're welcome, sir.
Mr. Helmsley,
I presume.
Miss Roberts.
Woman: This is all
so confusing.
Woman #2: I know.
Okay, let me explain
it to you, all right?
Under state law,
if a landlord wants
to convert his buildings
from rentals to co-ops,
he needs 35%
of his tenants
to agree.
Now if he gets
the 35%,
then those that
don't want to buy
can be evicted,
their apartments
sold right out from
under them.
But listen,
if they don't get
the percentage they need,
then they can't go co-op,
and we get to keep
our apartments.
- Woman: That's not
what they told me.
- Who?
Miss Roberts.
Her.
According to her,
I could lose my apartment
in 30 days.
All I said was
it was smart to buy
your apartment
at the buyout
price now.
She said I could
get evicted.
It's true.
I'm trying
to protect you.
I can't afford
to buy my apartment.
The banks don't
give loans on co-ops.
It'd take all my savings.
I'm on a fixed income.
If I lose my apartment,
where do I go?
Wait, now everybody,
listen, okay?
Co-op conversions
have been happening
all over the city
and up until now,
tenants have run scared,
signing over
their apartments
out of fear.
But now we are
organizing.
We have a tenants'
committee,
and I assure you
that if we stand
together,
we will win.
- Okay?
- [ Applause and cheering ]
The tenants
voted US down.
What's worse,
it happened in
two other buildings
that Harry put me
in charge of.
I never had a failure
with nederland.
Now it's happened
three times in a row.
Don't sweat it.
I know of an opening
if you need a job.
Oh, honey, Harry would
never fire me now.
It's much too late
for that.
[ Doorbell chimes ]
Well?
What do you think?
Beautiful,
just beautiful.
I've never ever
felt this way before.
You're the most beautiful
thing I've ever--
shh.
You deserve it, Harry.
You're the king.
Leona:
Good morning, mama.
Look what
I got you.
Your favorites.
And...
Cotton.
What do you think?
Hmm?
Perfect for spring.
Did I tell you, mama?
Jay is divorcing Myrna,
gonna marry some girl
I don't even know.
[ Chuckles ]
But you'd be
proud of me.
I am working for
Harry Helmsley.
He owns almost
all of New York,
and I am his
best saleswoman.
I've even been
written up
in "the New York times."
Yeah, your little girl.
Mama,
remember when you told me
nothing would ever
be enough for me?
Maybe you were right,
but is that so bad?
I mean, I've
always gotten
almost everything
I went after.
Almost everything.
But all my life,
the one thing I wanted
Was for you
to look at me first.
But I've always
been the last--
the last.
I could never figure out
what I did wrong.
Mama?
Mama!
Look at me.
Do you see me?
Do you know it's me?
Mama.
Harry: As you can see,
my wife Eve and I
have taken
the top two floors
of the park Lane hotel
and converted them
into a 10-room duplex
with a pool
on the top floor.
Beautiful,
don't you think?
The park Lane
is the first luxury hotel
to be built in Manhattan
in seven years.
There are 47 stories,
640 rooms,
and it's the tallest structure
on central park south.
I want you to know
the credit all goes
to my wife Eve.
That's all true.
Come here.
Come on.
Eve is a quaker.
Quakers tend to stay
out of the limelight.
Quakerism teaches you
to stay in the background,
not boast about
what you have--
like a good husband.
Park Lane is
Eve Helmsley's hotel.
They're both
pretty special,
don't you think?
Now, if you'll
follow US, we'll
take you to the pool.
Eve: Harry gets
his exercise
by swimming.
He loves to swim
every morning.
- I prefer walking.
- On water, no doubt.
Ooh, you are acting
like a jealous schoolgirl,
and on a woman your age,
it's not quite becoming.
- I don't know
why I like you.
- Oh yes, you do.
I'm the only one who
knows that inside that
rough exterior of yours,
there's an even
rougher one on the--
I know your game,
I know your next move.
I can call foul
even before you
hit the ball.
Keep me your friend, Leona.
You don't want me
walking behind you.
I'm gonna get him.
You are looking at
one very determined broad
who is gonna knock
a quaker queen off
her throne.
Miss Roberts,
you can't go in there.
Mr. Helmsley
is in conference.
Lunchtime.
Excuse US, gentlemen.
Leona, we're right in
the middle of a meeting.
It can wait.
You know what time
it is, Harry?
It's 10 minutes
after 1:00.
That's right, so?
From now on, lunchtime
is at 1:00 sharp.
- Excuse US,
gentlemen.
- Harry?
Sorry.
Maybe we can finish
this off after lunch.
Skim milk,
vitamins,
fruit group,
and skinless
breast of chicken.
[ Laughs ]
Lee, this is all
very nice of you,
but you can't just
bust into my office
like this.
Harry, do you know
how attractive you are?
No.
You're tall, you got
a great physique,
you're quick,
you're alert,
you got power.
But you gotta start
taking care of yourself.
I'm not talking
about swimming.
I know you do that
every morning.
I am talking about
a maintenance schedule--
eating properly.
Look at this chicken breast.
So your body knows
that it can depend
upon you
to take care of it.
I baked that this morning.
So from now on,
lunch is at 1:00 sharp.
Dinner is at 8:00.
Not 9:00,
not 7:00.
8:00.
But I have meetings,
obligations to fulfill.
The only obligation
you have is to keep
yourself healthy and fit.
Please don't
fight me in this.
You are so adorable.
No, not now, Harry.
Now you eat.
Come, darling.
[ Laughing ]
Want me to cut
that for you?
There, my sweetheart.
Here.
Eat.
65 signatures?
That's four more
than we needed.
Well, file the papers
immediately.
No, now.
Right now.
- Secretary:
Ms. Roberts?
- No calls.
- But there's
a Mr. Benjamin schecter--
- I said no calls.
Are you deaf
or you stupid?
Do that again
and you're fired.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Roberts is in
a meeting at the moment.
May I take a message?
It's not 1:00 yet,
is it?
I did it, Harry.
345 east 56th street
went co-op.
65 tenants signed.
Four more than we needed.
It's a birthday present
just for you.
That's wonderful!
Wonderful!
You're wonderful.
Lock the door, Harry.
I've got another
present for you.
I gave Sylvia
all of mama's furniture.
I hope you don't mind.
No, she needs it.
Besides, she has
no taste.
I was wondering
if you wanted mama's watch.
No.
You keep it.
Besides, she always
wanted you to have
it anyhow.
I love him.
I'm good for him,
and he knows it.
You should see US
dance together.
It's as if we've
been dancing together
all our lives.
Everybody says so.
Everybody
says so.
You want this?
No.
We're good
for each other.
It's me, sweetheart.
My god, you're beautiful.
Oh, you make me
beautiful.
Tonight is very special.
Veal in white wine
and lemon sauce,
- asparagus--
- look at all these flowers.
Harry, come here.
Give me your jacket.
I have a surprise
for you.
Where did they come from?
- Here, sweetheart.
- I didn't send them.
Put this on.
Give me your arm.
Come on.
Harry, feel this.
Doesn't this feel
like butter?
Nice, nice.
Thank you.
You look so handsome.
Let me put on
another record.
Who's Vincent?
I thought I put that
with the box.
What are you
talking about?
Who the hell is Vincent?
Did the roses
come from him?
Harry, I didn't
know what to do.
I mean, when
the first ones came,
I threw them out,
but then he just--
he kept sending
more flowers.
- Give me that.
- Harry!
I said give it to me.
He wants you
to move to Atlanta.
He wants me
to marry him.
He's given me 10 days
to make up my mind.
- Have you been seeing
him all the time--
- oh, Harry.
I met him long
before I met you.
It didn't mean anything,
not as far as I was concerned.
At first he sent letters,
and then--
then the flowers.
I love you, Harry.
But I am not gonna be
somebody that you see
two or three nights
a week and then--
then you go home
to your wife.
Lee, we've talked
about this before,
about my being married
to Eve for 33 years--
has she been
your lover, Harry?
Does she make you feel
the way I do?
No.
But there's more
to marriage than just--
well.
Then there's something else
you ought to see.
You can't be serious.
He's devoted to me.
Well, so am I.
You're married.
For 33 years.
- Are you happy, Harry?
- For 33 years, Lee.
Are you happy, Harry?
I don't see how I can
possibly tell her that--
she's such a gentle woman.
So kind, so--
we're very comfortable
with one another.
For over 33 years,
we've done everything
together.
Including growing old.
I love you, Harry.
But I am not gonna
be your mistress anymore.
If we can't be together
all the time,
then I am gonna move.
I am gonna go to Atlanta
because it will be
too painful
to stay here
and watch you
become an old man
because it's comfortable.
Life's too short, Harry.
Don't you think?
[ Phone ringing ]
Sandra on phone: Hello?
Leona:
He bought it, Sandra.
The letter,
the phony ring,
the whole bit.
- He's getting a divorce.
- Sandra: Congratulations.
Leona:
I'll get the ring
back to you next week.
Sandra: Keep it.
It's just cheap
costume jewelry.
I'm surprised
Harry couldn't tell
it was a fake.
Leona:
Harry wouldn't
know a fake
if it hit him
across the face.
Sandra:
That's obvious, Leona.
Good night.
[ Phone line disconnects ]
The state Attorney General
has filed a motion
with the Manhattan
state supreme court
to enjoin the owners
of 345 east 56th street
from selling
their 172 apartments.
He charges that the owners
of the building--
that's me, Leona,
and their sales brokers,
that's you--
get to the point.
Go ahead.
You explain it to her.
He charges
that you obtained
your 35% quota
by loading the building
with sham sales
to friends and relatives
who never had any intention
of buying.
He further claims
that you harassed tenants
who refused to sell.
Bottom line is that
he's asked the court
to declare
the co-op conversion
null and void,
and he's demanded that
you be permanently barred
from selling cooperatives
in the state of New York.
That is not
going to happen.
Will it, Harry?
I mean, we're not talking
about Leona Roberts here.
We're talking about
the future Mrs. Helmsley.
You are the most
important man in
this city.
Even the mayor
walks in your shadow.
Harry, you're not gonna
let this happen.
Excuse US, please.
You're the king, Harry.
They can't treat you
like this.
We practically
support this city
on the taxes you pay.
Somebody out there
owes you a favor.
Now you pick
up the phone,
and you collect it.
[ Dialing phone ]
And I want
that lawyer fired.
By the authority
vested in me
by the state
of New York,
I now pronounce you
man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
- Look up, look up.
- Mm-hmm.
Busy busy busy.
Watch your step.
Well well well,
look what the cat
dragged in.
- Mrs. Helmsley.
- Where have you been?
Don't you ever
talk to your office?
I've been trying
to reach you for days.
I was on a buying trip
with some other clients,
Mrs. Helmsley.
It wasn't possible
to return your call.
Oh, it wasn't possible.
Well, you should have
made it possible.
I pay you plenty,
buster.
And when I wanna
talk to you,
I don't care where you are,
you get back to me pronto.
I'm here now,
Mrs. Helmsley.
What's the problem?
These chairs
are the problem.
But those are the chairs
you had me bid on
at the auction.
Well, the paper said
the whole lot were
second-rate,
and anybody knowledgeable
would have passed on them.
You told me
to bid on them.
You should have
known better.
And there is no way
that I am taking some
second-rate antiques.
Just what do you
expect me to do
with them?
- [ Laughs ]
- Paul: Leona.
Well, I don't care
what you do with them,
but they are not
staying here,
and I am not
paying for them.
You're quite right,
Mrs. Helmsley.
There's only room
in this apartment
for one second-rate
antique.
You shall be hearing
from my lawyer.
Oh, oh!
[ Laughing ]
I'm glad you think
that's so funny.
Oh, come on.
It was a hell
of a good line,
and frankly,
you deserved it.
If you weren't
so full of yourself
you'd be breaking
up now too.
There is no way
I'm gonna let some
little jerk
who works for me
get away with that.
He tried to make
a fool of me.
Let it go, Leona.
Why shouldn't
I be tough?
Nobody ever
gave me anything
till Harry.
Why should I let
anybody get away
with anything?
You are always tough.
That's one of the things
I like about you,
- but you used to be fair.
- I'm still fair.
No, you're mean now, Leona.
There's a difference.
What kind of friend
are you?
You only liked it
when I was taking it?
You don't like it
when I dish it?
I don't like it
either way.
I'm the kind of friend
who's not afraid
to tell you so.
How many of those
do you have left?
Well, I like the green.
Mrs. Helmsley,
they go with your eyes.
[ Laughs ]
Well, the bracelet
is nice.
Yes, this is
our finest set.
But the earrings
are too small.
- Do you have
something larger?
- Larger.
- [ Intercom buzzes ]
- Secretary: Excuse me,
Mrs. Helmsley?
I told you I did not
want to be disturbed.
But Mrs. Helmsley,
it's about your son.
I don't care
what it's about.
One more interruption
- and you're outta here.
- He's had a heart attack,
Mrs. Helmsley.
[ Beeping ]
Leona: I talked
to your aunt Sandra.
She sends her best,
whatever that is.
And your aunt Sylvia
is sending brownies.
You know her answer
to everything is sugar.
You could have
prepared me,
you know.
I didn't plan on this.
I'm talking about
those people out there.
You got a new wife,
you got new kids.
You haven't spoken
to me in three years.
I don't know why.
Jay...
We need to be more close.
In a few weeks,
when you're feeling better,
I'm gonna talk
to Harry about you
coming to work for US.
You'd look younger
with a toupee.
So, what do you
want me to do about it?
Make Jay president
of deco incorporated.
- What?!
- He'll stay in Orlando.
You don't even
have to see him.
[ Chuckles ]
Lee...
Deco does all the purchasing
for the hotels.
Jay can do that.
How can he do that?
He's had no experience
with that sort of thing.
Harry, you like
being seen with me?
You like the way
you feel with me?
I am no dried-up
little quaker
sitting on my ass
knitting doilies.
I have made you look
20 years younger.
I've made you feel
Harry, you owe me.
Don't you think
you've had enough?
Vodka with a twist.
Double.
Excuse me.
Mr. Helmsley?
I'm Deborah pauley,
and I know this
is terribly gauche,
but I saw you
and Mrs. Helmsley
on the dance floor
a while ago
and well, my husband
would kill me,
but he's not
a very good dancer,
and i--
I love the samba.
Mrs. Helmsley,
would you mind
very much
if I asked
your husband
to dance?
There's not a chance
in hell that's gonna
happen, honey.
Harry:
That young lady was
so charming and so innocent.
Leona: Innocent?!
You are more innocent
than she is.
Harry: Oh yeah?
Well, let me ask
you something.
Damn it to hell!
Don't keep walking
away from me.
- I am trying
to talk to you!
- If I am so vulgar,
why don't you crawl
back to your sweet,
simple Eve?
Don't think that
hasn't crossed my mind.
At least I had
some peace then.
I could fight my battles
in the office,
but home was like
a sanctuary--
- calm and peaceful.
- It was killing you.
You were becoming
an old man.
Sometimes
you suffocate me.
In public,
you grab ahold of me
like a jealous schoolgirl.
You comb my hair,
pick the lint off
my jacket.
You treat me like--
I treat you like
you are the center
of my universe.
[ Groans ]
When I'm with you,
it's--
it's as if
everything else
is out of focus.
You're right.
I don't want
anybody else near you.
And I would be
perfectly willing
to kill anybody
who tried to take
you away from me.
Harry.
Harry!
If anything
happened to you,
I would die.
Together,
we're immortal.
We make magic.
Everything I do
I do for you.
So you better
decide, Harry--
what is it
you really want?
Sweet, simple Eve
or me?
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm sure you're all wondering
why I called
you here today.
Well, it's for
a very special reason--
the unveiling
of our plans
to build the most
magnificent hotel
New York
has yet to see.
I give you
the palace hotel.
As this model
clearly shows,
we've kept our promise.
We've done everything
possible
to preserve and restore
this exquisite villa
by connecting it
to the tower behind.
The palace will be
the finest hotel
in New York.
No expense
will be spared.
Now I want to introduce
you to the woman
who will
not only oversee
the creation
of this magnificent hotel,
but will also be president
of the newly-formed
Harley hotels
across the country--
Leona Helmsley.
[ Applause ]
I want to know
what we can throw out,
what we can keep.
Okay, what you wanna do
is preserve the interior
to the fullest
possible extent
because of
the historic nature.
The cubicles
the church put in--
they can go.
- Mark, are you
taking notes?
- Yes, ma'am.
The gold room,
thank god,
is pretty much
the way it was.
And the chandelier's intact.
- But in here--
Mrs. Helmsley?
- Huh?
In here, we're talking
millions of dollars.
I know that, Sarah.
I don't care
about that.
The rag.
Now, I have the highest
possible standards.
If we are gonna spend
millions of dollars
redecorating
and restoring
this hotel,
then I want
only the best
from you.
If you're up to that,
you've got the job.
Oh, I'm up to it,
Mrs. Helmsley.
Good.
Oh, good.
Bring a pad, Mark.
Come on, Sarah.
As you know,
Mrs. Helmsley,
part of the condition
of appointing your son
vice president
of deco incorporated
was that I supervise
all bookkeeping,
- invoices,
transactions.
- Yes, Stanley.
Since your son had
little experience
in this field,
Mr. Helmsley felt that
in-house regulations
be put into effect.
Leona: Stanley,
are you going to get
to the point eventually,
or should I order lunch?
Your son is ripping
off your husband,
Mrs. Helmsley.
The Helmsley corporation
is being double-billed,
sometimes triple-billed
for furnishings
and services
ordered by deco.
For a 200-room hotel,
he orders furnishings
for 300 rooms.
The surplus is then sold
to another chain
and Jay pockets
the difference.
Now I understand
he's in daily
contact with you.
Of course he is.
He's my son.
Well, I'll
look into it.
- That'll be all.
- All right.
Oh, have you told
Harry about this yet?
Not yet.
Don't bother.
I'll tell him myself.
Oh, and Stanley...
Yes?
You're fired.
Mark!
- Mark!
- Yes, Mrs. Helmsley?
Get me my son.
He's in London.
- You know the number.
- Yes, ma'am.
- I gave you
that job as a gift.
- Leona: Harry--
do not interrupt me, Leona.
Your mother said you
needed a job.
You needed taking care of.
I took care of you,
didn't I?
- Didn't I?
- Yes.
Vice president of deco
with one job to do,
one simple job.
What was that job, Jay?
Give me a job description.
To organize
and supervise
the purchasing
and installation
of all the furnishings
for the Harley
and Helmsley hotels.
- No other hotels,
no other chains?
- Yes, sir.
Then what the hell
is this?!
Harry, there is no need
to scream at him.
I'll scream at whomever
I damn well please,
including you
if you don't shut up
and sit down.
Well?
Jay:
It's our catalogue.
I've been around
a long time, hotshot.
I know all the schemes.
Half of them
I invented.
And no snot-nosed
little brat
is gonna get away
with double-ordering,
double-billing,
and selling furnishings
that I've already
paid for to other hotels
and then pocketing
the difference!
Jay would never
do such a thing.
Why not?
He's your son,
isn't he?
Yeah, you've been
pretty clever.
Somehow you've managed
to sidestep Stanley
on most of this.
Well, no more.
From now on,
he's gonna be breathing
right down your neck.
You're gonna have to get
his approval on every
damn thing you do,
even when you
go to the toilet.
You understand?!
And he'll send me copies
of every purchase order,
every memo,
every scribble
that you make.
How will I explain
that to my staff?
You've had three
heart attacks.
Tell them that your
stepfather is concerned
about your health
and sent someone down
to help you out.
And Leona,
I'm rehiring Stanley
permanently.
Now get this straight,
both of you:
Just one more time,
one more thing
like this,
and you're both
out on your asses!
Oh!
I apologize for interrupting
your honeymoon, Mimi.
I wish you
both happiness.
Thank you.
As you know,
I am a very
determined person.
And I determined long ago
that I was gonna marry
a man so powerful
that just by
being his wife,
I would command absolute
attention and respect.
Well...
I have done that.
I have done better
than Sandra.
than Sylvia.
I have done better
than most women would
ever dream possible.
And if you think,
as my son,
that you can do anything
to destroy that,
you are gravely
and sadly mistaken.
Now if you ever
do anything again
that puts my marriage
in danger,
I will hang you
out to dry.
You're not going to be
an anonymous manager,
Mrs. Helmsley.
Absolutely.
You are
this hotel.
You've been
the focal point
in all the press.
That's right.
- Oh, Mark, make a note.
- Yes, ma'am.
Harry woke up
with a backache
this morning.
Yes, ma'am.
Remind me to call
the mattress supplier.
I warned him if my Harry
could not sleep,
we were changing brands
in every hotel,
in every room.
Damn right I am not
an anonymous manager.
Absolutely.
Now what do you
think of this?
Instead of running
a single full-page ad
for publication,
we're going to go
with three smaller ads
in a row--
each one in the upper
right-hand corners
of successive pages,
all of them featuring
you, of course.
Beautiful gowns,
jewelry.
Mark that down.
I get to pick
the jewelry.
I get to pick the jewelry,
and I get to pick the gowns.
I call it
the "why should you?"
Campaign.
- [ Knocking on door ]
- Will you get that?
Yeah.
Here's one under
a picture of you
that says,
"I won't settle
for skimpy towels.
Why should you?"
- Well, I wouldn't.
- Exactly.
And in this one,
the copy reads,
"I couldn't get along
without a phone in the
bath. Why should you?"
- Perfect.
- Tea?
No, thanks. The airline
publications are giving
US three pages at least
and we're going nationwide--
newspapers, magazines,
week after week,
all featuring
the same headline
with your picture
under it:
"The only palace
in the world
where the queen
stands guard."
I love it.
You're a genius.
No, it's great.
I couldn't be happier.
Mark, get them
outta here.
Wait a second.
- Don't touch your food.
- What's wrong?
Close the door.
Close the door!
Look at your lettuce.
There are water droplets
on the lettuce.
- You're kidding.
- How dare you do this?
How dare you
do this?!
- Mrs. H., it's fine.
- It is not fine.
The palace does not
serve wet lettuce.
Not in my hotels.
You are lucky
I do not fire every
damn one of you.
Now get the hell out.
Go on, out out out.
Go on, Mark.
Out!
Close the door!
Where was I?
Oh, yeah.
Something I want
to show you.
See this?
Pictures
of the royal family.
That's what I want.
My picture on 52 cards.
We can sell
them for mementos
at the hotel.
What do you think?
Well, I think it's
a terrific idea.
Mama's on her way.
Thanks.
Mama's coming.
She wants to start
in the dining room.
Now what's wrong here?
Hmm?
Come on, come on.
Matches.
Where are
the damn matches?
Every ashtray is supposed
to have matches.
Now get them.
Hey, I'm the only one
who snaps fingers
around here, buster.
[ Sighs ]
- What is this?
- It's being repaired.
No no, that's dirt.
How do you repair dirt?
Now tonight's
the grand opening.
Get that carpet cleaned.
And I want every
square inch of carpet
in this hotel checked.
- Understood?
- Yes, ma'am.
Okay, let's go.
Matches?
- Man: I'll get them.
- Leona: Oh, good.
You got them.
You've got
nothing to do?
There are no guests
yet, Mrs. Helmsley.
I don't pay people
to do nothing.
Get his name.
You'll be lucky
if you last six months
with me, young man.
- Only the best
last with me.
- Guard: Yeah, uh-huh.
Well, what did he say?
- Uh-huh.
- Hang up.
Are you a security guard?
Why aren't you
at your post?
- I'm on my break.
- Was this a personal call?
Yes.
- You're fired.
- But--
Mrs. Helmsley,
the man has five children.
If he kept his pants on,
he wouldn't have a problem,
would he?
He's fired.
Well, what
do you think?
Oh, you've done
a great job.
Well, thank you,
kind sir.
- You ready for
tonight's opening?
- Sarah, I have some bad news.
- Leona sent me down
here with a message.
- What?
You're fired.
[ Laughing ]
What?
For what?
You know the lady.
You've done your job
and she wants to take
the credit for it.
She doesn't want
you around taking
the focus off of her.
But I designed
this whole lobby--
the hallways, the lights,
the fabrics.
No, you haven't.
The queen has decided
that you don't exist.
You never have.
I'm sorry.
[ Ballroom music playing ]
Ladies and gentlemen,
your attention, please.
The king and queen
of the Helmsley palace.
[ Band playing
"I'm just wild about Harry" ]
Everybody dance.
[ Door opens ]
I found theart.
- What?
- Our house.
Wait till you see it.
I am so excited.
It'll be my first
real house.
What do you mean,
first house?
Well, you know.
We've always lived
in apartments
or condominiums
or hotels.
I mean, this will be
my first real house.
It has trees
and a big lawn
and it only costs
$11 million.
Harry:
$11 million?!
Leona:
Furnished, Harry.
Furnished!
I am having a clock made
for Harry's birthday
in the shape
of the Helmsley building.
It's gonna cost
a little over $43,000,
but we can charge it off
to the business, right?
I mean, after all,
we are the business,
aren't we?
The I.R.S. Can't object.
Don't worry about the I.R.S.
You're covered.
All these invoices
you and Harry are initialing
I've got them
all billed to either
the graybar building,
the Helmsley building,
the Harley hotels--
all buried
in their accounts
charged off
to deco incorporated.
So it's all
a business expense.
Not only do you
not pay for any of it,
- it's a tax write-off.
- Why not?
Only the little people
pay taxes, right?
- Lee.
- Dreamboat.
What are you doing
home so early?
Good, we can talk about
the pool enclosure,
- because I just
found out--
- Lee.
- What?
- Jay's had another
heart attack.
Where is he?
Take me to him.
[ Sobbing ]
It's too late.
He died over
an hour ago.
Oh, Harry.
Take me out of here.
Now it all makes sense.
What?
I wondered why
that precious
daughter-in-law of mine
had to rush back
to Orlando after
the funeral.
What are you
talking about?
She left New York
before Jay was even
cold in his grave.
She did not sit Shiva,
she did not stand
by US as a family,
and now she is claiming
she has a legal right
to take over deco.
That's impossible.
We own the business.
Well, she is
trying to jump in
and grab it.
Now we are going
to have to lock her out,
and we're gonna
have to move fast.
Okay, I'll get
a court order.
No!
I want a lock
on everything tonight.
She did not honor Jay,
and I'm gonna
teach her a lesson
- she will not forget.
- Okay.
I want her evicted
from the house.
I want--
I want her and the kids
out of the house.
Okay, but where are they
going to live?
I don't care!
Jay is dead,
and as far
as I'm concerned,
she killed him.
No, Lee...
Your son died
with his pants down
in a hotel room
with another woman.
Well, if she were
a better wife,
it wouldn't
have happened.
I want her
out of my life.
Harry!
What is it?
What's wrong?
Harry?
Huh?
What?
What happened?
Nothing.
Nothing happened.
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Did you ever play
52 pickup, may?
I thought you loved
the playing cards.
You personally approved
every photograph
of yourself.
You picked the colors,
the style of the numbers.
Leona, we have
printed up
10,000 decks
of cards here.
We've packaged them,
we've wrapped them
in cellophane,
we've spent a year
designing the damn--
excuse me.
These cards have been made
to your specifications,
and it's too late
to change them now.
They're too small.
They're regular cards.
Harry plays with
pinochle cards,
and they're larger.
My picture is on those cards,
and I want it to look right.
These cards are gonna
go in my hotels.
I wanna make sure
they look like
they belong,
so I want them larger,
and I want
the edges gold-leafed.
Gold leaf?
You said you didn't
want gold leaf.
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
I gave you that option,
and you specifically said
you didn't want it.
No arguments.
I'll get right on it.
Oh, and may?
Every time you send
a messenger with
your ad copy,
it costs me $5.95.
Don't you think
mailing it makes
more sense?
Whatever you say.
- [ Door slams ]
- [ Sighs ]
Well?
Pick those up.
Don't just stand there.
Pick them up yourself.
While you're at it,
pick that up, too.
Hold on just a second.
Ransdell, pick up 8086.
- Something about
the helmsleys.
- Thanks.
Hello?
Woman:
Are you interested
in winning a pulitzer prize?
[ Chuckles ]
Of course.
I'm serious.
If you meet me tonight,
I assure you you'll
win a pulitzer prize.
That's good salesmanship,
but what's this all about?
The helmsleys.
They're thieves.
Meet me tonight
and I'll tell you
the whole story.
First tell me
a little bit more.
For instance,
their mansion in
Connecticut--
they've built a brick-
and-marble enclosure
for their outdoor
swimming pool.
It's the finest
that money can buy,
and it didn't
cost them a penny.
They dummied up
a bunch of expenses,
a bunch of bills,
and sent them
to the graybar building
and the Helmsley building
for payment.
The helmsleys
personally initialed
a million dollars' worth
of these fake invoices.
And you're gonna
love this:
Included is a $12.95
bloomingdale girdle.
- A business expense.
- [ All laughing ]
She tried to fill a table
for a charity event
and couldn't find
one person to join them.
They had to fill it
with business acquaintances.
Man:
If they come home
at 3:00 in the morning,
the staff has
to get out of bed,
get dressed
and stand outside
until they drive up.
Once they go upstairs,
the staff can go
back to bed.
I've heard her sit down
with Mr. Helmsley,
man #2:
Go through a list
of his associates,
make him feel insecure,
and then demand
that he fire them.
But I'll tell
you something:
I think he's had
some strokes.
Woman:
He's slower.
Sometimes
he drifts.
You know, I think
she takes advantage
of that.
She once
threatened to fire
one of the housekeepers
because the sheets weren't
ironed to her satisfaction.
She said the crease
kept her awake
all night.
Al, you said
you needed more proof.
Well, you got it.
Take a look at this:
You got $250,000
worth of invoices
all charged
to the helmsleys'
office buildings and hotels.
But it's really for
goods and services
for carpets,
chandeliers--
you name it--
installed at
the helmsleys' mansion
in greenwich, Connecticut.
And Harry and Leona's
initials are on every
single invoice.
"H.b.h., l.M.H."
It's unbelievable.
Leona!
The state Attorney General
has indicated
that in addition
to federal charges,
he may initiate
state charges.
We've done nothing wrong.
Former employees
have come forth
and accused you
- of being tyrannical.
- Why don't you
print the good news?
Where's the story that
Harry and I donated
$33 million
to New York hospital?
Or that in
the last five years,
we have paid
$340 million in taxes?
That's over a quarter
of a billion dollars.
How much did you pay?
I have a search warrant
pertaining to certain records
on file here.
- Man: Harry,
I want to speak to you.
- Woman: Mr. Helmsley!
Please, please,
clear the doorway.
Mr. Helmsley,
you've spent a lot
of years in real estate.
What do you consider
your greatest accomplishment?
I married her.
Woman: Leona,
Harry, just a few more
questions, please!
Just a few
more minutes
of your time.
He's been found
incompetent to stand trial
because of the strokes,
memory loss.
Well, then I'll have
to face it alone.
That's right.
Up to now,
we haven't had
to face anything alone,
have we, Harry?
Sometimes you were
such a boy.
I had to straighten
your tie.
I had to smooth
your hair.
You would get
so impatient with me.
Right from that
very first dance,
we were perfect partners,
weren't we, Harry?
Oh, how we danced.
Man:
Leona.
Leona, we're due in court
for the verdict.
I'll be right there.
Are you
all right?
Wait till they see
this performance.
- Male reporter: Leona!
- Female reporter: Leona!
- Male reporter #2: Leona!
- Male reporter #3:
Mrs. Helmsley!
[ Reporters clamoring ]
Young Leona: Mama,
mama, look at me.
Look at me.
Leona: Mama?
Mama, look at me.
[ Ballroom music playing ]