by RentAnAdviser.com
Can′t stop addicted to the shindig
Cop top he says I am gona win big
Choose not a life of imitation
Distant cousin to the reservation
Defunkt the pistol that you pay for
This punk the feeling
that you stay for
In time I want to be your best friend
East side love is living
on the west end
Knock out but boy you better come to
Don′t die you know the
truth is some do
Go write your message on the pavement
Burn so bright I wonder
what the wave meant
White heat is screaming in the jungle
Complete the motion if you stumble
Go ask the dust for any answers
Come back strong with
fifty belly dancers
The world I love
The tears I drop
To be part of
The wave can′t stop
Ever wonder if It is all for you
The world I love
The trains I hop
To be part of
The wave can′t stop
Come and tell me when It is time to
Sweetheart is bleeding
in the snow cone
So smart She is leading me to ozone
Music the great communicator
Use two sticks to make
it in the nature
I will get you into penetration
The gender of a generation
The birth of every other nation
Worth your weight the
gold of meditation
This chapter′s going to be a close one
Smoke rings I know your
going to blow one
All on a spaceship persevering
Use my hands for everything
but steering
Can′t stop the spirit is
when they need you
Mop tops are happy when they feed you
J. Butterfly is in the treetop
Birds that blow the meaning into bebop
The world I love
The tears I drop
To be part of
The wave can′t stop
Ever wonder if It is all for you
The world I love
The trains I hop
To be part of
The wave can′t stop
Come and tell me when It is time to
Wait a minute I am passing out
Win or lose just like you
Far more shocking
Than anything I ever knew
How about you
Ten more reasons
Why I need somebody new just like you
Far more shocking than
anything I ever knew
Right on cue
Can′t stop addicted to the shindig
Chop top he says I am gona win big
Choose not a life of imitation
Distant cousin to the reservation
Defunkt the pistol that you pay for
This punk the feeling
that you stay for
In time I want to be your best friend
East side love is living
on the west end
Knock out but boy you better come to
Don′t die you know the
truth is some do
Go write your message on the pavement
Burn so bright I wonder
what the wave meant
Kick start the golden generator
Sweet talk but don′t intimidate her
Can′t stop the gods from engineering
Feel no need for any interfering
Your image in the dictionary
This life is more than ordinary
Can I get two maybe even
three of these
Coming from space
To teach you of the pliedes
Can′t stop the spirit is
when they need you
This life is more than
just a read through
www.RentAnAdviser.com