[howling]
WOMAN: Even a man
who is pure at heart
and says his prayers
by night may become
a wolf when the
wolf-bane blooms,
and the moon is full and bright.
[music playing]
[breathing]
[squeaking]
Tim?
Tim, is that you?
[breathing]
[squeaking]
[clattering]
Tim?
Tim, help me lock these doors.
He's out there.
[screams]
[making noises]
Couldn't help it, could you?
Nuh-uh.
[laughter]
Bill Parker?
A little jungle rot.
Nothing serious.
- You Jake?
- Right.
Jake Sutter.
He with you?
[growl]
If you say so.
He's good at what he
does, and does it all.
Hey, man.
None of my business.
I'm just a coordinator.
This one must be a
beaut, because nobody's
talking back in Washington.
I'll brief you
before we meet the doc.
Stein, wasn't it?
That's right.
Dr. Ivan Stein.
He requested you by name.
You must know him.
Never heard of him.
[music playing]
SONG: Friends say they see
you walking in the street.
You talk to--
Nice cold beer sure
does hit the spot.
That it does, Jake.
So who's you piss off
to get stuck out here?
It's not so bad.
You know, I've been doing
your country's dirty work--
Our country's
dirty work, Bill.
Right.
Our country's dirty
work for 10 years.
I hear I'm one of the best
special agents around--
Yeah, I think you
started that tumor.
Yeah, and I can't find
out what's going on.
Excuse me.
You said you're
going to brief us.
Brief us.
I was told to bring
you in to meet Dr. Stein.
He seemed to know you.
You sure you haven't
heard of him?
I wouldn't know
him if I fell on him.
What's his specialty.
The human mind.
[laughter]
A shrink?
Behavior specialist.
He's here studying
the sun's radiation
effects on the humans.
Out here?
Especially out here.
There's no humans here, Jake.
Hate to be the bearer
of bad news, boys,
but we have a serious
ozone problem.
No shit.
But why us?
There's a lab outpost
in the jungle, a place
where they run tests and stuff.
About a week ago,
we lost contact.
Terroristas?
You tell me when you get back.
Oh, I get it.
We go in there.
We deal with it.
You smuggle us out, right?
Quick and quiet.
You were never here.
We never had a problem.
Where's Stein come in?
It's his operation.
Why wasn't he there?
Honeymoon.
His aid It was supposed to
pick him up at the airport,
but he never showed.
Where's the drop zone?
Drop zone?
That's good.
Yeah, you're new here.
This is the Amazon.
You don't fly in.
You don't fall in.
You walk in.
Walk?
As in on foot?
Only takes a day.
Well, that's goddamn
inconvenient, Jake.
You'll get used to it.
If not for my
rosary and my beer,
I probably couldn't
survive out here.
Speaking of which--
You've got it, Bill.
Rosary?
Hello.
Hi, honey.
Bring these boys a
couple of cold ones.
Sure thing.
Good kid.
Not bad.
I'm glad you like her.
She'll be the one
who guides you in.
Things are
brightening up already.
She got a sister?
[howls]
Dr. Stein?
Good morning, gentlemen.
Please, sit down.
Well, my job's done.
- Bill--
- Jake.
Good luck.
Thanks.
I have a special goodbye
planned for Rosary.
- Uh-huh.
- Lee.
You must be Mr. Parker.
Do I know you, doctor?
No.
Because Jake was telling
me you requested me by name.
You have quite a reputation
and come highly recommended.
I've been convinced
that you are one
of the best men for the job.
Yeah, what job is that?
DR. STEIN: Escorting
my wife and me back
to our outpost in the
Amazon, and finding out what
happened to my scientific team.
What makes you think
something happened to them?
They haven't been heard
from in over a week.
And frankly there are
quite a few theories
as to what has happened.
It's probably
a gorilla attack.
There are many mysteries
in the Amazon, Mr. Parker.
People from all over the
world explore the region.
Some of them cite findings
of things that have
never been seen before by man--
insects, plants.
Some of them even
live to tell about it.
Well, I don't think plants and
bugs are to blame for the loss
of contact with your team.
And I don't think gorillas
are the answer either.
Well, what do you think?
My wife told me that
you are impatient.
Among other things.
Sheila?
How are you, Bill?
You two know each other.
In a previous
life, I'm afraid.
I'm sorry, Bill,
but we need you.
Oh, this is just great.
If the Lone Ranger was here,
the reunion would be complete.
He's here.
Cody's here?
I had to ask him
in case you refused.
Why would I refuse?
I didn't know it was you.
I'm afraid it was my fault.
Your fault?
What did you do?
Steal her from Cody after
she left me for him?
[violin]
- Shut up, Lee.
- Hey, man.
This is getting good, man.
BILL PARKER: Please?
Well, that's no
way to make friends.
DR. STEIN: My
research team and I
have been doing a
great deal of study
on the effects of the
destruction of the ozone layer.
There are many
individuals and countries
that would do anything
to get their hands
on this information.
When I mentioned my
concerns to my wife,
she told me that you
were one of the best
men for the investigation.
And if you wouldn't
take the job,
then Cody was our other option.
Where is he?
DR. STEIN: In the hall.
SHEILA STEIN: We had to
make a decision fast.
I thought you wouldn't show
if you knew I was involved.
And Mr. Carlson
resides in the area.
SHEILA STEIN: Unlike you,
Cody's kept in touch.
We need you.
We've got to find out
what happened at the lab
and hopefully find
our data intact.
And help any--
well, any survivors.
So as far as the
government is concerned,
this little problem you're
having here doesn't even exist,
right?
- That sounds about right.
You're escorting a team
of medical experts.
How's Cody fit in?
I've heard Mr. Carlson
is an excellent shot.
Yeah.
You're damn straight.
I just about found out
firsthand because of her.
Understanding are ever.
No wonder she left you.
Fuck you.
That's no way to talk
to an old friend, Bill.
You ain't heard nothing yet.
You need my help.
Oh yeah?
You could be up
against 30 guns or more.
BILL PARKER: I'm not
impressed by numbers.
I am.
CODY: I might have
been a lousy friend,
but I was always an
excellent partner, right?
The Lone Ranger and
Tonto, remember?
Yeah.
I remember kemosabe
running off with my girl.
That was personal.
This is business.
Now when do you want to leave?
Ah, hell.
We leave in the morning.
Does that thing
help you figure out
the effects of the black ozone?
Well as you know,
the ozone is a layer
of gas that protects us from
the harmful rays of the sun.
I'm funded to find a link
with this ozone problem
to a deadly skin
disease known as lupus
erythematosus chronic discord.
It's a disease of
unknown origin that's
brought on by excessive
exposure to the sun.
You means skin cancer?
Something like that,
although more complicated.
Tests show that
next to Antarctica,
this is the location of the
largest of the ozone holes.
The weather readings
indicate that within a year,
the Amazon jungle will become
a desert, uninhabitable
during the daylight hours.
Sounds like you're describing
the end of the world, doctor.
That's precisely
what I'm describing.
My colleagues and
I have compiled
several hundred pages
of extensive data
backing up our theory.
We need that data.
It's too late to start over.
Why?
Yesterday was 118 degrees.
Water boils at 212.
Every day it gets worse.
[music playing]
SONG: Don't look at the sky.
It'll only set your mind
in motion, at a speed
far greater than an ocean.
You question.
Through a looking glass I--
I notice you, almost as if
you seeped into the cold,
pouring rain.
No one is to blame
for the dilemma.
For the dilemma.
Don't look at the sky.
It'll only set your mind
in motion, at a speed
far greater than an ocean.
You question.
Don't you question?
Bye.
Everything all right, doctor?
Dr. Stein?
It's a lot than where we left.
Sorry about the way
I got you involved.
I got to admit, I
was a little surprised.
I thought I'd never
see you again.
That's why I
couldn't tell you.
I really wanted you to come.
Not just for the
project, either.
I wanted to see you again.
Better watch it.
You're a married woman.
Don't want to upset Ivan.
Why Cody?
You really don't want to
get into that, now do you?
I'm tough.
I can take it.
Why him?
Convenience.
Convenience?
I don't know.
He was just there.
He never pressured me or
talked about settling down.
He wanted me to
have my career, too.
It was a choice I had to make.
You made the wrong one.
SHEILA STEIN: Yeah?
Well, maybe I did.
That won't change things now.
You saying you didn't love me?
That's not the point.
It's my career I
want, and I won't give
that up for anything--
not money or security or--
or even love.
But that's all behind us.
So how long did it last?
Three months.
You know our Cody.
Hi ho, Silver.
Away.
So now you just
married into your career?
Ivan's different
from both of you.
I wanted to marry you.
I know.
That's why I left.
Don't you see?
If I'd stayed, you
could convince me
of anything-- even to settle
down and raise a family.
I just couldn't.
I had to cut it off before your
dreams became my realities.
So here we are--
you, me, Cody, and Ivan.
God hates me.
It's hot.
Yeah, but you know,
this is no humidity.
No, but I noticed
little animals
exploding all around us.
You ready?
Funny.
Yeah, I'm ready.
Ha!
[clattering]
It's clear.
What a stink.
It's through here.
This place is too well
hidden to have been hit.
Yeah, I was thinking
the same thing.
Is that all
that's on your mind?
You know, now
that you mention it,
Cody, there's a few things
I'd like to clear up.
Like?
Like I thought
we were friends.
What are you doing
going out with Sheila?
I'd like to think
we still are friends.
How long have you two--
We weren't.
Just came as a big a surprise
to me as it did to you.
Just something that happened.
Just seemed like a good idea.
Let's drop it.
Yeah, sure.
Besides, we're both
out of the picture now.
Whoa.
Lee, I want that ventilation
system going ASAP.
No problem.
Man.
What the fuck died in here?
Cody, come with me.
Hey, shouldn't we
wait for Bill or Cody?
They're looking for intruders.
This is my office,
and I'd like to make
sure our data's still intact.
Don't suppose either
of you has a nail file?
How about this?
That should do the trick.
Radio room.
I was just stepping
real close, man.
BILL PARKER: Whoever
did this meant business.
Damn.
- No sound effect, huh?
- Yeah.
"Taps."
I want you to find
that power right now.
I don't want to leave
the others alone.
[beeping]
I got it.
Come on, man.
We'll get Bill
and Cody and have
them secure the room first.
What are you afraid of?
They're within
shouting distance.
If my mother were
alive, she'd tell you
that if I didn't
become a doctor,
I would have been a cat burglar.
See?
Your heroes aren't the only
ones capable of breaking
and entering.
Follow me.
[beeping]
I can fix this.
Good.
Cody, let's get
this place secure.
I always hated
working in the dark.
Well, it doesn't
scare me, kiddies.
[laughter]
Go easy on him, Lee.
Don't go away mad.
Here, I got them.
Oh, Dr. Stein?
What is it?
[screams]
Sheila.
Let's go, quick.
Looks like he locked himself
in and committed suicide.
Yeah, well, look--
there's a hammer and nails.
Some wood.
Ah.
Ah, Sheila, when was the last
time you performed an autopsy?
Why?
These ulcerations
on the face--
It was obviously
a suicide, Ivan.
I'm aware of that, but why
is what I'd like to find out.
You all right?
See?
Didn't I tell you your heroes
were within shouting distance?
Who's he?
His name is--
was-- Dr. Springer.
Cody, give me a hand.
Let's cut him down.
I don't suppose you
found any survivors?
Who the hell did
you have working here?
Jack the Ripper?
What do you mean?
Well, I mean, you had eight
people manning this laboratory
and besides this poor son
of a bitch, all we've got
is a radio room full of blood.
Where the hell is everybody?
Well, it sure doesn't look
like a terrorist attack.
No, it doesn't.
The smell around here, I'd
say he's been dead a week.
When did you say
your last contact?
Oh, let's see.
About nine days ago now.
I'd like an autopsy
on this man, Mr. Parker,
if that's all right with you.
I'll tell you what, doc--
this medical bullshit,
that's your problem.
I'm just here to keep you
safe and get you back alive.
Everybody all right?
Yeah.
Hey, good job on the lights.
How about some AC?
Well, don't beat me.
I work cheap.
Lee, get the AC working.
[air conditioner starts]
- You feel that?
You feel that?
Good old American know-how.
Who da man?
I'll check the files.
Who's he?
Dr. Springer.
He needs a
serious-ass make-over.
Yeah.
Let's put him on the table.
Lee.
Have to beat the bongo.
If my memory is correct,
the doctor seems to have
all the symptoms of lupus.
Are you sure?
Now he's badly decomposed,
but look at the ulcerations here
and here.
I know I've seen this before.
We'll have to take these
tissue samples to the lab
to really know for sure.
Is this shit contagious?
No, Lee.
This shit is caused by
overexposure to the sun.
This place seems secure enough.
If worst came to worst, we
could make a last stand here.
I'm afraid that's
what Dr. Springer
thought as well, Mr. Carlson.
Lee, is our generator OK?
Actually, this place
runs on solar power,
and some of the main
services have been trashed.
- Trashed?
- Yes, ma'am.
Torn to shreds.
But we got a gas gennie
in the back and 10
gallons of Esso's finest.
So we're all right.
Well, that ought to
go in an emergency.
Whoa, whoa.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
You expecting an emergency?
Hey, I'm just making
this up as I go along.
I don't want to
use any more energy
than is absolutely necessary.
So let's secure the
lights we're not using.
We'll look for survivors
after we've had some rest.
We hadn't planned on resting.
Bill, I think we'd really like
to get to work on this autopsy.
Lee, Rosary, let's go
and secure a perimeter.
All right.
See you, doc.
What are you so jumpy about?
Look at that blood.
Until we can figure
out what happened here,
we're going to break in shifts.
This seems to be the only
sector within lights,
so I think we'll call this home.
Sounds good to me.
Cody, you and Rosary see if
you can find some blankets.
Lee's got the AC working so good
I'm going to freeze to death.
Bitch, bitch, bitch.
You gonna take the
first watch, Bill?
Yeah, I am.
Listen, we'll
each pull two hours.
We'll get some rest that
way, and then in the morning,
we can start looking
for survivors.
This is scary shit, man.
I hate this place, man.
I had this fucking place.
[squeaking]
Shit.
Lee will have to take
care of it in the morning.
What a mess.
Cody, shine the
light over there.
CODY: I don't like it.
Who could have done this?
CODY: Damned if I know.
Just grab a few blankets.
We're not going to find
any survivors here.
Ready when you are.
My, you look beautiful
when you're scrubbed.
Everything all right?
As well as can be expected.
I brought you a present.
How thoughtful.
Well, it's the only
color I could find.
And sheets too.
Why, William.
You shouldn't have.
Well, I didn't
think you'd want
to make too much of a mess,
so maybe those will help.
Parker, if you don't mind,
we've got a lot of work to do.
Sorry.
Thanks, Bill.
Sure.
Crazy fool still loves you.
Well, he can't be that crazy.
You love me, too.
I suppose Cody
still has feelings--
Quite possible.
Right now, we've got work to do.
[squeaking]
Who's there?
Lee, is that you.
Damn it.
[breathing]
LEE: Hold it.
Who goes there?
I am the master of these halls.
You may not pass.
Shh.
I heard something.
What?
So did I. Your licking hair.
Go ahead.
And you keep cool.
We just met.
BILL PARKER: Rosary,
Lee, where are you?
Oh, we better answer him.
Whatever was down here,
it ain't down here no more.
We're down here.
I'm going to go look around.
There might be some
scared survivors.
All right, all right.
Look, be careful.
I hate this place.
I know.
I'll be all right.
Here goes nothing.
Captain.
What's going on?
[screams]
Get Cody.
- No, I'm going with you, man.
- No, you're not, man.
Get Cody quick.
Check.
You all right?
Now we've found two.
What did this?
It wasn't lupus.
Lee, I want the whole place lit.
Forget saving power.
LEE: Yes, sir.
- The whole place, lit now.
- All right.
All right.
- Go.
LEE: Come on, come on.
Give me the flashlight, Bill.
Forget it, Cody.
Nobody's going in any
sector that isn't lit.
[howling]
So how do you know
a beast killed him?
BILL PARKER:
Something killed him.
And it wasn't
terrorists or gorillas
or some goddamned sickness.
What do you think did it?
I don't know, but
you can bet your ass
everybody in this place
didn't commit suicide.
DR. STEIN: Can you bring
the body back up here?
There's no reason
to get hysterical.
There's got to be a
logical explanation.
We've just not yet found it.
As soon as Lee gets this place
lit, we're going to find it.
Red, red, yellow,
yellow, brown, brown.
Boop.
Computer.
Betas.
Beep.
Warp core breach contained.
Ah, cool.
Let's just see.
Prepare for power.
Stand by.
Engage.
[breathing]
Ha!
Damn, I'm good.
I do all this good.
I got this shit going on.
I'm going to shoot you
if I can get that gun.
All right, hand-to-hand then.
Come on, you Chewbacca
motherfucker.
Come on.
What's that?
Christ, that's Lee.
Lock this door.
Don't open it till we get back.
No, thank you.
I'll leave the killing
to the lover-boys.
I'll take it.
Hey, look-- I lived with Bill
and Cody, and believe me,
I can use this thing
better than both of them.
You don't want to see him.
It's--
Oh, man.
You bastard!
Come out!
Where the fuck are you?
Save your strength.
What are we up against, man?
Wish I knew.
You still think we're
getting hysterical?
I think we could stand to
be a little more rational.
Rational?
This thing just tore
my partner to bits.
This same thing wiped out
your entire medical team.
Now excuse me, doctor,
if I seem like I'm
a little overly concerned.
The autopsy turn up anything?
The body does indeed show
symptoms of advanced lupus,
mask of the wolf.
What the fuck is that?
Apparently Dr. Springer
spent too much time in the sun.
People don't kill themselves
over a fucking sun burn.
DR. STEIN: Not unless
they fear dying anyway.
With that thing out
there, I'm surprised
he wasn't scared of it.
I meant a slow death, where
his flesh would be slowly
eaten away by the sun's rays.
That would be enough to force
anyone to take his own life.
The final step of sanity
is to become insane.
Look, we've
gotten the documents
we need for the ozone project.
I say we get the
hell out of here.
In the jungle at night?
Are you nuts?
Look, I need a few hours.
A few hours?
We won't last a few
minutes if that thing
decides he wants inside.
I need time, till sunrise.
By then, we'll know what
happened to our colleagues.
I can tell you what happened.
They were ripped to shreds.
Mr. Parker, I need you
to control your emotions.
Your orders were to
protect us and find
out what happened here.
And that's precisely
what I'm going to do.
What do you suggest, doctor?
First, I think we should
bring Lee's body back up here.
I think another
autopsy is in order.
I don't want you dissecting
Lee like some animals.
Mr. Parker, please.
If I'm going to find
out some answers,
I'm going to have
to do this my way.
By examining his
wounds, we'll be
able to find out what
type of instrument
was used to kill him.
Rosary, I'm going to
need your help with Lee.
Sure thing.
If you wish, you can
dispose of Dr. Springer.
You mean bury the man.
DR. STEIN: Whatever.
Cody--
Got it.
He was right here.
Are you sure he was dead?
Yeah.
Yeah, he was torn to bits.
Bill, look at this.
Leads right through that door.
Maybe we should seal it in.
Thought you knew
how to use that thing.
- I do.
- So what are you worried about?
Finding something
to use it on.
Me too.
Come on.
Let's go.
I'm telling you,
we get a hammer
and we board it up inside.
I'd like to know
what we're up against.
Funny.
I'm not that curious.
You ready?
I'm ready.
[screams]
[gunshot]
You OK?
Bill--
Cody!
Cody, come up here
and secure this door.
Come on.
We've got to get you to Sheila.
Come on, quick.
Cody, get up here.
Bill, describe what you saw.
I'm not sure.
It looked like a man, but he
acted like a wild animals.
I can only tell you what I saw.
What you saw, or
what you think you saw?
I'm not crazy.
Rosary saw it too.
Bill, no one's
calling you crazy.
Everyone OK?
Yeah, aside of me being
nuts, we're doing fine.
Did you manage to get that--
Don't worry, Bill.
If he were Houdini, he
couldn't get out there.
Rosary's babysitting.
Good work, Cody.
Do we have any wild
guesses what this is?
Well, it's either a
figment of my imagination
or some kind of wolf-man.
What, a werewolf?
Not quite, but close.
CODY: I thought
werewolves were something
created for the movies.
There are many werewolf
legends and stories
found in all parts
of the world, some
with more validity than others.
But as far as I know, there's
no such thing as a werewolf.
Did you see fangs or hair?
I'm not sure.
Perhaps Bill's right.
What are you thinking, Ivan.
Perhaps what you
saw is a lycanthrope.
A what?
Why does that sound familiar?
"Lycanthrope--
formerly a man believed
to be transformed into a wolf.
A werewolf."
BILL PARKER: I thought you
said there was no such thing.
Let her continue.
"Now known as the person
affected with lycanthropy."
BILL PARKER: What?
SHEILA STEIN: It says it's an
insanity in which the patient
supposes himself to be a wolf.
I've heard about
this back in Germany.
It is indeed
something to behold--
a plain and simple
type of schizophrenia
in which one of the
multiple personalities
is that of an animal,
or in this case, a wolf.
SHEILA STEIN: Combine this with
the effects of being exposed
to the sun without
ozone protection,
and we've got one serious--
CODY: One sick fucker.
Not quite the medical term
I'd give it, Mr. Carlson,
but for now, it will do.
BILL PARKER: Look,
Ivan, this guy
was strong enough that he
tore Lee apart and dragged
him up a flight of stairs.
What you saw was
a man who thought
himself a wolf, a lycanthrope.
Look, I saw this
guy's face up close.
He growled at us.
He snapped at us.
He was like a--
A monster?
The human mind is indeed
something to behold.
- Here we are.
- What?
What you got?
Kevin Johnson.
He's our man, Bill.
Read this.
You're not going to like it.
Six foot five, 275 pounds.
What kind of scientists have
you got working for you?
This guy was ugly
before he became a wolf.
He's not a wolf.
He's still a man.
He just thinks he's a wolf.
- Oh, that's terrific.
We've got Mr. Universe
trapped upstairs
and he thinks he's Lon Chaney.
Now what?
We must bring
him back for study.
Ivan, he's a human being.
He should be taken
back for treatment.
Yeah, but he's killed.
All the more reason.
What we are witnessing here is
a kind of reverse evolution.
We have tranquillizers.
We can sedate him.
I can't believe you'd
make a scientist out
of a guy that size.
According to
his personal file,
he's been with the
program for two years.
Played some college football.
Even competed in the Olympic
trials as a weight-lifter.
He was one ugly bastard.
That was the
overexposure to the sun.
We have no idea of
the transformation
he's undergoing internally,
as well as externally.
Why is it I don't
feel sorry for him?
- A natural fear of the unknown.
- Ah, fear.
Hell.
Your friend's already
killed nine people.
I'm for doing him in.
That's out of the question.
He quiet OK.
Lets out with a howl
from time to time.
How's that arm?
Oh, itching like crazy.
What are you doing?
Taking precautions.
Silver?
The Lone Ranger, remember?
Besides, they're supposed
to bring you luck.
You afraid of werewolves?
Nah.
[howling]
But I'm damned close.
So am I. Where'd
you find them?
An old guy at a village
not too far from the base
made them for me.
Cost me a buck a bullet.
Ah, can you get two for me?
Sure.
It'll cost you $5 a piece.
$5?
I thought you said
it cost you one buck.
Supply and demand.
If you want, I can show
you where the village is.
Ha, ha, ha.
Very funny.
Suit yourself.
[banging]
Maybe I'll take one.
I'll pay you when we get back.
One?
One is all I'm going to need.
You all right?
I don't feel too good.
How's she doing?
SHEILA STEIN: Shock.
High blood, highly unusual.
Take care of her.
SHEILA STEIN: Will do.
How can you
think such a thing?
Not only as my wife,
but as a scientist.
I was merely suggesting that
perhaps it would be in the best
interest of the expedition if
we left Kevin behind for now
and came back for him at a later
date with the proper equipment.
Absolutely not.
He'd starve to death
trapped like that,
then we'd never be
able to study him.
We have no idea how much
of his human emotions
are still intact.
But you're
forgetting why we were
sent here in the first place.
We have him contained.
You don't know that for sure.
I mean, what if he becomes
immune to heat and just
walks right out of here.
We don't have the
man power, Ivan.
Tranquilize him.
Yeah, right.
Ivan, he's killed nine people.
He will surely try to kill us.
Kevin's no longer human.
He thinks he's a wolf.
A werewolf.
A werewolf?
I prefer the term lycanthrope.
I was bitten by a werewolf.
It's all right.
It's going to be just fine.
But it bit me.
Do you know what that means?
It's sheila.
I'm here.
Everything's going to be fine.
I promise.
He bit me.
It's just an old wives tale.
Surely you don't really
believe that, now do you?
It's all right.
Just calm down.
Look, I've cleansed the
wound, so there shouldn't
be any infection, all right?
I think it might be wise if
we gave her a little something
to sedate her.
Perhaps you're right.
It was a werewolf, wasn't it?
Don't be absurd.
There's really no
such thing as--
Yes, you're right.
It's a werewolf.
And it bit me.
And I'm going to turn
into something like that?
Help me, please.
Don't worry,
it'll be all right.
Ivan, what are you saying?
It's no use hiding
it from her, Sheila.
We've got to tell
her the truth, then
we can kill the lycanthrope
and get her back to the states
where we can help her.
If we leave him where
he is, he'll die anyway.
It's the humanitarian
thing to do.
Either kill him, or let him go.
Is there anything you can do?
Or am I going to turn
like that thing out there?
I'm not sure yet.
But now I'll show you
why I became a scientist.
Just lie calm and relax.
Go ahead and give
her a sedative.
I feel myself changing.
Of course you do.
Now just relax.
What are you telling her?
She's not changing.
What kind of mind game are
you playing here anyway?
You're trying to
control her, aren't you?
I'm not doing a thing to her.
She's going to do
it all to herself.
That's the strange
thing about science.
All I've got to do is observe.
She's a simple native.
Her mind is weak.
It's the power of suggestion.
I'm sorry, but I can't let
you do this, husband or not.
You didn't feel the
necessity to bring
back the lycanthrope for study,
so I'll create one of my own.
That's impossible.
Not with the human mind.
By taking her back, we'll be
able to observe her through all
the stages of change.
And by letting
Kevin go free, I'll
be able to come back and see how
an advanced case of lycanthropy
develops.
You talk about
Kevin and Rosary
as if there were some
kind of lab experiment.
And Rosary's not
even lycanthropic.
Not yet, but she may well be.
She's well on her way to
becoming quite insane.
This is a side of you
I've never seen, Ivan.
It's what I do, darling.
I study the human mind, and
you protect the environment.
And our government pays us
quite well, if you'll remember.
But this is cruel.
This is science.
Now give her a sedative.
I'll take care of the rest.
Please help me.
No, don't worry.
Everything's going to
be just fine, I promise.
I'll give you something
to help you sleep, OK?
Is everything all right, Cody?
He's been quiet for
almost 30 minutes.
You're against taking
him back, I suppose?
It's a risk we
don't have to take.
If man didn't take risks,
where would we be today?
No tools.
The luxuries.
No atom bomb.
The world would be
a far better place.
For you, my friend.
You're a survivalist.
You like living
hand-to-mouth, coming
and going as you please,
nothing to tie you down,
no business to keep up.
Just the survival
of the fittest.
Dr. Stein!
Stay where you are, Cody.
Stay away from that door.
I may not be as good a
shot as you or Mr. Parker,
but I will hit something
vital at this close range.
Think of what you're doing.
[gunshots]
Cody.
What happened?
Stein.
Son of a bitch.
[screams]
[gunshots]
Come in, Mr. Parker.
Drop your gun on the floor.
Kick it over here.
Have a seat.
What the hell is going on?
He's lost his mind, Bill.
Yeah, I know.
He just killed Cody.
Was he your
favorite, my darling?
I'd like to say it
was either him or me,
but I don't think Mr. Carlson
would have pulled the trigger.
He wasn't half the beast
you made him out to be.
What did she
tell you about me?
Oh, you would have
shot me dead, Mr. Parker.
You've got to stop him, Bill.
He's turning Rosary
into a lycanthrope.
How?
It's a mind control thing.
Suggestion.
As a matter of fact, she's
become quite lycanthropic.
That's impossible.
It hasn't even been
three hours yet.
It's a form of
insanity, my darling.
We know very little about it.
We must study it.
What's he talking
about, Sheila?
He's convinced her she's
been bitten by a werewolf.
It's a disease, Mr. Parker.
Insanity, remember?
We know very little about it.
We must study it.
She's going to turn
into one of those things?
She has become one of those
things, haven't you, my dear?
This has got to
be a bad dream.
Oh, no.
I assure you it's
a very good dream,
a scientist's dream come true.
Well, somewhere along the
line, doctor, you've become
very side-tracked.
I was supposed to come
down here and help
you find the data that
your team compiled
about the loss of the ozone.
I think you told me that
the fate of the world
depended on it.
Well, I'm convinced.
I've seen your lycanthrope, OK?
DR. STEIN: But we
were also supposed
to find out what
happened here, and that's
precisely what I'm doing.
A find like this comes
along once in a lifetime.
A find?
You call a murderous
monster a scientific find?
I can't explain it to you if
you won't have an open mind.
Stop!
It's my life's work!
[screams]
[gunshot]
Sit down!
Too bad.
I'd hoped she'd be the
one I could take back.
Now I'll have to tranquilizer
Mr. Johnson and take him back.
You'll never be able to
take him alive, doctor.
He's just going to kill
you and come back after us.
It's a risk I'll have to take.
SHEILA STEIN: You're a murderer.
Tie him up.
Listen, doctor, you
want to capture him,
you got to let us help you.
Sorry, but that won't work.
You've never going to
be able to do it alone.
There's a definite
conflict of interests here.
You're witnesses to a murder.
I've got to figure out
what to do with you two.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
I guess a double dose
should do the trick.
You're just going
to walk up to him
and ask him to drop his pants?
Let me worry about that.
Come here, my dear.
What are you going to do?
You didn't think I
was going to tie him up
and leave you loose, did you?
Even if you are right and
I am mad, I'm not stupid.
Well, I wouldn't call
going after that thing
with a syringe exactly bright.
Someday, you'll understand.
Psst.
The knife.
What?
Rosary's knife.
[squeaking]
Wait!
I'm not going to hurt you.
Wait, Kevin.
Think of it-- you're going
to be a great discovery.
Imagine, a man who
thinks himself a wolf.
Wait, wait!
Take your papers.
Got them.
Come on.
I'm not going to hurt you.
I'm not going to
let anyone hurt you.
I'm just going to put you
to sleep for a little while,
take you home.
[screaming]
[screams]
You'll hit Ivan.
I don't care.
[gunshots]
You hit him.
If it bleeds, I can kill it.
[screams]
[gunshots]
[howls]
[gunshot]
Silver bullets, my ass.
Well, Rosary, what do you
say we blow this pop stand?
[breathing]
[monkey squealing]
[heartbeat]
[animal noises]
[screams]
- Hey, hey, hey.
Relax.
It's just a dream.
Wow.
It seemed so real.
Yeah, well the bad
ones generally do.
Is this normal?
Normal?
For who?
Look, you've been through a lot.
I'll have the nurse stop
in and give you a sedative.
It'll help you sleep.
- Oh, no.
I don't want to sleep.
The dream.
Yeah.
Jake said he could set you up
with some counseling in Rio.
Jake?
You spoke to Jake?
Yeah.
You know, if I
didn't know better,
I'd say he was
checking up on you.
He told me the whole story.
You know, you are one
tough little girl.
He wants to take you home.
This came for you.
What is it?
It's a card.
Open it and see.
It's from Jake.
No!
What is it?
A silver bullet?
A friend of mine gave me this.
Doctor, when can I go home?
Well, as a matter of
fact, I told Jake he could
come pick you up tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
So soon?
Well, aside from
loss of blood,
some dehydration and fatigue--
and I took a piece of
lead out of your side
about the size of a quarter.
There's nothing I
can do for you now.
There's no reason why you
can't go home and recuperate.
You could recuperate
on a beach in Rio.
Let me take a look.
Now breath.
One more time.
Heart seems to be working.
Well, how does it look?
On you, my darling,
anything would look good.
You are too kind.
Look, I have some
other rounds to make.
I'll be back to
check on you later.
I'll have the nurse come in
and give you that sedative.
Try to get some rest.
I'll try.
But I keep on having this
dream I'm turning into a wolf.
It's all right.
The sedative will work.
I promise.
I don't know, doctor.
Rosary, there's no
such thing as a werewolf.
You were bitten by
a man, a human--
not a werewolf, but a human, OK?
Just keep telling yourself,
no such thing as werewolves.
Yeah.
Sure.
Whatever you say.
Sally?
Yes, doctor?
You need to check
the girl's vitals.
And a sedative,
something strong,
something to help her sleep.
OK.
Poor thing.
She's been through
a lot, hasn't she?
Yeah, but I'm going
to let her go tomorrow.
Do you think that's
a wise decision?
Doesn't matter.
There's nothing more
we can do for her here.
All right.
Well, I'll take care of it.
[screams]
You know, I've been doing
your country's dirty work--
Our country's dirty work.
Right, our country's dirty
work for the last 10 years.
I hear I'm one of the best
special agents around.
Yeah-- I think you
started that move.
Yeah, I can't find
out what's going on.
- Excuse me.
- Why are we here--
DIRECTOR: That's got it.
Do it again.
Why?
That was fucking great.
Understanding as ever.
No wonder she left you.
Fuck you.
That's no way to talk
an old friend Bill.
You ate her--
You need my help.
DIRECTOR: Cut.
You didn't think I
was going to tie him up
and leave you loose, did you?
Even if you are right and
I am mad, I'm not stupid.
Well, I wouldn't call going
after that thing with a syringe
exactly right.
Someday, you'll understand.
Psst, the knife.
I think we're--
[laughter]
You have quite a reputation
and come highly recommended.
I've been convinced
that you are one
of the best men for the job.
Yeah, what job is that?
Escorting my wife
and me back to our--
shit.
DIRECTOR: Cut.
Take two.
Escorting me and
my wife-- oh, shit.
DIRECTOR: Cut.
That line.
Escorting my wife and me back
to our outpost in the Amazon
and finding out what happened
to my scientific team.
Uh, excuse me, doctor.
What makes you think?
[babble]
DIRECTOR: 68, take four.
You think you hear something.
Who's there?
Lee, is that you?
DIRECTOR: You're sure you do.
BILL PARKER: Somewhere along
the line you got side-tracked,
doctor.
I was supposed to help
you find and return
data compiled by your
associates to repair the ozone.
I believe the fate of
the world depended on it.
Now that I've seen your
lycanthrope, I'm convinced.
DR. STEIN: But we
were also supposed
to find out what happened.
DIRECTOR: Cut.
[laughter]
48, take two.
Who's he?
Dr. Springer.
Got a real pretty mouth
on him, doesn't he?
He squealed like a pig.
Look at him now.
[laughter]
Who's he?
Dr. Springer.
Fucking Romulans.
Excuse me?
DIRECTOR: Cut.
[laughter]
23L, take four.
Action.
JAKE: A nice cold beer
sure does hit the spot.
That is does, Jake.
[airplane]
DIRECTOR: Cut.
Speed.
Mark.
[MUSIC - PITCH BLUE JAM, "TAKE A
REST"]
SONG: Mississippi delta.
Hot day, crying child.
Mother, no father.
Yeah, the river runs wild.
No idea.
And a thoughtless brow.
Like the people of the daily.
Be the youth too wild.
You got to take a rest now.
Take it easy.
Take a rest now, baby.
Man and a boy are staring
at the edge of the pond.
One sees days to go while
one sees days long gone.
Yeah.
Restless pond, and
a reminiscing smile.
The man and a boy, they're gonna
take a little rest for a while.
Take it easy, baby.
Take a rest now.
Take it easy.
Take a rest now, baby.
You got to-- got to
take a rest now, baby.
Want to take it easy now.
You got to take a rest now.
Take it easy.