[music playing]
[gutteral growling]
[animal cries]
[bell ringing]
NARRATOR: After a promising
start at the Calgary Herald,
I took the train across
Canada and sailed to London
to make a name for myself.
But after a year as a junior
reporter on the Gazette,
my biggest assignment was
a dispatch on the opening
of the king's private zoo.
I was going nowhere,
until one day I
decided to speak up for myself.
Heard from Arthur yet?
No.
Nothing yet, Mr. Malone.
- Evening, Mr. Malone.
- Hey there, Jim.
McArdle in there?
- He is.
I was just off to
give him these.
MAN: Where the hell is that boy?
Coming, sir.
Let me do it, Jim.
Mr. McArdle.
Evening, sir.
Mr. Johnson.
I need to speak
with you right now.
All righty.
Well, what is it, Malone?
I request a transfer to the
front, sir, of whatever war
that might be in need
of a good reporter.
I'm sorry, Malone,
but we have a--
a shortage of good
wars at the moment.
Oh.
Well, uh, whatever dangerous
assignment that might
justify a man's existence.
Justify a man's existence?
Yes, sir.
Preferably far, far away.
Well, I'm afraid I have no
wars on distant, exotic places
I might send a junior reporter.
There is one assignment
of some importance.
What's that?
It might be just the
thing you're looking for.
Well, there's a George
Edward Challenger.
Oh, yes.
Yes, we do need a--
a good man to get an
interview with him.
Well, so Challenger, my boy.
This is your man.
There are some who
say he's the most
dangerous man in all London.
But I know that you are
just the man to handle this.
Now, if you'll
excuse us, we do have
a paper to get out tonight.
Oh, yes.
Thank you, sir.
You will not regret giving
me this opportunity.
[raucous laughter]
MCARDLE: 5 pounds he doesn't get
past Challenger's front door.
What's the angle, Mr. Malone?
ED (VOICEOVER): The
angle was I'd been had.
Are you off to
get an interview?
But they'd laugh out of
the other side of their faces
if I could just get
the Gazette a scoop.
The only interview
with this Professor
Challenger, whoever he was.
Everybody back home says
I'm a whiz with accents,
so I sent him a note posing
as a foreign scientist.
He fell for it.
Don Milan, I
received your letter,
and though I cannot think of
what part you may have in any
discussion of my
work, I will deign
to meet with you at the request
and time of my question.
You will have two minutes only.
Yours faithfully, George
Edward Challenger.
Como estas, senora.
Yes?
(ITALIAN ACCENT) I
have an appointment with
the great Professor Challenger.
You've obviously
never met my employer.
I have not had
the honor, senora.
Well, I apologize
to you in advance.
He's an absolutely
impossible person.
Absolutely impossible.
Forewarned.
As they say, he's fore-armed.
It is most considerate of
you, senora, forewarning--
Go quickly out of the room if
he seems inclined to violence.
And don't wait to
argue with him.
Several people have
been injured doing that.
I shall try to
keep that in mind.
I have no intention of arguing
with the great professor.
Well, see that you don't.
Don't mention reporters.
Reporters.
Of course.
That's as good a way as
was ever invented to ensure
a violent rage from the man.
[knocking]
Professor Challenger?
Your guest has arrived.
Now, remember what I told ya.
Professor Challenger.
Guiseppe Milano?
Yes.
I have come very far,
and at my own expense--
although that's no problem--
to tell you that you--
You say that you are a
great admirer of my work.
What exactly do you admire?
Why, your great research
into the field of animals.
My research on animals?
Of my vast body of work
in a myriad of fields,
you are particularly fascinated
by my research on animals?
Is that what they're
teaching of mine in, um--
Italy, was it?
Yes.
Where exactly in Italy?
Milano.
Guiseppe Milano from Milano.
How neat.
[speaking italian]
Si.
Si?
[speaking italian]
Ah, si.
Si.
So, uh, you agree that,
uh, the cranial index
is a constant factor.
Si.
And that you're
a fat, bald woman
with boils in your
behind, and two green cows
that give purple milk.
Uh--
You're the damndest
impostor in London!
A vile, crawling journalist with
no more Italian blood in you
than you have human decency
in your composition.
Sir, I only hoped--
To make a name for yourself
by furthering the preposterous
lies and fairy
tales that are told
about George Edward Challenger!
It's time that you
had your ears clipped,
and by God, George Edward
Challenger's the man to do it!
Listen here, sir, you can
be as abusive as you like.
All right, I'm not Italian--
in fact, I'm Canadian by
birth, but there is a limit.
You shall not assault me.
Shall I not?
You'll not be the
first of your kind
that I have thrown
out of this house.
You will, in fact, be
the 28th, I believe.
Don't be a fool, professor.
I'm 165 pounds,
as hard as nails,
and some 20 years your better.
[shouting]
Had enough?
What's all this?
This maniac attacked me.
Did you attack him?
It's not the first time, either.
You were in trouble last
month for the same thing.
And the month before.
Do you want to charge him, sir?
No, I don't.
I was to blame.
I-- I intruded on him.
He gave me fair warning.
Well, you're the first
one not to charge him.
Let's have no more such
goings on from you.
If there's anymore
trouble from him,
you call me straight
away, ma'am.
[laughter]
Now what?
Come up with me, mister--
Edward Malone.
Come on up, Mr. Malone.
Come on up.
Fond and frolicks in this house.
Sit down, Malone.
So, Mr. Guiseppe
Malone, journalist and
famous Italian impersonator.
Why have you gone
to such extravagant,
albeit inept
lengths, to find me?
I need a break, sir.
I need to make a name for
myself at the Gazette, so I--
I asked them for
a challenge, and--
the papers sent me to you.
McArdle and Johnson up to
their old tricks again, eh?
Mhm.
So, you want to challenge, eh?
Here.
Take a look at that.
Maple White.
Maple ?
That's an unusual name.
It's, uh, pretty
pedestrian stuff.
Press on.
What is this?
That, my young friend,
is the lost world.
Two years ago, I journeyed
to the upper reaches
of Lualaba river in the
heart of Central Africa.
It was my business to
visit that little known
and partially explored
country, and to examine
and catalog the fauna.
I was interrupted
from my studies
when I was summoned by a passing
tribesman to the deathbed
of a fellow traveler.
An American.
Over there!
GEORGE (VOICEOVER): I
knew nothing of this man,
nor what service I, with only
a slight knowledge of things
medical, might do for him.
But the tribesmen
were insistent.
Inside I found a man
who, through later
perusal of his scant belongings,
I discovered to be one
Maple White.
The tribesmen had
found him stumbling
through the jungle, bleeding
and half-mad with sickness.
My drawings.
My sketchbook.
You must go there.
They won't believe you.
But it's all true, you see?
It's all true.
It's the lost world.
GEORGE: It is his sketchbook
that you hold in your head.
From the contents
of the knapsack,
it was quite clear
that Maple White
was something of
an artist, and also
something of an adventurer.
You ever seen
anything like that?
No, I haven't.
And to what known species
might that bone belong?
I must confess that I
haven't the faintest notion.
[laughter]
You need not be ashamed
to confess your ignorance.
For I doubt that the
entire membership
of the Royal Zoological
Institute could identify it.
It belongs, I am quite
sure, to that beast there.
What the hell is that?
That is exactly what I
was intrigued to find out.
So intrigued that I
resolved at that very moment
to abandon my own
travel itinerary,
and to set out to find
that strange place.
I continued downriver by
canoe, and my companions
where Pedro, a Portuguese
who served as a translator,
and a powerful man named Pujo,
the leader of my small band
of native bands.
I had found a rudimentary map
in Maple White's belongings,
and I set out to
retrace his steps.
Let's try over there.
GEORGE (VOICEOVER): The map was
vague, and difficult to follow.
Many times we were
forced to retrace
our path after days
of futile paddling
in the wrong direction.
After many weeks on the river,
I finally found the spot where
Maple White had gone ashore.
We continued on foot for many
days, our supplies of food
running dangerously low.
It was tough going, and it began
to wear out at our strength.
And at Pedro's loyalty.
Unbeknownst to myself
or the loyal Pujo, Pedro
had become fixated
upon the knapsack.
He was sure it contained
some great treasure--
jewels or valuable stones--
because I guarded
it so intently.
This I did not learn
until we'd almost
reached the hidden plateau
of Maple White's book,
and by then it was
almost too late.
Pedro, what the
devil are you--
[screaming]
[gunfire]
Challenger!
GEORGE (VOICEOVER): Pedro
had cut my leg to the bone.
Our bearers ran
off into the night.
There was no choice
but to turn back.
But first, I had
to get a glimpse
of the astonishing world
Maple White had sketched.
When I saw that great
vista, the pain in my legs
seemed to disappear.
But I knew that I had
found something tremendous.
Tremendous and
completely unprecedented.
We've found it, Pujo.
We've found it!
[shouting]
GEORGE: That was
all I saw of it--
a glimpse.
But it was enough
to make me believe.
Believe what?
That what I had seen
was a pterodactyl.
A creature thought extinct
for millions of years,
and that they lived there, in
a world cut off from evolution
and the forces of nature.
The lost world.
That's-- quite a story.
I'm afraid that
is all my colleagues
are inclined to call it.
A story.
No one would believe me.
On my return to London I
attempted to communicate
my great find to my colleagues
at the Royal Zoological
Institute, only to be met with--
derision and cruel jokes.
Certainly you had photographs,
or some kind of proof?
No.
All lost.
Lost in a run in with some
rapids that capsized our canoe,
and nearly cost Pujo
and myself our lives.
Well, if you were inclined
not to believe the story,
what would you say to that?
I think that any man that
has the courage to make a claim
like yours--
to seem foolish, to--
to accept ridicule,
and not give up the fight--
I think that man has earned
the right to be heard out.
You are no fool, Malone!
You are no fool at all!
You want a challenge.
Is that it?
Well, by God, you
shall have one.
Your coming here today has
given me a capital idea--
an idea on how to
turn the tables on all
those fools that scoff at me.
Come with me tonight,
and I will give
you the challenge of your life.
ED (VOICEOVER): An
exclusive interview
with the infamous George
Edward Challenger.
And what a story.
I mean, this is
front page material.
Old man McArdle's going
to lose his 5 pound bet.
Too bad.
Mr. Malone!
Mr. Malone?
What-- Jim?
What are you doing here?
I thought you might need--
an assistant.
I thought I was going
to be the youngest
reporter in London.
Come on.
Let's see what trouble
we can get into, eh?
[pounding gavel]
Ladies and gentlemen,
please, can we have some quiet?
Thank you.
Now to business.
We are gathered here today
to present an award of honor
to our distinguished
colleague, Professor Summerlee.
[applause]
Where's Challenger?
Probably out in the streets,
slugging it out with a cabbie
over the price of a fare.
[applause]
Distinguished
guests, friends--
You are no friend of mine.
How dare you?
I repeat, you're no
friend of mine, Waldron.
Nor of science.
If you are, as I suspect, about
to lavish praises on that--
that boring fraud who dares
to call himself a scientist--
Challenger, you scoundrel.
Are you referring to me?
That I am, Summerlee.
You wish to honor
the man that made
Professor Summerlee the
exalted scholar he is today?
Then honor me.
That's quite
enough, Challenger.
[laughter and applause]
Professor Summerlee's entire
distinguished academic career
has been made
solely by rebuttal,
but his own personal standards.
The man has furor.
I'll give him that.
While I risked life and limb
accumulating the hard facts
of science, and-- and
molding them into theories,
Professor Summerlee sat
comfortably by his nice
kitchen fire, in his armchair.
Theories?
Facts?
No, Professor Challenger.
Fantasies.
Pipe dreams.
Claims of such little worth
as, say, the discovery of what
you call the lost world.
Oh, you may laugh.
You may laugh!
All-- all discoverers have
met with the same response.
Bravo!
You deride those who push
back the frontiers of science.
You persecute the prophets.
Galileo, Darwin, Challenger!
[applause]
Or, perhaps, you've
already found Galileo
and Darwin living happily
in that lost world of yours?
[laughter]
No, sir, I did not.
But you may.
What do you mean by that?
Are you prepared to
stand by your word?
I demand that this institution
mount an expedition
to examine my findings,
to verify or disprove
my claims that prehistoric life
still exists upon this planet.
I demand it in the
name of science!
[applause]
And I demand that Professor
Summerlee leads the expedition.
[applause]
[pounding gavel]
Order!
Mr. Challenger's motion will
be discussed in due course.
In due course.
Deal with it now!
Order, order!
We will have order!
In the meantime--
In the meantime,
we are left to wonder
if perhaps the professor's
claims are true.
And who might
you be, young man?
I'm Edward Malone,
from the Gazette.
I think the people of
London-- my readers--
deserve to know the truth.
Yes, well, I'm sure you and
your readers would like nothing
better than have the institute
spend a fortune traveling far
and wide simply to refute
the claims of a well-known
madman and liar.
You libelous pennant!
Yes, sir.
And what's more, I volunteer
to go on this expedition.
That is, if you are
leading it, sir.
What are you gonna
say, Summerlee?
Well, Summerlee?
I will be delighted to
lead any expedition that
will expose Professor
Challenger as the utter fool I
know him to be.
And he will, then.
It is decided.
Professor Summerlee will lead
this expedition to Africa,
and Mr. Malone will report upon
his findings to the newspapers.
Are there any other volunteers?
Could I come?
A boy?
[laughter]
I volunteer.
I would like to join
this expedition.
Well, if there are no
more serious volunteers,
I announce this
meeting adjourned.
Excuse me.
The doctors of the institute
will meet tomorrow morning to--
JENNIFER: Mr. Chairman?
Discuss the funding
of the Sumerlee--
JENNIFER: Mr. Chairman,
I demand you hear me out.
Mr. Chairman?
[applause]
I want to go, Mr. Malone.
I could be a big help.
You know I could.
Well, I don't know, Jim.
I mean, these
scientists won't be too
happy to have a reporter along.
To take a boy, as well--
I'm not a boy.
I'm almost 13.
You have to let me go.
I just don't see how
I can manage it, Jim.
I thought you were my friend?
Jim?
Congratulations, Mr. Malone.
That is really--
- Thanks.
Jim, wait!
It's out of the question.
I will not have Challenger
on my expedition.
Your expedition?
I have explored
Africa for over 20--
You nominated me as
leader, Challenger.
I will not have you along,
messing up my well-made plans.
If he goes, I will not.
Confound you, Summerlee.
I will stay behind.
MAN: Miss, you simply
mustn't go in there.
JENNIFER: There's no
way you're going to--
Yes?
And we're going in.
This is private.
My card, Professor Murray.
Miss J.A. Nielson, of Chicago.
I'm sorry to
interrupt, gentlemen,
but I was not given a
chance to speak last night.
Unforgivable.
The students are a
rowdy lot, you see?
I would like to
join this expedition.
Good lord.
A suffragette.
Exactly.
I am an experienced wildlife
photographer, professor.
For the Smithsonian and the
National Geographic Society,
among others.
You will need documentation of
anything you find in Africa.
I have traveled most of the
world, and could possibly--
Yes, I'm sure
you have, my dear.
I'm sure you have.
But unfortunately, the
policy of this institute
does not allow women to
go on our expeditions.
Policy?
Well, gentlemen, it's 1912.
I'd say it's time you
changed your policy.
You'll be hearing from me.
Monstrous.
Extraordinary.
Her family is one of
the wealthiest in America,
and great contributors
to science.
Perhaps we could consider--
Murray, I am adamant.
The woman will not
go on the expedition.
She will only
endanger the mission.
Morning, my dear.
Good morning,
Professor Murray.
Good morning, Malone.
Professor?
Murray, I thought
we agreed that
the policy of the institute--
My dear Summerlee,
I have to inform you,
the directors of the institute
have granted a special approval
for Miss Nielson to
accompany your expedition
as our official photographer.
She offered to fund
the entire project.
My dear Summerlee,
how could we say no?
Good luck, Miss Nielson.
Get a fine photograph
of my pterodactyl.
Professor Challenger,
I assure you,
if there's anything to
photograph, I'll get it.
If we could get
on board, please?
We do have a timetable.
Ah-- I do wish I was
going with you both.
- Malone!
- Henry!
Over here!
Excuse me.
For the long, hard nights.
Bon voyage, old chap.
Good luck.
Happy hunting, and all that.
Thanks.
ED (VOICEOVER): Dispatched
to the London Gazette,
by Edward Malone.
After much controversy, the
Summerlee expedition set
out today for darkest Africa.
Some members of the
expedition doubt the wisdom
of leaving Professor
Challenger behind,
but Summerlee is adamant.
The question remains, however--
how will Summerlee lead us
to a place he does not know?
Preposterous, Challenger.
After all, I am the
leader of the expedition.
Cabin 5B, please.
Summerlee, you will
take this letter,
and you will not
open it until you
reach Kalemie at the headwaters
of the Lualaba river.
Then, at the designated
hour, you will open it,
and you will receive your
directions to the lost world.
Amateur theatrics.
Come on, Mr. Malone.
We've wasted enough
time already.
Goodbye, sir.
Goodbye, lad.
That eye's looking
better already.
Oh, if only he wasn't
such a pompous ass!
Oh, I say, how good of you.
Ha ha!
Tally ho!
Fine sailing!
Bon voyage, mon capitan!
Au revoir, professor.
Adieu.
Ah.
Wow.
Is there someone down here?
[coughing]
Hard to get
comfortable in here.
A stowaway, you say?
Well, where is he?
Oh, this is him.
Why, I thought it was--
what's the meaning of this, boy?
I only wanted
to help out, sir.
Help out?
How could you possibly help out?
Well-- I'm very handy, sir.
And-- I wanted an adventure.
I wanted a chance
to prove myself.
Let me give him a
talking to, professor.
Yes, you do that.
I've got more--
Jim?
Captain?
I'm surprised at you.
- I'm sorry, Mr. Malone.
- Yeah?
Well-- don't be.
I know what it's
like to be ambitious.
You gotta take chances.
Jim, you're on the team now.
But Summerlee--
What's he going to do?
Turn the boat around?
Throw you overboard?
Nope, we're stuck with you.
Shake on it.
ED (VOICEOVER): To the London
Gazette, dateline Kalemie.
This missionary outpost
is at the farthest end
of the road from Das Es Salaam.
It is an odious collection
of gold prospectors, natives,
missionaries, Portuguese
on the run from the law,
donkeys, and goats.
This is the last dispatch
I can send by telegraph.
From here we travel
down the Lualaba river,
through unsettled territory.
We hope Professor
Summerlee can find
the spot from which
Maple White trekked
inland from the lost world.
- Malu?
- Yes?
Don't let the
children wander off.
Excuse me?
I couldn't help noticing
that you're American.
Edward Malone, London Gazette.
Kate Crenshaw.
I run the settlement store.
Oh.
And this is, uh--
Rebecca.
Miss Rebecca.
It's not often that I meet
someone new who speaks English.
Yes, well, we're hiring
porters for an expedition up
the river, and so far the only
one we've found that speaks
any English is, uh-- him.
Ah.
Gomez.
Yeah.
He is Portuguese,
from the coast.
Not one of my best students.
He learned the language, but
I'm afraid the basic principles
of Christian charity
were lost on him.
I was afraid of them.
Personally, I have absolutely
no doubt about your honesty.
These testimonials you
gave me are impressive.
Very impressive.
We should hire, uh, only
those men who are very strong,
who can carry the heavy
loads, and who know the river.
Mm.
[non-english speech]
These are the men
from the Mojo tribe.
They are the best.
What language do they speak?
Only I can speak both their
languages-- yours and theirs.
That's not so, Gomez.
- Malu?
- Yes?
Could you come here?
Professor Summerlee, could you
join us for a moment, please?
There's someone I'd
like you to meet.
This is Malu.
She could accompany you
as interpreter and guide.
It's an honor
to meet you, sir.
My pleasure.
And you, sir.
You, uh-- you speak
excellent English.
I learned at the
mission school, sir.
Miss Kate taught as well.
Certainly did.
I'm, uh, Professor Summerlee.
This is Edward--
I'm-- I'm Edward Malone.
This is-- Professor Sumerlee.
And I'm Jenny Nielson.
Nielson You don't have
to call us sir or madam.
That, uh, rascal back
there, that's-- that's Jim.
Hiya.
Is she the only one that
can speak both languages?
Meeting capable women is
a new experience for him.
I would like to come with you.
That is, if you can manage
the children, Miss Kate.
Oh, we'll get
by somehow, Malu.
We always do.
Very well.
Gomez, you select the men,
and make the arrangements.
Yes, professor.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Now, these canoes--
A tuppenny worth
of all candies, miss.
Stocking up, are you Are
you a part of the expedition?
- Oh, look at this.
- Yeah.
Ah.
Where are you going?
Well, this has
gotta be the warmest.
Where is that?
No, not that one.
Why not?
I did a photo story
on a family of zebras
at the San Francisco
zoo last spring.
I'd hate to think of them
turning out like that.
Well, personally, I'd rather
be skinned than in a cage
for the rest of my life.
[mock whimpering]
I don't like to
think of wild animals
as caged or skinned, Mr. Malone.
And I don't like people
who make jokes about it.
Really?
Well, I'm not freezing to death
on account of some stupid idea
about zebras' rights.
I'll take it.
And, uh, four of those.
Attention, everybody.
I have a very important
announcement to make.
To be opened at Kalemie upon
the 15th of November at 12:00,
precisely.
Ah.
One minute to.
Should be precise on that.
Nothing.
No map.
This is the proof that
the lost world is a fraud,
and that buffoon Challenger
is a liar, and a fake.
Am I late?
I thought the time
agreed was 12:00
noon, if I recall correctly.
[chiming]
Perfect timing.
Ha ha ha!
If this is your idea of
a joke, I am not amused.
Oh, my dear
Summerlee, you don't
really think that I would allow
you to go without me, do you?
Besides, since I'm the only
person who knows the way,
they have to take me with them.
All right.
You might be coming
along, you scoundrel,
but let us not forget who is
in command of this expedition.
Of course not,
my dear Summerlee.
[laughter]
Come on!
ED (VOICEOVER): Somewhere
on the Lualaba river.
We've been paddling
for 17 straight days.
Sometimes we feel we're being
watched from the jungle,
but it's been a week since we
saw a human being of any kind.
Is Challenger lost?
How about a
little help, Gomez?
I'm so sorry, princess.
[non-english speech]
How far downriver
do we travel?
Professor Challenger's
the only one who knows.
He's keeping it a secret.
If you have a map or
a chart, Challenger,
I should like to know
where we are heading.
Any map is up here
in my head, Summerlee.
And as for where we're heading,
you as the intrepid leader
of our extinction should know.
To the lost world.
ED (VOICEOVER): On the Lualaba.
Much relief all around.
Challenger has found the
spot where Maple White's map
says we should start inland.
Right.
That's as far as we go by canoe.
From here on, it's on foot.
ED (VOICEOVER): After
19 days on the water,
all are happy to
be on firm ground.
Listen!
[drums playing]
What are they saying, Malu?
The drums speak to the
tribes in the highlands.
They say we are coming.
Right.
We'll cover the canoes as best
we can, and then press on.
We'll spend the night here,
and start early in the morning.
As you wish, Summerlee.
I'm sleeping over here.
Gomez, my cot.
Gomez!
ED (VOICEOVER):
Camp on the Lualaba.
It is impossible to
tell from the drums
how close the natives are.
We must be constantly
on our guard.
[sigh]
I'll keep watch.
You're cold.
- You should see the zebra.
- Malone!
Would you call me Edward?
Please?
Edward.
Do you think they
want to stop us?
Maybe they do.
Maybe they want
their world to stay--
lost.
Miss Nielson, go ahead.
Come along, now.
Chop chop.
Are they going to
attack us, professor?
Oh, I don't think so, my boy.
Their purpose is
far more subtle.
They mean to frighten us.
It's working.
How much further, Challenger?
Oh, a day or two.
Three.
Are we lost?
Because if we are--
It seems that our pursuers
will follow us no further.
Which means, my dear
Summerlee, we're getting close.
Wonderful.
Come on.
Oh, look.
Ah.
Come here, you fellows.
This is the place.
There it is.
Just as I said.
JENNIFER: It's beautiful.
Well, there's
nothing remarkable.
We've all seen igneous
extrusions before.
You'll see, Summerlee.
You'll see.
The way ahead lies
through that valley.
Well, it can't be any
worse than the jungle.
Come on.
[non-english speech]
ED (VOICEOVER): The closer
we get to the cliff,
the higher it looks.
The rock face is
sheer, and very steep.
There seems to be no way up.
It looks like it may
be impossible to climb.
That is not a
pretty way to die.
John Cougan Detroit.
Companion of Maple White.
Somebody left him there to
make sure we got the message.
Visitors not welcome.
We're being followed.
[non-english].
Challenger!
Don't shoot!
It's Pujo!
Pujo!
Yes, Challenger.
My good and faithful friend.
How did you find us?
In Kalemie I learned
too late of your return,
but the drums tell
me where you are.
You've arrived in good time.
We are about to
enter the lost world.
[non-english speech]
Good heavens!
Did you see that?
I didn't see anything.
Damn your dim old
eyes, Summerlee.
That was a pterodactyl.
Oh, fiddlesticks.
It's a stork.
A stork?
Why not a giant
African fruit bat?
They're as blind as you are!
And you, sir, are a fantacist!
Unless we can fly like a
bird, pterodactyl or otherwise,
how do we get up there?
Yes, well, what do we do now?
We are better prepared
than you think, Summerlee.
George, that box.
Put it there.
Professor Challenger,
you never cease to amaze.
And you continue
to delight me, Jenny.
Need some help, Professor?
No, no, no.
George, the grappling hook.
George.
[non-english].
Right.
Everybody stand well back.
Now, you might care
to cover your ears.
1, two, three!
JIM: It's brilliant.
Ha!
First time.
Right.
Who's going up first?
I'm a little overweight
for this sort of thing.
I've never climbed
a mountain in my life.
I must admit that in my youth,
my hobby was mountaineering.
Frankly, I was rather good.
Oh, come now, Summerlee.
No time for your jokes.
I never joke about
risking my neck.
Uh, could I come?
Why not?
Up you go, lad.
[non-english speech]
You all right, lad?
Yes, sir.
Look at that.
We did it!
Heave.
Heave!
Take my hat.
You can do it, Mr. Malone.
Good for you, sir.
It's up the top, Pujo!
Yeah.
Take a look, Malone.
Quite meticulous.
Pujo.
PUJO: Yes?
Take the men, and
set up a base camp.
Will do.
[non-english].
Gomez.
Gomez!
Yes?
Guard the end of the rope.
Fine!
Any help with that
camera, Miss Nielson?
First let me take a picture.
Hold still.
Good.
I'll be right there.
We should fence ourselves
in with these thron bushes.
Who knows what's out there.
[laughter]
What was that?
Malone?
Come with me.
[laughter]
Challenger!
You remember Pedro?
Who died two years ago?
Your killed him!
He was my brother!
Now you are trapped,
and you will die!
You are a greater
scoundrel than Pedro, Gomez.
And you deserve the same fate!
[gun cocking]
Save your
ammunition, professor.
We may need it.
We're stranded here.
Now, Pythagoras said--
ED (VOICEOVER): Base
camp in the lost world.
With our long road
gone, we have no hope
of getting back down the cliff.
I hope this dispatch
will somehow
find its way to the Gazette,
so I will continue writing.
Come along, Challenger.
ED (VOICEOVER):
Despite our despair
at being stranded
on this plateau,
we plan to begin
exploration at first light.
Going to drop today's
report in the next mailbox?
Ha.
Actually, the last letter I
sent back was from Kalemie.
Challenger won't let me
publish till we return, anyway.
Don't lose that notebook.
I wonder-- what's it
really like out there?
Edward?
Look.
The stars are all turned around,
and the moon's on its side.
It really is a different
world out here.
Well, it's not London.
Chicago, maybe.
Do you think Malu
would find our world
as strange as we find hers?
I never thought about it.
Why?
I was just wondering.
Goodnight.
Oh, look.
[animal cries]
[growling]
Dinosaurs.
Thought extinct for
millions of years.
Alive and well, and
standing before us.
Challenger-- I misjudged you.
Let me shake your hand.
I must get a picture.
Careful!
It's all right, Miss Nielson.
I believe that they
are anatosauri.
So Plant eating dinosaurs.
Perfectly harmless.
But that doesn't apply
to all dinosaurs, does it?
Oh, no, no.
There were huge,
carnivorous dinosaurs.
Potentially man eaters.
What?
All right.
Hold still, boys.
Huh?
[laughter]
ED (VOICEOVER): Trekking
in the lost world.
One imagines an encounter with
dinosaurs would be frightening,
but the anatosauri were
not at all intimidating.
[squawking]
ED (VOICEOVER): We press on,
in search of new discoveries.
Oh, I say--
I'd like to take some
geological samples.
To help me establish
the age of plateau.
Go ahead, my dear Summerlee.
Oh-- A bit of a stench.
It's interesting.
What is?
It looks as if it
could be oil bearing--
Professor!
Whoa!
Are you there?
Professor Summerlee!
I'm all right.
Thank you.
If only I could find
my blasted glasses.
[chittering]
I have them.
Ah!
Oh--
What's down there, professor?
It's extraordinary.
What is?
Blast you, don't
keep us in suspense!
It's a cave of some sort.
Very old.
Probably the result of
some geological upheaval.
I need some light.
Please.
Thank you.
[heavy breathing]
Hello?
[echo]
[screeching]
Hey!
Give me the rope.
[shouting]
Could you please--
ah!
[screeching]
Professor Summerlee,
are you all right?
Can you help me, up, please?
Hang on!
Ah!
[screeching]
Great scott.
They're pterodactyls!
[shouting]
Good man, Malone!
Come on, now!
Thank you.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Oh, good.
Confound you, Summerlee.
You've frightened them.
Ah, they're all right now.
Well, thank you, my dear.
It's not very serious.
Vicious birds.
Pterodactyls, Summerlee.
Pterodactyls.
Not birds.
The ancestors of birds.
And judging from the
rocks around their pit,
they could have been there
since the, oh, triassic era.
Cretaceous era, I think.
Challenger, I may have been
wrong about the dinosaurs,
but don't tell me my geology.
It's my field.
Speaking of rocks--
I've been looking at that one.
We should be able to get
a pretty good overall look
at the plateau from up top.
You're not proposing to
climb it, are you, dear boy?
Well, as we know, I'm not
much of a climber, but, uh--
No problem.
Keep an eye out for snakes.
Well done, Jim!
There's a great, big lake!
It's amazing!
I'll tell you all about
it when I come down!
I saw an ape.
Or a man.
What?
A little of both, actually.
He had a painted
face, like a skeleton.
We'd better keep a
close watch out tonight.
Yes.
[snoring]
[growling]
Whoa!
[shouting]
Where were you going?
I'm sorry, Mr. Malone.
I saw a light from up that rock.
I thought I'd
investigate a little.
The jungle is no
place for a kid--
What?
[shouting]
What is this, a
late night party?
Let me up.
Oh, up?
Yeah.
You should learn
to be more careful.
If I hadn't recognized you,
I would have used this.
Come on.
Let's go.
- Yeah.
Back to the camp.
I want to see that lake.
Jim!
It's not far.
All right.
But I'm going first.
The two of you
follow, close behind.
No.
I think that I should go first.
I am more accustomed
to the jungle.
All right.
Come.
Mr. Malone.
Look.
I wonder what's under the water?
That's not an animal.
That's sulfur.
Nasty stuff.
Well, I've seen
enough for one night.
I'm right behind you.
I read in a book that
man eating dinosaurs
may have hunted at night.
I hope this dinosaur
didn't read the same book.
I think he did.
- Run!
Run!
Come on!
[growling]
[sniffing]
It smells us.
- Wait here.
- Wait.
Malu!
Smear the juice on your face.
What?
Just do it.
[sigh]
You stink.
So do you.
Morning.
It's a wonderful day.
They'll be wondering
what happened to us.
I smell like a
prehistoric fruit salad.
So McArdle bet Johnson
he couldn't do it.
Is that right?
No one's ever
done this before.
Getting with the
Challenger, I mean.
Really?
This whole thing--
Jenny?
Challenger!
Someone's been in the camp.
Summerlee!
Blood.
Blood?
Jenny!
Oh, god!
How could I have
left them alone?
Oh, poor Jenny.
It was that skeleton man.
More than one, I'd say.
They know nothing about guns, or
they wouldn't have left these.
The blood has left a trail.
It's fresh.
Maybe an hour old.
Let's pray
they're still alive.
[shouting]
[singing]
There's Summerlee.
And that's Jenny.
What are they doing to them?
And-- and who are
those other people?
It looks like
they're preparing
them for some kind of ritual.
Where is Challenger?
There.
On the right.
[shouting]
[horn blowing]
What's he up to?
[roaring]
Listen.
Ha ha ha!
[non-english speech]
Yes, yes.
Now, my name is Challenger.
Professor Challenger from
Cambridge University.
Member of the Royal
Zoological Society.
Yes, yes.
Now, look, my dear chap--
[non-english speech]
[shouting]
[singing]
They're going to feed
them to the dinosaurs.
But why?
- No time to wait for an answer.
- Wait!
There's too many of them.
We can't just let them die!
Wait a second.
I just remembered
something I read in a book.
It might just work.
I need wood, for
a very hot fire.
And-- and the linint
of your jacket.
Quickly.
[singing]
Where are you taking him?
What are you
doing with this man?
Let this man go!
Let this man go, you--
what the devil is it
you're doing with him?
[non-english speech]
[growling]
[screaming]
[non-english speech]
Let go of me!
Untie me!
Get your hands off me!
Let go of me!
I said, let go!
Summerlee, I'm terribly sorry!
That's all right!
I hope Jim's idea works.
There it is.
[gunfire]
Look!
Balloon!
Balloon from the gods!
Run!
Run for it!
Excuse me, please.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Jenny!
Over here!
Malone!
I thought you'd never get here.
This way!
Good work, Malone.
Look out!
[gunfire]
Come on, Jenny!
[shouting]
Go, Malone!
[gunfire]
[shouting]
Come on!
You can do it!
Do those people
look friendly to you?
Look there, professor!
Handy form of defense, then!
Here!
[non-english speech]
But
He is Palala, the
chief of his tribe.
And this is their home.
He welcomes us to join
him and his people,
where we can all be safe.
Tell him we
would be delighted.
[non-english speech]
[drums playing]
[singing]
[laughter]
Malu.
Does this dance mean anything?
The dance speaks of
the history of the tribe.
It calls upon the gods
to reunite the tribe,
to heal the good ones.
The good ones?
The skeletal man and
chief Palala's people
were all one once.
they worship the dinosaurs
as the embodiment
of the spirit's will on Earth.
So, how do you tell a
good one from a bad one?
The plant eating
dinosaurs are the good ones.
They represent the
spirit's kindness.
Chief Palala's people
have lived in peace
with them for centuries.
So, the bad ones
are man eaters, then?
The man eating
dinosaurs are feared,
like evil gods or devils.
How did the tribes divide?
Not so long ago,
the witch doctor
convinced some of the
other members of the tribe
to worship the evil ones.
[non-english speech]
Good heavens!
Oh, look.
A baby pterodactyl.
Poor little chap.
You don't look so well.
It's sick, isn't it?
All the good ones are sick.
The tribe tries to heal them.
They dance every night
for their recovery.
Hello, Percy.
It's fascinating.
Quite a specimen.
It all but confirms my theory
of Jurassic extinction,
all predicated on
microbiologic contagion.
Your stupid theory?
Is that all you care
about, professor?
Living creatures are dying, and
you're hatching a new theory.
Mr. Malone!
It's Summerlee!
He's gone!
Huh?
[non-english speech]
I understand, Imana.
Shh.
Quiet.
They're the same t same
leaves they had on us.
They feed them to the dinosaurs.
The plant is a medicine.
Just as I had supposed.
[growling]
[shouting]
Come on!
I need some of those leaves!
[shouting]
[non-english speech]
Go!
Hide!
[shouting]
[non-english speech]
Summerlee!
Where in heaven's
name have you been?
I was intrigued
by those wreaths
that the skeleton men
put around our necks
when they attempted to
feed us to the dinosaurs.
I wondered if that wasn't
the point of the whole thing.
I'm afraid I don't
follow you, Summerlee.
Well, when you
were a child, didn't
your mother ever try and
disguise your medicine
in something sweet?
Chocolate, for example?
Well, it's the same
concept here, Challenger.
We were the chocolate, and
these plants are the medicine.
Oh.
He likes it.
I think he likes it.
[screeching]
It's a miracle, professor.
Not really.
Just good science.
You were right, professor.
The Summerlee theory on the
extinction of the dinosaur.
They all became ill.
Some prehistoric
version of the plague.
And yet here, there
are some survivors.
Ergo, the antidote must
grow here on the plateau.
And Imana was a
brave young girl.
She showed me the way.
Imana.
[non-english].
Hello.
Summerlee?
That was a jolly good show.
Well done.
Thank you, Challenger.
[singing]
And it runs around the
split bamboo aqueduct
to the central point.
And the water is distributed
thusly, keeping the soil
in optimal growing condition.
[non-english speech]
It's a wonder,
Professor Summerlee.
Modern horticulture to
grow a prehistoric plant.
With the help of
modern technology,
Chief Palala's
people should find
a way to keep their good
ones healthy and strong.
Hey!
Give me my hat!
Come here, Imana.
I'll wager that now that
they've lost their leader,
these skeleton people are
anxious to rejoin the tribe.
[non-english speech]
[shouting]
Chief Palala says he will
do anything to repay you.
What do you wish for?
Thank the great chief.
Tell him our only
request is that he
show us a way down
from this plateau,
and back to our own world.
[non-english speech]
What's he say, Malu?
Palala says he will do
as we ask on one condition.
[non-english speech]
He says we must all
make a vow that we will
return if his people need us.
[non-english speech]
And we must all six return.
He says our power is as a group.
[non-english speech]
It's a tunnel!
Funny.
The compass is going wild.
Perhaps some volcanic
or seismic disturbance?
[non-english speech]
Without the compass,
Challenger, how can we
find our way out of this place?
Oh, come now, Summerlee.
I'm sure the chief
knows the way.
I think we're going
around in circles.
Oh, do shut up, Summerlee.
- What about over there?
- Malu, are we lost?
Huh?
He hasn't been this
way for many years.
[non-english speech]
This way, Summerlee.
Don't get lost.
Come on.
Good heavens.
[non-english speech]
Should have had a circus
training for this, Summerlee.
So at your university,
I suppose anything went.
Thanks.
That's quite a load
you've got there, Jim.
You want me to take
it for a while?
No.
I can handle it.
Due south again?
Look over here!
[non-english speech]
What did he say?
He said they
can go no further,
or they will be cursed
by their ancestors.
[non-english speech]
He says, do not
forget your vow.
We shall not forget.
It even smells
different down here.
It smells like home.
Now, if you dropped a plumb
line from the top of a pyramid,
what you would have is a series
of right angled triangles
to each corner.
So it's quite possible that,
uh, Pythagorus was influenced
by the Egyptian mathematicians.
Because they were quite
clearly sterling engineers.
Our canoes!
Ha ha!
And Pujo!
Professor!
Pujo!
My good friend!
Oh, Pujo!
It's so good to see you!
Where are the others?
They are cowards.
They hear strange noises
and see giant bat.
They leave.
I tried to stop them.
But the faithful
Pujo remained behind.
[gunshot]
Get down!
Take cover!
Get down, Jim!
GOMEZ: Challenger!
I knew you would return!
Just as I knew I would
be here to meet you!
Anyone see him?
GOMEZ: I do not want to
hurt the rest of you!
I just want Challenger!
All right, all of you--
put your guns down.
- What?
- Do I say.
Put your guns down.
What are you
doing, Challenger?
You've all risked your
necks proving my theories.
I cannot endanger the lives
of my friends any further.
All right, Gomez.
Come out.
Do your worst.
[laughter]
There he is.
Very large of you, Challenger.
On your knees!
Go to hell.
Adios, Professor Challenger.
[shouting]
Look out!
The gun!
[gunshot]
Should I kill him, professor?
[screaming]
No!
No.
Let the jungle have him.
[whimpering]
Thanks.
Goodbye, Edward.
Do you want to go
back to England with us?
My life is here.
I wouldn't be happy
anywhere else.
And as you know, this is quite
a different world from London.
This is my home.
Edward.
I hope we meet again someday.
Jenny.
A bit of Africa
to remember us by.
Thank you, Malu.
Oh.
Goodbye.
Sensational Challenger
meeting tonight!
Papers!
Sir!
Thank you, sir.
I say, what's
the meeting about?
I can make no comments.
All I can say, gentlemen, is
that you have the right place
for a great moment in history.
Mr. Summerlee--
Edward.
Tarp?
How good to see you.
Same here.
I brought a friend
of yours along.
Mr. McArdle!
Good to have you
back, Mr. Malone.
Well, I must admit, you don't
look any the worse for wear.
Thank you.
Here they come.
Oh, look.
There he is.
Ladies and gentlemen,
distinguished members--
I stand before you tonight
with irrefutable proof
of the existence, in
the heart of Africa,
of the land that I discovered
more than a year ago.
The lost world.
Professor Summerlee has agreed
to join me on this stand
to support my claim.
Bravo.
[applause]
Bravo!
Summerlee?
Don't tell me he managed to
pull the wool over your eyes?
Your claims are preposterous.
Professor Murray, perhaps
you would, uh, recap
the evidence that we placed
before your committee
this afternoon?
Professor Challenger, we
have examined the evidence.
Examined it very carefully.
And we find what
it proves nothing.
Yeah.
[crowd gasping]
- What a waste of time.
What do you mean?
What about the photographs?
Easily faked.
Well, what about
the reproductions
of the rock paintings?
The skullasaurus tooth!
You can't say
that that's faked!
It just does not stand up.
Not when what you claim is so--
absolutely unbelievable.
You're both men of science.
Surely you realize
that the onus--
the burden of proof--
is upon you.
You want proof?
Maybe I can help you.
What is he talking about?
No idea.
On our adventure, I
made a very good friend.
I think it best that
you all meet him.
There's nothing
that can convince me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
distinguished colleagues--
let me present a
creature thought
extinct for millions of years.
Percival, a baby pterodactyl.
No.
No!
Come on.
[screeching]
[applause]
Thank you.
This is amazing.
Nice to see you.
Take care.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Yes.
Would be for the
scientific testing.
So then I said, well, what
do you think, Mr. McArdle?
Do you think now you can
find a war for me to cover?
Jenny?
I hardly recognized you.
Malu gave me this emerald
when we left Kalemie.
It's beautiful.
Miss Nielson,
at the age of 12 I
wrote my first scientific
paper, on the metamorphosis
of the butterfly.
Your transformation outshines
anything I have ever seen.
Thank you,
Professor Summerlee.
It's a charming compliment.
Well, I propose
that we drink a toast.
To the five of us, and
our absent friend, Malu.
Six intrepid
travelers, who risked
life and limb in the pursuit
of science and adventure.
And to that special
land that we discovered.
To the lost world.
To the lord world.
[clinking]
Did you like them?
Very large, huh?
Can't wait to see him.
Closing time,
ladies and gentlemen.
The zoo will close
in five minutes.
Closing time.
Closing in five minutes.
There he is.
Percy?
Percival looks very unhappy.
He must be.
Alone in a cage all day long,
with people poking at him,
and staring at him.
I'd love to take you
home with me, Percy,
but you'd probably
rather be free.
You're not suggesting
we, uh, open the cage?
We're all alone here.
Nobody need know who did it.
Well-- I don't know.
Hurry, Jim.
Come on, Percy.
[screeching]
Come on.
Percival.
Fly.
This is your last chance.
ED: Percy, get going!
Go, Percy!
Fly!
[wings flapping]
Goodbye, Percival.
ED: Percy!
JIM: Goodbye, Percy!
[music playing]