What has water but no fish,
forests but no trees,
and deserts but no sand?
Help me out.
No, it's a riddle.
Come on,
you're not gonna help me out?
Wait, so you're gonna
leave me hanging?
- I don't know.
- It's a map.
-That's what I said.
-No, you didn't.
- I said map.
- Mm-hmm.
I whispered it,
you didn't hear?
-No.
-I said, "map."
- No, you didn't.
- I did.
Mm-mm.
Let's make up something.
♪ I was at the vet... ♪
♪ ...with my pet, George ♪
I mean I-- you're the singer,
I never said I was a singer,
you said
you were a singer, so--
- Hey, Kayla.
- Hi.
I'll take him now, okay?
Don't worry, he'll be right
back, okay?
You worried about George?
Yeah, but I think
he'll be all right.
Yeah,
I think he will too.
But if he's not,
we can't just say yes,
we have to talk
to your mother first
and see
how much it's gonna cost.
Screw the cost.
-Don't say "screw."
-Screw, screw, screw.
Hey.
George is very lucky
to have you watching his six.
We'll figure it out.
-Mama is still not quite--
-She's trying.
Just wish
she'd try a little bit harder.
Give her some time,
she'll get there.
- Hey, Kayla.
- Hi.
Wanna come back
and see Georgie?
Yeah.
All right,
it is the first one
on the right.
Hi, Georgie.
How are you? Good.
Hang on there, George,
hang on there, sweetie.
Oh, hi.
I don't think we've met.
- Hey.
- This is LT.
He's my dad's
commanding officer.
- Paul.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
George doesn't have
an infection
and that's what
we were most worried about.
But we did find out
- that he has asthma.
- Wow.
There's medication
to treat him, okay?
But you're going to have to
give it to him every day,
probably
for a couple of years, okay?
That's fine. It's fine.
Okay.
We've got George's six,
right LT?
No matter what.
Made of glass
I'm 'bout to shatter it.
- Come on. Let's rock.
- Do your thing, man.
Ooh, you look like
a straight chicken
right here, boy.
Give him
everything you got, Stevey.
Imma cook you tonight.
What're you gonna do, dawg?
Full tilt boogie,
baby, let's go.
God damn!
- Very nice.
- That's it, Stevey!
Back okay?
- Yeah.
- Good.
That's what
I'm talking about motherfucker.
How was that?
It was good,
you're making good decisions,
you're thinking fast.
-Any more?
-Him and him.
- Step right up, fellas.
- Same time.
Try this shit
with me, Stevey.
Look how serious he looks.
Come on, man, let's go.
Come on, motherfucker.
Let's go.
Hey, hey!
Nice!
Watch your back!
Hit me in the fucking throat.
- Nice!
- All right.
Enough.
Everyone walk away
and take a fucking chill pill.
This is supposed
to be training, fucker.
Talk about
a fucking party pooper.
Nice floor work,
but he's playing too rough.
Throat's fucking throbbing.
What do you want?
It's tough enough
finding somewhere
that will let you spar.
Three on one and somebody
wearing handcuffs.
But he gets a reputation
as a crazy fuck.
This could be crazy or fucked.
Teddy will make us
all find another gym.
Get him to pull it back.
He's got one place
where he can let it hang out,
come on.
Somebody saying something?
-Yeah, me.
-You want to say it to me?
Oh!
A little too rough for you?
Pull it back.
Stevie.
You trying to hurt
one of these guys?
- Is that what you want?
- Okay, okay.
He copies you.
Say, "okay" Stevie.
-Okay, Stevie.
-Okay. Let's hit the shower.
Yes, sir, Dr. Freud.
Hitting the shower.
I'm Dr. Freud now.
You should be a tag team,
get you in here.
I'm sure I can find an opponent
who'd love to kick your ass.
Yeah, I'm good.
Are you?
It's been so long
since you fought,
I can't remember
if you are anymore.
Let's get some sushi.
What is it?
I need you
to clear that area
in front of the elevator.
We're talking
to the detective,
we're gonna get it all sorted,
okay?
And we're gonna find her,
I know it's a lot,
but it's gonna--
Hi. Family friend, Paul.
Hi, I'm Alex.
I'm Kayla's therapist.
Her mom's in
with the detective right now.
- Thank you for being here.
- No, of course.
Um, you know what,
I actually have to get somebody
to cover my afternoon,
um, trauma group so--
Well, hey, you know what?
-I got this. We're good here.
-Got this, have you?
No, no, I--
I need to be here.
-I need to be here.
-No, we're good here.
I need you to move away
from those elevators,
we gotta keep
that space clear.
Okay,
just give us, uh, one second.
Could you give us
a minute please?
Um, are you okay?
Are you sure?
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
-Tell me what happened.
-The fuck do you care?
Put that shit aside for now.
You can go back to hating me
as soon as she's home
safe and sound,
but for now,
we're on the same side.
Yeah?
We got woken up
by the cops this morning
saying they found her bag
on the sidewalk
outside some bar.
Anything taken?
Mm-mm.
Shit, that's bad,
isn't it?
Not necessarily.
Look at it this way,
if her stuff was missing,
we wouldn't even know anything
had happened to her yet.
There'd be more time.
The cops would be behind them.
- "Them?"
- I just meant--
Oh, my God.
You think it was a them?
No.
So then
what are you saying?
No. I'm sorry, but no.
You don't get
to do that right now.
You're stronger
than your mother.
I love Lucy like a sister,
but stable is not a word
I'd use to describe her.
So, you got to be tough.
Who was Kayla with
last night?
A few friends,
but she walked home by herself.
LT!
They took her,
LT, they took her.
It's day one.
We don't know anything yet,
all right?
We know
they've taken my baby.
Okay, uh, now look,
I read your initial statement
to the officer
and you said
Kayla was with friends--
I don't fucking know
who she was with.
You don't know who your daughter
was with last night?
Was she--
was she at someone's house?
Was she in the street?
Was she at a bar?
My 12-year-old sister
was not at a bar.
-We found a backpack in front--
-I know what you're doing.
I'm trying to help-- I'm trying
to find your daughter.
You're saying
I'm a shit mother.
No, I'm not-- I'm not--
I'm not saying that.
Can we get another detective
over here, please?
Please lower your voice,
this isn't McDonald's,
you don't just order
any cop you want, okay?
Obviously we got McAsshole.
Okay, enough. Enough.
- Hold on for one second.
Everything all right
over there, Chris?
Terry, Terry--
Just give us a second.
Look, you gotta clear
those people out of the hall.
We know
about your elevator, Terry.
Clear out,
use the office.
We got it, we got it. Okay.
Just a second, um, Detective,
thank you for everything
- that you're doing.
- Of course.
Ma'am, is there any chance
that your daughter might
just be still out partying?
I'll say it again.
She's 12.
I-- I understand that,
I can't assume anything.
We assume
you're being a dickhead.
-Please watch your mouth.
-All right, um--
-Fuck off.
-Come on, now.
All right, look,
I'm trying to help...
-I-- I-- yes. And we--
-...okay?
And I'll-- I'll reach out
as soon as we know anything.
- Yes.
- Okay?
-Thank you so much.
-Okay.
Thank you, we really
appreciate your help.
It's okay.
It's all right.
They're gonna help.
I'm sorry. All right.
- Hey, let me, please
- All right.
We're going to
figure it out, though.
Okay?
They're on it. We get...
Say it.
- He should be here, not you.
- I know.
You know, there's a part of me
that will always blame you
for what happened to him.
There's a part of me
that will always agree with you.
But I've seen you
with Kayla...
and I know this isn't you just
keeping some promise you made.
I know she's precious to you
like how she was to him.
You were precious
to him as well.
Just bring
my little sister home, LT.
Please.
Bella, what the fuck
are you talking about?
Look, I read the stats.
It'll just go on a pile.
The cops barely find people
in cases like this,
so they hardly try.
Look, I'll do
everything you ask, okay?
I promise.
I'll be the tough one
and I'll swallow it all down
and I'll keep everyone
in decent shape.
-But you find her.
-Bella, this is a mess.
- What can I--
- Right there!
That look in your eyes.
Use that.
Look,
there was only four of us.
We lost a quarter
of our family that day.
We can't lose another.
We can't be down to half.
You promised him.
You gave him your word
you would look over her.
And you have.
You take her
to soccer practice
and you bring her home
every time.
I'm just asking you to do
what you always do.
Bring her home.
Okay?
What can I get you, man?
-Soda.
-All right.
-What kind you want?
-Surprise me.
- Your place?
- Yeah.
-For better or for worse.
-Hm.
Did you know a girl was taken
from out front of here
- last night?
- No, no, no.
- Yeah, she was.
- No.
Cops found some purse
outside there this morning.
I don't want you in here asking
about some missing girl, man.
Is she your daughter?
My friend's daughter.
Uh...
- Claro, claro.
- Yeah.
-Anyways--
-Amigo.
Hey, papi, let me-- let me
walk you to the door real quick,
make sure you don't slip
on your motherfucking shoelaces
on the way out.
Did you notice
this girl last night?
No.
Could you look at the picture,
please?
What picture?
This one.
Think it's time
for you to go, brother.
Excuse me.
I need to talk to you
for a second.
I want to ask you
if you've seen this girl.
Dude,
I'm just trying to chill here.
She was taken
from out front of here
last night.
I'm going to pass
this phone around.
I want everybody
to take a look.
Please, take a look.
- Okay.
- Give it here, man.
It's not that
kind of party, baby.
Now you done fucked up.
You're making
a mistake here.
You, all by yourself.
Jesus Christ!
- Hey!
- Oh, my God.
God damn.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Look at the photo.
Please, man. Please.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, fuck.-
Please.
I've never seen her, bro.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God,
did you see that?
I know.
good God, that was insane.
You know,
because I used to be fun
and the life of the party,
everyone liked me
the way I was.
So, apparently
I did some bad things
- when I was drinking too much.
- Right.
But, I really don't understand
how to be any different.
So, you feel like
without the alcohol,
you are not the same person?
And that person,
you were validated for?
Yeah, yeah.
I was funny,
it was fun, and really,
if it hadn't been
for those little incidents,
um, I think
I would be fine and great.
And I don't think I really
needed to quit drinking,
but, to be honest,
I think I drink sometimes
to make
other people interesting.
Interesting.
Okay, there's a lot that
we need to, um, unwrap here,
but we need to end
our session now.
But we will continue
with that next time.
I hope I will see
each and every one of you
at the Be Positive barbecue
this weekend.
Um, and until then,
I hope you have a great week.
- Okay? Bye, you guys.
- Bye, Dr. Alex.
Thank you, Graham.
- Excuse me.
- Mm-hmm?
Hi, um,
my name is Paul and--
Oh, Paul.
Right, right, right.
How's Lucy?
She's, um,
not doing so hot.
Yeah.
Uh, can I ask you
some questions?
Of course, yes.
Um...
I was just wondering
if there was anything
you can tell me
about your time with Kayla.
Um, anything
she may have said--
You know,
I wish there was, Paul,
I really do.
I mean, Kayla was a happy kid.
I mean, you know that.
She used to spend sessions
trying to make me laugh,
-you know, making up those, um--
-Her riddles.
Riddles.
Yes, the riddles.
You know, I-- I...
I don't think she ran away,
if that's what you're asking.
No, I don't either.
I-- I meant more um...
were there any friends,
older maybe,
that she talked about,
people she might have
just met who--
You know, Kayla's sessions
were court-ordered, right?
Because of all the stuff
with her mom.
So, if anything
like that happened,
I was mandated
to let CPS know immediately.
-Oh, yeah, no, I'm not saying--
-No, no, I-- I know.
I'm just-- listen,
I will answer your questions
for as long as you want.
I just wish that
there was something more helpful
that I could offer you.
Do you mind if I play
therapist for a second
and ask you
how you're doing?
I'm good.
You know...
Kayla told me a lot...
about you,
she talked about you a lot.
But,
what she didn't tell me...
was how bad of a liar
you are.
Wish I had been there
when she needed me.
No, no, no, no.
Paul, don't do that.
We always want to find
something to blame
in moments like this.
Even if it's ourselves,
but you can't do that.
It's not helpful.
Hm.
Shit, motherfuck--
Hey!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fuck you, Eddie,
what would you be saying, man?
You see me like this,
right?
I'm all right.
I'm good, bro.
Don't you worry about me,
all right?
I'm okay.
Fucking buck up.
This shit right.
Upstairs.
Yeah, up here.
Let's get him
in the bathroom.
- We gotta move.
- Come on, man.
Come on, up you go.
Easy. I got him.
Put him down here.
LT.
What'd you take, man?
Hm?
What did you take?
What did you take, asshole?
Wake up, man.
Answer him.
Hey, he's gonna keep on
doing that 'til you answer, man.
Yeah, I got pulled off a date
for this shit.
Slap you for fun, now.
I know, Stevey.
Shit.
Here you go.
Into the tub.
Xanax and Valium.
That shit's coming up, right?
LT, I'm gonna stick my fingers
down your throat.
If you bite me,
I will break your fucking nose.
All right?
Stop fucking moving.
Where the fuck are we,
Paul?
There's more.
One more time, man.
One more time.
The fuck, man?
Paul,
this shit's gotta stop.
-Nobody asked you to come over.
-You fucking called me.
- I called you?
- Yeah.
- Why would I do that?
- Fuck if I know.
You know, usually,
if you're really gonna do it,
you don't call.
I was probably calling
to say goodbye.
Next time, don't.
- Dude--
- Fuck you.
I failed him, Mac.
I swore I'd look after
his daughter, and I...
We owed him.
What happened to Bobby
was our fault,
our responsibility, we---
I don't ever
want to hear those words
come out of your mouth again.
You got it?
I love my brother
and I love you.
But I won't let you hurt us,
just to unburden
your own conscience.
Come on, man.
Seriously!
Where the fuck are we, Paul?
Airbnb.
Pretty nice spot.
Go out in style?
Eh, something like that.
Jesus Christ.
Stevie,
go call a cleaning company
and find somebody, maybe Dean,
to fix the front door.
Copy.
- Steve?
- Yes, sir?
You said
you was on a date.
I did.
Going well?
Fuck you both!
Oh, God.
How did you find me, Mac?
- Don't worry about it.
- Mac.
Jordy.
Shit.
Put a track and trace
on your phone
after you called me.
What'd he tell his boss?
He said he was following up
a lead on a case.
He lied.
This shit's got to
hit the road, brother.
You got to be done with it
and then be done with it.
I got to get home.
It's my weekend with the kids.
Stevey will stick around.
Get this shit straight.
Don't try
to kill yourself again today.
I already looked for her.
Didn't even go
looking for her.
You kept her dog.
She loved that fucking dog
and you kept it safe.
That's something.
That's bottom
of the fucking barrel.
Maybe that's all
you got left to give, man.
While the fire fight
is going on...
the VC button planted
an anti-tank mine.
-So, he got blown up.
-Instead of you.
-Instead of me.
-Yeah.
So, now what happens is,
I get out of my track
and show up
and I go running up to him
and the poor guy was--
he was covered...
he didn't wear his--
the flack jacket,
so he was covered
from the waist up
with burning oil.
The only part of him
that wasn't burnt
was his actual hair
because he had,
you know, the--
one of the--
-the track helmets on.
-Right.
Everything else was burnt.
So...
when I ran up to him,
he started to fall.
Natural first reaction,
try to catch him.
Yeah.
Uh...
-All right.
-You're all right.
Yeah, I just have
a little problem with this.
And, uh, his skin
came off on my hands.
-You know what I mean?
-Yeah.
And my nickname in the service,
for whatever reason, was Tiny.
And the last words
I got out of him was, you know,
"Tiny don't let me die."
We got him on the medevac.
He lasted about a month
and then the heart gave out.
Hey, Tiny. Where's LT?
He's in the bathroom,
making himself look pretty.
LT! I wanna buy you a drink
It was because--
because it was--
It was probably
the first war ever
that they didn't do
anything strategically.
Where they took a--
they took a place, whatever,
because they wanted numbers,
they wanted body counts
and so forth.
So, we took this thing
three times
to give it back each time
Washington wanted you
on the hill,
then they wanted you
off the hill.
Well-- but, I mean--
Yeah, but you know what?
It was the first war that
I know of that was actually,
instead of being run
by the Pentagon,
it was run by Congress.
And that was just
plain asinine.
No, because you got
all politicians there,
you know, making decisions.
And they're not the--
Brendan!
Brendan, you alcoholic!
He's actually not kidding.
You want to
mumble that again?
He never shuts up.
What the fuck?
A human IED.
- Hey, welcome home.
- Oh, I'm fine.
Hey, shut up--
Who told you guys
to talk? I said be quiet--
- Tiny!
- Never saw it coming.
You don't look good.
What do you mean
I don't look good?
You don't look good.
You look like you're bad
saying you're good.
- That doesn't even make sense.
- It does make sense.
Jordy--
You're saying the word good,
but your eyes don't read good,
your eyes read bad.
You know,
when you're coming back
and you're getting
all this stuff.
Because I had one time,
you know, uh,
division at the time,
just mechanized
infantry division.
And we were attached to the...
Screaming Eagles,
the 101st.
Hey, Paul.
Do I know you?
I come in peace.
Come in peace,
standing exactly where you are.
Tell your friend behind me
my knife will be buried
in your heart
before he's ever
raised that gun.
Let's get to who you are
real quick, yeah?
I am someone
whose 12 year old cousin
was abducted from the Bronx
three days ago.
Pick it up
on your way out.
How do we know that
you don't have a gun in here?
I do have a gun in here.
Sorry about your cousin.
- Sophia.
But I don't know
how I can help.
We know you were looking
for a kid awhile back.
Just tell us everything
that happened
with your friend's daughter.
And we thought you might
sympathize with my situation,
given your loss.
- Who am I talking to here?
- Nigga, can you count?
-Both of us is here.
-Talk to me.
-Guess I know now, huh?
-What're you smirking for?
Hey.
Tell this nigga if he goes
for the backup piece
on his ankle,
he'll die right where he stands.
- AJ.
- Huh?
Chill out.
-I'm cool.
-No, you're not.
You should rest.
AJ.
Go sit in the corner
and think about
what you've done.
Put down the gun and get
in the conversation, Paul.
Because worse than
AJ pulling out the wrong weapon
would be certain people
finding out
that you pulled a weapon,
any fucking weapon,
on Juan Gomez's daughter.
Who's Juan Gomez?
You're daddy's little girl?
I don't think you want to
be talking to me like that.
He's locked up right? Daddy?
Can you tell me
what happened
to your friend's daughter,
please?
I didn't find her.
That's what happened.
I have a witness...
who thinks that
he might have seen the van
that Sophia was kidnapped in.
He even got part
of a license plate.
An A and a Y.
Kid drew it for us.
We don't want to go
to the police
for obvious reasons.
So, I thought that
you might have some contacts
who could help us
under the radar.
Kind of contacts
who could get an ex-soldier
out of lockup
the day that he punches a cop
on a street full of people.
- Should I be flattered?
- No charges.
-You used my phone call.
-You punched a police officer.
-Time to go.
-I'll pay you.
Ten grand?
Time to go.
Big Juan, it's Juan Gomez.
Who the fuck's Juan Gomez?
Juan Gomez, he's got
a giant piece of the drugs
coming in and out of Queens.
My colleagues
have been investigating
this piece of shit for years.
He's doing ten years upstate
as of a few months ago.
His daughter runs the operation
while he's gone.
So we're getting in bed
with Mexican drug dealers now,
are we?
Good stuff.
Good decision making.
What?
What that?
What is it? What?
Do you remember
that time Bobby laughed so hard
that he shat himself
in that fucking bunker?
And we had to stay there,
we couldn't--
there was nowhere to go.
- Fucking stew eating idiot.
- Oh, my God.
So, what did you say
to the Mexican chick?
I said no.
No, no, you're not--
Jordy, come on.
You-- you know everyone, man.
And your office alone--
just get
one of your colleagues
to give us a list
of registered sex offenders
in the area and I can---
You can go door to door
and beat up everybody in Queens
until what?
You happen upon
the asshole who has her?
You're making this
about Kayla.
What do you want me
to do, Jordy?
- Go be with Bella and Lucy.
- Why?
Let the Mexicans
do their thing
-while we do ours.
-Which is what?
Which is to look after
Bobby's family,
like he would have done
for any of us.
This is not gonna
bring Kayla back.
I hate to be the one
to say it.
- That girl's dead.
- We owe Bobby better.
-Go the fuck home.
-It was our idea.
-You mean it was my idea.
-I made the call.
You act like you're the only one
who loved him.
Like you're the only one
who hurts.
Like, you're the only one
who misses him.
Well, it's bullshit.
We were all there, man.
All of us.
We all hurt, and we all see
his face in the dark
when we're alone.
You don't own that.
I made the call, Jordy.
Yeah. You made the call.
the fuck you want?
Yeah, yeah, shut the fuck up.
You don't sleep anyway.
Listen, I need you to get
one of your colleagues
to look into something
for me.
And Hernandez
is coming tomorrow.
- Mm-hmm. Wired. Yeah.
- Wired.
AJ!
Please tell me
I can throw him out.
No. Send him over.
And AJ. Be polite.
Show him the side of you
that I know.
Not this guy.
-That's how I look?
-Yeah.
It's not cute.
Swipe right.
Is that the van?
Maybe.
Who gave this to you?
If I told you that,
he'd stop doing favors for me.
-I mean, this has got to be it.
-Might be.
- Do you know where it is?
- Parked in the street in Queens.
- Where?
- Three things.
First, you don't make a move
without me.
-As in not one.
-Wait.
Sorry,
you're giving me conditions?
Do you have any idea
what I could do to you?
No, what could you do?
I hire and fire
tough guys like you everyday.
Oh, I'm not a tough guy.
Second, I'm in charge.
We do it all as a team,
but if a call is needed,
I make it,
-you comply.
-The fuck?
Someone has to be in charge
and it sure as shit
ain't gonna be you.
Why the fuck
would I let you--
Do you know
where the van is parked?
Okay.
You're the man.
-What's third?
-Third, no cops.
Fuckin' duh.
We could be waiting days
for this guy to even show up.
Or girl.
Sure, I'll play.
We could be waiting days
for this girl
that we're going to fuck up
to show.
How many guys
does your father have
looking for Sophia?
Um.
He doesn't know you and AJ
are looking for her, does he?
What are you talking about?
He didn't want to bring
attention to the business,
did he?
That gonna be a problem,
Lieutenant?
I prefer
playing off the radar.
Okay, good.
Hey, look.
- Wait, wait, wait--
- Yeah, whatever you say, boss.
We don't even know
if that's the guy.
Fuck.
You want to chat
while I'm chasing?
That's exactly
what I want to do.
Keep telling me
where you are.
He's running
like a fucking bat out of hell.
-Don't shoot him.
-I don't have a gun.
Why the hell
are you chasing him then?
He's-- he's going
into the dry cleaner.
No, don't go in after him.
He's gonna try
to go out the back.
Who the fuck are you?
No!
Oh, okay, okay.
I-- I'm in the dry cleaner's.
I'm in the dry cleaner's.
Okay.
Hey!
- No, no, no, no.
- The fuck is going on here?
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Shut up!
Fucking English, man,
how many times I gotta tell you?
Now shut the fuck up.
Stop talking to him.
She don't get the-- hey,
do you know
where the fuck you at?
Did you say Lopez?
As in Sonny Lopez?
No, I know Sonny Lopez.
Oh, good.
So does everybody
and his fucking momma.
No, I-- I--
I really know Sonny Lopez.
No, I-- I, um--
Bitch, stop talking to him
-and talk to me.
-Okay. I'm sorry.
I'm talking to you.
Jesus, how many fucking
many of you are there?
Look, bitch,
I'm just gonna chop your ass up
into little pieces,
spread you all over
this fucking city.
All right, well,
that would be a bad idea
because I run
with Big Juan's crew.
- Big Juan?
- Yeah.
Jungle Club owner Big Juan?
Big Juan, Big Juan?
- Yeah.
- The fuck out of here.
-You for real?
-Yeah.
Yo, yo, yo, prove it.
What's the name
of those three big ass dogs
Big Juan lets
roam around over there?
Apollo, Rocky, and Adonis.
What's the name
of them dogs, man?
-I don't fucking know.
-Fucking morons.
- I'm the--
- Stay still.
I'm the manager
at the Jungle.
- Shut the fuck up.
- My name is Lola.
I was just
at that motherfucking club
two weeks ago
and they had told me
that Big Juan's daughter
is the one that manages the--
-You said your name was Lola?
-It's nice to meet you.
Fuck... fuck...
Lola, shit. It's me, Jimmy.
You remember?
Last year we met
when we were going to go over
that garbage truck thing
we were all going to get into?
-Remember that?
-Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can you not point the gun at me
anymore, please?
- Oh, shit, sorry.
- Thank you.
That's just a misunderstanding.
You know what I mean?
We ain't got to tell
nobody about this.
- This should stay between us.
- Yeah.
-Ain't gotta go nowhere.
-Hey, relax.
-No, it was my fault.
-I mean, it kind of was.
I mean, I ran into the shop
unannounced.
So, totally justified
for you to point
- a fucking shotgun at me.
- This ain't our shop.
We just here grabbing up
the money and the gear.
The fool that owns this joint
owes Sonny 15 Gs.
Oh.
All right,
well, I gotta bounce.
I was just in here
chasing this guy
- who came through here--
- Wait, hold up.
You're talking like a gringito?
A little white boy?
-Yeah.
-You mean, this white boy?
You can never be ready
for this.
Time is gonna move very slowly
for you in this room.
And I want you to have something
that will remind you of life.
Of good.
Of a place other than here
that you can hopefully
get back to
if you tell me
what I want to know.
I haven't done this
in a long time,
so I have to admit
I'm kind of excited.
Are you excited?
No, no.
- No.
- No? No what?
Gang's all here.
All right, guys,
Nathan and I were just
getting to know each other.
He wants to be of service.
- Right?
- Mm-hmm.
Have you seen this girl?
No.
Where is she?
I don't know.
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- Are you sure?
- Mm-mm.
Mm-mm.
You guys believe him?
- You believe him?
- No.
- I don't know.
- Sorry.
- I'm outvoted.
No, no, no, no!
Put the towel--
there you go, there you go.
- Don't, don't!
- Water, Lo-- Lola.
No, no, no, no!
- Water, water.
- No, no, no, no, no!
More, more, more, yeah.
Yeah, more. Yeah, yeah.
Another one, another one.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, just like we talked,
just like we talked.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All in there. All in.
Yeah, Yeah.
Another one, another one.
Uh-huh. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, there you go.
There you go. There you go.
More. More. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Come on.
Bring him up.
Where is she, Nathan?
Nathan.
Nathan. Where is she?
Fuck you!
Huh? How 'bout that?
I don't fucking know!
I don't fucking know.
I don't know.
Good for you.
No, no, no, no, no!
Please! Please!
Please, please!
No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
There you go.
There you go. There we go.
Now we here. Now we here.
Come on. Now we focus.
There we go.
Oh, yeah.
He wants more. He wants more.
Going fishing
underwater, huh?
Yeah. Yeah.
We don't miss
out on no shit, man.
Come on. Come on. Again.
There you go.
Another one.
Go ahead, another one.
Water gonna solve that.
Talking all that shit.
All right,
bring him up.
I don't know!
I don't know.
- Nathan.
- Please, God.
You're gonna kill me
and I don't--
Hey, hey, hey.
I don't wanna kill you.
- I don't wanna kill you.
- I don't know.
Where is she?
I don't know.
Excuse me, Nathan.
What if it was just a van
with a similar design?
Then we're going to
break an innocent man
in a way that
he'll probably stay broken
until he hangs himself
in his closet.
This is what it is.
You want to get Sophia back?
Yeah.
Then we gotta look
under the rocks
and ignore all the bugs.
You gotta choose, Nathan.
And it's a simple choice.
Nobody holds out
with this method.
Nobody.
And there's no shame in it.
Bad motherfuckers
cave in to this shit.
I saw one guy.
One. Fahid was his name.
One of bin Laden's
personal bodyguards.
He took it for five days,
but that's all
he'd been trained to do
his whole life.
Resist torture.
Nathan.
Have you trained
your whole life
to resist torture?
You'll tell me eventually.
We'll keep doing this
'til you die.
- Do you know--
- Yes.
Is she alive?
Is she?
You took this girl?
- When?
- Uh...
a few days ago.
Is she alive?
I don't know.
You don't know?
How could you not know?
I just do
pick up and delivery.
Pick up
and delivery for who?
- I don't know.
- All these "I don't knows."
I don't know, I'm--
I'm telling you the truth.
I don't know. Fuck.
I don't waste time
with little fingers
and earlobes,
like the CIA does.
Answer my questions.
I'll cut off
both your thumbs.
Pick up and delivery for who?
I don't know.
Oh, Go-- I swear, okay?
I swear.
I don't even see
the people, okay?
But I don't think
they do any harm to them.
I really don't think
they do any harm to the girl.
How could you know that?
They told me to put,
um, blankets
and-- and food in the van.
They told me
what music to play them,
just to keep them calm
in the drive, okay?
Music?
Where did you take Sophia?
Deep in the woods upstate.
I call them
and they tell them,
uh, how long it's going to
take me to get there.
And then
I just drop them off.
I just drop them
off and I drive away.
And I don't see anyone.
I don't see anyone.
And then I get
the money in my account
a few hours later.
How many times
have you done this?
Um--
How many times
have you done this?
About nine. About nine.
About nine. Okay?
I've been doing it
for about eight months.
How do you choose the girl?
I don't.
I don't choose them.
I don't choose them, okay?
They-- they just call me
when they have one
and, uh,
they give me their name
and their location
and, uh, the music.
The music, right?
And then-- then I have
ten days uh, to locate them
or-- or it's voided.
Tell me
everything that happened
from the second
you took Sophia.
Fuck, you're gonna
fucking cut my finger off.
- That's right, I am.
- Or what?
Um, she--
Answer the fucking question.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
She took her gag off
in the van, okay?
And this never
happened before.
And, um, I-- I couldn't stop,
because I was on the highway,
so I-- I just had to
let her keep it off.
And-- and-- and she talked
the whole time,
the whole ride up.
What did she say?
"My name is Sophia."
Over and over.
Did she say anything else?
She begged me
to take her home.
Hi, guys.
- How are you?
- Great.
-Is everything all right here?
-Mm-hmm.
He's not eating his food.
Can I get you something else?
No.
His appetite comes and goes.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, as long as--
We might get it to go
when we leave,
- but I will let you know.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Okay, thank you.
- Yeah.
I lost one of my men.
I broke off from my team
with another guy
to investigate a building.
I spot my gunnery sergeant
insisted wasn't safe.
But...
I knew better.
We got pinned down
by the enemy
as we were coming out.
And my team
had to come back for us.
My gunnery sergeant
was killed trying to save me.
That's...
I don't know shit about--
shit about war, but, like...
That's what happens, right?
Like, you would have
gone back for him, too.
We were looking for money.
Jordy,
the guy I was with,
got a tip from a local,
that the Taliban stashed
a bunch of cash
in the apartment.
We went to collect it.
The whole platoon knew.
Everybody
was gonna get a share.
There was only one guy
who didn't wanna do it.
-Your gun guy.
-My gun guy.
Bobby.
Kayla's dad.
Stupid fuck put himself
in front of my bullet.
You can't blame
yourself for that.
Yes, I can.
Tell me about you and AJ.
Nice move.
You give me your tragic
war story and then--
I have to tell you
whatever it is you ask,
otherwise
I'm a total bitch, yeah?
Yeah.
-Fuck no.
-A few weeks.
Give it to Jordy.
Fuck.
Give me the dog.
So, uh...
Everything you need
is in here.
I need your rifle.
-Trouble?
-No.
Maybe.
I'm helping someone.
You need some help
helping someone?
You're a big man,
but you're out of shape.
And for me,
it's a full time job.
So behave yourself.
See you.
Seriously.
I'm good.
You need the scope?
Thai food is, like,
the perfect delivery food.
And we haven't gotten it once.
We've gotten pizza,
we've gotten Chinese.
- Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
I like Thai food,
too, though.
For me, the-- the top
deliveries would be--
It'd go: Thai, pizza,
sushi, and Chinese.
- Mexican.
- Mm-hmm.
-Italian.
-Wow.
-For delivery?
-Mexican.
- Okay.
- Italian.
Chinese-- sorry.
Mexican, Chinese,
Italian, Thai...
Jamaican.
I've never ordered Jamaican.
I can tell.
What's up?
Why'd you guys get so quiet?
Just finished
the blitz.
Find the phone.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. I got it.
Hey, it's right here.
I've never seen you
do one of these calls,
so I don't actually know
how it normally goes.
But if I see an eyebrow raise
that I don't like...
a bullet
goes into your skull.
Okay.
And your mom, Diane,
she gets the same
by midnight.
Okay. All right.
But I gotta get this right now.
Go.
- Hey.
- Hey, can you talk?
Yeah.
We're doing Victory
Reserve. Remember?
I remember.
It's the same spot
that I dropped off,
uh, two drop offs ago.
Right, all the way
down the dirt road up there.
Uh-huh.
After the second exit.
Right. Okay. Okay.
Uh-huh.
The usual drop off drive.
- Okay.
- I understand.
Thanks.
Okay,
they're gonna send a text
with the name,
uh, schedule,
and personal information,
all right?
Just in a few seconds.
It'll just take
a few seconds.
-Literally, a few seconds--
-Maybe up to a minute.
Bianca.
A 12-year-old,
who apparently likes
female singer-songwriters.
Hey, come here for a second.
We can't actually do this.
I'm calling it off.
Are we actually
gonna watch...
this guy kidnap
some other scared little girl
and gives her
to fuck knows who?
No, we're not.
Okay.
I'm going to help him.
Shit.
The tracker's working.
Stay back about half a mile
In case they're watching.
The tracker will lead us
wherever they're taking her.
Okay.
I know
we're chasing Sophia,
but we put Bianca
in that van.
Keeping that girl alive
is our number one priority.
Bianca? I'm Graham.
My friends
call me Gray-Gray.
Hey,
it's gonna be all right.
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be all right.
Stop it! No!
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be all right.
No one's gonna hurt you.
Stop! No!
It's gonna be all right.
It's gonna be okay.
Yes, yes. Lock it!
AJ, follow the tracker.
Where's AJ?
Don't turn around.
Don't fucking turn around.
You're not gonna
shoot me in the back.
If I run, you're not gonna
My name is Nathan!
No.
Okay, let's go over
the plan again.
Um...
I approach
the larger cabin.
While I cover
the lower end of the house.
And I move in
to breach the smaller cabin
where we believe the girls
are being kept and free them.
I bullshit my way
into the house--
Hold up.
Who's this?
- Hey.
How are you?
Holy shit.
LT.
That was Sophia's
grief counselor
when my aunt passed away.
I've met her. I-- I know her.
I can't go in that cabin.
We have to swap.
You go into the ca--
She was
Kayla's therapist, too.
I met her too.
How are you doing?
Hey, there.
It's okay
I step on your property?
Uh, I mean, technically,
you already have.
We own everything
up to the road.
Oh. Oh, really? Okay, I'm--
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to trespass.
-Oh, sorry.
-It's okay, I get it.
Uh, so, I broke down.
My phone's dead
and I really need to charge it.
I'd just really
like to call AAA.
Is that something
we could do?
- Uh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Is that possible?
Thank you so much,
I appreciate that.
Maybe just
let me see if, uh...
we, um--
So, where did you
say the car was, though?
Uh, to-- up the road?
The bigger lake?
-To the left or the right?
-To the left.
- The left. Walking that way.
- Okay.
Yeah, I guess
I'm just not exactly sure
where that was,
but, I mean, maybe we can--
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Hi. Hello. Hi.
- Your car broke down?
- Uh, yes.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
Um, well,
we can help you.
Thank you so much.
I-- I appreciate that.
I'm Alex.
How are you doing, Alex?
It's AJ.
- AJ. Okay.
- Yeah.
Well, hi.
Welcome to our humble home.
It's not a lot,
but it's ours, so.
- AJ.
- Mm-hmm.
-What does that stand for?
-Ooh. Nope. Not telling.
- You're not telling?
- No.
Really?
So it's that bad, huh?
That bad, yeah.
- Like Amadeus or something?
- Nah.
- No?
- Yeah. Is that a name?
I don't know, you tell me.
Yeah, it kind of
triggers some trauma.
- Oh.
- I was bullied as a kid.
Believe it or not.
I-- I'm sorry to roll up
on you guys like this.
No! It's fine. Sorry.
No, we're just--
we're not used to people,
you know,
rolling up on us, so...
Um, did somebody
offer you some water?
- No, no.
- Tim.
he just walked up
from the-- the lake.
- Go get him something to drink.
- Yep.
- Water would be fine.
- Okay.
And also, is it possible
I could use the restroom?
- Of course. Yeah, let's go.
- Right. Thank you.
Um, once you smell
Graham's chicken wings,
we're not gonna be able
to get rid of you, so--
- Okay, okay.
- Just letting you know,
- I'm interested in that.
- All right.
Is it charging?
Yeah.
It's not the first time.
Hold on a sec.
Should we do some
quick intros while we...
- wait for your phone?
- Yeah, sure.
Yeah? So that's Tim.
- who you met outside.
- Right.
That behind you is Graham.
I like to call him
Gray-Gray for short.
Gray-Gray.
But that's a long story
for another day.
Uh, Beau's the one
who you can hear on the phone.
How's it going?
And then this one.
Dan.
I like to call him
Danny the Heartbreaker.
Just because
he's really hot.
Yeah.
We know AJ's...
not going to tell us what
his name stands for.
Are you?
Still keeping that?
Still close to the vest
with that one.
Is it Andy?
No. No, it's not.
Andy Jerome?
- No, but I like it.
- Is it Jerome?
No. No.
Arthur Jacob?
Like that, Arthur Jacob?
Mm-mmm. No.
Andrew Jackson?
No.
That's not it at all.
- Not even close?
- No.
You like him?
No, no, no.
You don't like Andrew Jackson,
the president?
No.
Antonio Jose?
At least
we're getting more cultural
with the guesses now.
Gray-gray.
- Is this not--
- Armand?
Is it an "Ar"?
Is it "Ar"?
Is it "Ar" word?
Like Arthur?
- Arl?
You've never heard of Arl?
-Are you serious?
-No. Who is it?
- Aaron?
- No.
Adam? Abel?
Abraham?
- Is he just gonna keep--
- Arthur?
- I'll never tell.
- Arthur? Arthur?
- I'm not gonna--
- Hey.
What?
I said Arthur
and you looked at me.
My name's not Arthur.
It's-- it's not Arthur,
so, uh--
Gray-Gray.
- It's Arthur, all right?
- Okay.
-It's Arthur. It's Arthur.
-This is bullshit.
Fair.
Your name's Arthur.
Just kidding.
My name's not Arthur!
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
Who are you?
We're here to take you home.
Where's Graham?
Where is--
Just be quiet, please.
God, you're so dirty.
- Graham!
- No, no, no.
We don't want them
to hear--
-What the hell are you doing?
-She was gonna scream.
Yeah, no shit.
Do you want
something else to drink?
No, water's fine.
I'm good, actually.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Um, you know what?
I'm going to try
and make this call.
I think I'm at 5%.
It should be enough, right?
To reach out.
You know what?
He makes amazing wings.
The ones I was
telling you about outside.
- Okay. Gotcha.
- Yeah.
Did you-- are there
any left from lunch?
- Oh, yeah.
- You want some?
Uh, I'm-- I'm all right.
These are really,
really great wings.
I-- I appreciate it.
Uh, you know.
Maybe later, but no,
I'm-- I'm good right now.
- You're good?
- I didn't eat that long ago.
You know?
Okay.
You're not gonna scream,
are you?
No?
See, he is actually
one of the good guys.
He's just
in a very good disguise.
We don't want the bad man
to hear us, do we?
- Okay. Not gonna scream.
- Okay.
- No.
- No. Great.
Okay, great.
That's better, right?
Hi. What's your name?
-Phoebe.
-Phoebe. I'm Lola.
Okay, we're here
to get you out of here.
- Where's Graham?
- Who's Graham?
He's Graham.
Okay.
We're gonna
get you guys out of here
and I need your help.
But Graham
hasn't done his trick yet.
-His trick?
-Yeah, I ate my lunch.
I did my whole workbook.
He has to do his trick.
What's the trick?
It's always a surprise.
Obviously.
Graham's amazing.
You'll love him.
Graham sounds really great,
but we gotta go.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Okay, you know what?
Um...
5% should be enough
to make a call.
Then I'll get out
of your guys' hair.
I'll call AAA
in a little bit.
Listen.
I think that
you eat the wings,
and then Dan
will drive you to your car
and he'll fix it for you.
- He's a great mechanic.
- He could fix anything.
Anything.
And then
it won't cost you any money.
It's easy.
Um, I don't want to be
too much trouble.
Honestly,
too much trouble would be
not letting this one
show you his skills.
He likes a little applause.
- Don't we all?
- Mm.
Would it offend you
if I-- if I pass?
Um, it's not that I don't trust
you with my car, it's just--
There is no car.
What?
Okay-- whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Are you okay?
Hey, Soph?
Soph?
Am I right?
You didn't break down.
Did you?
No?
Abraham?
Honest Abe? Honest Abe!
Are you Honest Abe?
What's wrong with her?
They drug you
the first few weeks,
so you get
used to being here.
Then they stop,
so you can learn.
What do they make you learn?
I'm learning
how to speak Russian.
It's really hard.
That's why I'm still here.
We can't leave
until we get it perfect.
- Are you Honest Abe?
- Why do you lie?
It's embarrassing.
It's okay, tell us.
I, uh--
So, I didn't-- I didn't come
out here by myself.
-I--
-You didn't?
-Who did you come with?
-My girlfriend.
Whose clothes are these?
Do they dress you up like this?
Except on photo day.
Wha-- what's photo day?
It's when they make us
dress up and do our hair.
-Time to go.
-Okay.
Okay, come on Soph.
We were at the lake...
but then we--
we got into it as we do.
About marriage.
Um...
she got mad,
yelled at me,
got in the car,
drove off,
left me stranded.
Phone was dead.
Wanted to charge it
so I could call my brother,
get back to the city.
Not my type
of scenery here.
Okay, ready?
Do you have what you need?
- Easy--
- Where'd you get this?
-It's mine.
-This is Kayla's coat.
- Hey. Hey!
- This is Kayla's coat.
What are you doing?
Stop it!
I don't buy it.
You're not calling
your brother.
You're calling
your girlfriend.
Let go of me!
- It's Kayla's coat!
- You're scaring her!
- You're scaring her, LT, okay?
- They hurt her.
You just scared
the shit out of her.
This is--
this is Kayla's.
Okay. I need you
to take them-- I know.
- Did I nail it?
- You are right.
I am calling my girlfriend
who left me here
stranded in the woods.
Just wanted to smooth
things over before I got home.
Yeah.
LT, we have to
get them out of here.
Did you know her?
What did they make her learn?
Hey, we have to
get them out of here.
Hey.
Why don't you
show them the trick?
- Now?
- Yes, now.
I couldn't possibly.
I'm too shy.
Okay. All right.
You talked me into it.
Mix them up really good.
Okay, and then
I want you to reach in
and just take
any old card you want.
Doesn't matter.
Does not matter at all.
Okay? Let everybody see it.
I don't want to see it.
Mix them all up.
You can see it.
I don't see it. All right.
Did they hurt her?
Just-- please,
tell me, just--
Okay, we'll ask her
all this later, okay?
We gotta get out of here.
Put it back somewhere.
Anywhere.
-Right in there.
-Oh.
Yeah, that's good.
Now hold the cards
in your hand
and shuffle them up.
Yeah, just give them
a little shuffle like that.
I'm not
the best shuffler
- in the world here.
- Oh, that's great.
I need you to take
Sophia and Bianca.
She's not going to
come out--
-We gotta get out of here.
-Yeah, good idea.
- Okay.
Look.
First, with my right.
Then with my left.
I just go like this.
And I do a little of that.
Snap.
Nothing in my hand.
And I reach right in my pocket.
And there is your card.
- Is he right?
- Get the fuck out of here.
Okay, I got Bianca.
Grab on.
There you go.
Where did you learn
to do that?
- Isn't that weird?
- What the fuck?
All right, girls.
Let's go.
Baby, are you okay?
We have to get out of here
right now, okay?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
You're going
the wrong way, please.
Phoebe. Please, just come.
Right-- right now!
I'm not fu--
I'm not messing around.
Please. Please. Phoebe.
Go check
on the girls, Graham.
- No. Tim, you go.
- Okay.
- Tim, stay.
Graham, you go.
Hey, Phoebe.
Sweetheart, I-- I need you
to come out right now.
Okay? Come on.
Come on.
Come on, sweetheart. Okay.
Phoebe? Sophia?
You guys okay?
Clean up the fucking body.
We don't have
any lye in the cabin.
Yeah, we do.
It's in the basement.
-Then go get it.
-Guys.
Amari James, bitch.
Don't, don't, don't.
Fuck!
Dr. Alex!
Okay, uh...
The guy had a vest on.
There'll be more coming.
How could you
let this happen?
Go get the girls.
I'll meet you
at the safe house.
Phoebe.
Phoebe, I need you
to come out right now.
Phoebe. Right now!
Hey, hey, hey, it's me.
It's me.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm f-- fine.
- Okay.
Did you hear
those gunshots?
Okay, listen.
Just grab her,
take her to the van.
- I'm gonna go get AJ.
- Okay.
Come on. Let's go.
Hey, Phoebe.
I need you to come
right now, please.
I'll meet you at the van.
Hey.
Let me take a wild guess.
This is the part
where you tell me
I should walk away right now.
No, man,
that's not on the table.
I was just gonna ask
if you knew
if the Knicks were up
at the half?
I will shoot
these fucking bitches
if you don't put
the gun down.
No, no, no.
How many more of you are there?
They're all dead.
Everybody.
They are.
My piece of shit boss bailed.
Left me
to clean up the mess.
Left you here to die
is what he did.
Go find our boy.
- You got her?
- I got her.
Phoebe?
It's okay, sweetheart.
Come on out.
The bad man
can't hurt you anymore.
I want you to go
outside on the porch.
Cover your ears real tight,
count to 100, okay?
Okay. Go ahead.
Close the door behind you.
Quiz time.
Sudden death round.
Yeah, I know her.
She was a real
pain in the ass.
Kept trying to escape.
I fought for my country.
And this is all my little boy's
gonna remember me by.
You answer
my next question properly
and I'll make sure your son
never knows you were here.
Right inside pocket.
What's the code?
0009.
It's under
the file "gardening."
You still gonna keep
your promise?
You ready, soldier?
She's in Johannesburg.
When do we leave?
♪ Welcome in ♪
♪ Can I give you
something to drink? ♪
♪ I am okay ♪
♪ Trust you're ready
to go on holiday ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I know that
the times are tough ♪
♪ Yeah, it's touch and go ♪
♪ Say hi to the wife ♪
♪ Worry not, I love my life ♪
♪ As the curtain falls ♪
♪ And the lights go off ♪
♪ And I take my mask ♪
♪ And I rip it off ♪
♪ And the makeup runs ♪
♪ And no one's around ♪
♪ And I say to myself ♪
♪ I'm all right ♪
♪ I'll be all right ♪
♪ What's that crack ♪
♪ In the corner of my mind? ♪
♪ Hurts to smile ♪
♪ But I'll still be doing it ♪
♪ For the love of the game ♪
♪ And for everyone
that's just the same ♪
♪ The sun is out ♪
♪ But I still
don't hold myself ♪
♪ As the curtain falls ♪
♪ And the lights go off ♪
♪ And I take my mask ♪
♪ And I rip it off ♪
♪ And the makeup runs ♪
♪ And no one's around ♪
♪ And I say to myself ♪
♪ I'm all right ♪
♪ I'll be all right ♪
♪ Na-na-na-na
na-na-na ♪
♪ Why should I be best? ♪
♪ What about the rest? ♪
♪ Everyone is fine ♪
♪ When that daylight's white ♪
♪ And I say to myself ♪
♪ I'm all right ♪
♪ I'll be all right ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la
la-la-la-la ♪