I know what you're thinking.
Pretty weird choice
for a host, huh?
Who better than a sneaky little bad
boy rolling around town such as myself?
Let me straight up with you.
This is the kind of place it's going
to make you feel uncomfortable.
I can promise you that.
You may laugh.
You may get offended.
Don't worry,
that's the whole fucking point.
You see here we don't
believe in dreams.
We live in nightmares.
Still don't get it yet,
do ya?
Speaking of not
getting it to the
right of me is the
Thompsons residence.
On the surface, Thompson seems like
your everyday all American young couple.
But tonight that's
going to change.
For tonight...
Is game night.
Uh oh.
Who invited these guys,
come on guys welcome in!
Good to see you,
good to see you!
We got wine and
stuff girls, IPA for the
big man, and we
got a bunch of chips.
Basically used to be,
but I don't remember being.
I don't ever and I've
seen any man.
Well I can't do the math.
- I can't do the trick.
- I have the magic.
Uh oh. My turn?
Right hand blue.
- Blue.
Alright brace for impact guys
I'm bending over for this one, so...
That's what she said.
Who's she?
That's funny.
Who is she?
Are you serious?
No.
Left hand red.
- Goodnight guys!
- What are you talking about?
- Have a good night.
- Thank you guys.
Good night!
- Bye!
Yeah great, thanks for coming.
You OK?
- Yeah.
Okay.
That's what he said.
Who is she?
She.
OK, so I saw those curtains
on Way fair,
the uhm, the space curtains.
It sounds ugly but it's not.
It's really cute
so I'm
thinking the space curtains in the
bedroom and then we move
the bedroom curtains into
the other rooms and nobody
ever has to see it again.
It's disgusting.
Then we can move...
Yeah, once we do that then.
You know what I mean?
Anyway, yeah, so I think
you could do that...
Who is she?
Hey honey.
Uhm...
What's going on here?
OK, because you know it's one
thing if you can't do the dishes,
but it looks like you're
peeing in jars so...
Dishes...
Oh, the dishes...
Yeah, the dishes.
It's what I said.
What?
Did you shit on the fridge?
That's what you said.
Excuse me.
You said?
Honey.
Do you have any idea
what I've been through?
You know how hard things have
been for me?
Oh my God.
- I've been having some ideas.
Floating around in my head.
Trying to figure out who she is.
Who's she?
There you are.
You...
that's what you said.
It's what you said.
That's what you said, honey.
That's what you said...
- I don't know what you're talking about...
- That's what you said!
That's what you said.
Okay stop, please, stop okay.
Just just breathe
okay let's just breathe.
OK.
Honey look at yourself.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry I don't know
what I did.
I didn't mean to do anything.
I'm so sorry,
Okay?
I just want my husband back.
Can I have him back?
Can I just have my normal
husband back OK?
You're right.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay...
Well, I've been acting weird.
I've been, uh,
acting strange so...
It's embarrassing.
Uh.
All right.
Mid life crisis alert, I'm gonna
do the dishes.
Sorry about that.
Uh.
Don't know what that was so...
Let me just...
No. No honey,
there is one thing.
About the dishes.
I could use a hand.
- Get it in the hole!
- Help me!
- Please!
- Get in the hole!
Just get it in the hole!
Squeal like a pig baby!
Scream like a freaking baby!
Fucking baby!
It's game night.
She has a fan.
No.
I am she.
Oh my God,
I'm so sorry you guys...
What are you doing bud?
I am her, she is me.
I am always she.
Call 911?
Please.
Okay...
It's OK, honey,
we're right behind you, OK?
Alright.
Your wife's pretty cute man.
Gonna have to get you better,
or I'm going to steal
her from you.
Heart rate is dropping
seems to be leveling out.
Sir, can you hear us?
Sir, nod if you can hear us, OK.
Looks like someone's
coming back to reality.
You're gonna feel a little pinch
here on the count of three, OK?
1... 2... 3...
It's gonna make you feel
a lot better.
How's that feel?
It feel...
It feels good.
I feel good.
That's what she said.
We're coming in with a male
unknown-
That doesn't sound good.
See that's why I gotta stop
taking these night shifts.
I can tell you.
Nothing good ever happens
after 10:00 PM.
Anyways.
I'm hungry.
This is Edna.
She's full of dreams and ideas
that never came to be.
She spends most nights
here crying alone
in this dusty kitchen.
Revisiting the better times
of her memory.
Pretty depressing stuff, huh?
The only clear and constant
thought that crosses her mind.
Is if she only had a man
to get through life with,
maybe things will get better
but only had a man
to get through life with.
Maybe things will get better.
Trip to Aspen this year
was amazing.
So incredible yeah,
we stayed at the scene.
Yeah.
- Oh my God I love it.
It was so nice.
Yeah no but the spa's
way better.
It's way better. And Stephen
took his clients there last year...
She didn't want to be
here anymore.
So she chose a bridge.
She listened for a voice
to stop her.
But it never came.
Only the daunting whispers of
wind pushing her further to the edge.
Then...
when she least expected it...
Something grabbed her attention.
Oh my God, that looks so good.
Oh I've also been spit balling
some names.
What do you think
about Ricky, hmmm?
Yay or nay?
Yay!
Ready! Here comes the airplane.
She finally found a man
to get through life with.
Things were better.
He was everything she
ever wanted.
A good listener.
A shoulder to lean on.
The strong silent type.
The prom date she never had.
She was so glad they met.
I'm so glad we met.
And although he may
have been dead.
For the first time in years.
She was alive.
Oooh.
Can't even begin to tell you,
how long, so long, we've been
waiting for Edna to find a man.
Not that long.
All right,
subject change,
So... Ricky,
tell us about yourself,
what do you do?
He's so cute,
and so shy.
Busy bee...
- OK, you know what,
I can't, I there's
no way I can do this.
Nope.
- Do what.
Are you?
Seriously gonna make me say
this right now.
Mm-hmm
He's...
He's dead.
Can you please just try
and be happy for me just for once
I would be happy for you if you
brought a boyfriend
along that was alive.
- God. Can you stop?
- He's not so.
He's not.
I get it all right.
Please stop.
- Edna.
- You're embarrassing me in front of my date.
- You can't do this.
- Yes I can.
- There's nobody...
Oh my God!
- No.
- Oh God uhm.
I find a man that I am
in love with
and you can't even be
happy for me.
It's disgusting. I would not
tell her what is going on here,
- I... uhm...
- Yo.
Help me out here.
Uhm... Well.
Yeah, it's pretty disturbing.
Edna.
You can't do this.
I'm really worried
about your mental health.
Fine.
That's the way you feel.
Come on Ricky.
They hate us because
they ain't us.
Yeah, that's it.
Oh I'm so...
sorry.
Got him, there, okay...
I'm never going to be able
to come here again.
So I was thinking we could go to
don't know the beach
or something tomorrow.
I know you're not the biggest
fan of water, but.
I don't know.
We could do a picnic or...
They never did make it
to the beach.
Instead, she just stayed up
for days,
fueled by her friend's
harsh opinions.
In fact,
the more time that passed,
the more lifeless he
seemed to become.
Then once again,
when she least expected.
Something grabbed her attention.
What happened to me?
You weren't dead.
And I brought you back to life.
That was pretty cool of you.
He explained how his
actual name was Cider.
My actual name is cider.
Really?
- Like the drink?
- I know it's biblical.
It means liqueur derived
from the juice of fruits.
Yeah, so like the drink.
Sure.
Uh... well...
It's just, I've been calling
you Ricky so...
- Ricky?
- Yeah.
Man do I seem Latin to you?
No, no, I just,
always liked that name.
Let's just stick with Cider.
I feel like it's part
of my core.
It's part of my essence.
Oh yeah, of course.
I mean it is your name.
Rename you that's crazy.
I'm dying for a grilled cheese.
Doesn't that sound good?
Those are fattening.
This place is really cool,
but it seems like they're trying to
capitalize on a young generation,
revisiting vintage Americana,
and I would think that would
include vegan options to just show
a nod to that generation.
Hey, we know you, we get you.
We know what you want.
Oh I didn't know you're a vegan.
No I'm not.
But...
You don't have to be
vegan to care.
What are you laughing at?
OK, be honest.
What do you think?
My ho useless friend Vic spent two years
collecting clothes and reclaimed fabrics,
and we gave birth to this outfit right
after our first experience with the DMT.
That's exactly what it
looks like.
No,
I think it makes my ass pop too.
What's uh?
What's this?
Well, I didn't want to come
right out and say it, but this is me.
Really?
That's you.
- Singing...
- Singing, drumming, strumming, producing.
I spent three years of my life
traveling with Russian hobos
on the back of a cargo train
and I wrote this song.
It's about that-
Oh shh, shh, Shut up.
Wait.
This is my favorite part.
This is the real genius seed.
Come on, look at what I'm doing.
- Lower body. Lower.
- Like this?
Like th-Lower!
Like.
- Ah.
Yeah, it's not really your
fault, it's your body.
OK, ready, watch this.
It was then she realized
she was never going to let
her happiness be dependent
on another human again.
As he forwarded down that river,
she realized that true importance
and power of independence.
The lonesome nights and string
of bad dates
were a dream compared to
the nightmare she called Rick.
But whatever the fuck
his name was,
as you'll see in our next story,
we're going to focus
on the power of friendship.
Might want to grab some popcorn
on this one.
It's about to get wild.
3 little piggies
came to the market.
Everyone get the fuck down.
I said everyone get the
fuck down!
Not you fat boy.
Get up.
We're going to make
this nice and easy.
You do exactly as we say.
Let us do our thing
and that's it.
Do you understand?
Do you understand!?
Why you doing this?
What a great question.
Dude you've been looking
at her all night. Just go talk to her.
Why do you do this?
Do what?
Push me.
I don't push you. Luke
do I push him?
You're trying to help?
He's trying to help.
- Thank you.
Listen guys, I appreciate the sentiment
and everything but I'm fine..I... I...
I don't need it.
You know why you guys do this
every week after week.
No.
Because you guys have settled
down, we've gotten older,
you've gotten comfy and listen,
there's nothing wrong with that at all.
It's totally fine,
but you guys want to go
talk to a girl like that.
I don't, you do.
Okay.
And you project that
onto me and it's... Wow.
- I'm projecting?
- You're laughing,
it's true though.
- I'm trying to help you out.
What kind of friends would we be
if we weren't trying to
get you laid?
You guys would be
awesome friends, like friends
that I would wanna come
out with every Wednesday
and do this kind of shit
but this...
tired of it.
Jesus man.
Sorry, it's just it's more complicated
than you guys would think okay?
- What's so complicated about it?
- There you go pushing.
I'm not pushing.
I'm asking a question.
He's asking a question.
A friendly question.
- It's out a concern.
- Stop being so sensitive.
- I can't come.
OK.
Say what?
I...
Come here.
No come here.
I can't come.
I've never been able to.
What like never?
Once.
I came close.
I was like 14.
Was laying in bed and I.
Figured why not.
And so I.
Was in the middle
of going at it, and I
heard a window
break in the other room.
And I got out of bed.
I pulled up my pants and...
Peaked my little head
around the corner.
There was this burglar.
He was just taking a bunch
of my dad's shit.
Shit, so you're like
traumatized,
that's that's the thing I...
I sat there and I,
I watched him.
I...
And lo and behold, I...
Was as hard as a rock.
Wait, what?
It's like the more shit this guy
grabbed.
And the heavier his...
His breathing got.
The harder I got.
I was weirdly kind of hot.
So like I said.
It's a lot more complicated
than you would think.
Yeah.
So shots or...
I have an idea.
Take it all,
then let's kill the kid.
Sounds good.
Should we like cut off
his face and take turns wearing it?
Yeah.
Guys I...
I know it's you.
Okay.
- You gotta die now!
Can you get that out of
my eyes please? It's really early.
- Are you hard?
- Nope.
- You sure?
- Positive.
- Can we see it?
- Nope.
What what was it
that didn't work?
I can 100%
see your faces right now.
Well, that's super
disappointing.
I want to go, this is stupid.
Okay.
- Bye dude sweet dreams.
- Yup.
Jimmy, this is getting
ridiculous man.
We almost had him man.
No, no, we didn't.
We need something bigger,
something better.
Like what?
Why are you doing this?
Anything?
No.
What about this?
No no.
Fuck!
The fuck! No!
I need you to be fucking straight with
me right here right now, is this happening?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean you don't know!
I'm sorry!
What?
Get down.
KCPD!
- Get down!
- Put your gun down!
Put your fucking gun down!
Get on the ground now!
On the ground, there you go!
Don't move.
Oh Jesus.
We gotta guy down over here.
I'm sorry.
This was huge mistake.
No.
It wasn't.
We gotta go!
Hold your ground!
Don't do it!
Drop the gun!
What kind of
friends would we be?
If we were trying to get laid.
The best friends.
The best freaking friends
I ever had.
Hey baby girl baby girl.
Yep, I just just dropped off
my last package.
That's cool.
But hey listen, I got 2 words
for you
red box.
Yep.
Daddy is going to
pick up a little flick and
then he's going to
give you a little di-
Hey, let me let me
call you back.
Hello.
Kritika Express, I need a
signature here! In the back!
We're uh, we're advised
not to do that, Sir.
I just need a signature
and I'll be on my way.
Try and find me.
OK...
Hello.
Sir.
Wow.
Yep.
Just need a signature
here on the package
and I'll be on my way so...
- We don't have much time,
so I'll brass tacks it.
Probably wondering why
you're holding a package
addressed to here,
but with your name on it.
Yeah.
Coincidence?
How did you know that's my name?
Look in order to not disturb
the space time continuum,
I need to be injected
with your... with our DNA.
Otherwise the chance
the whole process fails,
and then we're fucked.
What are you talking
about talking about?
I'm talking about the end
la fin, vamoose, extinction
in exactly 92 minutes
and 46 seconds an asteroid
is going to come down-
Oh, I get it.
You're one of these crazy
desert guys, huh?
You talk to lizards and,
hang out in the sun.
I don't have time
to small talk with details.
I'm you from the future
and you're me from the past.
And the only way to stop this thing
is if you blast me with your DNA.
What?
- Oh come on, you think it's funny?
Well, it won't be so funny
when we're tiny bits of ash.
All right, let's let's play,
pretend and say I believe you,
which I absolutely do not.
You expect me to do what just,
pull my hair out
and give it to you.
It's going to take more
than that, buddy.
Saliva.
Close.
Blood.
Ooh, gross...
But warmer.
I think you just,
need the sign for
the package sir.
Well unfortunately I
can't do that.
Until you do what's necessary.
Well...
Kritika's policy you can just
pick it up at the office.
Mm hmm.
I ain't happy about it
either, kid,
but it's the only way to ensure
the survival of mankind.
Sorry, the number you
have dialed is not in service at this time.
Not one fucking bar.
I'm you from the future.
You're me from the past.
You're gonna be okay.
This...
Come on, come on.
It's unbelievable.
- Well, if that ain't fate.
I don't know what to tell you.
Well it's not.
It's not fate, it's illegal,
you're kind of holding me
captive here so...
You think it was me.
I've been here with you
the whole time.
Relax man.
You hungry?
No.
How about a cold one?
No, I'm good.
So what do you suggest
that I do?
I told you, man.
Look, I know it's a lot
to take in,
but with all due respect,
I'm the one that's going
to have to take it.
I'm not gonna fuck
you, man. This is insane.
Well unfortunately fucking me
is the only way
you're getting out of here.
And if you don't, you ain't going
to have much time to do anything.
Oh yeah, it's the only way I'm
getting out of here. Well watch this.
Oh well you know it's a long walk
from here what you plan on hitchhiking, ha!
Good luck.
This guy is fucking insane.
He's a desert rat.
That's all he is
just a fucking desert rat.
Full of shit.
His voice is fucking 2... 3
octaves higher than mine.
Hey look,
I know that seeing yourself
living in shit like this
isn't the picturesque life
you imagine for yourself.
But you know its got
its perks, you know.
You live a very full life.
Sure, there's that little black tar heroin
phase that eventually leads to most,
if not all, friends and family
cutting you out completely.
But you know, that's what 25 years
of delivering packages does to a man.
Can you just please shut up?
Please.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, sure, no worries
Hey, you know we got
a birthday coming up.
That's exciting.
How did you know that?
- I got a bottle of the good stuff in the Dome.
We could, maybe do this
thing black out.
Nah I'm good man.
I don't know how else to tell you that.
- Okay, alright.
All right.
Hey look
why don't we like I don't know
ease into this thing.
I could start like nibbling at
your neck, or something like that.
Stop please.
You're so fucking weird.
Are you not reading
my body language at like...
Can you just shut
the fuck up please?
OK I got it.
Why don't we go inside?
It's kind of cold out here.
I promise I ain't gonna
do anything weird.
Absolutely nothing weird.
Scouts honor.
Come on, it's cold out here.
You know how I know
you're not me?
Your TV sucks.
Hmm.
This do anything for
your big boy.
Your... your nipples?
No makes me feel,
Pretty uncomfortable.
- Don't knock-'em till you try-'em.
I got a girl with perfect
nipples.
Waiting for me at home
in a nice bed with,
clean sheets.
They're not always clean.
What is that supposed to mean?
Let's face it, you ain't
Brad Pitt.
She's a hot club girl.
Tons of options.
And that Armenian DJ that's
always hanging around.
He's a friend.
- Oh wake up man.
Who's in your Christmas
card last year?
So she's she's cheating on me
now. Is that what you're saying?
Why am I watching a children's
show with a dirty bum, in a dome.
What am I even doing here.
Yep, I'm leaving can't do it.
There he goes again, wait!
- What.
- Open the package.
- What?
- The package you brought, open it.
You need to see what's inside.
There's no way.
Go fuck yourself.
I'm you from the future
and you're me from the past.
I'm not gonna fuck you
man. This is insane.
Well, unfortunately fucking me
is the only way
you're getting out of here.
And if you don't, you're not going
to have much time to do anything.
Hey.
Hey yourself.
What are we doing?
This is nuts.
We're doing what's necessary.
Let's bring this thing
home, brother.
Oh.
1.
2.
3.
Fuck yes!
Fuck yes.
Meat lovers.
Wild Bills!
Pizza!
Another day.
Another cream pie.
Let's make this more
interesting.
Yeah.
Wow.
Yep.
Let's change subjects.
This one starts on
the other side of town
with a group of poker
playing mobsters.
Set up you've seen
1000 times before.
Only this.
Has a twist.
Oh, oh, oh I got one,
I got a good one.
Why do Italian men grow
mustaches?
Uh.
So they could look
like their mother!
Their mother!
Hey! You know, Tony.
I mean, I'd fuck your mother!
You want to fuck my mother?
Tony it's just joke.
Yeah, it's a goof.
You son of a bitch,
you just see your face.
I got you.
Oh my God, Tony!
Yeah man.
Nearly shit myself.
Almost shit my fucking pants.
Oh my God Tony.
Could a given me a heart attack!
Holy shit.
Whoo.
What the fuck!?
You little shit.
What are you guys doing?!
Get in there.
Come on, get in.
Oh.
Hey!
Hey guys!
Tony!
Get up, let's go.
Get up.
Hey!
Carmine.
How you doing?
Hey Carmine.
How you feeling you doing OK?
- Guys a...
Fucking legend.
She giving you a grape juice
every day?
Drinks more juice than
Sammy fucking Sosa.
Hey ma, you remember Tutti,
don't you?
Yeah.
Hi boys, Tutti.
Are you staying out of trouble?
Wish we were.
Actually Tutti he said he
wanted to fuck you Ma.
Ain't that right?
Tell her.
Tony come on this is
real fucked up.
I'm going to get-
- You ain't going nowhere.
Is that right Tutti?
You wanna pound me Tutti?
Ah don't be shy today,
just about an hour ago
you said that you wanted
to fuck ma,
pound the pussy and give it
to a real good.
Come on, get in there,
go fuck her.
Come on Tutti don't
embarrass me.
She hasn't been with a hog
in a long time.
Get in there and pound that
pussy and fuck her real good.
Come on show her what you got.
Come on, big shot.
Why don't you come on in?
Get this cream cheese factory
going, huh?
Come on, come get it,
I'm right here,
big boy I'm waiting for ya.
Get up all in.
Come on Tutti.
Balls.
This is some fucked up shit.
Shh.
Come on big boy!
Alright I'm gonna fuck you.
Yeah!
Yeah baby.
Yee haw, yee haw!
Alright Tutti!
Atta boy Tutti get in there!
Mama.
Getting full. I
know this food is so good.
- It's so good, it's amazing.
- Right? This place is great.
And I'm just gonna go ahead
and say it right now.
This is going-
- Extremely well.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I was gonna say the exact same thing.
I mean, it's we're finishing
each other's... Sentences.
Come on with it, you're killing me.
- This is so good.
I mean honestly, it's so hard
to date here.
Oh yeah.
Last week I went on
a date with...
- a blind guy.
- Ohh! A blind, really?
- It was a blind date literally yeah.
- Literally.
Yeah.
I mean, obviously
there's nothing wrong with that,
but give a girl a heads up like
tell me, your tell me you're blind.
Could have shot you a text
or something right?
- Yeah!
- Yeah or...
He couldn't. I don't know do
blind people text I have no idea.
God, I don't know.
I've never thought of that.
- No idea how that works.
Guess I'll never find out because
I let him to go after the first date.
Oh yeah, yeah,
well, I guess he never saw it
coming, huh?
Right?
God, you're so bad.
All right,
what's going on here?
Little bumpski.
Yeah, OK, sure I like cocaine.
- Alright she's a part girl, I guess.
- Yeah, yeah, just be careful.
Don't draw attention to it.
Oh well, that'll put
hair on your chest.
- Sure will.
- Just when I thought you couldn't get any cooler.
Aww...
You just snorted my dad's ashes.
What?
Mmmm.
I said you just snorted
my dad's ashes,
So that is what you said, right?
I'm not...
Is that the joke name you call
cocaine, are you playing with me?
No actual ashes.
I got-'em from the crematorium.
On Saint Clair Street.
- What the fuck are you talking about?
Oh it's nothing.
It's just that you snorted
my dad's ashes.
That's not nothing, sweetheart,
that's your daddy in my
throat right now.
Dude, I feel that.
- Well that's so great.
I'm so glad.
- It isn't that great.
It sucks.
You are so cute.
Is your hair naturally curly?
OK, you're a psycho, right?
Psycho about you.
Oh...
That's so sweet.
Yeah... Uh...
Soon as we get that check!
- Yeah where is she?
Ohh bowling could be fun.
Oh my gosh,
we could get ice cream
Oh my gosh Oh my gosh
I have to wake up early.
I am remembering in the morning.
- Oh no.
- Got that old shift.
Ugh, that's the worst.
- Yup.
Well, maybe Saturday night we could
do something if you're not doing anything.
Maybe you know gonna
play by ear right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, alright, alright.
Bye, I'll see you later.
Bye!
Excuse me, do you happen
to have a bookmark?
Yup.
But my name's not Mark it's Sam.
OK.
You want your milk in the bag?
No, I think the carton
will be okay.
Oh, I'm sorry,
that was awful, bags great.
Would you like to try our new
"Java Rama" coffee fountain?
It comes with five
different bold flavors that
will make you start
the day like a savage.
No, I think black's going to be
okay, but don't worry,
I'm not driving or anything.
Oh I did it again.
What the fuck is this?
Oh my...
God!
Ohhh you're gonna be alright
baby, you're gonna be okay.
Everything's cool.
Get some Java going.
What don't.
No, Sir,
no sir, no sir.
On your ass, buddy.
Ohhh.
So we are not going that fast
not in this neighborhood.
Not in this neighborhood.
Are you kidding me?
What is he doing? Hold up,
I gotta film him.
A little fast back
there ay boys?
Huh?
Where's the fire?
He just, he stumbled!
Hey.
Tubby, what's up man?
Hey smile for the camera! We
were going a little faster for you there?
- Dude, check this guy out.
- There's kids around here.
What's up man?
- Tubby.
What's up?
Hey!
There's kids around here.
There's kids around.
Oh!
Get up, there's kids around man.
There's kids around.
It's kinda weird though.
You've reached Tina and Dad
leave a message.
Hey, uh, look who's still
not picking up.
Really wish you would have told me
about the side effects of this shit, hmm.
Anyway, guess you found
your fucking address.
I'm on my way.
Honey, I'm home.
I look like Ben
fucking Franklin.
Hey.
What the fuck?
Hmm.
I think I just asked you
a question, Missy.
Daddy, you're home early.
Yeah, well we finished up early
wrapped up and the ball said-
My God help me please!
God it's hot here, you hot?
How many times I'm going to say
it don't touch the thermostat
we're not heating the whole
neighborhood here, okay?
Dad!
But I'm chilly!
- Hey there chilly, I'm dad. God, help me!
You're so funny.
You got to start answering some
questions, OK? Cause I'm...
You know, I've lost it fully and
and I just would really like to
counteract whatever the fuck's
going on with me right now and.
Oh.
Go to your room.
Now.
Get to steppin' sister.
I'm not playing with you
this time.
So unfair!
I didn't do anything.
Yeah, like that.
It's our song Daddy!
Fuck this!
Good God.
Hey.
Hey daddy!
Nice set up y'all.
I dig the titties.
Thanks daddy.
Let's get an apron on that boy.
I like this one.
He's going to be good.
That was fun.