My name is Sung Neng Yee.
This is my story.
You may not believe it all,
but I lived every moment...
and more.
The years of my childhood
were like a beautiful dream.
I was a princess...
Spoiled, pampered.
Reigning over my every whim.
When the Japanese overran all of Shanghai,
they discovered my private kingdom.
[war planes flying overhead]
[music]
[sounds of truck engines doors slamming,
and soldiers running]
Mama!
[Asian talking]
[crashing sounds]
Mama... I'm afraid.
[people crying]
[Asian talking]
[People screaming and crying]
(NENG YEE) War stole my privileged childhood.
It was gone like a leaf on the wind.
[firecrackers] bang, bang, bang
(NENG YEE) In the Chinese way of counting,
1950 was the Year of the Tiger.
After such a long period of mind-defying
violence.
we were grateful to be alive and free.
(DR. SUNG) What is the matter? Are you cold?
(MRS. SUNG) Firecrackers..they've lost their
magic.
Too much like gunfire!
Cheer up. Look for Neng Yee.
She said she would be near the dragon.
(NENG YEE) The Red flag seemed
China's hope for the future.
(NENG YEE) My parents... I'm home.
Your daughter sends you love and best wishes
for the New Year!
Is this how it is going to be with you?
What, Mama?
This marching business?
The Communists are Chinese.
They have returned our country to us.
We must show respect. Come, I have presents...
(CHUNG SHIN) Did you have self-criticism
this morning?
(NENG YEE) Of course!
(LING MEI) Did you stand up?
Well, I couldn't think of anything really good
so I promised to never wear lipstick again.
Were you sincere?
I was this morning.
[laughter] ha, ha, ha!
I'm starving!
I heard the Communists have actually stopped
all business on Euzhow Road.
The red-light district?
What about all the Singsong girls?
They will be re-educated, of course!
I don't think they excel
because of their intellectual ability!
Oh, boy! Western clothes!
An upperclassman... Lam Cheng Shen.
Hong Kong money.
His family is very rich.
Handsome, too.
I'd forgotten men could look like that.
Forget it!
He's never dated anyone at school.
A real loner...
Give me a few weeks.
I can change that.
You wouldn't dare!
A dinner date... within the month.
Trapped by your own words.
So bourgeois!
If you lose, big mouth,
you have to do my homework papers
for a month!
I'll get him to take me somewhere.
The duties of a mother.
You have money to gamble, Mama.
Where did you get it?
It is not appropriate for you to question me.
Where? Tell me.
An old silk scarf. Just a memento.
We haggled over it for an hour.
We got a good price. That was fun!
Tell me, daughter, where would I wear
it in these times.
Hopelessly out-of-fashion!
Perhaps we should have left China.
I should have taken you out when
the Japanese were defeated.
Nonsense!
Who would have expected it to
go this way?
Look!
I will be a big potato for the Communists.
You just watch, Okay?
If the front door is locked,
I'll go in through the back.
You were not raised to be a "potato!"
What a common expression.
[talking on a bull horn]
[whistle blows]
Neng!
Look! His name. Lam Cheng Shen.
"Volunteers are requested on Saturday
to clean-up the grounds.
Please do your duty for the betterment
of all."
Not on Saturday. Not me.
I have a paper that is due.
It is important to volunteer.
We must show the proper spirit!
Excuse me.
Do you need help here?
I have completed my assignment.
(CHENG SHEN) No, thank you.
I am nearly finished.
I have heard it said that our great
Chairman Mao
does not approve of flowers for
the new China.
Perhaps he prefers weeds.
We had beautiful flower gardens when
I was a child.
These were cut by mistake.
It seemed a waste to see them tossed
with the weeds.
We have not been properly introduced,
I apologize.
What is it?
Homework.
Yes?
Do you live here?
What a surprise.
I'm just selling concert tickets to benefit
poor children.
Chopin.
I just knock on any door.
I'm sorry-- I'm leaving for Hong Kong.
Oh, but the concert is two weeks away.
You will return in time.
I mean, surely you wouldn't miss
two full weeks of classes.
Your tickets-- are they expensive?
I have a wonderful plan.
Nylon stockings have disappeared
from Shanghai.
If you would consider making a purchase
for me in Hong Kong.
I would be most grateful.
And in return for your kindness
I will purchase two seats for the concert.
The tickets will not cost you anything!
That should be enough.
You are asking me to buy nylon stockings?
If it is not a problem for you,
I would be most pleased.
I suppose we should eat first.
Dinner and a concert.
It almost sounds like a "date."
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It won't be expensive. I don't eat much.
Hey, do you always carry so much money
when you go shopping?
Yahoo!!
Your father is late. Something has
happened.
It takes longer now, Mama.
It is not the bicycle.
It was the raven at the kitchen
this morning.
Listen, Mama, you worry for nothing.
Don't use that patronizing tone!
I can read the signs.
I'm going to see Shek Tong Ting.
She'll convince you.
(MRS. SUNG) He was born before dawn
on September 1 1. 1900.
A dark cloud hangs over him at this moment!
Now do you believe me?
(SOLDIER'S VOICE) You have brought
deep shame to China...
our soldiers are sickened to touch you
or of your flesh from the decadent past...
She is soft under her sweater.
Like a young pigeon.
Let go! You animal! Get away from me!
What is it?
She was escaping, Comrade.
You do not look like a Singsong girl.
My father is a very important doctor
at Hwa Tung Textile Hospital.
He did not come home for the evening meal.
Your men detained me, Lieutenant,
on my way to see what emergency has
kept him from his family.
Perhaps my men were over zealous.
Our apologies, Sung Neng Yee.
May I go now?
Of course, but it is not wise
to travel alone at night.
Shanghai still contains many dark elements.
It will take time to eradicate them all.
Thank you, Lieutenant.
Please my card.
(SOLDIER'S VOICE) Seek the forgiveness of
our great Chairman Mao.
or you will be cast aside as worthless
and empty-headed.
Excuse me... I am the daughter of Dr. Sung.
Is my father still on duty?
Dr. Sung? He is not known to me.
Not known to you? Impossible!
He has practiced here for years.
This hospital has many new doctors.
You are inquiring about Dr. Sung?
Where is he?
Papa!
You should not be here, Neng Yee!
No, please!
Papa, what are they doing to you?
I am under "the submission of the people."
Go home.
Dr. Sung is a "clean man!" A patriot!
He loves his country...
No! No! Shut your mouth!
You will only make it worse for Dr. Sung!
Over population and modern technology
are capitalism's own seeds of self-destruction.
Eventually, machines will replace people
in all professions and the masses
will forget how to work.
Their societies will collapse from within.
That is why every citizen of China
must experience labor training.
The time is near when we will be classless
a nation of laborists.
You have something to say?
Excuse me, sir,
what provision is being made
to protect the rights
of the innocent--
those who have been or will be
unjustly accused.
Chairman Mao has repeatedly told us,
"A revolution is not a dinner party!"
Identify yourself!
Tell me about your parents.
Why?
'Cause, they are your family!
Well-- my mother has small feet--
exceptionally small feet.
My father has numerous concubines,
and I don't know how many half brothers
and sisters I have.
Is that all you can say?
Isn't that enough?
I think you have built high walls
about your life.
Are you a student of Psychiatry now?
She really did it!
[piano music]
Will you remove those ugly posters
when we are gone?
Your father stole large sums of money
from the hospital.
His crime is against the people.
The truth must be published.
Lies can be published too!
The witnesses agreed. It is a matter
of record.
You have no confession from Dr. Sung!
Neng Yee! It is enough.
(NENG YEE) Our family's humiliation
was eased
when I graduated with honors from
Soochow University--
the third highest in my class!
The Communist professors could not
ignore my achievements.
I had forced their respect.
It was exhilarating.
My daughter tells me that you have been
a great help with her studies.
I doubt that she needed my assistance.
I may have met your mother
before the war--
at the French Club.
It is possible.
My mother found pleasure in gambling.
Oh, I wish we could go there now
and celebrate.
Why? You would like to dine with ghosts?
Well, if only ghosts came
they would not charge us
for the meal, would they!
Do you always see friends to the door?
Special days should never end.
Why did you tell your parents I helped you
with your studies?
I just wanted them to be in your debt.
But for what purpose?
Couldn't we go inside?
The walls have ears.
I share the flat with two other families.
[music]
[soldiers chanting]
Let's go.
The old palace is just up the road.
The Governess used to take me
for very controlled walks along this street.
Tuesday afternoons and Friday mornings.
We were always on schedule.
A "controlled walk?" What's that?
Shirley and I were in the wagon.
The Governess was forced to pull!
Shirley? Who's Shirley?
She was an American movie star
about my age.
It was bombed during the war,
but completely restored.
I'm glad they didn't change it.
A big general lives there now.
You always find a joke in everything.
[Classical piano music]
[Upbeat piano music]
Boogie Woogie!
[romantic music]
Happy smile!
[laughter and giggles]
Kissing in the new China is not only in
questionable taste
but quite possible unhealthy.
That was in the paper this morning.
Doesn't that depend on the parties involved?
Ouch! I just laid on a rock.
It's not a rock! It's an egg.
Two dozen, I think.
It's an old custom to bring us luck.
Did they have to be red?
It's the color of fertility.
They've already worked their magic.
We'll have them for breakfast.
Neng Yee, Promise me something.
Anything...
Teach our son to laugh!
[laughter] ha, ha, ha
My name is Lam Neng Yee.
I have been given the opportunity of teaching you
two courses-- History and Political Science.
You have been selected to study here
because you are all brilliant soldiers.
Now our government is giving you
the opportunity
to be brilliant scholars, as well.
This will be an intensified course.
You will gain six years of knowledge
in three!
But I have instruction now.
As a matter of policy
all teachers here are being examined.
How is that possible, Colonel?
Why did you family stay in Shanghai
when your relatives were fleeing
with their personal fortunes?
When the stock market collapsed
and all money was converted to Japanese yen
we became refugees in out own city.
But still my father would not leave China!
May I please have some water?
At what age did your parents enroll you
in the McTyler Christian School?
Nine or ten, I'm not certain.
Why did they send you to
a missionary school?
I don't know...
for the instruction.
Isn't it logical to suggest that they did this
because they had strong
Christian sympathies?
They are not religious.
My father had some Catholic instruction
in France.
but I've never known him to pray.
And then after the war you were enrolled
in a boarding school-- also Christian.
The Mary Farham School.
It was Presbyterian.
It rated very high academically.
Is that when you became a Christian?
I was young... impressionable.
It didn't stick!
It was just something you did
when you were in school.
Why do these questions make you
uncomfortable?
My baby resists sitting so long.
She married a man from Hong Kong.
He brought her nylon stockings.
He smuggled them into China.
Thank you.
Smuggling is a serious offense.
This will take consideration.
First, write about your life at
the Mary Farnham School.
Reconsider every event in your time
with the Presbyterians.
You must return all paper that is used.
Even the false starts.
But my family, My baby--
I must go home.
Consider this a chapter in
your autobiography.
The more you write,
the sooner this matter will be closed.
(NENG YEE Speaking) In China,
the family name gives meaning to a person.
I write this with true awareness that
the history of my family
is of deeper importance than
who I have become.
After the defeat of the Japanese in 1945,
my father brought us back to
our beloved Shanghai.
I was 13 years old...
Many of my classmates wore gold crosses
about their necks
I did not want to say that I was not
a Christian
so I told them I was saving my neck
for a string of perfectly-matched pearls!
At first I had difficulty keeping pace
with my classmates.
The teachers often spoke of the Bible
and Jesus Christ
in a most natural way.
As if He were more than a
historical figure.
I found this puzzling, but I dismissed it.
My studies demanded all my attention.
Your writing is too specific.
As if you were hiding something.
Fiction can perhaps be more
rambling in style.
I am not a writer of fiction!
(NENG YEE Speaking) A self-criticism
and confession
are the first steps to social reform,
I will attempt to explain my involvement
with Christianity
at this impressionable age.
It began like a tiny seed planted
in my spirit.
I was away from my parents and
lonely for something.
Living God, can you hear me?
Please help me claim You as my friend.
(NENG YEE Speaking) At a time of
personal stress.
I did profess to be a Christian.
It was the night before we faced
the Middle School entrance exams.
The strong emphasis on high test scores
made me apprehensive.
[singing]
(NENG YEE Speaking) By the time
I reached 16 years.
the Christian God was forgotten.
I now look to our great Chairman Mao
for instruction and guidance!
Religion will ultimately disappear
from human history.
But it will be a slow process
of re-education.
Old ideologies and cultural habits
from the past
cannot be eliminated in one generation.
The era of pure Communism is a prize
for the future.
That will be China's millennium!
For now, it must be determined
if you are worthy to assist us in our goals.
Will it always be unfair like this?
Perhaps you should write again
in more detail!
I am about to give birth, Colonel.
My baby needs adequate rest.
The softness of your past is most evident.
You are preparing your baby for life!
I talked to You when I was a child.
Do You remember my name?
Comrade, good evening.
I am hoping to request a small favor.
You see, I have a friend who teaches here.
We had a terrible argument.
I need to see her to patch things up.
Classes are completed for today.
My friend is a serious Party member-
very dedicated.
Hours mean nothing to her.
In fact, that's why she keeps me waiting.
Her name is Lang Neng Yee.
If you could check...
The Admissions Office opens at 8 o'clock.
Passes are issued there!
How can you sleep so late?
An indulgence of the lazy capitalist class.
The revolutionary masses have been
at work for hours.
The Colonel is not here?
He has more important duties.
May I please request some water?
Just a glass of water.
You must learn self-discipline.
I have nothing further to confess.
We will help you to remember.
[Chinese command]
We demand a full confession
of your counter-revolutionary activities.
You will begin by admitting that
you are a Christian!
If it were true, what is the crime?
Our constitution guarantees
religious freedom
for all the people.
You play games!
[Chinese command]
You accepted an honored teaching position
wearing a mask of lies!
Did you intend to infiltrate the minds
of our brave soldiers
with your decadent beliefs?
That is absurd.
[Chinese command]
Why did you marry a man
from Hong Kong
who is not a member of the Party?
I came to love him...
Love is a bourgeois conceit!
It has no place in this classless society.
You speak of a classless society,
yet you deliberately separate those
whose background
was more privileged than your own.
My background? Explain yourself! Whore!
Your manner of speaking--
the cutting way you express yourself--
Maybe the custom in Northern China
but not here.
You betray yourself!
We must eat from the same rice bowl!
You will answer "yes" or "no"
to my question.
Are you a Christian?
He may be distant from me,
but I will not deny His presence.
Yes or no?
Yes...
Comrade, could I trouble you to call
and check and see
if she is still working?
She hasn't been home for three nights.
You understand the problems men have.
I need to see her.
You are crazy and weak to let a women
have that power over you.
Put your mind and energies to your duties.
You are allowed two minutes.
God... I am unable to think.
"Though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death
I shall fear no evil...
for Thou are with me."
Women, they're always a problem,
right?
The hours are long till morning, huh?
She has probably found a new friend
and not bothered to tell you.
Please forgive me for my years of silence.
Help Cheng Shen... my parents...
But my heart is with my child.
Oh, God, is this a sin against my baby?
[gunshots] bang, bang, bang
[remembering gun shots] bang, bang, bang
It has been determined
that it was some form of
electrical disturbance--
A freak storm.
Colonel, I respectfully request
the opportunity
to speak to someone who was there...
Perhaps one of the soldiers.
Why? To what purpose?
I would like to ask--
If they observed a lightening bolt
from heaven?
To explain... words seem too small.
Why would the Christian God create
a miracle for you?
Since you do not claim Him.
Perhaps, He remembers more than
our minds can hold.
You have been released from your
teaching position here.
I am sorry for that.
I regret my appearance.
May I go home, Colonel?
My time is near.
Fifty six days maternity leave is granted
to all the new mothers of China.
But first you will give attention
to another chapter in your autobiography.
This time you will write about
your husband...
[water bag breaks and water leaks out]
Nurse, When can I see a doctor?
You are number 27, The Doctor is seeing 14.
Patience. First babies take their time.
Remember when I was a little girl
you told me I must be the first to walk
on the moon?
Because no one ever remembers the second.
Where is Cheng Shen?
Why isn't he with me?
I have told you.
They keep him at the Courts at night.
Sometimes until after 1 1:00.
Mama, listen to me!
Of all the stories I have told you,
this one is the most true.
I have a promise from God
that we will all escape from China.
I don't know how, but I have His promise.
We will be free!
Of course, darling.
He spoke very clearly. It wasn't a dream!
Oh, mama... mama...mama!
It's all right... it's going to be all right, darling.
[groaning and pushing sounds]
I want Chain Man to see flowers and green grass.
You think he'll remember?
Here.
He smiled.
May I ask you a private question?
This is about as private as Shanghai gets.
Today, the mother of my son can
ask me anything!
Do you still believe in God?
It's amazing how your mind works... God?
You mean in the Christian sense?
Mao cut out his tongue years ago.
I still hear His voice.
In the wind, no doubt.
You are so handsome.
Absolutely perfect ears,
and a wonderful, distinctive nose...
Lam Sung Neng Yee?
What is it?
Only six more days. They want me back.
Mama, I have to find milk!
...bus 42.
Central line, please.
Ah, the baby-- a boy or girl?
I bet your first. How old?
A boy and yes, my first. Seven weeks.
You worry about leaving him so soon.
He needs milk.
I don't know when I can be with him.
The stores in our district have been
out for weeks...
My shift ends in twenty minutes.
You wait!
We'll talk about the milk.
We meet on market days.
No one pays attention.
(Pastor) "The Lord is my light
and my salvation:
whom shall I fear?
The Lord is the strength of my life:
of whom shall I be afraid?"
The Scriptures tell us that we are
"children of the light."
We see and hear what our tongues
can not always speak.
Let us offer a silent praise.
What shall we sing?
"Take My Life And Let It Be."
[singing in silence as not to be heard]
[music]
This sister is being criticized by
the authorities.
She has an urgent need for milk
for her son.
I can bring fresh milk from the country
every Wednesday.
(Woman) She must have some
powdered milk too.
Carrying it so far-- The milk can sour.
(Another woman) All powdered milk
is exported.
But I have a friend who works in
the government store.
I will speak to her.
Today, you will write the history
of your husband.
With respect, Colonel,
I'm not that acquainted with
his personal history.
Recall for us every conversation from
your first meeting.
There is particular interest in
the money deposited
each month in your account
from Hong Kong.
A small amount.
It comes from his family.
How else would we survive?
You! You come up! Come! You come up.
You! You, back there!
You forgot this last night.
Don't be so careless next time.
Thank you.
Mama! I have milk. Powdered milk!
Oh, you found it.
He just went to sleep.
I miss touching you.
I measure each second that
we are alone
like chapters in a book.
He will have no childhood.
Cheng Shen, I have a plan!
Don't you tell me anything!
They compare our stories.
We must keep a low profile--
live longer!
What else did you bring back
from Hong Kong besides stockings?
I told you.
I bought possibly two shirts-- pajamas.
Why did you choose that
particular restaurant
before the concert?
I checked the menu. The prices
seemed fair.
Where did you buy so many
phonograph records
you keep in your apartment?
I was a collection from over the years.
What was the exact amount of the bill
for your dinner?
I don't remember. How can it matter?
Why did your father have
so many concubines?
Do all rich men have such
an appetite for sex?
Is your mother without passion?
Be silent!
Cheng Shen!
I am ready to lie,
but I don't know what to lie about.
What have they done to you?
I wanted to see if it would still fit.
I can hear you playing the piano.
Two keys are stuck. It is driving you crazy!
Stop it! Stop it!
How did we ever find each other?
I knew you were mine the first time
I saw you.
You play "what if" because "what is"
is to impossible to confront.
Today the temptation came
to give them what they want
and let them win...so that I can lose.
It would all be over.
Don't look at me!
[NENG YEE Thinking] They bend us like
saplings in the wind.
Our separations are more eloquent
than our meetings...
I wonder, will we ever again dare
to be graceful together?
I know you value a trusting heart.
But Cheng Shen is drowning in
some private despair.
Please forgive this little push...
if it is wrong.
Wednesday's the market day.
I always try to go.
The vegetables come straight
from the fields.
Do you shop there?
I don't know that I'll be free Wednesday.
Would you mail this for me?
To Hong Kong.
Ticket!
When did you last see your father?
My father?
He has been detained at the clinic.
Several months... I'm not sure as to
the exact date.
Dr. Sung recently contacted the flu.
He has been removed to the hospital
for observation.
Perhaps you should visit him.
Colonel, I respectfully seek
your permission.
Papa...
so, they're treating you like a big shot.
Private room for a flu patient.
Your Mother?
She's worrying about you.
Never letting Chuin Man out of her sight.
You know Mama.
Promise, Neng Yee, promise you will
take care of her!
Maybe they'll let you come home at last.
It's only the flu, Papa.
You have always been blessed with
strong dreams.
As much a son as daughter to me.
Papa...
They're experimenting with a new drug.
It causes extensive bleeding.
Nurse! Nurse! We need help!
[NENG YEE speaking] Our daughter, Chuin Way,
was one month old when Papa left us.
The crime was murder without
proof of intent.
We have to take what happens.
Swallow the bitterness.
Oh, God, I confess to you
that my faith is small.
Not all of us will escape the fire unscathed.
Some will stumble so that we will be
refined and purified for His purpose.
When you plant melon seeds,
you harvest melons.
When you plant bean seeds,
you get beans.
When you plant seeds of faith,
you find God!
I want to thank you for helping
my babies.
and for helping me.
This is our sister of the Firing Squad.
China has seen many things
that some of us would call "miracles"
since the Revolution.
He has given me a message for our sister.
Our Lord has asked you to trust Him for
one day at a time.
The days will become weeks,
and weeks into months and months
will fall into years.
one day at a time.
[screaming and shouting]
Do not resist. Do not resist.
Word has just reached me
that your husband
has made a full confession
to our charges of espionage.
A spy!
Guilty of conspiring with
foreign governments.
They told me that you made
a full confession
that I was a spy...
Lies...
that I betray my country...
Lies... Lies...
They said that you were very convincing.
Lies!
It's okay... it's okay.
It's impossible. Not now.
Reality, Mama.
Reality is always possible.
I'll go to Shek Tong Ting.
I'll buy the strongest potion of ginseng
and you must go to the Bath House
and sit in a tub of scalding water.
It's past the time for potions, Mama.
It's already the second month!
Oh, you had a letter from Hong Kong
this morning.
Where is it?
There.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you make my heart stop!
His father is dying, Colonel.
He asks to see his son for the last time!
My mother-in-law has enclosed
a certificate
signed by the Doctor.
I respectfully request a 30 day exit permit
for my husband
to visit his father at this time of sadness.
What assurance can you offer that
he will return in 30 days?
I will be your assurance.
His parents have never seen their grandchildren.
I humbly request that his daughter
be allowed to accompany him.
Your husband has been assigned to a camp
where he will experience labor reform.
All educated people should learn how
to work with their backs.
Could that order not be postponed
for 30 days. Colonel?
How do you know he won't abandon you?
I have his son.
Family ties remain important even in
the new China.
And I am two months pregnant.
Having children is proof that we are alive--
that we have worth!
Don't be a dreamer.
They will never let you go.
I will come back.
No! You must not even consider it.
I may not see you again while I am still
in my twenties.
Perhaps even my thirties.
Please wait for me!
If I am in my forties,
Mama always said a touch of gray
was becoming.
I hope you'll agree.
I have instructions for Chuin Way.
A safe journey for your husband
and daughter.
The penalty for escaping to Hong Kong
is a minimum of ten years in prison.
I am not escaping, Colonel.
It has been decided that you will serve
you husband's term as forced labor
until he returns.
I hear you were once a teacher.
Chemistry was my subject--1 7 years!
We don't talk here.
But I miss intelligent conversation.
They work us like animals,
but what is in our minds will not go away.
Don't help me. Stay back!
I am here to apply for an exit permit.
I intend to visit relatives in Hong Kong
during my 56 day maternity leave.
You should have applied months ago.
Your baby will be sitting up
before the applications
are stamped by all the official agencies.
But will I be permitted to fill out
the "appropriate forms?"
The forms are easy. The procedure
is difficult.
Any news for Lam Neng Yee?
My exit permit?
Oh, yes. I have news for you.
Go to the bathhouse. You smell
like a beggar!
I will return in two days!
I told you, you're dreaming.
Two days!
Lam Neng Yee?
Report to the medical section.
I haven't felt the baby move
for two days now.
The heartbeat is strong.
There is evidence of a kidney infection.
That is why you are retaining fluids.
The nurse will give you some
vitamin C tablets.
Could you have miscalculated the time?
Your ninth month?
Yes.
The baby will not be born in China!
Then where?
I forgot to ask.
Somewhere free...
I don't understand why God should speak
to you directly.
Because nobody else could deliver
the message!
I read a book once about Christian saints
in the Middle Ages.
They spoke like you.
I have His promise, Mama!
Has He promised to keep you alive
in that hell hole?
(Guard 1) The old cow is slowing down.
(Guard 2) That baby's going to get
dumped with the rocks.
How can you find the strength?
"You tell the world the Communist Party
has brought freedom to China.
I want to go to Hong Kong to see
my father-in-law who is dying.
You will not let me go!
I am using my 56 days maternity leave
to go
so it will not interfere with
my labor training job.
You have no reason not to grant me
an exit visa.
Please check with other departments
to see what they are doing
about my application."
It is over 21 words, you lose the rate.
Very expensive for you.
Every word is important.
I will pay!
Where do you want this to go?
To our great Chairman Mao Tse Tung.
To Zhou Enlai, Vice-Minister of Foreign Affairs
and the Central Police in Beijing.
I don't have a name.
You want to send 3 telegrams to Beijing
each 91 words?
I have cash. Let me check your count.
You again! Don't ask! Just Go!
Why is it nobody in Shanghai has
any answers.
I have to go to the top of the ladder.
You can go where you want to go
just as long as it's away from here!
Top of the ladder!
You! The fat one! Out! Go back!
Go Back!
It's bad enough that you use
that old gimmick
of your maternity leave.
In 56 days you could go
around the world.
Then I would be back in Shanghai,
Captain.
Cunning like a beggar too, huh?
Beijing has called us twice about
your application.
This office has been unduly criticized.
You have caused us to lose face!
Sign! Report to this address.
I was about to have tea.
Please, sit. Come.
I assumed your children would grow up
under the Red flag.
You have had capitalistic ideas
from birth --
but your children...
Perhaps it was a personal goal.
You've served your husband well.
I would be pleased for the opportunity
to express that personally.
That may be possible, Colonel.
One day...
A higher authority has granted
your exit permit.
It is known, of course, that you will
not return to China.
Only God knows... China is my home.
Please take your God with you.
Tell Him it is His last chance to escape.
Within a decade He'll be locked away
in a museum.
To do that, Colonel, you would have to
imprison the wind!
Safe journey.
(NENG YEE'S VOICE) You will come, Mama.
I have His promise!
Let me go now. Please.
A way will open for you...
Oh! Chuin Man!
Chuin Man! Look!
I'm going out there.
Neng Yee!
You made it in your 20's after all.
Look at us.
I am so ashamed.
I missed your presence.
When our son is born,
I promise to be young again.
You won, Neng Yee.
You won for all of us.