(vehicle hums)
(engaging dramatic music)
(wind blows violently)
(engaging jazz music)
(shop commotion murmurs)
(jazz guitar riff)
- Hey Charlie, you got a quarter, man?
- Another phone call, there you go.
Hey, man.
- Beer?
- Yeah, thank you, mate.
- How about one of these?
- Two dollars?
- Yeah, American.
All right.
(bar music plays)
(engaging dramatic music)
- I put the whole load on the table.
And guess what?
- What?
- Bang, blackjack again.
I got a load of money
and I said to myself,
"Joshua, it's time for you to leave Vegas.
"Swing around to Hollywood."
- Why don't you try this one?
- I don't know man, I'm
already fucking legless.
What's your name?
- Charlie.
- Nice to meet you, Charlie.
- Nice to meet you.
- Thanks.
- What's troubling ya?
- Ah, cheers.
- You know, with all the
wandering you're doing, man.
- Yeah.
- Are you gonna like get a job?
Or are you just gonna keep on moving on?
You know from town-to-town,
like a drifter, man?
- I don't know, man, I really don't.
- Are you running away
from something, man?
- No.
- Are you running away from somebody?
- I'm not running away from anything.
I'm not running away.
Why are asking me these things?
What do you got against me?
- To me, it seems like a real lonely life.
- What are you running away from then?
- [Patron] Hey, Charlie,
can I get a cold one?
- Yeah, I'll be right back, man
I'll be right back.
- Christ.
Christ, Jesus.
Hi.
- Hey.
- I'm Joshua.
- I'm Anna.
Have you got a cigarette?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks, do you have a light, too?
Well, are new in town, huh?
- How'd you guess?
- Let's see, you're not an actor,
you're not a director, lie to me.
No, okay, a musician?
Han-Solo?
- I'm a fryer, fish and
chips and french fries.
You know?
- That's good stuff,
I like fish and chips.
- I don't do it anymore.
- Well, what are you gonna do now?
- I'm gonna try and split
'cause I'll walk out of this place.
(engaging dramatic music)
- Oh my God, how can you
drink like this, man?
You're gonna fuck yourself
up at this rate, you know?
- I'm feeling really sick now.
Well, the restroom's back there.
(vomiting)
- Fuck.
Shit.
- [Anna] You could come
on over to my place.
- I don't want to make a fool of myself.
- Let's go.
- All right.
♪ I've been 40 days in the wilderness ♪
♪ Haven't had a touch of tenderness ♪
♪ On a tender little
clock, got limited time ♪
♪ But that don't stop
me from doing the bar ♪
♪ What I can't done and
squeeze my alligator ♪
♪ There's some motherfucker
that's buzzing my elevator ♪
♪ And we're gonna rock ♪
♪ We're gonna roll, R-O-L-L ♪
♪ We're gonna rock ♪
♪ Oh, we're gonna R-O-L-L ♪
♪ I said we're gonna rock,
gonna roll, R-O-L-L ♪
(birds chirp)
- Very cozy this is.
Where'd you piss around here?
- Over there.
- Where?
- Are you wanting me to
take that off your hand?
♪ Vicar has only got one ball ♪
♪ The other is in the Albert Hall ♪
♪ His mother, the dirty bugger ♪
♪ Cut it off when he was small ♪
(piss runs)
Very interesting process it is, you know?
It's really good to get drunk sometimes.
Oh Joshua, Joshua.
(engaging jazz music)
- Wicked.
- Like it?
I've had a good sight of you.
You know, you can come in on lay down
on the bed with me if you'd like to.
But, only if you take
your pants off first.
(engaging jazz music)
Do you know why men call women chicks?
- No, why?
- 'Cause women always pick up worms.
- Night.
Do you want me to turn the light off?
- [Anna ] No I don't want that.
- Yeah.
- [Anna] I'm afraid of the dark.
Nighty-night, don't let the bed bugs bite.
(jangling)
I'll be back soon.
- Hey, Anna!
You can't leave me like this.
Oh, you terrible, terrible human being.
(clanking)
Fuck.
Fuck it.
(clattering)
♪ Shadows from the trees ♪
♪ On the sidewalks ♪
♪ Dead leaves ♪
♪ Aching in the heart ♪
- Are you hungry?
- [Joshua] Sure I'm hungry.
- Good, because I brought you
the best burger and fries in town.
(muffled arguing)
Well go, hit me.
Go on, what are you gonna do, kill me?
Hmm.
- What am I here for?
Fucking hell, why am I here anyway?
Come on, why, tell me why.
- 'Cause you're my prisoner.
- Oh, I'm your prisoner.
And what am I accused of?
- Think Joshua, think.
I'm sure there's something
you can come up with.
- Somebody is very funny
around here and it's not me.
(glass clatters)
Whatever you're talking about,
you've got the wrong guy.
- Look, I can't let you go
Joshua unless you tell me
what you've done, 'cause
unless you tell me
what you've done, I can't let you go.
- Hey, hold on, what the
fucking hell is this?
I've never heard such crap.
- Now, Joshua, I don't like
it when people yell and swear.
- All right, what have you got?
You've got a resentment to men's lives?
- I hope you can do better than that.
(engaging dramatic music)
- So that's what's going on,
it's not me, it's that
instrument you're using.
- Not that simple.
- What a waste, this is, St. Matthew.
- What do you know?
- [Joshua] What do you
mean, what do I know?
- You don't know shit.
- Everybody knows.
You can see what it does to people.
- Oh yeah, what?
- It simply destroys them.
If you wait for me then
why have you hated me?
(engaging dramatic music)
Are you trying to kill yourself?
♪ Feel like a big boulder ♪
♪ In and out ♪
♪ Give your life ♪
♪ And every time they come ♪
♪ They take a little
piece of you with them ♪
I feel like I don't exist anymore.
Suddenly all my feelings disappear
and all the pain vanishes.
- You should trim your hair, you know?
Your ends are to starting to split.
You know, you're a very delicate flower.
- I'm a wilting flower.
- No, you're not.
- They're not in there, you know.
- Well, where are they then?
- You still don't get it, do you?
I'm not going to tell you.
- I don't know what to tell you.
Give me a clue.
- Stop pretending you're stupid.
You're starting to bug me.
Hey, Joshua.
Save me.
Save me, Joshua, I'm falling!
Hurry up!
- [Joshua] I can't reach.
- Well try, try harder.
- [Joshua] Come here.
- No, you have to do it.
Charlie, I'm caught.
- [Joshua] Come on, come on.
- Charlie, I-
- I got ya.
- Steven, is Steven here?
Yes, it's Steven, you're such a cheater.
(panting)
No, no.
Get off me.
Get away from me.
(engaging jazz music)
(dark unsettling music)
Do it yourself.
(romantic music and panting)
Joshua.
Now, who do you love more?
Your mother or your father?
- Not my mother or father.
- Your friends?
- I don't really got any friends, as such.
- Country?
- Country where I can live like this.
- Beauty?
Beauty, only if she were
a goddess and immortal.
- Money?
- No, I hate money as
much as you hate God.
- Well what do you love then?
- I love the clouds.
- Clouds?
- Yeah, over there.
- Where?
- Over there.
- Up there, those beautiful,
magnificent clouds.
(birds chirp)
- Oh, you look beautiful
- What are you doing?
- I bet you would drive
everybody crazy like this.
- Hang on.
- No, no.
Look, see first, ta-da!
- Oh cute.
- Like it?
- No, when did you do that?
- Your told me to.
I think it's pretty neat.
- Not sure I do.
- It looks sexy on ya.
- You know, you're
gonna have to let me go.
Anna, just explain to
me, what do you want, eh?
- Just promise you're not gonna leave me.
- How can I do that?
- Just promise.
Just promise!
- Look, I've gotta decide for me self.
- Can't you promise?
- Look, you know that.
Listen, when I was 16, I sent a letter
to me mum, saying that my father was dead.
I even made it look as
if it came from America.
I was just trying to get
her to stop waiting for him.
But she, she wouldn't believe it.
She thought it was all a conspiracy,
that he was like being
held prisoner somewhere.
Her mind was going though.
She was really sick.
Anyway, about six months later, I actually
got a letter saying that he was dead,
and you know, I couldn't tell her.
- You're gonna leave, ain't you?
- I don't know.
- See those, take 'em.
- Anna.
- Go.
- Anna, look.
- Just go, see ya, bye.
- Look, I didn't mean to
give you the wrong idea.
- Don't say anything, just go.
(door opens and closes)
(traffic and commotion buzzes)
(engaging jazz music)
I've been out and around
town to sell a few things.
I sold a few today.
- Wow, those are real nice.
These are real nice.
How much can you sell these for?
- Well, about 10 bucks.
- That one's a bit special.
- This is really pretty.
How much did you say?
- 10 dollars.
- 10 bucks?
- Wow, it's cool.
- You can have it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- You know that girl?
The girt that sitting
next to me at the bar?
The girl, Anna?
- Yeah.
- I mean what about her?
I mean, I'm really worried?
I think she's addicted to heroin.
- Really?
What makes you think that, man?
- These couple of guys, they were cool,
at least the time when I worked.
Do you know of 'em sort of
like personally, intimately?
- What are you getting at, man?
- Well, can they ever get off I mean?
- I got other things on my fucking mind.
- Yeah, well, I'll work it out, Charlie.
- Yeah, we'll see, Joshua.
(door knocks)
(bottle clanks)
- You hungry?
- No, just fucking frustrated.
- All right, let's see what I got.
(plates clank)
Californian wine, bananas,
some crystals, bread.
You know, you look a little pale.
- I'm always pale, Joshua.
(plates clatter and bags rustle)
- You're missing out on
your feast, you know?
I went to that bar.
I saw our friend, Charlie.
- What do you mean you saw
him, what did you tell him?
- I didn't tell him
anything, we just talked.
- You think you're just
walking out of here?
- Not while I'm eating.
- I'm not on drugs, Joshua.
- What are you on about?
- You're all the same, fucking studs,
pigs, you're all the same.
- Why are you being a bitch?
- Because.
- Hey, put that down okay?
Put that down it might be loaded.
Come on, come on.
(banging)
Jesus Christ.
Anna, put it down.
Jesus, what are you
doing, what are you doing?
- What time is it?
- I don't know, around seven o'clock.
- Seven, seven o'clock.
Dinner's ready.
Come on Anna, everybody's waiting for you.
I remember when mother used to call me
and I'd come on down, and
she'd bring in the food
while my Father and
Johnny, my brother didn't
sit at the table, and I'd sit
in front of 'em, and talk to my mother.
Well, my dad and my brother,
they'd just be sitting,
waiting, waiting, doing
nothing but watch TV.
My mother used to complain
about them all the time.
She'd cook the nicest meals too.
But, I think she's upset now.
She won't even talk to me anymore.
Joshua?
- [Joshua] Yeah.
- Why did you come back?
- [Joshua] Needed somewhere to stay.
- Oh you liar.
Do you think he could
ever love someone like me?
- Someone as crazy as you?
- What did you say?
- A Bernadette.
- You better watch your mouth.
(light banging)
(voices murmur from outside)
- Oh, great.
Joshua.
Joshua!
Damn him.
(engaging jazz music)
(bar commotion murmurs)
- So I kinda like made up a story
to tell the guy she was with.
What's happened to you?
You look like a total wreck.
- What's happening to you.
Are you sick or something?
- Charlie, I need to talk to you.
- [Charlie] About what?
- Can you get somebody off this stuff?
- Get somebody off of what?
- Bloody fucking heroin.
I wanna get her off of it.
- Good luck, Superman.
That's gonna be a tough one.
- Yeah, I know.
- Who the fuck are you man,
have you ever tried it?
You don't know nothing about it, man.
- [Joshua] If somebody
would explain it to me
I think I might understand it.
- Look, take it this way, man.
You can't get somebody to
leave the ways they wanna be.
That's the way it is.
(engaging dramatic music)
- Ow, ow, stop it.
What's the matter with you, are you crazy?
- Who the fuck do you think you are?
Jesus Christ, the fucking Savior?
Joshua, what did you with my stash?
- I threw it away.
- Oh you did, huh?
Well guess I want it and it was mine.
You can't do this, Joshua.
You can't stop a junkie from doing
from doing what he does
because it's not a joke.
- I do it for myself.
- Joshua, you can't help me.
Don't you get it?
You can't help me.
I wanna do what I'm doing, it's my life.
- [Joshua] I'm going to be
right here with you, Anna.
- I'm sick Joshua, I feel like shit,
like shit, like shit, like shit.
(vomits and retches)
(water rinses)
- Tell me a story, Joshua.
- A story?
- Yeah.
- And what about?
- I don't know, anything, just a story.
Talk to me.
- All right, yeah, okay.
There was this guy.
He lived in this little old
town, just outside Liverpool.
It was full of closed-down factories,
and every morning he'd
get up and go to work
in this fish and chip joint.
He'd start at seven o'clock,
maybe cleaning all the
grease from the ovens.
And then at 12 o'clock
when the shop would open,
he'd start frying the fish
and watching the bubbles,
and he'd see the grease build up,
and build up, all over again.
He never had time to smoke a
cigarette or talk to anyone,
and at night, when the shop would close,
he'd go home to this
tiny little Council flat,
and he was so greasy and so
smelly, that he could never find
a girl that could stand him
for more than five minutes.
And he'd dream, oh he
dreamed, that he could just
walk out, and start all over
again, living for himself.
But every morning it
was the same old thing.
He'd just get up, and go to work,
and wipe and the blade of all the grease.
Until one day, while he was staring
at the oil bubbling in the pans,
he had this fucking explosion,
and for the first time in this
old chip shop's history,
the ovens blew up.
Well, that sound would
never leave his memory.
And then guess what?
- [Anna] What?
- That was the first time
he realized it was time
to get the fuck out and start living.
(chains clank)
Settle down.
- I don't care and what are you
going to do about it anyways?
I'm sick of this chain!
- Bitch, listen to me, I
don't mean it all like that.
- Let me go, go.
- Get down, get down, love, for me?
(intense pulsating music)
- Jesus, get off me.
- Can't you feel me?
- Fuck me, then fuck me.
(tense dramatic music)
(Anna moans)
(engaging jazz music)
(Anna pants)
Don't stop, don't stop.
(playful jazz music)
I'm so cold, I'm so cold.
I'm too warm, I'm too hot.
I'm too hot, too hot.
No, no, no.
No, no!
No.
(Anna pants)
(engaging jazz music)
- I'm getting rid of pain, yeah.
It's getting better.
♪ Getting better ♪
♪ All the time ♪
- Keep away from me, motherfucker.
Just stay away.
Who the fuck are you anyways?
You tell me you are just a little shit
from Liverpool, England
with fucking screwball ideas
and narrow, so narrow visions,
oh, if you only had an idea of how narrow
your little teeny, tiny fucking mind is
and you're trying to tell me what to do?
You can't even take care of your own self.
You wanna take care of me?
You haven't even got a place?
I mean, I don't get it.
Can't you see that all this is bullshit,
all of this, whatever you've been doing
It's a bunch of crap and how can anybody
know what anybody else feels anyways?
Can you?
No, you're just an
arrogant son of a bitch.
You're a pig.
I mean, Joshua
- Mm-mm.
- Can I have a puff?
You're smoking that whole
cigarette aren't you.
Such a cheat, you know, you always cheat,
you cheated the other
time, that other time too,
the first time, do you remember?
- I'm cheating.
- Oh bananas, aha, I
don't feel like bananas.
I don't wanna eat bananas
right now, go away.
Go away, leave it alone.
I'm still hurting, you know?
- No, no, oh, no, no.
- Back is, yes my back is.
(coughs)
Drink some.
Now, I gotta pee.
No.
- You gotta keep yourself hydrated.
It's really gross though.
It tastes like cranberry juice.
- I love it.
- That's not funny.
I mean I have to drink all this shit.
I don't even like alcohol.
- Feel better, bird?
- No.
- Okay, ow.
The ash just burned me.
Kiss it, you have to kiss it.
- Why?
- You have to kiss it.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm gonna go, Joshua, let me,
I have to lie down somewhere.
I don't feel all that good.
Watch, you're gonna smoosh the banana.
Did we put the ashes in here?
Oh that's great, that's just wonderful.
- Both of us knew.
- You wanna natural and that's real good.
Delicatessen, you should try
this, natural and banana.
It's my recipe.
(laughs)
Is it good or what?
Okay, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm serious I wanna go back to bed.
Let me go.
What did you do with this chain anyways?
- I'm not gonna let you go.
- My hand cramps.
Can't you take them off me?
- No.
- Can't you take 'em off me now.
Please?
- No.
- Can't you open them
up and let me go there.
Look, I'm all bruised and so sore.
Now, it's really hurting.
I hate you, I hate you.
- I like it.
- You're doing this to me and
I didn't even ask you for it.
Witch.
(kicking)
Anna lay down, Anna.
Ah yes.
(engaging jazz music)
♪ Little girl in the woods ♪
♪ Looking for a wolf ♪
♪ The bad one ♪
♪ But she can't find him ♪
♪ Nowhere ♪
♪ I wonder why ♪
♪ She said I wonder why ♪
♪ Aint I gonna die ♪
♪ Am I not supposed to ♪
♪ But the wind blew through the trees ♪
♪ With much dignity and told her no ♪
♪ And told her no ♪
- Just one.
- No, I have one, two, three, four,
four and more necklaces,
four and one more to go.
Can I have one more, please?
(romantic jazz music)
(uptempo jazz music)
♪ Hitler, we only had one ball ♪
♪ The other was in the overhaul ♪
♪ His mother, and their brother ♪
♪ Cried out when he was sick ♪
- Hey, man, what's going?
- Hey, Charlie.
- Hey, this place is still
looking as funky as it always did, man.
- Yeah, I know
- So, where have you been for
the last couple of days, man?
I haven't seen you around like.
Like somebody, something,
knight in shining armor?
Ah, can I have a seat?
- Sure, you can go ahead.
- Oh wow.
- I was just here.
- You know that girl, Monica, your friend?
- [Anna] Right.
- Right, well she owes me
200 bucks from last month.
- [Anna] Does she?
- And she's telling me now
that she doesn't have it
and she doesn't have to pay me.
I mean, what am I gonna do, you know?
I gotta pay my suppliers, man,
And this girl's not going to pay me
and I'm in a lot of trouble, you know?
So, essentially what happens
is she's putting me in a bad spot,
and this is the last time I'm gonna
be letting people me
fuck around like this.
You know what I mean?
This is the last time I'm letting
anybody fuck me around like this,
but you know, I'm not talking about you.
You're too sweet.
- Yeah, sure, Charlie.
- So come over here, man, have a seat.
I got something.
I've been hanging on to this stuff.
I just got it in, great stuff, man.
I got the best in town,
air tight, China White.
(tense dramatic music)
- [Waitress] Hey.
- Hi, I'm waiting for Charlie is he here?
- He's not here yet but
he should be here soon.
Would you like some more coffee?
- Oh, please, thanks.
- [Charlie] Here, come on.
- Charlie, I've gone cold turkey.
- What?
What are you talking about?
- I'm serious.
- Don't you know a good
gesture when you see one?
- Yeah, I do.
- Look it, this stuff isn't
going to be around all the time.
You're gonna want it, man
and you're gonna come looking for me.
So you might as well.
- No, I'm not Charlie, I want
to stay without it for a while.
- [Charlie] What are
you talking about, man?
- I want to stay without it for a while.
- Wait a second, whoa, hey.
Is anybody home?
I mean is anybody around
here, anybody anywhere?
Hello, hello?
Come on.
- No, Charlie, no, man,
what are you doing?
What the ruck are you doing?
I mean you've never shot up.
You don't know what it's like.
- Wait a minute, wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
Hello, anybody?
Oh, really?
Come on, man.
I mean, what's going on here?
Hey-
- Charlie.
- [Charlie] There's
somebody else isn't there.
- Wait.
- [Charlie] What, wait a minute.
Hang on.
- [Charlie] Look it,
look it, don't care, man.
Here, you know.
- Charlie, go to hell.
- Go to hell?
- Yes, fuck off.
- Is that what's really going on here?
You know what, man?
I know what's going on here, man.
It's this fucking, you know what,
you can have his fucking
necklace too, man,
because the mother fucker's gonna
be around here in a
couple of minutes anyways.
You know, that's what's really happening.
Hey?
- [Anna] I don't mean to shut you out.
- Hey, come back over here.
Anna, come on, come
over here and sit down.
Come over here and sit down.
- I'm sorry, man.
- Look, you know, you're
still a wildcat, man.
(engaging dramatic music)
- Anna?
Anna, what's a matter?
Anna, baby doll.
Oh, baby.
What the fuck has he done to you?
Anna come on, come on, wake up.
Come on Anna, wake up, wake up.
It's gonna be okay.
Anna, come on, come on, come on, baby.
Come on, come on, come on.
I'll get you out of here.
All right, it's gonna be okay.
No, it's gonna be okay.
(engaging dramatic music)
Okay, okay.
It's gonna be okay.
All right, all right.
Let's go back in there.
Come through here, that's
it, that's it, that's it.
Come on Anna, that's it.
Now, you're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay.
You stay there.
All right, all right, come on.
Come on wake up, Anna.
Come on, wake up.
Come up on, wake up.
Come on, baby, have a shower.
Come on, baby.
You gotta wake up.
Come, that's it.
Anna, come on, wake up, wake up.
Please wake up, Anna.
Come on, come on.
You'll be okay.
Can you hear me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, okay, okay, baby.
(Anna pants and mumbles)
That's it, come on.
Walk, you've gotta walk.
Come on, you've gotta walk, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, walk.
Okay, move your feet,
move your feet, come on.
Okay, walk Anna, you got walk now.
What's your wrong with your legs?
You've gotta move your legs, Anna.
What have you done with your legs.
Come on, that's it, come on, that's it.
That's it, that's it, yes.
(struggling and grunting)
Okay, you can do it, you can do it.
(grunting)
Okay, okay, got you.
(engaging dramatic music)
(birds chirp)
(trains and machinery hum)
(engaging dramatic music)