[music playing]
-Hello I'm Toby, I'm
your next door neighbor.
-Hi.
Oh, that goes in the Asian room.
Yes.
Oh, I like your magic ring.
-Oh thanks.
Well, welcome to
the neighborhood.
-Thank you.
-Oh boy, it's here.
-All right, found it!
-Is that it?
-I think so.
Ah, locked.
-We'll never find the key.
-I suppose not.
Hey, I got an idea.
All right, bottom
of the ninth, bases
loaded, fastball
down the middle.
Yes.
Once more, once more.
All right.
Yes.
Here we go.
Home run.
Why is Aunt Violet
making such a big stink
about me living with you?
-Eh, I don't know.
In the two years since
your mom has died
aunt Violet has run out
of people to pester.
It's just our turn.
-It seems weird.
-Yeah, try to be nice.
She means well, all right?
Wait a second, wait a second.
Yes.
-Mom's will?
-You betcha.
All right.
My son Tobias shall remain withhis stepfather, Chet Emerson,
in the eventuality
of-- case closed.
-Yeah!
I'm starved, can I get pizza?
-I'm going to make lunch.
-Dad please no,
don't cook, please.
-All right, all right, allright, I get the point.
Here.
Be back by 12:30?
-Gotcha.
-Miss you.
-What do you think?
I sure hope this settles it.
I don't want to leave dad.
Aunt Violet does
have a cool house.
Remember all those Christmaspresents last year?
[barking]
That was cool.
Come on, let's go
get some pizza.
Hi Aunt Violet.
-Hello darling.
I happened to be in the area soI thought I'd drop by and see
how my favorite
nephew is fairing.
-Dad and I found
the-- how's Gramps?
-Hanging on.
Are you getting enough to eat?
-Yeah, Lucky and I werejust going to grab a slice.
-Oh, here's a littlesomething to help you out.
-Cool.
-The custody hearing
is coming up you know.
-Yeah.
-Who knows, maybe you can
come and live with me.
[barking]
Of course we'd have
to get to you a new
haircut and some
clothes from Zebo's.
Anyway, run along,
go have your pizza.
And be thinking of
the hundreds of gifts
you'll be receiving
for Christmas.
-Oh boy.
-Come give your
aunt Violet a kiss.
Tuesday, complained of
no food in the house,
had to give him
money to subsist.
Bartholomew, it's not fair.
I'm the rightful heir.
It's inconceivable that mynephew is the last Stanton man
and stands to inherit myfather's enormous fortune.
But not if I can help it.
-You don't want to live with
aunt Violet, do you boy?
[barking]
You and me both.
-Hey punk.
Get over here.
-What?
-Get over here.
Don't go walking around
this neighborhood
talking to your dog.
It's going to make theneighborhood look whacked,
which is eventually going
to make us look whack.
Yeah, you don't
want that do you?
-Are these things defective?
-You're defective.
-Hey.
-You know what, now you did it.
[barking]
You know, that
flea picnic of your
ain't going to be
around here forever.
-Yeah he is.
Adios loser.
[barking]
-Hey Vito.
-Hey Tony.
Enjoy, my friend.
Oh, is lucky.
Here we go.
This is especially for you.
-Thanks Vito.
-Ah, I take care of my friend.
Hey and say hello
to your pop for me.
-Hey.
-Give me the money.
I know you got it in there.
I know you got it.
Give me the money.
-Let me go.
-Give it up, give it up.
-Let me go!
-Excuse me boys.
-Who's that?
-I don't know, but
she looks loaded.
Come on.
-12:30, encountered twoslacker hoodlums in the park.
Look dumb enough for the job.
Are you two interested
in making some money?
-Money?
I remember the stuff.
-Shut up.
Doing what?
-Slightly dangerous, and itinvolves brains and brawn,
and you have to keepyour mouth shut about it.
-Well that's no problem.
I'm the brains and the brawn.
And, well he's my associate.
-I resent that.
-Do you know who Toby Emerson?
-What that little dweeb
that talks to his dog?
-I want you to
confiscate something
from his house for me.
-No problem, we love break-ins.
-No break-in.
Just walk in.
Don't you want to know whatit is I want you to steal?
-A big screen TV?
-No.
A small grey file box.
A hundred now, a hundred later.
And don't screw it up.
-Smile honey, smile.
Come on, there, good.
That's it, nice.
-Oh come on, honey,
that's enough.
Give me the camera.
Give me, give me the,
give me the camera.
-Those were the days, huh.
-Mom, we love you.
We love you.
-It's not healthy watching
that tape over and over.
-Hi dad.
-Let's not wear
out that tape, OK?
-I know.
I'm just thinking about mom.
-Hey, uh, we got to come upwith a new show at the station.
Got any ideas?
-Yeah.
The Toby and Lucky Magic Hour.
-Not bad, but we got to appeal
to the late night crowd.
Oh, late night.
Speaking of which, I
got to go out tonight.
Jill's going to come by.
-I thought we were going tothe fake wrestling match?
-Sorry pal.
I got to interview one
on the prospective hosts
for the new show.
-I understand.
-Hi it's Chet Emerson,
is Jill there please?
Hello?
Um, you can have it.
It hasn't worked in years but--
I just, I just couldn't bearto let this go to the dump.
I mean this, is LeBeau lamp.
He's a very famous designer.
I'm an interior designer myself.
-Jill.
Sorry.
-It's OK.
-Cheerleading practice?
OK, thanks.
Baby sitters, they're reallyhard to come by these days.
Hi, Chet, I manage the
local cable station.
-I'm Phoebe.
I believe I met your son, Toby?
-Oh, yeah, yeah.
-Yeah.
-You're the new neighbor?
-Yes I am.
Yes.
I think Herman and I
will it here very much.
-Herman, I haven't
seen him around.
-Well that's because
he stays in mostly.
You know, I'll babysit foryou, since you're in a bind.
-Really?
Are you sure it's not
too much of a problem?
-Yeah.
No, I mean no.
I meant no, it's not
a problem at all.
Toby seems really sweet.
-Oh, great, um, could youcome over, at say, uh, six?
-Sure.
Oh.
-Emergency at the station.
You're a lifesaver.
Thanks.
-Yeah.
I'm--
-Um.
[barking]
-Now sir, I will bet
you a dog biscuit
that I'll pick the
card that you chose.
[barking]
-That isn't it, is it?
-Give me a break, I
just got this trick.
If only I could read Chinese.
Let me try that again.
-Hey Tobes.
-Yeah dad.
-You know Phoebe,
our new neighbor?
-Yeah, she's cool.
-She is and she's going to
be watching you tonight.
I've got to go.
There's an emergency
at the station.
You know Sam's outside.
Why don't you go
out and shoot hoops?
Um, yeah.
Here's some pizza dough.
Love you buddy.
And love you too.
[barking]
-Love you.
[doorbell]
-Uh, I'm coming.
Oh, hi Chet.
-Hi Phoebe, I have to
leave a little early.
Is that OK?
-Sure.
-And Herman won't mind?
-No, I don't think it'll
ruffle his feathers any.
-Uh, Toby and Sam areshooting hoops out front.
What?
-It's, uh, a little crooked.
There.
-Thanks.
-Welcome.
-See the new neighbor?
-Yeah, she's
watching me tonight.
-Toby, I'll be over
in a little while.
-OK.
She's cuter than Jill.
-Don't you think she's
a little old for you?
-Yeah but not for my dad.
-Now you're thinking.
-The ten of clubs?
-Whoa!
Pretty good, huh Luck?
[barking]
-Nothing to it.
-You have to show me.
-OK.
After somebody's picked
a card, you very gently
bend the bottom corner of it.
And look for the bent
card and you've got it.
-Phoebe you're the bomb!
[barking]
[doorbell]
-Pizza, Pizza!
I'll get the drinks.
-Hey small fry.
$10.35.
-You didn't spit on it, did you?
-Thought you liked it
with everything on it.
Short a buck.
-Hey!
Nice try pizza jerk.
-Go in there and get a
tip from your father.
-That was almost funny, ha ha.
He's isn't here.
-Really?
You don't say.
[barking]
-Later.
-See ya, wouldn't want to be ya.
Loser.
I've heard such wonderful
things about you Chet.
Professionally of course.
-I'm fatter.
I mean, flattered that
you asked me to dinner
to pitch your idea.
-Well my brother said you neededa late night show, pronto.
-Lane's your brother.
Well, I'll have to remind
myself to thank him
for setting up this
little meeting.
He also said you're a dancer ?
Modern ballet?
-Oh, no.
Wanda would have nothingto do with formal dancing.
Wanda's too much of
a free spirit who
has to explode across thestage in a fireball of passion.
I call the show, Wanda's
Dance Fusion Hour.
I talk about my life indance, have guest appearances,
and perhaps, do a newdance routine every night.
-Where is it that you dance?
-At the Chunky
Chicken off the 215.
-So my friend, is
this a blind date?
Or have you just gone blind?
-Business.
Just business.
-Oh, thank God.
-Can you hurry up with somemore of that free bread, senor?
-Oh, certainly.
Just let me go and
call the bakery.
-Goodnight sleepy head.
-Will you show me
how to walk the aces?
-Sure.
We can do it tomorrow.
Oh my gosh, I forgot
to feed Herman.
Oh well, he's probably
asleep by now anyway.
-Who's Herman?
-He lives with me.
-Oh really.
-He thinks he's the
love of my life.
Good night, sweet dreams.
-Toby come in.
Over Toby.
-What's she like?
-Pretty cool.
But she's living with
some guy named Herman.
-Bummer.
I've never seen him.
-He probably works thenight shifts or something.
Toby out.
-Sam out.
And Toby?
-Yeah?
-Cheer up.
-She would've beenperfect for dad, perfect.
-Even if my idea
doesn't work out,
I hope we can remain
close friends.
It was a very special evening.
-I, uh, I never
thought you would
really dance on our table.
-Never double dare Wanda.
Would you like to come in fora deluxe private performance?
-No thanks, I'm still digesting.
You know the
breakdown of enzymes
is a very important
metabolic process.
-I'm a night creature Chet.
-Wanda I'm sorry, I don't thinkthis is going to work out.
-Fine.
You know, I don't need a show.
My two shifts at theChicken satisfies that need.
Besides, you're a dork.
-My middle name.
-Hands up jail birds.
Get away from the bomb, now.
Stephon, you there?
-Come on.
Quiet.
Shh.
Go, go, go, go.
-All right.
-What was that boy?
Lucky come back!
[barking]
[screaming]
-Hey!
Toby!
-Phoebe!
Come on, call 911!
-Get out of here,
get out of here.
-Come on Lucky!
Get 'em boy!
Get 'em Lucky!
Sic 'em boy!
Don't let 'em get away.
Come on, get 'em Get 'em!
-Open the door!
-I'm trying!
-Let's get 'em boy.
-Toby!
Toby!
Don't you--
-Go, go, man!
Faster, faster,
he's gaining on me.
[squealing tires]
[dog yelping]
-Lucky?
-Run!
Run!
Come on!
-Come on boy, get up.
You're OK.
Come, on buddy.
[whine]
We're going to take
you to the doctor.
Maybe they'll put a cast on you.
Won't that be funny?
[police siren]
-Son, can you give
me a description
of what they look like?
Are you the mother?
-No I'm just babysitting.
-Please don't die.
Hang on a little longer?
[crying]
-Oh, Toby.
I'm sorry.
-Toby.
Hey, come on son.
It's going to be OK.
-I was just driving, andthese, these kids ran out
in front of me, and Ididn't, I didn't see the dog
and I just hit him, hit him.
-So all they got was
a small grey file box?
-Yes.
-Well, considering what
they didn't get it,
could've been worse.
-Isn't that evidence?
-Oh, yeah.
-Look officer, his mother's
will is in that box.
I've got a custody hearingin a couple of days.
Without the will,
his aunt may get
temporary or permanent custody.
-Well the door
doesn't look jimmied.
Was it locked?
-Yes.
I believe so.
I'm not exactly sure
if I locked the door.
-Well I've looked
over the whole house,
and unless they had a key,I don't know they got in.
-Oh, what a rush.
-Yeah but you had to
make so much noise.
We could've had all the stuff.
The camcorder, the TV.
I can't believe you.
And that dog ripped
my favorite jeans.
-We got another hundred coming.
That's all that counts.
-Come on we've
better bury that box.
-Hello Chet.
-Hello Violet.
-How's Toby?
I heard about what
happened last night.
-I think he's pretty upset.
-Are you raising that
boy or torturing him?
-Your sarcasm is
not appreciated.
-You know this
isn't going to look
well at the custody hearing.
What did that bandit's
make off with?
-Oh, in addition
to the-- actually,
it's none of your business.
-Really?
-Really.
-Well I only stopped
by to comfort the boy.
I suppose I can come
back another time.
-Toby are there?
It's breakfast time.
Come in Toby, are you awake?
Come on Toby, pick up.
I know you're there.
Are you home?
-Yeah.
I don't ever want
to get out of bed.
-I know.
I'm sorry about Lucky.
-I lost my best
friend, except for you.
Now I think I'm going
to lose my dad too.
-What?
-My mother's will was
in that stolen box.
My dad needs it to
keep custody of me.
-Oh boy.
We've better get pizza and talk.
-Here you go, he he.
Toby, I, I hear
about last night.
I'm so sorry.
Poor, poor Lucky.
I have my mother say a novena.
That's a little, uh, prayer.
Anyway, the uh, the pepperoni
pizza is on the house.
-Thanks Vito.
I hope the cops find that box.
-Well, what wouldsomeone do with this box?
-I don't know.
-Sell it?
-Nah.
It's just an old tin box witha bunch of legal papers in in.
-Looks like we've got to
find out who broke in.
Is something else bugging you?
-It's dad.
He needs to meet someone.
Since mom died he hasn't doneanything except take care of me
and Lucky.
-Excuse me, but
uh, I like you dad,
but uh, I think he
could use a lot of help
in the female department,if you know what I mean.
-I know.
But if he found someoneit'd be a lot more likely
he'd be able to keep me.
-Hmm.
You know, I think I got an idea.
-Ma'am, I can't wait sixmonths for a copy of the will,
without it I'm a sitting duck.
I'm a widowed,
working stepfather,
and she's a blood relative.
And she's rich.
I don't care if the
attorney's in Grease,
it's a two hour play, hecan get it to me tonight.
Oh, the country.
Thanks.
-This really work?
-Sure it will work.
I mean this is how myuncle Mike met his Betty.
Oh, cute girl.
Hello, yes, I'd
like to place an ad.
And I would like it toread, "Single father of one
12-year-old, seeks
lady for fun, romance,
and walks on the beach."
Oh yes, and she must be liketo bake chocolate chip cookies.
Tomorrow's edition?
Good.
Alright just put it on
my monthly paper bill.
Thank you.
-And God bless daddy, and
mommy, wherever she is.
And Sam.
And God bless Phoebe next door.
I wish we could find the will.
I want to stay with dad.
And I wish he could
find someone special.
He's lost his best friend too.
Lucky, I hope you're up therehaving a wonderful time.
I miss you buddy.
-John.
-I'm Terry.
And this is "Pasta Talk."
Today we're going to talkabout our two favorite pastas.
One, penne, and two, rotelle.
-Dear Mr. Emerson, my
lizard Spanky and I--
-Oh no, that's not
what rotelle is.
-What are you talking about?-Rotelle isn't long and twisty.
Rotelle is round.
-No they're little,spiral, the spiral things.
-No, no, that a bow
tie or that's a twist.
-OK you're-- rotelle is round!
Get him off of me.
-Though I'm writing from jail--
-Oh my gosh.
Dad.
Lucky?
This can't be happening.
You got to tell me
what's going on boy,
because you're scaring
the heck out me.
-Uh, I really don't know either.
-You talk.
I must be dreaming.
-Hmm, this is the welcome I get?
Hey, who's your best buddy?
Look at me, I'm back.
Well, not completely back.
-You're a ghost dog, cool.
-Hmm, I guess I am.
-Did it hurt when
the car hit you?
-You know it's funny,
I didn't feel a thing.
But I sure was glad you werethere to help me crossover.
-How come you're back?
-I've been sent
back to help you.
-Hey, you can help
me find the file box.
-You said it Sparky,
it's payback time.
Oops, sorry.
-It's OK.
Some magic trick, huh?
-Yeah.
I'm glad you're here Lucky.
-Poor kid.
Maybe he would be better
off with someone else.
Toby!
Breakfast.
-Good morning dad, we're here.
-Morning.
Eggs?
-Dad.
-You like eggs.
-Look.
-You want your
eggs on the floor?
-Lucky's back.
-He's what?
-He's a ghost dog.
I know it seems
weird, but Lucky's
going to help us find the will.
-Sure, why not.
You know, uh, we could use
all the help we can get.
-I'm not visible
to everyone Toby.
-Really?
-Remember, I was sent
here to help you.
-Hey, uh, Tobe.
Why don't we keep Lucky
our little secret, OK?
-You could really see Lucky?
-Yeah.
Hi Lucky.
-Go, go, go, go, go.
-OK.
OK.
I'm with you.
-Point to him.
-Hey, ha, there he is.
Oh, good Lucky.
Kisses, kisses.
Oh, Lucky, your breath is bad.
-Brother, I don't think so.
-Dad, I was just kidding.
-Son, it's OK to miss Lucky.
-Let's go back to the
scene of the accident.
We might find something.
-Now that using your head.
-Hey look!
-Hey, I bit that out of thepants of one of the burglars.
-Our first clue!
-Oh boy, we're on
the right track now.
-Now we just have to find thepants that this came from.
Let's get at it.
-Toby?
-Look what I found?
-Are you all right?
-I'm better than all right.
I got a major clue andLucky's back-- I mean, oops.
-You were talking to Lucky?
-You definitely don't
see Lucky right there?
-Definitely not.
-Good, because he's not there.
-No, but you think he's there.
-I'm just so used to himbeing there that I forgot.
-Are you sick or something?
-I'll catch up to you later, OK?
-Sure.
Whatever.
-Yep, this is the spot.
Hmm, I don't see any clues.
-They took off into
the woods over there.
Come on.
-Oh, boy, this is great!
-Lucky, slow down.
-Ah, come on, it's beenawhile since I've done this.
Woo hoo hoo!
Hee hee.
-They might have dropped it.
Keep your eyes peeled.
-Why would they
go into the woods?
-I don't know.
-Hey, look!
That must be the
burglars hideout.
-Ha, my dog house
is nicer than that.
You think they were here?
-I'd say so.
Maybe there's a hidden
compartment somewhere.
Can't you see through
walls and stuff?
-Ha, what am I, Superman?
-Crooks always have
a hiding place.
-Hmm, I wonder where theyhid their vacuum cleaner.
-Maybe not.
-Hey check it out.
-What is it?
-Their stash hold.
I think they found the file box.
Bogus.
-At least we know
the crooks are local.
And by the looks
of this place, it
seems like they come
around here quite a bit.
-Let's tell officer Nelson.
-No, no.
If we attract a lot of
attention the crooks
probably won't come back.
-Yeah.
We should keep an eye on thisplace and see who shows up.
Come on I have to work onmy plans to stay with dad.
-Hi, my name is Greta
and I read your ad.
I'm am in my 30's also.
My friends tell
me I'm attractive
and I love little boys andchocolate chip cookies.
Call me at 555-7801.
-Should I call?
-I don't think this is the wayyour dad wants to meet women.
-Probably not, but I
got to do something.
Hi, Greta, this is Chet.
-Oh boy, I can't watch this.
-Yes, you read my ad?
Yes, I'm free tonight.
Hold please.
How is dad going to meet herwithout knowing what we're up?
-You didn't think this
out too well, did you?
-Would you like to meet my sonand maybe have a little dinner?
Seven.
OK.
We live at 2564 Terrace Court.
Goodbye.
-How are you going
to pull this one off?
-I'll think of something.
Dad, I'm really sorry,
you're going to kill me.
I forgot tonight was
parent, teacher night.
-You in trouble?
-Pretty deep.
-Don't give me any lip, mutt.
-I bet you pardon son?
-Hip, my teacher's really hip.
You'll like her.
It's just a standard meeting.
-Boy, this kid can
think on his feet.
-OK, what time do I
have to be at school?
-Actually, they're
starting a new thing
where the parent
and the teacher go
to a restaurant or something.
Get dressed up.
It's like a date practically.
-Date?
Did you bring home a note?
-Lost it.
-Fast again.
-I'm going to call school,something doesn't sound right.
-It's four o'clock,
they're closed.
And that means you only havethree hours to get ready.
-OK.
-There we go.
She's really cute, and
she's single by the way.
Don't feel like you have
to talk about me at all.
-What an adorable little boy.
I bet you like chocolate
chip cookies, ja?
-Ja.
-Oh, shall we go, it's 7:05.
-Sure, let's uh, hit the road.
-I'm doomed.
[laughing]
-Two gold medals.
-I was East Germany's greatest
female hammer thrower.
-It's hard to believe.
-Not really.
-So how's Toby doing at school?
-You're asking me?
-Yes.
-Toby?
Fine I suppose.
You are keeping up for him
to do his homework, ja?
-Ja!
Having any trouble at school?
-What?
-With your kids?
Sometimes they can be unruly.
-I wouldn't know.
I'm childless.
-You're what?
-But it doesn't
have to be that way.
-Hey Vito, how's the date going?
-She ordered raw
meat for dinner,
how do you think it's going?
Kid, why did you make
a move without me?
Your dad, he don't
look too happy.
-I love touching-- ah, teaching.
Despite the bruises.
-Really?
-A few scratches unavoidable.
One time, I had a
student in a hammerlock.
She flipped me, and
accidentally scratched
me underneath my
drazen flippsen.
-Jeez.
But, Toby's doing well?
-Oh, your son?
-Yeah.
Loves chocolate chip
cookies, about yea high.
-He's not enrolled.
-That little turkey.
-He can't, it's impossible.
-But I help him
with his homework?
-Mr. Emerson, I am a womanself-defense instructor.
-Would you like somethingstiff from the bar, sir?
-Personal ads?
For crying out loud Toby, Ican handle my own love life.
-Told you dude.
-Let's see here.
Must love 12-year-old boys andbaking chocolate chip cookies?
-You like chocolate
chip cookies too.
-Yes I do.
But that's not the point.
You lied and embarrassed me,and that weird Nazi woman.
Now I don't know what the
appropriate punishment's
going to be.
-But dad.
-Don't make him angrier.
You might get off light.
-Don't make me angrier.
Now go to your room.
-Relax, he'll cool off
and see the whole thing
with a sense of humor.
Let's talk about our next move.
Uh oh, mayday.
I don't like the looks of this.
-Over here, there's definitelyno decoration whatsoever.
There's a lint
ball in the corner.
It needs a woman's touch.
-What's going on?
-Can't be good.
-Hi aunt Violet .
-Toby!
Darling.
-Isn't dad here?
-Well, he left this note onthe door, had to go to work,
something about going toPhoebe's, whoever she is.
-That's OK, he's
been really busy.
It's cool though.
I have a key to get in.
-Do you often stay home alone?
-Just for about an hour afterschool until my dad gets home.
-The truth darling.
-It Is.
Who are you.
-I'm Peter Abelino.
I'm your guardian ad litem,I've been appointed by the court
to write a report that
will recommend who
should retain
custody of you Toby.
When's the last time
you had a hot meal?
-Uh, jeez, let me see.
-Don't answer that.
Hey, the cavalry's coming.
-It was this morning, oatmeal.
Good for the colon.
Hi, Phoebe.
I'll be taking
care of Toby today.
You ready for a healthy,
nutritious lunch?
I'll just take that.
And thank you, goodbye.
His next hot meal's
getting cold.
-Excuse me, Miss.
-Nice to have met you.
-Looks like the boy's
well watched, ma'am.
-I've never seen her
before in my life.
-She lives next door.
Convenient.
Saw the boy as soon
as he walked up, good.
-Would you stop with that.
The father's not
fit for custody,
I'm the blood relative.
He's only the step-father.
-That will be taken
into consideration
in the court ma'am.
-You read the policereport, they were robbed.
Who knows what thatdeadbeat dad is involved in.
-I'll put it all
in my report Ms.
-Mr. Abelino, or
may I say, Peter.
I hope you'll be fair andimpartial in your findings.
And I would most certainlymake it worth your while
if you would keep asympathetic eye open for me.
-Why, a, of course, Violet.
-As soon as I saw that cardrive up with exempt plates,
I knew they was trouble.
-Don't need it anymore chief.
Besides I wouldn't be
able to taste it anyway.
-Oh yeah, I forgot.
-Forgot what?
-Uh, nothing.
What was that guy
doing with Aunt Violet.
-Was probably checking
up on your dad.
-She means well.
She's just getting
batty in her old age.
-I'm not so sure.
Hey, I got something for you.
Hold on a second,
let me find it.
Yeah, there we go.
This is the Whitman
Book of Magic.
My dad gave it to
me when I was a kid,
and I want you to have it.
-Really?
Excellent!
-Go ahead, it's yours.
-Thanks Phoebe.
I better run, I got
a lot of work to do.
Come on Lucky.
-What did you just call me?
-I feel lucky to have
you as my friend.
-That's, that's sweet Toby.
-We got to speed up
the investigation.
We're running out of time.
-You said it.
I hate those guys in suits.
-Would you look at that?
Kid's warped.
-What's a guardian ad litem?
-I think it's a cross betweena lawyer and a baby sister.
-Hey twinkle toes, come here.
-Not again.
-I thought we had conversation.
-What, I'm busy.
-I thought you didn't wantthe hood to get a bad rep.
-I don't.
I live here too you know.
-Then why you walking aroundhere talking to your dead dog.
-If you're going to
talk to something dead,
at least talk to
Abraham Lincoln.
-Ha, ha, this
guy's really funny.
-Aren't you two late for apolice lineup or something?
-You know what, I hope youhave all day, because we're
about to make your
life miserable.
-Hey Tobe, look at his pants.
Look, look!
-You two broke into my house.
I can prove it.
Lucky tore this off
the burglar pants.
-I ripped that on my bike chain.
-I want the file box back.
-You know, why don't
you go pull a rabbit out
of a hat or something.
-I got an idea.
Let's remind them
I'm still here.
You get my drift?
-I'm putting a curse
of Lucky on you.
-Ooh that's scary Peewee.
-Until I get the file boxback, the curse of Lucky
will remain on both of you.
A demonstration.
-Whoa.
-An ordinary baseball.
Go play.
-And away we go.
-Go Lucky, go.
-Woo hoo!
Yeah.
-Watch out, I'm coming through.
-Yeah.
-How does he?
What is it?
-How did?
-Look out, here comes.
Hello.
-What is that?
-Wee!
Coming at you pal.
-Hey what's going on?
-Here we go, up,
up, up, up, up, up.
Wee!
-What's that?
-It's a baseball, it's
coming at us, run!
-Here I come.
Watch out kids, I'm
swinging right by.
-Mommy.
-What's going on?
-Oh, boy, it's going to
be great, here we go.
The knuckle ball
for the knucklehead.
-Think gentlemen.
That was just a demo.
I want the file box back
in two days or else.
-I think they got the message.
Way to go ghost dog.
I've been waiting to
see that for years.
-Yeah me too.
Ever since I was
little and Larry
put a laxative in my puppy chow.
-There you go.
Herman.
-That's Herman?
-Hey Toby.
He sure is.
He's my brother's.
I'm taking care of him
while he's on vacation.
-Herman's a bird?
-He's an African Grey.
-That's fantastic!
-You like African Greys?
-African, Australian, Italian!
I love them all!
See you Phoebe.
-OK.
-I don't care if
Herman is a cockatoo,
I'm not going to ask Phoebe out.
-Why not dad.
She's cool.
-Well, I'm sure she's
busy with her business.
-She said she liked you dad.
-She did?
-Yeah.
-Well I'm busy with the
psychic healer show.
And besides remember thelast time you fixed me up?
-Come on Dad.
You can't stay busy forever.
-I'm busy Toby.
-Sure dad.
-Shh.
SAM [VOICEOVER]:
Dearest Chester.
TOBY [VOICEOVER]: Hiya, Phoebe.
SAM [VOICEOVER]: It
would be the fulfillment
of my innermost desire--
TOBY [VOICEOVER]:
You want to grab
some lunch with
me this afternoon?
SAM [VOICEOVER]: --if
you would luncheon
with me this afternoon.
TOBY [VOICEOVER]: Chet.
SAM [VOICEOVER]: Phoebe.
-Short notice.
-Wow.
-Bold.
I like that.
I'd love to!
-Me too.
Uh, 2 o'clock OK?
-Perfect.
-Don't tell me thatwasn't a major slam dunk.
-They'll have a great time.
-Ha, I'll admit,
even I'm impressed.
-Oh no.
-What?
-Fly in the ointment.
-Who's going to pay?
Each one thought they
asked each other out.
-What do we do?
-Don't look at me.
-Hello Vito.
-Hey Toby, hey,
how are you doing?
-Fine.
There's a major problem
and I need your help.
-Ah, don't worry.
I think we can
work something out.
-OK.
Yes!
How did I get myself
into this mess.
-They're here.
And for your sake I hopethey don't order champagne.
-Oh boy.
-Ah, buongiorno Mr. Everson.
Como esta?
Oh, the most discerning
palette in the valley.
Oh, madam.
Come with me, come here.
Ah, this is the best
seat in the house.
-Oops.
-Hey--
-Yes?
-No.
-Man, that was close.
-Here you go.
We have some good
specials today.
You got yourself a
cute one today, ah?
By the way, the manager hasinformed me that today's meal
is complementary due toyour recent successful liver
transplant.
-Great service here.
-Mamma mia, there's a
lot of people out there.
Keep going, keep going.
-Progress report.
-Well?
-Not so good.
No one's really saying anything.
-Are they smiling at least.
They're not miserable are they?
-Hey it could be worse.
-We've got to help.
Give him some
ideas or something.
-Aha.
I've got it.
I need you to get the chalkboard with the specials on it.
-I hope you know
what you're doing.
-Nice weather we're having.
-Yes, it's sunny.
It's warm.
-It's nice, it's uh,
really, really nice.
-Yes, it is a really nice day.
-Give me some ideas.
-Hey don't look at me.
I'm a dog.
-I don't know what
adults talk about.
-Property taxes?
-Funny, ha ha.
-I hate this job.
-Why don't you go out there
and see what you can do?
-Okey dokey.
-Excuse me sir, what do youand your wife talk about?
-About the ever-widening
socioeconomic chasm
that exists between the
classes in this country.
-Could you say that again?
-I'll take care of this.
You want it done right,you've got to do it yourself.
Oh, nice shoes.
There they are.
OK, here goes nothing.
One for you.
-Excuse me.
-And one for you.
-There it is, I've beenlooking everywhere for it.
What are you doing with
the daily special board?
-Give this to dad.
I wrote a whole bunch ofadult stuff here to help him.
-Ah you're crazy.
They already ordered.
Wait a minute, I
know what to say.
-I fixed everything.
Operation footsy now in effect.
-Lucky, get over to
Larry and Harry's
while I take care
of things here.
Keep the curse alive.
-Gotcha.
Oh boy, those slackerswon't know what hit them.
I'm out of here.
-The desert menu.
-We're not really
ready yet Vito.
-Yes you are.
-Would you like some
social chasm for desert?
-No thank you.
-You know he probably did itwith strings or something.
Like mirrors.
-He didn't have time to
arrange all that stuff.
He didn't even know he wasgoing to see us in the park.
-Well, there's no suchstuff as curses, and magic.
-Oh, really.
-I mean, give me a break.
That's the kind of thing
they only have like in,
Africa of something.
-Ha ha, we'll see about that.
-Well I'm not leaving this houseuntil that curse wears off.
-Well that's because
you're a chicken.
-The plug came out.
The curse.
Look, the curse, it's here.
-Alright who else some of me?
Come get some.
Ah!
-So, how'd it go yesterday dad?
-Not great.
-You didn't like her?
-I didn't know what to say.
Neither one of us is
the talkative type.
-See, you have
something in common.
-Well, it wasn't that bad.
I don't know, I'm just, shy.
-You should ask
her out for dinner.
-Are you kidding?
-Dad you can't give up on her.
You said you liked her.
She asked you out once,
now it's your turn.
-Yeah, but why
here at the house?
-You'll feel more
comfortable here.
-I'm not comfortable on dates.
That's the problem.
-Come on dad.
Give her one more chance.
Please, please.
-OK.
-Thanks dad.
-Got to run.
Don't forget to call Phoebe.
-Why do I have to carry it?
-Because you're adopted.
-I'm telling mom you said that.
-What are they doing?
-Looks like they're moving in.
-Hey genius, in here.
-I'm back.
What I miss?
-Check it out.
-What?
-Nothing.
-My pleasure.
I'm going after the bad guys.
-How long are we going
to stay out here?
-As long as it takes for
that curse to wear off.
-Well how long is that?
-How should I know?
Just chill and enjoy
the spoils of victory.
-Hey Toby, they're
just hiding out,
hoping the curse will wear off.
-They're probably hidingout, waiting for the curse
to wear off.
-Curse?
-I'll explain later.
We got them right
where we want them.
-You can say that again.
-Remember the Halloweenspecial my dad did last year?
I think I know how to putall that stuff to good use.
-Awesome.
-But first, I have
a party to throw.
-Phoebe, it's Chet.
Hi.
I was just wondering whether
you'd like to come over
to my place tomorrow for brunch?
You would?
Great.
Bye.
Yes!
-Come on dad, come on.
-Toby what is the big deal?
Whoa.
-What do you think dad?
-Hey, it's nice.
I just hope I can live
up to all you hard work.
-I have an idea that might help.
I'll be peaking in
from the stairs.
If things go slowly,I'll give you some ideas.
Like topics to talk about.
-Um, Tobes, you're
um, 12 years old.
What makes you think you
know what to talk about?
-Two heads are better than one.
-Yeah, I suppose.
It couldn't be any worsethan the last time, right?
-Dad, just turn around.
-OK.
Ah, ah.
I can't believe this.
-Time to go dad.
-All right let me
get my coat on.
All right.
Yeah.
-Go get her Tiger.
-All right.
Thanks.
-Good luck.
[doorbell]
-Coming.
Hi.
-Hello.
-Oh your tie's crooked.
-These are for you.
Um, hungry?
-Yeah.
-Welcome my friends.
-Vito.
-Come in please.
Me and the kid, we
got it worked out.
Yes, come on.
Yes, please, come right in.
-Wow.
-Over here, please.
The best seat in the house, yes.
Here, sit down, please.
Well, brunch will
be served soon.
But first, oh, the tantalizingmagic of Toby the terrific.
-Good afternoon.
[applause]
-For you madam.
-Thank you.
-Not bad.
-For my next trick.
I will need a member from
the audience to assist.
You sir, pick a card, any card.
Now, place the card
back in the deck.
Come to Vegas often?
Ha, ha, ha.
-Every once in awhile.
-Is this your card?
-Hey, very good!
-Thank you.
Thank you very much.
-When did you learn that?
-Enjoy your meal.
-Now, that was a very
impressive card trick.
Now , down to business.
These are your hours for
the next two weeks, OK?
-Thanks Vito, for everything.
-Hey, I take care of myfriends, you know what I mean?
-I'm going to go
take my position.
-Good idea.
Good ideas.
-Allow me.
-Yes.
Thank you.
I love the decorations.
Lovely table.
-Oh, does this look good.
Wow.
Are you ready?
Here it is.
Ha ha.
Oh for my specialty,
fettuccine alla vita.
-Thanks Vito.
-Testing, testing.
-Ah!
-Oh no.
-The food?
-This fettuccine is loud.
Whoa, big flavor.
-Oh, of course.
Yes it knock your socks off, eh?
So good.
-You know, uh, Vito, uh,the fettuccine is up here,
and I really hope your
salad gets really low.
-Sorry dad.
-Sorry I'm late.
My mom made me clean my room.
How are they doing?
-They got their mouths full.
-Have you fixed up
the old lamp yet?
-Almost.
-I'll go check on our
burglarizing brothers.
-Any suggestions?
-My mom likes it when my dadcompliments on her earrings.
-Dad, compliment
her on her earrings.
-You have beautiful earrings.
-Really?
-The earrings that you
wore the other day.
Now, those were beautiful.
-Thank you.
-Sorry dad.
Give me another idea.
Her hair kind of looks
like a swirling tornado.
Hey dad, say her--
-She wont' like being
told that her hair
looks like a swirling tornado.
Shoes are a big thing.
You guys never notice them.
-Dad, say something
nice about her shoes.
-I like your shoes.
-You do?
I didn't think you noticed them.
-Good call.
-They're plastic.
-Well they look
like real leather.
-How do you expect
to keep them talking?
You can't be around everytime they're together.
-Hopefully they'll find outthey have something in common
and really hit it off.
Dad ask--
DISPATCH [ON SCANNER]:
Suspect in 236
is heading west on fifth.
-The suspect on 236
heading west on fifth.
DISPATCH [ON SCANNER]: 13Mary four, all units respond.
Male in white jacket
running from the scene.
-Male in white jacket
Late model coupe.
He's crossing Culvert.
He's going to bail.
He's up and over the fence.
He's going, he's
going, he's going.
-He is a poet.
The Dr. Seuss of the valley.
-Oh, I didn't know
you were an artist.
How beautiful.
-Must of picked up
a police frequency.
-He's in custody.
Roger that.
Shots fired and
you broke my heart.
187, Newberry Park.
They went to heaven
in a great big arc.
Domestic disturbance,
quite a perturbance.
-Suspected stolen car.
Plate one, bravo, motel.
-Plate one bravo, motel, tango.
Your kisses are
sweeter than mangoes.
-Oh, bravo.
Bravo.
Magnifico.
-I didn't know there wasthis spontaneous side to you.
-Me either, I uh, kind of shy.
-Me too.
If you haven't noticed.
-Yeah, well, I-- I
mean, well, you know.
-Yeah, I know.
Have you ever noticed how somepeople have to fill the silence
with words if they feel likethey're doing something wrong?
-Yeah, there's a guy at
the station like that.
-Wow.
-If you're going to talk
a lot, make it count.
Like your poetry.
-Thanks.
-I can't believe it.
-So, you don't mind if we golong stretches without talking?
-Not if you don't.
-No.
-We did it.
Even It was by accident, they'reactually having a conversation.
-Isn't it romantic?
-Hey Toby, they're
still in the hideout.
It's now or never.
-Ready for phase two?
-Let's rock.
-I can't believe you.
Scoot over.
-I'm cold.
-Your deeds will
not go unpunished.
-The curse.
Who's out there?
-The curse of Lucky.
I've come for the file box.
-OK, OK.
-We don't have it.
-Let's make a run for it.
File box or your soul?
-We don't have it.
We gave it to the--
-Don't snitch.
-The file box.
-Come on let's book.
What's going on?
-Bombs away.
-I will haunt you to
the ends of the Earth.
There's no escape.
-Run!
Run!
-The file box, I want it!
-Throw some acid
to wash off them.
Yeah, ha, ha, ha.
-Woo hoo, that's cold.
-Yes!
-We gave it to the lady!
The lady!
Leave us alone!
-The lady, what lady?
-Maybe the got an accomplice.
-Beats me.
At least they admitted
they stole it.
That's something.
-Well, what evidence do we have?
-Let's get out of here.
DISPATCH [ON SCANNER]: Two codesix, 51 Tampa avenue, pit stop.
-Stop, hold on!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
-Hey what have you
guys been playing in?
-The curse of Lucky.
-What?
-We robbed the Emerson house.
And then Toby put a curse on us,because Lucky died chasing us.
-And the monster
threw acid on us.
-We were in the woods waitingfor the curse to wear off.
But they found us.
Let us sit in the back,
before it's too late.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What is this, spaghetti?
-They wanted the file box, but--
-Spaghetti.
It's spaghetti.
-OK, get up against the car.
You guys are under arrest.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say
can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
Did they confess?
-I got it all right here.
-Where's the file box?
And whose the lady you
were talking about?
-I don't remember.
Maybe I got amnesia.
-Is that contagious?
-Ah, shut up you dork.
-Don't worry Toby, I'll
get it out of them.
Come on, in the car.
-Mess.
-Come on.
-Hey, check it out.
-Thank you.
-Um.
-Looks like things worked out.
-I don't know.
Dad said the custodyhearing should be a cinch.
But it'd be a lot better
if we had my mom's will.
-Things will work out.
-Hope so.
Well, thanks for your help.
-See you tomorrow.
-What a wild day.
-I think she likes you, Romeo.
-Nah, come on.
-I really do.
I think there's a greatfuture here with you two.
Come on she lives
right down the street.
-All right, knock it off.
-Tobe, come on, we'll be
late for the court date.
-I'm coming, I'm coming.
-Hey pal, you OK?
Don't be nervous.
Even without the will, we
got a real strong case.
Violet, all she has is thefact that she's your aunt.
That's it.
Come on.
Let's take a look at you.
You look good.
-Chet, I wanted to
catch you before you
went all the way downtown.
It turns out, I had best willand testament all this time.
I thought you had it.
How inconvenient, so sorry.
Hello Tobias, darling.
-What about the hearing?
-Mr. Emerson, with thediscovery of your wife's will,
the court feels thatperhaps you should secure
legal representationbefore the custody hearing.
I've come here today
to offer the chance
to do just that bypostponing the court date.
-Who are you?
-I'm Peter Abelino,
Toby's guardian ad
litem appointed by Judge Sayers.
You were notified by mail.
-Uh, yeah.
-My evaluation of the child'scurrent living conditions
will be reviewed by judge
Sayers and considered
as a recommendation as towhat's best for the boy.
-I have the will.
I mean I did have it.
It was stolen.
-Yeah, I saw it.
-Well, why don't we
all save a lot of time
and consider the matter settled.
Beth's will is very clearabout her last wishes.
What do you think Peter?
-Under the circumstances,
I say that's an option,
that is if Mr. Emerson agrees.
-This can't be right.
-What dad?
-It says that your mom wantedyou to live with aunt Violet.
-Isn't that wonderful darling?
-It's a forgery.
-Oh Chet, don't be so dramatic.
-I don't know what to
tell you Mr. Emerson.
This will give Ms. Stump thelegal right to take the child.
Now if you plan on
contesting the will,
the boy will be placed in afoster home until such time
as a hearing can bescheduled in civil court.
-Foster home?
-Go fetch your things
Tobias, darling.
-Dad?
-You miserable, meddling--
-Don't raise your
voice to a lady.
-Uh oh.
The lady.
-I told you I had the will.
It was stolen.
And come to think of it--
-Lady, the lady.
Harry said he gave
it to the lady.
-you're involvement ofthis whole stinking thing.
-Well, until you find
your mysterious will,
I'm entitled to legal
custody of Toby.
-I want to talk to my lawyer.
-Under the
circumstances, I'd say
that's a good thing to do sir.
-Here you are darling.
-Of course, she has it.
-We got to get it back.
-Don't bother flea bag.
She doesn't have it.
She told those
ruffians to bury it
in the woods, where
nobody would find it.
Ha!
[barking]
-What is it?
-That little dirt-bag says it'sburied somewhere in the woods.
-The hiding place in the floor.
-We already checked.
The file box was kept
in the garage, right?
-Yeah.
-I'll be right back.
I've got some sniffing to do.
-Come here Tobias.
-Where is it, where
is it, where is it?
It's here, it's here, it's here.
Come on, come on.
-Europe will be in
just a few hours.
Pack light.
-I don't want to go.
-I know, change isn't easy.
But you can write postcardsto all of your little friends
and they'll be so jealous.
We'll have to hire
a tutor of course.
-I'd like to go toEurope, but not with you.
-Just for that
crack, we're going
to spend an extra
day at the louvre.
-I got the scent,
I got the scent,
oh boy have I got the scent.
-No please, don't
put me on hold.
No, no.
-Oh nix, nix, Chet.
Our plane leaves in two hours.
-I want to see my dad.
-Give me five minutes, please.
-You're going to
have to let go son.
-No.
-Hang in there
Toby, I'll save you.
-Hurry Lucky.
Hurry.
-Nose don't fail me now.
-You're not leaving
here with my son.
-Sir this is only going tobe used against you in court.
-Don't touch me!
-Now look, either you let
her leave with the child
or you file a motion to contestthe authenticity of the will.
Now you think about
what you're doing.
-I know exactly what I'm doing.
A son should be with
his father, period.
-Step-father.
Your father's histrionicswill aid us greatly in court.
-Aunt Violet, you suck.
-Hold it right there!
-What?
-Don't you run
over me, you witch.
-Phoebe.
-He's not going anywhere.
He's staying right
here where he belongs.
-You tell her Phoebs.
-Why don't you do something?
-I am sorry sir, but
I am going to have
to call the policeunless you let her leave.
-Call them.
I'd like to tell them
that you're letting
a woman with a phony legaldocument take off with my son.
-Hey, what's going on?
Toby?
-Dispatch, send a black andwhite to 2564 Terrace Court.
-Where is it?
Where is it?
Oh, I know it's
around here somewhere.
Come on.
-Mr. Emerson, what
seems to be the problem?
-She's trying to take Toby.
-Officer, this is the mother'slast will and testament which
states that she wants hersister here to have custody.
-Let's take a look.
-I think I got it.
I think I got it.
Jackpot.
-Everything seems to be
in order Mr. Emerson.
I'm going to have ask you tostep away from the vehicle.
-Over my dead body.
-Mine too.
-I'm not moving.
-Make that three dead bodies.
-You're scratching my car.
-Ma'am would you step
away from the car?
-Not on your life, copper.
-I don't want to
have to use these.
-This is it, this is
it, oh boy, this is it.
-I don't want it to get ugly.
-It already is ugly.
-Hang in there dad.
-Oh, tasty, but
totally bad timing.
OK, let's try over here.
Got it!
Come on, come on, come on.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
I'm close, I'm close.
I'm feeling metal.
-Don't let go.
-Come on dad.
-Dig, dig, dig, dig.
Bingo.
Hope I'm not too late.
-Mr. Emerson.
-Look.
-Do you see what I see?
-The file box!
-I can't believe it.
-Closer.
-Oh, good heavens.
Closer.
-What is that?
-The canine has landed Houston.
-That's it!
That's the stolen file box.
-Made if just in time.
-Like Jordan with
a three-pointer.
Hurry, take it over there.
-Toby, I can't give away
any of my trade secrets.
-Here.
-Hold on ma'am.
-This is the will.
The real will.
Let's see, right here.
My wife said, Toby issupposed to stay with me.
-Officer this is
obviously a last ditch
attempt to gain custody
by hook or by crook.
-May I have a look at that?
-This is an excellent forgery.
-It appears that a
miscarriage of justice
has been narrowly averted.
I apologize Mr. Emerson.
I don't think the state needs topursue this matter any further.
-Cool!
-Oh, you moron!
You promised!
-I promised to be fair andimpartial Violet -- Ms. Stump.
-Well just my luck I
find the one government
official who cares
about justice.
This isn't over.
-Oh this may be over.
Are you Violet Stanton Stump?
-Yes, of course.
-I just came from the homeof Larry and Harry Duzimsky.
And they told me that
you paid them to break
into the Emerson's house andsteal one grey tin file box.
-Nonsense.
-I knew it.
-Put your hands behind yourback, you're under arrest.
-Oh, Impossible.
-I don't think so.
-Violet, how could you do this?
-My father left all hismoney to the little dolt.
It should've been mine.
Mine!
You're just a kid.
What are going to spend it on?
Candy?
Toys?
Huh?
Ah, my hair!
-Well, I'll be
heading off too folks.
I'm sorry for any
inconvenience, but I
think things turned outjust the way they meant to.
-We won!
-Yes.
We sure did son.
We sure did.
-So what do you think,
should we take callers?
-Yes.
I want to help people with theirspecific decorating problems.
-Ha, ha, ha.
Martha Stewart, move over.
-Phoebe, congratulations onyour new late night show.
-Thank you sweetie.
-What?
-Go on, get ready.
And hurry up, we're going
to La Casona for dinner.
-Can't wait to tell
Vito what happened.
What a wild day.
-Toby.
-Yeah Luck?
-I'm not going to
La Casona tonight.
-Why not?
It's time for me to go back.
My work is done.
No, you're not leaving twice.
This isn't fair.
-I know.
But there's nothing
we can do about it.
So long pal.
-Not yet.
Before you go, do
you think I can
hold you just one last time?
-I think that might be possible.
Just once.
Don't be sad Toby.
Remember, even if
you can't see me,
I'll always be
with you, forever.
-I'll miss you pal.
-Goodbye Toby.
Thanks for being my best friend.
You're the coolest.
-Bye Lucky, you're the coolest.
-OK, I'm ready.
Dad?
-Surprise!
-Sam, you look great.
-Thanks.
-Dad what's going on?
-And guess what I found?
-What is it?
-Open it.
-Come on.
-OK.
Wow, cool!
Thanks dad!
-Look at his collar son.
-Luckier.
That's a great name.
LUCKY [VOICEOVER]: Remember,even if you can't see me,
I'll always be
with you, forever.
[music playing]