♪♪
♪ Standing on the border
♪ Looking out onto
♪ The great unknown
♪ I can feel my heart beating
♪ Faster as I step out
♪ On my own
♪ There's a new horizon
♪ And the promise of
♪ A favorable wind
♪ I'm headin' out tonight
♪ Travelin' a little light
♪ I'm gonna start
♪ All over again
♪ And buy a one-way ticket
♪ On a westbound train
♪ To see how far I can go
♪ Because I can
♪ Gonna go out dancin'
♪ In the pourin' rain
♪ Talk to someone I don't know
♪ Because I can
♪ I will face the world
♪ Around me
♪ Knowing that I'm strong
♪ Enough to let you go
♪ And I will fall in love...
I don't know why they say
all little girls dream of
becoming a princess.
I didn't.
I wanted to sing at the
Grand Ole Opry.
♪ I have walked through
♪ The fire...
But there's a lot of miles
between the dream and
getting there.
♪ Through the valley of
♪ The shadow of death
♪ And the truth came shinin'
♪ Like a light on me...
We weren't even close to
being there.
♪ I'm going...
Working small gigs at night
and draggin' ourselves onto
the bus after the show,
and then traveling all day.
Daddy drove the bus.
(horn honking)
Hey, you can't have 'em both.
One lane's for me,
one's for you.
Which didn't help
his disposition any.
♪ Buy a one-way ticket
♪ On a westbound train
♪ Gonna have my breakfast
♪ Pink champagne
♪ Gonna sail the ocean
♪ Gonna spread my wings
♪ Gonna climb that mountain
♪ Gonna do everything
With a country singer,
the bigger his career
the better his bus.
(engine sputtering)
So you can see where we were.
You drop that turkey
drumstick, everyone.
Hear what he's doing,
smooth, it rolls.
But Hamlet wasn't the only
one who saw the ghost of
his father, Horatio saw it and
so did all the palace guards.
That's right, but Hamlet
was the only one who heard
what his father told him about
the murder.
He was the one who was supposed
to avenge his father--
Wait.
♪ Over me
LeAnn!
Audrey!
Oh-- Oh!
♪ Blue
Oh, my God!
I can't believe it.
(cheering and laughing)
On that bus, on Daddy's old
beat-up boombox, all those days
and nights on the road paid off.
♪♪
♪ Now that it's over
♪ I realized
♪ Those sweet words
♪ You whispered
♪ Were nothing but lies
♪ Blue
♪ Oh, so lonesome for you
♪ Why can't you be blue
♪ Over me
♪ Over
♪ Me ♪
(cheers and applause)
Between Thanksgiving and
Christmas, my whole world
changed.
Oh! We got it!
They're booking you all the way
through next July.
Cleveland, Nashville, Peoria,
then we go Missouri, Wisconsin,
back to Ohio, then we go east
to Pennsylvania, Delaware.
Doesn't she get any time off?
I don't want any time off.
This is great, this is the best.
You think this old boy
will make it?
Who you callin' an old boy?
But not everything changed.
Demands were high but pay
was still real low.
And that rickety old bus
was still all we could afford,
even with a big hit like "Blue".
Daddy still drove the bus
and Mama took care of everyone.
There are three types of
these you're gonna have to
remember--
What do you think of this
for the chorus of "Light"?
♪ Don't ever lose
♪ That light in your eyes
(both) ♪ Don't ever lose
We're studying here, Larry.
So are we.
I like that, that's great.
Cool.
(both) ♪ Don't ever lose
♪ That light in your eyes
LeAnn.
Mom, I gotta get this.
You can get it after
you study.
♪♪
Like I was saying...
♪ Christmas
♪ Time for love and care
♪ Joy for all to share...
Night after night on the road
somehow Christmas lost
its magic.
(trailer horn blaring)
Avery?
You up, babes?
Yep.
Just checkin'.
Ohh.
Didn't the government put a ban
on prisoners living like this?
That's prisoners,
not musicians.
Someday I'm gonna have my own
fleet of buses.
Mm-hmm, in the meantime
why don't you turn off that
light and go to sleep?
I'm working on a new verse.
It'll be there tomorrow.
Go to sleep.
After a show, I could never
turn my head off.
I kept seeing myself up there,
onstage, singing.
I wanted it so badly.
When you want something like
that, you can't let go 'til
you get where you're going.
That was one of my Grandma
Teeden's sayings.
She always popped up when
I needed her.
(laughing)
I got you!
(screams and laughter)
No fair, Grandma Teeden!
You come around the side.
Well, you're too fast for me.
I had to be a little sneaky.
Ah, look what I got, Granny!
A nice, tender morsel.
Should we put gravy on her
and just gobble her up?
No, Grandpa,
then I wouldn't be here anymore.
Oh, yes, baby, you'll
be here.
Once you're in the heart
you're always there.
Come on.
Grandpa Luther was a cobbler,
but when the shop was closed
he got laid off.
He stood on that unemployment
line for weeks until finally
it ran out.
Made me sad to see it,
but Grandpa and Grandma
wouldn't have no sadness.
They made those summers I spent
with them the happiest of my
life.
Grandma Teeden believed
whatever you do in your life
you do it right.
You shaved yet?
I ain't even out of bed.
It's 5:30 AM, woman.
I'm putting up buns,
getting the milk, you get
yourself down here.
Your shirt's all pressed.
She believed a man gets up
and gets dressed and looks
for work, whether there is any
or not.
Where's my shirt?
On the chair.
If it was a snake it'd bit ya.
You are something else,
Theresa, going through this
foolery every day.
Well, I won't have the
neighbors thinking just 'cause
you was laid off you lie around
in bed all day in your
nightclothes.
Okay.
Just sit right there.
Right here, where everyone
can see you.
Right here-- sit down.
Grandpa was a good sport.
That's right.
Well, he made a fuss,
but in the end if it made
Grandma Teeden happy he'd sit
on the porch all day in his
suit and tie and wave at
the neighbors.
I called her Grandma Teeden
'cause when I was little
I couldn't say her name.
So she just stayed Grandma
Teeden.
She sat in the same seat
three times a week, rain or
shine, 'cause it was near the
piano and she wanted me
close to the music.
There's someone sitting
in your seat.
No one else dared sit
in Grandma Teeden's seat.
(clearing throat)
Young man, the Lord spoke
to me not minutes ago, and He
told me, "Theresa, this little
girl needs to sit
near the piano."
And-- And then He told me,
"You go over there and you
explain to him how important
it is for him to move."
♪♪
That was very nice of him.
♪ Shall we gather
♪ At the river
♪ Where bright angel feet
♪ Have trod
♪ With its crystal tide
♪ Forever...
Grandma loved to sing.
She said it was God putting
a holiday in your heart.
And I'm gonna sing on television
and records.
Well, I bet you are.
And I'm gonna be at the
Grand Ole Opry, like The Judds.
Now how do you know all that?
I just do.
I believe you.
Well, that means you're gonna be
away a lot, and you'll be
traveling here and there.
And-- And there's gonna be times
when you feel far away.
Grandma, what if you get
so far away God can't find you?
Oh, no, baby, He can always
find you.
When you start feeling that way
you just say to yourself,
"Who moved, me or God?"
I moved.
That's right.
God never moves.
We're the ones.
Good night.
LeAnn, honey,
LeAnn, baby, wake up.
We're pulling into Nashville.
You need to get up and get
dressed-- ooh!
Watch the head.
Nashville: across that bridge
was everything I dreamed about.
Hey, look, y'all, it's
The Grand Ole Opry.
But we weren't playing there.
We were playing the Graystone
Auditorium on West Fourth.
(cheers and applause)
But you know what?
Our bus pulled in and for
the first time in my career
there were people, fans,
wanting my autograph,
knowing my music.
It was amazing.
They put you in your own
dressing room.
It's got a shower.
Tomorrow you rest 'cause
the next day we got wall to wall
meetings.
Gotta be at the record company
at 10:00, then they're taking us
over to see some publishers.
Can I have your autograph,
please?
Sure, sweetie.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Uh, Lee, they want a picture
over here.
These gentlemen right here.
Hi.
Lee, you wanna go over
the set list?
You wanna do "Blue" right here
or where we talked about?
If we talked about it,
why would we move it?
That's what I told you.
You guys are driving me nuts.
Here's the rundown, no changes.
I don't care if the President
calls.
I do!
Leave it, Mom.
It's hanging in your face.
I like it, it's natural.
Looks like one of Grandma's
old mops.
I like it.
Okay, guys, it's time.
Okay, everybody.
LeAnn needs to get herself
together.
Let's take our office outside
in the hall.
(applause)
I've been asking you this
question since you were five
years old...
Go for it.
You sure this is what
you want?
Oh, yeah, I'm sure.
Okay, then.
♪♪
♪ Now that it's over
♪ I've realized
♪ Those sweet words
♪ You whispered
♪ Were nothing but lies
♪ Blue
♪ Oh, so lonesome for you
♪ Why can't you be
♪ Blue over me?
♪ Why can't you be blue
♪ Over
♪ Me? ♪
(cheers and applause)
♪♪
What?
LeAnn, this is it.
One of the acts fell out at
the Opry.
They want you to play there
tomorrow night.
The-- The Grand Ole Opry?
That's right.
Tomorrow night?
The record company is
thrilled.
Of course they're all gonna
be there.
Now, they want us to have supper
with 'em tonight at the Opry
restaurant, okay?
Okay.
Tomorrow night, the record
company, supper, the next album,
recording, tomorrow night...
...window of time
and they are setting up...
The Opry.
The Grand Ole Opry.
Can you believe it?
LeAnn, the next two days,
the most important of your life.
This is what we've been
dreaming about.
I gotta go there.
Oh, honey, they're closed
right now.
I don't care, I got to
see it.
Well, uh, they'll
let us in, come on.
Well, no, you don't
understand, I want to go alone.
Oh, no, honey, we'll go
with you.
Mom, everything will be fine.
Don't worry, the restaurant's
right next door.
I'll meet you there, okay?
(sighs) Dad?
Let her go.
Go.
You. (chuckling)
♪ So grab a piece
♪ Of mistletoe
♪ Put a log upon the fire
♪ 'Cause winter nights in
♪ Nashville ♪
♪♪
This is how I like it.
Wow.
Wow. (chuckling)
Is it really you?
Well, I don't know.
I think so.
(chuckles)
You're my Grandpa Luther's
favorite singer.
Oh, honey, I'm everybody's
grandpa's favorite singer.
It's hell getting old.
Oh, I didn't mean that.
I mean, you're my dad's
favorite and my favorite and--
I know all your records, but...
is it really you?
Well, now, that's the second
time you asked me that, and
I'm beginning to get insecure.
You're an itty bitty thing,
ain't you?
Need color.
First time in Nashville?
Mm-hmm.
And tomorrow's my first time
on the Opry.
I bet you've been dreaming
about it since you was a little
baby.
Well, we've got work--
Honey, you need spray.
I don't use that, it makes
my hair all stiff.
You mean like mine?
I love it.
My hair goes to bed looking like
this and gets up in the morning
looking better than me.
I heard you sing tonight.
You got the gift.
Really?
God knows where to give it.
My Grandma Teeden always
says that.
But... you could tell me
what it would be like.
Like nothing else.
Honey, there's things that are
here and things that are coming.
Keep your eye on what's here,
'cause after tomorrow night
they're gonna be pulling you
every which way.
They already are.
You just hang on to you.
You see that circle of wood?
I know, it's a piece
of the original Opry floor.
Well, ain't you
the smart one? (chuckling)
When you stand there,
you're standing where all the
great ones stood.
Like you.
The real great ones,
like Kitty Wells,
Patsy Montana, Johnny Cash,
Hank Williams.
You know what I'm talking about?
Well, yeah, but you forgot
to mention Roy Acuff and
Bob Wills--
You don't know them.
"Take Me Back to Tulsa",
"Wabash Cannonball".
What about Merle Travis?
"Sixteen Tons", "Divorce Me",
"Old Mountain Dew".
Well, that was long before
you was born.
How do you know all this stuff?
Boys know baseball
statistics, I know country.
I grew up on it.
What about Patsy Cline?
Hmm, Patsy Cline.
Well, I think you got me there.
♪ Crazy
♪ I'm crazy for feeling
♪ So lonely
Why, you little dickens,
you had me going.
♪ Crazy
♪ Crazy for feeling
♪ So blue
♪ I knew
♪ You'd love me as long as
♪ You wanted
Whoa, girl.
♪ And then someday
♪ You'd leave me for
♪ Somebody new
(both) ♪ Worry
♪ Why do I let myself worry?
♪ Wondering
♪ What in the world
♪ Did I do?
♪ Oh, crazy
♪ For thinking that my love
♪ Could hold you
♪ I'm crazy for trying
♪ And crazy for crying
(both) ♪ And I'm crazy
♪ For loving
♪ You ♪
I thought singing on the
stage at the Grand Ole Opry
with Faith Shawn was as strange
and as high as it could get.
But things were gonna get
a whole lot stranger.
(chuckling)
I want to do "Crazy"
in my act.
I used to.
We're going out tomorrow.
I know where you're staying,
I'll pick you up.
I got some things to show you,
even a smarty pants like you
doesn't know about.
What?
Gotta show you while
I tell you, can't do it here.
Why not?
Can't.
Well, you know what's going
on tomorrow, what if I can't
get away?
Then you'll miss it.
(scoffs) That's not fair.
You want something, you make
it happen, don't you?
What if I can't get out?
You've got a car, right?
'Cause I'm not old enough
to drive.
Yeah, I got a car,
but what's wrong with walking?
Walk?
I see legs down there.
Well, yeah, but I mean,
on the street you're
too famous--
Honey, you keep thinking
people's gonna bother me?
Ain't nobody remembers.
The tourists in Nashville
weren't born when I was hot.
And the ones who know me
is too old to care.
You're gonna be the problem.
Now here's what we're
gonna do, Missy.
You wear loose clothes,
you put your hair in a ponytail.
You pull it through the back
of an old baseball cap
and you slap on the biggest
sunglasses you can find.
Looking like that, you can go
anywhere in this town.
I don't know.
It's true, girl.
Reba does it, and she can walk
into any Walmart in the nation.
You think?
I know.
It's your turn, honey.
Tomorrow night.
It's all happening so fast,
I feel like I should stop and
take it all in.
That's what memories are for.
You remember every single
second of it.
For the rest of your life.
LeAnn! LeAnn!
(clamoring)
What'd I tell you?
Just one.
(clamoring)
Can I take a couple more?
I promise I'll get it to you.
That's it.
Thanks, guys.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Thank you.
That was so great.
I cannot believe I just got
my picture taken with you.
My dad's gonna go so crazy.
(laughs) Well, he's probably
the only one.
Honey, they wasn't interested
in me, it's you they wanted.
I'll pick you up tomorrow
outside your hotel, 1:00, okay?
Great.
And don't tell anyone.
It's our secret.
Okay.
♪♪
♪ Christmas joy to you
♪ And yours this happy holiday
Finally, a real bed.
You sleep as late as
you want to.
You've got a big date
tomorrow night.
Your mom and me got some
meetings with Jason, but you go
ahead and sleep in.
What meetings?
You think I need to be there?
Oh, no, honey, your rest
is much more important.
Um...
do you think I could go out
tomorrow afternoon?
Oh, sure.
We ought to be back by 3:00.
No, I-- I mean, by myself.
Oh, honey, no, not here.
You don't know your way around.
Well, I could go out with
some other singers or something.
I don't think it's a good
idea.
Okay, look.
I need some time by myself
to go Christmas shopping.
It's the only free time
I'm gonna have.
Well, where would you go?
Near the hotel I'm sure
there's tons of shops.
I'll be back in a couple
of hours, please?
I don't know, what if
somebody followed you?
I think it's a horrible idea.
It's too dangerous.
Mom.
I know, honey.
We'll find time to go Christmas
shopping next week.
How can I shop for you
and Dad when you and Dad
are right there?
Dad?
Your mother's nervous.
Daddy.
It'll work out.
♪ Have a very merry Christmas
She's 14, Avery.
I know the numbers, but she's
more sensible than most of the
people I deal with.
Sensible does not mean--
I know, but I trust her.
So do I.
Here's the thing, she's
leading a real difficult life.
Now she doesn't get to do things
kids her age get to do
and most of them go to the mall
and shop without their parents.
They're not LeAnn.
Since "Blue" she hadn't been
able to go anywhere without--
But no one has ever tried
to hurt her.
Now we've got to give her some
freedom, some time on her own.
It's just not right.
Avery.
We've got to let her.
The next day I did just what
Faith told me, except for
the baseball cap.
I am sorry, who did you say
you were?
(telephone ringing)
Hi, are you downstairs?
LeAnn?
Grandpa Luther.
I have been thinking about you
and Grandma Teeden all week.
You won't believe what happened.
Someone canceled, I'm singing
at the Grand Ole Opry tonight.
Grandpa, the Grand Ole Opry,
just like I always said.
That's wonderful, sweetheart.
Uh, do you know where Mom
and Dad are?
I couldn't get an answer
in their room.
Well, they're at some
meetings.
Is everything all right?
Well...
LeAnn, your Grandma Teeden's
had a bad spell.
Oh. What do you mean?
Is it her stomach?
Yeah.
Is she all right?
I don't know, darling.
Grandpa, she always rallies,
you know that.
She gets these stomach fits
all the time.
LeAnn, I'm calling from
the hospital in Jackson.
Oh, my God.
Well, what's wrong with her?
Well, they don't know yet.
They started her on a bunch
of tests and they said they'd
tell us something tomorrow.
Okay.
Okay, tomorrow.
LeAnn, I think maybe you
should all come.
You can get here tonight,
couldn't you?
Well, Grandpa, tonight's
the... Well, Jason said it's
like the biggest night
of my life.
I... And Grandma Teeden always
said I shouldn't walk out on
something I had to do.
LeAnn, they're gonna have
to operate.
The doctors are worried her
heart's weak.
She could have a heart attack
on the operating table,
what with her age and all.
I'll come, Grandpa.
After the show, I'll fly right
down to Jackson, I promise.
Grandpa?
Pray for her, honey.
Pray for her.
(telephone beeps)
(ringing)
Grandpa?
You ready?
I'm out front.
LeAnn?
You there?
Come on, girl, we gotta go.
♪♪
All right.
♪ They ring and sing
♪ Songs full of light
♪ Making each heart
♪ Feeling so bright
(choir singing in a round)
(car horn honking)
Get in.
Get in, I was afraid you
wouldn't recognize me.
Are you kidding?
Get in!
My Lord, child, you are slow.
We've got a lot of ground
to cover.
What's the matter?
You look more peaked than usual.
Oh, nothing.
Just things on my mind.
Well, better than nothing
there.
Are you hungry?
You don't eat meat?
Oh, yeah, I do, but I'm--
just-- I'm fine.
Well, then, you'll probably
eat these.
All right, you ready?
Where are we going?
Around.
(car engine starting)
(tires screeching)
♪ Oh, it's Christmas
♪ And there's a lot this year
♪ Friends and family...
Okay, I think you're in.
Got such itty bitty things
on wheels nowadays.
Ain't no space for a real car.
Come on, honey.
Oh, forget it, honey.
Ain't nobody gonna tow that car.
The towing fee is more
than the car is worth.
I kept waiting for somebody
to recognize her.
I couldn't understand it.
I mean, she hasn't made a record
in years but she was the biggest
and the best, a real legend.
Nashville, heh.
Looks more like Times Square.
Oh, this street, this street--
now there's Ernest Tubbs' place.
She must've known more about
Nashville than anyone alive,
but I still couldn't get her
to tell me what we were
doing here.
I'm pretty sure that's--
that's the place.
Oh, thank you!
Oh, this is wonderful.
Never know when you need 'em.
Merry Christmas!
(ringing)
Ho ho ho!
Merry Christmas.
(chuckling)
We'll have to see what we can
do about that, darling.
Now Santa's got to go and
deliver presents to all the
other good little girls
and boys.
Okay, Santa.
Ho ho ho ho!
Merry Christmas.
How did Grandpa Luther
get that cotton on his cheeks?
Ohh... (chuckling)
What you thinkin'?
Nothin'.
Well, Miss Nothin',
we gotta get serious here.
I've got things to show you--
Ooh!
Hey!
Didn't you used to be
Faith Shawn?
No, I didn't.
Faith Shawn used to be
Faith Shawn and she still is.
Didn't you used to be sober?
It was like she wanted me
to see things, but she wouldn't
tell me why.
♪ Remember Christ
♪ Our Savior
♪ Was born on Christmas Day...
Look.
What?
Watch him.
♪♪
Look at all them lives
in there.
He had to hock it to get home.
(bells on door jingling)
Did you bring me here
to depress me?
Then life's gonna
depress you.
It does sometimes, but I
don't go out looking for it.
Honey, you can see the Grand
Ole Opry every Friday and
Saturday night.
All glitter and shine.
This here's the Opry that goes
on 365 days a year.
Come on, I've got a couple more
things to show you,
then the story.
What story?
The one I'm gonna tell you.
This part you're gonna like.
I don't like this.
I gotta get back, I gotta go--
You're gonna be back with
plenty of time...
for whatever you have to do.
Come on.
Are you crazy?
I'm not going in here.
Ax murderers hang out in places
like this.
I've got ax-murderer spray
in my purse.
Okay, get up there, girl.
Oh, God, what is this place?
It looks haunted.
I don't like it.
How do you know
until you get there?
Well, you really don't have
to lay an egg to know
it's rotten.
Okay, it's locked, let's go.
(birds cooing, wings flapping)
Oh, this I wore the night
I first played the Opry.
Are these all your costumes?
Mmm, not just mine.
(screaming)
(chuckling)
Oh, that's just Horace.
We put him here to discourage
folks from breaking in.
We?
This is your place?
No, honey, this nice old man
used to let us keep our costumes
and stuff here when we went
on the road.
Pickle?
Who wore this?
Ernest Tubbs.
No way.
Yep, and these are his boots.
Bo Riddle made 'em.
Well, what are they
doing here?
Why doesn't anybody know
about this?
I know about it,
you know about it.
I mean--
It's private.
Oh, wow!
It's beautiful, what is it?
It's a set they built
for a movie I was gonna make.
Oh, look at the cute little--
Oh, it's Nashville.
But it doesn't snow
in Nashville.
Oh, yeah, it does.
But not like this.
It did once.
Look at the cute little bus.
Yeah.
It's an old one.
Them buses was always cold
in the winter, hot in
the summer.
Here.
What's this?
Part of the reason
I brought you here.
It was Tennessee's worst
snowstorm.
The temperature fell 62 degrees
in 24 hours.
An Arctic onslaught.
Them big newspaper words.
Took a lot of lives, that storm.
What does this have to do--
If you was on the road when
the blizzard hit,
you was in trouble.
Were you?
Why do you think I'm
telling you?
We had our own bus, but it was
forever breaking down.
And this day we had to ride
public.
♪ A poor old country
♪ Christmas
♪ A clear and starry night
♪ The snow lies white
♪ Upon the grass
♪ And everything feels right
Is this gonna fit in here,
do you think?
You're gonna have to put
that up in a seat.
♪ We sit around the hearth
♪ And the crackling of
♪ The pine cones
♪ Is music to your heart
♪ Let's have a good old
♪ Country Christmas
♪ The family's all here
♪ The tree is done
♪ The stockings hung
♪ What a magic time of year
Miss Shawn!
Can I get your autograph?
Sure.
Okay, what's your name?
Alana.
Oh, that's a pretty name.
Thank you.
She has all your albums.
Oh, thank you.
Okay, there you go.
Thank you.
♪ Have a good old country
♪ Christmas
♪ One full of joy and fun...
May I help you?
♪ A good old country Christmas
Thank you, miss.
Here, take my arm.
Step here.
It started out nice enough.
It was snowing and we was
freezing but that was natural
for back then.
♪ There's snowflakes
♪ In the air
♪ A good old country Christmas
♪ A clear and starry night
Miss Shawn.
Over here.
♪ It's a good ol' country
♪ Christmas
Do you mind?
♪ And the crackling of
♪ The pine cones
♪ Is music to your heart
I suppose you're wondering
what a blind man wants with
an autograph.
Not really.
Well, it's my secret.
♪ A real country Christmas
♪ The only way to go
Thank you.
♪ Friends and neighbors
♪ Smiling all aglow
♪ It's a real country
♪ Christmas
I had a show that night
in Arkansas and it started
coming down something fierce.
The windshields of the bus
was like milk, and you can't
see nothing through milk.
Why didn't they just
turn around?
They was country roads.
Two lanes with a stripe
in the middle, and the driver
couldn't see to turn around.
You want to sit back by
the back window, tell me if
anything's coming up on my left.
Do my best.
Excuse me, sir, I need to try
and see out this window here.
Better you than me.
Yeah, I guess.
I think we should stop
and let this blow over.
Stop where?
Can't, ma'am.
If I can't see nothing,
the cars behind me can't
neither.
They'll plow right into us.
(tires screeching)
(people screaming)
Are you all right?
Is everyone okay?
All right, yeah.
Everybody okay back there?
We didn't know what hit us
or what we hit.
Are you okay?
Is everyone all right?
I'm real sorry, folks.
We must have left the main road.
It feels like we hit something.
I'll try and get the door.
Looks like we're wedged
between two trees or something.
Can you get it open?
Nope.
She's wedged.
You mean we're stuck here?
It looks that way, ma'am.
See, it took a while for
everyone to realize the
situation we were in.
Well, how long were
you there?
Long.
All night?
All night and then some.
Makes me hungry thinking
about it.
Well, so, what happened?
I mean, couldn't the driver
radio for help?
This old bus didn't have
no radio, girl,
what are you thinking?
Pork rind?
Mm-mmm.
When we went into those
trees, we were on a blacktop
road just off the old state
highway between Lyles
and Wrigley.
Did you ever hear of
them places?
No.
I don't think nobody
but God had either.
(engine sputtering)
Once the motor went dead,
there was no more heat.
Well, how come you didn't
make a fire?
Carbon monoxide poisoning
in that closed place.
We would have fallen asleep
and woke up dead.
Speaking of which...
I ain't feeling so good.
I hope you don't got
a weak stomach, honey.
I'm just gonna give myself
a little injection here,
and soon...
I'll be feeling right fine.
Why did she bring me here?
To show me that she was
a junkie?
I didn't want to see it.
It made me sick.
Why do people always show you
things that hurt you?
I couldn't look at her.
She had been my idol and now
she was just a pathetic
drug addict.
I hated her for it.
I hope I didn't make you
uncomfortable, honey.
I-- I saw you was looking away.
Well, it embarrasses me, too,
but there's-- gotta do what
you gotta do.
I don't know why.
Honey, there's things
that you can't help.
But aren't you afraid of
going to jail or getting
arrested or something?
What did you think that was?
Dope?
Well, of course.
What else could it be?
Oh, my Lord.
Oh. (chuckling)
Insulin.
Oh.
I'm a diabetic.
I take insulin to regulate
my sugar.
Ain't you never heard
of a diabetic before?
Well, yeah, but...
I've never-- just never met one.
Well, there's thousands
of us out there.
People used to die from it
'til they discovered insulin.
I only need to inject it
twice a day, though,
then I'm fine.
Oh, I see.
Well... (chuckles)
I'm so sorry, I just thought
that... well, next time you
do it, I won't turn away.
I won't need to do it
until way late tonight.
What happens if you don't
take your shot?
I go into a coma.
Leave me that way long enough
and poof!
But it hasn't happened yet,
can't you tell?
Okay, so finish your story.
Where was I?
Are you testing me?
Well, you and all those people
were locked in this bus
in the blizzard, freezing.
That's right.
Well, in those days it took
a long time to get from one
place to another so people
packed lunches.
Picnic baskets.
This here sandwich
is froze solid.
Pass it over here,
I'll thaw it out for you.
Did you have enough to eat?
Yes, thank you.
I had me some sandwiches from
that kind little girl
and her mama.
He's blind.
We fetched him over and
took care of him.
They shouldn't be traveling
by themselves.
He's blind, not deaf.
Hey, hey, folks, folks,
we ain't at a church picnic.
Now look, we've got to have
some kind of plan.
If someone doesn't come for us
soon we're gonna be in
big trouble.
Do you know what the temperature
is here?
Cold.
Yeah.
Well, now, look, I think
some of us ought to go for help.
Come on.
Go where?
It's below zero out there.
You wouldn't get ten feet
in that blizzard.
At least we're safe in here.
When we don't get to where
we're supposed to be
they'll send people for us.
Well, well, now,
Miss Singing Star,
what makes you think so, huh?
I mean, you heard any cars
pass by out there in the last,
what, six hours?
We'd run out of water
hours before.
We was so cold and so thirsty,
the only thing left was to
try and sleep.
I wish we had a radio.
(chuckles) I'll give you
the news: Tennessee is under
ten feet of snow.
I mean for music.
You should go to sleep.
♪ I need thee every hour
♪ Stay thou nearby
♪ No tender voice
♪ Like thine
(both) ♪ When thou art nigh
♪ I need thee
♪ Oh, I need thee
♪ Every hour I need thee
♪ O, bless me now my savior
♪ I come to thee
♪ I need thee every hour
♪ In joy or pain
♪ Come quickly and abide
♪ Or life is vain
Well, wait a minute.
What about your insulin?
Did you have enough with you?
In time.
That's a big part of the story.
Well, I guess I'll hear it,
but I'd like it to be
in this lifetime.
What?
I was thinking,
how's your Grandma Teeden?
How'd you know about her?
You mentioned her.
I did?
When?
At the Opry.
Oh.
She's not doing too good.
She's in the hospital.
She gonna be all right?
Well, she always rallies and
she's real strong, but...
I really don't know.
How old is she?
About 60 or 70, I guess.
That's a big spread, honey.
How am I supposed to know?
She always looks the same to me.
I bet she knows
how old you are.
Well, of course.
She was there when I was born.
I wasn't there when she was.
That's a point.
Whoops!
Gotta go, come on.
Well, what about the story?
Come on, come on,
we gotta go.
Go.
We're always going.
We never finish anything.
We don't got all night.
You're singing at the Grand
Ole Opry.
I couldn't believe what
I was doing here with this
crazy woman in an alley
miles from anywhere.
I wanted out.
Where are you going?
That's our ride.
Get in.
Hi.
LeAnn, this is Carl,
my husband.
Well, you're...
(chuckling)
Wait a minute, he was the guy--
Things ain't always
what they seem, are they?
Well, get in, girl.
I don't know why I got in.
I just did.
That was the thing about her.
She made you think the
craziest thing was normal.
Then I started seeing headlines:
"Singer Kidnapped By Maniacs".
Seems like we were driving
forever.
It started getting dark and
I started getting real worried.
Where are we going?
Oh.
We're going to where you had
the bus accident?
Is there anything there?
All right,
it's right about here.
Get out, this is it.
Are we going to see the bus?
Where are you taking me?
What do you think, honey?
Ain't it a dandy?
It's got a steel frame
covered in weatherproof plastic.
You can almost see through it.
What's the word?
Translucent.
Yeah.
And the insides is filled with
12-volt bulbs, like car
headlights.
You can see it for miles.
Trouble is there usually ain't
nobody around for miles.
Did you think you was meeting
your maker when that light
came on?
How do you know about this?
I mean, how does it work
way out here in this field?
Carl and me made it.
He was a welder by trade
back when he worked.
But how does it...
It's got a motion detector.
This here is where 18 people
nearly breathed their
last breath.
Soon as we move on,
lights go off, it's black again.
Don't you know this cross has
scared a few people half
to death when it come on
way out here. (chuckling)
Why did you do it?
Memory.
I got one more story
to tell you.
I had a visitor that year
when I was in Nashville:
my dad.
He had ridden the bus all the
way from Conway, Arkansas,
where I was raised.
He had written me three letters
saying he'd be at my house
for Christmas, but I didn't
answer one of 'em.
Why not?
Well, honey...
my daddy and me hadn't spoken
for nigh on 25 years.
But--
Back when I left home,
nice girls didn't go into
show business.
Least not where I come from.
♪ I need thee
♪ Oh, I need thee
♪ Every...
I was always singing.
I guess everybody sung
back then, but I wanted to sing
country...
at the Grand Ole Opry.
If you'd open your Bibles
with me please to the book
of Isaiah.
As soon as I graduated
high school, I bought a bus
ticket out of town.
(voices arguing, muffled)
Listen, I can't give her
my blessing.
Listen to me, you step out
of this house, and you have
no daddy!
I mean it, girl!
You have no daddy.
You'll never see her again.
Daddy kept his word.
The only time he contacted me
was to tell me my mama had died.
I got his letter the day
after the funeral.
When I had them hit records and
everybody started to know me
all of a sudden people I hadn't
heard from in years
was related to me.
That's when I got them letters
from Daddy telling me
he was coming to see me.
You know what I thought
he wanted?
I thought he was coming to
ask me for money.
That's what everybody else
wanted.
You'll find that out.
But you didn't...
That's right.
I couldn't let go of my hurt,
my pride.
I didn't see my own daddy
when he came to town...
for Christmas.
I was still so angry,
I didn't ever want to see him
again.
I left him a note
and went off to do my show.
In two hours I knew I'd be
on that bus and out of town.
Then I discovered I didn't
have my insulin.
It must be in there.
It's not.
My whole purse is missing
and my medicine.
Maybe-- Maybe we put it in
with the music.
My shot was way past due.
If the cold didn't kill me,
I knew for sure the diabetic
coma would.
What's wrong, honey?
Nobody could've heard me
crying except a mouse.
I, um, I-- it's okay.
Uh, you wouldn't understand.
Maybe I would.
Never can tell.
Or a blind person.
I'm diabetic and I don't have
any insulin.
That disease took my sight.
I'll be danged if I let it
take my life.
It ain't gonna take yours
neither, honey,
'cause I got enough insulin
in here for both of us.
Seems like that old man
was there whenever I needed
something on that trip.
Your speaking voice is as
pretty as your singing.
You know me?
I know exactly who you are.
That's why I asked for your
autograph.
You're my favorite singer.
I can't believe you
recognize me just from
hearing me speak.
I see with my ears.
You also sang a hymn.
I'm hoping someday you'll
record a gospel album.
Gospel's what I love.
I guess you say things
in a situation like that.
Things you never share
with a stranger.
He was a harsh man,
and he couldn't tell I had
this burning dream.
Well, sometimes you can't
see someone else's dreams.
People say you should take
pride, then in the next breath
they say you should swallow
your pride.
I didn't know what to do
with mine so I did the wrong
thing.
Oh, honey, it is so easy
to do the wrong thing.
Before you know it,
there's no time left
to do it right.
We all wait too long.
I don't know if I have
the time.
You have plenty of time.
Plenty.
Use it right and get some sleep.
♪♪
He had this little cross
on his satchel.
I just stared at that cross
for hours.
I knew as long as I could see it
I was still alive.
It was time for my shot,
and I hated to wake him.
(door creaking)
That's when we heard the men
beating on the bus door.
Hey, hey!
We're in here!
Let us out!
All right.
Hey, guys, come on in.
Hey, come on, everybody,
let's go.
Wake up.
Wake up, they're coming for us.
Come on.
Wake up.
Come on, come on,
you need your medicine.
Let's get you your shot.
Truth was he didn't have
no more insulin in that box.
He gave me the last...
to save my life.
The man died in the night.
I didn't even know he was dead.
(sniffling)
That man who saved my life
was left inside that bus,
alone in the cold and dark.
Those people who came within
inches of dying themselves
didn't want to ride with
a dead person.
We left him.
All alone.
The men had to come back later
with a wagon and get him.
That's why you and Carl
built the cross.
A few weeks later, I was
getting ready to go on stage.
I'll be right there.
They returned your stuff
from that bus ride.
Oh, that's not mine--
We've got five minutes,
everyone.
(sniffling)
The blind man was my daddy.
When I didn't see him in
Nashville he got on the bus
back to Conway.
Why didn't you recognize him?
I mean--
I hadn't seen him in over
20 years and he looked
so different.
He had all that white hair
and a hat and I didn't know
he had gone blind.
He probably didn't even know
I was on the bus 'til he
heard my voice.
Maybe he thought you all
would be rescued before
he had to take his own shot.
No.
He knew giving me his last dose
could kill him.
He just did it anyway.
He gave his life for me
and I refused to see him.
I can't take back nothing
I did in my life.
I ain't got no family no more,
but if I did,
they'd come first.
First before money, career,
success, fame.
You see, honey, you're gonna get
where you're going.
The question is...
who's gonna be there with you?
Well, we had us a good time.
Thanks for coming with me.
Will I ever see you again?
I'll see you around.
Bye-bye.
Say hi to your Grandma Teeden.
(door opens)
How's Grandma Teeden?
She's not good, honey.
Daddy just talked to Grandpa
Luther on the phone,
and they're gonna operate
tomorrow morning.
I want to be there before
they take her in for surgery.
LeAnn.
Look, I know what playing
the Opry tonight means,
but the Opry can wait.
Grandma Teeden can't.
I'll call and cancel.
Would you please tell 'em
a family emergency came up.
Yes, I need Barton Mathers
now.
You call the airline and
get the tickets, I'll be ready
in about ten minutes.
(mouthing) Okay.
We've got to cancel
the Opry tonight.
Something's come up.
I know, it's a family emergency.
You remember when I was in
the hospital with that
infection?
Mm-hmm.
You and Dad were working...
and Grandma Teeden slept in a
chair by my bed all night.
She held my hand and sang.
Now, honey, we can't sing
as loud in here as we do
at home or in church
'cause we might bother some
of the other patients.
So we're gonna kind of sing
in whispers.
That way nobody'll hear us
but the Lord.
(both) ♪ Amazing grace
♪ How sweet the sound
♪ That saved a wretch
♪ Like me
(man clearing throat)
Would you excuse us, ma'am?
I need to examine the child.
Well, I think I'll just
wait right here, doctor,
while you do that.
♪♪
She never left my side.
Hi, Grandpa.
Don't disturb her.
She needs her rest.
LeAnn, baby.
Hi, Grandma.
You don't have to talk.
Mom and Dad are here, too.
They say...
I got cancer.
I know, Grandma.
Don't talk.
I'm proud of you, honey.
I seen you on TV a whole lot.
Try to sleep, Grandma.
Remember how we used to
sing on the porch swing
when you was little?
I remember.
You know...
you're never as close to God
as when you're with family.
Are you still close to God,
LeAnn?
Do you still talk to Him
every day?
Yeah, Grandma.
'Cause if you're away
from God, you know who moved?
I moved a little, Grandma,
but... I'm back now.
Would you, baby?
It's the medicine.
She doesn't know what she's
saying.
I do too, Avery.
Would you?
I want to hear you sing
one more time.
I can't sing real loud like
we do at home or in church,
but I'll sing in a whisper.
Nobody'll hear us but the Lord.
♪ Amazing grace
♪ How sweet the sound
♪ That saved a wretch
♪ Like me
♪ I once
♪ Was lost
♪ But now
♪ I'm found
♪ Was blind
♪ But now
♪ I see
♪ When we've been there
♪ Ten thousand years
♪ Bright shining
♪ As the sun
♪ We've no less days
♪ To sing God's praise
♪ Then when
♪ We've first
♪ Begun ♪
You can't go any further.
I can go to the operating
room.
I'm sorry, you can't.
Well, what if she's not
asleep?
I want her to know I'm here.
She's sleeping, honey,
and she's dreaming of
your beautiful voice.
♪ Today I watched a robin
♪ In our front yard
♪ I thought by now
♪ That they should all
♪ Be gone
♪ With winter around
♪ The corner
♪ And snow on its way
♪ Surely there must be
♪ Something wrong
♪ Then in that old oak tree
♪ I finally saw her...
Mom, she looked so scrawny.
Not even Grandma.
Grandpa says she's been
eating like a little bird.
Grandma loves to eat.
You know your Grandma Teeden.
She wouldn't go to a doctor.
That cancer's probably been
eating at her for months.
She kept saying it was
indigestion.
She could hardly
digest a thing.
How long now?
Three hours and some.
What you making, Grandpa?
Gloves.
Gonna line 'em with fur.
Soft.
They're for your Grandma
Teeden to wear to town,
when she gets well.
She'll like that, Grandpa.
Yep.
♪ It's just a broken wing
(vocalizing)
♪ It's just a broken wing ♪
Mr. and Mrs. Rimes?
She's doing fine.
I think we got everything.
Oh, thank the Lord.
Her liver was clear and
that's what we were most
worried about.
We won't know for sure until
all the lab results are back,
but I'm real satisfied.
Can I see her?
No, they'll be bringing her
up in a little while.
Your grandma's one strong woman.
She came through like a trooper.
I knew it.
Thank you, God.
Where do we go from here?
Well, she is gonna need
several weeks.
I am gonna recommend some
chemotherapy,
just as a precaution.
I thought you said--
Well, we got everything
we can see and feel,
but there can always be
microscopic cells we don't catch
and we don't want this thing
spreading, okay?
Grandma Teeden pitched a fit
over that.
I ain't doing it.
All my hair's gonna fall out.
You don't need any hair,
woman.
Besides I hear that baldness
improves your disposition.
Look it here, darlin'.
They're beautiful.
You can still stitch better than
any old machine.
I hope you like yours, too.
Grandpa.
It fits like a...
Glove.
How did you know the size
of my hand?
From years of holding it,
darling.
The next six months were
the roughest yet.
We were booked clear across
the country.
But we got our new bus,
and Daddy designed it.
And of course nobody could
drive it but him.
The record company...
(indistinct conversation)
(cheers and applause)
The funny thing about dreams
is that they really do come
true, but in their own time.
I was finally opening at
the Grand Ole Opry.
(cheering)
It was thrilling,
but like most good things
it was going by too fast.
I just wanted to stop and
take it all in.
Faith was right.
I did get there,
but the question was
who was gonna be there with me?
LeAnn.
Just talked to the record
company.
They're throwing a big party
after the show.
They're gonna announce the
release of the new record.
They're very high on it.
Think we're gonna get at least
three big singles...
Look at this place.
So nervous I can barely breathe.
It'll be fine.
Take deep breaths.
In and out, in and out.
♪ 'Til I find myself
♪ Another pot of gold
♪ I can't help the love
♪ That I deserve...
Excuse me. Thanks.
Honey, I know this is the
big one, but I still have
to ask you.
Yes, Mom, I want this
more than ever.
(whispers, inaudible)
Hey, guys, quiet time, okay?
Thanks.
Oh, Miss Rimes.
I told you I'd get you these.
Oh, great! Thank you.
Can I get some more
pictures tonight?
(mouthing) Yeah, sure.
I couldn't wait to see
the photographs that night with
Faith Shawn and me.
What you got, honey?
Oh, I can't wait for you
to see these, you won't
believe this.
Where is she?
Oh, they're lovely.
She's not in them.
Who?
When we were here last time,
I didn't tell you about it
because, well, I don't know,
but, anyways, I couldn't wait
to get these pictures so I could
show you but--
Honey, what are you
talking about?
Remember when Grandma Teeden
got sick?
Faith Shawn, I met her at the
Opry, and we took pictures
together and we spent a whole
day together and she told me
about this horrible bus accident
and how her father saved her
life, and-- and...
she's not here.
Honey, you must be mistaken.
Faith Shawn died two years ago.
Daddy said most folks didn't
even know she had died.
(applause, distant)
She spent her last years with
some old boy she married helping
the homeless in a mission.
Someone sent Daddy a clipping
from a Nashville paper because
he had been such a big fan.
She died in an accident.
Do good, honey.
It's your night, Lee.
She is one of the youngest
country music performers to have
a top ten record on all...
There was a storm.
She and her husband were hit
by lightning, near a cross
somewhere.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Miss LeAnn Rimes.
♪♪
(cheers and applause)
This is a very special night
for me.
First, because I'm finally here
singing at the Grand Ole Opry.
(cheers and applause)
And second...
well, so many country performers
have grown up singing in church.
I did, too,
but even before that, I sang
with someone very special,
and she's here with me tonight--
my Grandma Teeden.
(cheers and applause)
She taught me that real music
doesn't come from the throat,
it comes from somewhere deep
down.
It's God, putting a holiday
in your heart.
May you always have a holiday
For you, Grandma.
(applause)
♪♪
♪ I've never been so certain
♪ I've never been so sure
♪ We're on the side of angels
♪ If we believe
♪ This love is pure
♪ Is it so hard to trust it?
♪ 'Cause we've been wrong
♪ Before
♪ There comes a time
♪ In every life
♪ We find the heart
♪ We're waiting for
♪ After all
♪ The might-have-beens
♪ The close and instant calls
♪ After all the try-agains
♪ Don't be afraid to fall
♪ We're on the side of angels
♪ After all
♪ Every time you touch me
♪ Don't you feel it too?
♪ The gentle hand
♪ That's guiding us
♪ You to me
♪ Me to you
♪ After all
♪ The might-have-beens
♪ The close and instant calls
♪ After all the try-agains
♪ Don't be afraid to fall
♪ We're on the side of angels
♪ After all
♪ Heaven only knows
♪ Why this took so long
♪ But only heaven knows
♪ If love is right or wrong
♪ After all
♪ The might-have-beens
♪ The close and instant calls
♪ After all the try-agains
♪ Don't be afraid to fall
♪ We're on the side of angels
♪ On the side of angels
♪ After all
♪ Ooh, yeah
♪ On the side of angels ♪
(cheers and applause)
♪♪
I never saw her again.
Someday I'll get a chance
to thank her for coming.
But I know it won't be
in this life.
♪♪